You're so sensitive.
Mai... it's cold here...
Don't worry. Soon your body will be so hot you'll forget the cold.
There...
No matter where Mai touches me, it feels so good...
Does it feel good?
I want to hear your sexy voice.
I-Idiot! What if someone hears us?!
Don't worry, most people have gone home already.
I know that... but...
I can't.
If that's your attitude...
No! Not there...
Stop, Mai... Mai!
Hearing your voice... really turns me on.
M-Mai...
It's true.
So please... touch me too.
Wow... you're so wet there...
Mai, you're so cute.
You're the cute one, Reo.
That's not true.
Seeing you in ecstasy... is adorable.
If you suck... my nipple that hard...
Well, yours are getting harder and harder...
It's because of you.
Just being touched by you makes me feel so good.
Mai.
Look, if you do that...
I want to hear Mai's voice when she moans...
If you keep licking like that, I'll...
No! Mai!
Mai...
Don't!
Stop it... That's my job...
Reo...
No, Mai, I can't take any more!
Come with me, Reo.
Okay.
A Kiss for the Flower Petals - Linked with your Sweetheart
It's all because we had sex in the infirmary.
Definitely.
Geez, it's all Mai's fault...
Mai must be in class now...
I want Mai here with me.
I hate being alone.
Mai...
M-Mai?!
Wh-Wha...
How are you feeling?
What are you doing here?
Come on now...
I'm clearly visiting you because you're sick.
I-I'm not that sick...
Hmm? Weren't you crying from loneliness?
I wasn't crying...
I really wasn't crying!
Okay, okay.
Look, if you shout, you'll worsen your cold.
Anyway, Mai... Aren't you supposed to be still in class?
Yeah, I was worried about you so I left early.
Left early...
Your face is kinda red.
Do you still have a fever?
I knew it, seems like you still do.
Reo, does it feel bad?
My throat's... dry.
My throat's dry! I want some water.
Here.
I thought you might say that, so I bought some things on the way here.
Huh? W-Wait a minute!
Do you want some more?
I'm good, thanks.
Reo, you're sweating, right?
You should get changed.
It's okay!
No it's not. The quickest way to get better is to remove sweat and sleep.
Really?
If you're changing, I'll wipe your body for you.
You can't bathe right now.
I-I'll do it myself, thank you.
Come on, there's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Leave it to me.
N-No!
I can manage, leave me alone!
Look! You'll just get worse like this!
Quit stalling!
Geez, Mai...
Don't worry about it, leave it to me.
I'll get you hot towels and fresh clothes!
Reo?
Don't worry.
I'll stay by your side all day long.
Mai...
Why are you chasing me?!
Because you're running away!
Is it because you hate me?
Was I a bother, always trying to help you?
N-No way!
It's the opposite.
It's because I like you!
"Like" me...?
You're not a bother...
I...
Mai, I... I love you!
Reo... You...
Love me?!
You moron!
You're so slow!
Er, um... uh...
Saying this all of a sudden...
I'm a burden to you, right?
So just leave me alone!
I didn't care if you hated me, I made up my mind and said it.
Reo...
I love you too.
Huh? That's your reaction?
Then, let me prove it to you.
Mai...
I'm back, Reo.
Have you been staying put?
I'm sick...
...so of course I wouldn't move.
Sorry for leaving you alone.
Don't get mad.
I'm not really mad.
Well then, let's start with a sponge bath.
Are you cold?
I'm okay.
Reo, open your arms.
Sorry...
I can't...
...stop myself.
I want you right now.
Dummy! I'm sick right now!
Don't worry.
If you get another fever, I'll stay with you and look after you.
Reo?
You don't like me kissing you?
It's not that...
I just don't want to give you my cold.
If it's your cold, I don't mind catching it.
B-But that's...
Not right.
You're right...
You're sick.
So having sex would be...
...a bad idea.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm just going out for a bit to calm down.
I'll be with you all of today.
I...
I want you to touch me...
Reo...
It can't stop now.
Are you sure?
As if you'd stop if I said no...
You're shaking...
Sorry, you're cold, right?
Mai's scent...
Your body is so hot...
I do have a fever, you know.
If you don't feel comfortable, tell me immediately.
The places that Mai's lips touch...
...are tingling...
Does it feel good, Reo?
I-I'm not going to answer that!
Not going to answer, huh?
Reo...
I want you to tell me...
And then, I can make you feel even better...
Mai, you pervert.
But I want you to feel as good as possible.
Not there!
That's not what your body is saying.
You're so wet.
Mai!
Wow...
You're growing down there...
Shut up...
Stop saying things like that...
No!
It's embarrassing... but that doesn't make it feel bad.
Reo...
Reo, I love you so much.
You came.
I-I got too excited...
You're a pervert...
Sorry, Reo.
I'm really sorry.
If your cold worsens...
...I'll take responsibility and look after you.
No! What are you doing all of a sudden...
You're so cute.
Mai...
Don't do it!
It's not fair.
It's not fair...
I also...
...want to hear your voice!
Mai...
Touch me... more.
Me too... Mai!
Mai...
Let me hear your voice.
Let me be the only one to hear it.
Reo... Reo...
Reo...
Do you... love me?
What? Why suddenly ask such an embarrassing...
I'm not telling!
I want you... to say it to me...
Mai... I love you.
More...
Say it more, Reo!
I love you! I love you, Mai!
I love you so much it can't be put into words.
Reo...
I love you too, Reo.
38.5 degrees...
Looks like I got your cold.
Geez... I told you so!
I'm okay...
You should go to school.
It's okay.
If I stay home and sleep today, I'll get well again.
See?
Okay?
Right then, off we go!
I do feel pretty sick, actually...
Reo?
Why...
Don't you know I can't do anything on my own?
S-So get well quickly and go to school with me!
Thanks, Reo...
I don't know...
I feel so... happy.
Stop saying stupid things, just get better quick!
I'll be by your side until you're healthy again.
Until my cold is cured?
So... you'd only be by my side till then...
Always...
Even after your cold is cured...
Anyway, it's not like you can separate yourself from me.
You have absolutely... no... choice...
Reo...
This fansub was brought to you by SHiN-gx Fansubs
ENGLISH CREDITS:
Translation: 10sigh_baka
Translation Check: Chef Trace
Editing: nx0, Endersgame
Timing and Encode: SHiN_aKuMa
Quality Control: Lycurgus
Special Thanks: kobi, Lester
ADDITIONAL TRANSLATION:
Indonesian: faithtear
Norwegian: tom
Hungarian: Radzeer
Tagalog: Takuya, Modhesh
French: Silkypico
Russian: Cyber1
German: Kiba-san
Italian: NeoX, Messer Azzone
Portuguese: peter147, kanguru-kun
Blog: http://shingx.wordpress.com
IRC: #SHiN-gx@irc.rizon.net
Please support the creators of the anime by buying the
original DVDs/Blu-rays when they are available in your area!