[Script Info]
Title:(18禁アニメ) 姉、ちゃんとしようよっ！ 第1話 「空也故郷へ帰るの巻」 (DVD 640x480 WMV9)[CRC 909A].ass
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.13,0:00:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來告訴你更多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.14,0:00:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然藥的效力讓你不能動了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.89,0:00:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣看來更好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.94,0:00:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耳朵有感覺了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.48,0:00:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不會是已經到極限了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.28,0:00:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姊 那裡是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.82,0:00:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經變的這麼大了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.49,0:00:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會感到狹窄嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.24,0:00:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姊 慢一點
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.83,0:00:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是還沒什麼嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.21,0:00:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.00,0:00:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我會怕要芽姊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.51,0:00:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個溫柔的姊姊哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.26,0:00:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也啊 你在想些什麼呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.39,0:00:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在回想起來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.35,0:00:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才會說出那樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.36,0:01:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母死後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.86,0:01:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己一個人來到梓家後
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.86,0:01:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周圍只有六個姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.86,0:01:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而男孩只有我一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.15,0:01:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被她們當作玩具一樣玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.66,0:01:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是被疼愛的回憶很多很多
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.41,0:01:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是心裡感到最興奮的\N就是和要芽姊在一起的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.72,0:01:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然要我到沖繩寄宿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.04,0:01:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼下去的話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.05,0:01:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我如果成為沒用的男人的話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.80,0:01:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸會擔心的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.30,0:01:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說 要做像人生\N第一次告白那樣子的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.68,0:01:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.64,0:01:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡要芽姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.56,0:01:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等空也再長大一點
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.81,0:01:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候我再回答你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.27,0:01:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候自己 像感覺到溫柔的親吻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.28,0:01:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直像做了什麼契約一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.42,0:02:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺像是被緊緊地縛在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.84,0:02:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後當我學習結束
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.59,0:02:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到了姊姊們在的住所
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.59,0:02:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午後果然是一天最熱的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是應該快來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.06,0:02:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真無聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.11,0:02:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 空也
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.28,0:02:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了 瀨蘆裡姊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.49,0:02:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼等會家裡見
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.99,0:02:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 難道不是來接我的嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.75,0:02:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來幹什麼的啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.25,0:02:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.00,0:02:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不見 海姊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.25,0:02:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該說我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.75,0:02:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.51,0:02:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是姊姊喔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.26,0:02:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎你回來 空也
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.01,0:02:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.26,0:02:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了 巴姊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.76,0:02:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.27,0:03:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 終於到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.02,0:03:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿～沒想到空也居然也長這麼大了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.61,0:03:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 高嶺姊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.36,0:03:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還是這麼的盛氣凌人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.87,0:03:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不過是弟弟還這麼得意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.54,0:03:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是弟弟就不要躲開啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.96,0:03:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 要芽姊呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.12,0:03:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.73,0:03:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.56,0:03:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好久不見 我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.90,0:03:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經長大成人了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.07,0:03:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 這種不協調的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.53,0:04:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有點奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.96,0:04:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 還真是有點長大了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.42,0:04:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雛乃姊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.29,0:04:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不見 空也
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.21,0:04:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丸 這個是我的弟弟 空也
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.30,0:04:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.34,0:04:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰也不會認為雛乃姊是最大的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.27,0:04:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 把頭伸過來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.31,0:04:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.98,0:04:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,額頭上刻著「大叉」啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.31,0:04:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.32,0:04:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上就是我的歡迎會
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.07,0:04:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舉辦這樣的會雖然很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.03,0:04:38.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但為什麼要我自己做飯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.37,0:04:41.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好有巴姊來幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.62,0:04:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這兩個人就在邊上看著
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.33,0:04:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為麻煩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.58,0:04:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒菜不要給我炒焦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.17,0:04:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電視上正在放作為律師的要芽姊的採訪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.97,0:04:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後是這座村莊留下來的神隱的孩子們
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.47,0:05:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桌子上擺滿了飯菜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.47,0:05:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著大家滿足的吃著飯菜
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.31,0:05:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也稍微有點安慰了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.23,0:05:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯哼哼 這樣才好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.11,0:05:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瀨蘆裡姊在所有的姊妹中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.24,0:05:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯有她的母親 跟其他人的不相同
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.78,0:05:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 空也 你的臉好像有點紅喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.12,0:05:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是芽姊那裡拿的酒太強烈了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.04,0:05:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姊怎麼會在這麼晚出現
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.30,0:05:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呢 喜歡空也喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.97,0:05:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我也喜歡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.43,0:05:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是LIKE 是「LOVE」喔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.43,0:05:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.18,0:05:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 頭開始昏了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.68,0:05:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝多了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.39,0:05:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以剛進這屋裡的被子裡\N就成了這個樣子了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.08,0:06:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不快點起來的話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.74,0:06:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要亂動
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.54,0:06:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.92,0:06:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還怦怦的一直跳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.42,0:06:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有那麼緊張嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.30,0:06:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.50,0:06:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平常都不會這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.80,0:06:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是姊姊才這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.30,0:06:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為要芽姊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.47,0:06:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是個可愛的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.06,0:06:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又變大了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.64,0:06:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是單純啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.77,0:06:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.73,0:06:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 有什麼意見嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.82,0:06:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.49,0:06:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼的堅硬 炙熱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.99,0:06:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,味道也很棒 又好大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.45,0:06:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的東西不知道\N要迷倒多少女孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.96,0:06:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣射了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.63,0:07:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.47,0:07:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 大姊這個樣子太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.59,0:07:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.39,0:07:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快醒醒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.64,0:07:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恢復到以前大姊的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.73,0:07:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要拘束喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.48,0:07:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再弄了我不想再射了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.65,0:07:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.40,0:07:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後還要「10」次那麼多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.61,0:07:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子 好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.53,0:07:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在想射都不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.28,0:07:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 讓我聽聽你那動聽的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.42,0:07:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的聲音還真是不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.67,0:07:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就好像是壞人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.42,0:07:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你心裡是這麼認為的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.97,0:07:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你卻很高興呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.35,0:07:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是很爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.23,0:07:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 忘記對你說了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.77,0:08:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎你回來 我可愛的弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.54,0:08:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 我進來了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.33,0:08:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 姊姊還很睏喔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.09,0:08:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一起睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.42,0:08:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.97,0:08:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 快點救我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.85,0:08:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也變成人乾了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.10,0:08:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大早的在吵什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.81,0:08:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.94,0:08:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會變成這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.02,0:08:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 振作點
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.02,0:08:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 振作點
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.03,0:08:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是狗 我是人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.99,0:08:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他到扔這裡面估計\N應該會清醒一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.87,0:08:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 空也變回原樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.13,0:09:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的喔 不管發生什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.84,0:09:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊都是站在空也這邊的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.05,0:09:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對大姊做了什麼需要道歉的嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.76,0:09:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 你這個笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.81,0:09:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的內褲我幫你洗了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.77,0:09:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多謝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.27,0:09:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是屈辱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.27,0:09:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放在這裡的牛奶不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.86,0:09:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 在意剛剛的聲音嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.78,0:09:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底做了什麼啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.54,0:09:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 從這裡偷窺高嶺的屋子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.25,0:09:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣做是犯罪的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.42,0:09:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.84,0:09:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝的太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.39,0:09:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 來了來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.14,0:09:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.64,0:09:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這樣下去胸部就會增大3cm
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.39,0:10:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就會加入到大人的行列中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.40,0:10:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們就等著瞧吧 烏賊 小貓 眼鏡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.07,0:10:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的腦子到底在想什麼 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.66,0:10:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.66,0:10:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得她瞞著我們郵購了什麼東西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.62,0:10:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個也有點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.33,0:10:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點對我來說既有精神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.41,0:10:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又對自己的身材有自信
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.92,0:10:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然被人說的很像貓
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.96,0:10:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那裡還是很好的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.55,0:10:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 慢著 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.17,0:10:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 上面和下面全部給我脫光光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.85,0:10:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比在浴室裡看到的還要大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.35,0:10:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.23,0:10:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撒驕的話 也就是說\N嘗嘗的話也是可以的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.86,0:10:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我溫柔一點嘛 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.98,0:10:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是稍微有點害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.82,0:10:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實就是可愛喔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.83,0:11:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來挺著的狀態還真是不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.92,0:11:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還發撒驕這種聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.67,0:11:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.71,0:11:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是用手來撫摸好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.13,0:11:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.64,0:11:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經快要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.93,0:11:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和我H嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.56,0:11:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.43,0:11:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 讓我看你射的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.98,0:11:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 射出來了 射出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.40,0:11:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.24,0:11:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准馬上射出來 要忍住喔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.99,0:11:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.24,0:11:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿那麼 插進來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.33,0:11:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.25,0:11:44.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊想著和空也合成一體 也有點興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.67,0:11:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看見了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.09,0:11:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.55,0:11:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 我要動了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.05,0:11:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然硬硬的就是棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.35,0:11:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.64,0:11:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.35,0:12:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會把我一半的快感傳授給你的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.69,0:12:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面好像軟軟的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.94,0:12:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像絞合在一起了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.19,0:12:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 跟著我的下面一起動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.61,0:12:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.95,0:12:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動的話會射出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.45,0:12:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是為了那樣\N才先讓你射了一次的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.12,0:12:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.17,0:12:26.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.67,0:12:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 那樣不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.67,0:12:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.70,0:12:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.70,0:12:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.37,0:13:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.25,0:13:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 我好像不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.84,0:13:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.27,0:13:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.77,0:13:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的喘息 結束了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.40,0:13:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.61,0:13:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 我的芥末麵
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.08,0:13:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烏賊 馬上給我出去買 快去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.83,0:13:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.33,0:13:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沖繩的朋友拜託帶的書也買了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.05,0:13:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強硬的長輩墮落了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.05,0:13:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對25歲美貌年輕人\N迷惑的苦悶每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.55,0:14:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是暗示了這麼多東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.52,0:14:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有點恐怖喔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.32,0:14:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是鞋子的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.44,0:14:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光著腳的嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.99,0:14:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.70,0:14:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,cosplay嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.41,0:14:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神隱難道就是這傢伙幹的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.97,0:14:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.93,0:14:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.19,0:14:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎麼說這個也有點
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.15,0:14:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要對姊姊們保密
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.61,0:15:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話又說回來 那個聲音…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.03,0:15:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.61,0:15:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像在哪裡聽到過
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.83,0:15:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.45,0:15:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼 這套服裝還真是很色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.46,0:15:13.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我在努力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.54,0:15:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了成為女人中的大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.38,0:15:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.30,0:15:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛那鬼是緊身服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.26,0:15:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭又來緊身女王裝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.22,0:15:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.63,0:15:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來給你加上個記號\N來證明你是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.97,0:15:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這該死的烏賊  好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.47,0:15:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做為我的弟弟白天還那麼得意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.44,0:15:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好聽我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.31,0:15:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只看著我一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.86,0:15:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那個還真是有精神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.03,0:15:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個到處留情的種
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.57,0:15:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了表示你對我的服從
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.99,0:15:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來舔我的腳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.33,0:15:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你那是什麼表情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.17,0:15:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼怨言嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.79,0:15:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.75,0:16:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我還以為你是變態呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.26,0:16:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做到這種程度
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.89,0:16:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 味道怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.06,0:16:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得大姐頭的腳味道真好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.85,0:16:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.52,0:16:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呀 從以前就是這樣的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.73,0:16:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要遵從我的命令 什麼話都不能說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.73,0:16:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能老實的遵守
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.03,0:16:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.86,0:16:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去給我到床上睡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.53,0:16:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.32,0:16:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很煩耶 安靜的給我去睡就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.41,0:16:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好 你還能用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.92,0:16:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了和男性的經驗 就能成為女人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.38,0:16:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 這個就是陰莖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.63,0:16:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪裡學到這樣的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.67,0:16:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往這裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.18,0:16:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.00,0:16:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭 你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.94,0:17:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 這點算不了什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.57,0:17:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.24,0:17:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.30,0:17:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.89,0:17:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.22,0:18:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭 我快要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.74,0:18:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.67,0:18:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.59,0:18:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了餓了哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.09,0:18:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的芥末麵味道有點淡了喔 烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.93,0:18:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姊 你那份是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.56,0:19:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有一點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.10,0:19:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.19,0:19:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是什麼 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.98,0:19:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來還真是不錯的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.90,0:19:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那個是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.36,0:19:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看只有空也一個人在做飯\N就覺得不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就學著做了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.28,0:19:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要來嚐嚐味道啊 空也
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.49,0:19:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小海做的飯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.79,0:19:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.79,0:19:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又多了一個殺人犯的材料
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.00,0:19:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過份..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.88,0:19:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 要哭了的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.80,0:19:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.05,0:19:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊自己都已經嚐過了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.80,0:19:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿海稍微有點不同
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.56,0:19:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個做的可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.35,0:19:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 周圍怎麼在轉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.40,0:19:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 領教了她的厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.15,0:19:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先洗個澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.17,0:20:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有名的律師在浴池裡面睡著了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.01,0:20:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.31,0:20:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在浴池裡面睡著了是不行的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.11,0:20:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 下一步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.19,0:20:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.94,0:20:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔下我是不行的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.91,0:20:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要芽姊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.66,0:20:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像跟以前並沒有多大的改變
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.71,0:20:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.05,0:20:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.80,0:20:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.55,0:21:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是我的房間吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.31,0:21:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼姊姊會…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.81,0:21:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.95,0:21:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊居然會有這樣的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.00,0:21:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.00,0:21:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.25,0:21:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.96,0:21:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 慢著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.93,0:21:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.84,0:21:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是姊姊不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.31,0:21:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的房間裡做那種事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.77,0:21:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為聞到空也的被子裡\N散發出來的氣味
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.77,0:21:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有點興奮了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.02,0:21:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.48,0:21:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊真美啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.99,0:21:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等等
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.36,0:21:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種情況不好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.33,0:22:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也真壞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.25,0:22:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.16,0:22:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還沒有看過姊姊隱秘的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.58,0:22:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.92,0:22:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 真害羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.46,0:22:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊還是安產型的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.05,0:22:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.30,0:22:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.34,0:22:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你摸我的胸部我都沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.43,0:22:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那裡真的很丟臉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.98,0:22:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.48,0:22:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想看著姊姊害羞的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.94,0:22:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊的這裡很可愛喔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.19,0:22:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡難道不舒服嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.70,0:22:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 這樣真的很丟臉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.12,0:22:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像平常那樣親吻或是擁抱就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.25,0:22:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我就來親吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.96,0:22:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是是這邊的這張嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.13,0:22:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 討厭 為什麼要那麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.26,0:23:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 難道你不知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.72,0:23:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子的那個不在那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.18,0:23:05.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在更前面的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.18,0:23:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.68,0:23:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再放鬆一些
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.35,0:23:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 就這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.15,0:23:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是插屁眼也會有感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.40,0:23:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊還真是淫蕩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.95,0:23:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 那個是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.70,0:23:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.70,0:23:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想就這樣從後面做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.79,0:23:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.88,0:23:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我想就這樣繼續下去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.63,0:23:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想進入姊姊的裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.17,0:23:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和姊姊做愛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.09,0:23:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.89,0:23:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就按你喜歡的方式做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.14,0:23:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我身體的全部都是為了空也而保留著的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.56,0:23:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不痛嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.52,0:23:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.02,0:23:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也知道下一步該怎麼做嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.03,0:23:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.61,0:24:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題 都到這裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.86,0:24:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就從這裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.13,0:24:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.84,0:24:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的熱熱的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.55,0:24:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我動了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.02,0:24:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.37,0:24:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.63,0:24:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.13,0:25:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.18,0:25:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.93,0:25:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.69,0:25:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射在裡面了喔
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.44,0:25:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.19,0:25:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 射了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.20,0:25:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.70,0:25:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.45,0:25:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.67,0:25:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.72,0:25:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.23,0:26:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下子 姊姊的身心都是屬於空也的了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.61,0:26:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯


