[Script Info]
Title:(18禁アニメ) 姉、ちゃんとしようよっ！ 第4話 「愛と罵倒の日々の巻」 (DVD 640x480 WMV9)[CRC B308].ass
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.19,0:00:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能見到柊學姊我真的很高興呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.76,0:00:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳身體健康真的是比什麼都還重要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.87,0:00:07.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且人也變得更漂亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.47,0:00:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們兩個才是呢 今天真的都好可愛哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.74,0:00:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好討厭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.17,0:00:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呿 竟然碰到這幾個麻煩的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.19,0:00:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 方便到我家喝杯茶嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.63,0:00:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.66,0:00:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 妳看那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.72,0:00:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然有人會在人這麼多的地方接吻
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.35,0:00:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個混蛋東西！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.93,0:00:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊學姊 妳剛才說什麼啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.21,0:00:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 沒什麼事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.24,0:00:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.37,0:00:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜歡空也的味道了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.07,0:01:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才芝麻冰淇淋的芝麻沾到臉上了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.56,0:01:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我漸漸開始習慣跟姊姊們生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.27,0:01:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有時也會發生一些小插曲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.49,0:01:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過每天過得還蠻愉快的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.36,0:01:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些美麗而可愛的姐姐們\N每天也都過得很快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.24,0:01:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是這麼認為的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.63,0:01:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像吃太多含水分的東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.76,0:01:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好難過
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.05,0:01:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點把門關上啦 你這個烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.02,0:01:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.81,0:01:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你進來幹嘛啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.75,0:01:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.44,0:01:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一直盯著這邊看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.03,0:01:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹嘛又回頭啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.99,0:02:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噓 是要芽姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.62,0:02:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果被她知道我們兩個一起上廁所的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.18,0:02:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭 妳下面還沒長毛嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.43,0:02:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都叫你不要看了 你這個烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.47,0:02:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎麼辦啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.57,0:02:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.98,0:02:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.30,0:02:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垃圾烏賊混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.90,0:02:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是懲罰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.34,0:02:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我大白天的在這邊灑水
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.11,0:02:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算什麼大姐頭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.35,0:02:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這還真不是普通的熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.17,0:02:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水剛灑馬上就蒸發了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.96,0:02:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問有事嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.69,0:02:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.86,0:02:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是這個家的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.77,0:02:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那你就是空也對吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.93,0:03:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.02,0:03:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨 讓你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.34,0:03:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是高嶺小姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.00,0:03:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.03,0:03:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生是父親的舊識
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.81,0:03:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說他是海洋生物學的學者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.81,0:03:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經常搭船往返於世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.59,0:03:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是乘著考察旅行順便來我們家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.96,0:03:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過大姐頭的表現有點可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.82,0:03:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎麼回事啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就先告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.77,0:03:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 請下再來玩哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.58,0:03:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離下一班船出發還有幾天的時問
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.38,0:03:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以會暫時在這個鎮裡待一陣子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.22,0:03:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請…請問 是真的嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.89,0:03:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會常來這裡玩的 沒關係吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.17,0:04:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 請你一定要來這裡坐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.53,0:04:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼空也 我們下次再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.20,0:04:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 這下機會來了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.44,0:04:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,機會…該不會…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.88,0:04:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳喜歡上壬生先生了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.95,0:04:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.31,0:04:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能被我這種人喜歡上\N壬生先生也應該感到榮幸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.04,0:04:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的假的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.54,0:04:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生可能沒辦法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.39,0:04:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高嶺可是很任性的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.00,0:04:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.82,0:04:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實如此
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.95,0:04:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不會把妳當成他的對象啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.40,0:04:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不說年齡的差距
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.45,0:04:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傲慢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.15,0:04:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有二條辮子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.26,0:04:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這和髮型沒關係吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.94,0:04:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貧乳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.69,0:04:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,態度高傲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.72,0:04:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二條辮子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.10,0:04:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.91,0:04:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,適合那種大叔的女人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.54,0:04:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是那種荷爾蒙爆多的成熟女性才對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.48,0:05:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高嶺妳還是個小女孩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.04,0:05:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.92,0:05:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.12,0:05:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之後壬生先生就常常來這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.20,0:05:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對大姐頭而言 每次都是嚴苛的接待挑戰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.68,0:05:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然大姐頭她是認真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 壬生先生到底是什麼人啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.75,0:05:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姊 妳還真的是很喜歡照顧庭院呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.50,0:05:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我很喜歡土地的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.25,0:05:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了啊 大姐頭？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.85,0:05:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.53,0:05:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.11,0:05:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.56,0:05:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.66,0:05:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.44,0:05:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜 那些花很可憐的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.20,0:05:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得這麼漂亮的花…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.38,0:06:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊你們還不是隨便就把雜草除掉了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.83,0:06:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.77,0:06:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼因為不因為的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.07,0:06:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,草兒可是不畏風雨 拼了命地努力長大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.81,0:06:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是妳們卻毫不猶豫的就除掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.88,0:06:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們的屍體還在那裡袋子裡面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.39,0:06:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還發出呻吟的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.39,0:06:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明還活著、還活著…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.70,0:06:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.56,0:06:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高嶺大姐頭好像被壬生先生邀請\N要到海邊玩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.00,0:06:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了做事前預演 大家都來了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.56,0:06:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然壬生先生邀請妳是沒錯啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.80,0:06:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.61,0:06:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我游泳可是很行的哦」\N這種謊話還是不要說比較好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.07,0:07:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才來這裡特訓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.69,0:07:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭 妳現在能游多遠啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.38,0:07:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全都不會游 不行嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.26,0:07:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我允許你教我游泳
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.48,0:07:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這對奴隸來說可是不可多得的優待哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.45,0:07:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好感謝我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.36,0:07:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.88,0:07:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 總之妳先打一下水試看看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.37,0:07:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 你想把我害死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.91,0:07:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.77,0:07:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進步得很快呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.50,0:07:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我稍微放手一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.04,0:07:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之一定可以成功的 大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.90,0:07:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要芽姊姊被不良少年騷擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.70,0:07:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要芽姊姊 沒事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.57,0:07:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我心情鬱卒的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.82,0:08:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連續來了幾個垃圾 真令人傷腦筋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.56,0:08:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳沒事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.56,0:08:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高嶺她學得怎麼樣啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.63,0:08:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭她…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.83,0:08:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.41,0:08:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭變成小魚了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.06,0:08:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有咧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.31,0:08:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這樣 接下來我允許你教我煮菜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.86,0:08:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次換煮菜了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.28,0:08:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹嘛那麼追求完美啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.09,0:08:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就可以追上姊姊她們了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.32,0:08:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道壬生先生為什麼會來我們家嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.91,0:08:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.68,0:08:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是來找要芽姊姊的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.98,0:08:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳會不會想太多了啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.82,0:08:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.05,0:08:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生約姊姊吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.34,0:08:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常來我們家為的就是要見姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.87,0:08:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生還若無其事的說\N「要芽小姐在家嗎 」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好難過…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.45,0:08:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然以我為藉口來找姊姊\N我決不會原諒他的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.08,0:09:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會讓他回心轉意的 為了這點…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.83,0:09:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.85,0:09:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 空也？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.80,0:09:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙就這樣自己昏過去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.06,0:09:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有大困難
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.29,0:09:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是有一顆不失敗低頭的堅韌之心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.34,0:09:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 跟姊姊一起洗澡吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.28,0:09:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 空也？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.52,0:09:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我腦子裡都是被大姐頭欺負的回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.23,0:09:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你擋到路了 滾開啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.27,0:09:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.83,0:09:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那是什麼眼神啊 有意見嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.58,0:09:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把這傢伙弄哭還真是有趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.29,0:09:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你來當馬讓我坐在上面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.89,0:09:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很高興吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.02,0:09:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高興的話就給我笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.92,0:09:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.19,0:09:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你這種沒用的傢伙 點心我全部拿走哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.35,0:09:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就含著手指頭看我吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.86,0:10:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼粗暴的人竟然也有喜歡的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.06,0:10:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我是很想幫她啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.86,0:10:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生還真是帥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.19,0:10:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有內涵呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.89,0:10:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個紳士呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.46,0:10:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 再怎麼說\N你們兩個年齡也差太多了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.63,0:10:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛是不分國籍和年齡的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.93,0:10:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像妳這種眼鏡妹是沒有辦法理解的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.10,0:10:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 壬生先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.38,0:10:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種大叔到底是哪裡好啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.07,0:10:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等妳當歐巴桑了\N那傢伙可能都變成滿臉皺紋的老爺爺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.32,0:10:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.45,0:10:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管時光怎麼流逝\N年齡差別還是不會縮短的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.09,0:10:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要心靈的差距有縮短就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.88,0:10:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要芽姊姊妳認為呢 像這種類型的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.52,0:10:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 以一般來說他算是不錯的了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.42,0:10:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.98,0:10:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是喜歡空也你這種類型的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.73,0:10:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊也是空也這邊的 放心好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.61,0:10:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個大叔感覺就好像是在礦坑裡挖礦的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.25,0:11:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃飽了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.16,0:11:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道了 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.79,0:11:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 高嶺？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.42,0:11:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生他…壬生先生他…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.27,0:11:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在閃閃發亮的星空下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.83,0:11:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位少女將前往那被月光照耀的海邊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.16,0:11:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會錯的 一定是告白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.46,0:11:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過真沒想到壬生先生會在晚上\N叫我去海邊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.86,0:11:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣不是很好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.70,0:11:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真的是告白的話\N那妳做的努力也沒有白費了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.28,0:11:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.97,0:11:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.43,0:11:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿腦子都在想著被告白
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.73,0:11:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真像個傻瓜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.10,0:11:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能是告白啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.91,0:11:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎麼樣也只是藉酒邀約罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.36,0:11:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過讓她受點挫折\N對她來說也是個不錯的學習呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.95,0:11:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生的STEADY
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.68,0:11:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是說STUDY吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.48,0:11:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等她回來了就對她說「好可惜啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.48,0:11:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再幫她開個可惜派對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.11,0:12:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實如此\N給她個跟聖母峰一樣高的炒麵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.19,0:12:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個 說不定是真的告白
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.60,0:12:09.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就準備派對有點不太好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.43,0:12:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把門關上就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.90,0:12:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭 不管結果怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.26,0:12:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不要太受傷了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.15,0:12:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊\N像這種情況你應該說 「妳真的要去嗎 」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.33,0:12:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是「不要去好了」才對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.77,0:12:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 為什麼大姐頭要跟我說這些話呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.67,0:12:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真是個遲鈍的傢伙呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.78,0:12:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說些我聽不懂的話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.41,0:12:47.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了安全起見 就跟蹤她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.89,0:12:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 對妳的受邀說聲謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.36,0:12:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不會啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.32,0:13:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在說什麼啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.14,0:13:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.64,0:13:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是聽得一清二楚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.48,0:13:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要打起精神仔細聽了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.69,0:13:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我來讀唇語吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.91,0:13:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳從哪學來的啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.77,0:13:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才郵購買來學的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.82,0:13:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生 還記得我們初次見面的時候嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.30,0:13:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那個時候妳正在練習騎腳踏車吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.76,0:13:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被月光照亮的少女
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.85,0:13:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻使月光顯得更耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.41,0:13:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.20,0:13:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.17,0:13:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的妳真的很美
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.27,0:13:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都知道的 高嶺小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.38,0:13:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實妳愛著我的對吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.58,0:13:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.13,0:13:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道妳在隱瞞什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.50,0:13:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還說什麼我在自以為是之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.86,0:13:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不是的 不是自以為是 不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.57,0:13:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一位海洋學者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.50,0:13:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一位深愛著蔚藍大海的水之旅者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.47,0:14:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想在一個地方久留
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.72,0:14:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我無法回應妳的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.40,0:14:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.09,0:14:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我對壬生先生充滿著憧憬…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.66,0:14:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過妳希望我讓妳留下\N這個夏天的回憶的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.85,0:14:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望讓我用一個夜晚來回報\N初次見面時的那份感情的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.61,0:14:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以做到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.20,0:14:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個…壬生先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.13,0:14:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生…等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.09,0:14:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個的話還是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.90,0:14:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.63,0:14:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.32,0:14:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.65,0:14:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壬生先生 不管你是不是真的喜歡她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.65,0:14:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之別想就這麼簡單地得到她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.09,0:14:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你這麼緊張的樣子…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.16,0:14:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是喜歡你的高嶺姊姊啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.24,0:14:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的沒錯吧 空也？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.10,0:15:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事無所謂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.22,0:15:02.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我說中了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.91,0:15:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了\N那麼就用男人之間的對決 來決勝負吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.52,0:15:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我接受
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.06,0:15:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.97,0:15:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我會在大姐頭的房間呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.61,0:15:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要芽姐姐說 你是為了我才受傷的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.93,0:15:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以當然要由我來照顧你才對
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.89,0:15:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.06,0:16:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…雖然事情發展得有點出乎意料…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.35,0:16:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎麼說…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.89,0:16:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你贏了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.85,0:16:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 是我贏了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.15,0:16:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你 還有…謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.56,0:16:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該說你真的很帥\N還是說我該對你刮目相看了…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.78,0:16:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.80,0:16:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.75,0:16:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.53,0:16:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然我贏了 我應該有拿獎品的權力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.89,0:16:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到一個烏賊竟然會這麼溫柔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.74,0:16:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不像大姐頭妳這麼粗暴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.86,0:17:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.23,0:17:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 大姐頭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.75,0:17:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.83,0:17:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭很敏感呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.57,0:17:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.42,0:17:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也 也讓我幫你弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.83,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大…大姐頭 很好吃吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.57,0:18:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然囉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.40,0:18:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大…大姐頭！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.55,0:18:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.34,0:18:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的…很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.91,0:19:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.11,0:21:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.15,0:21:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.98,0:22:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該還可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.87,0:22:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空也的…好熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.54,0:23:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧…再激烈一點…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.95,0:23:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.09,0:24:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經醒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.00,0:24:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是第一次看到大姐頭彈鋼琴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.12,0:24:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.85,0:24:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的琴曲可是很珍貴的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.32,0:24:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在遇到可以談心的男人的時候\N我才會彈的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.35,0:24:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.29,0:24:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為要成為完美的女性
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.22,0:24:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才會允許你來幫我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.36,0:24:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要感謝我哦 烏賊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.30,0:24:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.30,0:24:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這的確挺困難的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.96,0:24:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 把我當傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.25,0:24:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說話 好好聽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.97,0:24:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烏賊


