[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 960
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,45,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00943c5a,&H80551055,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,15,15,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.43,0:00:12.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我反抗什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.76,0:00:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝大小姐妳還不行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.44,0:00:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.48,0:01:04.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了　快跑
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.67,0:01:23.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們的嘴巴只會說說而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.83,0:01:25.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是沒根性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.67,0:01:26.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.51,0:01:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐘白翔一\N運動神經超群，是水泳部的社員
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.26,0:01:34.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過他也不是很認真就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.18,0:01:36.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後，接下來該怎麼做呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.43,0:01:39.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼乾脆讓我來．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.02,0:01:41.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經夠了．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.94,0:01:43.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在最要緊的事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.85,0:01:46.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.62,0:01:59.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳說要我做什麼\N我都願意去做的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.62,0:02:02.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我是老師的男奴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.21,0:02:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.88,0:02:13.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老．．．老師
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.64,0:02:20.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐘白翔一，可以用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.20,0:02:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侵害玲世的那時失敗．．．\N還有歌須美
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.29,0:02:44.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往後會開始有趣多了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.63,0:02:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你那樣子\N表示進行得不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.63,0:02:56.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩已經被我征服了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.47,0:03:00.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要的試卷我也拷貝好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.22,0:03:06.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就是校長的醜聞\N請你小心的放回去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.04,0:03:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹂躪美好花園之地之刻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.93,0:04:24.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.70,0:04:48.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.49,0:05:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了，弄得這麼暗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.34,0:05:39.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴乃怎麼還沒回來？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.34,0:05:46.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完飯之後\N她自己就會回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.68,0:05:50.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有吃的，我幫妳準備去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.93,0:05:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用好了，就快點下來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.27,0:05:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是．．．是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.62,0:06:11.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這時間．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.12,0:06:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這．．．這個是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.72,0:06:25.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校長，你怎麼會想來的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.89,0:06:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是突然想見盛澤老師而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.64,0:06:33.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這麼生疏，叫我舞子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.23,0:06:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞子，這是學校
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.56,0:06:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校長在保健室和妳現在做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.32,0:06:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫聲盛澤老師也沒錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.40,0:06:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校長大人真是愛欺負人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.66,0:06:47.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎，我愛欺負妳嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.57,0:06:50.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我就繼續下去囉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.00,0:06:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.92,0:06:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳說謊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.42,0:07:00.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都這麼濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.75,0:07:02.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我將威力加強吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.44,0:07:21.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.28,0:07:26.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離不開吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.03,0:07:29.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣，想要我再欺負妳下去嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.87,0:07:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來換這只，像蟲一樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.13,0:07:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣！味道如何，感受得到嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.31,0:07:54.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.81,0:08:01.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要插第二隻哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.32,0:08:04.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔！真美的臀部
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.40,0:08:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美少女的小穴\N就讓我來侍奉妳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.91,0:08:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再摸那裏了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.58,0:08:14.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快要變奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.91,0:08:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點，快點
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:18.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎，是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.75,0:08:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要上了哦，要上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.18,0:08:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，很好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.19,0:08:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞子老師，那感覺真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.61,0:08:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳的肛門，真讓我受不了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.19,0:08:49.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好強．．．\N給我．．給我．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.78,0:08:53.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也給我的小穴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.70,0:08:57.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒．．再來．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.12,0:08:59.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激烈點
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.54,0:09:03.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小穴像是快被撐爆了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.88,0:09:06.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別．．．那麼快．．．\N那麼快了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.31,0:09:17.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是，學校方面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.14,0:09:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能跟校長匹敵的\N只有宮理事長而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.15,0:09:25.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛好到了需要打招呼的時候了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.82,0:09:27.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個讓人忌憚的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.57,0:09:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宮歌須美
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.41,0:09:36.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然讓身在宮集團的我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.74,0:09:40.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在學校受到處分
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.91,0:09:45.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她以為我有那麼容易對付嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.09,0:09:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她大概以為這樣就可以安心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.09,0:09:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然敢將兩個女兒送來這學校
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.93,0:09:55.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣手中就有人質了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.26,0:10:00.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時就讓她們幫忙一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.43,0:10:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.77,0:10:04.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前我也說過了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.19,0:10:07.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這段時間我托妳辦的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.44,0:10:14.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從上任宮集團\N前院長大河原成的醜聞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.54,0:10:24.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下次開委員會時\N我就揭穿宮理事長的醜聞
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.46,0:10:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時，盛澤老師
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.46,0:10:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳也會
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.06,0:10:48.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚\N我就一直在想著翔一大人就練習了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.82,0:10:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴乃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.08,0:11:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.08,0:11:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來，再激烈點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.76,0:11:21.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒，好棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.45,0:11:43.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再快點，再快點
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.62,0:11:48.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.71,0:11:53.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我，給我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.47,0:12:05.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來，你已經知道了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.81,0:12:10.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要緊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.56,0:12:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宮小姐\N妳好像很不舒服的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.07,0:12:16.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一節是自習課
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.40,0:12:17.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳要不要到保健室休息一下呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.24,0:12:19.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保健室？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.07,0:12:23.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也好！\N嗯，我這就去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.66,0:12:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我陪妳嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.25,0:12:26.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了，沒那麼嚴重
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.67,0:12:31.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是？\N要放回校長室去？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.33,0:12:33.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽屜並沒有鎖上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.67,0:12:35.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校長所坐的桌椅
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.26,0:12:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在它最右下角的抽屜裏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.76,0:12:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將它放回去鎖上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.51,0:12:44.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴乃\N妳只要乖乖的聽我的話去做就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.52,0:12:47.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是，翔一大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:05.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找這個嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.82,0:13:41.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳在做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.83,0:13:54.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒經過允許\N擅自進入校長室做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.09,0:14:00.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我乖乖的聽話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.18,0:14:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱，什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種燥熱的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.18,0:14:13.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是．．宮的女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.11,0:14:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宮鈴世
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.02,0:14:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴乃的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.86,0:14:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她看見我們所做的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.03,0:14:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她跟理事長說
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.45,0:14:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就會被校長處分\N逐出學校
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.53,0:14:26.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也會被退學
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.28,0:14:28.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會不能再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.04,0:14:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎樣做才好呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.87,0:14:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.62,0:14:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓這位妹妹跟她的姐姐做相同的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.79,0:14:37.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓她成為你的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.96,0:14:40.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親姐妹都成為我的奴隸．．．嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.38,0:14:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在就要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.14,0:14:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裏就隨你喜歡的用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.22,0:14:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯！我就不客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.25,0:15:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很擅長不是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.09,0:15:22.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我給妳一點獎勵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.18,0:15:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別停！給我繼續含下去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.85,0:15:37.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好．．好棒．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.36,0:15:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.03,0:15:47.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理事長
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.20,0:15:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校長，這到底是怎麼一回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.87,0:15:55.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這．．這是．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.29,0:15:58.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知是誰，將這資料傳到我這裏？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.46,0:16:01.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所想要做的行為
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.96,0:16:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經過我的調查證明了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.30,0:16:07.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再繼續下去\N我就跟你沒完沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.30,0:16:10.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呈如我所想的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.55,0:16:12.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你背叛我的父親對你的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.81,0:16:15.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然為了自己的自私與欲念
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.06,0:16:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.15,0:16:24.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個聲音，該不會是．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.57,0:16:32.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴乃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.33,0:16:39.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.34,0:16:49.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛！請溫柔點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.18,0:16:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我．．我有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.60,0:16:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然發出高興的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.11,0:17:08.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽，別．．別看我．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.29,0:17:17.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了\N好．．好舒服．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.74,0:17:53.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你．．你在做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.58,0:18:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算對我做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.42,0:18:03.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一學長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.59,0:18:13.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裏還不夠濕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.18,0:18:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還是處女吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.68,0:18:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這裏卻開始濕透起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.43,0:18:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想要這樣．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.18,0:18:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.02,0:18:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.27,0:18:28.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱！竟然會這麼熱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.36,0:18:37.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也好熱．．．\N從以前到現在都沒這麼熱過
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.45,0:18:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.04,0:18:44.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天該談些什麼才好？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.29,0:18:46.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近日的比賽很不得了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.30,0:18:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.39,0:18:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牆壁有密室
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.73,0:19:07.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.57,0:19:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.82,0:19:15.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始\N才要認真侵略妳母親呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.24,0:19:21.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真可惡\N竟然對我們做這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.83,0:19:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別以為我會放過你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.66,0:19:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次的宮集會\N就不會這樣就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.84,0:19:33.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時\N就是讓你這代的理事長退任之時
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.01,0:19:36.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都虧這個力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.76,0:19:42.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有這個新聞
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.52,0:19:48.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能會有這回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.86,0:19:49.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那這一台呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.63,0:20:12.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是妳害我無法解決妳們\N竟然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.80,0:20:16.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先讓妳跟妳凡的女兒一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.80,0:20:20.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓妳品嘗前任理事長\N所享有的味道也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.72,0:20:23.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請別將我跟那個女的相提並論
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.31,0:20:26.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是那個女的\N可真抱歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.73,0:20:29.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛澤老師
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.06,0:20:31.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.07,0:20:36.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個女的就是我母親
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.16,0:20:50.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年紀大的你，還縱欲過多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.25,0:20:53.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是對你的處分
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.50,0:20:54.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這是做了什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.26,0:20:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是妳指使的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.01,0:21:00.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在才剛開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.93,0:21:05.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓妳體驗我所曾受過的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.52,0:21:08.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是讓這種上年紀的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.77,0:21:11.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是一個年輕人來上妳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.44,0:21:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後會無期了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.86,0:21:22.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有光
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.46,0:21:29.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.71,0:21:33.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鈴世
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.21,0:21:35.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對我女兒做了什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.88,0:21:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女兒？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.05,0:21:40.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要，住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.89,0:21:45.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一大人，住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.97,0:21:49.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親，別對她出手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.48,0:21:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是感情滿深的母子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.31,0:21:55.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是只是想獨得我的寵愛呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.48,0:21:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是那個呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.24,0:22:02.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳就是她們兩人的母親啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.16,0:22:06.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦，果然還能夠用
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.83,0:22:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，都濕淋了我的手指
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.41,0:22:10.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點住手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.50,0:22:20.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行！\N讓我．．由我來代替吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.76,0:22:23.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快停下來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.63,0:23:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:07.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳終於醒過來了啊！\N鈴世大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.14,0:23:08.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別離開
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.47,0:23:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.06,0:23:14.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裏也別拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.65,0:23:18.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人的欲求還真大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.57,0:23:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.49,0:23:27.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.08,0:23:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.75,0:23:35.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.58,0:23:41.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹，別侵犯我的妹妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.09,0:23:41.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.76,0:23:45.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊，不要．．別看．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.51,0:23:48.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次是姊妹情嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.26,0:23:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裏可是很興奮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.85,0:23:54.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道妳敢說\N這裏都沒有自慰過嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.60,0:23:56.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒．．沒有．．．\N我沒有自慰過
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.77,0:23:58.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別跟我說假話
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.86,0:24:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.03,0:24:07.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛，快停下來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.95,0:24:10.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎，那麼就停吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.12,0:24:11.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去跟妳姊姊做
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.70,0:24:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一大人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.21,0:24:16.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.13,0:24:25.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣？求我啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.22,0:24:27.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好．．好棒．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.30,0:24:29.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一大人，再快點，快點
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.64,0:24:33.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱．．好熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.14,0:24:39.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要丟了．．要丟了．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.06,0:24:40.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.23,0:24:41.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要．．不要．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.73,0:24:43.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過份，好過份
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.23,0:24:45.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.41,0:24:49.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了．．要去了．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.91,0:24:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要．．不要．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.25,0:25:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐在高潮後\N原來還會撒尿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.34,0:25:08.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是品格高尚啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.26,0:25:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了，讓妳久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.35,0:25:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了，好了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.01,0:25:20.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翔一大人的那裏剛剛享用過妳姊姊了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.10,0:25:21.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳來幫我舔乾淨吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.44,0:25:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，很好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.78,0:25:28.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換下一個步驟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.87,0:25:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，不能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.12,0:25:38.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了，要上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.29,0:25:41.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.38,0:25:50.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳不是想要嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.83,0:26:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好．．好熱．．．\N不行．．出來了．．．
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.33,0:26:26.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好！\N真看不出妳是剛喪失處女的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.84,0:26:29.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓妳們兩姊妹成為女人的我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.51,0:26:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就請妳們繼續讚美我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.85,0:26:44.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全員一致通過
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.11,0:26:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由前理事長宮歌須美推薦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.27,0:26:51.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盛澤舞子成為理事長了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.20,0:28:30.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（完）
