[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.00,0:00:11.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使布蕾德真的會來這個城市嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.50,0:00:13.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻象女王陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.77,0:00:17.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是在八小時以前就確認的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.40,0:00:19.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卡琳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.47,0:00:21.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是，母后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.83,0:00:25.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是十二小時前拍到的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.64,0:00:28.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在機場大廳的影像
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.33,0:00:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這幾個女人嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.79,0:00:32.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.30,0:00:34.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神宮寺萌奈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.30,0:00:37.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不動綾女
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.36,0:00:40.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有椎崎莎雅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.66,0:00:48.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是活潑好動的女孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.98,0:00:51.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳也不希望太無聊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.69,0:00:55.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就好好跟他們玩玩吧，韋德
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.02,0:00:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謹遵吩咐，幻象女王陛下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.65,0:00:59.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靜候佳音
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.51,0:01:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過\N怎麼沒看到尼爾凱薩的人呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.87,0:01:06.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她怎麼了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:08.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莫非..
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.49,0:01:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是天使布蕾德嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.62,0:01:16.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉修
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.77,0:01:17.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滋列奇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.74,0:01:22.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快去準備迎接幾位千金小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.88,0:01:29.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎來到我們的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.12,0:01:31.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使布蕾德
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.18,0:01:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很期待跟妳們見面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.11,0:03:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了，萌奈？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.25,0:03:33.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,臉色這麼差
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.27,0:03:35.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼放不下的事嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.20,0:03:37.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊...沒、沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.44,0:03:41.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是在擔心響香小姐吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.63,0:03:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.64,0:03:49.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,響香阿姨！！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.82,0:03:55.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一定會沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.76,0:03:59.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要靜養幾天就會好了\N醫生也有說過啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:05.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次我把妳們拉到\N我來拍寫真集的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.78,0:04:10.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是為了等響香小姐恢復的時候\N大家都能用笑容來迎接她啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.40,0:04:11.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.96,0:04:14.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.84,0:04:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要下去游泳了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.81,0:04:22.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要從那裡跳下來...？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.55,0:04:23.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她要上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.63,0:04:29.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是無人能登頂的酒店名勝\N高99公尺的...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.03,0:04:32.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,傳說中的跳台
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.98,0:04:35.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她好像真的要跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.40,0:04:39.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個該不會是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:41.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,綾女
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.87,0:04:44.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫她不要太出風頭的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.47,0:04:47.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她的忍者血統又在作怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.16,0:04:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，是忍者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.47,0:04:52.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大和，跟我決鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.51,0:04:53.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼、什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.95,0:05:01.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,氣死我了，please
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.48,0:05:05.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她打算來真的啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.63,0:05:21.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳想用那把劍戰勝我的洋槍？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.06,0:05:25.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會用速度制勝
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.05,0:05:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,綾女小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.16,0:05:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個...綾女小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.68,0:05:46.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳...妳的泳衣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.53,0:05:49.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好美啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.18,0:05:51.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳現在的打扮...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.38,0:05:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,簡直美若天仙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.29,0:06:01.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還看什麼？白痴，快把髒手拿開
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.63,0:06:07.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,What's your name,Samurai gilr？\N(妳叫什麼名字啊，忍者少女？)
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.01,0:06:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫萌奈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.68,0:06:11.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.91,0:06:18.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾爾菲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.76,0:06:22.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾爾菲‧艾夫曼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.46,0:06:33.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本週挑戰的項目就是這裡\N馬上為大家送上養老之湯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.01,0:06:38.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正如各位所見，目前正在更衣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.01,0:06:40.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N挑戰者就是如平常的這位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.31,0:06:43.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,橘夜月小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.54,0:06:46.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,HI！大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.69,0:06:47.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼，今天要搞什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.92,0:06:52.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本次的挑戰者要進行蒙眼檢查\NIN養老之湯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.83,0:06:53.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.57,0:06:55.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係，只要聲音就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.20,0:06:58.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,敢騙我的話就宰了你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.85,0:07:01.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.19,0:07:04.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家的目光都集中在她身上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.24,0:07:06.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊，夜月小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.39,0:07:09.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挑戰成功
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.45,0:07:10.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看那一搖一擺的雙峰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.04,0:07:13.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道這就是重力作用嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.97,0:07:16.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，下次就輪到內褲了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.61,0:07:18.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就頭痛了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.17,0:07:19.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的是相當頭痛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.75,0:07:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們為了救出響香阿姨\N闖入了暗黑之母的城堡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.92,0:07:36.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們中了計
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.27,0:07:39.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被引到了一個謎樣的房間
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.17,0:07:53.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這道光...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.42,0:08:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知為何我們竟得以脫身
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.75,0:08:20.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暗黑之母的首領
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.77,0:08:21.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻象女王
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.19,0:08:35.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.62,0:08:44.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使之劍也無效了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.74,0:08:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她是最強的敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.56,0:08:53.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.36,0:08:56.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我聽到她在自言自語
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.43,0:09:02.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌奈...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.51,0:09:11.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那時候我沒聽錯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.52,0:09:13.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幻象女王
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.12,0:09:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼她會知道我的名字？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.88,0:09:25.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳有什麼心「凡」的是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.83,0:09:29.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...心煩的事啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.24,0:09:32.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道自己以後該怎麼辦才好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.52,0:09:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來真的是「凡」人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是要聲音而已\N一定要矇住眼睛嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.52,0:09:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都看不到還調查什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.73,0:09:59.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等，我們要去哪裡啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.57,0:10:00.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,TAKE IT EASY
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.79,0:10:02.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蒙眼布我要解開了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.50,0:10:05.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.23,0:10:10.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅...莎雅...莎雅！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.59,0:10:13.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:14.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,年輕真好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.30,0:10:16.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美麗真好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.14,0:10:22.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅，保持那種目光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.88,0:10:24.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳的目光很銳利
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.81,0:10:30.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誘人的身材，還有那叛逆的態度
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.56,0:10:33.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股、膝蓋、叛逆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.70,0:10:41.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,判逆，那是對君主的正面挑戰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.08,0:10:42.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.87,0:10:44.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,繼續、繼續、繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.32,0:10:45.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,繼續~
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.05,0:10:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,繼~續，之後!!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.29,0:10:51.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.36,0:10:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.77,0:10:56.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼眼...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.17,0:10:59.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,眼神！！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.28,0:11:19.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真討厭，做觀眾也夠累人的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.90,0:11:21.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我硬拉妳們來的，抱歉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.78,0:11:24.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做偶像也很辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.89,0:11:26.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正一直都是這樣的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.13,0:11:30.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳不覺得那個攝影師\N有點怪怪的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.54,0:11:32.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，妳說彌生先生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.51,0:11:33.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,彌生先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.42,0:11:35.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天辛苦了，掰掰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.71,0:11:40.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天的攝影順利結束
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.40,0:11:43.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次的攝影就拜託了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.68,0:11:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經八個小時沒上廁所了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.96,0:11:48.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,白痴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.05,0:11:49.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要...要尿出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.12,0:11:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼，我要回旅館了\N綾女妳呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.19,0:11:57.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我還想在這裡休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.41,0:11:59.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了，好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.29,0:12:00.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.30,0:12:17.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,短暫的休息啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.20,0:12:21.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,萌奈...妳沒事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.37,0:12:33.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贏...贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.63,0:12:35.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是我贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.02,0:12:39.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害啊，萌奈，武士女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.87,0:12:41.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有啦，偶然的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.53,0:12:43.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是運氣好...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.49,0:12:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳沒事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.95,0:12:49.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳的關心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.16,0:12:52.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們來玩愛爾菲小姐的強項吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.09,0:12:58.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾爾菲小姐玩射擊遊戲很厲害吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.78,0:13:06.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...射擊遊戲呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.67,0:13:10.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了，艾爾菲小姐，找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.13,0:13:15.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾爾菲小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.26,0:13:23.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呼，下次的攝影就在\N附近的攝影棚裡吧，大介先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.07,0:13:25.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭，不要叫我下面的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.62,0:13:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫彌生，要叫我的姓
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.15,0:13:34.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，妳走錯地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.81,0:13:36.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找錯地方了...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.56,0:13:38.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳給給给我離遠一點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.07,0:13:40.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是男廁所
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.09,0:13:47.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有妖怪啊！！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.03,0:14:52.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人妖？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.42,0:15:08.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾爾菲小姐泡到哪裡去了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.72,0:15:14.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是太得意忘形了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.39,0:15:16.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害她不高興了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.81,0:15:25.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停電嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.08,0:16:00.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛的蝴蝶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.60,0:16:02.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳是誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.86,0:16:03.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.91,0:16:07.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想知道別人的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.01,0:16:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要先報上自己的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.11,0:16:12.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽沒敎過妳嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.02,0:16:14.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神宮寺萌奈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:18.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不對，是天使布蕾德
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.03,0:16:23.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她居然知道我？！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.19,0:16:24.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.65,0:16:28.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是暗黑之母的人？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.02,0:16:32.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯、沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.05,0:16:35.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.76,0:16:37.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好很好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.40,0:16:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.61,0:16:41.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再大膽一點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:42.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來~
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.94,0:16:54.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯沒錯\N擺出「誰都可以來上我」的神態
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:08.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那件飾物太不配了，拿下來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.54,0:17:11.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.88,0:17:14.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點拿下來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.21,0:17:14.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.02,0:17:17.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小薰~~
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.23,0:17:20.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個就拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.31,0:17:30.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個也要脫掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.38,0:17:34.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.44,0:17:40.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.83,0:17:48.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你脫什麼褲子啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.58,0:17:49.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼為什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.74,0:17:51.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳是「為什麼星人」嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.63,0:17:54.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想脫別人的褲子\N先要脫自己的褲子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.82,0:17:58.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽沒過妳嗎，莎雅？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.22,0:18:02.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不對，是天使恩達
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.70,0:18:08.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了，可愛的萌奈小姐\N打算怎麼辦呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.48,0:18:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是要保持可愛蝴蝶的樣子\N被蜘蛛絲纏到死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.28,0:18:19.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是要變身打我打倒呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.94,0:18:25.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了，正義天使布蕾德
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.66,0:18:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,見到敵人不是壞人的話\N不願意出手呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.55,0:18:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.82,0:18:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就有戰意了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.84,0:18:43.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然是暗黑之母的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.88,0:18:46.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,終於決定要出手了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.00,0:18:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使變身
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.46,0:19:09.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使布蕾德，參見
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.35,0:19:12.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.29,0:19:15.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我也報上名來好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.50,0:19:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫韋德
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.97,0:19:20.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是幻象女王陛下的手下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.72,0:19:23.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.06,0:19:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使之劍！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.24,0:19:31.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊，這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.94,0:19:41.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？力量被吸走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.45,0:20:05.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.73,0:20:07.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這副驚恐的表情我拍下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.89,0:20:11.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過，這個寫真集的主題是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.70,0:20:16.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「誰看了都想上的女人」\N所以妳還要更淫蕩點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.60,0:20:19.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,誰...誰要更淫蕩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.99,0:20:27.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴說不要\N一抓咪咪臉上又有絕佳的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.21,0:20:28.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是專業級的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.64,0:20:31.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,攝影師和模特兒都是專業級的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.57,0:20:35.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是專業級的~對照相機說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.37,0:20:42.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.14,0:20:46.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶像莎雅秘密的...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.78,0:20:49.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,森林、森林、森林
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.24,0:20:50.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.80,0:20:53.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.35,0:20:58.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笑一個
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.65,0:21:02.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要、不要拍
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.98,0:21:06.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅的屁股又大又圓
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.83,0:21:09.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅的屁股也來笑一個
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.58,0:21:12.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦？怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.20,0:21:17.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莎雅的這裡都做水災了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.50,0:21:22.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裡面還一動一動的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.59,0:21:35.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都已經堅硬如鐵了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.54,0:21:39.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插入的時候到了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.41,0:21:41.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要、不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.58,0:21:43.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.40,0:21:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.22,0:21:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.83,0:22:05.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.76,0:22:09.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插得這麼深
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.08,0:22:17.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要~
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.58,0:22:22.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要說不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.36,0:22:24.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股也要動起來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.76,0:22:25.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.01,0:22:35.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要...要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.43,0:23:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍到好照片了，莎雅
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.95,0:23:06.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下來...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.48,0:23:09.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好戲現在才開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.04,0:23:31.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本來還期待妳化身成漂亮的蝴蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.82,0:23:33.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼愛的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.77,0:23:38.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過真可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.51,0:23:44.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然是隻青蟲啊\N真是低及生物呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.49,0:23:47.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,力量使不出來...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.67,0:23:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本來還想跟妳玩玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.92,0:23:54.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜘蛛大姐我現在肚子餓了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.71,0:23:57.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼，我就不客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.33,0:24:28.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,枉費我追的那麼辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.99,0:24:29.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼快就完蛋了？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.62,0:24:32.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐我還沒玩夠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.70,0:24:42.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是，反正也是可愛的小青蟲
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.27,0:24:47.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡面一定有漂亮的腹肌呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.55,0:24:56.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...是誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.98,0:25:04.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當局的聖天使
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.21,0:25:09.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使巴列特
