[Script Info]
Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Editing: 
Original Timing: 
Synch Point: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0
Last Style Storage: Default
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 9
Aegisub Active Line: 20

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF9300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,20,20,10,1


[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.52,0:00:52.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一二 一二...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.86,0:01:37.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麗奴 ～小夜子之章～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.15,0:02:10.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.12,0:02:12.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請放我回家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.10,0:02:19.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.30,0:02:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.38,0:02:38.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手!! 不要!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.65,0:02:41.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.77,0:02:45.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請你住手!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.19,0:02:53.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手...請你住手..
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.37,0:02:56.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請讓我回家..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.56,0:03:06.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.21,0:03:08.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請你住手..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.17,0:03:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.36,0:03:12.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.44,0:03:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,調教才剛剛開始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.76,0:03:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在起 我要慢慢揭開你的真面目
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.80,0:03:24.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.64,0:03:25.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.81,0:03:30.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揭發妳喜歡被男人強暴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.82,0:03:32.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,淫亂大小姐的本性
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.75,0:03:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不淫亂 我才不淫亂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.66,0:03:45.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣子嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.61,0:03:47.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好熱..
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.79,0:03:50.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好熱啊.. 為什麼?!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.46,0:04:10.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高橋理事長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.16,0:04:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼我能幫您的呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.50,0:04:16.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,犽子嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.53,0:04:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來的正好 攝影機給妳負責..
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.58,0:04:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 理事長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.09,0:04:24.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理事長..嗎...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.48,0:04:27.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這頭銜真好聽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.67,0:04:39.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳調配的春藥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.06,0:04:41.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,效果依然那麼好呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.39,0:04:45.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的誇獎是我的光榮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.23,0:04:47.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理事長
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.11,0:05:05.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前任理事長
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.35,0:05:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是這個年輕人的叔叔嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.33,0:05:14.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即然是他的推薦 那就沒辦汰了\N你看如何? 大老
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.07,0:05:18.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過你要知道..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.08,0:05:22.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這學校的老闆是我們
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.09,0:05:24.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你拿走理事長的權利
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.41,0:05:26.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就得履行自己的義務
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.76,0:05:34.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把女學生調教成女奴 獻給我們組織
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.60,0:05:37.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,期待你有好的表現 年輕人..
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.40,0:05:39.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.72,0:05:54.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把年輕的性奴隸 獻給當權者的網路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.23,0:05:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走著瞧 你們這些老頭子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.71,0:06:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要!! 不要拍啊!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.60,0:06:31.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,引誘少女們沉溺於性慾中
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.87,0:06:36.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是多麼愉快的一件事呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.84,0:06:39.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知世事的身體為我奉伺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.16,0:06:42.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,歡喜嬌喘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.75,0:06:47.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成就我的名聲 權勢地位
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.42,0:07:23.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是夢嗎..?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.45,0:07:25.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.86,0:07:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是夢就好了..
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.81,0:07:43.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.84,0:07:47.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天不繞那個十字路嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.05,0:07:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.60,0:07:51.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛過來時堵車很嚴重
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.60,0:07:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊!! 原來是這樣啊??
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.30,0:07:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能得稍微繞點遠路
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.09,0:07:57.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別在意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.31,0:07:59.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾走不同的路也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.25,0:08:01.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦?! 那個女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.97,0:08:04.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是我們學校的學生嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.46,0:08:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 起床了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.23,0:09:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 妳想做什麼?!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.81,0:09:03.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手 別對我的那裡..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.30,0:09:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要~~
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.05,0:09:20.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..不要!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.12,0:09:28.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,濕了...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:30.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭.. 那裡好熱..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.41,0:09:41.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好..好舒服!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.04,0:09:42.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我..
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.78,0:09:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生病了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.23,0:09:45.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是說...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.56,0:09:51.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要揭發妳的真面目
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.64,0:09:54.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揭露妳的本性
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.76,0:09:59.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的本性..?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.76,0:10:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是妳心底期盼的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.60,0:10:10.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我..那種事..
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.30,0:10:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種事..我不知道!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.70,0:10:15.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.08,0:10:16.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.98,0:10:20.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潛藏在妳深處的慾望
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.62,0:10:23.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我太清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.53,0:10:27.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被男人強暴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.16,0:10:30.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,淫亂哀叫的小夜子大小姐的模樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.71,0:10:34.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:41.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我..並不淫亂..才不淫亂呢!!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.98,0:10:59.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切感覺就像不久前發生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.92,0:11:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎唷..
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.49,0:11:04.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你好像很高興的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.37,0:11:05.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,議員先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.71,0:11:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下星期有小夜子的生日派對
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.50,0:11:13.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想在餐會後 播放幻燈片給大家看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.86,0:11:16.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.09,0:11:18.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子一定會不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.94,0:11:20.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.27,0:11:23.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她招待那麼多朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.43,0:11:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸你還是點到為止比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.87,0:11:27.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.87,0:11:28.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.53,0:11:33.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好令人懷念的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.93,0:11:36.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挑選時真的很難取捨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.20,0:11:39.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這孩子真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.41,0:11:41.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老是像個小孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.75,0:11:42.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.44,0:11:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子睡著了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.46,0:11:46.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯.. 早就睡著了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.35,0:11:48.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知在學校發生了什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.81,0:11:53.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總是看她很累的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.51,0:12:55.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隨時都可能有人經過
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.05,0:12:57.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我..卻做出這種丟人的事..
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.16,0:13:00.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好運用妳的嘴巴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.71,0:13:02.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不讓我高潮的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.48,0:13:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳就得這個模樣到校園散步哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.90,0:13:14.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃著老師的硬東西..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.58,0:13:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺變的好奇怪..
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.08,0:13:22.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服哦 小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.41,0:13:27.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變大了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.65,0:13:33.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.73,0:13:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全部吞下去!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.18,0:13:51.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做的很好 小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.91,0:14:21.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前幾天辛苦妳了 沒受傷吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.14,0:14:24.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的!!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.55,0:14:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,託妳的福
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.59,0:14:29.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才能得到小夜子的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.63,0:14:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天的調教就當是獎勵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.72,0:14:39.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝您
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.65,0:14:46.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽犽子說 妳是用身體收買小夜子的司機的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.45,0:14:49.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主人的那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.72,0:14:53.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比那個土包子好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.05,0:14:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳真的成長成好奴隸了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.33,0:15:08.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,(當然不是那樣 說真的...)
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.42,0:15:09.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.12,0:15:25.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主人..
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.94,0:15:28.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我高潮的樣子...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.05,0:15:29.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請仔細的看清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.97,0:15:43.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,關於前幾天在組織派對上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.22,0:15:45.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出道的鈴波 唯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.27,0:15:48.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目前的顧客
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.57,0:15:50.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對她的評價異常的好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.90,0:15:53.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然的了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.47,0:15:56.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是我親手調教的女奴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.06,0:16:02.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您這樣很像以女兒為傲的父親
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.73,0:16:07.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有個理論說 沒有愛是無法調教的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.04,0:16:09.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.37,0:16:11.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是用我的寵愛方式
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.61,0:16:38.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂..
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.03,0:16:39.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是三月小姐嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.91,0:16:42.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳母親還好嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.00,0:16:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎? 那太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.88,0:16:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,學生會假日還開會嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.68,0:16:50.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳太熱心了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.79,0:16:53.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是以當女政治家為目標呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 啊..祝賀的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.56,0:17:00.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟她本人講比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.70,0:17:01.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.97,0:17:05.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 什麼事? 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.92,0:17:10.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳的電話哦 謝謝爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.05,0:17:13.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三月嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.02,0:17:16.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎...還沒辦法來呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.88,0:17:19.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎? 就這麼說定了!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.30,0:17:22.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要來哦 拜託妳了 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.52,0:17:25.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子 稍微看一下這邊~
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.40,0:17:34.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討..討厭 爸爸真是的!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.38,0:17:40.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,祝妳生日快樂 恭喜你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.87,0:17:44.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊! 非常謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.20,0:17:46.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你了 小夜子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.31,0:17:47.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.65,0:17:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.25,0:17:52.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝大家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.00,0:17:59.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上流社會的大小姐跟淫亂的女奴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.43,0:18:03.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪一個才是真正的妳呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.42,0:18:31.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.65,0:18:32.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還拉不出來嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.52,0:18:39.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.90,0:18:41.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快點的話
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.30,0:18:43.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會被樓下的人發現哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.84,0:18:49.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.92,0:18:53.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼只有我遇到這種事..
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.20,0:19:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我.. 覺得自己快變成別人了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.25,0:19:05.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好不安
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.95,0:19:07.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.65,0:19:09.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這證明了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.26,0:19:12.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳體內被虐待狂的本性開始覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.92,0:19:13.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會..
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.90,0:19:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.80,0:19:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正的妳並不是什麼大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.24,0:19:22.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是天生的女奴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.18,0:19:24.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙人.. 你騙人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.44,0:19:25.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再誠實一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.59,0:19:29.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在越恥辱的情形下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.36,0:19:31.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越能激起妳的熱情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.99,0:19:34.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳以為我不曉得嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.35,0:19:42.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.60,0:19:48.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會.....尿出來的!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.60,0:19:54.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.70,0:19:58.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.70,0:20:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.20,0:20:39.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,突然把妳找出來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.77,0:20:43.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我告訴妳哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.51,0:20:48.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽說我們學校有女生被強迫賣春
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.56,0:20:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳知道嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.76,0:20:52.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不..不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.45,0:20:55.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 這只是普通的謠言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.95,0:20:57.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子妳是美人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.99,0:21:00.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別老是呆呆的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.00,0:21:01.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要小心點哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.10,0:21:04.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是 好友給妳的忠告哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.35,0:21:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過妳爸爸是議員
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.53,0:21:11.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家裡管得很嚴 應該沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.60,0:21:23.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是 你又在看小夜子生日派對的照片了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.71,0:21:25.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.07,0:21:27.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳看看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.70,0:21:31.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的 拍得可愛又漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.47,0:21:32.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.62,0:21:34.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是在我們呵護下長大的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.70,0:21:38.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子 妳是我的寶貝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.10,0:21:41.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的..老公你..
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.21,0:21:43.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是個標準的傻父親
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.29,0:21:46.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多了 時間也不早了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.14,0:21:48.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯? 已經到了這個時間了?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.42,0:21:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法 該去睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.28,0:21:57.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等小夜子要結婚時 你一定會很慘了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.29,0:22:00.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要! 我不會讓她嫁出去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.13,0:22:03.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真是自私的父親(哈)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.90,0:22:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.20,0:22:43.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我..不行了...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.55,0:22:48.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳的本性是淫亂的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.47,0:22:50.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對吧? 小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.76,0:22:52.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳經過我的調教
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.85,0:22:55.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經變成一個女奴了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.81,0:22:56.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.74,0:22:58.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是..的!!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.97,0:23:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感覺如何?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.04,0:23:32.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.55,0:23:36.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的.. 很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.60,0:23:41.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡很舒服呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.60,0:23:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的屁眼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.04,0:23:53.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的硬東西...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.83,0:23:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一直.. 進進出出..
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.00,0:24:00.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我的屁眼裡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.15,0:24:01.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這個無恥的娼妓..
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.78,0:24:04.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是一個大小姐該說的話哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.51,0:24:20.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說 妳是什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.15,0:24:24.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是主人的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.38,0:24:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.04,0:24:27.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是一個淫亂的女奴..
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.14,0:24:27.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的..
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.82,0:24:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是一個喜歡性愛的淫亂女奴
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.61,0:24:36.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說的真好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.37,0:24:37.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給妳獎勵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.25,0:24:40.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感謝您
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.06,0:25:04.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒..好棒..好棒...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.11,0:25:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在抽送著
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.08,0:25:08.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,主人的那根..!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.93,0:25:14.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多點.. 好棒!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.79,0:25:16.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.59,0:25:20.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳可以高潮..
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.78,0:25:30.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快..要高潮了..!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.99,0:25:44.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小夜子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.89,0:25:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳是最淫亂的女奴
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.76,0:25:50.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是..
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.92,0:25:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是主人的淫亂的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.15,0:25:58.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以後也請好好的寵愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.20,0:27:09.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只對我言聽計從的可愛女奴誕生了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.80,0:27:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,劇終
