Yes, the plan is slightly behind.
According to Mr. Nozaki,
we will be back on schedule.
I see.
Also, the usual group seems
to be tracking our movements.
Those guys...
You should know what to do.
Yes, we are being careful, as usual.
NEW TOKYO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
This is our next target.
Sasaki Kunio, 35.
With a Ph.D. in engineering,
he's teaching at an American college.
He is considered an expert
in nanomachine technology.
Wow, at such a young age!
I think he's my type!
Who requested this mission?
His co-worker, a professor.
She wants a child,
but doesn't care for marriage.
That's the story.
Everyone is different, I guess.
Mai.
As usual, Soda will give you the details.
That's it for now.
I expect excellence
out of all of my DNA Hunters.
The agent for this mission will be Mai.
About our plan, he's back in Japan.
Are you by yourself?
Yes, I am.
Would you like to have a drink with me?
It would be my pleasure.
That's great! Cheers!
Cheers!
Yes!
I never expected this to happen.
This is great, Mai.
I'm sensitive there!
Oh, and how about right here?
Yes!
You're so cute, Mai!
Now, it's your turn to make me feel good!
- You've made me so hard!
- Yes, you're really hard!
That feels great.
Mai...
...do you like the way I taste?
Yes, I love it!
- Do you like sucking cock?
- Yes.
Keep on sucking...
Oh, well, God damn it!
Sounds like she's having so much fun!
Oh, are you getting jealous, Masumi.
But the target was totally my type!
Yeah, but you know very well
we don't get to choose our targets.
So give up, already.
I should have started begging!
But Soda's really stubborn.
So it would have been a lost cause.
Can I help you?
Could I ask you a question?
Is everything all right, Masumi?
What are you doing here?
Yes!
Mai, you're so wet already!
Am I really?
Are you ready?
Oh, yes!
Then here I come!
Yeah, your pussy feels so good!
I love it!
You're so hard...
...and hot!
I'm going to cum.
Need to pull out!
Cum inside me!
Can I cum inside you?
Your...
...I want it.
I want it!
I'm happy, Mai.
I'm cumming!
Me too!
No, I...
...I'm...
...cumming!
That was very good!
Underground parking level.
- I'll drive you home, Mai.
- Oh, thank you.
Can I see you again?
What do you want?
Oh, Masumi!
Oh, Shiori!
What's going on?
Mr. Sasaki!
Are you OK?
Now, now.
Your troubles aren't over, sweetie.
I want you to tell me everything
about your boss and your operation.
I don't know what you're talking about!
Besides, who the hell are you guys?
You're not a very good liar, are you?
Ms. DNA Hunter Mai!
What?!
I know who you really are.
You whores fuck movie stars,
athletes, scientists, whoever.
What the...?
And you've just been conned
big time, mister!
This one is no ordinary girl.
She's a goddamned DNA Hunter.
She is on a mission to retrieve ejaculate
from her female clients' targets.
A fucking whore!
DNA Hunter...
Someone wanted to have your baby, mister!
You were this bitch's target.
You're not talking much.
Well, we'll make you talk, for sure.
We'll have our fun with the other two.
No!
This wouldn't have happened
if you were willing to talk!
They're drugged up with potent aphrodisiacs
so they should enjoy it!
Hey, Tegawa, Matsuoka, we'll show her
what we like to do to our bitches!
They should be starving
for some hard cock by now!
Suck on this, baby!
A DNA Hunter should be good at this!
I hope you don't mind if I join in!
I'll fuck her in the ass,
since that's the only hole left!
All right, here we go, yeah!
Ouch!
When did I ever tell you
to stop sucking, damn it?
Get back to it, bitch!
She's got a tight asshole!
Gives great blow jobs, too.
Shiori, I'm going to have some fun
with you!
We're going to play with this candle!
No, don't!
It's going to burn!
Here!
It feels good, huh?
Your nipples are getting hard!
You're a slut like the rest!
Here!
Now you're dripping wet!
You cheap whore!
Now, it's my turn for some serious fun!
My cock is called the "giant bazooka"
for a reason!
It might hurt some, baby!
You have a tight pussy!
Hey, this one's a pretty decent fuck!
What about you guys?
Oh, yeah, this one's happily sucking away
Too bad we have real work to do!
I'm about to cum!
I'm ready, too!
Oh, yeah!
I'm cumming inside ya!
Now that was a lot of fun!
We'll fuck more after we get some food.
Matsu, I hope you didn't
make the other girl too baggy.
God damn it! Of course not!
Next time,
I get to fuck the other girl, right?
You know what will happen
unless you tell me everything.
Well, at least you've got
some time to think about it.
Hey, Mai. Hey, Mai!
Mr. Sasaki!
I'm going to untie your rope!
How did you get free?
I was able to wiggle my way out of it.
Besides, they're gone for the moment!
It our only chance, hurry!
Yes!
Those men must be part of
the group that's following us.
Probably.
We'll refer this matter to security,
but how is everybody?
Shiori and Masumi are both
in the hospital just in case.
They'll be released in 2 or 3 days.
I thought Mai should have some time off.
She's having lunch with Sasaki.
Sasaki, huh?
Something up.
Yes, I think something's up with him.
- Kathleen?
- Yes.
I want you to do more research on Sasaki.
Right away, sir.
I'm sorry, Mr. Sasaki,
to get you involved in this mess!
Mai...
...it's all right.
Actually...
...I did some research.
I want you to take a look at this.
This is what your company is trying to do.
The Avalon Project?
- What is...?
- Take a look.
Avalon Project.
It's about breeding a superior race of man.
They're taking favorable genetic material
from men and women...
...to engineer and breed
the perfect human being.
They are planning to take over the world
with these engineered humans!
Mai, you're just being used!
And I also did some research
regarding your late fiancée.
He was not just a researcher.
He also recruited women
into becoming DNA Hunters.
No, you're lying!
I know you won't want to believe this.
He approached you to recruit you
into becoming a DNA Hunter!
Don't you think it's strange?
He probably didn't really die
right before your wedding.
You don't know for sure
what your company is really up to.
You're being...
Stop it!
Youji was not out to deceive me!
I don't believe a word you said!
Mai, are you going to keep working
for the people that lied to you?
I just want to help you out, Mai!
Oh, Youji!
Is what Mr. Sasaki said all true?
Did you really love me like you said?
Or were you just lying to me
to recruit me as a DNA Hunter?
I want you to find out the truth.
You should be able
to access the company computer.
The program in this disk will bypass
the privacy encryption system.
I really want to know
if this is the truth, too.
Mai, let's work together!
The program isn't working!
Kathleen!
What's the point of encryption
if it's so easily bypassed?
Mai, security has been tracking
your movements since yesterday.
We wanted you to know the truth...
...so Mr. Nozaki is here to explain everything.
Hi, Mai, nice to see you again!
Mr. Soda, is this Avalon Project
really happening?
Yes, it is.
This will be the next step for man.
That is the purpose of the Avalon Project.
I understand.
I really don't care about the Avalon Project!
But did Youji...
Was Youji just trying to recruit me
as a DNA Hunter?
Actually, he was not involved
in the Avalon Project at all.
He had no connection to us, either.
He was not aware of
the existence of DNA Hunters.
I want you to look at this.
You'll know we're not lying.
Kathleen.
Yes, take a look!
Oh, no!
After he met you,
he had a meeting with those men.
So Mr. Sasaki...
Yes, he's part of their big scheme.
He's involved with a group
that's been hounding us.
You were... No, we were tricked
with a false mission.
Now do you see?
I can't believe I'd suspect everyone,
even Youji, like this!
You really should have known
much better, Mai...
...that Youji was not that kind of person.
Yes.
Mai!
Thanks for coming!
You traitor!
You tricked me!
You're in with those three bastards!
And I believed you!
I can explain everything.
I really wanted to help...
You smart boys don't know
how to handle these situations!
You should have just believed the lies,
and you would have been OK!
You promised me you wouldn't hurt her!
Oh, boy, you can just butt
your smart head out.
Don't worry, I'm not going to kill her.
What do you want with me?
We'll have some fun until you decide to join us.
No!
Put this woman inside the car!
You're finally awake!
What do you want?
Like I said, we're gonna have some fun!
- She's got nice, firm tits!
- No!
Let's see if I can get a good taste!
Ouch, ouch, don't be so rough, please!
Ouch!
No!
Let's see the lower lips!
Don't move so much!
Otherwise you might get hurt!
Let's check this out!
Jackpot!
Let's see!
Ooh, it's a nice pink salmon color too!
No, please don't!
I'll join!
You're way too big, I can't!
Shut up and just do it!
Oh, that feels good!
She's really good!
Her precious nipples
are starting to get hard!
She's soaking wet down here, too!
She's really horny. Let's see
if I can find her G-spot now, eh guys?
Sometimes they squirt when
you stimulate them right here!
Let's see!
No, don't!
Me, too!
I can't take any more!
- She came hard!
- That was a neat show!
- We're not done!
- That's right!
No!
I'll take the pussy, then!
I'll have her blow me!
No, please, no more,
I can't take any more, please!
Come on, slide onto this cock, baby!
It's huge!
I'm going to fuck you in the ass!
Please, don't, I can't take any more!
And now you'll be air tight, here!
You guys like gangbanging this whore?
Yeah!
We do this kind of shit
better than anyone else out there!
Cumming!
Matsu, me, too!
Yeah, me, too!
I'm cumming!
Mai!
- Mai!
- Mr. Sasaki!
Hurry, get out of here!
Another one of your tricks?
I know you're not going to believe me.
I'm not lying.
They're all unconscious right now.
Two of them are lying in the hallway.
Why are you helping me?
To make some amends.
I should have never used you like that!
I'm really sorry!
There's a car outside.
The key's in the ignition.
Where are you going?
I'll leave when I'm done here.
They'll hunt me down, probably, but...
...I wish I had met you earlier.
- Goodbye, Mai.
- Goodbye.
Kathleen.
So it looks like we'll lie low for a while.
Yeah...
We'll keep a low profile
until we get a handle on that group.
Where are the others?
They're enjoying the beach.
The beach, the sun, the tropics!
Now it would be perfect
if I was with a cute guy!
Hey, Shiori!
Where's Mai?
She's out for a walk.
Oh, Youji...
...we're all here resting
and enjoying the tropics.
A lot happened,
and we're all on vacation for a while.
But please, watch me from heaven!
I'll work really hard until I have our baby.
The End