[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 970
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,42,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00000000,&H80323232,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,20,54,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.05,0:00:48.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏要喝酒嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.25,0:00:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那給我一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.75,0:00:51.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別那麼亂來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.30,0:00:53.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢才 湊近些不好嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.70,0:00:55.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妮麗特 會醉的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.40,0:00:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.62,0:00:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真痛快 我很久沒喝酒了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.10,0:01:00.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不夠啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.35,0:01:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶他們來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.60,0:01:03.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你渴望的討伐隊成員
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.11,0:01:05.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要讓他們加入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.86,0:01:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從左邊起的是卡力班
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.44,0:01:10.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那曼沙 山達斯 還有...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.78,0:01:14.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍者隊的賽依菈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.70,0:01:16.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她最自豪的是 她雙腿的驚人速度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.80,0:01:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且又柔軟 又修長
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.10,0:01:20.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是雙美腿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.78,0:01:21.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.39,0:01:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過性格有點問題
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.80,0:01:26.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要優秀就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.39,0:01:41.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MAP2『PRINCESS』
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.33,0:02:02.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我見這部隊的隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.34,0:02:15.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫碧安卡 是隆波尼王國的騎士
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.75,0:02:19.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我算不上什麼隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.18,0:02:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都是平起平坐的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.85,0:02:22.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是城堡裡的公主
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.69,0:02:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說這部隊是唯一能擊退路西佛軍的部隊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.94,0:02:28.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且現正打算繼續向東方進軍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.35,0:02:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的話 \N 請讓我加入你們
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.53,0:02:34.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們當然非常歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.28,0:02:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起戰鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.95,0:02:38.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請妳盡情發揮妳的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.87,0:02:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用測試一下我的實力嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.92,0:02:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是用劍或槍的話\N我有自信不輸給任何人的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.85,0:02:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果說我傷害了妳的自尊心的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.45,0:02:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我願意道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.20,0:02:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對於現在的我們來說 \N 不管是誰都很歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.63,0:02:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確 而且你們相當欠缺人才
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.15,0:03:02.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這麼說嘛 在這裡的各位夥伴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.40,0:03:06.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是為了要打倒路西佛而攜手戰鬥的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.65,0:03:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打倒路西佛!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.40,0:03:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天一早便要出發了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.57,0:03:17.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 今晚就先來喝一杯吧  碧安卡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.76,0:03:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道妳是來追我的?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.35,0:03:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 我...我只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.68,0:03:46.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想成為像媽媽那樣的魔導士
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.94,0:03:48.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而出來修練的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.77,0:03:50.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是來追你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.94,0:03:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳媽媽嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.45,0:04:00.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是大家已經都...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.03,0:04:02.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧 只要我們打倒路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.70,0:04:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也會回復原形的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.79,0:04:08.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也對 只要打倒路西佛的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.04,0:04:12.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.96,0:04:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你的護身符 你還帶著嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.71,0:04:16.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.55,0:04:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看\N 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.72,0:04:21.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.06,0:04:26.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 其實你早就弄丟了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.39,0:04:29.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是我送給你的護身符...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.07,0:04:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了 有了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.99,0:04:40.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 原本是戴在脖子上的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.82,0:04:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不知什麼時候 掉進褲子裡去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.91,0:04:45.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.41,0:04:46.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.66,0:04:48.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 我已經看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.91,0:04:51.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?有點臭吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.34,0:04:54.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙妳的 騙妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.92,0:04:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其實一開始便戴著它了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.92,0:05:01.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾從以前便老是這樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.59,0:05:02.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.59,0:05:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是這樣捉弄我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.68,0:05:06.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.60,0:05:10.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正正經經跟你說話 你卻捉弄我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.27,0:05:12.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是做些令我討厭的事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.85,0:05:14.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.52,0:05:16.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也該成熟一點啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.36,0:05:18.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使劍術多好 也還是令人討厭的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.28,0:05:24.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特很成熟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.62,0:05:27.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼突然提起埃特啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.80,0:05:29.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏喜歡埃特吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.87,0:05:33.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為...為什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.13,0:05:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.80,0:05:39.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了 卡凱爾你走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.48,0:06:05.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.32,0:06:06.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.16,0:06:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 你一直在看著的嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.50,0:06:18.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 你和卡凱爾吵架了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.01,0:06:21.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.84,0:06:23.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼卡凱爾總是那樣子的?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.84,0:06:31.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...\N我想卡凱爾只是關心娜塔夏而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.02,0:06:35.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是卡凱爾像個小孩子一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.94,0:06:38.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那是我送給他的護身符啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.86,0:06:43.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是騙妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.20,0:06:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是不甘心老實告訴妳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.70,0:06:49.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實他很珍惜那個護身符而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.53,0:06:50.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.95,0:06:54.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是怕妳知道而故意那樣說的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.29,0:06:56.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.54,0:07:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 埃特一直在偷聽的吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.13,0:07:03.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.40,0:07:06.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.12,0:07:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和卡凱爾每次說話都是以吵架收場的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.56,0:07:14.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾現在也一定是這樣想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.48,0:07:18.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後悔剛才不應該用那種態度對妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.81,0:07:21.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可沒有後悔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.65,0:07:24.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?妳看來很沮喪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.49,0:07:29.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是沮喪 只是生氣罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.99,0:07:31.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人都不夠坦白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.41,0:07:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.75,0:07:35.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳不是在想為何每次見到卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.66,0:07:37.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是那麼令人氣憤嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.67,0:07:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有生氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.09,0:07:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為妳這樣固執才會吵架的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.42,0:07:45.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說得好像很明白似的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.59,0:07:49.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.60,0:07:51.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.01,0:07:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然變得好像在跟卡凱爾說話一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.27,0:07:56.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.44,0:08:00.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去睡了 晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.62,0:08:18.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們追的是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.04,0:08:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那雙又漂亮又修長的腿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.56,0:08:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.49,0:08:54.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法隊 預備
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.67,0:09:05.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不行 多等一會兒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.84,0:09:08.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法隊 開始攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.86,0:09:25.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 碧安卡 別亂來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.78,0:09:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 還不可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.53,0:09:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 去阻止娜塔夏她們
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.12,0:09:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真亂來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.04,0:09:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騎士隊 步兵隊 突擊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏 快停止啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.71,0:09:49.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妮麗特 快停止魔法攻擊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.38,0:09:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那曼沙 不行啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.80,0:09:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧安卡也在裡面啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.06,0:09:58.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧安卡 小心!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.42,0:10:35.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力拉 一 二 三
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.10,0:10:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.35,0:10:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 我來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:52.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳 妮布瓊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.11,0:10:56.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妮布瓊!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.33,0:11:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要龍騎士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.83,0:11:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再忍耐一會兒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.00,0:11:54.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要說服我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.84,0:11:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我在便能封印路西佛的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.53,0:12:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就在這條何畢特村過夜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.29,0:12:30.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.55,0:12:41.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是隊長嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.14,0:12:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是工兵隊的成員嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.72,0:12:48.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也帶我們一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.64,0:12:50.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以幫得上忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.40,0:12:51.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.49,0:13:03.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝魯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.08,0:13:07.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.59,0:13:15.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.75,0:13:16.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.67,0:13:21.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.68,0:13:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是幽會的話 現在似乎...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.93,0:13:26.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你認為沒必要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.93,0:13:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也希望了解你的實力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.93,0:13:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在剛才的戰鬥中 妳還不清楚嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.60,0:13:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想直接和你交手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.27,0:13:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你也不會了解我的實力的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.61,0:13:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚妳的實力 所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.12,0:13:49.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想由你雙手來確認
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.29,0:13:50.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那個必要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.12,0:13:52.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當我是傻瓜嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.79,0:13:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我只是受夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.63,0:14:01.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳究竟想怎樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.88,0:14:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論如何我也要你拔劍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.47,0:14:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只會尊敬強壯的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.31,0:14:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經受夠了城裡那些只會
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.56,0:14:14.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空口說白話的懦弱傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.31,0:14:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是說我也是一樣嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.31,0:14:18.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個...馬上就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.16,0:14:24.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧安卡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.76,0:14:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是憑劍術來衡量男人力量的嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.99,0:14:31.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外還有其他方法嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.16,0:14:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還太稚嫩了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.92,0:14:38.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人的力量並不是那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.09,0:14:40.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 你說是什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.27,0:15:01.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼輕易的...就將我...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.94,0:15:03.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 夠了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.70,0:15:05.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.20,0:15:09.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多少次結果也是一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.70,0:15:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怕輸給我嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.20,0:15:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輸贏也好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.04,0:15:15.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的敵人究竟是誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.37,0:15:18.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在幹這種事的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.54,0:15:21.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛的軍隊又增強勢力了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.05,0:15:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在要做的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.47,0:15:27.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是該爭取休息時間盡快出發嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.72,0:15:29.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若不能令我信服的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.55,0:15:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不會善罷甘休的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.24,0:15:52.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了令妳別再做壞事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.24,0:15:55.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要教訓一下妳這個任性的公主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.75,0:16:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要幹什麼?無禮的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.26,0:16:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開我!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.27,0:16:17.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.44,0:16:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道觸碰我的身體結果會怎樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.69,0:16:28.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣 快點住手...我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.53,0:16:33.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 碧安卡公主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主 妳贏不了我的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.88,0:16:44.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是那種為了自己的尊嚴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.46,0:16:46.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便什麼事也會幹的女人嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.99,0:17:18.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是為了滿足妳的自尊心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.66,0:17:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而踏上這個旅程的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.34,0:17:33.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只在乎 個人尊嚴的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.18,0:17:36.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對我們來說只是個累贅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.76,0:17:38.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒這個空間
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.11,0:17:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的部隊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.11,0:17:50.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要這種任性的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.28,0:17:57.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要的是能夠同甘共苦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.62,0:18:00.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以打倒路西佛為目標的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.82,0:18:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 你的眼睛...看起來很悲傷
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.43,0:18:58.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...有個重要的人...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.60,0:19:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不能輸給路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.35,0:19:04.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 碧安卡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.10,0:19:06.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也需要妳的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.86,0:19:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.12,0:19:19.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有十二箱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.95,0:19:22.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起錨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.71,0:19:26.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.80,0:19:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.60,0:20:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒睡嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.69,0:20:33.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都睡著了吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.86,0:20:37.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要說服我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.11,0:20:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想再多補充一些箭矢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.28,0:20:45.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到了下個城鎮再想辦法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.38,0:20:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.90,0:21:17.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳見到路西佛後打算怎樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.57,0:21:19.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然是為同伴報仇
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.90,0:21:20.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.91,0:21:26.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳不是想妨礙我們打倒那傢伙嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.33,0:21:33.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼...你知道那種事...?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.17,0:21:34.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放棄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.75,0:21:37.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳一定會後悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.26,0:21:44.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎知道這件事的?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.60,0:21:47.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是妳自己這樣跟我說的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.60,0:21:50.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不記得我曾經跟你說過
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.77,0:21:54.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也對 是未來的妳說的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.27,0:21:56.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 我不明白你在說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.27,0:21:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳現在是不會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.44,0:22:05.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在說另一個歷史裡的未來...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.28,0:22:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未來的我...?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.55,0:22:21.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳說過妳出身於特利安的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.38,0:22:22.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是假的吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.22,0:22:27.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為妳是從很遠的地方來的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.81,0:22:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 我也是從很遠的地方來的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.81,0:22:36.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 應該說"回來"比較正確吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.82,0:22:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說是未來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.82,0:22:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未來的妳給了我一顆黑色的魔石
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.32,0:22:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才能回到這個時代
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.66,0:22:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑色的魔石?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.42,0:22:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳知道那顆石頭的 以及它的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.01,0:23:03.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮 我是卡凱爾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.01,0:23:11.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...那種事...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.52,0:23:12.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾是卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.60,0:23:16.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在是重返過去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.02,0:23:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難以置信嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.69,0:23:24.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我告訴妳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.20,0:23:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這艘船快要沉沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.12,0:23:38.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉沒?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.31,0:23:52.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.64,0:24:01.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趕快...不行了...快逃!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.49,0:24:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 瑪爾蕾妮  不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.50,0:24:18.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.68,0:24:35.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發射!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.69,0:24:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船長 船能撐下去嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.61,0:24:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 要沉了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.36,0:24:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船要沉了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.61,0:24:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的船啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.78,0:24:52.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 船首已經開始下沉了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.87,0:24:56.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎...怎麼辦?我不會游泳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.12,0:24:57.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想死的話 只有跳海了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.97,0:25:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.48,0:25:19.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.23,0:25:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.32,0:25:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.58,0:25:39.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要沉沒了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.00,0:25:42.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.92,0:25:45.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今後要怎麼辦?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.17,0:25:47.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先最重要的是別死了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.92,0:25:49.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有話稍後再說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.17,0:25:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.72,0:29:22.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該怎樣做才能打開瑪爾蕾妮的心?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.05,0:29:25.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與我心中的焦急相反
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.64,0:29:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰鬥越趨激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.72,0:29:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伴們相繼倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.23,0:29:31.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越接近萊姆林王國
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.23,0:29:34.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便越多路西佛的強力部隊阻礙我們
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.07,0:29:37.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是夥伴們的真正力量
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.90,0:29:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於都覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.57,0:29:41.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回 龍騎士IV
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.91,0:29:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MAP3
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.07,0:29:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,『DESTINY』
