[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 970
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,42,&H00ffffff,&H000000ff,&H00000000,&H80323232,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,20,20,54,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.72,0:00:53.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳沒必要在這裡 陪我們一起死啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.98,0:00:55.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.56,0:00:57.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳死了的話 便見不到路西佛的了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.74,0:01:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.75,0:01:22.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.09,0:01:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多死傷者了 怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.51,0:01:27.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特! 衝上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.26,0:01:30.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在這裡只會任人宰割而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.10,0:01:37.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他們全部趕盡殺絕!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.35,0:01:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人可以留給自己享用
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.95,0:01:49.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是謝魯!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.87,0:01:59.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好機會! 一舉攻上去吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.97,0:02:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 去吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.31,0:02:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.70,0:03:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們前進了不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.37,0:03:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們至少要三天 才能追得上我們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.37,0:03:24.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.63,0:03:27.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 我求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.46,0:03:30.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你別跟路西佛戰鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.22,0:03:32.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何這麼說？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.89,0:03:38.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不跟他戰鬥...那幹什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.47,0:03:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家...你 卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.56,0:03:45.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有娜塔夏...也會死的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.81,0:03:50.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳該明白我們沒選擇餘地的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.49,0:03:55.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有個姐姐還留在魔界
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.57,0:03:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我姐姐以犧牲自己
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.58,0:04:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來換取爸爸對路西佛的信任
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.08,0:04:04.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她寧願被詛咒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.58,0:04:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從子宮內取出一顆黑石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.50,0:04:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳姐姐...喜歡路西佛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.34,0:04:18.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果爸爸批准他們二人來往
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.43,0:04:20.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸是魔界之王
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.93,0:04:23.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說的話沒有人敢違抗的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.69,0:04:27.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳為了追尋路西佛而來到這世界
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.04,0:04:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是真心喜歡路西佛的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.54,0:04:53.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...愛路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.97,0:04:58.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為何妳叫我別跟路西佛戰鬥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.14,0:05:03.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何在船上保護我別受龍的攻擊？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.73,0:05:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果妳是愛路西佛的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.56,0:05:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我死了不是更好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.81,0:05:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮 妳其實並不愛路西佛的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.49,0:05:17.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒...那回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.24,0:05:23.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳那份感情...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.41,0:05:25.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是出於對姐姐的競爭心
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.66,0:05:28.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是純粹仰慕而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.58,0:05:31.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以妳才覺得自己無路可退
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.42,0:05:35.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再說了!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.18,0:05:41.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再說了 求求你...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.27,0:05:45.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是自由的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.68,0:05:49.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳去路西佛那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.35,0:05:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在這裡分手比較好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.11,0:05:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等...等等...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.53,0:06:05.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別走啊 埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.29,0:06:06.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了我 請你別離開
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.29,0:06:13.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.80,0:06:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.89,0:06:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早已察覺到自己的感情了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.56,0:06:28.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 我是魔王的女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.06,0:06:32.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你又是擁有神族血統的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.56,0:06:35.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使告訴你...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.82,0:06:39.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.90,0:06:45.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我實在不想承認自己的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.77,0:07:17.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好溫暖
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再令妳受苦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.03,0:07:28.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 即使將來會發生什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.62,0:07:32.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的我...卻是非常幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.37,0:07:35.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是夢的話...如果是夢的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.13,0:07:36.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的不願意醒來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.88,0:07:38.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮\N埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.25,0:08:15.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.92,0:08:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 進入我的體內吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.26,0:08:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別動
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.85,0:08:37.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫時不要動 我想感受一下你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.28,0:08:47.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 即使是謊話也好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.03,0:08:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你說喜歡我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.70,0:08:52.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡妳 瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.37,0:08:56.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果時間能停留在這一刻便好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.81,0:09:21.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...不要忘記我...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.40,0:09:25.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕對...不會忘記妳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.07,0:09:26.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.26,0:09:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 就這樣子...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.19,0:10:06.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.45,0:10:11.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再...再這樣子一會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.83,0:11:01.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:21.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.85,0:11:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事嗎？埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.69,0:11:27.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.28,0:11:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生還的...就只有你們嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.21,0:11:44.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.21,0:11:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過...前進吧! 去打倒路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.05,0:11:51.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 瑪爾蕾妮呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.55,0:11:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她稍後會追上來的 一定會
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.41,0:12:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡就是萊姆林城
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.75,0:12:22.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛就在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.16,0:12:26.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯 為了化成石頭的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.08,0:12:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有我們死去了的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.17,0:12:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 去吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.02,0:12:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝魯 你不覺得害怕嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.94,0:12:54.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要打倒路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.45,0:12:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸便能回復原狀了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.61,0:12:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要這麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.95,0:12:59.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便不會再心驚膽顫了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.13,0:13:11.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎你 卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.21,0:13:14.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪...哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.47,0:13:17.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是路西佛的聲音...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.47,0:13:19.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真卑鄙 現身吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.81,0:13:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別想要嚇唬我們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.81,0:13:24.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滾出來吧! 路西佛!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.23,0:13:28.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們帶給我不少樂趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.40,0:13:31.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到就這樣結束 實在很可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.40,0:13:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 現身吧!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.58,0:13:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些廢物就是卡凱爾的同伴嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.50,0:13:55.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是廢物 要打過才知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.42,0:14:02.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？不如你直接問問他們本人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.76,0:14:04.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟有多沒用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.18,0:14:07.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.77,0:14:13.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體...無法動彈...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.94,0:14:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾...就像變成石頭一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.36,0:14:19.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝...謝魯 救我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.20,0:14:21.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法動彈...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.87,0:14:23.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劍...拿不起劍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.03,0:14:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡...卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.62,0:14:29.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身體...也無法動彈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.04,0:14:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.96,0:14:35.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅伊菲雅 卡隆 娜塔夏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.96,0:14:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧安卡 埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.38,0:14:40.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 你對他們幹了什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.64,0:14:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.97,0:14:50.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 好戲還在後頭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.41,0:15:02.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救...救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.07,0:15:06.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡...卡凱爾 瑪爾蕾妮...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.83,0:15:07.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.91,0:15:14.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡...卡凱爾 連口...也...動不了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.08,0:15:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏!\N希玲尼...對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.42,0:15:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣？卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.26,0:15:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的同伴果然是廢物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.60,0:15:25.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜牲!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.36,0:15:37.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.20,0:15:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,束縛鬆開了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.21,0:15:52.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃\N瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.62,0:15:58.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 為何妳會來這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.13,0:16:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛 請你別殺他們
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.97,0:16:06.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃...是指瑪爾蕾妮...嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.97,0:16:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 路西佛\N瑪...瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.31,0:16:12.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何妳會認識路西佛的？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.64,0:16:16.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 妳是怎樣來到這世界的？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.40,0:16:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是用爸爸的黑石...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.15,0:16:26.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？妳是來找我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.74,0:16:34.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛\N好吧 伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.25,0:16:37.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我也該多關心妳一些的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.00,0:16:41.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 別再用什麼魔法陣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.01,0:16:46.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.01,0:16:49.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪...瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.18,0:16:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.68,0:16:55.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這女人不是叫什麼瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.44,0:16:58.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是魔界的支配者的女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.52,0:16:59.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.36,0:17:01.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.03,0:17:09.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛 求求你 請你回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.87,0:17:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去姐姐等著你的魔界
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.87,0:17:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 妳不是要站在人類那邊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.37,0:17:20.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.29,0:17:23.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.80,0:17:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.63,0:17:32.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳真可愛 伊娃 來我這邊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.64,0:17:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮 別過去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.64,0:17:41.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？妳是渴望得到我的愛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.32,0:17:43.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才來這個世界的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.32,0:17:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...根本不愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.57,0:17:52.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我...也無法愛上你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.08,0:17:58.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...愛的是埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.00,0:17:59.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.25,0:18:04.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.67,0:18:09.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 是人類嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.51,0:18:11.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃是魔族的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.76,0:18:14.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼能愛上人類呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.77,0:18:20.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛 你是永遠...不會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.27,0:18:23.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使來生也好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.36,0:18:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無聊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.44,0:18:29.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 伊娃 快過來我這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.11,0:18:32.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.20,0:18:36.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在清楚明白到自己所犯的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.12,0:18:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 米那克斯大人也會很傷心的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.38,0:18:48.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳姐姐瑪奴的詛咒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.05,0:18:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是永遠無法解除的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.80,0:18:54.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還叫我用石頭回去魔界!？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.15,0:19:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.82,0:19:09.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要殺你們簡直不費吹灰之力
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.82,0:19:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是為了埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.74,0:19:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算死我也不怕!\N住口!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.33,0:19:21.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去肉體的亡靈僕人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.50,0:19:24.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,替我收拾這些廢物 一概不留!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.42,0:19:29.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 這是最終一戰了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.26,0:19:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要打倒那傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.59,0:19:32.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和平也便重臨大地!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.26,0:19:34.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去了 娜塔夏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.18,0:19:36.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.85,0:19:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風神劍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.77,0:19:45.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.45,0:19:53.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎會的？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.03,0:19:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的想激怒我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.87,0:20:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.88,0:20:13.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想過很多種方法去招呼卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.72,0:20:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這個傷痕...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.39,0:20:18.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就以你的身體來回報吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.97,0:20:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.64,0:20:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.06,0:20:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡情地
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.01,0:21:01.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...你好卑鄙 路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.77,0:21:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外一個藏起來的也出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.61,0:21:13.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.44,0:21:15.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.28,0:21:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開瑪爾蕾妮 路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.95,0:21:22.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊娃 妳也很會愚弄他們呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.20,0:21:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有...愚弄他們
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.29,0:21:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡只有魔界的人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.54,0:21:30.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和擁有神族的血統的人才能進來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.88,0:21:36.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是何方神族聖？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.47,0:21:40.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路西佛 看來你也有不懂的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.56,0:21:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底...是誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.24,0:22:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...你...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.49,0:22:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混帳!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.66,0:22:06.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危險!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.76,0:22:20.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好機會啊 卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.10,0:22:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死期到了 路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.35,0:22:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可...可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.78,0:22:41.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒可能的...我...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.47,0:23:04.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.51,0:23:40.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特\N埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.51,0:23:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 埃特 你們成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.51,0:23:44.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.51,0:23:46.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傷勢沒大礙吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.10,0:23:50.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣爺爺便能回復原狀了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.44,0:24:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.37,0:24:13.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 埃特 帶我...一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.12,0:24:17.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特! 你要去哪裡嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.80,0:24:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.72,0:24:28.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你堅強了很多呢 卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.97,0:24:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功打敗了路西佛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.06,0:24:33.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全靠埃特啊 因為有埃特在
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.98,0:24:36.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才能一直戰鬥到底的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.31,0:24:38.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特 你到底要去哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.32,0:24:40.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要一起去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.57,0:24:44.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.49,0:24:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 我們要在這裡分別了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.33,0:24:55.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.08,0:24:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我長得很像你爸爸嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.34,0:25:02.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像爸爸年輕時的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.59,0:25:05.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是為什麼...？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.18,0:25:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N不要 別說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.85,0:25:21.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是...卡凱爾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.36,0:25:25.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是埃特吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.70,0:25:30.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 時間不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.87,0:25:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾...的身體...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.04,0:25:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著 你要守衛這個世界
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.96,0:25:40.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以讓它落入魔族的手中
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.71,0:25:43.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 你到底想去哪裡啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.96,0:25:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要一起去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.55,0:25:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去屬於我的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.89,0:25:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡凱爾 你要對娜塔夏好一點啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.56,0:25:57.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 到底是怎麼一回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.89,0:25:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝魯
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.48,0:26:01.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今後你也要多多照顧卡凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.90,0:26:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特是卡凱爾...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.07,0:26:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏知道一切的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.41,0:26:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見了 卡隆
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.91,0:26:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 埃特 可以...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.74,0:26:17.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做我的...駙馬...嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.25,0:26:20.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧安卡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.92,0:26:24.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳要成為一個出色的公主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.59,0:26:25.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.42,0:26:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅伊菲雅
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.92,0:26:29.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克拉莉絲一定會平安無事的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.43,0:26:33.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個一起回去多利亞村吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.60,0:26:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本來想叫埃特...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.43,0:26:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起回去特利安村的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.11,0:26:45.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔夏 卡凱爾拜託妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.28,0:26:48.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會忘記你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.28,0:26:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也絕對不會忘記妳
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.62,0:26:55.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 保重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.29,0:27:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠認識你們 實在太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.21,0:27:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.22,0:27:12.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.05,0:27:17.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別走 求求你...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.48,0:27:20.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要留下我孤伶伶一個人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.06,0:27:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪爾蕾妮...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.91,0:27:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永別了 瑪爾蕾妮
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.59,0:27:49.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃特...
