优良和我是在相亲的时候认识的
虽然发生过很多千奇百怪的事
但我们还是结婚了
It's like our love life started
after we got married.
Yura was more amazing than I thought.
I never thought
I could marry a girl like her.
Yura wasn't just a cute girl after all.
She's very honest and kind.
And she liked me for the person I was.
I was a 25-year-old virgin.
She was also a 25-year-old virgin.
But we got married anyway.
How do I explain this?
Feelings I never had before...
Yura and I are together.
But I had a little problem...
STEP UP LO VE STORY
Lesson 2 - Kiss, Kiss, Kiss
Makoto... Makoto...
Yura...
Sorry, I climaxed too fast again.
Don't worry, it felt good.
But you're not there yet, right?
Not there?
Climax, I guess?
I don't know what that feels like.
But it felt good, so maybe I climaxed.
No, you still haven't
experienced real pleasure.
Let's try again tomorrow, okay?
It's not like that...
Aren't you feeling a bit frustrated?
What?
If you're not satisfied, then I'll
make you feel good by licking...
No, it's okay.
I can't believe you said that, Makoto.
Sorry...
Makoto Onoda / Yura Onoda
I'm sorry.
I should've woke up earlier.
Nevermind that. Tonight we should...
What?
I can't believe you're talking
about tonight already...
What?
No, it's not like that.
We're going to have
dinner with my folks.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Now, we're talking about my parents, so
you don't have to worry about anything.
Should we meet at the station
instead of my house?
No...
I'll get there before you
and help them out.
I have to meet a friend of mine
who's here from Osaka.
I'll see you later!
Bye!
What was I thinking?
Maybe it's because
I have no experience.
I would like to introduce
the new member of our team.
I'm Kikuchi.
She's definitely my type!
I'm gonna get her before you!
Huh?
I may have seen her before.
What?
Yes, this is Onoda.
Hello?
Sis?
Oh, it's you, Rika.
What's wrong?
Nothing. What were you doing?
Laundry. Being a wife
isn't easy, you know.
I see.
You're having the time of
your life right now, right?
Not just now. Now and forever...
Rika, where are you calling from?
Does it matter?
Hello?
Are you feeling ill?
I feel fine.
But you sound funny...
Anyway, from what you said before,
it seems like things aren't going...
...well for you right now.
What are you saying?
We're very happy.
No, I mean in bed...
In bed?
Rika, what are you doing right now?
You see, sis...
You can't just keep on
getting it from him...
You have to be more aggressive.
Men need to be educated by women...
Really?
That's right. Men are like that...
Why are you talking
about things like this?
It's still too early...
Good luck!
What?
It stinks.
You should wash it. You're not
being nice to your girlfriend.
I'm sorry. Let's do it again. Please?
Nope.
This is delicious.
Great.
Oh no! Today is...
Coffee room
Good morning!
Hello, Sugiyama.
I haven't given up on you.
Onoda.
But I'm...
I...
Don't I know you from somewhere?
I guess you forgot about me.
What?
Kikuchi... Kikuchi...
Can you meet me after work?
What?
What's going on?
Are you working hard, Makoto?
I'm going to town
for the first time in a while.
Being a housewife is tough,
but I'll do my best!
Yura...
Hey Onoda, you have a visitor
at the front desk.
A guest?
Umm, I'm Onoda...
I'm Kawada. Do you have some time?
Yeah...
What are you doing here?
Is this a non-smoking area?
Yeah.
Damn.
Rika, this place isn't a school. You
can't just come here whenever you want.
You know...
I warned you, didn't I?
Warned me?
If you make my older sister
unhappy, I'll kill you!
You think that I'm not making her happy?
She seems happy in the daytime.
Daytime? What about during the night?
Aren't you making her feel frustrated?
I don't think so!
Probably...
Hope...
Aren't you ending it after you climax?
What are you talking about, Rika?
You just want to
stick it inside her, right?
Wait a minute! That's not true!
I do foreplay...
You're just touching her
boobs and cunt, right?
But isn't that...
Great.
I feel sorry for her!
What you said was inexcusable.
What's the best foreplay
to make a girl feel good?
What?
A kiss?
Of course.
We do it all the time.
A long lovely kiss.
Long doesn't mean it's good.
Then what do you suggest is good?
Slipping in your tongue from the
very beginning is just outrageous.
You simply get close, but no touching.
You enjoy it without touching the tongue.
It's also nice to
bite the lips very gently.
You trace over the lips gently with your
tongue and then stretch out your tongue...
...and lick the back of her front teeth.
And this can be felt to the
very bones of her body...
You can't be rough.
But it might be nice to suck
on her tongue once in a while.
I want you to leave! I'm still working!
I'm glad I was able to kill some time.
Now I have a date with
boyfriend number 4.
Thanks for the drink!
Bye bye!
What's going on with me today?
Let's see, Yu... Yu... Yu... Yu...
Damn! I can't type if it's this small!
Yura...
I'm working very hard...
Damn it! I have to reply to her fast!
Another mail?
Please come to the tearoom
on the other side at 6.
Miyuki Kikuchi?
What the hell? We've only
just met today, you know!
Miyuki...
Miyuki Kikuchi...
Riko, long time no see.
Both you and Hiromi
haven't changed a bit.
But Yura changed. She got married.
Yeah.
That's right. Sorry I couldn't
attend the ceremony.
It's okay. You're very busy
over there, Riko.
You're lucky to have a husband who's the
same age. My husband is really old now.
You're right, my husband
is a bit older than me too.
Can he get it up?
If he tries hard.
What about yours?
Umm...
You know those pills that help get it up?
Oh, how are they?
I...
Miyuki Kikuchi...
Miyuki
That's wrong. A relative
pronoun is used in this tense.
Wait a minute.
This is past tense. Got it?
What?
Do you get it?
Hey.
You had it right for those parts.
So that was the
middle schooler Miyuki...
She got beautiful.
But she hated me, right?
She never really talked to me...
That's right.
She's the reason why I couldn't
deal with girls that well...
But if I do it with my mouth,
he really likes it.
Yeah, we do it too.
What do you mean with the mouth?
Not just with the mouth.
I did some research by watching adult
videos.
Onoda
We did that too, you know.
Is it natural to do it with your mouth?
What?
You've never done it before?
No way...
Excuse me. I'm Onoda.
I'm in room 708 of this hotel
But I don't know how to do it.
You want me to tell you?
It's okay.
We're not going to
act it out here in public.
You're right.
But do men like that kind of stuff?
Well, we do it a little differently.
To say it in a clean way, doing it with
your mouth means showing lots of love.
The reason why Makoto can't do it well
is because I'm not being supportive?
Maybe we should show her how it's done.
Yeah.
Huh?
Miyuki...
What are you doing in this room?
I'm coming in.
It's okay.
Really...
We'll teach you how to do it real good.
But really, I'm...
Sorry I couldn't remember you.
But I finally remembered.
It's just that you changed so much...
I see.
So you finally remembered, Teacher.
Teacher, huh?
Brings back old memories.
I was the only one who tutored you...
It's been 6 years...
What? Miyuki!
Stop this, Miyuki!
Teacher.
I want you to give me your semen.
I don't want to marry anyone.
I just want a child.
What?
You can't just suck on it
from the very beginning.
Use your tongue like this...
Right behind this area is
where they feel it the most.
That's right.
Yura.
I have to do it too?
We're doing this for you!
I'm sorry...
Wait a minute! What are you saying?
I think we were destined
to be at the same company.
Don't do this, Miyuki.
Miyuki, I don't know what happened
to you. I'm not good at this kind of thing.
And you're much younger than me...
You're trying to tell me not to worry about
my bad experiences?
But I know I won't marry, no matter how
many men I meet...
That's not true!
It's important to listen to what you feel,
but sometimes it's more important...
...to be able to change your opinions as
well.
What kind of person would I be if
changed my beleifs?
Someday, you will meet someone
who you'll want to be happy with.
I got married just the other day.
I feel I'm really happy from my heart.
If I was able to meet a person who makes
me feel that way, you can too, Miyuki.
I liked you...
I liked you, Teacher!
Happiness...
If I had never met Yura,
then I would've...
...never thought that being happy
was the most important thing.
Huh? Did you just get here?
I'm sorry. I was with my friends
longer than I expected.
Hey, what about a baby?
Huh?
Not yet...
I see.
But I'm sure God will...
I'm sorry, Yura.
I'm sure you must be nervous
having dinner with my family.
But I never thought you could
marry a beautiful woman like her.
You're being rude!
What kind of man
do you want to marry, Jun?
Someone who's totally
different from my brother.
I wanted to come visit you
when you were still a student.
I feel the same way.
No, it feels different...
We can't do it here...
We'll just do it quietly...
What's wrong?
What? Yura!
No, I'm about to...
Amazing, it's better than usual.
I climaxed once, so I can go on longer.
Does it feel good, Yura?
Yes!
It feels so good!
Yura...
I think I'm happy.
Me too.
You try to make it look
as if nothing is wrong.
The knife of love won't show any mercy.
You just hold back your feelings
and live each and everyday.
You say you're used to it or
there's nothing you can do.
We should be much
more straightforward...
...and hug each other real tight.
Even if we're feeling
awkward at times.
On the night when I dream
as many times as I shed tears...
...l'm sure an angel will smile at me.
Let's dream of all the stars in the sky.
I hope you keep on smiling.
Next episode
Our next door neighbors
won the lottery and...
...they invited us to
go on a trip with them.
Makoto's cousin Kyoko
also comes along with us.
Makoto and Yura try to
make love at their hotel...
...but are worried
about their surroundings.
Can they move forward
in this step up love story?
Step Up Love Story 2.
Part 1-White Lovers.
I want you to love only me, Makoto.