It feeels good.
And up...
huh?
Oops!
Really...
I wonder why I had a dream like that?
Morning!
What's wrong?
Super ugly chick...
That's not true.
Hmm?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
Oh dear, dear, dear...
Oh! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Ahh...
I got wet...
I wonder which lipstick would be good for today?
Hey, which do you think is good?
Even if you ask me something
like that...
That's right. Isn't that pinkish one good?
Hmm...
I'll make it a flashy red.
Then don't ask me...
How is it? Pretty?
Yes, you're pretty.
Excellent!
Oh, no! I'm gonna be late!
I am going to go, okay?
Watch the house while I'm gone, okay?
I'm late!
Huh? It's that girlie, isn't it?
Late again today, is she?
In such a hurry! Watch out for them cars, you hear?!
No matter when I see her, she's
got a nice a body, that missy.
What? Oh, w... w... wait, wait! Oh dear, dear.
You are heavy now, you know? What are you doing?
Huh?
What's that lady doing?
Oh, no!
What was that? That lady...
Hmm... Pretty good-looking lady, wasn't she?
What's she doing? That lady...
Yagami Shouji, Yagami Shouji.
I wonder if I will see her tomorrow too?
Moe, something good happen?
Why is that, Section Manager?
You seem like you are having too much fun, so...
It's because my motto is 'work equals fun,' you know.
Oh, I will pour you some tea right now.
No, nowadays, if I had a female
employee do someting like that...
they had say I am sexually harassing you.
It's okay. Es-pe-cial-ly for yoy,
Section Manager Yamazaki.
Section Manager!
Good morning.
Morning.
I've kept you waiting!
Oh, right. Have you copied the
materials for today's conference?
Oh, no. I'll go get them right away.
Oh, really!
You did it, didn't you?
Mr. Takagi!
Mr. Takagi?
This copy machine hasn't been working well lately.
What?
See, 'Please, be careful when using the copy machine.'
Please be careful when you using
the copy machine. The Staff.
Oh...
Because you're so thoughtless,
Miss Yagizawa...
I'll help you too.
Umm...
This one and...
Miss Yagizawa!
What?
Your skirt's...
Huh?
The zipper.
Sorry.
Miss Yagizawa...
Oh, wait! These copies are...
Sewing tools... sewing tools...
There they are!
What a day! First that my zipper would break.
And then Mr. Takagi spotted it.
Oh, I wonder if he hates me now?
Ouch!
Really! I wonder if today's an unlucky day?
That girl is definitely nice.
Is this alright?
Yeah, it's alright. But...
Thank you for earlier.
You delievered the copies to the
Section Manager, didn't you?
Huh? Yeah...
Is it all right if I eat lunch here?
Yeah, I ate a noodle bowl at a street vendor, so...
Is that so?
What happened?
No, no, it's nothing...
Oh!
Miss Yagizawa?
I love iron rods.
Here we go!
Hey!
Miss Yagizawa...
Thank you for your hard work.
'Staff meeting, staff meeting!'
They say! What're they doing?
What is that girl doing?!
Senior!
What are you doing?
No... nothing...
You must not touch it yet.
That's right. Deliberately from the outside.
But Senior...
No! I said, 'No, 'didn't I?
I'll tell everyone!
That's right, from above.
The outside, smoothliy, okay?
Forgive me!
No.
Do you want everyone to know...
...that you were masturbating in the conference room?
No, no...
Do the rest yourself.
It feels good, right?
Say it feels good.
No!
Now quickly! Doesn't it feel good?
It... it feels good!
Sewing tools... sewing tools...
There they are!
What kind of day is today?
I've had anough already.
My skirt tore twice, even!
And I got a run in my panty hose...
Panty hose, panty hose...
Huh?
That's strange.
I put an extra pair of panty hose in, but...
Oh, crap!
Who are you?
Well, just a stranger passing by.
Why did you come out of that lady's locker?
Uh, umm, it's a magic locker? As if I'd think that...
What did you say?!
Excuse me!
A PERVERT!!!
Is she sleeping?
Oh? She is pretty cute, isn't she?
Uh... Uh-oh...
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Good night.
Huh? Hey, hey... wait a minute.
Huh?
Your panties are showing, you know.
Oh no, you haven't eaten, have you?
That's right. I am starving, you know!
Sorry! I will give you some right now, okay?
Now, eat a lot.
Oh, it is always the same thing, isn't it?
I'd like to eat sashimie very once in awhile.
Now, maybe I will try hard tomorrow too.
Right!
She is doing it again. She sure likes it, eh?