My name is Misuzu Kawamura.
To tell the truth, something is bothering me a little.
Would you please hear me out?
I am with the swim team at school,
and I also go to a swimming club.
My brother said that he liked the
sight of me in my racing suit,
and to please show him.
Thar dolphin-like shine when it's wet with water,
he said there's a deep flovor to it
that other swimsuits don't have.
I didn't think it was anything
just to show him, so I did.
But...
Brother, he said that he wanted to see it
when the swimsuit slipped off abit.
For example, like this,
when one side comes out the side.
Or when the swimsuit is pulled into the center,
and both breasts are showing.
He says he can't stand it.
Oh, and then,
brother says it's nice when half my ass hangs out too.
Well, it is embarrassing, so
please don't look too much.
Brother had the same expression.
And then he...
My swimsuit...
He said to pull it down to my stomach.
Then I started feeling kind of weird too.
Somehow, while I didn't even
realize what I was doing,
I did as brother told me.
And then, when I finally realized it,
I had pulled my swimsuit up all
on my own, and pulled it into me.
Up to where you could see my most important place.
Brother, who was watching this, was very happy.
My mind was already blank,
and before I knew it, I had spread my legs wide open
and slipped my swimsuit,
which was biting into me there,
up, down, left, and right and crying out sweetly.
Then, in the end, I dropped my
whole swimsuit under my ass,
and masturbated in front of my brother.
I was so embarrassed,
and I can't look my brother in the face anymore.
What should... What should I do?
Brother... Brother...
Brother, stop.
Misuzu...
Bro...
Brother...
Excuse me!
Teacher, good morning!
Morning.
Good morning.
Yes, morning.
Hey, Professor Mizukoshi's
changed a bit recently, hasn't she?
Yeah, you could say she's gotten a bit sexier.
Maybe she got a boyfrined or someting?
Everyone, you are mistaken.
That's not it, I...
Toilet
Amazing!
No... If you do it that much, I can't...
What should I do? Three have come at once.
Well, I get surprised when the
ringer goes off all of a sudden,
so I have it on vibrate.
What? Why do I have three?
Because I want to counsel as
many students as possible.
But I accidentally learned how to use them this way.
Eveyone, I am sorry that I
can't always answer the phone.
But the one who taught me to use them this way is...
I am sorry, I really have four.
It feels like I am going to come, but I can't quite come.
Doctor Fubuki, please.
I want it, please.
Doctor Fubuki, give it to me here.
I want it. I want you to call.
I will have to let her come soon,
or I will feel sorry for her.
It's coming!
Doctor Fubuki!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I have to hurry and get to class.
That's right. Doctor Fubuki, thanks
for making me feel so good.
Hello?
Brother?
What? Oh, you are mistaken.
I am sorry, I made a mistake.
Oh, just a moment.
Are you crying?
Oh, no...
Is something bothering you?
That is...
Well, if it is okay with you,
I will counsel you.
I am Sayaka Mizukoshi.
I am a teacher.
Come in.
I have been waiting.
Hello...
What a pretty person.
Are you Miss Misuzu Kawamura?
Yes...
Is that so?
So you were trying to apologize
to your brother, right?
Yes, I wanted to say that I wouldn't
do anymore disturbing things,
so please don't dislike me.
Is that so?
He is really kind brother who's
lived next door since I was small.
He is an instructor here,
and I started swimming because
I wanted to be like him.
He is a wonderful person then, right?
Yes...
But I don't think there's anything
for you to apologize about.
What? But I did something
like that in front of him!
But that is...
He probably already hates me.
You are like me.
I am sorry.
I can't leave you alone for some reason.
Professor Mizukoshi...
I had my soul and body
made one by a certain person.
Well...
I don't know if I can do it properly, but...
Professor!
How cute. Misuzu, your niples are begging me.
That's not...
They want me to suck on them.
No...
You can't. A place like that...
Please don't lick it.
Professor, I am embarrassed.
Please be more honest with yourself.
Professor, I can't stay standing.
It's all right for you to sit down on the bed.
Yes...
Wonderful, Misuzu...
Your ass, Misuzu,
there is a clear tan line all the way to here.
Why is it clear all the way down here?
Sister, I can't.
Anymore than that...
Misuzu?
Please call me Misuzu.
Yes...
Sister... Sister, your
lips smell like me.
Misuzu...
So pretty, it is wonderful.
Does it feel good?
Hey... I...
So good!
Sister!
Here, how should I?
There is... you know...
Like this?
Oh good, that's... I...
Something like this?
I will allow them to have an emotional reunion.
Doctor Fubuki...
Professor Mizukoshi...
It seems it's a little early for
you to initiate someone else.
But since you got her into
the mood, I will evaluate that.
Sister, who is this person?
Doctor Touka Fubuki, she is the
person who released my soul.
This person did?
Nice to meet you, Miss
Misuzu Kawamura.
How do you know my name?
Now, how do I, I wonder?
I have welcomed a special guest for you two.
Enter!
Toranomon!
Teacher...
I am sorry, Excuse me! Excuse me!
Excuse me!
It's going in! It's going in!
It's going in! It's in! It's in!
It's almost coming out! It's
coming out now! It's gone out!
It's amazing. Amazing...
Toranomon, have you been well?
Teacher!
I... I have been waiting to see
you all this time, Teacher!
What's wrong?
Excuse me!
Just like brother...
You have misunderstood.
Your brother left because you have sex appeal.
Let's make your brother even happier.
Now, it's brother.
Brother...
This child!
Doctor Fubuki...
More... Please teach me more
ways to make brother happy.
All right...
Well... Here... Is it all right to lick it?
That is a common pleasure
spot for both men and women.
Think of it as your brother's ass and lick it.
Sister...
It's to make your brother happy.
It can't be helped.
Misuzu, quickly... Lick it quickly.
I can't wait!
That's right. You must love with all your heart in it.
That's right, put some strength
into the tip of your tongue,
and take it out then put it in again.
You are doing well.
Slowly as if drawing the shape
of a coin, as if prying it apart.
Yes, you are good.
Can't take anymore!
Misuzu...
Sister...
It smells like me.
Now kiss, the supreme kiss that
can only be done between women!
Sister...
Misuzu...
Call me Misuzu!
Misuzu!
Sister...
Misuzu...
Sister!
Misuzu!
Misuzu Kawamura, you are a genius!
You're leading Sayaka to an even
greater release of mind and body!
Wonderful! It's wonderful!
If you'd like, you can do this to your brother.
Yes...
I intend to do something like this too.
Then, if you do this even more...
Then here like this...
That's really nice.