Miss Kannazuki...
Why don't you press your breasts against me next?
You are asking something of someone,
so it would be, 'Please,' would it not?
Please.
Next, I shall press upon you an important part of me.
It is your second favorite place.
Miss Kannazuki, of course it has...
It has not been washed in about three days,
so I think the smell should be exceptional.
Delicious...
Lord Baron, I think I would like to return to work now.
By the way, how are the arrangements for tomorrow?
Please entrust them to me.
Yes, I entrust it to you.
Well then...
For you only...
I wonder, did anyone say it was all right to stop? Continue.
What's wrong? You like iy, don't you?
Masturbation, that is.
And now...
Doing it while strangers are watching.
Now, continue!
Yes...
It seems you still don't understand, do you?
It's not fun at all to see just the figure of you masturbating.
It seems that you won't understand until I teach you, hmm?
No...
No one will be pleased unless you
show it properly while doing it.
You feel it more when someone is properly watching, don't you?
No, something like that is...
I wonder if you will get more excited this way?
Please, anymore than this is...
You still don't comprehend your position, do you?
Now you have permission to come.
Now have them look at your embarrassing appearance.
What is wrong, Dark?
Come here...
What are you doing, Miss Morimura?
Good morning.
Good morning, Miss Morimura.
I told you that tomorrow is a very important day for the Master,
as well as for you.
You do not have time to play with
Dark, you know.
Yes...
Come to my room later with Miss Mizutani.
Understood?
Yes...
All right? Tomorrow's evening party is to become
something more important than all those before now.
You two will take this to heart and entertain them thoroughly.
Yes!
It seems they have arrived. Enter!
I shall introduce you.
Miss Ayako Konno and
Miss Mayu Hoshino.
We will have them assist us with tomorrow's evening party.
Oh, the both of you are so honest, aren't you?
You can't help but be interested by this, right?
Miss Morimura, close your eyes.
What?
Now, quickly!
Oh my, I haven't done anything yet.
but you grasp it as though you were a natural.
That is so indecent.
Miss Mizutani, that will enter into you soon.
How about it? You get wet just thinking about it, do you not?
Nana, please. Put this thing inside me, hurry.
Please...
Oh my, Miss Mizutani, to demand it of your own accord...
It seems you do not yet understand your position, hmm?
Miss Hoshino, bring that.
Yes!
That is a nice expression, Miss Mizutani.
Miss Morimura shall take you into a wonderful world.
It feels good, does it not?
Now, more intensely.
Risa... Risa..., I...
And that is that, which is just as should be expected
of they who the Master selected.
With this, tomorrow too...
Miss Kannazuki...
I would like an appointment with you concerning tomorrow.
Yes, immediately.
Now, you maids...
I am sorry, I can't return to the world in which you exist anymore.
Lord Masquerade...
The setting of the tables will be completed shortly.
Is that so.
To me, and to you as well.
this evening party should become an important assembly.
I am most assured ly counting upon you.
Yes, please leave it to me.
Welcome, everyone.
At this evening's party, I shall have you view another show.
It is an tremendous honor to us, also.
These evening parties, at which
you have enjoyed many sacrifies,
have been a recurring event, and this will be our tenth year.
Today, which will be commemorated,
I have prepared the most excellent of sacrifices.
I have received numerous requests before now,
but this is the sacrifice I could not give a response to.
It is sublime, the ultimate sacrifice
since the dawn of these evening parties.
Yes, Mai Kannazuki!
Stop it, all of you!
Now, my cute maids.
Baron!
The ring leader who dragged you, who were pure and proper,
into this abnormal world.
Punish Mai Kannazuki amply.
It was all for the sake of my Lord Baron!
Shall we begin with 'Drooling Hell'?
Risa.
To this woman, who ordered you to put on a ball gag,
it would do well for you to have her understand fully...
what it means to put one on.
Wait a minute, Miss
Mizutani, I am your...
Oh? It does overflow, indeed.
You were holding it in so it would not flow before now,
weren't you, Risa?
Please let me do some too, Lord Master!
Would it be all right for ne as well,
Lord Master?
How about you, Nana?
No, I...
How about you?
Yes...
Now, all four of you together, cover
Mai Kannazuki's face...
with saliva for her.
Lord Baron! Please cease your jesting!
You! Do you understand what will
happen if you do these things?
I am your...
Ladies and Gentlemen, the amusement has only just begun.
Stop this!
Oh!
Lady Kannazuki! That you had drip so
much from them being taken off!
It is so very indecent!
Now, Nana, Kannazuki's punishment.
Kannazuki desires and is waiting for punishment, you know.
Miss Morimura, stop this!
Even though you have fallen over and are in this position,
you have still held it it firmly inside you, and it's drenched.
How indecent, Kannazuki!
That's not.
Just one is not enough for you, is it,
Lady Kannazuki?
Mai... Kannazuki, is it a pleasant sensation...
to have the maids embrass you thusly?
Baron... No...
Is that so...
You must not, Lord Masquerade! No!
Lord Masquerade...
Cute Maids, drive Mai Kannazuki into a frenzy.
Lord Masquerade!
Enter.
Excuse me.
Lord Baron, it is almost time for the new maid to arrive.
I shall leave it to you.
I understand.
Is this it?
Excuse me! Excuse me!