I am Sayaka Mizukoshi.
I'm a teacher at this school.
I'm 164 cm tall, and my bust is 98 cm.
My waist is 60 cm.
My hips are 89 cm.
My age? I am already twenty-four years old.
Please don't look at me with such leering eyes.
I'm a teacher.
It is inconvenient to be seen that way.
Teacher, good morning!
Good morning!
Morning.
Yes, morning.
Professor Mizukoshi sure is a nice lady, isn't she?
That impression of purity.
There is not many like that nowadays.
Yeah...
Everyone has the wrong idea about me.
The sound of the bell at Gion Shoujya...
echoes though the businesses and...
The color of the Buddhist high priest's flower...
After taking the train...
During glass, my body gets unbearably hot.
Why is it that my body gets so hot?
Why? Why?
Everyone is studying
like they should be.
I... What am I doing?
Teacher, what's wrong?
Are you all right?
What? No, that's... Oh, O am sorry.
I am just out of it.
It seems I have abit a fever.
Ladie's Room
I did it again.
They are so wet.
Really, I can't believe it.
Am I a pervert?
Why did I do that while I was
standing up at the podium?
If everyone knew about my state back then,
they'd probably be disillusioned...
that I had do something so bold.
It's almost like I am not getting enough.
Whoops...
Sorry.
Professor Mizukoshi?
Lady's Dreassing Room
I have to get a hold of myself!
Professor? Professor Mizukoshi?
You know, I called out to you
many times. Professor Mizukoshi.
Now, please get out of the water, and come with me.
Yes...
Professor Mizukoshi...
The school is now closed.
Those who don't have any further
business here, please hurry home.
Have you come to?
Who?
Oh, please don't misinterpet this, all right?
You collapsed in your swimsuit,
so I took that off and clothed you in a blouse.
Then, perhaps you saw me naked...
Well, who knows?
Oh dear, you have turned red.
Just like the rumors say,
you are such a pure young lady professor, aren't you?
Young lady professor? What do you mean by that?
Are you being sarcastic?
But you are, aren't you?
I'd think you could have at least said.
'Thank you,'
before you asked that question.
I'm sorry.
Well, that sort of thing doesn't really matter, but...
That aside, Professor Mizukoshi,
I'm more curious as to why you
ended up losing consciousness.
That is where my interest lies.
Shall we consider what might have caused it?
Could it be stress?
Aren't you really trying to keep strangers
from finding out about the real you?
You must have been raised very
strictly by your parents, corrects?
Everyone around you had high expectations,
and so you tried your hardest to be
a good girl in front of everybody.
After all, it was having strict parents
that made sexual matters particularly taboo, right?
That's right. It was absolutely forbidden, but...
But you were curious, just
like anyone else.
During college, I worked part-time as a tutor.
Toranomon, are you listening?
You have to try harder.
This will be your second time, right?
Toranomon...
Wait! What are you doing, Toranomon?
Teacher, what I want to study is...
Stop it!
What I want you to teach me is...
Stop! Stop!
Is about the female body!
No!
Teacher, teacher!
You can't! You can't, Toranomon!
No! No!
Teacher, teacher, it is amazing,
your breasts are amazing!
You can't!
No! No!
No!
Teacher, I am sorry, I am sorry!
But please forgive me, forgive me!
It's going in! It's going in!
It's in!
It's coming out now!
Oh dear, so it ended as an attempted rape?
Yes, ever since then,
boys younger than me...
When those boys look at me so intensely,
my body becomes so unbearably hot.
I think what happened them has
become a trauma to my soul.
Trauma? What kind of amateur diagnosis is that?
Am I wrong?
It's like this.
You don't understand yourself at all, do you?
Doctor Fubuki?
Now, don't be a home psychologist!
Tell the truth!
And then purge everything
that's been piling up in here!
No!
It's all right. You don't need to worry about anything.
Now, concentrate!
Now, how about it?
Admit that Sayaka Mizukoshi isn't getting enough!
How awful! That's not so!
Excuse me for a bit.
Doctor Fubuki!
These breats, ripened and overflowing in this Icup;
such pale pink nipples.
These...
Need to be examined physically.
Professor Mizukoshi, may I ask you one thing?
Yes...
Are you teaching class as you should?
I really, like everyone thinks...
So nobody will notice...
behind the podium, secretly...
Pushing it against the podium and such.
I am holding it in.
But...
This thrill is such a pleasurable feeling.
Should I have someone com over here?
It's no use...
My butt, there is a chill going
through my butt. It feels so good!
It's serious, isn't it?
Wait a minute! Doctor
Fubuki! What is this?
Don't make such exaggerated sounds!
Un til we ask this right here,
we won't know, now will we?
No, stop it!
Doctor Fubuki! Please stop this joking!
You aren't being very honest, are you,
Professor Mizukoshi?
You have come this far, you
can't say that it's just a joke.
Is there someting?
Doctor! Doctor Fubuki, please say something!
You pantyhose is in the way.
Well, well, this is...
Such a troublesome thing.
Doctor Fubuki?
Please calm down and listen carefully.
Professor Mizukoshi,
you need an operation.
Professor Mizukoshi, this
will be a special operation.
Yes...
Leave it to me!
To my skills, which were called
back in my student days,
'Touka's Operation!'
Please...
Relax your body.
It's embarrassing.
There's nothing to be embrassed
about, Professor Mizukoshi.
Let's heal you slowly.
Sensitive, isn't it?
It's important to be able to easily feel it.
Now, don't tighten up your body up so much.
Professor Mizukoshi, may I
ask you some more questions?
Yes, what is it?
What sort of masturbation do you usually do?
No, don't do it so much, I will tell you!
I will tell you!
Oh my, you have masturbated in the staff room?
I held back, like I should,
though that was only at the beginning.
What did you intend to do it
the other theachers saw you?
That is... I did think about it, but...
But you can't control yourself, can you?
I do have self-control.
But my body... my body just...
Perhap's that's it, it's your body's fault.
It's my body's...
It's definitely my body's fault!
I am a teacher, you know!
I am a teacher.
You are a teacher in mind.
However, your body won't
listen to you.
That's it! My body is bad.
It's not me!
Professor Mizukoshi, your body
truly is this sensitive, isn't it?
That's right.
It's better if you don't use hard things, isn't it?
Yes!
You're really sensitive.
Professor Mizukoshi,
I must consider the kind of
operation you need right now, okay?
Please...
Doctor Fubuki, that's...
Something to make your body and soul one.
Japan's high-tech, low frequency wave therapy!
Will I really be healed?
This operation requires concentration.
It's cold.
It'll get warm soon.
The other part is low-tech, but
you must not underestimate it.
It's the most important part of this operation.
With this, setting is okay.
I will begin the operation.
You are shaking, aren't you?
Not yet, with just this much,
for your body, which doesn't
listen to you,
it should not be enough.
Next, it's time for the low-tech.
No!
Already... already...
How are the high-tech and
low-tech operations together?
The third one is my original.
Professor Mizukoshi, now open your soul.
You are to become one with your body.
I will be healed from this, right?