[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人来到黑川家已过了一周
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.08,0:01:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后  我都不敢正面看爱莉莎的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.88,0:01:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于美香的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.50,0:01:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介 添饭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.23,0:01:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要我…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.80,0:01:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 这就去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.51,0:01:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片的事以来  完全被美香踩在脚底下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.48,0:01:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…爱莉莎？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且每晚来到我房间  拿老二当玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.76,0:01:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  都这么硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.85,0:01:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样  舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.75,0:01:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介要去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.14,0:01:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的生活  从今往后也…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.61,0:01:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  添饭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.13,0:01:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.19,0:01:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不机灵
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:01:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想出点对策的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.31,0:01:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碗里有什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.02,0:02:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…那个…美香…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.76,0:02:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.19,0:02:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊对了  今天社团活动  回去会晚一点
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.31,0:02:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.41,0:02:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  那我做一餐美味等着你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.22,0:02:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK  我期待着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.95,0:02:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然继续这样下去的话不太妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.75,0:02:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.53,0:03:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  一个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.75,0:03:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.32,0:03:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想找你一起回去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.87,0:03:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎…超可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.93,0:03:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是宗介的相机？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.92,0:03:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.84,0:03:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  宗介的父亲还是摄影家呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.00,0:03:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…说起这个…我有个请求…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.97,0:03:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介君？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.56,0:03:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.78,0:03:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎能不能做我的摄影模特
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.96,0:03:43.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？  我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.46,0:03:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行…么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.39,0:03:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我很高兴  拍吧拍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.95,0:03:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我没有做过模特  但是宗介的话我非常乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.81,0:03:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的！？  那么既然机会难得…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.94,0:04:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定穿上这个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.62,0:04:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么桌子里有这样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.10,0:04:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…摄影道具
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.74,0:04:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  面向这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.48,0:04:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介这么正经的表情  第一次看到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.72,0:04:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有点…帅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.45,0:04:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍完了  爱莉莎  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.47,0:04:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  也让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.66,0:04:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～  拍的真好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.79,0:04:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是模特好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.41,0:05:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  爱莉莎  这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.05,0:05:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  相机给我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.66,0:05:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说  这个是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.47,0:05:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.90,0:05:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.11,0:05:25.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我呢  对拍照时的宗介  有点心动了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.15,0:05:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介从这个角度看还真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.49,0:05:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.62,0:05:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以KISS吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.56,0:05:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的初吻  给宗介了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.43,0:05:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.78,0:05:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的处女也…宗介的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.75,0:05:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.79,0:06:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  我也一直对爱莉莎…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.46,0:06:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.21,0:06:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然揉得那么用力的话…会痛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.23,0:06:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过被宗介这么用力揉  很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.74,0:06:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎的这里  已经湿了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.64,0:06:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.72,0:06:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被那样说的话  我…又要湿了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.36,0:06:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎的身体  很H
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.10,0:06:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里  小豆豆  不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.89,0:06:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部和小豆豆  有感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.54,0:06:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小豆豆  好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.85,0:07:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  喜欢温柔一点还是激烈一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.45,0:07:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,激烈的  我喜欢激烈的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.46,0:07:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力  再用力一点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.65,0:07:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不行了  再这样下去的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.12,0:07:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是的  只用手就高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.27,0:07:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像…快疯掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.43,0:07:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真丢脸  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.16,0:07:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经去了啊  爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.57,0:07:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.58,0:08:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次轮到我奉仕了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.68,0:08:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是  男人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.61,0:08:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比在浴室看到的时候  好像又大了点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.55,0:08:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为爱莉莎  它兴奋了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.16,0:08:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.32,0:08:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是第一次  可能做得不好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.24,0:08:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很上手啊  爱莉莎  很爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.55,0:08:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来让你舒服  宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.39,0:08:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  那么激烈的话  爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.36,0:08:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.03,0:09:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射…射了！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.37,0:09:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  爱莉莎  不小心…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.83,0:09:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是…精液
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.64,0:09:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这么多  粘粘的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.33,0:09:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.27,0:09:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.49,0:09:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.53,0:09:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去要小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.13,0:09:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,88
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.45,0:09:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,88
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.31,0:09:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真的是很晚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.71,0:10:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.67,0:10:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  真的可以么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.85,0:10:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  这次要在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.24,0:10:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.43,0:10:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.50,0:10:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.52,0:10:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  不要停
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.00,0:10:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的处女  是要献给宗介的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.84,0:10:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了  那么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.67,0:10:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.90,0:10:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害  这就是男人的…  好大
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.65,0:11:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛吗  没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.99,0:11:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  用力  在里面…再用力一点  宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.70,0:11:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在爱莉莎的…那里抽插  我也…很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.14,0:11:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  插得那么深  好舒服  好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.84,0:11:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫水也…流个不停
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.35,0:11:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  宗介的  又变得更大了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.23,0:11:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.78,0:12:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里  发出淫靡的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.02,0:12:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快不行了宗介  我已经
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.12,0:12:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.95,0:12:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的  如果是宗介的话  可以射在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.35,0:12:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  我…我快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.30,0:12:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  在我的里面  把白色的  狠狠射出来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.10,0:12:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了  宗介的精液  在我的里面出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.20,0:13:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.77,0:13:16.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  爱莉莎  射在里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.90,0:13:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的  能和宗介合为一体  我好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.10,0:13:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  宗介君  这件事不要告诉美香
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.68,0:13:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我一定不说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.90,0:13:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  美香还没有回来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.49,0:13:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说有社团活动  会晚一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.21,0:13:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可这也太晚了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.55,0:13:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿的少就老是想上厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.35,0:14:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  这里可是女厕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.33,0:14:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么啊  你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.04,0:14:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.39,0:14:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  你个臭女人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.08,0:14:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会痛的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.08,0:14:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要反抗的话  会少吃点苦头  七濑美香
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.71,0:14:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是就是  惹毛这家伙会很可怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.06,0:14:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,含着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.89,0:14:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你含着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.71,0:14:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  绝对不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.86,0:14:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多给我…老实一点了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.42,0:15:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像做梦一样  能和学校的偶像做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.25,0:15:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  舌头再灵活点  这样可一点都不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.39,0:15:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边可夹得够紧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.50,0:15:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OH NO  要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.27,0:15:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出来了  让我尽情中出吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.09,0:15:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也差不多要…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.75,0:15:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.31,0:16:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话  当然是因为有的爽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.74,0:16:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轮到我了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.10,0:16:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里  那里不行  好痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.75,0:16:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊花不行  拜托  拜托快停下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.94,0:16:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手好像闲下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.13,0:16:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.15,0:16:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  这个洞比较爽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.97,0:16:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再用点劲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.70,0:16:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不是盖的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.13,0:16:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不行了  这么紧快射了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.74,0:16:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给这婊子来个精液浴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.72,0:17:11.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不～要～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.71,0:17:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次干她姐怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.81,0:17:27.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好主意  我批准了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.29,0:17:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们几个  在这里做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.10,0:17:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑川
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.94,0:17:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕  我们给拍到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.26,0:17:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.01,0:17:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你们和照片交给警察
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.64,0:17:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快撤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.07,0:17:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.97,0:17:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  你怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.37,0:17:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.02,0:17:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以安心了美香
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.10,0:18:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么对我这么温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.63,0:18:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说为什么也…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.50,0:18:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直对宗介说很多过分的话  可你还…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.64,0:18:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点都没放在心上  这才像美香嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.20,0:18:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜  呆子  臭屁宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.06,0:18:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么了  美香
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.78,0:18:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我忘掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.49,0:18:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子的话回不了家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.57,0:18:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的事  宗介要让我全部忘掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.89,0:18:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.11,0:18:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.51,0:18:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香到底上哪去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.06,0:18:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去了哦  宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.95,0:18:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.31,0:18:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个宗介  已经变得这么硬了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.95,0:18:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  美香
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.46,0:19:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  今天特别放你一马
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.78,0:19:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  这招爽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.00,0:19:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜  为什么你先舒服起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.02,0:19:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.27,0:19:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这样如何
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.60,0:19:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介的大东西  在我的里面进出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.27,0:19:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…美香也有感觉了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.31,0:19:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多嘴  为什么要被宗介这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.04,0:19:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要～  呆子  乳头…不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.57,0:19:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  那里是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.67,0:19:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  美香胸部很敏感对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.10,0:19:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  那么就  让我更舒服一些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.06,0:19:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  美香  我会让你忘记一切的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.77,0:20:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服  大大的在里面抽动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.32,0:20:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高兴  第一次能让美香说很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.88,0:20:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  宗介的巨物  撑得那里好涨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.37,0:20:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  宗介
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.69,0:20:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H时的美香  表情好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.24,0:20:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆瓜  别突然这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.58,0:20:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  我快…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.31,0:20:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快去了是吗  那我也一起…和宗介一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.41,0:21:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了  美香
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.14,0:21:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  射出来  直接射到最里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.88,0:21:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了  宗介的精液  在我的里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.91,0:21:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.22,0:21:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.54,0:21:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.40,0:21:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你去哪里了  我担心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.48,0:21:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香要是出了什么事  我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.53,0:21:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是担心死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.95,0:21:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  爱莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.91,0:22:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后数天
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.78,0:22:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从有了肌肤之亲  我和爱莉莎的距离急遽缩短
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.73,0:22:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  这边倒还是老样子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.96,0:22:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别那么用力  那里被用力吸的话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.25,0:23:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.16,0:23:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要  宗介的  现在  立刻就想要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.93,0:23:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.59,0:23:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  今天的晚饭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.77,0:23:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.38,0:23:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.25,0:23:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.66,0:23:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  今天回来的可真早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.20,0:23:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  这件事  其实有很…简单的内情的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.56,0:23:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有爱莉莎爽太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.20,0:23:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和宗介打炮是我的工作的说
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.72,0:23:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香  你在说什么啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.41,0:23:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  美香也想和宗介做？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.22,0:23:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.18,0:24:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  难得的机会  不如3P吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.80,0:24:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连爱莉莎也…啥咪咪啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.11,0:24:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  既然爱莉莎都这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.78,0:24:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底为什么会变成这样的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.81,0:24:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么宗介  有什么不满吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.31,0:24:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不…完全没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.52,0:24:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有精神嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.04,0:24:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介君  反应很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.51,0:24:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两面攻的话我…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.27,0:24:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  已经很湿了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.16,0:24:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那里也舔一下
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.92,0:24:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香的这里  已经洪水泛滥了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.90,0:24:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  那么说的话  羞死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.02,0:24:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香真是的  发出那么淫荡的声音  连我也兴奋起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.11,0:25:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  已经放进去了么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.94,0:25:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我的下面全湿了  已经忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.41,0:25:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吗  爱莉莎  那么大的东西进到里面  很爽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.36,0:25:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  好舒服啊  一边抖动着  一边在里面疯狂搅动
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.12,0:25:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服  好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.04,0:26:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介  舌头再用力一点
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.29,0:26:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像宗介的大东西一样  伸进来～
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.86,0:26:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里面又变大了  这样的话…不行…宗介～
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.31,0:26:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了  爱莉莎  我快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.59,0:26:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦  宗介  要去的话  要一起
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.93,0:26:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力  再用力
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.53,0:26:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽  好爽啊  宗介搞得好舒服  我快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.42,0:26:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香也要去了吗  我这边也顶到最里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.98,0:27:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉莎  射了  在里面  爱莉莎  啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.08,0:27:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊美香  突然拍起照来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.63,0:27:29.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再把我排除在外
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.54,0:27:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把这些照片散发给爱莉莎饭们
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.19,0:27:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？那是啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.79,0:27:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宗介是我的专用玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.09,0:27:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有我的许可不准上其他女人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.23,0:27:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是爱莉莎也不行  明白？
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.27,0:27:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不明白～
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.20,0:27:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美香真是的  这么爱吃醋
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.28,0:27:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会大件事的快还给我（不要～）
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.46,0:27:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  以后就有得玩了


