[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-02-02 13:27:24
; // 版本: 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Original Script: Maho.sub
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
PlayResX: 480
PlayResY: 272

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,微软雅黑,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H008000FF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: staff2,微软雅黑,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H008000FF,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: up,微软雅黑,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.66,0:00:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.06,0:00:25.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个 长大后 一定要 娶我做妻子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.52,0:00:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.05,0:00:39.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 得手了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.27,0:00:40.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.48,0:00:41.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是我！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.70,0:00:44.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人从今天将开始成为
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.53,0:00:49.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们神山财阀神山家的当家
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.50,0:01:00.10,staff,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}后宫时间 让您久等了 当家大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.50,0:01:00.10,staff2,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)}魔穗字幕组 翻译：暴走野猪 时间：BIU 后期：显血
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.90,0:01:05.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让您久等了 当家大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.60,0:01:26.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤玲二大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.80,0:01:30.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天开始请您成为神山家的当家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.73,0:01:34.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下啊！ 为什么是我？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.70,0:01:40.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您的母亲曾是前代当家的妾室
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.93,0:01:46.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如今流着神山家血液的 已经只剩玲二大人了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.95,0:01:48.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么会这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.20,0:01:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我成为财阀的后继人什么的 做不到啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.20,0:01:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为想尽快让您继承当家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.29,0:01:58.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这之后要决定正妻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:01.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从而正式地继承神山家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.65,0:02:06.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 根据玲二大人的喜好把女孩子给找来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.80,0:02:11.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 知道我的喜好...？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.25,0:02:14.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事前调查的结果而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.02,0:02:16.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 大家！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.70,0:02:21.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 请来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.11,0:02:25.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 我还没说要继承！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.30,0:02:30.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 不要让女孩蒙羞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.39,0:02:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等 等下！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.98,0:02:39.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 请放松
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.75,0:02:42.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶！骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.32,0:02:49.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好大！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.10,0:02:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请交给我们 会让您感到舒服的！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.70,0:03:06.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 用我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.90,0:03:14.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人的肉棒 慢慢地变大了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.70,0:03:26.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能有感觉 我好高兴！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.48,0:03:28.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.37,0:03:32.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前端有汁水出来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.93,0:03:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳头 变硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.70,0:03:43.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.10,0:03:47.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像很好吃的样子...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.40,0:03:49.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等 不好了...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.09,0:03:51.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.59,0:04:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要射了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.66,0:04:15.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.20,0:04:25.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 这么多...！好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.04,0:04:40.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要这么吸！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.10,0:04:45.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好浓厚 味道和气味都超棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.90,0:04:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再多让我尝一下味道！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.50,0:04:51.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚才射过！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.88,0:05:01.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 现在才真正开始哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.27,0:05:05.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么先由我来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.40,0:05:09.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人的大肉棒 我收下咯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.50,0:05:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的要做到这步？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.50,0:05:19.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大~一下子就亲到子宫了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.20,0:05:23.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是 神山家当家的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.25,0:05:25.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 好厉害！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.19,0:05:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,里面 到最里面了...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.95,0:05:38.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 咕叽咕叽的 缠绕着肉棒 好舒服！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.97,0:05:42.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不行了~！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.61,0:05:50.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了去了 要去了！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.96,0:05:56.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了~！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.70,0:06:05.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 接下来是我 请插进我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.70,0:06:08.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 就来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.90,0:06:10.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进进出出的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.76,0:06:15.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好厉害 好厉害的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.79,0:06:23.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要 我也要！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.90,0:06:28.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.60,0:06:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我的小穴里搅动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.98,0:06:37.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 也请给我精子吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.70,0:06:43.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在小穴的 里面 大量的射出来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.60,0:06:44.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.87,0:06:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来了 玲二大人的精子 来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.00,0:06:55.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在里面大量的！去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.77,0:07:01.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.48,0:07:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不管什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.31,0:07:09.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下流的事也会做的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.08,0:07:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请尽管弄我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.60,0:07:19.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳头 乳头不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.00,0:07:24.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在吸乳头的话！我...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.70,0:07:29.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴收得好紧！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.27,0:07:34.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 肯定会怀上小孩的！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.44,0:07:44.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 连这种事也能做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:48.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.59,0:08:08.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 喜欢 好喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:12.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽管射吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.87,0:08:21.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我的小穴里怀孕吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.00,0:08:28.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让大家都高潮了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.13,0:08:33.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是玲二大人 将成大器之人呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.90,0:08:36.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,未报名字真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.96,0:08:39.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫如月爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.70,0:08:42.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我正是正妻候补首席
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.88,0:08:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算你说正妻...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.59,0:08:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 我们一直爱慕着玲二大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.09,0:08:57.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 我想要玲二大人的 小孩...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.56,0:09:03.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.43,0:09:04.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.25,0:09:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按玲二大人喜欢的样子来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.70,0:09:14.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把我弄得更加乱七八糟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.86,0:09:20.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这 好厉害 要去了啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.32,0:09:19.31,up,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我 已经 脑内一片空白了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.62,0:09:21.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.30,0:09:27.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.70,0:09:30.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起 一起 去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.70,0:09:37.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人~！！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.66,0:09:46.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 我 成为正妻后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会想办法让您变成优秀的继承人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.10,0:09:54.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经做到这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.66,0:09:55.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再说的话虽然有点那个...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.56,0:09:57.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.08,0:10:00.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已经有喜欢的人了...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.61,0:10:04.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 抱歉...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.02,0:10:08.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下 淳子姐！这和说的不一样啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.34,0:10:11.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.40,0:10:14.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就H到忘掉那个人为止！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.78,0:10:17.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人有思念之人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.40,0:10:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有必要调查一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.08,0:10:24.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人 请做好觉悟吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.00,0:10:27.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下 真的 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.33,0:10:46.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平泉前辈 今年的校花
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.70,0:10:49.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,击沉了几十个男人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.40,0:10:51.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从来没在她身旁看到过男人的影子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.54,0:10:53.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎眼光很高
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.59,0:11:01.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 夜路很危险 我送你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.90,0:11:08.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 肩膀借我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.49,0:11:14.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平泉前辈 今天喝了那么多吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.41,0:11:20.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 不知怎么喝地很高兴 一下子就喝多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.70,0:11:23.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好像也很醉的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.73,0:11:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恩 有点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.44,0:11:29.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.08,0:11:31.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回去了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.17,0:11:34.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶不上末班车的话比较麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.48,0:11:45.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都特地送我到这了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.36,0:11:54.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为只是偶然地来劝诱你么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.08,0:12:01.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新生？旅行社团 有兴趣么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.09,0:12:06.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是！有兴趣！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.59,0:12:20.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺中意你的 不会让你逃了哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.28,0:12:24.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢前辈 所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.18,0:12:35.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 难道很会哄骗女孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.15,0:12:40.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坏孩子 一定要惩罚呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.50,0:12:44.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 真的啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.71,0:13:10.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的舌头 好棒...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.42,0:13:24.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.12,0:13:30.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像积累了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.80,0:13:35.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呐 这次由你来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.18,0:13:40.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.42,0:13:50.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像做梦一样 能和前辈H
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.74,0:13:54.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一开始 就想干这个么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.20,0:14:05.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一开始 最想摸前辈的胸部！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:08.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 就多摸摸吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.09,0:14:14.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小穴也 尽管插...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.10,0:14:25.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到现在为止每一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.78,0:14:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都想象着前辈来自慰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.11,0:14:33.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽说些谎话...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.07,0:14:38.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,顶到 最里面了...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.31,0:14:57.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.00,0:15:03.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.37,0:15:12.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还想 做么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.26,0:15:13.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.13,0:15:17.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以 再做些想做的事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.18,0:15:22.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想再做些更H的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.20,0:15:25.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.70,0:15:30.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的胸部 像小穴一样被你的肉棒给侵犯着
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.50,0:15:43.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.70,0:15:57.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再 可以再多做一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.10,0:15:58.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 这样么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.83,0:16:02.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股 麻麻的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.75,0:16:06.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 被打得 好舒服！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.18,0:16:15.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抽打前辈的这里的话 就会收得很紧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.44,0:16:20.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很疼却有感觉了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.37,0:16:24.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 更加 更加激烈一点！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.24,0:16:37.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒 好舒服！！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.82,0:16:42.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里 很脏的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.32,0:16:45.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我帮你舔干净
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.76,0:16:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很想帮你舔 你羞耻的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.24,0:16:54.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 这么激烈的话 又要...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.26,0:16:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦 射出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.50,0:17:03.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脸上 在我的脸上射出浓浓的吧！感谢我吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.40,0:17:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感谢！感谢前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.15,0:17:10.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,浓浓的射到脸上了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.97,0:17:19.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 好像 又要去了 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.78,0:17:23.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 越来越下流了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.87,0:17:27.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.53,0:17:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也 很舒服吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.88,0:17:39.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦 按你喜欢地来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.12,0:17:43.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的这里 太舒服了 停不下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.78,0:17:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.73,0:17:52.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 射了这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.15,0:17:55.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦 第一次见到你的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.21,0:17:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就想被你的精子给包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.78,0:18:10.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我 尝到最后吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.24,0:18:20.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 差不多该起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.97,0:18:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.25,0:18:30.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经 要去大学了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.76,0:18:35.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迟些时间也行 记得把我家钥匙还我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.74,0:18:40.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚的事 忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.34,0:18:43.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,互相都醉了的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.48,0:18:46.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就会发生这种事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.70,0:18:59.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事情 就是这样的...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.37,0:19:02.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是做了这样的梦么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.24,0:19:05.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是真事啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.80,0:19:08.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 平泉不可能会醉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.96,0:19:11.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她 很能喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.59,0:19:15.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你去哪？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.65,0:19:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.32,0:19:24.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来还钥匙了么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.70,0:19:27.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚 两个人去喝一杯么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.24,0:19:34.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再 醉了的话我可不管哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.20,0:19:49.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来到了神山家数日后
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.06,0:19:53.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,淳子姐 带来了新的正妻候补
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.22,0:19:55.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但那人竟然是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.87,0:19:59.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花泽小姐？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.05,0:20:04.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佐藤君 是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.07,0:20:06.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.53,0:20:10.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也被选为正妻候补了 所以
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.05,0:20:12.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.83,0:20:16.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.05,0:20:21.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这 一定是做梦！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.76,0:20:26.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是这触感却是确确实实的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.69,0:20:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.73,0:20:32.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花泽小姐 做什么？！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.33,0:20:37.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样子是第一次 有可能做得不是很好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.92,0:20:40.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花泽小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.85,0:20:48.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想做！我想和花泽小姐 sex！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.75,0:20:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然 我还是做不了这事！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.44,0:20:58.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.99,0:21:02.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和神山财阀的人约好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.74,0:21:05.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸的公司快倒闭了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.10,0:21:09.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和你 H的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.86,0:21:11.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就会出援助金给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.26,0:21:13.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.02,0:21:18.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,变成这样的话 契约决裂了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.47,0:21:23.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 妈妈会从神山家离开 现在我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.94,0:21:30.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像这样 用金钱随意来摆弄其他无力的人 就是你们的做法对吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.74,0:21:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我 果然不打算回神山...等下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.98,0:21:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的 这是我提出的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.85,0:21:44.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸的公司很困难那是真事 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.18,0:21:48.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 刚才只是因为突如其来的事吓了一跳而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.13,0:21:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果对方是你的话 我有点高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.72,0:22:01.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 慢慢了解你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.19,0:22:06.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先从 朋友开始做起好么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.77,0:22:09.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太嫩了 太嫩了啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.96,0:22:13.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,玲二大人不快点决定正妻的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.61,0:22:15.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不会信服的！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.69,0:22:19.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所 以 说！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.36,0:22:21.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我们H吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.33,0:22:25.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.49,0:22:37.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要~
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.87,0:22:42.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好紧...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.34,0:22:46.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,进来了 佐藤君的那个 到我里面来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.57,0:22:52.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 第一次就这样不要啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.03,0:23:06.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 玲二大人 好好地品尝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.01,0:23:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花泽小姐 我 从以前开始就一直
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.83,0:23:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢着你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.35,0:23:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人 为什么在这种时候...？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.57,0:23:33.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？好舒服！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.78,0:23:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗人！好棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.21,0:23:40.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,花 花泽小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.77,0:23:45.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,决定了！我果然想当正妻！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.71,0:23:53.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢！喜欢肉棒！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.28,0:24:01.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为 成为正妻的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.00,0:24:08.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以每天和你做这么棒的事不是么？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.36,0:24:14.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢！最喜欢你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.66,0:24:17.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以娶我做妻子吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.31,0:24:24.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了~
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.99,0:24:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样算 结果好就好了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.35,0:24:37.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会承认的！！！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.65,0:24:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是 这个故事还会继续
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.09,0:24:50.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请期待下回吧