[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.25,0:00:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子裡面的小穴被攪個不停…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.38,0:00:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼被撐開了…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.56,0:00:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會這麼舒服…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.27,0:00:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.27,0:00:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰叫您沒有…沒有告訴過我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.08,0:00:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.27,0:00:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.58,0:00:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢貨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.70,0:00:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭公主的高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.33,0:00:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豈是你等鼠輩能夠接納的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.62,0:01:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.93,0:01:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔族可不是這麼軟弱的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.19,0:01:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想讓我任您擺佈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.12,0:01:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還早100年啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.44,0:01:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.94,0:01:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,31歲以下的女人不准穿衣服？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.07,0:01:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.63,0:01:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 太亂來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.54,0:01:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔哦 真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.23,0:01:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大色狼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.67,0:01:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？女人不能穿衣服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.29,0:01:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從明天起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.29,0:01:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應帝盧克大人的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.17,0:01:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人從肩膀到下身
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.79,0:01:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都不能穿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.49,0:01:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從肩膀到下身的話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.12,0:01:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就基本上是全裸了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:01:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.93,0:02:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人也不能穿嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.24,0:02:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人的話
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.24,0:02:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能露出自己的肌膚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.18,0:02:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？那臉怎麼辦？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.24,0:02:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你們這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.81,0:02:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醜的要死的臉不能看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.75,0:02:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是帝盧克王的命令
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.54,0:02:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[姬騎士 莉莉婭 vol.5 悅獄 霧子和蕾娜]
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.99,0:02:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克大人 您找我？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.31,0:02:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.34,0:02:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.28,0:02:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我命令的事情是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.45,0:02:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.70,0:02:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部按照您的指示辦的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.36,0:02:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.55,0:02:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓城市的女孩們禁止穿衣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.05,0:02:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城堡裡面的侍女們
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.37,0:03:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也全部換成了帝盧克大人的喜好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.07,0:03:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.52,0:03:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們兩個也快點轉轉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.08,0:03:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓帝盧克大人好好看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.58,0:03:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.83,0:03:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不准遮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.70,0:03:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反對的人和逃跑的侍女
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.14,0:03:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都關在牢房裡面了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.95,0:03:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔幾天不給他們飯吃 他們就說「還是裸體的比較好」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.10,0:03:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.37,0:03:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.62,0:03:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難得的不可能的難題
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.87,0:03:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 蕾娜怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.49,0:03:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.49,0:03:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也正準備展示給帝盧克大人看呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.59,0:04:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.03,0:04:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把蕾娜帶到內園
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.29,0:04:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.98,0:04:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.11,0:04:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔的肉棒…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.03,0:05:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.36,0:05:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快摸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.36,0:05:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揉啊 吸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.49,0:05:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.34,0:05:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.65,0:05:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭和那裡都很有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.72,0:05:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.66,0:05:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰來摸我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.84,0:05:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.53,0:05:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.53,0:05:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.97,0:05:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.28,0:05:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.28,0:05:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭會變成怎樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.85,0:05:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.92,0:05:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.73,0:05:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快插我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.04,0:05:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欺負我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.09,0:06:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.46,0:06:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在救出媽媽之前…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.12,0:06:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.05,0:06:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.96,0:06:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是誰都好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.34,0:06:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快和我做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.15,0:06:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.15,0:06:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好熱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.17,0:06:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克 帝盧克 帝盧克…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.41,0:06:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快插我的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.35,0:06:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把肉棒插的深深的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.17,0:06:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使勁兒攪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.23,0:06:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部也
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.16,0:06:33.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部也揉揉 吸吸乳頭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.89,0:06:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.08,0:06:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 該去散步了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.45,0:07:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.39,0:07:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把蕾娜大人帶來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.64,0:07:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 很慢啊 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.83,0:07:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 給蕾娜大人打扮了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 很久不見了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.66,0:07:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.86,0:07:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 該打招呼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.15,0:07:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.03,0:07:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久沒見了啊 帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.96,0:07:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被調教了的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.34,0:07:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫亂的蕾娜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.71,0:07:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請慢慢享用
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.99,0:07:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.55,0:07:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹得不錯 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.61,0:07:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 帝盧克大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.30,0:07:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很不錯的打扮啊 母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.30,0:07:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很愉快嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.86,0:07:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.29,0:07:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 愉快的話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.25,0:07:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快點搖搖尾巴看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.56,0:08:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人變成狗了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.09,0:08:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.97,0:08:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼從今以後
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.31,0:08:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就把你當做寵物來養吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.05,0:08:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.11,0:08:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手 帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.11,0:08:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要對母親大人做這麼過分的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.03,0:08:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.91,0:08:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭大人也在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.41,0:08:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久違的母子相見啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.68,0:08:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.06,0:08:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同為我的寵物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.76,0:08:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好相處啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.63,0:08:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.19,0:08:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.09,0:08:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.41,0:08:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寵物之間也是很值得一看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.66,0:08:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.63,0:09:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾娜大人的調教程度
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.94,0:09:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人也是有夠軟弱的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.69,0:09:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不要這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.63,0:09:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.87,0:09:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是為了救母親才忍到現在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.12,0:09:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.61,0:09:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭 莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.36,0:09:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我的莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.42,0:09:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.35,0:09:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也會做的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.60,0:09:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭 莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.04,0:09:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可愛的莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.42,0:09:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親大人 相當的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.67,0:09:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.46,0:09:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就陪你一小會兒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.22,0:10:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 你沒法反抗我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.10,0:10:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你很快就射
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.41,0:10:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丟臉丟到家
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.69,0:10:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來啊 快射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.75,0:10:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.37,0:10:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼 快射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.18,0:10:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這軟腳蝦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.81,0:10:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.34,0:10:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.34,0:10:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真美好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.66,0:10:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子也一起愉快一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.43,0:11:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什麼 荒謬
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.49,0:11:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.99,0:11:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子 你的嘴可閒下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.54,0:11:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這難道是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.36,0:11:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的弱點是屁眼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.90,0:11:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.15,0:11:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你這肉棒咬斷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.09,0:11:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.09,0:11:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼不行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.09,0:11:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔族的女人還真是在特別的地方有弱點啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.40,0:11:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.46,0:11:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.80,0:11:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.49,0:11:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡還沒有讓任何人…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.03,0:11:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.04,0:11:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子 你的屁眼還是處女嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.54,0:12:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔族的霧子 屁眼也是處女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.41,0:12:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.68,0:12:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.54,0:12:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你那骯髒的肉棒拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.06,0:12:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 給我記著
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.81,0:12:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這人類
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.12,0:12:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫吧 鬧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.68,0:12:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想看你這副德行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.43,0:12:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.25,0:12:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.31,0:12:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類肉棒的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.25,0:12:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.50,0:12:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.56,0:12:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天我要宰了你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.00,0:12:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.12,0:12:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先把你調教成和莉莉婭他們一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.00,0:12:46.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有我的肉棒就活不下去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.69,0:12:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰會變成那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.86,0:12:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.42,0:12:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.26,0:13:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.32,0:13:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭 把你的手掌全部都放進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.63,0:13:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.56,0:13:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 很不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.13,0:13:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子鬆懈的屁眼開始收緊了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.94,0:13:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.44,0:13:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 你要把手伸進多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.05,0:13:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.36,0:13:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以把手放進子宮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.49,0:13:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭公主 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.11,0:13:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.05,0:13:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面抓緊我的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.55,0:13:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.11,0:13:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.69,0:13:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做這種事的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.84,0:14:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.84,0:14:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子會壞掉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.33,0:14:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.71,0:14:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.71,0:14:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.59,0:14:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊 莉莉婭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.90,0:14:16.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擼的再激烈一點
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.27,0:14:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.57,0:14:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已經不行了 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.06,0:14:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射到你的裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.44,0:14:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好難受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.00,0:14:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.50,0:14:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我射到你骯髒的屁眼裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.53,0:14:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一而再再而三
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.47,0:14:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.91,0:14:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下等的人類…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.37,0:15:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就憑你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.61,0:15:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要掌控本大爺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.62,0:15:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還早十萬年
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.30,0:15:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要能拿到你這手環
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.36,0:15:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.80,0:15:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 給我記著
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.39,0:15:56.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這還真是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.27,0:15:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你們來到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.27,0:16:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽從魔王大人的指示
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.25,0:16:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們來協助帝盧克大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.22,0:16:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是貝魯庫魯 夏布裡耶 亞當
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.47,0:16:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此參見
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.03,0:16:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著情況
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.72,0:16:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不需要我們來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.72,0:16:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.47,0:16:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.10,0:16:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已經遠道而來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.16,0:16:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請盡情指導莉莉婭公主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.65,0:16:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.84,0:16:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始儀式
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.71,0:16:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 動手 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.21,0:16:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（咒文）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.14,0:16:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是有白色騎士之稱的姬騎士莉莉婭公主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.08,0:16:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個不錯的胸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.89,0:17:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯 姬騎士的小穴 是什麼感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.73,0:17:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.70,0:17:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.71,0:17:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相當的…夾得很緊的小穴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.02,0:17:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可真是值得調教
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.46,0:17:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面 在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.34,0:17:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的肉棒的前端
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.15,0:17:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會將你的肌膚的每一片都貼的緊緊的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.59,0:17:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡…小穴…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.27,0:17:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就插屁眼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.15,0:17:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有什麼 進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.28,0:17:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞當閣下還是一點沒變
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.15,0:17:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡屁眼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.84,0:17:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強硬插進不該插進的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.47,0:17:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這感覺太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.78,0:17:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴和屁眼…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.40,0:17:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦呀 哦呀
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.59,0:17:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是下流的嘴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.90,0:18:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己去咬住別人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.00,0:18:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是姬騎士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.94,0:18:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有張不錯的嘴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.51,0:18:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.26,0:18:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然被強幹了 但是好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.33,0:18:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.77,0:18:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.65,0:18:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.72,0:18:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再盡情的揉捏我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.59,0:18:58.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.28,0:19:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也開始渴望我的肉棒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.34,0:19:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰會啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.88,0:19:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨便啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.38,0:19:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就先讓你吃飽我的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.35,0:19:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好喝下去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.42,0:19:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不錯的德行啊 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.17,0:19:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次就換這邊吃個飽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.16,0:19:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好品嚐啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.40,0:19:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.71,0:19:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克王 我也一起可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.72,0:19:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被那邊排擠了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.16,0:19:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.52,0:19:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.73,0:19:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.37,0:19:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.50,0:19:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能救你的人已經不存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.96,0:20:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經協商好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.46,0:20:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用城市1000個女人的高潮作交換
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.60,0:20:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他們把你整治整治
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.54,0:20:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要怪我哦 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.74,0:20:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我居然被區區人類…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.80,0:20:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此等屈辱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.99,0:20:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不甘心嗎？霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.68,0:20:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為你力量源泉的手環
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.31,0:20:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經到手了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.87,0:20:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也沒法再反抗我了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.52,0:20:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克…大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.95,0:20:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.77,0:20:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要嗎 母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.58,0:20:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.45,0:20:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾娜的小穴 想要巨大的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.98,0:20:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丟臉的人啊 母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.79,0:21:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 就把小穴張開 好好祈求啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.79,0:21:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 求您了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.05,0:21:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用巨大的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.30,0:21:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進我的…蕾娜淫亂小穴的深處
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.71,0:21:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我舒服一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.91,0:21:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是魔界也沒有的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.79,0:21:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫亂女皇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.57,0:21:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊 母親大人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.88,0:21:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帝盧克
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.58,0:22:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快射了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.08,0:22:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的肉棒射的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.08,0:22:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龜頭會膨脹 絕對不讓對方逃掉
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.36,0:22:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.30,0:22:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴和屁眼要裂開了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.18,0:22:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒在裡面相互摩擦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.30,0:22:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.99,0:22:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從小穴的深處…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.74,0:22:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 全身都好像變成小穴了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.24,0:22:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管摸哪裡都好有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.37,0:22:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.68,0:22:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也快射精了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.63,0:22:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.01,0:22:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要被純白的東西 玷污全身
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.88,0:22:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.85,0:23:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啊 快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.04,0:23:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.73,0:23:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子 這邊也要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.17,0:23:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將你子宮的深處
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.04,0:23:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都射滿我的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.79,0:23:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.29,0:23:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.36,0:23:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我怎麼能被區區人類
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.98,0:23:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玷污這麼多次
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.48,0:23:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要用人類的精子懷孕 霧子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.30,0:23:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.36,0:24:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.68,0:24:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也在屁眼裡使勁兒的射出來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.43,0:24:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.32,0:24:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉婭大人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.83,0:24:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.64,0:24:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.95,0:24:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是本大爺
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.83,0:24:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別太得意了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.33,0:24:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.83,0:25:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次就是最後的儀式了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.40,0:25:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.53,0:25:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記著嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.28,0:25:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後的儀式裡
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.90,0:25:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公主的高潮不能完全收集的話
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.13,0:25:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.19,0:25:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧子就隨你處置
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.38,0:25:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.00,0:25:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在最後的儀式上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.44,0:25:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能把莉莉婭公主
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.04,0:25:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神聖的高潮全部收集得時候
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.97,0:25:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用你的生命來補償
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.98,0:25:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的儀式只有兩次了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.61,0:25:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,7天時間
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.93,0:25:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.37,0:25:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在下一次儀式上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.93,0:25:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你的頭掉下來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.06,0:25:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是我陷落
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.74,0:26:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是值得一看
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
