[Script Info]
Title: [淫獣学園 La☆BlueGirl 復活篇][MP4][03][第3章][DVD 960x720 x264 AAC]
Original Script:
Original Translation:
Original Timing:
Original Editing:
Script Updated By:
Update Details:
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 640
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point:
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no
Audio File: ?video
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0


[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H0000FFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,1
Style: 22,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.13,0:00:08.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让三千世界欢喜颤动的至福之源
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.83,0:00:10.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,统治那里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.63,0:00:12.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可超越空间与时间
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.07,0:00:17.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自由自在控制人们的烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.83,0:00:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们通往色魔之脑路径 怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.59,0:00:26.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.53,0:00:28.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算知道我也不会说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.75,0:00:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.69,0:00:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,青鬼魔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.59,0:00:31.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.62,0:00:34.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.84,0:00:36.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弥久
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.52,0:00:39.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美童美子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.67,0:00:42.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔幌场众 万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.06,0:00:50.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绿牙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.40,0:01:52.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.42,0:01:54.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我快高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.06,0:01:59.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还要 还要更激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.88,0:02:00.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.42,0:02:04.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美优 我已经不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.34,0:02:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 你要忍住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.65,0:02:09.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我再差一点就高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.64,0:02:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.92,0:02:17.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.49,0:02:21.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出来 全部射在美优体内
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.16,0:02:28.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好多热热的精液在我体内
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.65,0:02:32.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮...美优要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.27,0:02:44.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 还可以再继续做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.26,0:02:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 你该适可而止了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.63,0:02:48.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在妹妹的房间里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.02,0:02:50.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要搞几次你才会满意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.17,0:02:52.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞几次？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.63,0:02:54.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也才做两次而已
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.58,0:02:56.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有两次的话就够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.05,0:02:59.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要把男人带到家里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.04,0:03:04.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为这里离摄影地点最近
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.88,0:03:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.10,0:03:07.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.49,0:03:09.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.74,0:03:12.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子 你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.38,0:03:15.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找出通往色魔之脑的路了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.31,0:03:21.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该不会你忘记了色魔之脑的重要性了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.05,0:03:23.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我并没有忘记...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.13,0:03:25.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.82,0:03:29.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,色魔之脑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.49,0:03:35.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是三千世界中控制一切的宇宙之源 神圣之地
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.13,0:03:37.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,控制那里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.76,0:03:43.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就可超越空间与时间 自由自在掌控众生的烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.02,0:03:46.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经打倒魔幌场众了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.50,0:03:49.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很难保证没有人再觊觎那里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.41,0:03:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.63,0:03:52.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护色魔之脑
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.60,0:03:55.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以一定要找出那条路才行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.37,0:03:58.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,探索那条路的大任就交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.60,0:04:00.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见啰 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.03,0:04:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的床我就要继续使用了呦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.88,0:04:05.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.75,0:04:06.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下呀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.97,0:04:08.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.98,0:04:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是美子的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.58,0:04:15.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是弥久的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.07,0:04:16.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是吹雪的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.92,0:04:19.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么突然搬计算机来 吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.22,0:04:22.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是要使用它嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.44,0:04:24.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍 你去准备饮料来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.78,0:04:26.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.34,0:04:34.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个接这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.59,0:04:36.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.42,0:04:45.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三人都毫无防备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.81,0:04:49.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她们没把我当男人看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.66,0:04:52.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个叫做鼠标啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.39,0:04:55.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我说美子啊 你认真点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.76,0:04:57.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与青鬼魔大王的约定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.60,0:04:58.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你忘记了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.47,0:05:00.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.85,0:05:04.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我们勉强把来袭的魔幌场众跟蝴蝶他们击退
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.35,0:05:10.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道何时色魔之脑可能会再被盯上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.56,0:05:13.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪与弥久才...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.35,0:05:15.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了帮助我 才住在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.14,0:05:17.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,合作搜集资料的不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.49,0:05:19.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是收获是零
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.82,0:05:23.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看来光靠我们要找出通往色魔之脑的路
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.54,0:05:25.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.49,0:05:30.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想从老婆婆那边找弥勒众的族人帮忙 可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.62,0:05:35.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这条线也不顺利呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.22,0:05:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽是这么说 但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.25,0:05:39.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弥勒众大部分的人都分散了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.85,0:05:43.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边就算想找也是找不到线索
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.62,0:05:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.00,0:05:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才要使用计算机
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.31,0:05:50.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,利用网页找
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.72,0:05:53.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做个弥勒众的网页
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.35,0:05:55.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在时代这么进步
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.04,0:05:58.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,失去联络的弥勒众同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.64,0:06:00.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会过来与我们联系也说不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.81,0:06:06.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若能顺便得到色魔之脑的情报 那就一举两得了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.77,0:06:07.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.29,0:06:11.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 你是何时变得这么先进的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.48,0:06:13.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这只是常识而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.43,0:06:16.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍者也得跟上时代的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.07,0:06:23.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鼠标的感觉怎样呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.76,0:06:25.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了 忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.51,0:06:31.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...网页真的能找来弥勒众吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.38,0:06:32.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不试试看怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.25,0:06:37.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别忘记我们使尽各种手段都没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.63,0:06:40.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 总比不做要来得好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.08,0:06:42.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到弥勒众的宗家
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.95,0:06:44.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪是色魔众
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.25,0:06:46.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在的弥勒众
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.74,0:06:48.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只剩下忍忍与弥久
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.04,0:06:51.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这都是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.61,0:06:56.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,总之 若是有弥勒众利用计算机来联系的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.10,0:07:00.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们可能因而辗转得到色魔之脑的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.27,0:07:02.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这件事全部看你的了 吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.33,0:07:03.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.48,0:07:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们完全不会计算机
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.75,0:07:09.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.38,0:07:13.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在学校有没有朋友会做网页
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.48,0:07:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦...吹雪 你不是会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.30,0:07:18.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是很努力想跟上时代
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.32,0:07:20.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是还未出师呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.14,0:07:24.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鼠鼠 鼠鼠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.37,0:07:28.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍 你趁乱做什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.89,0:07:32.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人类大脑的作用
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.47,0:07:35.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有许多不明的部分
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.28,0:07:36.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有种说法认为人的大脑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.99,0:07:40.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一半以上是没用到的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.23,0:07:44.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连人类的脑都搞不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.85,0:07:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,色魔之脑当然更难搞定了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.66,0:07:51.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都怎样才能到达那里都不晓得了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.68,0:08:03.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.74,0:08:05.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,百合
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.71,0:08:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于跟哥哥联络上了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.93,0:08:09.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他说从计算机店回来时会顺路过去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.95,0:08:10.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.13,0:08:13.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有说一个小时后就到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.25,0:08:15.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.69,0:08:16.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 琉璃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.04,0:08:18.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这没有什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.55,0:08:22.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴有机会跟你亲近
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.13,0:08:23.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.38,0:08:26.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能跟琉璃相处得这么好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.75,0:08:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也没想到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.19,0:08:36.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了 再那里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.17,0:08:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥 怎么这么快呀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.09,0:08:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 琉璃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.43,0:08:44.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是突然怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.69,0:08:48.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这令人有点激动有点心酸的感觉是...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.41,0:08:59.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.83,0:09:06.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,初次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.04,0:09:08.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是琉璃的大哥 真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.89,0:09:10.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平时多谢你照顾舍妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.90,0:09:12.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我是美童美子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.06,0:09:14.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勉强拜托你帮忙 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.01,0:09:16.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.54,0:09:17.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么脸红红的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.48,0:09:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.60,0:09:21.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别因为平时没女人缘
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.07,0:09:24.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就对美子出手是不行的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.78,0:09:25.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.17,0:09:28.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在朋友面前 你胡说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.60,0:09:30.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 哥 剩下的交给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.28,0:09:31.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.25,0:09:33.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天我还有事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.13,0:09:35.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天在学校见
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.53,0:09:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.51,0:09:39.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么搞的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.32,0:09:42.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明是第一次见面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.01,0:09:45.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却有怀念的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.10,0:09:52.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.65,0:09:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就得暂时等一阵子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.03,0:10:04.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.98,0:10:07.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我脸上有什么东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.69,0:10:09.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.52,0:10:10.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.74,0:10:13.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我拿饮料过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.70,0:10:15.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.21,0:10:26.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.13,0:10:37.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.89,0:10:39.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.07,0:10:43.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听说你带会作网页的人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.75,0:10:46.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.65,0:10:58.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天很谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.71,0:11:04.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福 吹雪她们才不用为网页烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.65,0:11:05.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.59,0:11:07.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这点小事随时可以找我帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.47,0:11:11.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.52,0:11:13.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.46,0:11:16.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,计算机方面如果有什么不懂的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.91,0:11:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽管可以过来问我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.81,0:11:19.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就麻烦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.61,0:11:26.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子 成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.25,0:11:28.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马上有类似弥勒众的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.93,0:11:30.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们的网页联络了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.98,0:11:31.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.32,0:11:33.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.22,0:11:36.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,关于弥勒里之桃花那个题目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.99,0:11:41.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个人回答 是不是上一代弥勒众宗加美童桃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.58,0:11:43.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我问他住在哪里 竟然就住在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.81,0:11:45.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在忍忍就去接他过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.43,0:11:47.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到这么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.77,0:11:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就能找到弥勒众的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.38,0:11:51.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.72,0:11:54.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 请进 不要客气
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.49,0:11:56.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.01,0:11:59.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.94,0:12:02.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你该不会就是...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.19,0:12:05.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,网页上的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.53,0:12:08.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我叫加奈子 美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.49,0:12:10.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.82,0:12:13.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直梦想着这一天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.81,0:12:14.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被弥勒众宗家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.28,0:12:16.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美童美子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.98,0:12:19.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,召见的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.69,0:13:03.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊大人...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.72,0:13:05.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你别太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.37,0:13:10.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过世的奶奶从小就交代我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.48,0:13:15.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将来有一天要为弥勒众宗家的美童大人效命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.81,0:13:18.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以从小时候就教我淫术
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.93,0:13:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你也修炼过淫术
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.40,0:13:22.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.91,0:13:25.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平时我跟一般人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.30,0:13:27.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到看护学校上学
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.89,0:13:28.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.12,0:13:34.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不知道怎么跟弥勒众的宗家联络
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.56,0:13:36.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过去一直孤孤单单的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.16,0:13:38.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.92,0:13:39.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.50,0:13:42.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道有像你这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.49,0:13:49.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是在常去的网页上偶然间看到弥勒众的暗语
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.11,0:13:51.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就想搞不好是...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.74,0:13:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,结果就真的有如做梦般的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.12,0:14:00.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遇到了我最崇拜的弥勒众宗家的美童美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.41,0:14:02.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.64,0:14:05.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子 我没这种兴趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.24,0:14:09.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 你也会淫术吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.30,0:14:10.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.78,0:14:12.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.87,0:14:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.28,0:14:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子 你就当她姊姊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.58,0:14:21.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 总之不管做什么事 最重要的就是经验
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.34,0:14:23.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个太过份了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.74,0:14:27.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就只会在旁边看戏说风凉话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.09,0:14:41.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.46,0:14:43.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.11,0:14:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对于美童美子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.70,0:14:46.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要放着不管吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.90,0:14:50.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.12,0:14:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想接近色魔之脑的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.55,0:14:55.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不论是谁...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.98,0:14:56.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都不会破例放过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.20,0:15:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把她诱入老地方收拾掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.42,0:15:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.64,0:15:04.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.78,0:15:19.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,命运又再度重复上演吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.57,0:16:35.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.40,0:16:39.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.13,0:16:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,触手来自计算机
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.04,0:16:45.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弥久
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.83,0:16:46.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.02,0:16:50.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂...加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.12,0:16:52.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.76,0:16:54.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.26,0:17:03.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.27,0:17:05.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.15,0:17:08.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是稍一离开
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.02,0:17:10.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么计算机会伸出触手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.97,0:17:14.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生命并没有危险
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.08,0:17:17.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是她失去意识了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.97,0:17:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就好像醒着做梦一样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.87,0:17:22.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呈空白状态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.79,0:17:24.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我见习的医院
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.81,0:17:26.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有这方面的专科医生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.75,0:17:29.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,专门做睡眠治疗研究的医生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.99,0:17:32.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马上送去请他看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.66,0:17:33.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.86,0:17:34.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.85,0:17:37.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先想办法让吹雪恢复意识吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.12,0:17:38.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.38,0:17:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.35,0:17:42.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能拜托那位医生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.71,0:17:44.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 马上跟他联络看看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.25,0:17:45.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.01,0:17:47.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶快叫救护车来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.15,0:17:48.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.54,0:18:02.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.29,0:18:04.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一定是在梦中被强暴了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.04,0:18:15.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在梦中被强暴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.20,0:18:17.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该从何救起呢...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.02,0:18:22.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子 吹雪能够恢复吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.01,0:18:25.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟随见习的那位医生 绝对没有问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.66,0:18:28.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是睡眠治疗的权威
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.40,0:18:30.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国际上出名的博士
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.00,0:18:35.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全国热心的年轻医生都很尊敬他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.10,0:18:37.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.71,0:18:43.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚打了镇定剂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.09,0:18:45.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该会暂时平稳一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.59,0:18:47.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趁这段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.63,0:18:50.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会找出让她痛苦的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.46,0:18:53.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能够看到吹雪做的梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.23,0:18:58.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 睡眠分成雷姆睡眠与非雷姆睡眠这两种
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.31,0:19:02.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪所做的梦是属于非雷姆睡眠
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.91,0:19:05.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们称之为觉醒梦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.95,0:19:07.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是非常接近现实的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.49,0:19:09.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉醒梦?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.79,0:19:10.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.90,0:19:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,部份世界出名的发现
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.50,0:19:15.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,科学原理的诺贝尔科学家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.37,0:19:19.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及看透人生和宇宙真理的异人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.83,0:19:23.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是在觉醒梦中苏醒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.17,0:19:25.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将梦中得到的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.03,0:19:28.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,向全世界发表而得到盛名的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.31,0:19:31.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是吹雪现在看到的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.16,0:19:32.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.18,0:19:36.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生在她接近想知道的真实之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.32,0:19:40.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常逼真的梦之考验
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.00,0:19:41.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.40,0:19:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当吹雪一心一意想找出通往色魔之脑的信道时
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.66,0:19:48.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而引来淫兽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.42,0:19:50.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.41,0:19:51.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请想办法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.63,0:19:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把吹雪的意识平安唤醒
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.58,0:19:54.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.97,0:19:56.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我尽力试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.67,0:20:03.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我是美子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.15,0:20:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.03,0:20:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.54,0:20:07.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.71,0:20:08.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.78,0:20:09.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在能与你见面吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.86,0:20:12.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你看一个东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.90,0:20:14.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.67,0:20:17.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我不能离开
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.11,0:20:18.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,地点我写在邮件上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.40,0:20:20.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定要来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.92,0:20:22.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是很重要的事 我等你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.93,0:20:23.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.91,0:20:25.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.63,0:20:26.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.56,0:20:30.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上次帮我们做网页的真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.63,0:20:31.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我马上去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.00,0:20:34.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都想见我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.95,0:20:37.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要给我看很重要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.26,0:20:38.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的声音很急...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.31,0:20:40.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.95,0:20:42.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.00,0:20:44.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是弥久...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.43,0:20:45.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪她...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.56,0:20:47.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.04,0:20:49.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.49,0:20:50.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会陪在她身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.86,0:20:51.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弥久
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.75,0:20:53.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.04,0:20:54.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.27,0:20:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.90,0:20:58.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.97,0:21:00.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.73,0:21:01.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.82,0:21:02.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.07,0:21:03.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.79,0:21:06.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.18,0:21:08.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要到什么地方去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.25,0:21:09.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样太过份了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.09,0:21:12.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人家我不想与美子姊姊分开
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.02,0:21:14.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子也要一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.28,0:21:15.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.30,0:21:16.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.73,0:21:19.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能照顾吹雪的...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.01,0:21:21.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就只有加奈子你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.64,0:21:22.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.79,0:21:24.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然是美子姊姊的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.66,0:21:25.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子一定会接受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.61,0:21:30.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.88,0:21:33.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,该找出恶梦的真面目了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.69,0:21:33.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.45,0:21:35.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.97,0:21:38.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.15,0:21:45.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大堂里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.31,0:22:02.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是适合开启道路的牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.77,0:22:06.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样色魔们就会满足了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.68,0:22:07.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.71,0:22:09.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些人在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.12,0:22:14.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从刚才看她挣扎的样子就知道是好货
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.16,0:22:17.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开启道路之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.50,0:22:20.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就好好再跟她玩一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.03,0:22:22.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把色魔呼唤出来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.53,0:22:23.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这之前
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.52,0:22:25.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就先跟她玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.26,0:22:28.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呼唤色魔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.60,0:22:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.00,0:22:39.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.94,0:22:53.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.99,0:22:55.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要折磨我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.85,0:22:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.52,0:23:07.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,医生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.36,0:23:08.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.54,0:23:10.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,弥久
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.89,0:23:13.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请与吹雪的觉醒梦同步
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.65,0:23:15.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与吹雪的觉醒梦同步
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.99,0:23:17.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种事做得到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.83,0:23:18.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事态紧急
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.45,0:23:22.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觉醒梦的痛苦若继续持续下去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.34,0:23:25.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她的精神就会崩溃
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.20,0:23:28.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必须赶快有人与觉醒梦同步
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.81,0:23:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把她从梦中救出来才行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.18,0:23:32.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.41,0:23:40.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.50,0:23:41.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快上车
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.38,0:23:42.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.91,0:23:49.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你会搭末班车来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.59,0:23:51.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来不报太大期望的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.07,0:23:53.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴能在遇见你 美子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.48,0:23:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.71,0:23:58.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.31,0:24:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种感觉...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:04.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为何我会对真帆产生这种感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.40,0:24:14.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.40,0:24:15.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.75,0:24:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.44,0:24:52.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.06,0:24:55.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.03,0:24:57.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.92,0:25:06.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.43,0:25:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.00,0:25:10.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.11,0:25:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.66,0:25:13.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.03,0:25:17.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,五色色魔来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.22,0:25:20.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把她也抓来当牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.10,0:25:28.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.45,0:25:31.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.73,0:25:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.91,0:25:34.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是青鬼魔的女儿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.97,0:25:37.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,青鬼魔 不认识
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.38,0:25:40.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这女孩在胡说些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.93,0:25:42.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很新鲜
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.52,0:25:44.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是好货啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.19,0:25:46.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然不知道爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.11,0:25:48.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不是色魔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.80,0:25:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底这里是哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.24,0:25:58.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.53,0:26:01.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 真帆 不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.54,0:26:02.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.60,0:26:06.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.43,0:26:22.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以 美子 不能有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.14,0:26:24.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆在看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.13,0:26:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这点攻击不算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.29,0:26:34.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 拜托 别再继续了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.78,0:26:49.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不行 唯有那里...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.89,0:26:51.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能在真帆面前
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.65,0:26:53.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要在真帆的面前...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.00,0:26:54.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,饶了我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.18,0:26:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.42,0:27:21.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经要高潮了...高潮了...要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.26,0:27:23.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.06,0:27:26.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 真帆 不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.31,0:27:26.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.08,0:27:42.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 已经要高潮了 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.50,0:27:47.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.33,0:27:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.69,0:27:54.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真帆

