[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 960
PlayResY: 720
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,45,&H00ffffff,&H0000ffff,&H00943c5a,&H80551055,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,15,15,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.59,0:00:35.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們是甚麼人？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.60,0:00:41.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讓你瞧瞧這個實驗的成果
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.01,0:00:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那個
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.83,0:01:10.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女...女人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.90,0:01:12.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怪物要做甚麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.83,0:01:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為甚麼會這樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.32,0:01:34.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是貴國製造出來的淫獸怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.72,0:01:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是具有搜查裝置的\N世界最強大的殺人武器
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.73,0:01:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確如此，他是最厲害的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.02,0:02:10.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他滿腦子想的就只有做愛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:41.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，怎麼會這樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:06.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...不要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.48,0:03:12.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快停止吧，這樣下去會出事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.05,0:03:42.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.54,0:04:09.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.70,0:04:35.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎麼會\N製造出這麼恐怖的怪物啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.92,0:04:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是上天的懲罰呀\N才會做成如此結果
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.01,0:05:13.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類是可以變成神的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.54,0:05:17.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然，至少也能變成惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.50,0:05:36.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Spy of Darkness (淫獸VS女スパイ)
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.37,0:05:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[香 港]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.78,0:05:52.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.51,0:05:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太美妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.79,0:06:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快受不了呢，來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.47,0:06:17.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.21,0:06:30.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深一點...再插深一點啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.56,0:06:40.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了，射吧...射到裡面去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.86,0:07:12.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.06,0:07:13.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長官
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.46,0:07:16.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳那邊都順利解決了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.53,0:07:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N李老頭剛剛已被我幹掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.80,0:07:21.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N李老頭剛剛已被我幹掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.07,0:07:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他所偽造的有價證券\N也被我毀掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.81,0:07:28.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡的損失可減到最小
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.08,0:07:29.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.48,0:07:34.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來想讓妳好好地\N玩賞香港之夜，但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.48,0:07:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研究室的情況如何呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.55,0:07:40.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國家機密暗碼，第四級
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.22,0:07:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四級？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.69,0:07:49.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也會指示蕾拉和席婉\N妳們需要Q機動小組的協助
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.03,0:07:51.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解，我立即回國
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.31,0:08:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化名：安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.31,0:08:05.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內閣秘密調查室特務機關
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.18,0:08:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[Q機動小組] 隊長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.78,0:08:09.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本名，年齡，籍貫等，一概不詳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.52,0:08:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精通武術，狙擊高手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.12,0:08:22.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[紐 約]
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.35,0:08:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.02,0:08:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太棒...棒透了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.77,0:09:05.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.57,0:09:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心都快飛了，好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.65,0:09:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高...高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.59,0:09:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解，長官
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.99,0:09:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉，沒辦法陪你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.73,0:09:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下交給CIA處理了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.86,0:09:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是乖乖地，說實話比較好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.60,0:09:37.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰叫你要盜取國家機密呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.61,0:09:42.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CIA人員的辦事態度\N可不像我這麼溫柔哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.55,0:09:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化名：蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.55,0:09:48.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內閣秘密調查室特務機關
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.35,0:09:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[Q機動小組] 隊員
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.42,0:09:52.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本名，年齡，籍貫等，一概不詳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.29,0:09:54.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,電腦專家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.82,0:10:02.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[巴 黎]
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.32,0:10:23.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳真像是一件藝術品呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.53,0:10:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的，繼續做呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.40,0:10:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈囉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.47,0:10:44.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是席婉嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.68,0:10:52.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.29,0:11:04.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂! 妳這是幹甚麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.83,0:11:11.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本來是讓你爽到底\N當做是我的賀禮呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.03,0:11:13.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是，突然我有急事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.04,0:11:21.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所製造的一萬元偽鈔\N看來像極了藝術品，可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.11,0:11:24.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本政府方面，卻傷透了腦筋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.86,0:11:39.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化名：席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.66,0:11:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內閣秘密調查室特務機關
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.53,0:11:43.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[Q機動小組] 隊員
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.26,0:11:45.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本名，年齡，籍貫等，一概不詳
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.40,0:11:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆破高手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.80,0:11:51.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[東 京]
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.61,0:12:07.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們全到齊了，好久不見呀\N能見到妳們，我真是高興啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.15,0:12:09.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀! 真令人吃驚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.89,0:12:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.23,0:12:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一向都不在乎我們嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.63,0:12:17.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你常說我們只是你的棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.90,0:12:22.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出任務喪命，一切與你無關
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.10,0:12:29.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不會忘記我的部下的\N尤其是不忘說客套話
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.38,0:12:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就別浪費精力啦，長官
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.18,0:12:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們所需要的\N就只有你的命令而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.65,0:12:43.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是我們Q機動小組的\N化名美女情報員
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.19,0:12:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言歸正傳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.06,0:12:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我國政府委託民間製造的\N生化開發計劃中的實驗人體
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.67,0:12:58.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被不明人物搶奪逃跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.81,0:13:04.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這案子真辣手耶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.14,0:13:06.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歹徒不是省油的燈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.68,0:13:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實驗人體，是一名叫阿龍的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.35,0:13:13.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在研究所內，大家叫他淫獸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.49,0:13:17.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫獸？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.09,0:13:19.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遺傳因子的操控不當
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.36,0:13:22.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,造成腦內充滿性衝動，破壞慾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.76,0:13:26.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因而變成不斷強暴婦女的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.24,0:13:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本次會議的結論是\N生化開發計劃的強制取消
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.04,0:13:38.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.11,0:13:45.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果政府開發軍事用途的\N人類改造計劃，以及...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.59,0:13:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,製造出了淫獸這種怪物的事實證據\N留下的話就糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.06,0:13:56.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我國將受到國際的譴責
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.46,0:13:59.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國際社會的信用\N也會蕩然無存啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.27,0:14:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正式命令Q機動小組
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.54,0:14:05.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立即找出奪走淫獸的歹徒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.67,0:14:08.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並且消滅歹徒及淫獸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.01,0:14:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.36,0:14:32.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手...不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.08,0:15:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不斷地強暴婦女的淫獸\N是不會中途罷手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.68,0:15:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.48,0:15:28.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，立刻查出這兩天內\N婦女遇害的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.56,0:15:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.70,0:15:43.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，資料過多，找不出來呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.64,0:15:45.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒用的電腦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.31,0:15:46.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳說甚麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.51,0:15:52.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可沒時間爭吵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.52,0:16:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時候，只有問專家最可靠了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.09,0:16:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，阿龍，在這裡不能用
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.03,0:16:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不好？只要你乖乖聽話\N你想要多少女人，我都找給你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.19,0:17:07.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了，阿龍
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.26,0:17:09.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是最棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.54,0:17:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂! 帥哥們，有些事想問問
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.10,0:17:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有問題要問你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.50,0:17:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下，辦完事再問嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.51,0:18:02.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天倒楣到，連女人都被搶了\N剛好今天疏解疏解
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.94,0:18:37.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們知道，你們把受害的女子\N當成是食物一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.21,0:18:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說甚麼女人被搶\N到底是怎麼一回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.68,0:18:43.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖地招供，是為了你好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.68,0:18:46.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們是...女警嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.62,0:18:52.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是女警就好了\N她們還會對你們溫柔點
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.83,0:18:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不招供，馬上要你脖子斷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.10,0:19:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上，我們在橫濱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.91,0:19:14.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是用強拉輪暴攝影威脅的老手法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.32,0:19:19.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手...住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.79,0:19:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果那傢伙...怪物不在的話\N就好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.93,0:19:29.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.33,0:19:30.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是...是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.80,0:19:37.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣？舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.94,0:19:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不想妳的丟人錄影帶外流的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.01,0:19:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就乖乖聽我們的話吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.74,0:19:45.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請饒了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.88,0:19:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，妳是我們的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.09,0:20:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.31,0:20:23.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是甚麼東西？她是我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.86,0:20:34.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太看扁我呢，要你好看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.74,0:20:44.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇! 怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.21,0:20:46.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕，被瞧見了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.02,0:21:03.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了沒有？走為上策呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.78,0:21:27.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.40,0:21:46.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人作嘔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.07,0:21:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們還真的是不斷地強姦婦女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.60,0:21:55.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無窮無盡的慾望\N也許淫獸的原形，就是人類啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.28,0:22:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是最後一卷
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.63,0:22:14.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.03,0:22:16.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請饒了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.83,0:22:20.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，妳是我們的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.10,0:22:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是甚麼東西？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.24,0:22:29.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.98,0:22:34.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎我們沒搞錯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.78,0:22:37.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫獸果然是兇狠無比
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.85,0:22:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇! 怪物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.93,0:22:47.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒帶一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.46,0:22:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.27,0:22:55.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫停
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.67,0:23:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是凡內莎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.14,0:23:01.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.47,0:23:08.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她專門盜取國家機密\N也不管主義主張地四處亂賣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.21,0:23:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫無主張的激進恐怖份子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.42,0:23:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯，就是她啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.55,0:23:18.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是她，一定會搶走淫獸\N我猜的準沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.70,0:23:29.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥，你認不認識她們？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.37,0:23:30.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不認識
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.64,0:23:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.51,0:23:40.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你告訴我，原本想陪你玩玩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.34,0:24:08.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.48,0:24:16.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.09,0:24:26.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾也讓我們嚐嚐新鮮的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.96,0:24:31.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想到那怪物和女孩們做愛\N真是令人受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.57,0:24:34.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.91,0:24:40.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖聽話吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.53,0:25:01.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有問題
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.95,0:25:29.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫獸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.76,0:25:31.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡內莎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.96,0:25:39.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了，我在橫濱港貨輪...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.43,0:25:43.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐，妳在幹甚麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.30,0:25:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傷腦筋耶! 我們也有私隱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.04,0:25:51.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.78,0:25:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死，那女孩不是普通人物
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.05,0:26:01.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.13,0:26:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.68,0:26:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫獸
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.76,0:26:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...住手
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.49,0:26:43.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿龍，住手
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.36,0:26:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下，再讓你好好爽一爽
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.90,0:26:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，蕾拉，怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.37,0:26:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.11,0:27:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有發現嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.71,0:27:05.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想她可能被凡內莎抓走了\N不會錯的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.72,0:27:09.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的，蕾拉除了電腦以外\N其他的都不會
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.19,0:27:13.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在說這些也沒有用啦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.34,0:27:31.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是蕾拉的...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.97,0:27:59.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈，可愛的小女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.51,0:28:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡內莎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.91,0:28:05.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳知道我的名字\N妳是日本的情報員？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.25,0:28:15.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想好戲應該上場了才對\N再加上妳這美人，更棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.74,0:28:31.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.41,0:28:35.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以上囉，盡情地享用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.81,0:28:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...別過來
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.55,0:28:45.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.63,0:29:01.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.11,0:29:09.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳真是口是心非呀
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.89,0:29:59.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不乖乖地回答的話，就要你好看
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.23,0:30:04.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡內莎是不是在這艘船內？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.17,0:30:07.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不肯告訴我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.10,0:30:14.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈...謝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.98,0:30:19.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.00,0:30:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了，阿龍，只要你聽話
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.47,0:30:48.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會把全世界的女人都給你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.75,0:30:54.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.49,0:31:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.02,0:31:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們是誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.36,0:31:03.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.70,0:31:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連肚皮上都有那玩意耶
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.70,0:31:21.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜，席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.73,0:31:43.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.93,0:31:46.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要過來呀
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.68,0:31:59.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡內莎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.88,0:32:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於來了比較難纏的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.49,0:32:14.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們要不要嚐嚐這玩意？\N有意想不到的快感哦
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.23,0:32:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是開船的時候了\N馬上就可以脫離日本了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.17,0:32:32.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡內莎，妳難道不曉得嗎？\N淫獸對人類的傷害有多大嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.38,0:32:37.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與我無關...對我而言\N淫獸只不過是貨物罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.78,0:32:42.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫獸他充滿了性衝動與破壞力呀
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.79,0:32:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果連他僅存的一點理性\N都喪失了的話，就糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.87,0:32:59.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼說都沒有用\N他是我的奴隸呀
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.87,0:33:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳們就準備等死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.08,0:33:09.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時就只有我和淫獸而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.44,0:33:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他開始不對勁了，終於大發獸性
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.45,0:33:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為何...不聽我的命令？再...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.39,0:33:55.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.19,0:33:56.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤退吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.81,0:34:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，為甚麼喪命於此地呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.15,0:34:20.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.36,0:34:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不能讓蕾拉白白犧牲
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.43,0:34:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.23,0:34:30.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.24,0:34:47.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整艘船都即將被淫獸所控制\N只不過是時間的問題罷
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.78,0:34:49.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的辦法，就是炸沉整艘船
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.45,0:34:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是，在東京灣是無法炸沉的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.79,0:34:59.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要在船舶一進入太平洋
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.26,0:35:01.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在船內佈置炸藥
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.46,0:35:02.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後再啟動爆破裝置
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.93,0:35:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即可將船沉入大海
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.16,0:35:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就沒問題了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.02,0:35:35.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後的一顆炸彈\N裝置在燃料箱上就大功告成
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.03,0:35:36.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了，走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.64,0:35:43.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.78,0:35:51.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.51,0:35:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.18,0:35:57.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走，淫獸拜託妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.58,0:35:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席婉
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.85,0:36:02.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走啦，不要拖啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.83,0:36:47.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，我去陪妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.52,0:37:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後的子彈了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.76,0:37:50.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.42,0:38:56.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了...席婉，蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.17,0:39:12.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不甘心這樣子就死
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.34,0:39:41.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是甚麼妖怪呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.94,0:39:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩最後一顆子彈了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.08,0:39:54.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定要想辦法\N除掉這個淫獸怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.83,0:40:12.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了我的兩名隊員\N我不甘願就此輸給了淫獸
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.85,0:40:31.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席婉，我會替妳報仇
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.13,0:40:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕾拉，我去陪妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.78,0:41:28.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任務檔案
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.25,0:41:30.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO 164-5-19-2339092
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.18,0:41:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四級
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.05,0:41:33.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功消滅敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.92,0:41:35.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化名：安娜，席婉，蕾拉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.85,0:41:37.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然三名情報員的屍體
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.59,0:41:39.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,未能找到，但證實三人全死
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.86,0:41:41.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...之後
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.26,0:41:45.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本檔案永久禁止任何人閱讀
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.50,0:42:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Spy of Darkness (淫獸VS女スパイ)\N** 全編完 **
