[Script Info]
;   This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
;   For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
;   go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
;   or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;   
;   Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,5,5,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.20,0:00:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.21,0:00:48.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I'm  coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.21,0:00:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.20,0:01:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流星  而且有两颗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.81,0:01:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里  这不稀奇吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.81,0:01:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  我要先许愿！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.81,0:02:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在欧洲  那代表不吉利啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.82,0:02:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你要许什么愿啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.83,0:02:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果生下来的是女孩子便好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.83,0:02:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？认真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.83,0:02:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说谎的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.77,0:02:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟说这种不吉利的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.77,0:02:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对付这种家伙  要从后面来！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.28,0:02:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在这地方！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.80,0:02:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个吓了一跳啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.81,0:03:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那边新闻也有说的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.81,0:03:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  想不到在我附近
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.81,0:03:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有这种东西掉下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.81,0:03:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  担心我打电话给你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.82,0:03:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.82,0:03:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  如果你来这里的话我会更高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.76,0:03:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.77,0:03:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经……
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.77,0:03:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个月没见过面了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.78,0:03:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.78,0:03:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂寞……寂寞得……
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.78,0:03:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我……
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.78,0:03:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被其他男孩子引诱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.79,0:03:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也完全没有去玩啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.79,0:03:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挂念着勇！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.79,0:03:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着勇的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.79,0:03:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心不断地跳
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.80,0:03:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且……
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.80,0:03:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那儿已经湿淋淋的了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.80,0:04:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勇也有这感觉吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.80,0:04:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那话儿越来越大了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.81,0:04:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说笑了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.81,0:04:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.80,0:05:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.81,0:05:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说那陨石上确认到有生命吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.74,0:05:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的话  以我的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.68,0:05:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能接线给你？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.68,0:05:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才在火星陨石上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.68,0:05:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到有机体的残骸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.69,0:05:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是那样简单的了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.69,0:05:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有较明确的生命痕迹？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.69,0:05:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是痕迹！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.69,0:05:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是实际生存着的！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.63,0:05:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生存着？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.63,0:05:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确来说是增殖中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.63,0:05:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是以很高的速度
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.63,0:05:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像亚米巴一般的单细胞有机体
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.64,0:05:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会有什么影响吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.64,0:05:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例如未知的病原体之类
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.58,0:05:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难这样快下判断
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.58,0:05:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总之不是传染病之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.58,0:05:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是……   只是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.59,0:06:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是身为科学家的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.59,0:06:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能这有机体
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.59,0:06:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是前所未有的发现
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.59,0:06:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以打电话给你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.60,0:06:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望就快想出对策
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.60,0:06:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  马上告诉首相
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.60,0:06:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上组织对策部门
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.60,0:06:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  筑波君  相信你也明白
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.54,0:06:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是极其秘密行事的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.54,0:06:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你范围内的人也下禁止令吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.55,0:06:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.95,0:10:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙淋上醋酸也没事的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.75,0:10:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来迟了一步了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.75,0:10:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？  发生什么事了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.75,0:10:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们马上把这样本和触肢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.75,0:10:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去冷冻保存
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.76,0:10:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.69,0:10:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天晚上7点过后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.69,0:10:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在涉谷的某处后巷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.70,0:10:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了有4名少女牺牲的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.70,0:10:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎奇杀人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.70,0:10:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么今天交通会这样堵塞呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.71,0:10:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危险！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.71,0:10:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.72,0:11:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以睡在那种地方呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.73,0:11:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会为你看病的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.73,0:11:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.54,0:11:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信大家都有看过管生君的报告
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.55,0:11:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再确认一次的是：
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.55,0:11:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近频频发生的猎奇杀人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.55,0:11:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北海道、仙台、岩宫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.56,0:11:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有东京、横滨……
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.56,0:11:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直像有意志般在南下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.56,0:11:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么首先看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.56,0:11:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾担当陨石调查  化学系的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.57,0:11:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前天被杀害的筑波不二子的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.50,0:11:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,验尸报告
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.21,0:11:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是总担化验科长铃鹿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.21,0:12:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到北海道警察帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.21,0:12:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结合在道内发生的陨石坠落
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.22,0:12:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近频发的猎奇杀人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.22,0:12:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有筑波所员被杀害事件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.22,0:12:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得出了有关联的结论
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.36,0:12:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有关联？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.23,0:12:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一连串猎奇杀人事件的受害者和
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.23,0:12:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,筑波所员都有被强奸的痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.24,0:12:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害者的子宫内
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.24,0:12:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有类似精液的物体
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.24,0:12:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据DNA鉴定的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.25,0:12:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫人吃惊的是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.25,0:12:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些都拥有同一构造
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.25,0:12:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是说……
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.26,0:12:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指同一犯人所做的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.26,0:12:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎奇杀人事件的犯罪时间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.20,0:12:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和筑波所员被杀的犯罪时间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.20,0:12:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起来推断的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.20,0:12:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.20,0:13:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  还有一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.21,0:13:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.21,0:13:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信属于加害者的精液DNA
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.15,0:13:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我们手头所有生物的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.15,0:13:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DNA组织
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.15,0:13:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不一致！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.15,0:13:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.15,0:13:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以相信的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.15,0:13:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残留在被害者体内的精子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.09,0:13:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不存在于地球上！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.09,0:13:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一附着在陨石上的有机体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.10,0:13:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,筑波小姐留下的资料
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.10,0:13:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和残留在受害者体内的DNA组织
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.10,0:13:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当酷似
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.10,0:13:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.10,0:13:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说那是像亚米巴般的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.11,0:13:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单细胞动物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.11,0:13:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外宇宙来的接触吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.11,0:13:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,筑波君所说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.11,0:13:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一向以来的生物不同的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.12,0:13:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察官！   是！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.12,0:13:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集结警视署的总警力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.06,0:13:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把预测今后会发生事故的地点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.99,0:13:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点加以警戒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.99,0:13:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.03,0:14:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是新的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.03,0:14:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据事件发生的次序
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.03,0:14:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把收回来的样本综合来看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.04,0:14:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现了DNA的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.04,0:14:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正急速起变化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.04,0:14:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不断和接触的有机体同化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.04,0:14:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断增殖  可怕的生命力量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.05,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  更可怕的是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害者的生殖器官
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.05,0:14:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还生存着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.05,0:14:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.05,0:14:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确来说是被使它生存着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.06,0:14:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从精子中那爆发性的能量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.06,0:15:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.06,0:15:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的推论
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.06,0:15:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但相信是事实！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.07,0:15:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.00,0:15:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能力保护自己的蛋的虫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.94,0:15:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会把自己的蛋混进其他生物做蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.94,0:15:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使其成长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.94,0:15:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事态很紧迫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.94,0:15:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受害由北海道开始南下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且越来越快
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.95,0:15:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带陨石来到东京
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.95,0:15:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为了致命伤吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.96,0:15:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更可怕的是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.96,0:15:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陨石是生存着的精子之源
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.96,0:15:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是外星怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那陨石才是生命体
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.96,0:15:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是单体
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.97,0:15:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸收了女人的精气后成长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.97,0:15:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人的子宫培养了外星人的后代
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.97,0:15:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是可怕的侵略
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.91,0:15:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是比喻
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.91,0:15:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果日本的……不
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.91,0:15:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界中的女性都被那家伙强暴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.92,0:15:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底会怎么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.92,0:16:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在太少样本  但……
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.92,0:16:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人被杀女人被播种
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.92,0:16:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约在一年后
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.93,0:16:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推定二十亿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.93,0:16:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全世界吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.93,0:16:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是日本内
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.93,0:16:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为证据的现场
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.93,0:16:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以二十万人口的都市为中心南下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.94,0:16:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信这家伙是对只有女人才有
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.87,0:16:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的东西产生反应的特征
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.88,0:16:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以这样的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.88,0:16:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那家伙和我们人类是不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.88,0:16:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是最近
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.89,0:16:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有根据踏足地面的力度和体温
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.82,0:16:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来分辨性别的感应器出现
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.82,0:16:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例如嗅到荷尔蒙的气味等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.83,0:16:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以都市为中心南下也可以想像
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.77,0:16:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把自卫队个幕僚都叫来总部
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.77,0:16:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有是向总理报告！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.79,0:17:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想不到
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.79,0:17:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到你有这嗜好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.79,0:17:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真真正正的爱好者呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.80,0:17:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢我的东西吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.80,0:17:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我最喜欢这个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.80,0:17:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.80,0:17:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在涉谷捡起你时  说真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.74,0:17:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你是危险的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.74,0:17:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我多些……
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.75,0:17:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也来啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.75,0:17:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来我这里……
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.76,0:17:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快啊……
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.76,0:17:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你那热辣辣的给我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.76,0:17:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人行啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.77,0:17:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.77,0:18:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力些！  用力些啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.78,0:18:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放深一些啊  把你们的……
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.78,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的……
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.78,0:18:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.79,0:18:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不成！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.79,0:18:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的……放入我的口中！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.73,0:18:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.73,0:18:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要吮到最后一滴……
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.68,0:18:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真淫乱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.68,0:18:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也真是因为喜欢这个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.62,0:18:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而四处去玩的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.62,0:18:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我真是第一次遇上这么窄的洞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.62,0:18:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是有点像处女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.56,0:18:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你傻的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.56,0:18:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后洞怎么可能不窄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.56,0:19:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是一般出来玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.57,0:19:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都弄得很松的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.57,0:19:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的真是极品
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.57,0:19:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,技术也很厉害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.57,0:19:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只顾和你做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.58,0:19:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底你是从哪里来的？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.58,0:19:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.58,0:19:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.59,0:19:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里……
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.60,0:19:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的天太污浊  看不见
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.61,0:19:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那红色星星的后面远方……
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.62,0:19:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  算了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.62,0:19:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想说是有你的理由吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.62,0:19:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们这里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.55,0:19:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢住多久都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.56,0:20:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至可以卖掉这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.56,0:20:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会很值钱吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.50,0:20:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是拍小电影
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.50,0:20:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不成了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.50,0:20:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事  看……
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.51,0:20:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还很健康
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.51,0:20:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我多一些
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.52,0:20:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要吮到你们直至最后一滴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.52,0:20:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到最后一滴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.53,0:20:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了……
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.53,0:20:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以内阁总理大臣的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.47,0:20:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正事要求自卫队出动！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.47,0:20:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作战代号——冰火行动
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.47,0:20:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据各首府长官指示
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.47,0:20:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作战圈内三十公里居民避难
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.48,0:20:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公关科向各报道机关
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.48,0:20:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下令禁止报道的通告
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.48,0:21:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是……可是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.49,0:21:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是人类存亡的大事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.42,0:21:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  这种作战可以公诸于世吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.43,0:21:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自卫队特殊战略部队队长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.44,0:21:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈山洋三报到！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.37,0:21:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.37,0:21:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自卫队引以为荣的年轻精锐部队
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.38,0:21:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你们很大期望的！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.38,0:21:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.38,0:21:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  真的要这样吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.38,0:21:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.19,0:21:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是他的提案
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.39,0:21:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的  是荷尔蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.39,0:21:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有荷尔蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.39,0:21:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙一定会来  一定来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.34,0:22:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复  今天  根据通告
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.15,0:22:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,内阁发表了对自卫队请求出动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.15,0:22:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是为什么要出动
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.15,0:22:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还未知道
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.16,0:22:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向东京、神奈川、群马的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.16,0:22:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以主要高速公路为中心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.16,0:22:17.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,县内十公里的住民
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.16,0:22:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发出了避难命令
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.10,0:22:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对自卫队在国内正式出动的事态
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.10,0:22:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各在野党一齐提出反论
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.10,0:22:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般市民间的动摇也在扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.09,0:23:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北森先生  为何不准采访？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.09,0:23:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对自卫队这样的正式出动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.09,0:23:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从未有过的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.10,0:23:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这岂不是情报封锁！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.10,0:23:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.10,0:23:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且……而且？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.10,0:23:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.10,0:23:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事就算想给你们看
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.11,0:23:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是也做不来的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.05,0:23:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷达有反应  目标物
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.05,0:23:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在以时速25公里移动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.05,0:23:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信会在预定地点出现
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.05,0:23:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.99,0:23:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铃鹿先生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.99,0:23:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备闸门
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.99,0:23:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到发讯的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.85,0:24:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是满P焦点杂志
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.86,0:25:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是岩端吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.86,0:25:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来发生这么多事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.86,0:25:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在玩吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.86,0:25:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.87,0:25:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？  店内没有女孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.87,0:25:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  今天去了很多地方
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.87,0:25:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浴室、发型屋、舞厅、酒吧……
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.88,0:25:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之所有店内都没有女人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.81,0:25:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是警察的卫生检查啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.81,0:25:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事！  我本来也这样想
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.82,0:25:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新宿、池袋、五反田等地
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.82,0:25:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数得出的店铺也一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.83,0:25:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得可疑所以调查过
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.83,0:25:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问相熟的店铺
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.83,0:25:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说国家买走了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.83,0:25:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.83,0:25:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察和自卫队
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.83,0:25:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不拘捕反而买起整个风俗行业
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.84,0:25:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  怎么可能？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.84,0:25:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察还可以  但为何是自卫队？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.84,0:25:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.85,0:25:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这很可疑啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.85,0:26:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说想调查店里的人十分害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.85,0:26:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说可能会被封铺
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.85,0:26:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以别胡来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.79,0:26:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  我的朋友中
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.79,0:26:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有知道这方面的人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.79,0:26:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向他打探一下
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.80,0:26:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了  总编辑
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.74,0:26:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岩端你调查时也要小心点啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.74,0:26:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  再见！
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.75,0:26:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能和今天
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.75,0:26:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自卫队出动有关也说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.76,0:26:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  请接自卫队的后补室……
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.76,0:26:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是深受市民爱戴的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.76,0:26:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上自卫队……
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.77,0:26:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉  今天的电话服务
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.77,0:26:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经终止
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.77,0:26:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对自卫队及宪法第九条的查询……
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.65,0:27:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据自卫队指示
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.65,0:27:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中央道、东明、小田原高速公路
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.65,0:27:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各处的收费公路及一般道路
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.65,0:27:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经封锁
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.66,0:27:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般市民不能通过
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.66,0:27:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为报道人员不能进入
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.60,0:27:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以无法报道情况
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.60,0:27:22.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于这次的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.60,0:27:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们民间放送联盟
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.60,0:27:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正考虑作出抗议
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.63,0:27:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说如此  但也太大气味了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.63,0:27:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散布了的人造荷尔蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.63,0:27:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是无色无味的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.63,0:27:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是香水的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.57,0:27:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,香水？
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.57,0:28:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当很多不同香水气味混合起来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.57,0:28:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会成为粪便的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.58,0:28:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科学合成的东西的话是不会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.58,0:28:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是以自己的身体为本钱的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.58,0:28:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花很多钱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.59,0:28:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这很难忍受啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.59,0:28:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说这种话的时候吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.59,0:28:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们一个不好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.59,0:28:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会成为今次作战的牺牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.53,0:28:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是贵重的牺牲者啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.53,0:28:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么可以这样说？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.54,0:28:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到有效果的时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.55,0:28:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.51,0:29:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荷尔蒙本来是雌性为吸引雄性
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.51,0:29:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而散发出来的物质
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.51,0:29:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是很多人不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.51,0:29:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雄性会对有意思的雌性
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.52,0:29:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散发出荷尔蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.52,0:29:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说是负荷尔蒙
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.53,0:29:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类也有相同情形
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.53,0:29:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.46,0:29:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.47,0:29:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然会引来怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.47,0:29:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜的是  有副作用发生
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.47,0:29:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,副作用？  怎么会？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.48,0:29:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说过的吗？  会成牺牲品
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.49,0:29:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们如果不作献身的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.49,0:29:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这作战也不会成功
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.49,0:30:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.49,0:30:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能你会觉得我很卑鄙
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.50,0:30:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要阻止它只好如此
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.43,0:30:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.43,0:30:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈山先生
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.37,0:30:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这状态也能说明问题……
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.37,0:30:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有说服力
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.35,0:31:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太难看了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.35,0:31:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算是大日本帝国军人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.35,0:31:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冈山先生
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.36,0:31:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种发言太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.36,0:31:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种情况坦白一点说  对健康有益
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.36,0:31:13.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.30,0:31:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是为何你会没事的？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.30,0:31:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的已经枯萎了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.31,0:31:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不中用了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.31,0:31:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原……原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.31,0:31:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,队长  快些！
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.32,0:31:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞槁君  连你也……
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.32,0:31:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标物反应
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.32,0:31:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法捕捉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.33,0:31:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？  出现了？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.33,0:31:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不……还未……
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.27,0:31:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的技术很好呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.27,0:31:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？  什么技术？
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.27,0:32:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有生物体反应！  北东2时方向！
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.28,0:32:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北东2时方向  距离？
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.28,0:32:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.28,0:32:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离……差不多   差不多了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.30,0:32:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.30,0:32:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  铃鹿先生
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.31,0:32:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样真的有效吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.31,0:32:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  那家伙的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.31,0:32:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尽量把精子注入更多女人体内
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.32,0:32:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来动物射精后便会死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.32,0:32:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答案很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.25,0:32:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使那个家伙精液耗尽
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.26,0:32:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便是我们的胜利！
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.28,0:33:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是很绝伦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.28,0:33:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有疲倦的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.28,0:33:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙的精液体积是我们一万三千倍
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.15,0:33:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以人类一次射精有3cc来计算
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.16,0:33:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出39公升的精液便该枯朽的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.16,0:33:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对那家伙正不断巨大化一事
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.17,0:33:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有忘记吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.17,0:33:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙是吸收精气成长的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.17,0:33:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度的做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.17,0:33:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它是没可能会枯朽的！
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.11,0:33:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太大意了……
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.11,0:33:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在过着科学家生活的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.11,0:33:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童贞生活了32年的影响
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.11,0:33:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟在这时候出现……
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.12,0:33:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是推卸责任的时候！
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.06,0:33:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.06,0:33:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般市民不能进来！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.63,0:35:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第四层云种星人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.64,0:35:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你犯了宇宙联邦法
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.64,0:35:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟逃到地球！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.64,0:35:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算天可以原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.58,0:35:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这全银河风俗巡逻队员
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.58,0:35:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能原谅！
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.52,0:35:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟来到这边境
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.52,0:35:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.52,0:35:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  她们的体内
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.53,0:35:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经被我放下了种子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.53,0:35:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在一切已太迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.53,0:35:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可怎么说？
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.53,0:35:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能你还未知道
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.53,0:35:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和人类
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.54,0:35:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗传因子DNA的排列
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.54,0:35:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是致命的不同
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.54,0:35:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.47,0:35:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的精子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.48,0:35:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算和地球人的卵子结合
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.48,0:35:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细胞分裂到某个程度
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.48,0:35:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会发出红色讯号
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.48,0:36:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  那细胞
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.48,0:36:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地球上只能生存三分钟！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.43,0:36:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.43,0:36:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你太蠢！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.43,0:36:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岂有此理  就算这样
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.43,0:36:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你打败我
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.43,0:36:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样要继续播种
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.44,0:36:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,播种啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.44,0:36:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种！  种！  种！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.44,0:36:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,种！  种！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.44,0:36:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在此之前  我会收拾你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.39,0:36:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好像怪兽电影
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.41,0:36:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放过我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.27,0:38:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难听的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.28,0:38:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是……什么……声音
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.28,0:38:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.23,0:38:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊……看啊……很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.23,0:38:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样快！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.24,0:38:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收拾你！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.25,0:38:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  快射出来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.19,0:38:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也忍不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.19,0:38:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,播种！播种！  播种！播种！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.66,0:38:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.19,0:38:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.14,0:39:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.09,0:39:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.09,0:39:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你们协助
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.39,0:39:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见！
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.10,0:39:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔  很不错的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.11,0:39:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为何不求她和你做一次？
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.11,0:39:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放过我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.11,0:39:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信那怪兽不会是最后一只
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.12,0:39:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也一定要对宇宙的侵略
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.12,0:39:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加强防范
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.12,0:40:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具体来说打算怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.72,0:40:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先是主动保卫兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.63,0:40:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机械性爱人造人
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.56,0:40:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.56,0:40:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字也已决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.57,0:40:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫SUPER SEX如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.50,0:40:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把对手的攻击以一万倍反击
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.51,0:40:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.44,0:40:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  别留下我一个！


