[Script Info]
Title: [淫獣学園EX La☆BlueGirl][WMV][03][邪恋地獄篇][DVD][WMV9][QB90][24f VGA]
Original Script: 
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H0000FFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,10,1
Style: 22,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.22,0:00:15.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美…美…美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.21,0:00:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是雁魔罗狂四郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.23,0:00:20.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他又复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.00,0:00:22.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.50,0:00:25.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快停止那恼人的笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.33,0:00:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.95,0:00:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.04,0:00:55.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.82,0:01:02.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.81,0:01:06.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.09,0:01:58.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.07,0:02:03.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是色魔族之一
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.29,0:02:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.45,0:02:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就让你带我去见\N你们色魔阴界的大王吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.95,0:02:11.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑\N你别小看我了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.03,0:02:13.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我今天就让你死在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.15,0:02:17.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知天高地厚的小妮子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.76,0:02:19.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会像刚才那么仁慈了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.52,0:02:22.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你瞧瞧\N色魔族第一战士的威力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.50,0:02:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠢东西，不自量力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.26,0:02:51.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个色魔族的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.53,0:02:54.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你招架得住我的淫术吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.17,0:03:06.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.26,0:03:10.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你一副高兴愉悦的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.64,0:03:15.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会怕你的淫术的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.93,0:03:19.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你无法避开我的眼神的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.21,0:03:31.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.66,0:03:36.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.07,0:03:42.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.65,0:03:45.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看着我的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.39,0:03:49.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.82,0:03:57.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.07,0:04:05.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要停下来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.19,0:04:08.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要我的宝贝挺身而入吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.36,0:04:10.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.68,0:04:14.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用你的手摸摸看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.73,0:04:21.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想不想尝尝我的宝贝?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.51,0:04:25.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放入口中后保证你爽
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.28,0:04:29.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要用你那温热的舌头\N亲一亲的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.14,0:04:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,保证你的淫乱如决堤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.72,0:04:32.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请给我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.98,0:04:36.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我这有着坚实肉壁的宝贝
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.58,0:04:39.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对你的体内吹进一股寒气
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.01,0:04:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并与你的下体结合\N摩察蠕动
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.88,0:04:45.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你快放进去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.25,0:04:47.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想亲吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.86,0:04:50.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要我放进去吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.30,0:04:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…我受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.74,0:04:56.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你，求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.63,0:05:02.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你，我想要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.37,0:05:06.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人，求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.33,0:05:11.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去的话\N我会欲火焚身的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.27,0:05:17.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你就带我去色魔阴界
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.72,0:05:19.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的纯情小美女
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.89,0:05:21.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可爱的色魔族小女人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.80,0:05:24.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这宝贝就送你尝尝看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.56,0:05:30.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,午夜十二点，往正北方去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.04,0:05:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经被我的淫术控制住了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.92,0:05:58.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人振作点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.34,0:05:59.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.87,0:06:00.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.28,0:06:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.36,0:06:04.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了，醒过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.05,0:06:06.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪小姐呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.16,0:06:09.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道被逛尸郎带去哪里了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.05,0:06:11.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能再躺了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.62,0:06:16.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们去找英正及沙那姬
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.13,0:06:17.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那美子大人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.45,0:06:19.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要回色魔阴界去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.45,0:06:24.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,复活的狂尸郎为了复仇\N可能会对父王不利
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.54,0:06:25.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.18,0:07:08.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,朝正北方做手淫…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.71,0:07:11.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太…太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.71,0:07:14.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌，色鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.20,0:07:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这样我怎么能专心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.11,0:07:19.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起，因为太久没看到\N都看呆了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.71,0:07:30.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大王，真利亚女王
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.88,0:07:32.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是夜久
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.27,0:07:35.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我听说色魔阴界\N正面临一场大危机
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.07,0:07:36.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就飞奔而来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.56,0:07:38.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你来得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.45,0:07:40.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.37,0:07:41.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他和吹雪小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.55,0:07:43.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,正在追查狂尸郎的踪迹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.15,0:07:47.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大王…\N亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.28,0:08:02.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.76,0:08:04.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是雁魔罗的喽啰们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.93,0:08:08.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎已经来到色魔阴界了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.16,0:08:09.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.46,0:08:11.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家快保护大王
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.90,0:08:38.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夜…夜久小姐\N美…美子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.58,0:08:43.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.92,0:08:45.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.65,0:08:47.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶快，赶快吹你那女笛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.66,0:08:50.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是这样一来，母后你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.54,0:08:53.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想现在这样\N才能压制住那男笛的笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.14,0:08:55.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真利亚女王
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.38,0:08:56.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子，快吹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.52,0:09:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快吹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.78,0:09:02.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.05,0:09:26.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停下来，不要再吹了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.42,0:09:32.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎\N让我夜久跟你比划比划
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.24,0:09:35.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.36,0:09:45.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.16,0:09:51.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.16,0:09:55.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把那笛子还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.17,0:10:06.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么哭?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.15,0:10:09.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么而哭泣?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.81,0:10:12.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什么好悲伤的?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.23,0:10:15.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手，请你住手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.87,0:10:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是敌人?\N还是自己人?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.49,0:10:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为何流泪?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:28.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你把英正还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.59,0:10:32.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,英正?\N谁是英正?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.62,0:10:36.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.09,0:10:45.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手，别再吹了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.68,0:10:54.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.83,0:11:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.36,0:11:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我无法打败他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.64,0:11:08.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.31,0:11:47.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪，你还认得我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.51,0:11:52.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你是大王殿下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.18,0:11:53.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做了什么事?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.85,0:11:57.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你中了狂尸郎的淫术了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.02,0:12:01.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我差点就被你宰了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.83,0:12:04.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.68,0:12:08.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还好你没事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.66,0:12:15.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.10,0:12:19.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来美子有过这么一段往事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.62,0:12:23.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得他那失神的样子\N不太寻常
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.36,0:12:25.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子总算平静下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.68,0:12:27.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.53,0:12:29.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是，大王
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.08,0:12:33.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么狂尸郎怕那笛声\N而变得精神错乱呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.25,0:12:35.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是他在含恨九泉时
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.45,0:12:39.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将他对沙那姬的爱意\N倾注于那笛声之中的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.10,0:12:44.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他生前的爱意与恨意\N在那笛声中交战着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.82,0:12:47.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得没错\N你一眼就看穿了他的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.85,0:12:51.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我以前是弥勒宗的美子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.19,0:12:55.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以能分辨笛声中所隐藏的\N男女情思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.39,0:12:58.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎不会就此罢手的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.59,0:13:01.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次我一定要讨回面子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.55,0:13:04.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪小姐好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.77,0:13:06.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么，忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.67,0:13:09.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会重蹈覆辙的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.35,0:13:11.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这件事就交给我来办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.24,0:13:15.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你跟美子还迷恋着\N狂尸郎的前身英正
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.81,0:13:19.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以潜意识里\N你们无法对他下手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.29,0:13:22.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.69,0:13:24.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎由我来收拾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.70,0:13:25.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.91,0:13:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛，你这个波霸女人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.62,0:13:33.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这是对巨乳的侮辱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.28,0:13:36.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要你改口，你这洗衣板
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.49,0:13:38.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洗…洗衣板?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.18,0:13:40.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你居然说我最在意的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.19,0:13:42.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住口
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.86,0:13:46.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在应该是\N大家合力打倒邪魔的时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.57,0:13:49.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而不是斗嘴互道长短的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.06,0:13:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是不让美子彻头彻尾地\N忘记那段初恋情怀的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.09,0:13:58.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能会变成他的致命伤
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.70,0:14:00.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去叫美子来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.28,0:14:00.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.30,0:14:03.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若三人不同心协力的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.70,0:14:06.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是无法打败狂尸郎的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.44,0:14:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不得了了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.00,0:14:11.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美…美子大人他…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.00,0:14:12.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.19,0:14:14.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.95,0:14:17.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.24,0:14:33.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙那…沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.74,0:14:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么背叛我，为什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.32,0:14:46.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙那公主送来的礼物\N在哪儿?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.49,0:15:06.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是那沾满你全身的\N曼陀罗花香吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.50,0:15:15.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么背叛了我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.68,0:15:32.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那眼泪是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.77,0:15:57.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.76,0:16:01.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你若是真的沙那公主\N请告诉我实情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.22,0:16:03.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道事情的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.36,0:16:14.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.45,0:16:20.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你我都中了色魔他们的计了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.48,0:16:21.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.89,0:16:26.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都是色魔阴界那帮人搞的鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.65,0:16:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请听我道来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.26,0:16:44.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圣殿失火了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.38,0:16:48.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那狂尸郎大人他…大人他…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.60,0:16:53.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然沦落至此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.73,0:16:57.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,希望…希望能藉此笛声
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.28,0:17:01.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,传达我对狂尸郎大人的爱慕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.73,0:17:24.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.29,0:17:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.61,0:17:30.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.68,0:17:32.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了，你没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.26,0:17:33.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.80,0:17:38.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我中了色魔的诡计\N差点连命都丢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.46,0:17:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,色魔的诡计?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.10,0:17:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.00,0:17:45.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来打算成为\N这个世界与色魔阴界的霸主
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.49,0:17:48.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却被青鬼魔他们摆了一道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.49,0:17:50.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我出嫁的日子里?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.16,0:17:53.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N若是我与公主成婚的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.44,0:17:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就能抵挡色魔大王的魔力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.75,0:18:01.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如此一来\N色魔就奈何不了我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.20,0:18:04.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.51,0:18:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只想跟您结为夫妻
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.15,0:18:13.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让我们结合在一起\N让那些色魔们知道厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.34,0:18:29.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.74,0:18:50.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我们一起为复仇而战吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.20,0:18:51.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.56,0:19:00.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人，狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.05,0:19:02.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要，我要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.78,0:19:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要的是这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.13,0:19:17.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请将那温热的肉棒\N送入我的口中
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.37,0:19:26.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.59,0:19:28.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙那公主，你在说什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.15,0:19:30.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那根不是狂尸郎大人的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.94,0:19:31.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.91,0:19:34.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可是圣殿的沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.57,0:19:38.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我分辨不出\N狂尸郎大人的宝贝吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.94,0:19:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶，你跑不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.22,0:19:49.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即使用暴力，也要逼你就范
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.91,0:19:52.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别挣扎了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.25,0:19:55.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要用我的宝贝\N把你变成我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.38,0:19:59.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界和色魔阴界\N都将成为我的天下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.19,0:20:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是青鬼魔，你骗了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.18,0:20:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶，你好大的胆子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.65,0:20:28.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.71,0:20:44.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的青鬼魔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然让我以为是\N沙那公主背叛了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.68,0:20:49.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好恨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.83,0:20:52.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狂尸郎大人，我好恨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.14,0:20:54.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要雪此大仇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.69,0:20:56.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要让害我们的青鬼魔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.61,0:21:01.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,及那些色魔阴界的人好看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.67,0:21:03.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我太愚昧了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.76,0:21:07.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有没有让你复活的方法?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.47,0:21:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要用三位少女的淫水
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.35,0:21:13.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加上邪魔的法力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.30,0:21:15.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就能复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.09,0:21:17.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.74,0:21:20.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会一并讨回这笔血债的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.23,0:21:31.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子人呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.40,0:21:32.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找不到人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.74,0:21:34.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.43,0:21:52.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里找过了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.70,0:21:56.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,色魔的众家子弟\N已经把这座公园都找遍了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.19,0:21:59.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是那些家伙\N应该还藏在这附近才对
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:22.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这叫做『千鸟香炉』
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.97,0:22:24.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是个稀世珍宝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.91,0:22:26.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得很适合你用
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.19,0:22:29.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么哭?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.63,0:22:31.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了什么哭泣?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.47,0:22:36.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若是说狂尸郎\N藉由英正的肉体复活的话
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.45,0:22:41.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么杀了狂尸郎\N英正也会死
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.75,0:22:46.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.21,0:22:49.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护父王\N母后及色魔阴界…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.68,0:22:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去\N夜久小姐及吹雪小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.70,0:22:55.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会和色魔众家丁一起\N拼命地和狂尸郎战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.32,0:23:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此\N与其被大家围剿至死
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.89,0:23:08.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不如我亲手杀了狂尸郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.75,0:23:12.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.86,0:23:13.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.34,0:23:15.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你果然在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.86,0:23:18.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我发现你房间里的千鸟香炉\N不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.20,0:23:21.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以猜想你可能跑到\N英正先生的家里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.78,0:23:24.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍，你愿意帮我吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.58,0:23:26.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望其它人对狂尸郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.48,0:23:29.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不，是英正先生下手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.69,0:23:31.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.74,0:23:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.16,0:23:37.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我最了解美子大人的心意了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.58,0:23:39.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你，忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.54,0:23:45.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子大人，这个千鸟香炉…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.90,0:23:47.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个香炉怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.09,0:23:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞不好可以用这个香炉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.16,0:23:52.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来唤回\N被狂尸郎附身的英正先生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.78,0:23:54.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.18,0:23:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是美子大人将全身擦满
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.92,0:23:59.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与这个香炉的香料\N一样的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.50,0:24:01.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为只有英正先生一个人\N知道这个香味
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.48,0:24:03.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定可以破解魔咒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.18,0:24:05.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.76,0:24:08.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借我看一下香炉\N你要干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.41,0:24:12.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要闻出\N这个香炉所用过的香料
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.31,0:24:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我试试
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.71,0:24:17.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会一直用同样的沈香吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.34,0:24:19.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这可是天祥年间的东西呀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.80,0:24:22.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,英正先生说这是贵族所用的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.62,0:24:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以可能是\N用昂贵又稀少的沈香
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.69,0:24:30.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道美子大人你不知道\N去世的老佛爷是香料专家?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.34,0:24:31.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说奶奶他…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.55,0:24:35.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N我现在就赶去老家查一查
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.91,0:24:37.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍，拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.91,0:24:39.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.21,0:24:45.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若是能从狂尸郎的身上\N唤回英正先生的意识
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.61,0:24:48.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也许就能破除邪魔的魔咒了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.11,0:24:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奶奶，请您…\N请您助美子我一臂之力
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.09,0:25:07.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.95,0:25:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.26,0:25:18.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.83,0:25:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,公主，沙那公主
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.93,0:25:42.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吹不下去
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.21,0:25:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没办法吹这支\N会让真利亚女王痛苦的笛子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.48,0:25:51.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夜久，现在完全要仰赖你的嗅觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.32,0:25:54.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去侦查的色魔众家丁\N没有一个回来报告
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.26,0:25:56.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,美子跟忍忍也找不到人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.98,0:25:58.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.71,0:26:01.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一切等月圆出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.60,0:26:13.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.19,0:26:46.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个吠叫声是…夜久小姐
