[Script Info]
; This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;
; Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,SimHei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00808080,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.65,0:00:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.57,0:00:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.57,0:00:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.49,0:00:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,原来是这个原因啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.41,0:00:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,这个胸罩不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.83,0:00:32.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,什么 发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.58,0:00:37.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我以前不是说过 我经常在电车上遇到痴汉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.92,0:00:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我终于知道原因了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.17,0:00:43.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,仔细想了想
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.09,0:00:47.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,发现都是带这个胸罩的时候才遇到痴汉的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.01,0:00:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,只是一件普通的可爱胸罩而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.52,0:00:56.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,这胸罩难道被诅咒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.94,0:01:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,讨厌 我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.69,0:01:03.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我已经不能再用这个胸罩了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.95,0:01:07.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,那么 我和你交换
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.72,0:01:25.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子 带这个胸罩不会有问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.98,0:01:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,真的会引来痴汉也说不定哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.40,0:01:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.15,0:01:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我不坐电车就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.49,0:01:44.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.50,0:01:46.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.27,0:01:58.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,为什么这么挤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:02:00.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,而且全部是男的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.19,0:02:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,走楼梯该多好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.38,0:02:25.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么了 叶子 脸好红啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.97,0:02:36.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,好像谁在摸我的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.81,0:02:40.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不会吧 在这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.23,0:02:44.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.66,0:02:47.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,救我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.00,0:02:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不行 我也动不了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.42,0:02:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,啊 这次是胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.67,0:03:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,喂 叶子 不会有事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.69,0:03:14.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.69,0:03:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.44,0:03:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,讨厌 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.80,0:03:34.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,为什么会在这个地方遇到痴汉的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.39,0:03:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,难道是那个胸罩的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.06,0:03:42.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不会是那样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.06,0:03:43.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,痛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.06,0:03:44.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.24,0:03:52.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.66,0:04:04.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.33,0:04:10.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,请住手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.42,0:04:12.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么了 叶子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.42,0:04:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不行 说不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.63,0:04:49.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,你再不住手的话 我要叫了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.31,0:04:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,随便你叫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.56,0:04:57.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,如果有人来救你的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.06,0:05:00.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,喂喂 看那个女的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.90,0:05:01.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,被痴汉侵犯了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.23,0:05:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,那女的不就是叶子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.90,0:05:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.17,0:05:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我也想干
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.86,0:05:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子一定是发生什么大事了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.19,0:05:38.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,那里一定被侵犯了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.28,0:05:42.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,乳头被多次抚摸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.20,0:05:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.45,0:05:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,如果我遇到这种事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.63,0:05:53.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,会高潮也说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.81,0:06:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不会吧 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.24,0:06:10.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,求求你 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.75,0:06:19.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.08,0:06:23.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.17,0:06:26.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,这样做可是电梯痴汉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.59,0:06:27.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,过份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.60,0:06:37.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子真是淫荡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.93,0:06:41.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叫得真好听
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.45,0:06:44.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我的也勃起了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.45,0:06:47.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我也忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.38,0:07:00.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我的在叶子的嘴里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.48,0:07:15.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,淫荡的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.23,0:07:17.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,屁眼也开始蠢蠢欲动了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.57,0:07:23.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,声音真大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.24,0:07:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.32,0:07:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,真热啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.83,0:07:30.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,里面好像终于有感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.01,0:07:36.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么办 谁也来欺负我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.10,0:07:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,对不起 快要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.35,0:07:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不要 不要射在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.36,0:07:56.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.62,0:08:06.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,还没软哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.21,0:08:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,再来一次怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.96,0:08:10.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.21,0:08:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,小穴在哪儿呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.88,0:08:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,等等 那里不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.07,0:08:23.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,哦 真紧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.32,0:08:26.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,虽然入口很紧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.65,0:08:29.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,里面却很爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.41,0:08:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.91,0:08:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.92,0:08:39.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,真厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.67,0:08:42.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,叶子的屁眼 还是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.11,0:09:07.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不行了 太紧了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.45,0:09:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.30,0:09:17.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.88,0:10:31.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,胸罩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.30,0:10:32.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.55,0:10:35.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,只要扔掉胸罩的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.08,0:10:55.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,不愧是强人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.00,0:10:57.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,这是最后的了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.51,0:11:02.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.98,0:11:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.40,0:11:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,这不是一般的胸罩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.74,0:12:06.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,!Effect,来 打起精神 我送你回去
