[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style:Default,zhunyuan,27,&H00FFFFFF,&H004080FF,&H00C14F0D,&HFFFCAE3A,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,0,2,1,2,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個女孩是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.00,0:00:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是夢嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼\N我會和這麼美的人作愛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.00,0:00:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了，她叫奈美
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.00,0:00:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我不記得
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.00,0:00:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說是我的青梅竹馬
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.00,0:00:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊,我想起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.00,0:00:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暑假時我去鄉下奶奶家玩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那裡和三個\N青梅竹馬的女孩重逢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個女孩是小杏
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.00,0:00:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同樣年紀，卻喊我哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.00,0:00:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個奇怪的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.00,0:00:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的口交技巧很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.00,0:00:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照這樣下去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.00,0:00:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定我也可以跟
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.00,0:00:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的朱雀和另一個女孩\N順利上床呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.00,0:01:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇！太傷腦筋了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.00,0:01:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人太受歡迎就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.00,0:01:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體會受不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.00,0:01:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.00,0:01:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.00,0:01:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真雪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.00,0:01:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在等你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.00,0:01:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為在這裡等可以碰到你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.00,0:01:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戀姬 第二話 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.00,0:02:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟以前一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.00,0:02:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.00,0:02:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山丘上的大樹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.00,0:02:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及河水
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.00,0:02:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨著季節轉換的草木
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.00,0:02:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有下雨後就變得泥濘的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.00,0:02:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連稀草屋頂的甜甜香味\N我全部記得
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.00,0:02:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是除你們之外...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.00,0:02:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.00,0:02:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.00,0:02:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問武藏你喜歡這裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.00,0:02:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是就類似我的故鄉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.00,0:02:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你永遠留下來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.00,0:02:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是 幾十年後
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.00,0:02:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年紀大了退休了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.00,0:02:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒想在這個村子養老
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.00,0:02:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾十年...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.00,0:03:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來會下一陣雨了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.00,0:03:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我送你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.00,0:03:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了，沒關係的，告辭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.00,0:03:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.00,0:03:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍王好像終於注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.00,0:03:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來需要做懺悔了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.00,0:03:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懺悔？跟這裡的族長嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.00,0:03:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太難得了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.00,0:03:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就知道你們解結界\N引導武藏過來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.00,0:03:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.00,0:03:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了,我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.00,0:03:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍王在生氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.00,0:03:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並木大人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.00,0:03:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽們該也注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.00,0:04:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我趁她們生氣前先溜出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.00,0:04:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雀跟小雪不知道怎樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.00,0:04:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下我再去看看情況吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.00,0:04:13.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈美姐，以後該怎麼辦好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.00,0:04:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我們能做的是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.00,0:04:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在族長他們到達前\N把武藏起來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.00,0:04:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大的雨\N頭一次遇到這樣的驟雨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.00,0:04:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.00,0:04:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.00,0:04:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了，雨勢這麼大
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.00,0:05:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.00,0:05:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.00,0:05:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.00,0:05:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你幫我脫的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.00,0:05:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿著濕衣服會感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.00,0:05:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話是這樣沒錯\N但沒必要連褲子也脫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.00,0:05:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別在意\N又不是沒見過男人裸體
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.00,0:05:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.00,0:05:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你全身都濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.00,0:05:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的,我無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.00,0:05:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎麼了\N從剛剛開始就怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.00,0:05:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點也不像你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.00,0:06:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許...\N我們做了無法挽回的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.00,0:06:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必要的時候我會保護你的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.00,0:06:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.00,0:06:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.00,0:06:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說了,讓我來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.00,0:06:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.00,0:06:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟剛才完全不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.00,0:06:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼大怎放進去...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.00,0:06:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀.你不用勉強的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.00,0:06:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋,少丟人了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個一兩根才沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.00,0:06:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪了\N需要時怎麼放不進去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.00,0:06:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該這樣的...\N好像是這裡吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.00,0:07:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.00,0:07:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.00,0:07:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放不進去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.00,0:07:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然放進去是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.00,0:07:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不甘心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.00,0:07:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.00,0:07:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小時候我從沒輸給你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連這種時候都輸給你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.00,0:07:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後我怎麼見你嘛,丟臉死了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.00,0:07:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻瓜,你怎麼會在意這個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.00,0:07:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.00,0:07:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再把身體放鬆,心情放鬆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.00,0:07:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好癢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.00,0:07:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦,我會發出好怪的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.00,0:07:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可以笑我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.00,0:07:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有笑你呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.00,0:07:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很可愛哦,朱雀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.00,0:08:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.00,0:08:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像小孩子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.00,0:08:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.00,0:08:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服,再多吸一些
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.00,0:08:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想這次應該能進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.00,0:08:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插...插進來...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.00,0:08:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你再溫柔一點
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.00,0:08:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害,真的進去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.00,0:08:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害，沒想到...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.00,0:09:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒，再...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.00,0:09:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還會痛嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.00,0:09:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以動嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.00,0:09:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜歡你哦，武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.00,0:09:39.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.00,0:09:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害，真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.00,0:09:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朱雀，我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.00,0:09:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係，來吧，射啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.00,0:09:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你這樣動\N我會射在裡面的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.00,0:09:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係，就讓它在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.00,0:09:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.00,0:09:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係\N讓我們到最後都在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.00,0:10:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在呼喚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.00,0:10:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們談好了嗎...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.00,0:10:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要躲在這裡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.00,0:10:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這孫女太荒唐了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.00,0:10:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.00,0:10:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不，感覺好像不大對
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.00,0:10:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣，武藏\N跟我孫女作愛的感想
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.00,0:10:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺，你怎麼飄在空中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.00,0:10:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是被人類稱為妖怪\N的精靈種族
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.00,0:10:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是風部的族長
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.00,0:10:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伴都叫我天狗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.00,0:10:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪？天狗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.00,0:11:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然要你理解有點困難
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.00,0:11:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之你先聽我說我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.00,0:11:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個村子是你們人類與\N我們一族共同生存的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.00,0:11:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我們風部之外
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.00,0:11:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有火部
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.00,0:11:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰部
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.00,0:11:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及水部，這四個種族
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.00,0:11:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每族都有個族長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.00,0:11:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都沒有爭執的和平生活
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.00,0:11:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在這裡的人類\N只剩下你家老奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.00,0:11:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而四個種族有四個公主
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.00,0:11:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們你全部都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.00,0:11:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四個公主，不會吧...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.00,0:11:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我們
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.00,0:11:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們三人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.00,0:11:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.00,0:11:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是妖怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.00,0:11:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為你們要說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.00,0:12:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太荒唐了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.00,0:12:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.00,0:12:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託，告訴我這不是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.00,0:12:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我若不是妖怪的話\N那我看起來像什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.00,0:12:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了，我知道，我相信
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.00,0:12:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們是妖怪，好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道就好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.00,0:12:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來替你消除記憶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.00,0:12:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在就給我離開這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.00,0:12:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在這村子看到，聽到\N做過的事全部不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.00,0:12:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後不准再回來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.00,0:12:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.00,0:12:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我把在這個村子看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.00,0:12:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽到的\N做過的事全忘記，這...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.00,0:12:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.00,0:12:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.00,0:12:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我忘記她們？別開玩笑\N我才不答應呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.00,0:12:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.00,0:12:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個要求是為你好\N你不知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我死也忘不了她們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.00,0:13:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法，是你要討皮肉痛的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.00,0:13:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.00,0:13:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才武藏的話讓我下定決心了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.00,0:13:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管族長們說什麼\N我不會讓你們碰武藏一根汗毛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.00,0:13:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在胡說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.00,0:13:20.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天狗大人，拜託你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.00,0:13:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別搶走我們的大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.00,0:13:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們知道自己做的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.00,0:13:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.00,0:13:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先打破禁忌的人是我們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.00,0:13:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早覺悟到事情會變這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.00,0:13:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.00,0:13:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事態比你們想像的嚴重
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.00,0:13:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經沒有時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.00,0:13:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒趕上呀...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.00,0:13:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來答案是出來了，天狗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.00,0:13:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.00,0:13:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍王大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.00,0:13:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那傢伙交給我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.00,0:13:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸。請原諒他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.00,0:14:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然玷污我女兒\N殺死他也無法消我心中之恨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.00,0:14:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.00,0:14:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我自己決定的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.00,0:14:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣講他，太難聽了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.00,0:14:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杏，快給我讓開
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.00,0:14:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.00,0:14:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這聲音是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.00,0:14:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真雪的媽媽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.00,0:14:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜子夫人說由我們決定\N你們死心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.00,0:14:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是族長的決定\N我也不會把武藏交出去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.00,0:14:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白費力氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.00,0:14:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我飛了?!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.00,0:14:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為\N小雀是天狗的孫女
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.00,0:14:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.00,0:14:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然遲早會被抓住\N但是,能逃多遠就逃多遠
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.00,0:14:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.00,0:14:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是沒關係\N問題是小雪怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.00,0:14:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雪她...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.00,0:14:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕很難承受這場騷動...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.00,0:14:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是,以後知道的話\N她會更傷心的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.00,0:15:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣後果很嚴重的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.00,0:15:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪是那麼可怕的問題兒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.00,0:15:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次\N大哥哥走後村子消失不見時
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.00,0:15:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雪哭了好久
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.00,0:15:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把全村都凍成冰了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.00,0:15:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凍成冰?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.00,0:15:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為小雪是雪女嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.00,0:15:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先是天狗,然後又是雪女...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.00,0:15:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有,小杏是屋敷童子\N奈美姐姐是龍哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.00,0:15:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽得我頭開始暈了...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.00,0:15:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍捲風來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.00,0:15:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽很生氣的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.00,0:15:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家抓緊了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.00,0:15:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍王,你好像做得太過火了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.00,0:15:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的女兒不會這樣就認輸的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.00,0:15:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇,我會被燒死的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.00,0:15:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係,有我們保護你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.00,0:16:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.00,0:16:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我快不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.00,0:16:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油,不可以死心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.00,0:16:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.00,0:16:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.00,0:16:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人,幸好你沒有事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.00,0:16:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.00,0:16:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前好像在哪見過...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.00,0:16:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在夢中夢見的\N原來是你們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.00,0:16:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您終於想起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.00,0:16:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得那時候我們做了什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.00,0:17:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們好像喝了彼此的血
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.00,0:17:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對,那是定婚的象徵哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.00,0:17:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定婚?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.00,0:17:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我們一族的規定
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.00,0:17:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們約好的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.00,0:17:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是四個人一起定了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.00,0:17:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.00,0:17:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.00,0:17:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟四個種族的公主\N都定了婚了?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.00,0:17:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.00,0:17:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,規定不能改變
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.00,0:17:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須避開四個種族\N為了搶夫婿而爭鬥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.00,0:17:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以族長們一起開會
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.00,0:17:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決定把你的記憶抹消掉\N把你跟你父母逐出村子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.00,0:17:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的事跟父母沒關係\N你們太沒道理了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.00,0:17:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.00,0:17:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼,放開我,臭老頭
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.00,0:17:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後再問你一次
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.00,0:17:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想抹消記憶,離開這裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.00,0:17:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.00,0:17:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.00,0:18:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.00,0:18:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸,您想對武藏做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.00,0:18:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我再生氣,也不忍殺死\N在這村子長大的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.00,0:18:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以決定把他釘在這裡\N讓他長眠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.00,0:18:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.00,0:18:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過分,哥哥是人類,會死掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.00,0:18:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺,沒辦法阻止嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是大家決定的,沒有辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.00,0:18:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.00,0:18:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...武藏會死的...這種事...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.00,0:18:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.00,0:18:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雪!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.00,0:18:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行呀,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.00,0:18:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要武藏死掉...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.00,0:18:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.00,0:18:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍王,你來壓制真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.00,0:18:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.00,0:18:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.00,0:19:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我說了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.00,0:19:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去世界會結冰的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.00,0:19:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天狗大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.00,0:19:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜妃夫人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.00,0:19:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請像以前那樣\N快點阻止真雪小姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.00,0:19:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我女兒的心已經封閉起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.00,0:19:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.00,0:19:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她變成這個樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.00,0:19:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒辦法控制呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.00,0:19:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小時候的她都有那麼強的能力\N更不用說現在了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.00,0:19:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今連你都沒辦法\N那不就無人能阻止了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.00,0:19:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的方法只剩一個
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.00,0:19:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.00,0:19:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的可以嗎,讓我跟小雪...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.00,0:19:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的,請拯救真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.00,0:20:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的能力比平常人強
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.00,0:20:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以從小到大一直小心\N害怕被大家排斥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.00,0:20:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了跟她情同姐妹的公主們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.00,0:20:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓真雪打開心扉的\N就只有武藏您了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.00,0:20:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到做母親的\N會拜託男人來抱她的女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.00,0:20:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這感覺太複雜了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.00,0:20:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了\N把真雪身上的冰融化掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.00,0:20:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此一來\N她心也就會解凍了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.00,0:21:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.00,0:21:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.00,0:21:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了,你醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.00,0:21:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我做了什麼事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.00,0:21:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我沒穿衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.00,0:21:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.00,0:21:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說武藏大人愛真雪了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.00,0:21:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好高興，我覺得好像在作夢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.00,0:22:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.00,0:22:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害，還要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.00,0:22:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託，請你輕輕地，溫柔點
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.00,0:22:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭...呀...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.00,0:23:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行，我會壞掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.00,0:23:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.00,0:23:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒，這個感覺好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.00,0:23:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒，請你再移動，插到底
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.00,0:23:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.00,0:23:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.00,0:23:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪...真雪我...好幸福...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.00,0:23:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人\N您要永遠和我在一起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.00,0:23:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.00,0:23:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等幾十年後\N老了想退休了就回來村子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.00,0:24:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.00,0:24:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於佐佐木武藏的騷動
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.00,0:24:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.00,0:24:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聚集在此的各位
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.00,0:24:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的交給你們判斷了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.00,0:24:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望各位以靈魂之色\N來代表你們的意見
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.00,0:24:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決定武藏可以留下來的人\N點出紅色
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.00,0:24:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,認為應該驅逐他的人\N就點出白色
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.00,0:24:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，請不要動
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.00,0:24:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二三...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.00,0:24:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,數目相同
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.00,0:24:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下子又難以決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.00,0:24:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有人點燈嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.00,0:24:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.00,0:24:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有點
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.00,0:24:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.00,0:24:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒，這下子嬴定了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.00,0:24:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧，冰部的公主
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.00,0:25:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.00,0:25:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧，你搞錯了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.00,0:25:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真雪，可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.00,0:25:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.00,0:25:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.00,0:25:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣會無法跟哥哥見面呀
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.00,0:25:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏身為人類的寶貴未來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.00,0:25:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不應該擅自剝奪的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.00,0:25:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武藏大人的未來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.00,0:25:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.00,0:25:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寶貴的未來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.00,0:25:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類與我們不同
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.00,0:25:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾十年後就會衰老死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.00,0:25:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我...所以我...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.00,0:26:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡得真熟
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.00,0:26:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了一個怪夢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.00,0:26:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了，差不多該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.00,0:26:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全局終 謝謝觀賞!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.00,0:28:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.00,0:28:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.00,0:28:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是夏天耶
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.00,0:28:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劇終


