[Script Info]
Title:
Original Script:
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004865EC,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,100,2,20,20,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.48,0:00:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁克斯…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.51,0:00:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然把公安也卷进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.53,0:00:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他已按照计划被杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.57,0:00:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马希有上当吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.60,0:00:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.62,0:00:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了 代茵 去好好享受吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.93,0:00:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒…好棒哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.79,0:01:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏多被公安盯上了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.85,0:01:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去做个了结吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.87,0:01:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 遵命 威兹玛博士
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.63,0:02:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你手受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.67,0:02:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.69,0:02:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 只是神经受了一点损伤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.72,0:02:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.73,0:02:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在担心我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.76,0:02:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟是照看你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.78,0:02:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你的事向上级写报告会很麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.84,0:02:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放在厨房的维护装置
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.87,0:02:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.89,0:02:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬去起居室吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.91,0:02:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厨房太小 不方便
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.95,0:02:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.97,0:02:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 今晚不要让我回去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.40,0:03:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.40,0:03:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱你 请抱我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.44,0:03:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.46,0:03:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我一不留神 你就会离我远去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.49,0:03:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我要让你的回忆留在我的体内
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.55,0:03:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接近 女性 有武器
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.58,0:03:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.67,0:03:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.69,0:03:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警视厅公安部机动搜查科
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.72,0:03:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神蔚警部
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.75,0:03:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.79,0:03:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰先生 你妹妹来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.86,0:03:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事…这个女孩是谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.92,0:03:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.95,0:03:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我是来发牢骚…不对 是来抗议的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.99,0:04:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是上次的那件事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我们的管辖区
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.44,0:04:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是 被假情报骗得团团转
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.48,0:04:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有作任何说明
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.50,0:04:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是公安
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.52,0:04:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事不能说 你也是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.57,0:04:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大哥总是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.60,0:04:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然离家出走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.62,0:04:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知什么时候就在做危险的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.66,0:04:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 我跟你一样还是公务员
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.69,0:04:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 用不着一声不吭的就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.72,0:04:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少事情原委也可以说明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.75,0:04:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是有原委的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.78,0:04:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进入情报部
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.81,0:04:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.82,0:04:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 大哥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.83,0:04:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 什么 你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.85,0:04:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 一点也不听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.88,0:04:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九天堂啊 那件事的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.91,0:04:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.95,0:04:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第九天堂吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.98,0:05:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在快乐中心 流行的心灵毒品
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.41,0:05:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在布鲁克斯房间里发现的那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.45,0:05:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我调查了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.47,0:05:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现那就是新隆素粒子本身
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.49,0:05:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟爱丽丝使用的是同样的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.52,0:05:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似把某种资料输入人脑的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.56,0:05:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,检测完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.58,0:05:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有发现构成问题的异状
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.61,0:05:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.63,0:05:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道有不构成问题的异状吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.65,0:05:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.67,0:05:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少女的心是很复杂的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.71,0:05:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神 马上过来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.73,0:05:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我了 我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.78,0:05:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.80,0:05:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.82,0:05:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁克斯那件事后 你的感情有一些波动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.86,0:05:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我也察觉到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.89,0:05:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波动的原因是御子神先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.93,0:06:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…奇怪了…不能控制…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.42,0:06:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 爱丽丝你跟人类一样耶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.45,0:06:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类也会这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.47,0:06:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.49,0:06:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忠实于自己的心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.52,0:06:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进攻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.53,0:06:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进攻？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.56,0:06:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我攻击薰先生吗 这种事我做不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.63,0:06:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是机器还是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.66,0:06:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,思念是一样的 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.76,0:06:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.77,0:06:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史蒂芬·梅休
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.79,0:06:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边是爱丽丝的负责人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.81,0:06:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝的…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.84,0:06:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是CIA吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.86,0:06:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马希·史贝克塔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.88,0:06:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最初试验MJP的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.92,0:06:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MJP
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.94,0:06:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人脑和电脑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.96,0:06:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以自由沟通的技术
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.99,0:07:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好吗 把最高机密告诉御子神
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.44,0:07:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MJP应用于开发爱丽丝的技术
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.48,0:07:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她自己应该没察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.51,0:07:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的体内潜藏着真由美的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.55,0:07:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真由美吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.57,0:07:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了御子神好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.59,0:07:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望就这样什么都没发生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.63,0:07:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在御子神握有足以揪出马希的王牌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.68,0:07:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 代茵的一直的行动也很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.72,0:07:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是为什么雷登曼公司
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.75,0:07:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要委托杀死布鲁克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.81,0:07:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.83,0:07:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这跟喜欢不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.86,0:07:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.89,0:07:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.91,0:07:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么自言自语起来了 出故障了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.94,0:07:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢薰先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.97,0:07:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和薰先生相遇很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.40,0:08:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能与你相遇 是我一生以来最棒的意外
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.47,0:08:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.54,0:08:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钱呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.60,0:08:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认犯罪现场 现在 马上来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.63,0:08:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 怎么了 快回答
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.80,0:08:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里 就说…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.86,0:08:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棘手的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.88,0:08:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第九天堂 知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.97,0:09:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是嵌入了让脑活性化程式的晶片
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.42,0:09:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分为九种类型
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.44,0:09:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每种效果不同 不过
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.46,0:09:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果重复多次使用同种颜色
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.49,0:09:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或用法不对
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.51,0:09:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能导致使用者的脑部失控
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.54,0:09:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这九种类型 在某种顺序和期间内使用的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.60,0:09:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被认为能获得完全的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.63,0:09:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认为？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.65,0:09:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人知道那个顺序和期间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.68,0:09:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的也是假情报
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.71,0:09:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这也算是都市传说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.74,0:09:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道流通渠道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.76,0:09:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你的工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.82,0:09:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在做一件棘手的案子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.86,0:09:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个人做的调查
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.88,0:09:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.91,0:09:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要情报费到手的话就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.93,0:09:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.94,0:09:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.98,0:10:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要现付
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.46,0:11:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 薰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.48,0:11:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是你最棒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.60,0:11:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.71,0:11:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.73,0:11:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.91,0:11:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去IGAKAT那是夏多那批人的地盘
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.94,0:11:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就能抓到小喽喽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.40,0:12:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是两只狗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.43,0:12:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然其中一个是女的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.47,0:12:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男的被处理 女的被关起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.51,0:12:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人还没受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.52,0:12:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没受伤吗 好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.56,0:12:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然问不出什么情报 不过还可以当玩具用用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.63,0:12:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.66,0:12:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于夏多…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.74,0:12:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想说那女人被关在哪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.78,0:12:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.80,0:12:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这样 你耳朵就没用了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.87,0:12:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.89,0:12:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛？鼻子？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.92,0:12:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.98,0:13:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.43,0:13:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我 你们这么做 我不会轻易放过你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.48,0:13:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不会轻易放过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.53,0:13:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母狗 等久了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.57,0:13:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这身材当公安真是浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.60,0:13:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.63,0:13:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听话的话 就把你当宠物养
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.70,0:13:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于不听话的宠物 需要好好调教一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.77,0:13:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.79,0:13:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.81,0:13:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我 你们这些变态混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.88,0:13:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.40,0:14:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.61,0:14:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 没用的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.63,0:14:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子就失禁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.65,0:14:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是狗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.70,0:14:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.73,0:14:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.77,0:14:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还想做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.80,0:14:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调教是糖果和皮鞭并用的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.83,0:14:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.86,0:14:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是公安 该凸出的地方也凸出了的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.91,0:14:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 快住手 好恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.98,0:14:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想被上了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.41,0:15:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁想要被你上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.45,0:15:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子你还是处女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.51,0:15:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.58,0:15:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过了 现在起要给你甜美的梦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.62,0:15:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不行 不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.68,0:15:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…放开我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.78,0:15:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.83,0:15:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 舔那里的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.91,0:15:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会受不了的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.42,0:16:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.50,0:16:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么要来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.52,0:16:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.66,0:16:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小便之后是潮吹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.69,0:16:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不知羞耻的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.72,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙看来得需要更严厉的调教啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.78,0:16:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 好凉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.82,0:16:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要放进来 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.84,0:16:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.92,0:16:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出去 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.45,0:17:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了…进来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.57,0:17:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子要裂开了 要裂开了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.68,0:17:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好戏现在才刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.73,0:17:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.87,0:17:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.97,0:17:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好难过 要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.53,0:18:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了我吧 杀了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.61,0:18:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让你轻松
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.75,0:18:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.77,0:18:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要拔掉…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.53,0:19:16.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我加入公安的特别突击队了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.58,0:19:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会输给你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.61,0:19:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.70,0:19:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你应该在总部维护的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.72,0:19:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在薰先生的衣服下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.74,0:19:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确认有复数的武器
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.79,0:19:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是命令 回去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.80,0:19:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.82,0:19:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.83,0:19:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单独行动是被禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.88,0:19:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.89,0:19:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加柰子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.91,0:19:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 从爱丽丝那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.93,0:19:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这次是我个人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.97,0:19:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别妨碍…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.99,0:20:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以比薰先生你快0·1003秒扣下扳机
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.46,0:20:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得的机会 就三人去违反规定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.51,0:20:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.71,0:20:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是公安的走狗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.73,0:20:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯了也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.88,0:20:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红色和黑色 各给她5个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.91,0:20:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计是疯定了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.49,0:21:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我 哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.56,0:21:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.66,0:21:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.76,0:21:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 为了让御子神先生方便潜入
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.79,0:21:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就竟可能的大干一场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.85,0:21:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗 爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.89,0:21:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.65,0:22:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很棒的东西 你好好品尝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.70,0:22:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于变成听话的宠物了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.78,0:22:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁 你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.86,0:22:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.87,0:22:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止了 大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.89,0:22:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 人家很喜欢这件衣服的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.93,0:22:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害得我弄脏了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.96,0:22:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么赔我哟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.48,0:23:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.51,0:23:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 倒是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.53,0:23:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰先生呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.56,0:23:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔚 振作一点 蔚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.59,0:23:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我 已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.62,0:23:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.63,0:23:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 救救我……哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.69,0:23:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.72,0:23:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撞伤及擦伤无数
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.76,0:23:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会阴裂伤 阴道糜烂 子宫颈损伤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.81,0:23:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起外伤来更严重的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.83,0:23:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神方面被灌输了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.86,0:23:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是最近流行的心灵毒品 第九天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.91,0:23:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正式名称好像是MJP
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.96,0:23:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MJP…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.40,0:24:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.42,0:24:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发信者 爱茵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.44,0:24:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是清子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.45,0:24:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰 听说你去找夏多了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.47,0:24:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 救救我… 哥哥 救救我…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.56,0:24:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.58,0:24:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是马希
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.59,0:24:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于知道他的下落了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.61,0:24:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁克斯死的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.64,0:24:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正飘移最靠近的新隆类型的头脑
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.68,0:24:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是爱丽丝 马希潜在爱丽丝的里面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.71,0:24:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.74,0:24:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏多背后的靠山是雷登曼公司的社长
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.77,0:24:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代茵·崴兹曼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.79,0:24:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,详情 你就直接问他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.90,0:24:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.98,0:24:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,系统错误
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.40,0:25:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 是内部系统命令
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.45,0:25:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制御不能


