[Script Info]
Title:
Original Script:
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:960
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004865EC,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,100,2,20,20,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.42,0:00:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标是武器技术师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.37,0:00:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在找来数名娼妓之后 就展开了惊人的杀戮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.44,0:00:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能是JNJP引来的发作性犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.51,0:00:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的不错喔 感觉好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.96,0:01:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是这样 多用你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.32,0:01:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把我伺候好的话 我就杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.93,0:01:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准停
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.58,0:01:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部进入准备位置了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.35,0:01:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.73,0:01:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,103 快回答 怎么了 103 103…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.68,0:01:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点感觉也没有 你技巧太烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.50,0:02:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手 救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.32,0:02:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官 有两名兄弟牺牲了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.86,0:02:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要强行突入是不可能的 支援还没到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.12,0:02:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 下一个 该谁了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.51,0:02:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.99,0:02:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 会从哪里出来呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.65,0:03:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任务完了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.83,0:03:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.69,0:03:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人好像已经被射杀了 马上突入…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.15,0:03:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解 下一件…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.12,0:03:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 是干扰吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.66,0:03:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,XINN
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.63,0:03:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西元2039年9月1日
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.90,0:03:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有电脑因病毒而停止工作
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.93,0:03:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电脑屏幕只是不断的显示着XINN这4个英文字母
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.09,0:03:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一秒钟之后惨事发生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.31,0:03:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名叫网络
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.77,0:03:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个肉眼看不见的巨大生命体
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.62,0:03:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一秒钟的失常
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.77,0:04:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但给人类带来的损失是无法计算的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.65,0:04:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说停止时间的诱人旋律在世界中拉响了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.96,0:04:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒哦 薰君 再来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.05,0:05:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能就要这样高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.66,0:05:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…也要忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.75,0:05:44.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 就这样 薰君 射在里面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.35,0:05:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经…已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.59,0:06:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结论只有一个 薰君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.19,0:06:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就是我是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.20,0:06:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 薰君 你就是我的存在本身
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.25,0:06:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.57,0:06:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又…是那个梦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.84,0:06:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.94,0:06:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经睡了吗 不好意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.43,0:06:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美国大使馆警部的委托
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.35,0:06:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有原因吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.98,0:06:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必知道理由
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.15,0:07:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正那对我来说无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.55,0:07:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上层的城市道路可能塞车
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.37,0:07:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用专用电梯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.70,0:07:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 还有一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.02,0:07:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了现场之后 马上去取配备品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.02,0:07:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配备品？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.81,0:07:23.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标是马希·史贝克塔 18岁
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.81,0:07:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻求避难来到日本
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.09,0:07:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是来投靠的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.65,0:07:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可怜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.23,0:07:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是马希·史贝克塔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.58,0:08:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情报部的石川
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.81,0:08:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请坐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.83,0:08:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然急了点 讨论关于你对我国有什么要求…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.87,0:08:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也别做戏了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.31,0:08:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 该叫猴戏是吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.62,0:08:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和日本合作 这又不是第一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.62,0:08:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.22,0:08:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张椅子 我做了些手脚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.59,0:08:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是8G 要再重一点吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.72,0:08:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 我可没有一直看着\N你的身体像番茄一样烂掉的恶趣味
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.09,0:08:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国家安全调查局
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.54,0:08:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特殊情报局
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.50,0:08:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神薰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.69,0:08:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.37,0:09:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到吧 大名鼎鼎的杀手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.11,0:09:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会知道我？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.98,0:09:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢 我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.31,0:09:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是知道 仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.57,0:09:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.16,0:09:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.60,0:09:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,固定重力已解除了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.54,0:09:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没受伤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.81,0:09:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.31,0:09:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.52,0:09:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请叫我…爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.22,0:09:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰 今天起配备过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.95,0:09:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配备 你是机器人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.68,0:09:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 御子神薰先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.48,0:09:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 是我想太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.91,0:10:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情报外泄
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.20,0:10:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是暗杀马希的情报吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.70,0:10:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 他好像很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.57,0:10:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且那家伙连我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.94,0:10:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来对委托来源有些不安
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.59,0:10:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让爱丽丝去果然是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.77,0:10:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个又是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.08,0:10:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是美国陆军开发出来的兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.91,0:10:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被紧急派来支援的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.86,0:10:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚好想起了你之前跟我要过人手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.79,0:10:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要的是人类
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.66,0:10:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这种恶趣味的做爱人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.14,0:10:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 她还有做爱人偶这个用途啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.37,0:10:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,局长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.26,0:10:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她杀过的人可比你多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.30,0:10:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.26,0:11:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请把我当兵器使用 我是为此被制造出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.18,0:11:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神薰前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.99,0:11:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子 你是在加班吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.08,0:11:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正好在调查地壳下沉的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.44,0:11:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可一点进展也没有 要受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.18,0:11:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地壳下沉…还有那种事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.97,0:11:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还是一个月前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.79,0:11:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种调查交给搞学术的老头就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.59,0:11:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟长官有什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.95,0:11:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是那个女孩的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.91,0:11:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩是个好孩子哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.13,0:11:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有好与不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.03,0:11:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机器只有能用和不能用
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.37,0:12:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且美军的玩具 为什么派到我们这里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.41,0:12:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是我们这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.49,0:12:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝来这里之前\N配备到过海军、SWAT队以及其他很多地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.57,0:12:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能是想利用她在各地的经验\N用这些资料来量产化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.58,0:12:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所说 最强
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.35,0:12:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是LOLI控老头最喜欢的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.32,0:12:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对那些高官来说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.81,0:12:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是很听话的性娃娃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.93,0:12:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也累了 回家休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.34,0:13:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官指示 让我在这里待命
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.66,0:13:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那老头到底在想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.37,0:13:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以在这里设定备用品吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.94,0:13:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.57,0:13:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想放你的那些东西在我客厅里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.36,0:13:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了 那请指示适当的场所
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.65,0:13:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在空闲的只有厨房而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.34,0:13:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.58,0:14:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有一封邮件
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.43,0:14:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老哥 好久不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.29,0:14:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是蔚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.40,0:14:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还活着吧 最近都没跟我联系
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.66,0:14:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你交了女朋友了？ 不可能的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.62,0:14:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.19,0:14:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候在那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.91,0:14:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约在15秒前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.44,0:14:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然没有察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.48,0:15:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早餐准备好了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.33,0:15:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早餐吗 我没接到命令啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.27,0:15:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.94,0:15:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能对公司的配备期待那种东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.06,0:15:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.23,0:15:20.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 薰先生的话我不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是不好意思了 对自己说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.87,0:15:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 腼腆 丢脸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.16,0:15:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.51,0:15:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说还有点困难把
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.61,0:15:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是很困难
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.10,0:15:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰恩·布鲁克斯 年龄36岁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.52,0:15:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是雷曼登公司的AI软体开发部研究员
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.35,0:15:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷曼登 以技术专家为目标
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.51,0:15:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的是保护机密
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.72,0:15:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.65,0:16:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.34,0:16:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次作战的棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.16,0:16:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁克斯是这人很谨慎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.62,0:16:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他几乎不出门 保全设施又严密
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.17,0:16:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 在那方面就是有恶趣味
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.63,0:16:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.94,0:16:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是最适合爱丽丝的作战
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.61,0:16:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.22,0:16:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.07,0:16:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.11,0:16:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我检查许多食谱 做了最适合一般人吃的菜肴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.39,0:16:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么时候命令你做菜了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.91,0:16:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的自我判断
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.88,0:16:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.07,0:16:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我想这是在作战之外的自由选择范围之内
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.21,0:16:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没打算把当做你佣人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.27,0:17:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.21,0:17:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会吃的 不过总得先洗下脸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.56,0:17:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本部有联络来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.93,0:17:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本日2300进行作战计划
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.16,0:17:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全的九天堂 终于到这步了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.36,0:17:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了…来了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.29,0:17:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是MJP吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.66,0:17:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过一小时就补充完毕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.79,0:17:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在生什么气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.68,0:17:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到目前为止爱丽丝都尽责地完成任务
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.22,0:17:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许在那边 是以任务成功为重点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.48,0:17:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没有那必要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.30,0:18:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.54,0:18:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.56,0:18:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早餐那件也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.12,0:18:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝用她的方法接近你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.21,0:18:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这种事…太可怜了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.07,0:18:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想得太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.42,0:18:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是这样的 这是我的直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.02,0:18:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你虽然从事这种工作 有时候说话却不符合伦理
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.75,0:18:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我和爱丽丝一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.48,0:18:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.19,0:18:40.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也知道吧 我以前…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.35,0:18:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被情报员强暴的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.38,0:18:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 确实是不幸的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.54,0:18:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算打着情报员身份 结局也是个杀人犯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.14,0:19:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全是禽兽 我也没区别
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.93,0:19:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加奈子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.24,0:19:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.85,0:19:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果对象是前辈你 就算被强暴也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.69,0:19:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.39,0:19:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨女孩 这样不叫强暴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.38,0:20:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.47,0:20:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.19,0:20:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.29,0:20:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一点 好久没做了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.23,0:20:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 我会慢慢的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.72,0:20:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没关系了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.90,0:20:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.99,0:20:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.02,0:20:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感到什么 好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.96,0:21:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不行了 不行了前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.36,0:21:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新面孔啊 进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.89,0:21:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张人偶一般的脸真叫人兴奋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.42,0:22:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开启索敌系统 确定多名敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.44,0:22:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5名确认 武装确认
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.23,0:22:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有武装 是陷阱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.79,0:22:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边准备好了 任务继续进行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.76,0:22:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.27,0:22:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁克斯已发现了 危险 请马上撤离
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.46,0:22:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱莉丝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.40,0:22:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.17,0:23:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.18,0:23:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动 公安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.22,0:23:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟是公安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.68,0:23:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 为什么你们会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.02,0:23:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有情报说这里潜伏了武装恐怖份子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.77,0:23:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说哥哥你怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.99,0:23:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武装恐怖份子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.39,0:23:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 被摆了一道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.71,0:23:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在这里待命 知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.21,0:23:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么权利…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.60,0:23:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们被骗了 这里根本没有恐怖份子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.14,0:23:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗 不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.57,0:23:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.44,0:23:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.09,0:23:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.44,0:23:50.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御子神先生 请撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.50,0:23:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这房间里有…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.47,0:23:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.11,0:23:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起爆装置 是炸弹吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.08,0:24:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是看你和公安演了一出好戏
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.48,0:24:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你伪造了情报吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.39,0:24:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说很简单啊御子神君
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.81,0:24:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个脑波…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.47,0:24:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是绝对不会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.98,0:24:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马希…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.83,0:24:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算这个身体死了 我还是会来看你的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.09,0:24:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史贝克塔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.03,0:24:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.53,0:24:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是你不死在这里的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.10,0:24:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举起手来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.76,0:24:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.22,0:25:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱丽丝


