[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.06,0:00:21.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 胸部好像扯著…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.83,0:00:22.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.36,0:00:30.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.38,0:00:32.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開我 放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.33,0:00:40.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算妳說放開 小蠕蟲又怎麼捨得呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.43,0:00:42.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洛可可 妳…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.19,0:00:50.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不可以摸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.03,0:00:53.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.28,0:00:54.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.72,0:01:01.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要說謊哦 妳看乳頭都這麼敏感硬起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.64,0:01:03.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為…為什麼妳會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.58,0:01:12.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 那裡不可以 快要爆發了不行了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.21,0:01:16.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 姬布莉爾被人捏胸部有感覺了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.06,0:01:19.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 不是這樣嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.06,0:01:24.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還嘴硬哦 這樣的姬布莉爾就要…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.80,0:01:37.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明沒有奶的呀 為什麼…為什麼會有這種要爆發的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.00,0:01:40.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能這麼用力吸…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.56,0:01:46.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小蠕蟲 繼續用力吸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.19,0:01:51.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了 要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.35,0:01:57.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不行了 出來了 要出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.82,0:02:07.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙…騙人的 出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.49,0:02:11.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙人的 奶…奶出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.79,0:02:16.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加工成美食吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.09,0:02:23.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和那種連小孩子都知道的 有名的最高級牛肉Milk Dunk一樣哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.70,0:02:26.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這次要把這個插進去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.78,0:02:31.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.94,0:02:37.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進來了 蠕蟲碰到子宮了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.27,0:02:43.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣吸乳頭 又會出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.22,0:02:45.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奶又會出來的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.83,0:02:50.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 反正奶出來了 也很舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.99,0:02:55.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好粗的進來了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.76,0:02:58.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裡面都滿了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.18,0:03:01.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.88,0:03:08.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在奶又要出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.16,0:03:14.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是無可救藥的天使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.73,0:03:16.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 盡情高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.25,0:03:18.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳這大變態
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.77,0:03:24.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了 要去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:30.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.87,0:03:34.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又流出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.89,0:03:46.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎一切順利嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.87,0:03:48.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜜提芽衣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.56,0:03:52.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣繼續解放性欲能量的話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.87,0:03:57.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沉睡在姬布莉爾體內的魔王力量 要覺醒也只是時間問題
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.98,0:04:01.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,終於要從聖天使變成魔界天使了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.10,0:04:05.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有 那個女人的所在地找到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.40,0:04:09.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 正要去問候問候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.92,0:04:14.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 要是沒有礙事的傢伙也挺無趣的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.59,0:04:44.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了 光姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.20,0:04:48.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天妳心情很好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.73,0:04:52.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為我已經是成熟的女人了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.84,0:04:56.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且…第一次是和哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.56,0:04:57.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.81,0:05:01.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那今晚煮紅豆飯來慶祝囉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.81,0:05:02.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.80,0:05:05.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 妳們兩個
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.67,0:05:09.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 其實我還有點擔憂的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.01,0:05:15.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真是 你要好好的負責啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.92,0:05:21.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唔唔 原來這麼激烈嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.60,0:05:26.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是被戀人理華姊姊知道的話 事情就鬧大啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.05,0:05:30.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笨…笨蛋 我是為了救理華 沒辦法才和小光做的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.51,0:05:33.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有這種歪點子…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.84,0:05:36.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.15,0:05:40.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理…理華姊姊是戀人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.90,0:05:42.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.30,0:05:42.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.30,0:05:45.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒跟小光說過嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.98,0:05:50.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實我和理華從暑假就開始交往了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.30,0:05:52.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這 這個我沒聽過
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.04,0:05:57.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你和理華姊姊…那個…H過了我是知道…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.88,0:06:00.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過那只是為了儲存愛能
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.91,0:06:03.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒聽過你們是什麼戀人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.21,0:06:05.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳 妳生個什麼氣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.91,0:06:07.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為小光…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.06,0:06:09.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.17,0:06:11.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.58,0:06:15.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我吃飽了 先上學去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.40,0:06:32.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Question 3
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.59,0:06:35.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,What is it that goes
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.34,0:06:39.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,on four legs in the morning
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.44,0:06:43.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,on two legs at noon
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.61,0:06:47.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,and on three legs in the evening?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.29,0:06:49.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Do you understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.90,0:06:51.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,I will repeat again
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.58,0:06:54.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,What is it that goes...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.47,0:07:01.47,*Default,,0000,0385,0050,,From：小光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.47,0:07:01.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0010,,sub：午餐到屋頂來吃吧。( ^ ▽ ^ )/
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.36,0:07:15.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙款待
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.97,0:07:18.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別客氣 粗茶淡飯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.26,0:07:20.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.59,0:07:23.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上那件事…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.94,0:07:29.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事啦 我沒放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.52,0:07:30.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是…是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.20,0:07:32.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光只是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.89,0:07:35.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為覺得哥哥好像要離開自己身邊一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.86,0:07:37.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感到有點寂寞而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.35,0:07:41.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別說這個了 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.56,0:07:47.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要儲存愛能 學會秘技 不是一定要在學校裡H嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.15,0:07:49.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話是這麼說…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.09,0:07:53.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死拉芙 連這種事情也和小光說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.81,0:07:55.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以啦 所以啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.31,0:07:57.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小 小光同學?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.55,0:08:00.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼突然幹什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.81,0:08:10.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.00,0:08:13.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光沒問題嗎 在這種地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.92,0:08:18.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 只要是和哥哥 我可以做很多H的事情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.86,0:08:24.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經熱起來了 而且還越來越硬了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.45,0:08:29.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.30,0:08:35.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳的技術很棒 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.58,0:08:40.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.11,0:08:49.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,越來越大了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.73,0:08:53.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 哥哥 前面出來了什麼東西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.02,0:08:58.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個是前列腺液 舒服的時候就會出來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.97,0:09:03.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光讓哥哥覺得舒服了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.69,0:09:05.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好開心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.39,0:09:08.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那這樣又怎麼樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.22,0:09:10.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.92,0:09:19.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用小光剛脫下來的象內褲 這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.55,0:09:23.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有體溫餘熱的感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.49,0:09:35.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 小光的內褲舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.55,0:09:39.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一想到那是包著小光的那裡的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.05,0:09:41.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就變得好興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.31,0:09:44.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.23,0:09:49.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 要出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:54.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要出來了 精液要出來了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.34,0:09:58.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊 就這樣射在小光的內褲上面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.99,0:10:00.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.30,0:10:03.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來了 出來了 出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.23,0:10:16.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥射了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.66,0:10:20.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為太舒服了 妳的手和內褲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.94,0:10:25.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.99,0:10:37.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光的裡面已經洪水泛濫了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.44,0:10:44.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的手指在小光裡面動
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.36,0:10:51.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夾得真緊 剛才看到我射精已經興奮不已了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.20,0:10:55.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦 小光才沒那麼H嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.84,0:11:01.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要這麼用力 不行了 擦到裡面了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.66,0:11:05.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用手指就到此為止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.72,0:11:09.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.47,0:11:12.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 來吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.69,0:11:21.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.47,0:11:23.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.07,0:11:49.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡和胸部被哥哥這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.03,0:11:51.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太有感覺了 要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.06,0:12:08.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光色色的裡面…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.30,0:12:14.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的…粗大的…在動
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.44,0:12:30.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要來了…要來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.32,0:12:32.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.75,0:12:34.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 就這樣 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.97,0:12:37.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣在小光的裡面…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.89,0:12:40.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 在小光的裡面…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.14,0:12:42.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那裡面射精吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.86,0:12:43.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.39,0:12:47.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.19,0:12:56.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.13,0:12:59.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好暖…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.94,0:13:03.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的…好暖…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.62,0:13:10.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 小光 又射在裡面了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.29,0:13:16.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 因為哥哥在小光裡面出來很舒服是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.18,0:13:22.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥真H
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.06,0:13:43.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你的同學芽衣美在這所醫院住院嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.42,0:13:48.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 聽拉芙說 好像是在公園裡暈倒 然後被人送來了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.53,0:13:50.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是這裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.40,0:13:54.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.17,0:13:57.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音無 我來探望妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.40,0:14:02.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還在睡覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.50,0:14:18.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個…該怎麼說呢…反正
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.45,0:14:22.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 好大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.27,0:14:27.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥不能看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.18,0:14:33.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到了看病的時間了嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.79,0:14:36.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 吵醒妳了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.98,0:14:45.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神野君
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.64,0:14:50.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…我們是來探病的…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.34,0:14:55.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.47,0:14:57.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我真是的 穿成這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.45,0:15:03.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.84,0:15:06.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是那麼大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.34,0:15:10.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.81,0:15:16.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總而言之 沒事就最好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.89,0:15:19.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 謝謝你關心我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.11,0:15:23.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,請問 這位是?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.58,0:15:28.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙叫小光 是我的義妹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.17,0:15:32.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.87,0:15:35.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:38.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,割到手指一點點 沒什麼大礙的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.84,0:15:41.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼大礙…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.22,0:15:43.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是笨手笨腳 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.51,0:15:48.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 小光 我記得OK繃就在那邊的抽屜…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.81,0:15:53.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音無
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.27,0:15:55.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神 神野君?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.89,0:15:58.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳帶病在身 別亂動啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.65,0:16:00.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.87,0:16:17.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了 小光 剛才一直怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.30,0:16:23.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正小光的胸部 就是沒有芽衣美學姊那麼雄～偉嘛 哼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.99,0:16:26.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳又在發什麼脾氣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.41,0:16:29.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 光姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.95,0:16:32.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.90,0:16:37.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 光姊姊 大事不好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.73,0:16:43.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好啦 不好啦 大事不好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.14,0:16:46.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳為什麼會從垃圾筒裡面出來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.38,0:16:50.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搞什麼 髒死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.19,0:16:53.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別管這個啦 大事不好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.67,0:16:55.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.38,0:16:57.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天國情報部發來的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.61,0:17:01.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜜提芽衣要向芽衣美姊姊下手了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.78,0:17:03.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼? 音無?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.44,0:17:12.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,音無
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.38,0:17:24.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 好像慢了一步呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.26,0:17:27.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神野直人和蘿莉天使
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.88,0:17:30.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蜜提芽衣 混帳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.64,0:17:35.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不快點救音無芽衣美 她就要死掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.38,0:17:43.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等著 音無 現在就來救妳
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.07,0:17:46.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光姊姊 準備好了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.79,0:17:52.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 來吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.00,0:18:02.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Angel Amore
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.12,0:18:06.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為大家說明一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.38,0:18:12.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神野光利用愛能的力量 可以變身為聖天使姬布莉爾阿瑞斯-Djibril Aries-
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.82,0:18:17.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,與最愛的哥哥性交 喜悅和後患的矛盾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.57,0:18:19.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是她力量的根源
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.08,0:18:28.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,清麗脫俗 心懷正義 美貌出眾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.00,0:18:29.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓病人平躺下來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.59,0:18:31.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打針的Erotical
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.69,0:18:33.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H的犯罪 絕不能饒恕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.14,0:18:37.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聖天使姬布莉爾阿瑞斯 全新誕生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.36,0:18:45.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.42,0:18:50.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快想想辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.82,0:19:08.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.17,0:19:10.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼 好噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.16,0:19:12.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.56,0:19:18.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要碰我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.34,0:19:25.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 被觸手撫摸胸部有感覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.88,0:19:29.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到你們還能造出新的姬布莉爾來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.27,0:19:32.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正也是沒用的天使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.06,0:19:37.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧看吧 妳最重要的地方被蠕蟲盯上了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.66,0:19:41.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行 那裡不行 快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.57,0:19:44.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.43,0:19:47.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要擦那個地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.10,0:19:52.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能吸乳頭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.44,0:19:57.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被蠕蟲摩擦也會濕掉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.50,0:20:03.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是 太強烈所以濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.50,0:20:05.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還嘴硬嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.06,0:20:08.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲 繼續用力
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.87,0:20:12.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼激烈的話 會出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.74,0:20:14.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尿尿會出來的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.70,0:20:19.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 出來了 出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.79,0:20:31.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都看光了 尿尿漏出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.21,0:20:39.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是 居然還能在神聖的醫院尿尿
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.11,0:20:42.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.68,0:20:44.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要緊 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.50,0:20:49.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意妳尿床的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.82,0:20:53.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那只是因為哥哥是個大變態
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.03,0:21:01.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進來了 到我的裡面來了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.58,0:21:04.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服的樣子呢 阿瑞斯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.59,0:21:06.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這麼舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.24,0:21:24.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲 在天使的體內盡情釋放你污濁的精液吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.09,0:21:26.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.08,0:21:31.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥以外的精液 進來小光的體內…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.36,0:21:33.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,絕對不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.81,0:21:41.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.10,0:22:02.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.05,0:22:04.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,芽衣美姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.78,0:22:06.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 到極限了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.90,0:22:10.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以才說洛可可做的蠕蟲根本派不上用場
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.35,0:22:12.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.19,0:22:18.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 對不起 小光沒起來作用
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.82,0:22:24.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算你們走運 蠕蟲到了極限
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.36,0:22:28.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿瑞斯 下次而見的時候會好好疼愛妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.92,0:22:30.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,期待吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.38,0:22:41.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說話這麼傲慢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.45,0:22:47.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,輸給那種惡魔真不甘心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.03,0:22:55.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽好 回好以後要好好反省啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.77,0:22:57.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別怒氣沖沖啦 拉芙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.95,0:23:01.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正音無也沒事了 算了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.47,0:23:04.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥根本不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.20,0:23:09.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不打敗提芽衣怎麼救出理華姊姊啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.62,0:23:15.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 理華姊姊回來以後 哥哥就不再需要小光了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.10,0:23:21.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 小光是為了向你告白而回來的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.86,0:23:25.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 哥哥已經有了理華姊姊這個…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.30,0:23:28.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,戀人了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.33,0:23:37.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.71,0:23:41.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光姊姊好奸詐啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.68,0:23:43.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙也要 拉芙也要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.65,0:23:46.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿妳們兩個沒轍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.09,0:23:49.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 理華姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.80,0:23:55.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過 只是現在讓小光獨佔哥哥 可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.52,0:24:10.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小直 我想和小直做嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.02,0:24:14.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要那樣的觸手 我想和小直做嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.43,0:24:16.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小直…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.26,0:24:23.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要小直的那個 插進理華的裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.10,0:24:28.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 好像只有蠕蟲還滿足不了妳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.11,0:24:38.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個 小直的…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.95,0:24:43.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 姬布莉爾想要這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.85,0:24:48.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要 不要這樣的玩具 我要真的陰莖
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.41,0:24:51.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真沒辦法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.66,0:24:56.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久別重逢的感覺怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.34,0:25:00.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 好棒 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.53,0:25:03.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 終於肯坦露心扉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.03,0:25:06.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就獎勵妳 告訴妳一件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.84,0:25:08.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好…事?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.97,0:25:14.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神野光在蜜提芽衣面前變身為姬布莉爾了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.52,0:25:15.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.70,0:25:21.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,問題來了 神野光會和誰交尾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.83,0:25:23.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.11,0:25:29.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神野直人真是作孽的男人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.29,0:25:37.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被惡魔侵犯還有感覺 真是無可救藥的淫亂天使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.79,0:25:49.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快要去了 我會射在妳裡面的 好好感謝我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.55,0:25:54.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裡面不行 不是直人的話不能在裡面嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.24,0:25:57.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經…遲了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.60,0:25:59.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.92,0:26:01.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.78,0:26:06.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.20,0:26:12.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來了…出來了好多精液…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.02,0:26:29.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正妳就用H的姿態來迎接妳的神野直人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.67,0:26:36.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會那樣的…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.85,0:26:40.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小直說過最喜歡我的呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.12,0:26:54.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La La La La La
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.94,0:26:57.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La La La La La
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.64,0:27:00.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.41,0:27:02.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Little My Star Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.69,0:27:03.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.69,0:27:03.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.73,0:27:18.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開けばドア 始まるまた 色んなストーリー
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.73,0:27:18.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開啟門 開始各式各樣的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.12,0:27:24.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迷える道 照らす光 あたしのセオリー
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.12,0:27:24.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,將迷途之道照耀光明是我的理論
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.54,0:27:29.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打ち上げてよ あたしの空 あなたのロケット
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.54,0:27:29.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發射到我的天空是你的火箭
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.96,0:27:34.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一人よりも パワーアップするから
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.96,0:27:34.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比獨自一人還能提升力量
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.88,0:27:40.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,I know ずっとずっと 迷って Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.88,0:27:40.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,I know 一直一直迷惑 Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.98,0:27:46.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,きっときっと わかったいの
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.98,0:27:46.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必定必定想要知道
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.41,0:27:51.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,もっとホント 素直に
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.41,0:27:51.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更加真實坦率
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.77,0:27:56.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと 気持ちいえたら
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.77,0:27:56.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好地感受的話
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.22,0:27:59.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,１ ２ ３ ４ いいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.22,0:27:59.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3 4 可以唷
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.97,0:28:02.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Oh My Oh My Little My Heart
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.65,0:28:05.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇気を 出すから
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.65,0:28:05.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,提起勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.39,0:28:08.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Fighting Fighting Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.10,0:28:10.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使よ 目覚めて
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.10,0:28:10.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使啊 覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.47,0:28:10.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.47,0:28:10.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
