[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.00,0:00:24.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 我只是見到蠕蟲就…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.03,0:00:27.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變得這麼H了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.22,0:00:30.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 哎呀?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.91,0:00:35.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正妳也已經發情了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.27,0:00:37.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.95,0:00:42.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 真的變成了H的天使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.65,0:00:46.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.86,0:00:50.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,0K今天就讓妳完美墮落囉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.23,0:00:53.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 直人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.96,0:00:57.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好像喜歡上洛可的調教了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.59,0:01:10.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡…好癢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.02,0:01:16.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不能碰陰核
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.25,0:01:19.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡是敏感的地方呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.36,0:01:31.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吉普莉露真是 碰到陰核以後那裡的入口就一下子就緊縮了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.67,0:01:33.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要說
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.20,0:01:38.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好羞人 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.78,0:01:41.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,愛液一口氣出來了好多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.01,0:01:46.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 好羞人 身體好熱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.82,0:01:53.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發出色色的聲音 吉普莉露真的是H的天使呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.76,0:01:58.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 我是H的天使…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.20,0:02:02.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 開始坦率起來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.10,0:02:05.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 給妳獎賞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.38,0:02:23.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.82,0:02:31.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,裡面…再往裡面…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.80,0:02:41.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣說哦 再往裡面 插進子宮裡面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.08,0:02:51.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來了 碰到子宮了 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.25,0:03:01.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,揉搓著胸部 那裡也有觸手在深處遊走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.86,0:03:10.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁股…屁股的洞…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.90,0:03:14.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擦著那裡的裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.64,0:03:18.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡和屁股…都滿了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.49,0:03:21.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兩邊都充滿了很幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.35,0:03:25.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.74,0:03:30.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我變成傻瓜了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.45,0:03:35.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去我就只知道H了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.05,0:03:41.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣 這個色天使
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.81,0:03:45.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.59,0:03:47.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 就讓妳滿足吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.43,0:03:50.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲 灑在她身上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.30,0:04:03.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.91,0:04:21.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滿滿都是… 身體裡面都是精液了呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.08,0:04:25.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 全身都是精液了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.35,0:04:29.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣滿足了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.39,0:04:33.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒…還想要…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.09,0:04:37.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲的骯髒的精液 我還要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.10,0:04:43.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吃…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.67,0:04:50.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 很好 吉普莉露
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.91,0:04:53.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就讓妳做更多H的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.28,0:04:56.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的?好高興
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.56,0:05:40.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.83,0:05:43.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上課呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.84,0:05:54.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 你來這裡到底要幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.54,0:05:58.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天挑戰3P
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.91,0:06:00.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,3P是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.73,0:06:05.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦 我不要和哥哥以外的人H
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.19,0:06:11.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且 就算說3P 這裡也只有我們兩個哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.63,0:06:13.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別擔心 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.49,0:06:19.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在這種場面下 那傢伙不用叫也一定會出現的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.97,0:06:20.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.17,0:06:22.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對 那傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.71,0:06:24.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.14,0:06:35.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…你在叫拉芙嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.52,0:06:38.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然打中了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.73,0:06:42.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 妳嚇成這樣 簡直就像是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.66,0:06:45.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為拉芙是美少女天使一樣嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.86,0:06:47.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒人會這麼認為的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.86,0:06:51.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼拉芙會在這種地方的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.56,0:06:57.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還用說嘛 剩下的一個名額當然就是我拉芙啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.17,0:07:00.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 這三個人可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.97,0:07:04.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…拉芙的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.81,0:07:10.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好啦 交尾 交尾 交尾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.18,0:07:15.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙 不要說幾次啦 好難為情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.79,0:07:20.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 舌頭伸出來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.83,0:07:22.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.01,0:07:43.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 小光 這次趴在上面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.32,0:07:51.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣嗎 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.34,0:07:53.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.03,0:08:02.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得好難為情啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.98,0:08:07.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣…這樣擦的話 內褲…內褲要弄髒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.44,0:08:09.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就幫妳脫掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.55,0:08:12.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 好難為情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.53,0:08:23.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的手指擦著那裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.41,0:08:32.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.06,0:08:36.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.01,0:08:40.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.49,0:08:54.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光姊姊 妳去得也太快啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.10,0:08:57.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣儲存不到愛能啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.30,0:09:01.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我忍不住了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.77,0:09:05.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再來一次姊妹愛好啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.91,0:09:12.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 請認真舔拉芙的那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.27,0:09:20.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比想像中的還要有感覺啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.49,0:09:25.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.68,0:09:43.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.66,0:09:57.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多可以啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.64,0:10:03.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 把這個巨大的Penis插進姊姊裡面去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.17,0:10:04.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.74,0:10:08.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 我進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.18,0:10:19.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進來了 好粗的 進去那裡了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.59,0:10:26.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到裡面 到裡面去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.06,0:10:29.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,緊嗎 小光的裡面緊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.76,0:10:31.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.90,0:10:35.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 動起來吧 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.83,0:10:39.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給小光…給小光的裡面很多很多的愛能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.51,0:10:47.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡…那裡好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.20,0:10:53.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光姊姊的…很美昧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.70,0:10:57.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙的這裡也很香甜很美昧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.22,0:11:01.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 不好 快要出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.99,0:11:04.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊 哥哥 出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.53,0:11:07.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在小光的裡面射出好多好多的愛能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.90,0:11:14.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 出來了 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.91,0:11:28.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精液從那裡漏出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.09,0:11:35.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.28,0:11:39.13,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒啊 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.33,0:11:42.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣姊姊一定會Power Up了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.57,0:11:49.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就讓我看看Power Up的實力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.18,0:11:56.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.90,0:12:17.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.93,0:12:20.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 是梨佳
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.07,0:12:22.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 妳沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.84,0:12:29.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我啦 是我 直人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.58,0:12:32.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳怎麼了 梨佳 回答我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.25,0:12:38.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…是梨佳…沒錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.29,0:12:42.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 樣子有點古怪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.20,0:12:49.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很遺憾 神野直人 吉普莉露已經成為我洛可可的性奴隸了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.07,0:12:53.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說的話她根本不會聽進去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.80,0:12:55.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個…小不點惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.62,0:12:58.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳到底對梨佳幹了些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.38,0:13:01.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少囉嗦 不許叫小不點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.68,0:13:03.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不滅蠕蟲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.69,0:13:08.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.33,0:13:12.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然敢叫洛可可大人做小不點 這就是報應
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.70,0:13:16.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然把哥哥…不能原諒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.17,0:13:17.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.57,0:13:19.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:32.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Angel Amore
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.85,0:13:58.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把無罪的人們捲入其中
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.06,0:14:00.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把內褲潤濕的Erotical
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.65,0:14:03.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H的犯罪 絕不能饒恕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.23,0:14:15.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忠實的性奴隸 吉普莉露
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.23,0:14:20.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,讓阿瑞斯徹底墮落
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.47,0:14:23.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是 洛可可大人 請交給我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.64,0:14:32.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 好久不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.61,0:14:33.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳姊姊?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.16,0:14:50.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.27,0:15:00.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 那裡是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.24,0:15:04.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 陰核都已經準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.41,0:15:07.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要壞掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.41,0:15:12.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哭聲真動聽呢 好吧 再用力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.29,0:15:20.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,H的陰核呢 妳就是用這個來誘惑直人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.09,0:15:22.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不…不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.40,0:15:26.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.37,0:15:29.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 尿尿要出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.00,0:15:32.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,盡情失禁吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.44,0:15:38.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.95,0:15:42.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的要…出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.32,0:15:48.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:53.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好多的量 真羞人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.03,0:15:58.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停不下來…好難為情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.27,0:16:01.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別擔心 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.54,0:16:06.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對我來說失禁只是…Good Job啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.21,0:16:10.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說過那只是因為哥哥是個大變態
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.58,0:16:16.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳姊姊 那裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.45,0:16:19.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.25,0:16:22.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭也這麼硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.17,0:16:29.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒的反應 小光原來這麼喜歡H的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.90,0:16:32.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,身體不由自主熱起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.60,0:16:34.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.64,0:16:41.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那妳也喜歡被觸手玩弄吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.53,0:16:58.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好粗啊 進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.70,0:17:06.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我的裡面也…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.70,0:17:10.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,動起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.65,0:17:26.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,擦到了 那裡的裡面 觸手在摩擦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.26,0:17:32.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好緊 好喜歡觸手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.14,0:17:34.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.70,0:17:40.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光也喜歡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.93,0:17:43.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡 好喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.92,0:17:47.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,觸手和H都好喜歡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.35,0:17:51.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 妳在說什麼下流話
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.35,0:17:55.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥沒有養過這樣的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:02.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿瑞斯終於也成了蠕蟲的俘虜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.70,0:18:08.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳姊姊 小光…已經壞掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.30,0:18:10.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是…已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.51,0:18:14.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起…一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.94,0:18:19.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠕蟲 和平時一樣把白色的汁液灑上去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.02,0:18:27.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要死了 要去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.89,0:18:33.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了 小光也 白色的 白色的出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.81,0:18:44.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子裡面 全都是觸手的精液…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.08,0:18:54.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種感覺好喜歡 好有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.62,0:19:03.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了 哥哥 這樣下去光姊姊會…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.86,0:19:08.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福 被觸手射在裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.93,0:19:10.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.47,0:19:14.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉芙 小光…小光…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.37,0:19:17.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對哥哥也沒說過那樣的話啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.87,0:19:21.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜點 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.88,0:19:26.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 小光 和我一起墮落到某處吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.55,0:19:28.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 梨佳姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.39,0:19:33.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 不行 清醒過來吧 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.33,0:19:37.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒用的 沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.79,0:19:42.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.40,0:19:47.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連妳也被帶走的話 我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.09,0:19:51.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又變成孤零零一個了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.18,0:20:01.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.76,0:20:10.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別哭 小光
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.49,0:20:13.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會保護妳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.00,0:20:18.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.12,0:20:19.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.12,0:20:42.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.73,0:20:45.66,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿瑞斯明明已經墮落了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.36,0:20:47.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不滅蠕蟲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.87,0:21:01.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,洛可可 這是我和哥哥的…愛的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.56,0:21:20.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,功虧一簣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.30,0:21:23.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別跑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.43,0:21:26.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.86,0:21:31.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.91,0:21:35.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,光姊姊趕跑了惡魔啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.82,0:21:45.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 光芒四射
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.27,0:22:12.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.95,0:22:19.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小時候孤零零的我 哥哥就是這樣鼓勵我的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.86,0:22:24.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以現在該小光來鼓勵哥哥了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.70,0:22:26.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.11,0:22:32.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我心跳會這麼快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:22:35.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光只是義理妹妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.98,0:22:42.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 以後你也可以對小光做H的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.52,0:22:44.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.39,0:22:49.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和愛能沒有關係 請把我看成一個女人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.80,0:22:51.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光希望哥哥抱緊我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.12,0:22:54.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.61,0:23:04.18,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要緊 哥哥 來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.02,0:23:12.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兩邊胸部都摸到了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.22,0:23:16.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡小光的胸部 這麼柔軟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.18,0:23:21.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 乳頭…小光的乳頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.35,0:23:23.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.14,0:23:41.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的舌頭…舔著我最重要的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.21,0:23:43.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以舔得更激烈點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.92,0:23:45.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一點點啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.29,0:23:50.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 哥哥的舌頭舔得好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.76,0:23:59.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 不行 不要這樣弄陰核
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.90,0:24:07.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的…不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:09.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.37,0:24:17.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來這麼有感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.39,0:24:21.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還要再弄嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.16,0:24:24.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光…小光
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.39,0:24:26.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想哥哥進來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.99,0:24:31.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥巨大的…進來小光的那裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.00,0:24:33.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.48,0:24:54.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的好硬 在我的裡面動得很激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.59,0:25:00.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 那裡…那裡開始麻痹了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.03,0:25:04.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡是哪裡?告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.66,0:25:09.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是那裡 哥哥和小光合為一體的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.20,0:25:11.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光的…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.24,0:25:14.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 好難為情
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.79,0:25:35.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥 哥哥 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.20,0:25:37.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我快要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.97,0:25:42.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是 我也快要出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.61,0:25:50.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 哥哥 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.38,0:25:53.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小光
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.52,0:26:07.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像哥哥恢復精神了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.93,0:26:13.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的模樣全部都錄音下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.57,0:26:18.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了這個 一天三餐也可以開懷大吃啦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.24,0:26:27.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥的睡相好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.61,0:26:29.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨佳…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.62,0:26:40.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要緊 梨佳姊姊我一定會救出來的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.30,0:26:43.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以…到那之前…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.53,0:26:47.40,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥可以讓小光獨佔的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.30,0:27:09.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La La La La La
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.12,0:27:12.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La La La La La
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.82,0:27:15.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,La La La La Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.59,0:27:17.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Little My Star Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.87,0:27:18.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.87,0:27:18.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.91,0:27:34.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開けばドア 始まるまた 色んなストーリー
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.91,0:27:34.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,開啟門 開始各式各樣的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.30,0:27:39.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迷える道 照らす光 あたしのセオリー
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.30,0:27:39.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,將迷途之道照耀光明是我的理論
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.72,0:27:44.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打ち上げてよ あたしの空 あなたのロケット
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.72,0:27:44.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發射到我的天空是你的火箭
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.14,0:27:49.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一人よりも パワーアップするから
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.14,0:27:49.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比獨自一人還能提升力量
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.06,0:27:56.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,I know ずっとずっと 迷って Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.06,0:27:56.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,I know 一直一直迷惑 Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.16,0:28:01.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,きっときっと わかったいの
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.16,0:28:01.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必定必定想要知道
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.59,0:28:06.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,もっとホント 素直に
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.59,0:28:06.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更加真實坦率
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.95,0:28:11.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと 気持ちいえたら
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.95,0:28:11.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好地感受的話
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.40,0:28:15.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,１ ２ ３ ４ いいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.40,0:28:15.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3 4 可以唷
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.15,0:28:17.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Oh My Oh My Little My Heart
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.83,0:28:20.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,勇気を 出すから
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.83,0:28:20.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,提起勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.57,0:28:23.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Fighting Fighting Little My Star
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.28,0:28:25.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使よ 目覚めて
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.28,0:28:25.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天使啊 覺醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.65,0:28:26.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.65,0:28:26.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.15,0:28:28.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Oh My Oh My Little My Pain
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.65,0:28:31.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,強さに変えたら
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.65,0:28:31.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變強的話
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.45,0:28:34.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,Fighting Fighting Little Your Smile
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.15,0:28:36.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,夜空に見つけよう
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.15,0:28:36.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可看見夜空
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.50,0:28:36.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,ハイ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.50,0:28:36.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是