[Script Info]
;     字幕由最果ての神狐字幕組製作
;     其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈，謝謝!
;     製作人員
;     翻譯：Ericgod GP03
;     校對：GP03
;     時間：「伽藍」
;     後期：Z-KUN
; // 欢迎访问最果ての神狐 http://xuhu.org
Title:最果ての神狐
Original Script:最果ての神狐字幕組
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微軟正黑體,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0.5,0,1,2,0,2,20,20,5,136
Style: 00,微軟正黑體,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,20,20,0,136
Style: OPJ,微軟正黑體,25,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,85,85,15,128
Style: OPC,微軟正黑體,25,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,76,76,8,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.92,0:00:05.10,*00,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻譯：Ericgod GP03  校對：GP03
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.30,0:00:10.30,*00,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,時間：「伽藍」  後期：NTR型Z君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.50,0:00:15.00,*00,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最果ての神狐字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.57,0:00:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍者麽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.22,0:00:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你們麽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.32,0:00:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次居然是向鱷麻賀藩叛逃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.57,0:00:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一群不知廉恥的家夥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.74,0:00:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨便你說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.71,0:00:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們夜刀三人眾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.92,0:00:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白銀之空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.55,0:00:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是為了打敗你會不擇手段
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.03,0:00:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必殺 烈風活殺陣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.62,0:00:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.73,0:00:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.62,0:00:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裏...這裏好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.18,0:01:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太弱了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.52,0:01:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我記著
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.29,0:01:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一群煩人的家夥
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.70,0:01:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.55,0:01:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是沒這身緊身衣的話 現在怎麽樣就不知道了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.24,0:01:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.41,0:01:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳裝女友 動畫版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.54,0:02:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個可能有點不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.63,0:02:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 今天是和小廣玩泳裝PLAY的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.65,0:02:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺激點可能也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.60,0:02:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不錯呢 一定很好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.60,0:02:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 很不錯啊 樹理很適合啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.10,0:02:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實 也不是討厭的顏色　只是白色的比較受歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.55,0:02:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樹理 我隨便的反正就選白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.23,0:02:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 不要用下流的眼神看著我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.08,0:02:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.14,0:02:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H的是你耶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.36,0:02:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明在我面前一直還要大膽的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.02,0:02:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 如果買了這個泳裝 絕對
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.83,0:02:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦哦 非常合身啊 樹理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.43,0:02:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 果然還是色色的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.71,0:02:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少讓我先穿上護具吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.65,0:03:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 樹理明明也很高興的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.64,0:03:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.50,0:03:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽 幹什麽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.52,0:03:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 泳裝的觸感 超爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.59,0:03:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.96,0:03:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種地方 不要用肉棒磨啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.98,0:03:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的啦 這邊也要磨是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.31,0:03:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.92,0:03:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那裏因為我的抽插變透明了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.51,0:03:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 你有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.75,0:03:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.79,0:03:43.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 讓我用胸部作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.56,0:03:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服麽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.03,0:03:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣 舒服麽
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.71,0:03:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.02,0:03:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 真是驚人的新感觸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.04,0:03:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白癡 不要那麽興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.11,0:04:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我也變得怪怪的了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.49,0:04:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.70,0:04:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得沾上奇怪的興趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.44,0:04:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.64,0:04:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子好酥麻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.50,0:04:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才開始就濕漉漉的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.73,0:04:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.33,0:04:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經 快要出了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.66,0:04:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 弄得這麽粘糊糊的要怎麽辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.07,0:04:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.13,0:04:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關系的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.05,0:04:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳裝果然不弄濕不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄濕了超級性感啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.97,0:04:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 明明一開始就想這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.82,0:04:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽啊 我懂得啦 樹理
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.68,0:05:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討 討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.69,0:05:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發出好淫蕩的聲音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.10,0:05:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 是你搞得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.16,0:05:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 在那種地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.40,0:05:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 好像光這樣磨就又要出了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.90,0:05:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 這樣樹理就可憐了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.38,0:05:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子全進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.52,0:05:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樹理也有感覺了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.30,0:05:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 淋浴弄濕的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.20,0:05:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 即使說這種話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.74,0:05:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 那裏是我和樹理做了各種各樣的事才濕的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.52,0:06:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 不要這樣啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.62,0:06:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊 樹理的蜜穴好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.19,0:06:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙人的 那種事騙人的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.23,0:06:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭也是 變得這麽硬邦邦了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.25,0:06:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...但是 好舒...舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.41,0:06:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服 蜜穴 好有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.93,0:06:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 樹理
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.17,0:06:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也 我也 我也
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.92,0:06:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.78,0:06:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭了 射了好多在裏面
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.11,0:06:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.68,0:07:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.42,0:07:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 就選這件白的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.29,0:07:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.07,0:07:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 真的很H啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.16,0:07:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.50,0:07:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等一下 樹理
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.20,0:07:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,選哪幾個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.93,0:07:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳裝女友
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.35,0:07:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說來 好無聊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.63,0:07:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽辦啊 怎麽辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.75,0:07:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麽刺激的事請發生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.36,0:07:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在男友面前說的話麽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.95,0:07:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 不得了了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.55,0:08:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.94,0:08:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麽慌張 怎麽了 詩織
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.11,0:08:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我被優樹君邀約了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.88,0:08:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 不是很好麽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.62,0:08:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近好像沒有進展我還擔心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.20,0:08:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.56,0:08:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是第一次約會
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.29,0:08:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽辦才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.43,0:08:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢 那麽我來教你約會的秘訣好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.77,0:08:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能成為像姐姐那樣的絕妙的情侶麽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.67,0:08:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然了 詩織
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.94,0:08:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.22,0:08:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的這樣他會高興麽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.45,0:08:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然了 詩織
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.14,0:08:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合適哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.15,0:09:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但...但是 總覺得這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.09,0:09:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全被看光了 好害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.29,0:09:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請不要那樣看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.10,0:09:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦 不要隱藏
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.09,0:09:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就和博人作預先練習好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.47,0:09:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.03,0:09:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先作為淑女不了解男人的話可是不行的喲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.15,0:09:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 這麽的雀躍哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.83,0:09:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你穿著的衣服的效果哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.33,0:09:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這 這是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.71,0:09:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 詩織 面對肉棒要打招呼可是禮儀哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.69,0:09:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.76,0:09:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...好 肉棒先生...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.54,0:10:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來親吻它用嘴把皮剝開
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.57,0:10:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親吻？皮？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.82,0:10:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 男性都喜歡女性幫他剝的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.07,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是這樣的麽前輩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.91,0:10:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.08,0:10:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣用嘴把皮剝開
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.27,0:10:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.77,0:10:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要加油 要成為出色的淑女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.58,0:10:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剝開後要用嘴含哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.49,0:10:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前輩的肉棒 好熱 一顫一顫的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.17,0:11:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯哦 再用上喉嚨的深處來感受
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.36,0:11:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好奇怪 明明只是和肉棒說
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.76,0:11:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體越來越熱了 總覺得變得色色的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.35,0:11:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯哦 看來博人也很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.81,0:11:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能漏出來哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.21,0:11:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一滴不漏的喝下去才是淑女哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.23,0:11:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.73,0:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 就像品味美酒時一樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.73,0:11:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邊和空氣攪合邊品味哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.04,0:11:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多謝款待
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.27,0:11:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 詩織看來有些明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.37,0:12:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被吸著 被前輩胸部被吮吸著
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.14,0:12:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像嬰兒一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.90,0:12:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 現在開始是重要的地方了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.42,0:12:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 做什麽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.41,0:12:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身為出色的淑女
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.53,0:12:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊不好好準備一下可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.06,0:12:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裏已經洪水泛濫了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.40,0:12:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有這麽舒服麽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.03,0:12:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.65,0:12:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣看來可以很順利得進去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.91,0:12:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 不行的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.67,0:12:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 都進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.31,0:12:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 好過分
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.93,0:12:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家的第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.13,0:13:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩織不要哭 沒有關系的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.51,0:13:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國際上玩具不算在體驗次數裏的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.13,0:13:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣的麽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.42,0:13:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且初體驗的話一般來說是這邊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.95,0:13:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小詩 要去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.84,0:13:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前輩 等等 那裏是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.24,0:13:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.47,0:13:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒進到菊花裏了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.02,0:13:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩織 菊花怎麽樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.13,0:13:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得 怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.78,0:13:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裏面被攪動著 到底
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.99,0:13:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麽 我來讓蜜穴也變得舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.17,0:13:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.48,0:13:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裏 摩擦著菊花
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.61,0:14:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小詩的菊花 好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.52,0:14:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 我這樣子下去好像變得很奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.94,0:14:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩織變得這麽的下流
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.61,0:14:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像小狗一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.29,0:14:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 好像被姐姐大人侵犯一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.01,0:14:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩織把蜜穴提起來 會更舒服的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.42,0:14:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜穴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.74,0:14:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜穴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.78,0:14:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜穴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.83,0:14:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜穴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.73,0:14:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 好厲害 真的...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.82,0:14:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人 詩織 一起 一起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.90,0:15:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很舒服的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.81,0:15:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子詩織也成為出色的淑女了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.70,0:15:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個小詩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.73,0:15:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.40,0:15:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,優樹君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.83,0:15:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小詩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.13,0:15:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直準備好等待著哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.91,0:15:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小詩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.95,0:15:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請把我菊花的小穴搞得很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.47,0:16:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.57,0:16:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到瑞穂會自己提出在這種地方做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.62,0:16:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小廣君 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.19,0:16:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經小鹿亂撞了 不能再忍了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.79,0:16:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真沒辦法呢 好色瑞穂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.26,0:16:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還穿著泳裝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.01,0:16:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小廣君 我要 好想要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.87,0:16:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穂覺得比平時還要興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.49,0:17:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜜穴已經濕成這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.15,0:17:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了 來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.93,0:17:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 今天好好忍住不出聲了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.34,0:17:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是瑞穂居然是這樣的變態呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.78,0:17:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定祖先代代都有變態的素質呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.99,0:17:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事情..
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.18,0:18:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的任務是暗殺鱷麻賀藩主
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.51,0:18:05.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他雖然有幾名忍者侍奉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.88,0:18:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空 憑你的實力的話不是問題
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.26,0:18:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 領命
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.84,0:18:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又見面啦 空
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.94,0:18:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你們麽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.53,0:18:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真難纏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.29,0:18:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白銀之空 這次不會像上次那樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.71,0:18:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰會瞄準同樣的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.02,0:18:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那幅從容的樣子也到今天為止了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.04,0:18:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽 才這種程度麽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.27,0:19:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍法自在布
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.69,0:19:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.52,0:19:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吊起來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.76,0:19:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混賬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.21,0:19:31.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯的樣子呢 空
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.50,0:19:39.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大 這樣看 還真是不錯的女人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.02,0:19:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 這樣就結束了也蠻無聊的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.15,0:19:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大 讓我來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.70,0:19:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大 這家夥發出奇怪的聲音了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.87,0:20:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你也會發出像女人樣的聲音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.19,0:20:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 這是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.23,0:20:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽回事 股間被擺弄 力量就 這是什麽術麽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.19,0:20:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然這樣 就讓你發出更多聲音吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.33,0:20:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.33,0:20:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大 這家夥好厲害 異常的有感覺呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.96,0:20:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 這邊的感覺也是很厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.59,0:20:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.10,0:20:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.82,0:20:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連空的這裏也是這麽不中用的麽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事 和你們無關
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.72,0:20:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空喲 把我們耍的團團轉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.44,0:21:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不多給你點懲罰的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.93,0:21:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦 居然藏著這麽雄偉的東西呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.42,0:21:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們想幹什麽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.37,0:21:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽現在就讓你明白
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.79,0:21:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...別把...舌頭...伸進去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.28,0:21:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕成這樣 剛才就在想干了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.32,0:21:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.05,0:21:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要...在裏面攪動
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.75,0:21:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麽 這樣被他們玩弄 身體居然漸漸變熱了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.48,0:22:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這家夥 身為女忍性技不合格吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.74,0:22:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其收這種羞恥的淩辱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.75,0:22:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 殺了我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.87,0:22:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是吵鬧的嘴巴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.27,0:22:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就用這個塞住吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.41,0:22:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還給我死撐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.39,0:22:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 漸漸擺出一幅淫相了不是麽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.65,0:22:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯不錯 就這樣子讓身體任我們擺布就好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.26,0:23:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 腦子裏一片空白
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.07,0:23:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞成這樣已經連白銀之空的影子都沒有了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.04,0:23:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水淋淋的就吃下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.84,0:23:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麽 老大 請先
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.90,0:23:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這幅淫樣不錯哦 很適合你哦 空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.21,0:23:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.22,0:23:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就把你搞成一流的女忍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.53,0:23:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.22,0:23:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我插
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.76,0:23:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽樣 變成成人的感想
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.35,0:23:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽了 太爽了連聲也發不出了麽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.08,0:23:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.12,0:24:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.05,0:24:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麽 這麽快就投懷送抱了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.11,0:24:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的東西就這麽爽麽
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.30,0:24:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,月 影 給我上
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.94,0:24:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 老大
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.17,0:24:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那邊是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.87,0:24:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不使力了 感覺好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.87,0:24:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麽 口 菊花 蜜穴
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.20,0:24:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明都被肉棒這麽粗暴的玷污著 我 我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.75,0:25:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還差一點 還差一點 這家夥也
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.67,0:25:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒變得好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.98,0:25:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液到身體裏來了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.79,0:25:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得去了哦 月 影
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.43,0:25:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 老大
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.67,0:25:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞定了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.25,0:25:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活活 任何時候都可以再來找我們幹
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.94,0:25:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣已經夠了麽 滿足了麽
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.08,0:25:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.03,0:25:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 瑞穂 到底要做幾次
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.98,0:25:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 穿著 穿著泳裝突然就不能克制了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.28,0:26:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來 這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.74,0:26:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麽 這個舌技
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.62,0:26:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厄啊 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.25,0:26:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 老大
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.74,0:26:26.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,月 影 你們兩個
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.64,0:26:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液又出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.23,0:26:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 沒用的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.57,0:26:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麽 就幹到你殘
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.48,0:26:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,#@?$%!>
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.56,0:26:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.23,0:27:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說那啥 瑞穂 已經可以了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.47,0:27:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空 等等 已經夠了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.54,0:27:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你們幾個先開始的麽
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.08,0:27:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停不下來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.68,0:27:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.22,0:27:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.59,0:27:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道說這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.12,0:27:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓不得了的東西...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.98,0:27:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺醒了也說~不~定...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.98,0:28:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停不下來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.79,0:28:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來換這件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.99,0:28:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳裝女友


Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.61,0:28:42.12,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}やややや
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.21,0:28:46.29,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}や  や　 や ぱぱぱ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.61,0:28:51.83,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}ぱぱぱぱ ぱぱ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.09,0:28:57.00,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}最近、太った　言われても
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.52,0:29:02.99,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}むちむち　好きって　言ったのに
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.51,0:29:10.29,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}どうして最近、冷たいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.33,0:29:14.64,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}私はいつもと　同じだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.11,0:29:27.55,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}いっぱいすると、やせるって 彼氏が言ってた 本当かな
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.97,0:29:31.39,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}何回すればいいのかな？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.41,0:29:34.26,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}何回すればいいのかな？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.29,0:29:37.46,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}おっぱい　すればいいのかな？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.52,0:29:46.37,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}あなたのためなら、何でもできちゃう
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.50,0:29:52.23,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}あなたの聞くこと、何でも聞いちゃう
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.40,0:29:55.30,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}もっとご奉仕してあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.43,0:29:59.59,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}後続いてほしいから
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.61,0:30:03.43,*OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}ちゅちゅ　　　ちゅわ　　ちゅちゅ
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.61,0:28:42.22,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YAYAYAYA
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.31,0:28:46.29,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YAAA YAAA YAAA  PAPAPA
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.61,0:28:51.83,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,PAPAPAPA PAPA
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.09,0:28:57.00,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近被說胖了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.52,0:29:02.99,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明說喜歡肉嘟嘟的我的說
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.51,0:29:10.29,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爲什麽最近對我冷淡了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.33,0:29:14.64,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是一直的我呀
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.11,0:29:27.55,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男朋友說盡情的H的話就會瘦的哦 是不是真的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.97,0:29:31.39,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做多少次才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.41,0:29:34.26,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做多少次才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.29,0:29:37.46,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用咪咪幫你做好麽
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.52,0:29:46.37,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是爲了你的話 什麽都為你做
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.50,0:29:52.23,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是你的話 我什麽都會聼
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.40,0:29:55.30,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我更加的疼愛你
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.43,0:29:59.59,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後也要繼續愛我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.61,0:30:03.43,*OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親親 親 親親


