[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.08,0:00:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫長澤美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.02,0:00:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年春天從大學畢業
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.29,0:00:29.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天起 要在桃谷預備校當講師
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.83,0:00:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃谷是日本最大的補習班
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.56,0:00:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在東京郊外有廣大的校園
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.37,0:00:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,設施比一般大學還棒 非常聞名
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.77,0:00:43.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要當這裡的講師
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.51,0:00:47.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須通過競爭激烈的考試
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.64,0:00:49.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我算是勉強通過了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.25,0:00:56.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！今天起我就是老師了！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.33,0:01:16.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 電車這時候這麼擠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.95,0:01:29.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.42,0:01:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道這是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.69,0:01:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,色狼？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.17,0:01:52.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！很痛的耶！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.91,0:01:56.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 你怎麼了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.25,0:01:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.38,0:02:01.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這男孩特意保護我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.72,0:02:04.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.79,0:02:05.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.32,0:02:08.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.06,0:02:12.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還有香味
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.39,0:02:14.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡太擠了不能動
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.26,0:02:16.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你忍耐一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.80,0:02:18.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.67,0:02:23.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.07,0:02:26.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.50,0:02:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.24,0:02:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打攪了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.84,0:02:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼慢！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.91,0:02:58.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.04,0:03:00.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.91,0:03:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道現在幾點了嗎 長澤美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.85,0:03:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看時鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.85,0:03:11.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 很準時啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.19,0:03:13.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再仔細的看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.12,0:03:17.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 只差30秒…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.06,0:03:23.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.53,0:03:26.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他是不是30秒 遲到就是遲到！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.47,0:03:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.01,0:03:33.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有自我介紹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.01,0:03:34.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是森永綾子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.88,0:03:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與你同樣擔任英文老師
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.68,0:03:42.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,校方要我多教導你 可是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.75,0:03:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你第一天就遲到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.96,0:03:47.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.82,0:03:51.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是講師 要教學生的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.23,0:03:53.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該保持那個自覺！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.83,0:03:57.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聲音太小
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.17,0:03:59.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣子能教課嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.10,0:04:01.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽不見！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.17,0:04:06.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森永老師 連走廊都聽得到你的聲音哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.04,0:04:08.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由紀江老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.51,0:04:11.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有 這樣子欺負新人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.45,0:04:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會把人逼走的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.72,0:04:17.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.12,0:04:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.33,0:04:26.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瞭解你 因為計劃被拖到而生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.93,0:04:30.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我會代替你 帶她去瞭解校內環境
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.20,0:04:33.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣你心情好點了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.74,0:04:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧！就這樣！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.01,0:04:37.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.61,0:04:38.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.81,0:04:40.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是蝦名由紀江
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.28,0:04:42.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才別人喊我老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.95,0:04:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我不是教書的老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.95,0:04:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是負責保健室的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.55,0:04:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…你是醫生？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.02,0:04:49.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒那麼誇張
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.89,0:04:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過你也有夠倒霉的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.89,0:04:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會 要怪就怪我遲到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.29,0:04:58.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那個森永老師 搞不好慾求不滿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.69,0:04:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.30,0:05:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的眼神雖然壞壞的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.43,0:05:04.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是五官端正
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身材也好得沒話說
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.17,0:05:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偏偏到了32歲還是單身
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.10,0:05:12.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要她肯放低標準 男人應該很多得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.84,0:05:14.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個說法太…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.71,0:05:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.45,0:05:18.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,講的太露骨了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.18,0:05:21.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 她又聽不見
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.52,0:05:23.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說你討厭這個話題？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.92,0:05:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.59,0:05:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可愛嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.86,0:05:33.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長澤老師 到保健室休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.40,0:05:34.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.94,0:05:43.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個補習班好大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.81,0:05:45.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連保健室都有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.94,0:05:47.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很忙得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.48,0:05:50.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受傷得人有那麼多嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.88,0:05:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是治療受傷 其他還有忙很多事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.82,0:05:57.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.02,0:05:58.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如心理輔導
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.29,0:06:01.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連那種事都要做？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.29,0:06:02.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.16,0:06:07.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春期得男生太多了 很多都來詢問性得問題
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.76,0:06:11.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用那麼吃驚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.17,0:06:14.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生都是想那些事情的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.77,0:06:16.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.24,0:06:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什麼都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.37,0:06:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們都把擦身而過 的女性當成性對像
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.78,0:06:27.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還帶色情書刊到學校
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.58,0:06:28.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.32,0:06:33.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他們平均每天的自慰次數嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.99,0:06:34.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.06,0:06:38.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們就是得應付這樣得學生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.79,0:06:40.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該多研究一些得
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.93,0:06:41.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.86,0:06:44.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是處女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.80,0:06:45.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.87,0:06:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.07,0:06:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教導學生的人 自己卻沒有經驗…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.67,0:06:53.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們來做實技講習吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.34,0:06:57.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以教你很多的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.68,0:07:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.82,0:07:05.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以慢慢休息的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.89,0:07:12.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 就維持這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.23,0:07:21.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…到底…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.24,0:07:23.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什麼都不用擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.64,0:07:25.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包在我身上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.91,0:07:27.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要做什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.46,0:07:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多美麗的身材啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.99,0:07:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.26,0:07:49.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？你很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.93,0:07:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.27,0:07:55.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過這是為了讓你 成為獨當一面的講師
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.21,0:08:00.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.34,0:08:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡也美極了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:06.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請別那樣看我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.82,0:08:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.75,0:08:11.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼敏感
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.82,0:08:14.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你還能更敏感的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.56,0:08:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.69,0:08:19.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.36,0:08:25.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你也來讓我舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.39,0:08:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.39,0:08:53.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也拜託你了 你知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.53,0:08:58.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 就是那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.55,0:09:12.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝦名老師 我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.08,0:09:17.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別喊我蝦名老師 叫我由紀江吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.29,0:09:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由紀江
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.42,0:09:22.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好高興 美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.03,0:09:26.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也快了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.70,0:09:37.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何？ 是不是上了一課啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.11,0:09:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得很不對勁
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.37,0:09:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.44,0:09:42.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要否定的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.38,0:09:44.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問這件事…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.98,0:09:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會告訴任何人的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.58,0:09:47.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.12,0:09:49.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.40,0:10:03.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來你是這裡的學生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.27,0:10:05.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我叫御堂榮矢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.93,0:10:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是剛才你從保健室走出來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.20,0:10:10.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是身體哪裡不舒服嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.47,0:10:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不、不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.54,0:10:15.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那本書…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.41,0:10:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我一直在看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.08,0:10:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過有些部分看不懂 可能是我不夠用功吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.48,0:10:26.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大學時我看過這本書
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.16,0:10:30.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了早點看它…多瞭解它的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.16,0:10:33.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很努力的讀英文
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.83,0:10:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果 英文就好到可以當老師了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.17,0:10:45.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.31,0:10:48.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可能很像哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.65,0:10:59.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一天就發生那麼多事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.73,0:11:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.46,0:11:09.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在說什麼呀
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.33,0:11:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事太違反自然了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.00,0:11:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做那種事應該跟男人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.27,0:11:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟御堂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.63,0:12:50.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行呀 怎麼能想著學生自慰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.92,0:13:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御堂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.21,0:13:37.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,徹底的睡眠不足
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.68,0:13:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！對不起！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.42,0:13:43.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御堂！？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.35,0:13:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.55,0:13:46.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你每天都搭這班電車？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.42,0:13:49.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒課的日子我也會去圖書室
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.36,0:13:51.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那所圖書室 雖然室補習班附屬的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.76,0:13:53.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是藏書很豐富呢！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.71,0:14:10.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 老師
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.85,0:14:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 沒什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.25,0:14:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 我可以拜託你一件事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.39,0:14:19.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以後我每天都搭這班電車
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.79,0:14:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當我的保鏢吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.66,0:14:23.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保鏢？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.26,0:14:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 我討厭又 發生類似昨天的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.53,0:14:28.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.46,0:14:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天起一直？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.66,0:14:30.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.13,0:14:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.60,0:14:34.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都能跟老師
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.94,0:14:38.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個觸感每天都能…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.81,0:14:42.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.55,0:14:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御堂？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.01,0:14:49.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 老師 明天起我們一起搭電車
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.55,0:14:50.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.43,0:15:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 終於要第一次上課了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.70,0:15:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要打起精神來
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.37,0:15:07.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.58,0:15:18.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可愛嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.78,0:15:20.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯 真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.85,0:15:26.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是今天起一年內擔任 英文課講師的長澤美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.92,0:15:28.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.39,0:15:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.39,0:15:33.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有問題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.46,0:15:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問題？好啊 說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.53,0:15:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我們你的三圍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.00,0:15:43.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不回答這種問題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.01,0:15:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那麼內褲的顏色呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.87,0:15:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.08,0:15:50.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別氣嘛 美崎 不過是問這種問題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.08,0:15:52.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又不是小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.68,0:15:54.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該不會你還是處女吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.22,0:15:58.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.15,0:16:00.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你的初體驗是何時？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.82,0:16:02.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次做愛是在什麼地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.42,0:16:03.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅館嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.49,0:16:05.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟多少男人搞過啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.76,0:16:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別在說了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.83,0:16:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要小氣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.76,0:16:13.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能平息我們的苦悶 只有老師你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.77,0:16:15.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.91,0:16:20.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請接受我滿滿的熱情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.38,0:16:24.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 今夜我會以你為小菜 努力打手槍的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.45,0:16:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被由紀江說中了 青少年真的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.12,0:16:32.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 昨天你作過愛了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.32,0:16:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個禮拜自慰幾次啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.59,0:16:35.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡什麼體位？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.66,0:16:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們回座位上去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.79,0:16:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我們嘛 老師
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.06,0:16:41.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.13,0:16:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們別過分了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.53,0:16:49.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個做事 別老是像小孩一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.40,0:16:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.61,0:16:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.81,0:16:52.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.01,0:16:55.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別理他 我覺得掃興了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.94,0:16:57.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們找地方去玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.61,0:17:00.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 你們幾個…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.35,0:17:02.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 我姓佐山
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.75,0:17:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再見了 美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.42,0:17:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.49,0:17:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.29,0:17:09.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫栗子 南川栗子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.56,0:17:11.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 南川同學
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.09,0:17:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要你特別感謝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.76,0:17:17.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不爽那些人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.57,0:17:19.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是老師耶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.57,0:17:22.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對學生額騷擾行為 應該明白拒絕才對
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.51,0:17:27.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說 你是想借此吸引男生？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.71,0:17:29.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的話我向你道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.84,0:17:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.91,0:17:33.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我討厭那些白癡沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.85,0:17:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是看到 像你這樣的女人也很火大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.13,0:17:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,補習班的講師真難當
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.80,0:17:55.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一天就這麼累
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.60,0:17:57.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天起不知有沒有問題
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.87,0:17:58.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長澤老師
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.21,0:18:04.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.88,0:18:09.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為老師太可愛了 我們才不禁得寸進尺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.15,0:18:11.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.75,0:18:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.82,0:18:15.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係啦 你已經道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.62,0:18:19.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是 明天得課你要好好出席哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.63,0:18:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於這件事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.63,0:18:23.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是一開始就沒聽課嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.77,0:18:26.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怕明天起跟不上進度
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.30,0:18:29.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想請你告訴我 今天上課得內容
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.90,0:18:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此才來找你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:32.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.51,0:18:36.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 就是這樣 給我時間吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.71,0:18:39.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 我還以為他很可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.38,0:18:40.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到是這麼誠實
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.12,0:18:41.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.05,0:18:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.98,0:18:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是這裡不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.32,0:18:47.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道一個好地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.33,0:18:53.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡講堂很久 現在幾乎沒在使用
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.66,0:18:57.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用這裡不會有人講話的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.13,0:19:00.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.07,0:19:01.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了 佐山同學
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.00,0:19:05.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上課時間到了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.35,0:19:16.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.29,0:19:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.75,0:19:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個講堂很少使用
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.29,0:19:23.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再怎麼叫 都不會有人來的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.29,0:19:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.49,0:19:27.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了就乖乖聽話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.96,0:19:28.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.43,0:19:33.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 看你怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.84,0:19:35.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.97,0:19:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你不對
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.44,0:19:43.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我們這些年輕人面前 擺出一副完全沒經驗的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.65,0:19:49.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為做這種事 不會受到法律制裁嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.98,0:19:51.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我停不下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.25,0:19:57.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要恨的話 就恨你身材太好吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.80,0:20:04.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸起來真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.53,0:20:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.87,0:20:08.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你是師生關係 不可以做這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.94,0:20:10.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別說夢話啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.41,0:20:12.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.54,0:20:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.28,0:20:15.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形狀不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.01,0:20:18.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭也是漂亮的粉紅色
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.01,0:20:19.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.35,0:20:21.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 有點感覺了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.35,0:20:22.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.68,0:20:23.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.89,0:20:25.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是沒感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.82,0:20:29.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的乳頭又甜又好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.37,0:20:46.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.64,0:20:48.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.45,0:20:52.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明有感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.18,0:20:53.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.51,0:20:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭？教導學生不是老師的工作嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.79,0:20:59.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就教我性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.52,0:21:00.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也算是上課吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.99,0:21:02.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.19,0:21:03.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.26,0:21:04.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃這個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.13,0:21:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡的顏色也漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.75,0:21:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.62,0:21:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該讓我搞了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.89,0:21:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖乖聽話 我要插了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.51,0:22:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面很緊哦 美崎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.52,0:22:09.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼會這樣 不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.46,0:22:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然被學生給強暴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.62,0:22:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.03,0:22:50.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是處女啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.97,0:22:53.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得會這麼的緊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.17,0:23:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了 美崎 下次再給我補習吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.25,0:23:10.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,報警嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.25,0:23:13.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是對方是學生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.79,0:23:14.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 找森永老師
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.26,0:23:18.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.53,0:23:24.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 學生怎麼能跟老師…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.00,0:23:26.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得救她才行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.94,0:23:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 你的腰停下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:35.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.21,0:23:37.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上鎖了…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.48,0:23:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.62,0:23:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腰的用法不對
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.02,0:23:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.69,0:23:53.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎 要這樣插到底 打轉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.69,0:23:54.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.57,0:23:59.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.84,0:24:05.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.64,0:24:09.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 我快不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.31,0:24:13.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准 你得再忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.05,0:24:17.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.86,0:24:26.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是 你太沒用了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.66,0:24:27.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.00,0:24:32.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想跟我作愛得話 就好好學習 下次再來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.33,0:24:34.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 這是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.47,0:24:37.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,森永老師跟學生…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.01,0:24:40.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡太奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.70,0:25:03.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.70,0:25:08.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個補習班是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.91,0:25:15.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,春天 四月
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.04,0:25:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這應該是充滿希望得 新季節的開始
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.05,0:25:22.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果卻染上絕望的色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.05,0:25:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女老師開始走上的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.45,0:25:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是黑暗艱險的淫亂日子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.39,0:25:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.46,0:25:34.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她粉碎的夢想改變了形式
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.13,0:25:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昇華成另外一個模樣
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.47,0:25:41.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底 會帶來什麼樣的結果呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.14,0:25:47.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女教師肉體授業下卷 2004年春季發售
