[Script Info]
;  sub fixed by swoon
Title:(18禁アニメ 無修正) オーキッド★エンブレム (DVD 640x480 DivX6.2.1)[1F005AAF].ass
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,楷体,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,20,20,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.58,0:01:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.12,0:01:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然让新型麻药D99X草被人轻易夺走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.04,0:01:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制世界黑社会的特莱登特财团真是末落了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.09,0:02:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 一切都是我的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.58,0:02:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说是你的责任吗 那你就马上赎罪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.43,0:02:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总帅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.47,0:02:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰也来参加今天的超级杯擂台了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.62,0:02:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思 派机关枪乔去当她对手
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.53,0:02:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您要任她嚣张到何时呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.67,0:02:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都等四年了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.29,0:02:39.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不享受一下不是很可惜吗 你不这么认为么 阿龙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.72,0:02:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃烧吧 让身体颤抖吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.08,0:02:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级杯今天最后一场决战
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.59,0:03:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙争虎斗让人屏息一战
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.98,0:03:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从上个月开始创下九连胜的纪录
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.37,0:03:20.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不败的挑战者 16岁少女 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.59,0:03:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们伟大的冠军
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.78,0:03:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机关枪乔
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.46,0:03:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倍率又提高了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.75,0:03:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.94,0:03:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔对丽兰 1比36
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.38,0:04:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1比20 1比15 1比36 1比140
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.88,0:04:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都押机关枪乔赢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.58,0:04:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在抬高
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.97,0:04:18.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总帅是说 乔不会赢 是丽兰会赢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.21,0:04:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.98,0:04:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会疼爱你的 小猫咪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.99,0:04:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉丸子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.95,0:05:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么会躲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.19,0:05:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的踢击被档下了 我的踢击竟然被
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.46,0:05:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的踢击真不像话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.40,0:05:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的踢击 是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.30,0:05:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜者
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.39,0:05:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.51,0:05:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.58,0:06:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰30秒就打赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总帅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.07,0:06:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,念吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D99X在我这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.83,0:06:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天深夜两点到机场 兰也会来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.07,0:06:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4年来我一直相信你会回来 一直等着你来呢 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.36,0:06:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.04,0:06:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连赢10场呢 丽兰 我就相信你会赢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.13,0:06:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.93,0:06:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.21,0:06:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的格斗奖金 你收下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.64,0:06:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 丽兰 这么多钱我不能收
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.76,0:07:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意 这是答谢你让我住这的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.28,0:07:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 应该答谢的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.62,0:07:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是你救我离开那些坏人的魔掌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.32,0:07:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定早就被凌辱过卖给人口贩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.38,0:07:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 所以
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.60,0:07:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了 就把钱留下当生活费吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.24,0:07:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.80,0:07:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你 好喜欢喔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.34,0:07:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.64,0:07:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做的事…只有这个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.37,0:07:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.69,0:08:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 爱美 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.15,0:08:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.20,0:08:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.87,0:08:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱美 那里是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.13,0:08:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.68,0:08:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱美 爱美 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.09,0:08:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的也麻烦你了 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.17,0:08:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.14,0:08:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.96,0:09:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.76,0:09:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊 爱美 还要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.82,0:09:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.03,0:09:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.45,0:09:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.25,0:10:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它的量比古柯碱产量更少
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.51,0:10:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,价格高 持续时间为2倍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.65,0:10:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大量服用的话会激发出人类暴力本性
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.09,0:10:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化为杀人恶鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.46,0:10:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界各地警察都在找
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.83,0:10:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却从未得手的幻影般的毒药
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.47,0:10:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是D99X
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.42,0:10:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西听起来好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.50,0:10:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给警察吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.81,0:10:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用的 黑社会的人已经渗透欢乐城的警方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.06,0:10:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这是诱饵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.10,0:10:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是引出特来登特的总帅东条重要的饵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.12,0:10:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想打倒他吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.16,0:10:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 就在今夜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.83,0:11:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊 你再厉害也敌不过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.43,0:11:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.51,0:11:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你一起 天崖海角我都去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.14,0:11:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.04,0:11:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是4年来我唯一的目标
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.82,0:11:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不打倒东条
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.33,0:11:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就无法向前进
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.07,0:11:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.86,0:11:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.50,0:11:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是很担心你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.75,0:11:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.43,0:11:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想忘也忘不了的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.71,0:11:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.33,0:12:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那个男人 我的人生全毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.25,0:12:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了贩毒之外还有三人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.74,0:12:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你负责追击
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.57,0:12:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加藤跟莱卡负责后门
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.07,0:12:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ok
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.17,0:12:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心 准备随时用枪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.50,0:12:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 你怎么了 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.63,0:12:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天怪怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.24,0:12:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近搜查太累了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.00,0:12:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 这个案件办完后我们一起请假 如何
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.24,0:12:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要冲进去了 走吧 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.83,0:12:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如刚才所说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.46,0:12:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想跟我们继续交易
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.33,0:12:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请在明天以前准备一亿元来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.47,0:12:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.45,0:12:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.21,0:12:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.98,0:13:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准动 我们是DEA
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.05,0:13:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联邦司法署缉毒局的特务组
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.58,0:13:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以违法毒品交易法逮补你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.60,0:13:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.70,0:13:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.90,0:13:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你恶贯满盈的日子到头了 东条
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.84,0:13:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶贯满盈？该死是你们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.04,0:13:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 振作点 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.06,0:14:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如我所料 是个美女
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.76,0:14:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这乳型漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.80,0:14:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人我要带走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.78,0:14:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来会挺有趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.11,0:15:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.44,0:15:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.29,0:15:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒啦 DEA的专家丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.83,0:15:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是东条 这艘船的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.75,0:15:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想对我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.44,0:15:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格呢 他怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.89,0:15:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心男朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.03,0:15:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上让你见他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.58,0:15:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.61,0:15:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.82,0:15:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你们想做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.02,0:15:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 别过来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.81,0:15:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.67,0:15:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 拜托 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.79,0:15:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.23,0:15:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.27,0:15:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.43,0:16:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.49,0:16:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.36,0:16:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很敏感喔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.79,0:16:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个男人教的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.03,0:16:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请吧 东条大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.54,0:16:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊 再继续下去 我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.35,0:16:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再继续下去会怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.55,0:16:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 只能到这
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.54,0:16:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那里在说想要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.79,0:17:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.98,0:17:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多想要了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.61,0:17:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要被插就先用嘴吃干净
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.32,0:17:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.97,0:17:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不想要吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.23,0:17:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.19,0:17:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 就是这样 对 非常好 可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.95,0:17:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 这次说请插进来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.49,0:17:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不是想要我插才吃的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.72,0:17:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快插进来 插进我那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.57,0:17:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.43,0:17:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.18,0:18:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是第一次 所以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.69,0:18:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你是处女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.85,0:18:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.44,0:18:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 原来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.24,0:18:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个傻男人竟然没对你下手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.77,0:18:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要夺走她的处女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.56,0:18:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.84,0:18:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.30,0:18:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.13,0:18:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啊 道格 这女人想要我插她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.02,0:18:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗 这女人还是处女
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.28,0:18:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.88,0:18:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求你 不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.47,0:19:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算眼睛不看也听的到声音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.82,0:19:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见女友的叫声
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.84,0:19:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.91,0:19:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 丽兰的乳房很棒喔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.01,0:19:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有这边不知怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.59,0:19:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音好听吧 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.10,0:19:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 想要我做什么就说出来给他听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.72,0:19:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 道格 原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.07,0:19:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.82,0:19:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.44,0:19:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.55,0:19:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插进来 求求你 用那根插进我的里面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.12,0:19:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要东条的更甚于道格吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.44,0:19:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 你的 我想要你的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.32,0:19:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你这根让我成为女人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.54,0:20:02.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.73,0:20:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听见没 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.99,0:20:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我现在就让你成为女人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.65,0:20:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 快插进来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.59,0:20:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 快点 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.92,0:20:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.71,0:20:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前 你要说叫他看仔细这边情况
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.39,0:20:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看自己女友变成女人的过程
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.65,0:20:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.59,0:20:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你不是想要我更甚于道格吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.87,0:20:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 看我 快看我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.52,0:20:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我变成女人的过程
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.14,0:20:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我和这个男人做爱的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.27,0:20:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看啊 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.26,0:20:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在他要插入我了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.30,0:20:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要跟我做爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.76,0:21:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看啊 看女友被强暴的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.87,0:21:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看仔细了 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.39,0:21:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.78,0:21:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好厉害 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.71,0:21:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 好爽啊 非常爽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.51,0:21:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面超紧喔 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.63,0:21:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰这里很棒喔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.28,0:21:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.72,0:21:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 好爽 还要 还要啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.23,0:21:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在男友面前这么淫乱你不羞耻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.34,0:21:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我更淫乱 还要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.71,0:21:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 超棒的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.55,0:22:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.36,0:22:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要 我还要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.08,0:22:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在让我更痛快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.86,0:22:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你啦 我还要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.96,0:22:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.71,0:22:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次就这样淫乱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.83,0:22:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么紧勒住我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.34,0:22:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真爽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.92,0:22:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.19,0:22:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面 好有快感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.47,0:22:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.21,0:22:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啊 我的那根
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.19,0:22:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 又硬又大
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.62,0:22:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.60,0:22:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在插啊 把我那里插烂
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.56,0:23:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说给道格听吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.22,0:23:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 道格你看 他插进我的那里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.24,0:23:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那根好硬 好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.10,0:23:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.01,0:23:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.93,0:23:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 这个人看见女友被强暴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.00,0:23:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还勃起耶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.88,0:23:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧 不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.83,0:23:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条大人 这个人看见女友被强暴却勃起了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.10,0:23:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.98,0:23:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一点
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.89,0:23:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 还要 在更用力
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.43,0:23:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.43,0:23:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里 那里 插的好深
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.53,0:23:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插到子宫了 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.20,0:24:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.03,0:24:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 要射在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.78,0:24:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.65,0:24:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射在里面 让我高潮
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.04,0:24:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的女友平安地成为女人了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.04,0:24:42.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我搞过了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.35,0:24:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你失败了 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.59,0:24:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不甘心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.50,0:24:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是本组织的制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.90,0:24:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 我要感谢你一点 你没对丽兰下手
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.07,0:25:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.84,0:25:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.75,0:25:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.99,0:25:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格呢 他怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.38,0:25:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放他走了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.95,0:25:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在因该回DEA了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.21,0:25:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱衣服 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.01,0:25:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又想让我丢脸
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.55,0:25:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 是与你相爱
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.07,0:25:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你把我的手绑起来的 让我不能反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.53,0:25:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我也给你人生最棒的快感
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.80,0:25:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 可是
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.34,0:25:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是在道格面前做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.98,0:25:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱衣服吧 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.50,0:25:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.07,0:25:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.51,0:26:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.21,0:26:12.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要 再用力点插
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.92,0:26:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.83,0:26:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰小姐真好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.78,0:26:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.42,0:26:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啦 沙纪 我们只是东条大人的宠物
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.08,0:26:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来东条日夜不分侵犯我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.89,0:26:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准我穿衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.39,0:26:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天被他强迫做爱数次
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.65,0:26:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来不知不觉 我也开始渴求他的肉体
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.49,0:26:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟东条肌肤相亲
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.09,0:26:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的那根插入我里面使我感觉到快感
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.21,0:26:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰真漂亮 我也好想跟她做爱看看
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.91,0:26:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.21,0:26:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经有我了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.33,0:27:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条大人 陈老师来了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.66,0:27:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见 东条
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.51,0:27:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.99,0:27:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人找到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.05,0:27:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最适合刺上龙的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.60,0:27:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都希望你为我替她刺青
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.29,0:27:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.52,0:27:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多美的肌肤啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.32,0:27:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论光滑度
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.97,0:27:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是肌肉的发达度
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.23,0:27:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是奇迹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.93,0:27:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这个女人两周前还是处女
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.00,0:27:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太理想的素材 无懈可击
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.15,0:27:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我就为这女人刺青
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.75,0:27:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺上传说中升龙淫姿性图
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.00,0:27:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.12,0:28:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这图只能刺在快乐女人的肌肤上
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.29,0:28:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺青时间为三天三夜 连续与人不停交合
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.96,0:28:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得到吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.44,0:28:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吧 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.62,0:28:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.41,0:28:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很紧吧 女人被刺青时那里会勒紧男人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.66,0:28:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后女人的背上会留下刺青
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.99,0:28:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,升天一般的快乐持续下去
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.39,0:28:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一切都结束时
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.62,0:29:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人与女人才能忘记身体的区隔
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.14,0:29:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到最高的快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.83,0:29:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是传说中升龙淫姿性图啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.28,0:29:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就差一笔了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.93,0:29:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个可以高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.47,0:29:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 丽兰 我要射了 射在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.10,0:29:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射在里面 射在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.31,0:29:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.61,0:29:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得到男人精液 龙升天了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.25,0:29:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 过去从没有女人成功显现升龙像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.35,0:30:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙与龙在呼唤了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.11,0:30:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.93,0:30:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该要道谢的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.89,0:30:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头一次遇到这样的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.60,0:30:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得你能找到 东条
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.39,0:30:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰小姐 丽兰小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.81,0:30:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.56,0:30:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊 丽兰小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.79,0:30:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条大人吩咐过不可以进来这里
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.69,0:30:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我很在意这里
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.89,0:30:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条大人不在时出事的话我们会挨骂的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.49,0:30:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请回房吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.84,0:30:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.08,0:30:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.58,0:30:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 丽兰小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.55,0:31:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.61,0:31:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的 您快回房间去 丽兰小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.03,0:31:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.92,0:31:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.04,0:31:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.84,0:31:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让他逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.62,0:31:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在应该在DEA吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.42,0:31:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.25,0:31:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.60,0:31:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不记得之后怎么逃出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.87,0:31:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脑中只有逃离那里 逃离那艘船的念头
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.21,0:31:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是为了道格被杀死
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.01,0:31:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还无法原谅自己把身心都交给东条
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.33,0:31:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再也不回头
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.70,0:31:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今夜就要结束一切
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.86,0:32:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是龙
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.46,0:32:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来向东条报仇的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.59,0:32:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在总帅来之前 我陪你玩
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.06,0:32:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放马过来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.51,0:32:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.95,0:32:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强 不愧是超级杯最强的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.03,0:32:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 总帅
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.02,0:32:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是给你们的礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.52,0:32:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.60,0:32:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点脏脏的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.50,0:33:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带她去洗澡化妆会变漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.71,0:33:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头一次有人能让我感到棘手
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.58,0:33:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做女人太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.25,0:33:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 这样下去会输
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.48,0:33:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.18,0:33:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四年来你变强了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.89,0:33:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也变的更美了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.72,0:33:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豁出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.03,0:34:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.39,0:34:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连龙都被你打败了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.87,0:34:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你回来我身边了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.76,0:34:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了杀你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.09,0:34:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是让你成为女人的人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.53,0:34:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无法杀死带给你女人幸福的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.03,0:34:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易赢了却
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.50,0:34:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么逞强
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.34,0:35:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.95,0:35:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这女孩超厉害的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.72,0:35:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.03,0:35:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.56,0:35:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美奈 她那里敏感 再刺激她
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.40,0:35:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐姐 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.04,0:35:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.47,0:35:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 这女孩潮吹了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.51,0:35:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱的女孩 真淫乱
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.45,0:36:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 对不起 我太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.43,0:36:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.82,0:36:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.82,0:36:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我输了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.68,0:36:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒啦 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.12,0:36:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.09,0:36:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡了三天 有精神了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.89,0:36:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.73,0:36:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恨我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.10,0:36:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然恨
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.64,0:36:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你夺走我的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.77,0:36:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀死道格 拿我当玩具
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.98,0:36:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定很快乐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.67,0:36:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.18,0:37:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格是我送进DEA的间谍之一
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.70,0:37:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你胡说 别想骗我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.49,0:37:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你记得这是什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.51,0:37:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.61,0:37:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们组织的小道具
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.27,0:37:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面有发讯器
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.85,0:37:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的行动我寮诺指掌
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.26,0:37:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格什么都向我报告
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.60,0:37:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你干嘛杀他
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.11,0:37:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是制裁
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.79,0:37:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当双重间谍
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.93,0:37:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛是罪该万死
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.01,0:37:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点你应该晓得
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.67,0:37:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 这件案子结束后我们一起请假吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.07,0:37:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 这男人看到女友被强暴还勃起
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.39,0:37:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道格
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.41,0:37:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我 看我啊 道格
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.10,0:37:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:37:52.37,0:37:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不信
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.89,0:37:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想说大道理
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.40,0:38:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是黑社会老大
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.96,0:38:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是世上只有我有资格爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.97,0:38:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过 你是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.95,0:38:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这四年来到底是
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.53,0:38:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这期间你被几个男人爱过
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.35,0:38:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为要我的人只有你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.96,0:38:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的心里是怎么想的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.67,0:38:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是打从心底爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.53,0:38:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里也许是为了确认对你的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.68,0:38:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确认了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.46,0:38:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是属于我的 知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.84,0:38:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.49,0:38:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信升龙图等这天不知道等多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.25,0:38:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 摸我 用我的身体来证实
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.19,0:39:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再摸我
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.05,0:39:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要 我还要
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.29,0:39:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条 还要 再摸我
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.15,0:39:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经这么大了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.47,0:39:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.45,0:39:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.46,0:39:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃 求求你 射在我嘴巴里
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.61,0:39:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我吃你的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.06,0:39:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.40,0:39:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.51,0:39:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.77,0:39:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.34,0:40:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次换我那里
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.21,0:40:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你那根刺我那里
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.10,0:40:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.10,0:40:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 太爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.62,0:40:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条 东条
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.96,0:40:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再刺 插更深点 让我成为你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.79,0:40:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.09,0:40:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱美 给你看个好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.31,0:40:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要 还要 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.31,0:40:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.17,0:40:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她回来了 回到我们身边
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.92,0:40:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就向那时候一样
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.36,0:41:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里面 在里面 在插
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.71,0:41:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.92,0:41:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次吧 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.57,0:41:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东条 好棒 好棒 你真棒 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.10,0:41:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过四年 我的那里如何
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.93,0:41:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了 太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.63,0:41:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 那里好有感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.96,0:41:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要 再插我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.79,0:41:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.60,0:41:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.25,0:42:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挑战者 炸弹般的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.79,0:42:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:42:27.91,0:42:31.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野蛮人机关枪乔登场了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.54,0:42:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去吗 丽兰
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.23,0:42:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 总帅
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.06,0:42:45.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丽兰小姐 加油
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.81,0:42:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱美好狡猾
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.57,0:42:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下看我修理你
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.11,0:42:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 对不起 大姐姐\N- 别跑 爱美
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.26,0:43:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们天下无敌的女冠军 丽兰


