Felina.
This is...
What a beautiful flower.
Felina, you can talk?
Save me, please. Save me.
Princess Memory: Second Half
Collin!
Felina.
Felina, you've got your soul back?
Sly Felina!
Stop it! Please stop it!
A dream?
Felina, what am I supposed to do? Tell me.
This is...
What am I supposed to do with it?
Save me. Save me, please.
Lily.
So, you're going back?
I can't stop at this point.
For the sake of Sallian and Lily.
It's a charm for your safety.
Pony, I'll look after Felina,
so don't worry about her.
Yes, thank you.
Collin...
All right! Fight me!
What?
It's just a Nuvolian.
You've got a lot of gusto, don't you?
There's something I've got to complete.
What's that?
It's what Felina gave me.
Is that so?
There's a secret in that amulet.
Madonna Felina.
Felina can be restored
to her original self.
Only when all the characters of Felina
are sealed inside the amulet.
What a troublemaker you are.
Sly Felina!
Didn't you have enough already?
Besides, can you die for Felina?
Of course I can.
Without this amulet,
Felina's soul cannot be captured.
Understand?
- Stop that!
- Take that!
Just give up.
You won't be able to save Felina.
I will!
Collin, I can make it faster.
Have a good time in hell, won't you?
I can't believe this.
What? Don't!
You are...
Sallian!
Collin? Is it you, Collin?
Collin.
I was so scared down there.
The thought of dying alone
here drove me mad.
It's not safe here.
Monsters pop up all the time.
It's incredible.
Don't know why, but it's warm in here.
It's beautiful.
You're embarrassing me. Don't look.
It's not what I meant.
Pony, is she all right?
Yeah, she's doing fine.
Good. So long as she's okay.
Don't say that!
Sallian, you'll go back with me.
How are we going to get out
from the bottom of the world...
and find our way back?
It's okay. I don't mind dying here.
I'm not alone anymore.
Because, Collin, you're with me.
Please sleep with me.
Collin, I've been in love
with you for a long time.
Sallian, we shouldn't.
It's okay. It's just for this moment.
Don't look at me so closely.
You're are so beautiful.
Ready?
Just like in here,
it snows all day long...
quietly, outside this cave.
What a lonely place.
Snow never stops.
It's as if someone's crying.
I must go.
What was that?
Collin, let's play!
Come down here and fight me!
How many Felinas are there?
Sallian, just go ahead without me.
- Go on!
- Collin!
Sallian, just go ahead!
You've got no time to look away.
Go, quickly!
Please get inside the amulet quietly.
All right. I've lost.
But you'd better not think it's over.
Catch me if you can!
Wait!
Hey! Wait up!
Hurry! Catch me.
Now I've finally caught you!
I am Slut Felina.
Now, let's have fun.
- No, we can't.
- Why not?
I beg you.
Please get inside the amulet.
Why don't you forget that?
Besides, it'll feel really good. Here.
I'm begging you.
I see. You do really love her.
I want to go. I want to go home.
Collin, will you take me with you too?
Of course.
Thank you very much, Collin.
I'm almost there. But, I can't!
Pull! Pull with all your might!
Pull!
You, girl, from the village.
Where's Collin?
He's collecting the soul of Felina right now.
Is that right?
All right, then.
Collin will be able to do that now, I'm sure.
You've done well.
The last one remaining is Sly Felina.
You know her. I count on you.
Madonna Felina.
I'm not so easy like them.
Felina!
Don't call me Felina.
Yes, I will, for you are Felina.
I don't trust you. I trust no one.
This is the world that exists
in the center of your heart, isn't it?
A cold, frozen world.
Shut up and speak no more.
This world has turned Felina
into what she is today.
I told you to shut up. If you don't...
If I die, Felina will be gone forever.
Can't you get that through
your thick skull?
Look, Felina's suffering, as you can tell.
Can you feel her pain? Can you?
Stop it, Felina! Don't do that!
Felina's in pain. Now, try saving her.
That's right. You can't save her.
No one can.
Do you understand what I mean?
Felina, stop it. Please don't
hurt yourself any more.
The ice is melting. It can't be!
Felina, trust me. I've come here...
to save you.
Collin.
I've lost.
It's all over.
It looks like you've collected them all.
Collin!
I'm glad, Collin.
Thanks a lot for your help, Sallian.
There's a cliff over there.
If you jump off of it,
you can get back to your world.
This world and yours exist,
directly opposite each other.
Thanks everyone!
Sallian! Collin! I'm so glad!
Like I expected, you're back unscathed.
I was so sure you'd be back,
I prepared dinner for you.
I'm so glad. Really glad.
It's all thanks to you, Collin.
Collin, thank you so much.
Really, I mean it.
Felina, I'm on my way back to you.
Felina, I've finally returned home.
Dear, Collin.
Thank you, dear Collin.
You've risked your life to save me...
the Savage Felina, the Slut Felina
and even the Sly Felina.
How will I ever thank you?
How will I pay you back?
Felina.
My heart ached for so long,
I could never trust anyone.
Then you came.
I know. I noticed how
Sly Felina's eyes looked so sad.
My soul loves you.
They all love you, Collin. And I...
Iove you too, you know?
Felina.
I was very scared. I couldn't trust anyone.
How about now?
I'm not scared anymore,
because I'm with you, Collin.
Collin, I love you. I want to be with you.
We'll be together forever.
I can't.
I just can't. No!
Not there.
I'm embarrassed.
Felina, you're so beautiful.
Don't look at me so closely.
May I?
Does it hurt?
No. I can feel you
with my whole body. I'm happy.
Felina...
Don't!
Collin, it's great!
Collin, thank you.
I want to be with you forever, Collin.
But the world you entered...
the world beyond the bottom
of this world, is my world.
If I don't return, that snow will not stop.
Although I will never be able
to see you again...
I won't forget the warmth you've given me.
I will remember you forever.
Thank you.
Felina.
Felina, the petals of the white flowers
are like the snow I saw in your world.