Princess Memory: First Half
Collin?
Where am I?
- What's that?
- Collin!
- Collin?
- How do you know my name?
Save me.
Beauty. Tell me, what's your name?
Felina.
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Please don't cry.
Wait! Felina!
Felina!
What are you doing?
You pervert, Collin! You vile creature.
What's the matter with you?
Aren't we like siblings?
A woman has to do the roof repair alone.
Don't we have a man in the house?
No way!
Sallian. Hi there.
Sorry I'm late.
Let me get started on that.
It's done. It's all finished.
How disappointing.
- I've had it!
- Hey, take it easy!
Watch out!
I saved! I'm saved!
- Do you run this inn?
- Yes.
Yes I do.
All right, I'll be staying for a while.
You mean, Collin?
He was calling out
a woman's name in his sleep.
So, Collin's finally interested in women?
No! That should never happen!
Pony, why do you care so much?
I don't care about
anything like that at all.
What?
Save me!
This voice is...
Collin?
What are you up to, young man?
I'm glad it's only you, Elder.
I heard a strange voice from over there.
From over there? Don't go there.
I'm sure you've heard of it before.
That's a very dangerous cave.
It was a good thing I happened to come by.
If you were to enter that cave...
even one step inside is dangerous.
Even just a step?
If you were to enter that cave...
Well, that's enough for one day.
You've got no idea, do you?
You heard me.
Don't you ever go near it.
What an appetite!
Going on an adventure
really makes you hungry.
You can't fight dragons or ghosts
on an empty stomach.
- Another serving, please.
- Yes, of course.
Going on an adventure?
That's right.
The world's filled with wonders.
My dream is to see them all.
This food's good.
Going on an adventure.
That sounds great!
In this village there aren't
any dragons or ghosts.
I'm not so sure.
What do you mean?
That food was delicious.
What's for desert?
What is it?
There's something I want to ask you about.
It's about that cave
on the edge of the village.
What?
- You should've said that right away.
- Not so rough!
This is the skull that was found under
the throne of the King of Moo Continent?
A wooden imitation of the real thing?
It's a human skull. It's real.
It's precious. Handle it with care, please.
I'm very sorry.
In fact, the reason why I've come
to this village...
is to explore that cave
on the edge of the village.
That cave?
Do you know something about it?
No. Don't go there.
If you enter that cave even
if it's just a step...
Even just a step?
I guess that's about enough for today.
What is it? Tell me.
You said you wanted to go on an adventure,
but you're just scared.
You've got to be kidding,
I'm not scared at all.
Tell me the truth. You're scared.
I'm not scared.
I'm not.
Don't worry. Just leave this to me.
You'll feel much better soon.
Yours is pretty good.
Really?
Makes me want you badly.
Please save me.
Felina!
Feels so good.
How is it? You like it?
It's good.
Will you be on top next?
It's great!
Let's go to that cave together.
You're man enough. It'll be all right.
Will you come with me?
What? I'm coming...
- You'll come then, right?
- No, it's really not that.
What's wrong, are you scared?
No! It's not like that.
Let's enter then, okay?
Let's do this another day.
All right then, another day.
Thought I'd say that?
Unexpectedly bright.
Nothing's coming out, right?
Wrong. I sense something.
Maybe it's time for us to go back.
What are you so afraid of?
You're not a virgin anymore.
Collin!
Not another monster?
Not sure.
Just wait!
It's that girl.
- It's Felina!
- You know her?
Yeah, I think so.
Felina? It's you, right?
Save me. Please, save me.
They're here!
Looks like we'd better call it a day
for now, okay?
Felina? It's you, right?
Who is she?
You got me. I have no idea.
Collin seems to know her.
She's a stranger to me.
Here. Chamomile tea.
It'll calm you down a bit.
What's wrong with her?
She's been like this the entire time.
So, Collin, who's she? Tell us.
I was told her name is Felina.
I don't know her! Never heard of her.
But l...
- Pony, it's okay, you know?
- But...
I'm telling you:
She's not in her right state.
She's been like this the entire time.
Lost her memory?
It's more like she lost her soul.
What do you mean,
she's lost her soul?
Some time ago,
while on another adventure...
I saw a man who looked just like her.
What happened to him?
Felina as well?
The man I saw turned to dust in three days.
In three days?
Isn't there any way to save her?
That cave is the only place
we might find a clue.
In that cave?
Did you enter that cave?
He sure did with me. He was brave.
Collin?
I don't know if you've noticed,
but I'm not a kid anymore.
That place is loaded with monsters!
How could you enter
such a dangerous place?
What are you going to do
if a monster eats you up?
You idiot, Collin!
Don't you know anything?
Looks like I better go back
to the cave on my own.
Please save me.
I'm going with you.
Collin?
I'm sorry Pony, but I have
no choice. I have to save her.
I'm going to be a strong man.
No don't! Don't go there!
Let him go.
- But Sis...
- You know that Collin's a man.
But...
Don't worry. As soon as we find out...
the way to save Felina,
we'll come right back.
You don't have to worry about it.
Stop your blathering,
are you coming or not?
Yes, I'm coming.
It's fine. I'm sure Collin can do it.
Let me handle this one.
There're tons of them, Lily!
Will you do something? Save us!
Didn't you just say
you'd handle this one?
Help me! Don't kill me!
We won't kill you. We're Nuvolians.
We understand your language.
We're the inhabitants of this cave.
He reminds me of someone.
You're the ones
who took away Felina, aren't you?
You know Felina?
The white flower.
- The white flower?
- Yeah.
A flower that blooms in the place
beyond the door made of rock...
down the stairs.
If you take that flower to Felina.
If I take that?
Well, it's enough for the day.
You've got no idea, do you?
Down the stairs?
We came after them
because we were worried.
It'll be all right.
Once we enter the cave,
we'll be with Collin and Lily.
Hey, Pony!
I was so frightened,
I couldn't help running right in.
Let's get out of here.
Which way do we go now?
I don't think we can go back now.
Run away!
No!
Pony!
I did it!
Look, over there!
Is that the door made of rock
which Elder Nuvolian spoke of?
This is the white flower.
How beautiful.
Collin...
Felina.
Why are you here?
Don't be fooled, Collin.
It's impossible. Felina cannot be here.
I am the soul of Felina.
Soul?
Collin, I've been waiting for you to come.
Felina, you must be saved, right?
No, I cannot return to Felina, yet.
Tell me, how come?
Before I can, there's a condition
to be fulfilled.
A condition?
Yes, you see...
you hold the key for that.
I am Madonna Felina, a crystallization
of Felina's beautiful heart.
People have many different facets.
Just like everyone else,
Felina has various facets.
Gentleness, slyness, wisdom, sadness.
What do I have to do?
Can you love all of Felina in her entirety?
- All of her?
- Can you?
I can! To save Felina, I'll do anything.
Who are you, tell me!
Greetings. I am Sly Felina.
The smartest among all the Felinas.
Do you really mean you can accept me?
I will accept any kind of Felina.
Despite this?
Pony! Sallian!
Foolish woman. Look how
they all followed you here.
I'm sorry. We were worried.
I'll give you a choice.
I'll let you save one of them.
You choose which one you save.
Damn it!
If you don't choose quickly,
they'll both end up dying.
Collin! Please look after Pony.
She loves you.
She really loves you, don't forget.
I'll leave her to you, okay?
No don't!
- Just stop it!
- Try not to move!
Sallian!
That was no fun at all.
But since I promised,
I'll save one of them.
Pony!
Are you all right?
Collin. Sallian. Sallian.
I'm so sorry I came.
I've caused so much trouble.
Do you hate me now? You must.
Can you still love me?
Can you love me?
Damn it all to hell!
Collin, please don't be misled by Sly Felina.
Big brother, I want to go home right now!
What's the matter with you?
Aren't you a man?
I'm telling you,
they're all Felina's soul.
See, it's not that easy
to truly love a person. Is it?
I can't do anything.
How disappointing.
You've already given up?
Collin?
Don't give up.
I won't doubt myself.
They vanished.
Leave them to me.
Take Pony and the white flower. Hurry.
But l...
Just go quickly!
I'll break a path for you.
Pony, let's go.
It's you, Lily.
That was close, wasn't it?
Thank you.
You okay?
Collin, look at her.
Lily?
I lost focus. My mistake.
Let's go home and treat
your wounds right away.
It's all right. Just leave me.
I probably won't last.
It's all my fault.
Go on Collin, you take it.
It's a memento of my father.
My father always wanted a son.
A strong and brave son.
You can help me to fulfill his dying wish.
Don't give up, Lily!
You're going to see the world, right?
Remember to be brave.
So long as you believe in yourself...
the path will be sure to open.
Lily!
No please, don't!
Pony, it's me.
Pony, I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
I know it's my fault you're left all alone.
I want to forget everything.
Pony.
Collin.
I can taste your tears, Pony.
Not there. Please, no.
You feel okay?
I'm okay, I'm hot.
I feel you Collin, inside.
Then, let me move about a bit.
Does this hurt?
I like it.
I'm coming!
Come!
Felina.
This is...
A beautiful flower.
Felina, you can talk.
Save me please! Save me.
Save me.