[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.47,0:00:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了 不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.99,0:00:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.85,0:00:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩根一起來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.50,0:00:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頂到裡面了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.38,0:00:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛 乳頭被捏壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.68,0:00:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,適可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.44,0:01:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼齷齪的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.24,0:01:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要高潮了 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.22,0:01:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼 明明那麼痛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.30,0:01:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體漸漸熱起來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.42,0:01:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我變得這麼淫蕩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.51,0:01:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太勉強了 已經不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.16,0:01:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然這麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.20,0:01:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面搞的亂七八糟的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.00,0:01:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.58,0:01:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼粗暴的對待乳房
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.70,0:02:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了 太勉強了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.51,0:02:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別進來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.63,0:02:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 身體亂七八糟的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.51,0:02:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上卷 公開處女喪失
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.51,0:02:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長 光 ～被淫魔佔領的學園～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.53,0:02:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,召喚術
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.50,0:02:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對怪物 黑暗奴僕專用必殺 聖十字射擊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.75,0:03:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我流奧義 古賀破碎彈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.96,0:03:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被稱為最強的學生會也就不過如此啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.17,0:03:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泉光
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.93,0:03:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連這種低級妖魔都打不倒麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.48,0:03:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學園的防禦系統又不靈了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.59,0:03:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別膽怯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.20,0:03:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉醬 由紀醬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.35,0:03:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要打倒了巴姆魯斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.02,0:03:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個結界必然會消失
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.18,0:03:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣 試試看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.54,0:03:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我流究極奧義 刺客斬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.43,0:03:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.04,0:04:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是一直這麼說麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.17,0:04:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要注意 先攻擊的人的弱點總是在側面
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.90,0:04:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴音老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.54,0:04:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妨礙巴姆魯斯的人我不會原諒的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.43,0:04:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會 為什麼老師
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.00,0:04:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落入魔手了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.46,0:04:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從巴姆魯斯那裡得到了黑暗的力量和快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.69,0:04:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在最幸福了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份心情我來告訴你們
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.64,0:05:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 被菜鳥的我折磨的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你已經沒有抵抗的力量了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.21,0:05:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.16,0:05:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.54,0:05:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 塞拉小姐淫蕩的地方全被看到了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.98,0:05:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卑鄙的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.71,0:05:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用這種方式
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.53,0:05:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點也不羞恥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.30,0:05:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊看啊 有感覺就叫響一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.41,0:05:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.26,0:06:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被你摸怎麼會有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.70,0:06:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論身體怎樣為玷污
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.54,0:06:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心絕對
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.70,0:06:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好堅強啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.46,0:06:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣才值得我來摧殘
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.94,0:06:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這邊如何
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.15,0:06:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.57,0:06:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 這邊更有感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.23,0:06:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.92,0:06:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼髒的地方被玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.26,0:06:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.84,0:06:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是大小姐 菊花真不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.70,0:06:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請放過我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.56,0:06:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這變態
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.91,0:06:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反應真不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.13,0:06:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這邊的處女我先收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.50,0:06:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.18,0:07:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊花被侵犯什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.70,0:07:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出來 拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.86,0:07:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別在裡面動來動去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.12,0:07:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多更多的插入
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.78,0:07:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多更多的快樂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.34,0:07:32.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別自說自話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.03,0:07:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.11,0:07:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快樂無比不是麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.45,0:07:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漸漸沉浸其中了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.69,0:07:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡說 不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.88,0:07:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的爪子裡有妖魔淫藥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.31,0:07:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被感染的話 你的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.19,0:07:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會變成性器中毒的變態妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.05,0:08:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被好幾根觸手搞的小穴很有感覺的變態大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.54,0:08:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經變成淫魔了 淫魔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.21,0:08:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.51,0:08:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個乳房就讓我改造成我喜歡的爆乳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.87,0:08:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.77,0:08:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,褻瀆我身體的事情是不會被原諒的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.01,0:08:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.43,0:08:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼東西進入胸部了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.55,0:08:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 漸漸的膨脹了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.57,0:09:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 乳房
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.30,0:09:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.50,0:09:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.15,0:09:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了 射了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.22,0:09:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從現在開始
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.51,0:09:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是不停噴著淫蕩牛奶的母牛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.55,0:09:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 別吸 不要吸乳房
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.85,0:09:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好喝哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.22,0:09:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遲早讓你懷上妖怪的孩子 並用這乳汁來哺育
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.20,0:09:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由紀的身體被玷污了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.36,0:09:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是退魔士卻有這麼淫蕩的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.53,0:09:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.09,0:10:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被這麼齷齪的手摸著怎麼會有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只感到噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.64,0:10:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就現在說說了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.07,0:10:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.04,0:10:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法抵抗而被羞辱的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.52,0:10:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姆魯斯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.21,0:10:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.62,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再給你點厲害的瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.70,0:10:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.33,0:10:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.55,0:10:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在敏感區域直接施加高壓電
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.88,0:10:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今為止你在這裡所承受的屈辱
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.08,0:10:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本算不了什麼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.35,0:10:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特意親自來對你身體的改造
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.32,0:10:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消除肌肉削除戰鬥能力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.29,0:10:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭 陰核自不必說
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.67,0:10:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連菊花和陰道的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.87,0:11:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全身的性感帶提升數十倍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.93,0:11:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更壞的是 連擦到內褲都會有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.23,0:11:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決不會變的那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.44,0:11:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後由我的手來直接改造
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.93,0:11:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.64,0:11:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.47,0:11:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.13,0:11:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女膜還留著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.94,0:11:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高興的留在後面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.36,0:11:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.95,0:11:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在欺負我的身體了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.21,0:11:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣 知道麼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.33,0:11:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你的子宮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.89,0:11:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別碰 這是女孩最重要的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.62,0:12:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在連子宮也有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.39,0:12:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.94,0:12:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.45,0:12:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樣子不錯啊 光
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.75,0:12:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怨恨我們的話就快點殺了我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.78,0:12:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要你的命呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.62,0:12:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姆魯斯的目的是讓你們學生會成員懷上妖怪的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.45,0:12:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們已經無法反抗巴姆魯斯大人了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.95,0:12:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想拯救學園學生性命的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.62,0:13:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 還有什麼好害羞的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.28,0:13:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.22,0:13:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 學生會長的泉光 快說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.38,0:13:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同學們 我希望能夠積極的推進學生會團長間的交流
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.61,0:13:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是為了打消同學們不安而準備的娛樂活動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.37,0:13:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來由我們做示範
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.05,0:14:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 真的假的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.95,0:14:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會員表演脫衣秀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.16,0:14:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做什麼啊 真忍不住了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.07,0:14:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ站起來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.63,0:14:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂怎麼搞的 三個人手都停下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.63,0:14:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.28,0:14:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 那種內褲 那種胸罩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.45,0:14:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長穿那個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.66,0:14:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超色啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.02,0:14:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 由紀的奶子是那樣的爆乳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.28,0:14:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸罩太小了 要露出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.31,0:15:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 也看看塞拉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.70,0:15:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她穿的那麼色 忍不住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.24,0:15:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莫非他們想讓我們看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.94,0:15:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼從由紀開始
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.81,0:15:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們想讓大家知道女孩裸體的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.36,0:15:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接著是塞拉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.96,0:15:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有固定戀人的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.91,0:15:46.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們學生會負責
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.78,0:15:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用我們的身體來指導你們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.13,0:15:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼是指導
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.33,0:15:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詳細的說明一下 光
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.23,0:16:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以處理一切你們所需要的色色的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.57,0:16:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我們就像變態一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.58,0:16:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明不想在大家面前說這種事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.28,0:16:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 學生會長 真的什麼都可以麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.86,0:16:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴姆魯斯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.95,0:16:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就全脫掉 全裸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.18,0:16:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 在這裡裸體什麼的 怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.91,0:16:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 不行麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.51,0:16:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 學生會光說不做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.74,0:16:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 是啊 到這份上了全部給我們看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.88,0:16:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要看乳房
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.40,0:16:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要看小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.96,0:16:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫掉 脫掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.74,0:17:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 我脫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.93,0:17:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我脫就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.76,0:17:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 光 快脫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.58,0:17:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己說的不是麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.44,0:17:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.86,0:17:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼由紀也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.68,0:17:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉也是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.31,0:17:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我記住
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.04,0:17:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 全部都看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.73,0:17:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉的身體真淫蕩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.23,0:17:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別用淫蕩的眼光看我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.00,0:17:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由紀也很厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.39,0:18:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個奶子真大
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.74,0:18:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶頭已經硬硬的豎起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.41,0:18:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一直盯著人家看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.88,0:18:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泉光也全被看光了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.39,0:18:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長的乳房和小穴都露出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然黑色的長發還是我最愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.74,0:18:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們才不想這樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.88,0:18:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得誇獎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.91,0:18:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此 就讓我們看看更加有趣的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.64,0:18:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請住手
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.43,0:18:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.73,0:18:39.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真礙事 這2個
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.22,0:18:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.31,0:18:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要打攪巴姆魯斯大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.02,0:18:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.82,0:19:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開我 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.67,0:19:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀啊呀
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.42,0:19:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哦 這種酸酸甜甜的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.85,0:19:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦一 看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.61,0:19:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長的小穴還是處女哎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.88,0:19:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長是處女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.59,0:19:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女的小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.00,0:19:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 別看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.15,0:19:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要舔 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.68,0:19:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡 不要舔不要舔 那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.76,0:19:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要不要不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.88,0:19:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.96,0:19:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是處女卻有感覺了麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.67,0:19:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣怎麼會有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.01,0:19:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會輸給你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.87,0:20:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要舔那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.56,0:20:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭別進來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.94,0:20:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淫水漸漸的冒出來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.66,0:20:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如假包換的處女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.25,0:20:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.45,0:20:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼做這樣的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.52,0:20:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會有這麼下流的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.06,0:20:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的變的奇怪了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.56,0:20:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.60,0:20:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 給大家看看滿是淫汁的處女小穴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.52,0:20:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 大家別看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.11,0:20:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 一張一合的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.99,0:20:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長 證明給我們看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.00,0:20:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我們看處女的證明
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 處女膜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.22,0:20:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能辦得到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.18,0:21:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想回應大家要求麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.61,0:21:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.00,0:21:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就把他們殺掉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.16,0:21:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己用手把小穴張開給他們看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.32,0:21:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.42,0:21:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全看到了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.92,0:21:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處女膜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.18,0:21:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是學生會長的處女膜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.45,0:21:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼詳細地解說給大家聽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.90,0:21:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同學們 這是我泉光處女的證明
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.37,0:21:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的真好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.25,0:21:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼獎勵你成為我的女人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.98,0:21:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼快點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.87,0:21:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 自己來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.43,0:22:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 剛才告訴你的說給大家聽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.15,0:22:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對著大家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.91,0:22:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同學們 現在 光的小穴要讓JJ插入
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.34,0:22:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喪失處女了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.28,0:22:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光的破處 請大家仔細觀看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.01,0:22:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊 JJ進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.35,0:22:30.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快進去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.10,0:22:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼大 怎麼進得去 太勉強了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.60,0:22:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 這只算撫慰
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.25,0:22:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放進去啊 放到裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.94,0:22:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 進不去 進不去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.63,0:22:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你狡辯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.36,0:23:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱 好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.04,0:23:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裂開了 裂開了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.36,0:23:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴裂開了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.11,0:23:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 拔出來 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.10,0:23:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被中出 裡面要被中出了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.60,0:23:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣你就變成女人了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.07,0:23:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這對退魔士是致命的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.62,0:23:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別亂說 只要我有命在
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.65,0:23:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要堅持到最後
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.98,0:23:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才有被調教的意義
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.58,0:24:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈 太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.80,0:24:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.02,0:24:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太刺激了 太刺激了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.64,0:24:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.83,0:24:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身體不會這麼簡單就壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.27,0:24:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經把你的身體改造的可以承受一切了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.44,0:24:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你記住這個味道就無法離開我了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.64,0:24:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.28,0:24:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.75,0:24:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.03,0:24:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射入精液懷上我的孩子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.25,0:24:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要射
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.44,0:24:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要你這妖魔的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.95,0:24:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面射的滿滿的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.98,0:24:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.12,0:24:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光 好過分
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.20,0:24:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被這樣射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.37,0:25:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會懷孕的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.49,0:25:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破處加懷孕 不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.03,0:25:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.44,0:25:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的會懷孕的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.41,0:25:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.14,0:25:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的調教還沒結束啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.01,0:25:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.90,0:25:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厲害 第幾回了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.10,0:25:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直被幹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.35,0:25:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面好辛苦 要壞了 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.56,0:25:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出來吧 求求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.85,0:25:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔出來 讓我休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.40,0:25:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別擔心 我會給你忘記疲勞的快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.82,0:26:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.37,0:26:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你的子宮是最弱的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.61,0:26:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子宮壞了 子宮壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.11,0:26:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.50,0:26:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次輪到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.54,0:26:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 還在射 高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.28,0:26:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠了 請原諒光吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.22,0:26:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被幹幾個小時了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.19,0:26:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼下去光要壞掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.67,0:27:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 很快就會快樂起來
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.62,0:27:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.31,0:27:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 又在裡面 好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.26,0:27:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多該到後面了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.25,0:27:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是第一次 但再加上一根吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.15,0:27:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那裡是 住手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.06,0:27:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 夾的我好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.03,0:27:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂這邊也吃一吃
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.05,0:27:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被操了 菊花裡面也被操了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.37,0:27:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從菊花到子宮都在啪啪地響
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.25,0:27:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀呀上面的嘴還張著的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.00,0:27:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂快點吃
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.72,0:27:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂 4P啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.26,0:27:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴上說著不要 干的卻那麼猛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.89,0:27:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的想給我們看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.89,0:28:03.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學生會長真夠禽獸了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.55,0:28:11.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啊 我為了保護大家 才忍著屈辱
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.28,0:28:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真過分 大家真過分
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.35,0:28:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉 大家的樣子好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.40,0:28:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家被妖氣侵入了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.98,0:28:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 身上的洞都被插入的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.38,0:28:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多極限了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.17,0:28:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這邊也要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.70,0:28:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.96,0:28:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴和菊花同時被射舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.61,0:28:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的最舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.10,0:28:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴的JJ最舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.27,0:29:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收下吧收下吧 變成雌獸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.02,0:29:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.08,0:29:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JJ在小穴好好好好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.70,0:29:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懷上妖魔的孩子吧 泉光
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.01,0:29:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣 光
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.81,0:29:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來輪到你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.99,0:29:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞拉 由紀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.50,0:00:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.30,0:00:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,

