[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.30,0:00:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（咒語）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.00,0:02:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（咒語）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.63,0:02:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走極端的黑魔術活動
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.12,0:02:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泰勒瑪週期
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.93,0:02:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雷斯塔．克羅利的後裔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.00,0:02:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬蒂．克羅利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.50,0:03:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（咒語）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.19,0:04:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來釋放妳的緊張吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.01,0:06:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒　好棒…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.29,0:06:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴裡面…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.62,0:06:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.84,0:06:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…　不行了…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.33,0:06:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.83,0:06:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然　北見麗香她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.28,0:06:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緋色的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.84,0:06:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.49,0:07:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臨．兵．鬥．者．皆．列．陣．在．前
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.61,0:07:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.41,0:07:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬蒂嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.42,0:07:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結界？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.22,0:07:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城也在啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.37,0:07:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城師父…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.02,0:07:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城師父…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.63,0:07:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請振作起來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.88,0:07:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白木小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.38,0:07:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.44,0:07:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.55,0:07:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白木妳怎麼在這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.79,0:08:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今天起　我就是學校的代課老師了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.39,0:08:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳來得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.69,0:08:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪我一下好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.43,0:08:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要到學校的地下室
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.32,0:08:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要叫救護車嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.62,0:08:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.49,0:08:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,緋色的女人?!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.34,0:08:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.56,0:08:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高城師父
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.94,0:08:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"緋色的女人"是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.60,0:08:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿雷斯塔．克羅利　一直在追求的惡魔夥伴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.71,0:08:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔夥伴？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.84,0:08:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼可愛的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.14,0:09:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被狂熱的惡魔祟拜者們尊為
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.92,0:09:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教祖的阿雷斯塔．克羅利
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其後裔喬蒂．克羅利　被視為其能力的繼承者
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.12,0:09:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬蒂為了實現克羅利的預言
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.26,0:09:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在尋找約翰的默示錄
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.70,0:09:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第十七章中所述的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.33,0:09:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能生下力量超越\N地上所有王者的小孩的緋色女人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.74,0:09:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惜現在是下落不明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.74,0:09:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前為了將北見麗香
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.46,0:09:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,封印在伊萬里體內
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.09,0:09:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整理關係者資料時　偶然發現了她的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.05,0:09:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬蒂出現在我面前…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.09,0:09:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,設下結界保護這女孩\N已是我能力的最極限
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.29,0:09:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不曉得　她與北見麗香的關係為何
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.81,0:09:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白木
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.40,0:09:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事對校內的人一定要保密
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.50,0:09:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.50,0:09:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見麗香
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.17,0:10:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.76,0:10:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請假期間　這位白木老師將代替我教導各位
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.09,0:10:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸會　請大家多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.37,0:10:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼剩下的拜託妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.20,0:10:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油啊　白木老師
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.64,0:10:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝妳　佐伯老師
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.38,0:11:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.38,0:11:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐現在睡得很熟
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.99,0:11:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就會醒過來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.02,0:11:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天您可以放心的回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.86,0:12:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.83,0:12:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這女人誤以為我是她的老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.03,0:12:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您怎麼了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.20,0:12:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不　沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.40,0:12:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.87,0:12:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問照顧她的人是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.54,0:12:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位女尼姑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.52,0:12:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您去看急救室的資料\N應該能找到她的連絡方式
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.89,0:12:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.72,0:12:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大島先生　你被車子撞到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.66,0:12:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您記得嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.10,0:12:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原田繪理…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.07,0:12:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您不可以勉強自己啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.03,0:13:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼做這種事？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.87,0:13:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請什麼都不要問
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.23,0:13:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳出人意料的…大膽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.20,0:13:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過很適合妳哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.64,0:13:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！　太美麗了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.47,0:14:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.38,0:15:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.08,0:15:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…　好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.58,0:15:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.01,0:15:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你住手　大島先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.69,0:15:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以　大島先生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.04,0:15:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是醫院　不能…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.19,0:15:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能做這種事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.66,0:15:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.27,0:16:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳想指使我嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.30,0:16:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳這裡明明很渴望
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.81,0:16:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳剔得這麼乾淨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.29,0:16:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是期待很久了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.24,0:16:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乳頭尖立起來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.31,0:16:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下體也濕成這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.52,0:16:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在渴望著我的大東西插入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.77,0:17:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不見　伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.72,0:17:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不　現在妳是北見麗香
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.55,0:17:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是如何知道這裡的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.14,0:18:04.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪惡之氣籠罩在這一帶　遠遠的就能看見了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.69,0:18:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳來得正好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.23,0:18:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省下我找妳的功夫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.03,0:18:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不知道妳想做什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.13,0:18:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之請妳照先前的那樣\N乖乖的待在伊萬里體內吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.44,0:18:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上次是我太大意…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.31,0:18:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次不會那麼簡單了！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.85,0:18:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.90,0:18:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問有什麼事嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.97,0:18:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧江同學…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.93,0:18:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼晚妳怎麼來這裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.00,0:18:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起在等白木老師呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.04,0:18:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.45,0:19:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭！　討厭！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.84,0:19:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.82,0:19:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.78,0:19:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.45,0:20:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(咒語)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.38,0:21:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手　伊萬里…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.44,0:21:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.93,0:22:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被插屁眼　有快感啦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.65,0:22:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還是老樣子那麼淫亂
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.48,0:22:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼裡面很熱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.61,0:22:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對　妳曾用這裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.92,0:22:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用這個屁眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.02,0:22:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奪走我的南瀨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.55,0:22:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奪走我的南瀨的　對吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.60,0:22:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估計…　這屁眼很值得品嚐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.12,0:23:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.12,0:23:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.99,0:23:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了　這屁眼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.99,0:23:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.36,0:23:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳的屁眼在說請多欺負我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.26,0:23:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊…伊萬里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.97,0:23:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求妳…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.65,0:23:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別玩弄我的屁眼了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.07,0:23:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求妳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.51,0:23:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做就使用前面的洞…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.41,0:23:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳在胡說什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.91,0:24:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳的屁眼明明很有快感
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.98,0:24:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳還是老樣子的淫亂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.65,0:24:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用害羞的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.92,0:24:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳的屁眼很爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.20,0:24:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真痛快
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.60,0:24:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳越是抗拒　我越痛快
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.11,0:24:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…　不要用肛交…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.72,0:24:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了　這個被妳的屁眼弄髒了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.49,0:24:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳要負責吃乾淨它
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.43,0:25:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.00,0:25:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有結束呢…


