[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.38,0:00:17.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.04,0:00:21.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一天只給你吃這些聖代是不是太少了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.42,0:00:24.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不要我去叫爺爺多加點
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.50,0:00:28.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明明都是妳一個人獨佔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.33,0:00:33.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 進展如何了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.42,0:00:36.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,遇到了點麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.92,0:00:44.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:45.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.79,0:00:47.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你擺出那麼陰沉的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.38,0:00:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫我如何回味殘留在我口中的聖代餘味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.25,0:00:55.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只想聽到好的消息 知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.75,0:00:57.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.88,0:00:58.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟我來一下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.38,0:01:14.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐 在這種地方做會被人發現的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.58,0:01:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都勃起成這樣 還說這種話
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.04,0:01:24.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可...可是
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.38,0:01:32.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看 從肉棒的前端流出液體了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.04,0:01:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把這液體塗在龜頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.04,0:01:37.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒就會變得滑溜溜的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.54,0:01:40.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.29,0:01:49.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來就會很敏感吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.13,0:01:51.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,陰囊裡的 「蛋」 也愈來愈明顯了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.00,0:01:54.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,男人的私處真是有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.92,0:02:01.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射了?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.17,0:02:02.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.50,0:02:05.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那接下來你自己解決吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.29,0:02:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.13,0:02:13.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣吧 快看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.58,0:02:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.79,0:02:26.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 要去了 我要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.92,0:02:35.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.08,0:02:45.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已給你這樣的服務了 你可要多加油唷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.04,0:02:46.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.00,0:02:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.54,0:02:49.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.00,0:03:04.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了 開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.54,0:03:35.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.92,0:03:58.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 笑容 笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.13,0:04:09.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:12.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.17,0:04:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 妳這麼粗心 , 萬一斷掉怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.29,0:04:19.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託妳集中精神好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.29,0:04:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 我果然是學不好暗之新體操
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.21,0:04:28.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能那樣軟懦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.46,0:04:30.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪妳一定辦得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.75,0:04:35.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就加油吧 暗之新體操
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.04,0:04:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.08,0:04:45.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要在這裡特訓嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.04,0:04:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對  率直地感覺特訓
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.25,0:04:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.96,0:04:56.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳要想成\N'"這裡的人都是暗之新體操的評審和觀眾'"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.25,0:04:56.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.25,0:05:09.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.17,0:05:12.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪已這麼濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.79,0:05:14.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.54,0:05:16.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.75,0:05:17.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別討厭嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.13,0:05:20.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺的話就說出來嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.50,0:05:21.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種事...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.58,0:05:28.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把它撿起來 維持這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.25,0:05:31.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.42,0:05:34.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,害羞什麼啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.50,0:05:37.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺的話就盡情表現出來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.88,0:05:39.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不也是為了特訓嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.13,0:05:43.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.67,0:05:45.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要去了 小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.75,0:05:47.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.58,0:06:00.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 舒服嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.71,0:06:01.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.88,0:06:08.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺吧 很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.00,0:06:10.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老實說出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.88,0:06:13.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.50,0:06:14.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就要展現笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.21,0:06:17.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要把那感覺用笑容表現出來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.54,0:06:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.96,0:06:26.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這些人都是來看小雪妳那可愛的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.83,0:06:28.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要回應他們的期待
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.88,0:06:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 在這種地方高潮 太難為情了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.75,0:06:45.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 已...已經...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.54,0:06:57.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到達最後了呢 小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.54,0:07:02.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是這笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.25,0:07:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要是這笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.33,0:07:06.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,評審們都會給妳10分的滿分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.21,0:07:22.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界以我為中心而轉動
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.08,0:07:30.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我卻還是無法滿足
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.42,0:07:33.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種無聊世界...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.88,0:07:37.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想下令將它給毀滅算了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.67,0:07:43.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是一生都無法滿足 悲哀又可憐的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.83,0:07:49.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好累
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.00,0:07:54.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打掃辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.21,0:07:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,籐宮同學呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.42,0:07:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去沖涼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.54,0:08:02.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說到籐宮... 給你們看一樣好東西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.71,0:08:04.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.08,0:08:06.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,籐宮的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.71,0:08:09.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有其它的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.54,0:08:15.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.46,0:08:16.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.38,0:08:18.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哪拍到的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.96,0:08:20.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去便利商店時碰巧拍到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.96,0:08:23.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,籐宮和那男的感情不錯哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.38,0:08:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就叫相親相愛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.25,0:08:26.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪她...?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.21,0:08:29.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳是用偷拍的?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.00,0:08:30.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真差勁的嗜好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.29,0:08:33.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳...嫉妒? Jealousy?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.79,0:08:35.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳在吃醋吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.33,0:08:38.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正妳是交不到男友的 安心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.04,0:08:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼?!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.96,0:08:43.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為妳無胸又無臀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.25,0:08:44.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳憑什麼說那種話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.00,0:08:46.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂! 聽到了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.04,0:08:49.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 這照片裡的人是誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.25,0:08:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的男朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:51.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.17,0:08:51.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第二個男友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.96,0:08:52.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那這個呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.58,0:08:53.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大概是第四個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.83,0:08:54.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這也是男友!?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.79,0:09:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.67,0:09:20.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靠牆坐好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.04,0:09:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要做什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.58,0:09:27.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別動
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.71,0:09:30.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有感覺了?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.42,0:09:36.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不論對方是誰 小雪都會有感覺是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.54,0:09:46.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 這是什麼特訓?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.08,0:09:49.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這不是特訓
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.33,0:09:52.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.71,0:09:56.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是懲罰
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.04,0:10:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我無法原諒妳背著我和其他男人交往
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.71,0:10:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是指什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.67,0:10:03.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別裝蒜!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.29,0:10:05.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣 好痛 肚子好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.71,0:10:08.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 別這樣 吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.50,0:10:09.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那男人是誰?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.17,0:10:12.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和妳一起進便利商店的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.13,0:10:14.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們倆看起來感情真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.58,0:10:15.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.75,0:10:21.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 肚子快壞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.54,0:10:28.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜託 讓我去上廁所
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.96,0:10:30.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.50,0:10:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我幫妳治療吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.08,0:10:39.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪妳也和那男人做過這種事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.00,0:10:42.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 屁股好痛 要裂開了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.92,0:10:46.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我不知道的地方盡情地享樂是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.25,0:10:49.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒那回事 吹雪你誤會了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.96,0:10:52.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.17,0:10:55.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出來了 要出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.79,0:10:57.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦是吧? 難過是吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.04,0:11:00.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我內心也有相同感受 我們扯平了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.71,0:11:01.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.75,0:11:06.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪你不相信我的話 我會很悲傷的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.96,0:11:09.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只要能和吹雪在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.92,0:11:11.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼痛苦我都能承受
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.92,0:11:15.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,相信我 吹雪 相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.88,0:11:17.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 那男的是?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.67,0:11:20.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那...那男的是我兒時玩伴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.83,0:11:22.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,碰巧遇見的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.08,0:11:26.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後...然後怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.29,0:11:29.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他想要我跟他交往
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.67,0:11:31.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我拒絕了 就這樣而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.17,0:11:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的就只有這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.71,0:11:35.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.96,0:11:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 小雪 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.29,0:11:46.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能理解就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.75,0:11:49.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是...我已忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.17,0:11:51.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要看...不要看
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.04,0:13:25.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐...平時看她總愛逞強
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.79,0:13:27.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實際上很寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.33,0:13:31.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對她說這番話 可能會被殺的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.83,0:13:44.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,靜下來時倒是很可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.13,0:13:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真希望她再誠實一點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.83,0:13:55.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她這人有什麼原因?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.08,0:14:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.04,0:14:27.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睡著了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.75,0:14:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我打掃完了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.75,0:14:32.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說過的地方你還沒打掃過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.92,0:14:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了 可要給我打掃完
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.29,0:14:38.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可不允許你偷工減料
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.92,0:14:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像有股味道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.58,0:14:43.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像是墨水的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.00,0:14:45.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳多心了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.63,0:14:47.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 那就拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.08,0:14:53.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天也自行休假嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.96,0:14:55.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是夠隨便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.13,0:15:14.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是...?!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.96,0:15:24.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人能夠進入我的內心世界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.83,0:15:29.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人...沒有人...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.29,0:15:35.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人...沒有人...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.29,0:15:46.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,羽丘同學 去陪陪她吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.83,0:15:47.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.13,0:15:50.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她沒來這?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.33,0:16:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什麼? 現在是上課時間
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.33,0:16:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐才是 妳在做什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.96,0:16:17.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...為了維護校園的和平
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.21,0:16:18.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.29,0:16:22.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.58,0:16:27.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪她肚子痛 應該去保健室 可是她卻不在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.83,0:16:29.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,籐宮?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.13,0:16:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,該不會是逃跑了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.88,0:16:33.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不會這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.00,0:17:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.79,0:17:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹...吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.38,0:17:26.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 這是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.63,0:17:29.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我...明明是上課時間
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.88,0:17:32.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是我實在忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.88,0:17:34.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.79,0:17:37.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我這麼自說自話 真是對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.79,0:17:39.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.00,0:17:42.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪妳已能率直面對自身的感受了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.63,0:17:45.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,變得和我期望的一樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.29,0:17:49.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪...來做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.71,0:18:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.38,0:18:22.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 實在是太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.63,0:18:27.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 再來 再來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.46,0:18:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.83,0:18:37.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 我要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.25,0:18:40.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是...我也是...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.63,0:18:42.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吹雪 一起高潮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.96,0:18:51.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辦得到 現在一定可以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.71,0:19:01.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 到最後也別忘記保持笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.25,0:19:03.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.04,0:19:17.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小雪 就是這狀態
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.46,0:19:19.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們倆身體間的距離要注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.71,0:19:20.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.71,0:19:43.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了 完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.88,0:19:46.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.79,0:19:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做得不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.00,0:19:58.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,籐宮同學的進步真的超出我的預期
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.96,0:20:01.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳很努力 要表揚妳一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.50,0:20:03.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這都是吹雪的功勞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.00,0:20:06.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有個好教練指導妳很幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.00,0:20:07.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.21,0:20:12.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟妳教練有點話要談 妳能不能迴避一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.08,0:20:20.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,暗之新體操中 , 所謂的 「暗」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.25,0:20:25.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是讓自身被自己心靈侵蝕的狀態
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.58,0:20:29.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若在心靈的某處否定暗之新體操
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.04,0:20:32.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那種對暗之新體操的牴觸心理
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.50,0:20:36.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會不知不覺的使自己的心靈愈來愈自閉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.79,0:20:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能夠把自己感覺誠實表現出來的小雪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.63,0:20:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,並沒有被黑暗侵蝕\N我覺得那就是最好的證據
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.75,0:20:48.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.33,0:20:52.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 要將未來姐恢復原樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.29,0:20:54.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要讓她重新練習就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.46,0:20:58.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當然 教練是我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.83,0:21:00.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.13,0:21:03.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這人真是有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.38,0:21:05.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.21,0:21:10.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道你現在還相信暗之新體操嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.71,0:21:13.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.63,0:21:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說的那些話全是騙人的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.38,0:21:19.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看你太正經了 就故意戲弄你而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.04,0:21:24.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙我的? 妳在開玩笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.33,0:21:27.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟你說被騙了 竟然還不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.33,0:21:30.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你自己不就是個'"玩笑'"嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.83,0:21:31.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼這樣...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.13,0:21:34.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過有一句話肯定沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.29,0:21:37.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是 「羽丘實在是個有趣的玩具」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.04,0:21:42.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是...玩具...嗎...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.71,0:21:43.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.13,0:21:46.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一般人就算有戀姐廦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.25,0:21:49.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有誰會穿著水手服上女校的?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.00,0:21:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又有誰還會去穿體操服?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.42,0:21:51.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不敢相信
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.25,0:21:59.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.75,0:22:02.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你終於發覺自己是多麼的有趣了?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.33,0:22:05.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐妳...真是個可憐的人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.96,0:22:08.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊? 你在說什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.58,0:22:14.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.04,0:22:20.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,智美小姐妳封閉自己的心靈 就是這原因吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.75,0:22:23.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳為了擺脫這種恥辱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.50,0:22:25.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,故意顯得自己高人一等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.92,0:22:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真正被黑暗侵蝕的 是智美小姐妳自己啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.42,0:22:31.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那又如何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.67,0:22:35.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想用那些照片來恐嚇我嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.00,0:22:37.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想要多少錢?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.71,0:22:47.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.00,0:22:50.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.42,0:22:52.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.54,0:22:56.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 開始暗之新體操的特訓吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.46,0:22:59.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會好好地調教妳的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.79,0:23:10.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手...手...要斷了...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.79,0:23:22.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.25,0:23:25.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胸部要變形了 乳頭開始發熱了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.08,0:23:29.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,放開我 放開我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.38,0:23:30.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.21,0:23:47.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礙事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.50,0:23:55.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.83,0:23:57.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好痛?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.08,0:24:00.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙人的吧 妳看這是什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.38,0:24:04.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在問妳話 快回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.38,0:24:09.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳就是這種性慾強烈的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.21,0:24:13.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老實說出來吧 妳想要更多剌激吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.75,0:24:14.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.71,0:24:18.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.54,0:24:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還要? 妳說還要是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.50,0:24:28.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 接下來是後面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.46,0:24:32.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽不見嗎? 就是這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.79,0:24:35.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要把這個東西插進這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.46,0:24:38.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不行 就那裡不行
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.58,0:24:39.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.75,0:24:45.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.17,0:24:48.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過這樣一來妳前面的洞就會很閒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.63,0:24:49.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓妳充實的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.00,0:24:54.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.00,0:25:28.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳自己也許不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.83,0:25:30.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用磨牙剌激的感覺是最爽的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.75,0:25:33.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.42,0:25:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是妳的 快穿上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.71,0:25:41.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快點起來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.79,0:25:43.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.54,0:25:58.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.42,0:26:02.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妳在做什麼 妳這也算自稱天才的演技嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.17,0:26:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要小看暗之新體操
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.13,0:26:23.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 妳那是什麼表情
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.04,0:26:25.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,給我開心點
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.58,0:26:28.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過來
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.96,0:26:40.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就使勁點
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.50,0:26:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.25,0:26:49.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.42,0:27:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這世界是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.92,0:27:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隻身踏進這世界的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.21,0:27:05.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,羽丘吹雪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.96,0:27:08.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個男人...這個男人...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.75,0:27:13.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也許能把我從孤獨的世界中拯救出來
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.04,0:27:15.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.21,0:27:22.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說不定會很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.33,0:27:27.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 準備運動結束
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.29,0:27:29.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 教練