[Script Info]
ScriptType: V4.00
PlayResY: 960
PlayResX: 720
PlayDepth: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Aegisub Video Zoom Percent: 1.000000
Aegisub Scroll Position: 0
Aegisub Active Line: 11
Last Style Storage: Default

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00FF7C00,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,3,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.50,0:00:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勒緊啊!勒緊啊!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.80,0:00:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只一次也好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.00,0:00:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和穿著惱人制服的妳們
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.00,0:00:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣都要大幹一場呀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.94,0:00:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要…要洩了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.94,0:00:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於要上主菜了嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.80,0:01:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.54,0:02:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.30,0:04:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆基努斯的日照…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.30,0:04:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞紀君!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.50,0:04:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.30,0:04:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞紀君!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.20,0:04:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弓削…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,課長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.86,0:04:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驗屍間
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.70,0:06:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那兩具既然都檢查過了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.30,0:06:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屍體解剖幹嘛還要看…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.00,0:06:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼不可思議的事還是首次見到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.02,0:06:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到男方燒成焦炭為止都在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.90,0:06:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女方卻一點傷痕也沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.80,0:06:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保持地乾乾淨淨…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.70,0:06:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過主任
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.54,0:06:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件案子不是已從我們這
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.54,0:06:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉到特檢那幫人…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.80,0:07:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至於解剖報告
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.90,0:07:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非有管轄權的我們不可
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.58,0:07:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那幫傢伙不過是頂著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.70,0:07:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研究機關頭銜的民間人士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.74,0:07:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!對…對呀
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.66,0:07:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎有這種怪事!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.60,0:07:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生什麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.14,0:07:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?屍體復甦了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.54,0:08:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噯?嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.70,0:08:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛轄區刑警打電話來…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.42,0:08:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是資料
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.26,0:08:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤堂由希
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.50,0:08:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外陰部擦傷原因推論
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.30,0:08:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,依本人所見 燒死的級任導師
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.50,0:08:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉谷老師有施暴之嫌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.30,0:08:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他沒有異常並且健康良好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.00,0:08:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神狀況也很安定
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.70,0:08:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和接她的親人一起回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.40,0:08:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天開始新學期…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.06,0:08:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去學校看看那裡的狀況
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.70,0:08:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.50,0:08:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微休息一下再去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.70,0:08:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就去搜查
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.40,0:08:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里主任 樣子有點怪…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.50,0:08:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳昏迷時大概發生過很多事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.70,0:09:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不說這個 亞紀君!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.50,0:09:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀行失物的資料呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.10,0:09:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊!是 這就去拿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.02,0:09:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銀行金庫內 只有這個失竊了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.30,0:09:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,襲撃銀行的人全都死了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.50,0:09:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳和伊萬里君在被抓之前
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.30,0:09:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼特別的事 試著回想一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.30,0:09:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里主任和我對於…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.00,0:09:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在學校屋頂燒死的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.18,0:09:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉谷教師的考古學家父親…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.50,0:09:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉谷宗治的保管箱的內容…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.50,0:09:33.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要去確認 為了這緣故…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.98,0:09:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往那間銀行…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.30,0:09:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…和連續異常殺人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.50,0:09:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼關聯嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.50,0:09:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個吉谷宗治半年前行蹤不明
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.22,0:09:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說是為了發掘遺跡而外出…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.70,0:10:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不分國內國外
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.34,0:10:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,調出所有惡魔崇拜狂信者的手法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.94,0:10:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞紀君!妳去調查那件失竊物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.66,0:10:10.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,並與伊萬里君確實搜查學校
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.22,0:10:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.90,0:10:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師 有什麼事嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.10,0:10:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.42,0:10:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼一大清早的 真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.60,0:10:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.14,0:10:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要是一直對教育熱心的…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.50,0:10:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師的請求的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.80,0:10:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何況今天起就是新學期了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.74,0:10:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分感謝您
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.08,0:10:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請用
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.90,0:11:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次到這裡來…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.90,0:11:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師招待的茶都很好喝
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.70,0:11:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦?比平常來的苦一些…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.70,0:11:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 比平常放的多一些…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.50,0:11:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.50,0:11:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不說這個 教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.00,0:11:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於想拜託您的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.62,0:11:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請到這裡來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.98,0:11:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.40,0:11:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個學校竟有這樣的地下道…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.78,0:11:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是修道院的遺跡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.02,0:11:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我們還是學生的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.50,0:11:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽北見麗華老師說的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.30,0:12:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師也是這裡的畢業生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.38,0:12:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.50,0:12:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天起來代課的白木老師也…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.46,0:12:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說是這裡的畢業生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.46,0:12:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和我是同期生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.90,0:12:22.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外在這學校休息期間…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.90,0:12:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎發生事件了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.86,0:12:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐…佐伯老師
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.00,0:12:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從哪裡聽到這消息的…?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.50,0:12:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然捲入事件的學生會長…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.50,0:12:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桐谷早紀同學
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.82,0:12:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不曉得桐谷君知道些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.62,0:12:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據警方調査 是說愛慕她的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.50,0:12:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,級任導師吉谷老師
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.70,0:12:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心智混亂強姦了藤堂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.38,0:12:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道自己犯了大錯而燒身自殺
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.18,0:12:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…真是恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.00,0:13:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件由校長和她的爺爺…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.50,0:13:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤堂理事長…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.60,0:13:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說服警察而掩飾過去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.86,0:13:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過令人擔心的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.00,0:13:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤堂君所受精神衝撃的創傷…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.50,0:13:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的後遺癥方面…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.86,0:13:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是溫柔呢 教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.42,0:13:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這…這個是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.70,0:13:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤堂…君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.10,0:13:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.02,0:13:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這回有一點事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.02,0:13:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想請動見觀瞻的教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.00,0:13:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟學生會幹部們務必拜託…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.30,0:13:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.70,0:14:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藤…藤堂君!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.20,0:14:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳…妳們…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.00,0:14:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.00,0:15:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金屬成分?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.50,0:15:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 鐵?碳?鎳?鉻?鉬
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.80,0:15:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有微量的錳?鎢?釩?鈦?鈷
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.38,0:16:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些是遺跡的成分元素嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.40,0:16:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.60,0:16:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從銀行保管箱所附屬的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.00,0:16:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.90,0:16:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保管箱的盒子裡的殘渣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.50,0:16:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔細地調查過了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.20,0:16:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由它曲線端的形狀看來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.30,0:16:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是像槍尖之類的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.80,0:16:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那東西竟是五千年前以合金鑄造
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.80,0:16:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用來做成槍的可能性是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.50,0:16:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隆基努斯的日照…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.70,0:16:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噯?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.38,0:16:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是什麼啊?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.50,0:16:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歷經十個小時
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.20,0:16:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刺穿耶穌的側腹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.18,0:16:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地下室?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.74,0:16:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡有什麼嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.98,0:17:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佐伯老師…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.60,0:17:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.00,0:17:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和老師的交合…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.74,0:17:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教頭先生…非常飢渴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.00,0:17:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(嚥…)
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.00,0:17:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,場面會不會太刺激了?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.00,0:17:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對妳這個處女而言
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.50,0:18:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不是那裡啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.70,0:18:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.90,0:18:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧 教頭先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.62,0:19:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力…再用力點好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.78,0:21:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個到底是什麼儀式?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.70,0:21:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了從黑暗世界中復活
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.00,0:21:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 亞紀…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.74,0:21:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儀式這才要開始喲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.30,0:21:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.82,0:22:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儀式…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.82,0:22:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.00,0:22:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快一點的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.50,0:22:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚇!?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.82,0:22:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茱蒂…庫洛尼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.26,0:22:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊…萬里…主任
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.40,0:22:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣子…要對我…做什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.50,0:23:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦妳了 佐伯同學
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.50,0:23:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可真讓妳久等了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.90,0:23:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 能再會就很高興了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.80,0:23:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北見老師
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.20,0:23:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北…北見老師?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.80,0:23:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊萬里主任是…


