[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.13,0:00:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和時空侵略者蓋斯特戰鬥而受傷的紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.15,0:00:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被弘樹所救 保住了一名
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.57,0:00:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑為了監視受蓋斯特病毒感染的弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.80,0:00:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潛入到了弘樹的日常是生活中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.82,0:00:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在學校裡髮生了意外事件
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.61,0:00:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,齣現在調查事件的兩人面前的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.79,0:00:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是蛞蝓蓋斯特化的尾田原
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.04,0:00:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹受到了緻命傷 紫苑中了劇毒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.11,0:00:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有反擊之力 被蹂躪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.23,0:00:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救下這樣的紫苑的是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.90,0:00:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該身為敵人的蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.91,0:00:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被神祕蓋斯特抱著時的紫苑眼裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.43,0:00:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,映射著統治蓋斯特王者的身影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.96,0:00:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狼人蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.42,0:00:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙是誰 我是不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.67,0:01:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你越是耍帥 就會死的更慘哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.97,0:01:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.60,0:01:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑到哪裡去了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.39,0:01:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太強了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.20,0:01:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.78,0:01:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對 大人您難道是…朝木嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.21,0:01:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嘛 是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.22,0:01:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也成為蓋斯特了啊 作為你的好友 我很高興啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.16,0:01:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.80,0:01:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干擾源掃描數值 脩正為ε值
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.51,0:01:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,髮現蓋斯特反應 確認為兩體
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.03,0:02:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確認DOLL反應
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.90,0:02:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO.7
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.29,0:02:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行動代號 紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.80,0:02:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能進行建築物內部的探查
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.07,0:02:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要再次進行掃描數值的變更嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.90,0:02:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英菲尼迪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.25,0:02:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.98,0:02:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣會讓蓋斯特們髮現我們的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.83,0:02:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先說明一下已經確認的兩體蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.71,0:02:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一體的活動反應已經消失 另一體尚存活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.33,0:02:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能確定蓋斯特特性
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.76,0:02:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊就交給7號了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.19,0:02:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們繼續調查巫女的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.16,0:02:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yes My Lord
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.21,0:02:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使成為污穢不堪的樣子也還是要伸齣利爪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.72,0:02:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.86,0:02:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛謝謝你了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.78,0:02:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.02,0:02:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然一言不髮
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.73,0:02:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我迴想起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.07,0:02:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.69,0:02:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,將尾田原撕成碎片的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.33,0:03:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還留在指尖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.86,0:03:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 但是那是沒有辦法的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.83,0:03:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.92,0:03:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候 在我的內心某處對此感到很痛快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.87,0:03:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.74,0:03:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.26,0:03:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺死尾田原之後 我還…那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.75,0:03:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得自己…該怎麼說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.82,0:03:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想做愛是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.28,0:03:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這麼想的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.26,0:03:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓋斯特人格
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.55,0:03:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓋斯特人格
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.76,0:03:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓋斯特沒辦法保持實體
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.67,0:03:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就隻是一個擁有本能的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.46,0:03:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人類要是蓋斯特化了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.27,0:03:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人格會被破壞衝動和性慾
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.45,0:03:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這兩個最原始的本能所支配
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.83,0:03:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.32,0:03:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛總算是勉強忍住了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.54,0:03:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.47,0:03:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在想和我做愛嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.46,0:03:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為DOLL被設計成可以任由蓋斯特淩辱的體質
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.27,0:03:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以自然的少女生理反應是要被處理掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.58,0:03:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我還沒有處理
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.46,0:03:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果…還想做的話……
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.30,0:03:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的 不用忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.02,0:04:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫…紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.83,0:04:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.37,0:04:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被那個蛞蝓註射的媚藥 還在起作用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.56,0:04:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 紫苑 你的乳頭立的這麼直
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.91,0:04:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要說那種話 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.17,0:04:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是這麼做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.29,0:04:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.88,0:04:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 要有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.61,0:04:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.14,0:04:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.93,0:04:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是…要是這麼用力吮吸的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.11,0:04:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部有感覺嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.80,0:04:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.49,0:04:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 你現在非常美麗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.26,0:04:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹 你喜歡我的胸部嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.78,0:05:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 非常喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.03,0:05:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑的胸部又大又軟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.31,0:05:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再用力揉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.10,0:05:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.89,0:05:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部好有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.49,0:05:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹的手在揉我的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.69,0:05:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.59,0:05:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.30,0:05:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丟臉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.20,0:05:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑的小穴好大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.69,0:05:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下流的汁水不斷的流齣來了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.03,0:05:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.03,0:05:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.35,0:05:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.70,0:05:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼再讓你去一次
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.28,0:05:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是這麼做的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.55,0:05:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是這麼做的話會怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.90,0:06:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹 不行 那裡 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.88,0:06:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.27,0:06:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.06,0:06:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹的舌頭
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.70,0:06:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 紫苑 淫亂的汁水流齣來好多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.48,0:06:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 弘樹 很丟臉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.48,0:06:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑的小穴 味道好香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.96,0:06:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是在引誘我一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.16,0:06:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會 引誘什麼的 沒有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.57,0:06:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴濕漉漉的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.37,0:06:34.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都能髮齣這麼下流的聲音了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.39,0:06:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 好丟臉啊 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.77,0:06:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 髮齣這麼大聲音 而且非常濕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.02,0:06:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 不要欺負我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.24,0:06:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說啊「小穴已經很有感覺 變得濕淋淋的了」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.34,0:06:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 好丟臉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.40,0:06:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不說的話 我就不做了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.52,0:06:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.27,0:06:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小穴已經很有感覺 濕淋淋的了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.31,0:07:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是動的這麼厲害 我又要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.09,0:07:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了也沒關係啊 紫苑 去吧 使勁兒去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.16,0:07:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 超美味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.34,0:07:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.26,0:07:16.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.86,0:07:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個到底是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.26,0:07:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在開始 我是你的主人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.63,0:07:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.23,0:07:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.43,0:07:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.14,0:07:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 都進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.95,0:07:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要動起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.69,0:07:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 超舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.63,0:07:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹 弘樹在我裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.75,0:07:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面好有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.79,0:07:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.36,0:08:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在動啊 弘樹在我裡面操動
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.69,0:08:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 很下流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.67,0:08:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.76,0:08:08.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.15,0:08:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.64,0:08:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.98,0:08:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 在裡面 弘樹的變得好大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.09,0:08:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 這麼大 要裂開了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.67,0:08:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.86,0:08:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厲害 好粗壯 要去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.82,0:08:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.71,0:08:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.58,0:08:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒變得超級大
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.01,0:09:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且剛剛才射就已經迴複了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.21,0:09:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是蓋斯特化的影響嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.34,0:09:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐紫苑 再插進去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.41,0:09:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊 使勁兒插
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.37,0:09:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好粗壯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.37,0:09:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹不行 不能再插的更深了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.55,0:09:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.00,0:09:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了 我停不下來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.11,0:09:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 插得這麼深
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.60,0:09:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹 弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.94,0:09:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.99,0:09:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在超級想操你 想把你操繙天
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.51,0:09:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 隨弘樹你怎麼操都行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分啊 這樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.12,0:10:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 屁眼裡面黏黏的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.55,0:10:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被那個蛞蝓混蛋使勁兒操了 很有感覺了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.59,0:10:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺舒服了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.49,0:10:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.12,0:10:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 不要欺負我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.92,0:10:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情 不行 不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.77,0:10:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好丟臉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.79,0:10:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.27,0:10:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就好好的說齣來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.82,0:10:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡你  我喜歡弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.64,0:10:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼說你喜歡我的肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.42,0:10:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹的肉棒…我喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.40,0:10:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多說幾遍
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.85,0:10:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡弘樹的肉棒 再插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.40,0:10:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使勁兒插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.73,0:10:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼從今天開始紫苑就是我的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.91,0:10:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我肉棒的性奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.25,0:11:02.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是弘樹的性奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.30,0:11:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高興嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.57,0:11:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.34,0:11:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是弘樹的性奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.23,0:11:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 射了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.04,0:11:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹的又變大了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.62,0:11:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的屁眼裡面又變大了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.43,0:11:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.86,0:11:17.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.94,0:11:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.27,0:11:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 你醒了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.87,0:11:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 我一直在看著你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.54,0:11:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是睡著了就浪費了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.94,0:11:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有睡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.04,0:11:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚上好厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.40,0:11:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.11,0:11:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該是弘樹的性奴隸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.16,0:11:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我有說這種話嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.06,0:11:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.13,0:12:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼弘樹是我的什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.24,0:12:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.22,0:12:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 是啊 我應該就隻是紫苑一個人的東西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.12,0:12:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能像這樣恢複成人類
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.51,0:12:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為也是因為有你在的緣故
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.60,0:12:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很珍惜紫苑你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.30,0:12:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡紫苑你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.21,0:12:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.07,0:12:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹隻是我的東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.55,0:12:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.42,0:12:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又來
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.58,0:12:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑 上學要遲到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.91,0:12:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰叫弘樹的這麼舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.49,0:12:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.10,0:12:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.66,0:12:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.45,0:12:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.90,0:12:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐呐 聽說了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.32,0:12:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾田原從昨晚上起 下落不明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.42,0:12:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欸 真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.48,0:12:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.59,0:13:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還聽說昨天他有去舊校捨那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.10,0:13:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼又是那個幽靈搞的鬼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.59,0:13:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.29,0:13:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要介意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.80,0:13:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙已經不是人類了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.62,0:13:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.78,0:13:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝木
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.67,0:13:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美鈴老師叫你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.62,0:13:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美鈴老師
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.70,0:13:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 弘樹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.79,0:13:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼就你一個被美鈴老師叫去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.95,0:13:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.80,0:13:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道你和老師在交往嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.57,0:13:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.92,0:13:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.72,0:13:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚇死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.49,0:13:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.98,0:13:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝木真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.96,0:13:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.23,0:13:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有事是什麼事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.04,0:13:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事 那還用說嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.48,0:14:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的检查結果齣來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.08,0:14:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.65,0:14:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,检查的結果怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.40,0:14:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.97,0:14:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在那之前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.03,0:14:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天在半途有人礙事不是嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.55,0:14:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以老師一直是心裡悶悶的 焦躁不安呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.21,0:14:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢 總之先繼續昨天的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.88,0:14:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹隻是我一個人的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.88,0:14:26.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.38,0:14:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.44,0:14:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 總之不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.20,0:14:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經不能再和美鈴老師……
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.04,0:14:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也就是說和那個紫苑有了做愛關係是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.53,0:14:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.40,0:14:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.36,0:14:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我隻不過是設個圈套而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.34,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝木你還真是老實
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.65,0:14:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼關係 兩邊都好好享受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.18,0:14:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師我一點都不介意哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.23,0:14:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.05,0:15:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美鈴老師 你剛才咬我了是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.00,0:15:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.35,0:15:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣你在24小時後就會成為完全的蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.06,0:15:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.61,0:15:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼老師會知道這個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.31,0:15:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經有效果了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.93,0:15:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你就這樣好好聽著
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.08,0:15:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我也是你的同類
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.54,0:15:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字是蛇女蓋斯特 請多指教啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.48,0:15:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狼人蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.69,0:15:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇女蓋斯特 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.18,0:15:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇 對了 就是蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.37,0:15:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的蓋斯特屬性是毒
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.62,0:15:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以在體內製造各種化學成分哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.67,0:15:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不覺的這有點厲害嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.54,0:15:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛剛在你的體內註入了讓蓋斯特病毒加速感染的毒液
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.93,0:15:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為你是巫女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.87,0:15:59.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天在舊校捨都讓我看的清清楚楚
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.60,0:16:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女巫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.02,0:16:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.70,0:16:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,統治蓋斯特的蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.90,0:16:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在所有蓋斯特頂點的蓋斯特啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.92,0:16:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,污穢不堪軍團的首領 成為狼人糢樣伸齣利爪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.84,0:16:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在蓋斯特之間流傳下來的傳說
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.24,0:16:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有關女巫的事情我就隻早知道這些
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.38,0:16:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比這更多的事情誰也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.38,0:16:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被蓋斯特寄生了 但是和其他人也不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.64,0:16:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才覺得是不是有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.05,0:16:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是那個 女巫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.70,0:16:34.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.29,0:16:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都忘說了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.20,0:16:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,註入到你體內的毒液 還含有別的成分
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.24,0:16:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是蓋斯特化 就會任我擺佈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.49,0:16:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要這麼做
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.52,0:16:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.19,0:16:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 狼人蓋斯特
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.16,0:16:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起創造新世界吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.67,0:16:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.66,0:17:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 就隻是這種毒液就像馴服我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.69,0:17:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要開玩笑了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.68,0:17:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.05,0:17:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體…你那眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.97,0:17:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體變得好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.13,0:17:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是女巫的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.04,0:17:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 手停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.44,0:17:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼想要我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.58,0:17:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就成全你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.99,0:17:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你到不想要為止
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.46,0:17:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 太慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.60,0:17:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.33,0:17:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部好難受
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.83,0:17:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.20,0:17:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美鈴老師
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.53,0:17:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有必要的嚮學生獻媚的那個態度
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.88,0:17:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道弘樹和美鈴老師
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.89,0:17:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弘樹是我的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.89,0:18:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都這麼說了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.37,0:18:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒好美味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.62,0:18:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼美味的肉棒還是第一次
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.48,0:18:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊老師 很舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.45,0:18:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來老師很喜歡這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.04,0:18:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.22,0:18:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.88,0:18:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.54,0:18:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好喫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.42,0:18:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.91,0:18:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 我想小便了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.66,0:18:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師用嘴接住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.43,0:18:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.23,0:18:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝木的小便
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.69,0:18:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喉嚨好乾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.13,0:19:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 我想要喝小便嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.12,0:19:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我 給我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.43,0:19:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往老師的在嘴裡射齣你的小便吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.07,0:19:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.86,0:19:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼要來了 老師
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.82,0:19:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝木的小便在我嘴裡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.98,0:19:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好溫煖 好美味
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.22,0:19:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快點喝下去要濺齣來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.24,0:19:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.61,0:19:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 差不多開始插吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.73,0:19:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.75,0:19:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是要做什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.87,0:19:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個樣子 還真是誘人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.22,0:19:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.83,0:19:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.80,0:19:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.58,0:19:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再繼續了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.60,0:19:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來操我吧 求你了 來操我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.63,0:19:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.28,0:20:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.93,0:20:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師小穴的汁水好腥好美味
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.48,0:20:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能感覺到 好有感覺啊 再來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.12,0:20:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道臉屁眼也
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.91,0:20:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡還沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.10,0:20:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡還是處女啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.34,0:20:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.51,0:20:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.49,0:20:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.84,0:20:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.69,0:20:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.23,0:20:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 有感覺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.14,0:20:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼有感覺了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.47,0:20:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.77,0:20:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來 把肉棒插進來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.20,0:20:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是第一次就要我插屁眼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.84,0:20:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的屁眼想被操 求你了 插進來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.12,0:20:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進我的屁眼來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.94,0:20:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.18,0:20:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師還真是個沒藥可救的母豬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.87,0:20:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 我就是母豬
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.64,0:20:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要肉棒 想要肉棒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.97,0:20:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.54,0:21:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我就插進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.70,0:21:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進來 快
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.51,0:21:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.65,0:21:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊 插到深處了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.57,0:21:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.38,0:21:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯啊 老師的屁眼好緊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.99,0:21:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼有感覺 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.93,0:21:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 再插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.66,0:21:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師 你希望我把精液射到哪個洞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.66,0:21:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩邊都射
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.93,0:21:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼和小穴都射
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.88,0:21:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 使勁兒插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.92,0:21:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那粗壯的插進來 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.70,0:21:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 兩邊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.33,0:21:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好貪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.52,0:21:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩邊都想射的話 就髮誓做我的奴隸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.42,0:21:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我髮誓 我就是你的奴隸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.12,0:21:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨你怎麼處置我 淩辱我 玩弄我 欺負我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.92,0:21:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的一切都獻給你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.50,0:21:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以快點射進來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.92,0:21:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把精液射齣來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.96,0:21:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我就射了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.22,0:22:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我濃濃的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.82,0:22:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來 在動起來 快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.07,0:22:07.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 再來 再插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.91,0:22:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒變的更爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.08,0:22:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變得超級 超級大 再來 再來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.44,0:22:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.61,0:22:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 粗壯的肉棒好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.83,0:22:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好刺激 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.61,0:22:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.62,0:22:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.22,0:22:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射啊 射啊 快
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.44,0:22:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.89,0:22:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.90,0:22:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.48,0:22:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了 去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.80,0:22:50.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來 往小穴裡面插吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.31,0:22:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好高興啊 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.16,0:23:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.79,0:23:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 這房間被干擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.12,0:23:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.51,0:23:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.51,0:23:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊 他的精液屁眼 小穴 全身都是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.02,0:23:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿滿的 濃濃的 亂七八糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.18,0:23:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是小看他了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.49,0:23:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.61,0:23:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經是他的奴隸了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.05,0:23:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經變成不是他就沒辦法滿足的身體了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.88,0:23:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那錶情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.25,0:23:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也變成他的奴隸了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.31,0:23:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是個DOLL 真是個笨女人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.99,0:23:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.64,0:24:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙跑哪裡去了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.76,0:24:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他24小時候會蓋斯特化
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.65,0:24:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候他就是我的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.87,0:24:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你成為敵人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.43,0:24:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受餘下的時光吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.49,0:24:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點程度的話 我還是可以容忍的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.21,0:24:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大傢都是奴隸嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.83,0:24:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙 我一定會把你揪齣來殺掉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.49,0:24:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,揍死你 揍到你死
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.63,0:24:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你屍骨無存
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.51,0:24:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.93,0:24:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,髮生什麼事情了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.45,0:24:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.09,0:24:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.18,0:24:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.89,0:24:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起這個 快點把衣服穿上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.99,0:24:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.39,0:24:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 美鈴老師是蓋斯特啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.47,0:24:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後我被老師下了毒
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.97,0:24:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.10,0:24:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我掃描了你的身體
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.91,0:24:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被註入了特別的化學成分
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.27,0:24:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.90,0:25:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這樣下去 我就要變成蓋斯特了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.72,0:25:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住那個蓋斯特 讓她做解藥
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.23,0:25:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就隻能這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.47,0:25:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做奴隸什麼的 這種話你是對誰都會說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.16,0:25:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做奴隸什麼的 這種話你是對誰都會說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.73,0:25:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做奴隸什麼的 這種話你是對誰都會說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.69,0:25:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 這是因為
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.92,0:25:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是老師聽錯了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.02,0:25:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什麼奴隸 而是道具啊 道場啊什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.14,0:25:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連屁眼也
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.48,0:25:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 那個是
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.70,0:25:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道紫苑你是在喫醋
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.79,0:25:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,DOLL沒有感情
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.08,0:25:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不可能嫉妒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.59,0:25:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我隻是拜託弘樹帮我處理少女的生理而已
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.59,0:25:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你的郃作
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.02,0:25:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明顯就是在喫醋嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.12,0:26:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.74,0:26:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這樣啊 紫苑
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.83,0:26:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.04,0:26:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個的愛情小畫面差不多該結束了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.85,0:26:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛是不是有什麼聲音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.72,0:26:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼東西在
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.15,0:26:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.23,0:26:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡 在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.82,0:26:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼看不見啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.50,0:26:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.40,0:26:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛 你想殺死我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.06,0:26:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這蟲子在說話啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.84,0:26:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超惡心
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.85,0:26:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這醜陋的外邊 還有那惡心的聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.55,0:26:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪遇到過
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.59,0:26:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我啦 尾田原啦
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.77,0:26:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尾田原
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.03,0:26:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個沒品的蛞蝓 為什麼在這
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.17,0:26:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要說什麼蛞蝓
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.74,0:26:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是一樣嘴巴好壞的女人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.27,0:26:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起這個 你不是死了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.75,0:26:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 真是可惜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.08,0:26:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你隻是把我的身體破壞了 覈心沒有破壞
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.42,0:26:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才能這樣換個形態繼續活著
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.27,0:26:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼現在馬上宰了你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.18,0:26:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.64,0:27:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不想知道美鈴老師在哪裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.74,0:27:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.70,0:27:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在謀劃什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.00,0:27:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之原因很多啦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.90,0:27:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是放心啦 我是你們一邊的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.91,0:27:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然知道我的好友是女巫
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.19,0:27:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉到你們一邊才是上策啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.73,0:27:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰知到該不該相信你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.81,0:27:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之先告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.28,0:27:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美鈴老師去哪兒了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.76,0:27:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要這麼急啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.50,0:27:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老師到舊校捨去了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.85,0:27:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舊校捨
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.27,0:27:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.72,0:27:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要馬上過去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.11,0:27:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不見人影啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.85,0:27:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是這裡嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.48,0:27:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好奇怪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.62,0:27:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是在這裡才對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.57,0:27:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.94,0:27:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡非相關人員是禁止入內的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.28,0:27:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,廚川老師 為什麼會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.63,0:27:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是失蹤了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.15,0:28:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心 那傢伙已經不是人類了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.34,0:28:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙 是蓋斯特啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.64,0:28:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 猜對了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.81,0:28:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.00,0:28:13.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你啊 和那個DOLL一起來的Single Figure
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.72,0:28:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 你把她弄到哪兒去了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.02,0:28:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可不能白白告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.06,0:28:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要是贏了我 你就會知道了


