[Script Info]
Title: 未设定
Original Script: 未设定 
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB2C17,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,97,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.48,0:00:37.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是在旁边负责把风的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.69,0:02:42.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妈的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.30,0:02:54.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精液就好像从嘴巴里流出来一样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.83,0:04:05.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你都在迷这个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.38,0:04:13.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近念书念这么晚,也不过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.26,0:04:17.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你到底在做什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.66,0:04:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚松
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.37,0:04:27.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫这么大声啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.61,0:04:31.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会被骂哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.88,0:04:34.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.96,0:04:39.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我到处在找你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.32,0:04:43.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,骗你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.74,0:04:47.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天松
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.49,0:04:51.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可以叫这么大声哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.25,0:04:53.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可…可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.18,0:05:01.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,网络上的色情图片会比现实的还来的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.04,0:05:05.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:09.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天松…同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.82,0:05:21.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里变大了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.77,0:05:28.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,忍很久了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.84,0:06:55.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还可以射吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.50,0:07:02.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从后面来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.41,0:07:14.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方做会很兴奋吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.09,0:07:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以的,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.55,0:08:03.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,会高潮的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.70,0:08:25.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要这么粗鲁嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.42,0:08:46.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天松同学…我又要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.34,0:08:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天松同学的里面好紧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.60,0:09:13.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧,就这样射出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.75,0:10:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大丰收呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.20,0:10:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下自慰的题材可以撑一下子了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.78,0:10:52.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,差不多该叫冈田过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.99,0:11:03.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看那衣服好像要裂开一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.89,0:11:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你啊什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.05,0:11:21.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姬,怎么了啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.81,0:11:24.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知,这个人突然就冲出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.37,0:11:32.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎样啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.75,0:11:36.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小姬,不要再看了,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.76,0:11:38.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.05,0:11:40.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.84,0:11:43.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,装傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.46,0:12:15.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,(老地方)
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.54,0:12:33.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天是第几天了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.63,0:12:37.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.55,0:12:44.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你都没有自己弄吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.08,0:12:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实你每天晚上都在尻枪吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.02,0:12:55.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才…没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.60,0:13:08.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得自己做很可惜吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.61,0:13:17.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要射就射在我的里面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.57,0:13:20.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,少说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.50,0:13:25.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我啊,只要喝了男人的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.45,0:13:29.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算三天不吃饭也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.66,0:13:32.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.59,0:13:34.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很奇怪吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.26,0:13:39.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我可能不是人类吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.74,0:13:44.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对方应该还没来吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.03,0:13:46.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天没有人会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.65,0:13:56.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的嘴巴跟那里是与生俱来的淫荡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.67,0:14:02.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的身体是为了做爱而生的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.82,0:14:10.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.73,0:14:16.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.44,0:14:47.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都变这么大了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.52,0:14:53.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才说的一点说服力都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.46,0:14:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的舌头可是很舒服的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.02,0:16:01.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的口水很厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.29,0:16:03.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都起泡了,真不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.25,0:17:24.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.26,0:17:26.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.67,0:17:30.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用这边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.57,0:17:41.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.62,0:17:54.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有看到在动吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:58.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很像生物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.67,0:18:04.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冈田,看太久啰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.52,0:18:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.93,0:18:31.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爱液
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.73,0:18:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.02,0:18:59.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样啊,我的那里？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.24,0:19:31.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道冈田你那里的大小及形状
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.74,0:19:33.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我那里能感觉的出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.75,0:19:47.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.05,0:19:49.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好激烈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.40,0:19:56.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.79,0:20:10.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉棒在颤抖着…好像要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.21,0:20:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射在我的嘴巴里,射在舌头上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.32,0:20:46.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.56,0:20:52.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的精液跟血一样多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.39,0:20:58.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.76,0:21:13.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,女生有三个洞可以用来做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.59,0:21:17.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.45,0:21:23.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肉穴…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.13,0:21:27.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.15,0:21:30.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.66,0:21:35.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要来个完全打击吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.34,0:21:40.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用屁眼把你的精液吸出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.78,0:21:52.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看得很清楚吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.17,0:21:57.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,插进屁眼里了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.38,0:22:14.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？你是第一次搞屁眼吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.74,0:22:24.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射出来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.06,0:22:27.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧,就这样射在屁眼里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.82,0:22:57.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冈田在女孩子的屁眼里射得这么多…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.33,0:23:01.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真变态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.47,0:23:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦,不休息一下吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.93,0:23:15.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,屁眼…太厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.49,0:24:13.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冈田,要坏掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.41,0:24:17.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.64,0:24:20.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要…你要射了？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.16,0:24:23.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那可是女孩子的肉穴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.54,0:24:27.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要再动了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.98,0:24:30.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要射在里面吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.87,0:24:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,中出了…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.34,0:24:57.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.92,0:25:15.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等…不会吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.01,0:25:52.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来他是做到爽啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.77,0:26:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经结束了吧,冈田
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.37,0:26:16.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不是人类…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.07,0:26:20.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或者是…怪物
