[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-01-21 18:40:15
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 未设定
Original Script: 未设定
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB2C17,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,97,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.20,0:00:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾…雾岛同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.40,0:00:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要误会哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.89,0:00:45.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我觉得不舒服的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.24,0:00:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上会停下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.36,0:01:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说土屋,你不要靠这么近呼吸啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.09,0:01:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会痒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.63,0:01:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那样一直盯着看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.13,0:01:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾岛同学,都湿透了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.01,0:01:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋,快点舔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.40,0:01:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.28,0:02:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个胖子舌头竟然这么厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.31,0:02:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.99,0:02:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连里面也被舔了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.01,0:02:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾岛同学,我的也…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.14,0:02:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的,你最近胆子变得有点大哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.05,0:02:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了啦,我舔就是了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.28,0:03:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像比平常还要舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.90,0:03:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子好丢脸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.15,0:03:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了,身体已经停不下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.29,0:04:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土屋的肉棒…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.41,0:04:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然变得这么好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.89,0:04:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾…雾岛同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.94,0:04:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.37,0:04:23.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的,干嘛射出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.46,0:04:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家都还没去的说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.86,0:04:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.94,0:04:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我还可以继续
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.56,0:04:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就放进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.84,0:04:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.21,0:04:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就说放进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.33,0:04:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.96,0:04:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打扰你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.60,0:04:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能先停下来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.28,0:04:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然把我工作的地方弄成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.96,0:05:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅冈老师…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.61,0:05:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来得好好处罚一下了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.36,0:05:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.88,0:05:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.54,0:05:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是琴叶同学吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.28,0:05:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.64,0:05:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉特地把你叫出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.21,0:06:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.14,0:06:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.00,0:06:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…其实我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.78,0:06:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学你在保健室里面做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.73,0:06:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊,被看到啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.69,0:06:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没对老师跟其它人说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.83,0:06:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…那个…这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.40,0:07:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琴叶同学,你最近有做过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.48,0:07:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得我和远藤同学的作爱怎么样啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.83,0:07:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.86,0:07:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.07,0:07:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.06,0:07:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.99,0:07:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶,告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.49,0:07:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是看到肉棒插进我那里后\N兴奋起来了啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.71,0:07:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没那回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.81,0:07:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有点心跳加速而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.42,0:07:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只有心跳加速吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.94,0:08:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行,不要玩弄那里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.45,0:08:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着我们作爱\N有玩弄胸部和自慰吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.69,0:08:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没那么做
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.59,0:08:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会做那么下流的事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.67,0:08:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我已经注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.82,0:08:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看着我跟远藤作爱在自慰着
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.37,0:08:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.84,0:08:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能被其它人看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.81,0:09:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害,潮吹了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.30,0:09:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫远藤带朋友过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.31,0:09:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.36,0:09:24.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.21,0:09:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.56,0:09:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就远藤同学你一个？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.35,0:09:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉,这个时间找不到人来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.18,0:09:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.96,0:09:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.79,0:09:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.17,0:09:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说好是…咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.06,0:10:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你戴上这个把眼睛遮住
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.23,0:10:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暖暖的对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.48,0:10:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤我要舔啰
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.66,0:11:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓,我快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.02,0:11:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.03,0:11:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能靠墙壁站吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.98,0:11:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.40,0:11:45.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯,等一下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.39,0:11:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天这些都是我为你做的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.55,0:11:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的要在这里做吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.90,0:11:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘,先做看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.45,0:12:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤,舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.20,0:12:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被三仓的舌头包覆着,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.56,0:12:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤的好浓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.14,0:12:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌头弄得太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.34,0:13:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还可以射吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.65,0:13:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤,就这样从后面来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.69,0:13:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也湿透了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.05,0:13:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓,里面好惊人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.26,0:13:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.74,0:14:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害,插得好深
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.43,0:14:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了…要高潮了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.59,0:14:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.94,0:15:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓,你这样舔的话又会射出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.33,0:15:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我也想做呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.93,0:15:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就这样来我家做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.82,0:16:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师,人家想回去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.40,0:16:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行,好不容易到了我的自由时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.32,0:16:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说你们这样是第几次了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.09,0:16:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.09,0:16:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先趴下屁股朝向我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.77,0:16:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.97,0:16:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师,你到底想做什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.83,0:16:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于上课途中跑到保健是作爱的坏孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.29,0:16:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好的处罚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.62,0:16:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀你们看过啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.31,0:16:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是富重老师做的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.79,0:16:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要,如果喝下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.60,0:16:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又会变得欲望高涨的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.13,0:16:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能喝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.23,0:17:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没有拒绝的权利哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.41,0:17:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快喝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.65,0:17:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土屋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.40,0:17:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变更夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.88,0:17:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想当他的对手的话\N劝你还是喝下去比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.91,0:17:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真色啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.33,0:18:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个比之前的还要…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.76,0:18:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍为改良了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.93,0:18:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有效对吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.78,0:18:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要这样轻轻弄一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.30,0:18:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会射精呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.93,0:18:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了…我也要高潮了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.08,0:18:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个还不要这么早就结束嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.97,0:19:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看来担心是多余的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.27,0:19:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾岛同学,让土屋同学看看\N你那淫乱的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.82,0:19:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土屋,看到了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.99,0:19:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.00,0:19:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不让他插的话\N事情会变得更严重哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.90,0:19:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害,热热的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.00,0:19:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土屋热热的肉棒在我的里面…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.78,0:20:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一进来就射了…笨蛋土屋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.28,0:20:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.74,0:20:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.83,0:20:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在里面射了好多热热的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.68,0:20:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我竟然这么有感觉…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.57,0:21:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能真的是变态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.06,0:21:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好深…要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.62,0:22:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,土屋你这下子…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.49,0:22:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你胆子还挺大的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.29,0:22:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.44,0:22:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.58,0:22:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浅冈老师呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.72,0:22:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是,可能觉得无聊就先回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.77,0:22:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是什么时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.36,0:22:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.78,0:22:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.88,0:22:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.38,0:24:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用胸部吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.01,0:24:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.43,0:24:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很想用我的胸部夹到射精对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.45,0:24:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用忍放轻松吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.19,0:24:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样射出来也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.26,0:24:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
