[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2013-01-21 18:35:15
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: 未设定
Original Script: 未设定
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:704
PlayResY:396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB2C17,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,97,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.46,0:00:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说智久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.86,0:00:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀 远藤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.86,0:00:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐也在这里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.66,0:00:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐好可爱的说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.86,0:00:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛叫他瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.26,0:00:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗同学是归国子女吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.66,0:00:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正看起来像学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.86,0:00:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你干嘛蒙住我的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.66,0:00:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐的旁边有我的三仓同学在那
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.66,0:00:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会让你瞄到三仓同学的内裤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.26,0:00:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看 放开手 你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.66,0:00:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行就是不行 给我老实点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.66,0:01:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.46,0:01:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.06,0:01:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信的事发生了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.86,0:01:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐 为 为什么会给我这个
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.26,0:01:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 那里在做什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.46,0:01:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 那 那个 老师
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.86,0:01:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么溜出来到这里的了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.86,0:01:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 说我要上厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.66,0:02:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真老实 这点很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.46,0:02:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初吻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.06,0:02:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.86,0:02:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错嘛 只是接吻就勃起了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.26,0:02:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真下流了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.46,0:02:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久君 帮你口淫怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.86,0:02:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没让女孩子用嘴含过老二吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.66,0:02:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你射到我的嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.66,0:02:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.66,0:03:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还特地拿了本很棒的色情刊物来的说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.86,0:03:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在厕所里干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.66,0:03:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.66,0:03:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好有精神啊 随时准备爆发一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.26,0:03:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漏液也这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.06,0:03:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等哦 先用唾液来湿润你的老二
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.26,0:03:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 老二已经变得很润滑了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.66,0:03:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.46,0:04:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.66,0:04:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久君你看 我的菊门和私处你想要哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.86,0:04:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要玩哪 都可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.46,0:04:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.46,0:04:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射 射了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.26,0:05:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 好像还没有沾到制服上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.46,0:05:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾到制服上可不行哦 会有污渍的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.86,0:05:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 是我忍不住
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.26,0:05:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次可要射到嘴里哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.46,0:05:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以全部帮你喝下去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.46,0:05:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射得好多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.06,0:05:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想让我喝下那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.66,0:05:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.06,0:05:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.46,0:05:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分都结成块了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.86,0:05:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你平坦没有经常自慰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.86,0:05:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.86,0:06:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我脸上沾的精液抹干净
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.86,0:06:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.46,0:06:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很温柔 我帮你舔干净
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.66,0:06:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得比刚才还要大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.06,0:06:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次用粗大的老二使劲捅进我的喉咙里来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.86,0:06:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捅进去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.06,0:06:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.46,0:06:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住我的头尽情的摆动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.86,0:06:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的口当成是私处就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.26,0:06:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.26,0:07:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久九你看 胸部和私处可以随便你用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.86,0:07:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.26,0:07:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很舒服不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.86,0:07:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 进里面来 智久君
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.86,0:07:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.06,0:07:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喉咙里搅动着粘液 不断的摩擦着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.26,0:07:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.46,0:07:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你难受吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.46,0:07:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很难受 但这样很好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.26,0:07:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顶到喉咙里的感觉让我有受不了的快感
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.06,0:07:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得直立起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.26,0:08:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又想射了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.46,0:08:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久君 再伸到我的喉咙里来 前后运动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.86,0:08:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐的嘴里滑滑地不停搅动
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.06,0:08:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经到忍耐的界限了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.86,0:08:46.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射出来 尽情的射到我的嘴里来 顶到里面喷出来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.86,0:08:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 射出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.86,0:09:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.26,0:09:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉得到在嘴里的脉动
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.46,0:09:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沾到裙子上了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.26,0:09:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说不要射到衣服上的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.66,0:09:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.66,0:09:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是拿你没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.46,0:09:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗穗真是不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.26,0:10:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫她穗穗 在她面前显得很没礼貌的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.06,0:10:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 等很久了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.86,0:10:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了吗 一声不吭的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.26,0:10:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天出什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.26,0:10:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 有型吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.26,0:10:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呀 回家照照镜子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.06,0:10:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天我和瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.06,0:10:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山田 到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.46,0:10:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山本 到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.26,0:10:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉田 到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.66,0:10:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡 到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.66,0:10:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤和三仓逃课吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.26,0:10:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找一下他们两个 大家先自习
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.46,0:11:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤和三仓同学怎么凑一起逃课
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.06,0:11:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.26,0:11:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思了 远藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.46,0:11:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要你陪我一起逃课
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.46,0:11:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会不高兴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.46,0:11:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能会不高兴了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.26,0:11:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和三仓同学做爱这样事 我对好友智久都没有提
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.66,0:11:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近 我满脑子都在想着三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.06,0:11:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又是班里数一数二的美人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.86,0:11:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.06,0:11:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.66,0:11:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.66,0:11:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么要我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.86,0:11:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我有型的人很多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.06,0:11:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 但是我对外表不怎么在乎的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.66,0:11:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那什么人才合适了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.46,0:12:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.26,0:12:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 三仓 远藤
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.86,0:12:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两人不会是在做什么见不得人的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.66,0:12:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没有做过
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.86,0:12:18.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老帅 和我做爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.26,0:12:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和三仓到底是什么样的感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.06,0:12:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么年轻 应该有把手指头夹得紧紧的感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.06,0:12:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的体内被玩弄着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.26,0:12:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.86,0:12:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这样子扣动
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.26,0:12:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去 去了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.46,0:13:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.86,0:13:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 这回轮到远藤了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.86,0:13:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓  要我这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.26,0:13:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.06,0:13:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 怎样 嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.86,0:13:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那里感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.86,0:13:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学真是真棒啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.06,0:13:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不仅够润滑里面的肉还在动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.46,0:14:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞进去的感觉真是太美妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.86,0:14:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎么塞的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.46,0:14:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.26,0:14:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发出淫荡的声音
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.06,0:14:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩擦到最里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.66,0:14:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里感觉也好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.26,0:14:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一进一出的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.66,0:14:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.26,0:14:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 要射到里面来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.26,0:14:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要远藤君的精液射到子宫里面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.06,0:15:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤在干什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.46,0:15:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是和三仓同学在一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.06,0:15:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想和瑞穗学姐做到最后啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.86,0:15:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办才好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.06,0:15:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的淫水和远藤君的精液
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.66,0:15:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好暖和啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.86,0:15:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看远藤君射精时的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.86,0:15:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤君的精液好像可以射得很远
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.06,0:15:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才感觉到刺到子宫最里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.06,0:15:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射精的瞬间一定很壮观吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.06,0:15:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人都不在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.46,0:16:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗 远藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.46,0:16:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.46,0:16:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老帅 快进来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.86,0:16:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.46,0:16:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.06,0:16:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快射 快射出来 喷出来让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.06,0:16:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会从上面来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.06,0:16:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喷得好厉害了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.66,0:16:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次来量量看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.26,0:16:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗你的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.26,0:17:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 刚才那些精液漏出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.46,0:17:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.06,0:17:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 里面的精液被搅动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.06,0:17:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要出来了 三仓同学
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.06,0:17:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再射到里面去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.46,0:17:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我里面已经装不下了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.46,0:17:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.86,0:17:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多也要准备回去上课了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.06,0:17:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.26,0:18:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上回教室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.06,0:18:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远藤君
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.26,0:18:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.66,0:18:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上在家不要一个人做哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.06,0:18:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在我的体内全部射出来哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.86,0:18:17.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.86,0:18:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先回教室了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.66,0:18:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.66,0:18:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这件事威胁她
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.26,0:18:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能也可以做
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.26,0:18:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能做几次都行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.86,0:18:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老帅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.06,0:18:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.06,0:18:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 这件事 这件事要是对谁
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.06,0:18:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老帅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.26,0:18:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对谁 对谁说
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.66,0:18:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是对谁提起就有你好看的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.46,0:18:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗 老帅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.86,0:18:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.06,0:19:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊 智久
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.66,0:19:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要闷心里还不如说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.86,0:19:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都和三仓同学做过了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.06,0:19:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.06,0:19:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许会有出人意料的结果哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.06,0:19:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天 有什么事吗 智久君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.66,0:19:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 那个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.66,0:19:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有想着我的口淫自慰吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.86,0:19:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.26,0:20:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这样吸着 马上就要去了 瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.26,0:20:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.66,0:20:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要着急
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.66,0:20:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果到放学了能忍住不射精的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.86,0:20:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以和我做爱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.26,0:20:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一节的课间到视听教室来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.06,0:20:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 坐下来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.66,0:21:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接舔的话你会受不了的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.26,0:21:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.06,0:21:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.86,0:21:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以射的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.06,0:21:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐 要忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.66,0:21:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.66,0:21:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只摸一下就好像要跳出来似的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.06,0:21:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为代替 帮你吹这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.26,0:22:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍不住勃起了 得想想其它的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.66,0:22:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 出
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.26,0:22:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射出来哦 给我忍住
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.66,0:22:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.46,0:22:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再忍耐一会哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.06,0:22:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等放学后 衣服下面的全部可以任你享用
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.66,0:23:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 结束了 终于等到结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.06,0:23:06.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.86,0:23:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不用忍耐了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.86,0:23:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请尽情到我里面去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.66,0:23:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进去了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.26,0:23:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看智久君的老二正在被我淫荡的私处吞下去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.86,0:23:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好了吗 全部进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.46,0:23:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就射出来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.46,0:23:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.86,0:23:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 精液喷射到子宫里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.26,0:23:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.86,0:23:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彻脑海 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.06,0:23:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 射精停不下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.66,0:24:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.06,0:25:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.66,0:25:14.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只忍了半天就有那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.66,0:25:17.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果忍一个星期
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.66,0:25:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次隔一星期再一起做爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.26,0:25:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗 智久君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
