[Script Info]
Title:
Original Script:
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX: 704
PlayResY: 396
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00BB2C17,&HF0000000,0,0,0,0,97,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,15,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.72,0:00:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.66,0:00:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.08,0:00:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.75,0:00:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.24,0:00:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了 瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.16,0:00:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在洗澡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.01,0:00:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.80,0:00:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先躲起来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.84,0:00:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.69,0:00:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先潜下去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.59,0:00:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.71,0:01:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了来了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.79,0:01:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.03,0:01:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.52,0:01:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.36,0:01:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等下就去做饭 再等一等
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.51,0:01:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.54,0:01:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之后会变成什么样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.31,0:01:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 那就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.55,0:01:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋久君？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.46,0:01:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等下回来 再忍一会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.02,0:02:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸久等了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.65,0:02:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了松茸拉面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.96,0:02:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是久等了哦 松茸拉面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.08,0:02:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 做的真不错 极品啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.11,0:02:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开动了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.15,0:02:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我洗澡洗到一半 再去擦一擦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.86,0:02:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋久君没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.48,0:02:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋久君？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.43,0:02:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 憋久了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.98,0:02:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来帮你擦擦身 出来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.41,0:03:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转过来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.70,0:03:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想继续刚才的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.44,0:03:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.49,0:03:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久没来深插了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.92,0:03:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.88,0:03:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气啦 来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.36,0:03:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一口气插进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.73,0:04:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 嘴巴里面真舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.97,0:04:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.89,0:05:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 前辈不难受吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.26,0:05:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在喉咙里蹭啊蹭的 很爽的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.54,0:05:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再插的更深点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.93,0:05:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的嘴巴里湿湿的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.95,0:06:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍不住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.21,0:06:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.16,0:06:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,射到喉咙最深处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.06,0:06:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.76,0:06:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽吧 朋久君
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.51,0:06:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一炮？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.02,0:07:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗 我吃完拉面也一起来洗澡咯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.23,0:07:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.11,0:07:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起？朋久君 做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.84,0:07:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.54,0:07:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.79,0:07:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经洗好了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.98,0:07:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸你一个人慢慢洗吧 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.48,0:07:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想来帮瑞穗你擦擦背的说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.53,0:07:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次嘛 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.60,0:07:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.62,0:07:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样子 不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.22,0:07:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 总比裸体在外面乱跑要好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.57,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么跑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.42,0:07:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里出的去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.29,0:07:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点窄
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.17,0:07:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.38,0:08:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那么 我就努力插到窄的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.96,0:08:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋久你？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.38,0:08:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.24,0:08:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.71,0:08:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.20,0:08:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在洗澡的时候弄湿的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.82,0:08:43.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我任你摆布哦 朋久
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.13,0:08:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.45,0:08:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.53,0:08:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.37,0:09:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别叫的太响了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.23,0:09:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 你太激烈了 好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.31,0:09:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面 都插到里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.27,0:09:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 好紧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.02,0:09:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.64,0:09:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的里面变得热起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.88,0:09:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在里面射了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.36,0:09:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 要去了 我也要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.58,0:10:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋久君 我好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.27,0:10:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 瑞穗 怎么了 刚才是什么声音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.00,0:10:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.50,0:11:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 讨厌 别偷看女生上厕所
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.50,0:11:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把门关了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.94,0:11:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.41,0:12:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.20,0:12:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢神田？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.46,0:12:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这样的传言啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.73,0:12:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警官啊 其实
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.25,0:12:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快拿猪排饭来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.88,0:12:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了就搞不好想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.39,0:13:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在放送室的话 再怎么叫也没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.95,0:13:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插我 往更深的地方插吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.37,0:13:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好玩弄我的那里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.81,0:13:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 宫泽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.22,0:13:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那些人的错 连我都变得不幸了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.44,0:13:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.36,0:13:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽的那里 好热 像要被吸进去一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.75,0:13:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看的到吗 我插宫泽你那的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.90,0:14:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 看的到 小野君的棒棒 好热 进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.82,0:14:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,硬硬的棒子插进我淫乱的那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.89,0:14:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子里好舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.37,0:14:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.71,0:14:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想做爱而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.00,0:14:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经厌烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.40,0:14:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要装作很有感觉的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.34,0:14:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会被骗到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.98,0:14:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 我已经
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.26,0:14:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射在里面 全射到嘴巴里来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.23,0:15:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉射到脸上了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.59,0:15:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代替我被抓起来？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.82,0:15:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.62,0:15:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何 还是难以相信眼前的这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.08,0:16:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.10,0:16:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.61,0:16:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 小姬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.47,0:16:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 亚美
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.92,0:16:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 要停一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.17,0:16:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 继续吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.11,0:16:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.93,0:17:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来了 棒棒进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.04,0:17:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热 好热
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.43,0:17:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 宫泽 宫泽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.95,0:17:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和宫泽在交往？真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.24,0:17:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是她 她的洞洞很能吸 让人欲罢不能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.03,0:17:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,软软的 一下下就插不停了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.96,0:17:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里 好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.83,0:17:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我变得淫荡起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.57,0:17:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 叫得那么大声的话会被发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.17,0:18:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道为什么 变得好兴奋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.52,0:18:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是变态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.63,0:18:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子里好痒 我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.28,0:18:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽 好热 就像在烧一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.40,0:18:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面的棒棒 好热 好硬
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.34,0:18:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒棒 顶到里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.55,0:18:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.32,0:18:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能射在里面 射到外面 射到外面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.74,0:19:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要去了 要去了 要去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.43,0:19:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 射了那么多 衣服都黏死了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.02,0:19:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.47,0:19:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 我没生气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.91,0:19:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.05,0:19:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被神田君每天都当做玩具一样的玩弄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.87,0:19:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.63,0:19:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经遭到天谴了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.50,0:19:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽你没有错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.79,0:20:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该回教室了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.41,0:20:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.37,0:20:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下个休息时间我还在这等你来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.58,0:20:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就这样了 奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.18,0:20:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.22,0:20:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.42,0:20:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.90,0:20:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菊花和胸部也可以哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.99,0:20:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都任你玩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.23,0:20:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的精液都射到我里面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.48,0:20:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宫泽
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.41,0:20:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君 你有在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.35,0:20:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你在想着H的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.94,0:20:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小亚美 小野很H的你要小心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.89,0:21:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小色狼一边看着我一边想着什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.40,0:21:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.89,0:21:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂...喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.81,0:21:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦 大家都回教室里了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.14,0:21:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为被某人把衣服弄湿了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.65,0:21:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在什么都没穿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.65,0:21:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要回教室？ 还是
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.45,0:22:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君 放学后我等着你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.98,0:22:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.83,0:22:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姬
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.23,0:22:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚美 社团活动不去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.87,0:22:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社团活动？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.19,0:22:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,参加这种东西能干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.87,0:23:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后我等着你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.02,0:23:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以射好多哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.60,0:23:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  听我说嘛 小姬
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.30,0:23:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君他说他会代我被抓的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.93,0:23:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君说他想和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.39,0:23:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还说喜欢我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.38,0:23:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢的也就是我的身体吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.44,0:23:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换句话说也就是想H罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.50,0:23:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.03,0:24:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小野君 我一直在等你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.97,0:24:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.29,0:24:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那个 等一下 听不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.33,0:24:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小野君
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.52,0:24:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.43,0:24:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.62,0:24:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想变成宫泽说的那么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.08,0:24:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思 别把我和那种家伙相提并论
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.37,0:24:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 开门 刚才的广播是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.96,0:24:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给我开门
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.57,0:25:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姬
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.67,0:25:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打不开 可恶 门坏了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.27,0:25:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姬 你背叛了我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.25,0:25:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 为什么 我们不是好朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.93,0:25:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像乌鸦一样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.48,0:25:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.19,0:25:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一身黑 只是呱呱的叫着
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.34,0:25:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.56,0:25:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚美 一起去自首吧 有我在你的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.41,0:25:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姬

