[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00800080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.57,0:00:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.15,0:00:19.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡的解法 我有點不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.28,0:00:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個 首先要做因式分解才行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.03,0:00:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉 學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.61,0:00:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還要妳放學以後特地留下來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.32,0:00:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要緊 我最擅長教別人了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.49,0:00:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣會很糟糕的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.20,0:00:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 高年級的教室 氣氛就是不一樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.70,0:00:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.61,0:01:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗學姊的座位是在那邊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.99,0:01:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.49,0:01:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.57,0:01:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.03,0:01:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.86,0:01:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的...要...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.61,0:01:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.70,0:02:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是瑞穗學姊給我的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.86,0:02:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邀我前往她家的請帖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.24,0:03:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪 她平時不是都坐這班電車
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.40,0:03:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶子不小心拉斷了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.11,0:03:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這...這傢伙 從剛才就...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.36,0:03:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.49,0:03:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早...早...早安
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.99,0:03:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒想到會以這副樣子和她說話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.03,0:03:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即將到達放送橫町 放送橫町
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.86,0:04:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總算空曠了點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.70,0:04:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.40,0:04:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.45,0:04:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是站在女人旁邊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.74,0:04:27.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總覺得 他一臉的色相
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.65,0:04:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.86,0:04:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一直都有注意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.28,0:04:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.82,0:04:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.36,0:04:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.45,0:04:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一個站 會有兩個男人一起上車
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.45,0:04:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 一個像馬鈴薯一樣的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.82,0:04:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有一個有稜有角的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.57,0:05:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.24,0:05:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪個人會先上車 我們來猜猜看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.57,0:05:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯...嗯 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.32,0:05:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得是有稜有角那位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.20,0:05:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就猜馬鈴薯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.57,0:05:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.82,0:05:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.24,0:05:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.86,0:05:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 我贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.65,0:05:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.45,0:05:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.78,0:05:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.45,0:05:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰利品哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.45,0:05:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勃起到一半了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.99,0:06:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毛衣的感覺很棒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.74,0:06:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厚的皮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.32,0:06:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然變這麼熱了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.07,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 已經這麼濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.36,0:07:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係 射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.82,0:07:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清潔人員可要辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.53,0:07:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼再來賭一把怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.24,0:07:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你贏的話 我...就任你享用哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.20,0:07:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次讓你在我裡面摩擦到射出來為止
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.28,0:07:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.86,0:07:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一個站 那位女大學生會下鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.90,0:08:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才那兩個站在她前面的\N一定會有一個坐下去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.24,0:08:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.15,0:08:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.24,0:08:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就...有稜有角那個
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.15,0:08:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.95,0:08:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然跟著走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.95,0:08:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子的這裡 有那麼罕見嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.49,0:08:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.15,0:09:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要先做熱身運動才行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.99,0:09:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的...很濃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.82,0:09:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣可能會懷孕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.74,0:09:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 不要拖得太久
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.11,0:09:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明我還沒動
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.95,0:09:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面就已經開始蠢蠢欲動了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.24,0:09:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是動的話 會更舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.74,0:10:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才剛射過一次 現在又這麼硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.53,0:10:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為...因為...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.99,0:10:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在...太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.40,0:10:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.15,0:10:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太舒服了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.49,0:10:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被你的小弟弟侵犯的日子 我一直在等待
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.28,0:10:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你 再來 再激烈點
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.03,0:10:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那裡 你可以肆意蹂躪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.40,0:11:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.74,0:11:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.61,0:11:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題 哪裡都可以 盡情射出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.24,0:11:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要把牆壁射穿了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.40,0:11:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直就像牛一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.28,0:11:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一站是辛抱町 辛抱町
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.07,0:11:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要下車了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.15,0:11:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.53,0:12:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來是最後一次
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.65,0:12:12.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我在這裡大叫的話\N人會從哪節車廂跑過來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.32,0:12:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說 哪邊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.99,0:12:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說吧 猜中的話 我就當作什麼事都沒發生
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.53,0:12:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳知道嗎\N今天早上在這班電車上抓住了一個癡漢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.61,0:12:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧 真的?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.03,0:12:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說啊 還只是個年輕人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.45,0:12:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噁...不過不太可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.36,0:12:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.65,0:13:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰叫你老是色眯眯地看著我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.40,0:13:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...好大的房子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.36,0:13:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真慢呢 我明明給你畫了地圖的說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.61,0:13:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是說這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.57,0:13:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種地圖...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.99,0:13:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別客氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.24,0:13:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進來吧 反正家裡沒人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.40,0:13:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你口渴了吧 可爾畢斯可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.78,0:14:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真懷念呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.61,0:14:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看快看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.90,0:14:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像精液呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.07,0:14:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這...這種話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.11,0:14:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來餵你喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.20,0:14:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...學姊?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.57,0:14:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和香水不一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.78,0:14:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子特有的甜美氣息
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.32,0:14:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近只要一聞到學姊的香味
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.07,0:14:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體就不聽使喚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.45,0:14:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是條件反射嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.32,0:14:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情 要是被爸爸發現的話就糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.40,0:15:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.11,0:15:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會被殺了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.70,0:15:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.03,0:15:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦 以前來的男生\N進了玄關後才兩秒...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.07,0:15:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就被爸爸拖進他的房間
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.78,0:15:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.99,0:15:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.11,0:15:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.57,0:15:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要加嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.90,0:15:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我已經飽了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.61,0:15:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.45,0:15:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是從這裡注入哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.57,0:15:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.36,0:15:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 真是按時起床的乖孩子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.82,0:15:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說 一直都挺著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.07,0:15:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.57,0:16:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.90,0:16:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好...好柔軟...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.82,0:16:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓唾液流進裂縫裡去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.61,0:16:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學姊...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.32,0:16:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭 進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.70,0:17:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看 存了這麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.61,0:17:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底能存多少 很期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.28,0:17:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.36,0:17:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.82,0:17:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.28,0:17:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下應該會見血呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.65,0:17:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那麼不慌不忙 快救救我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.15,0:17:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊 過來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.57,0:17:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進去這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 妳在家裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.57,0:17:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.49,0:17:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了 給我弄點吃的來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋汁培根義大利麵好嗎\N(Carbonara)
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.90,0:17:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 麻煩妳了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.70,0:17:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智久君 現在還勃起著嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.86,0:17:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你留了一條縫隙哦\N讓你的小弟弟能伸出來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.40,0:17:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 這次我幫你含到喉嚨裡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.36,0:17:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想在嘴裡射精吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.65,0:18:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面的 義大利麵和...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.03,0:18:46.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舌頭...纏在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.45,0:19:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.11,0:19:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.45,0:19:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁我去送料理的時候\N你逃到二樓的房間去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.57,0:19:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Roger!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.74,0:19:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.49,0:19:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.61,0:19:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是貓
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.57,0:19:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會待在房間裡的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.45,0:19:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.61,0:19:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧 你還沒進來哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.70,0:20:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 我的那裡 已經濕淋淋了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.61,0:20:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學姊的...那裡...好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.65,0:20:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.95,0:20:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點痛 又有點舒服...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.86,0:20:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.99,0:20:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.86,0:20:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.86,0:20:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面不停地跳動
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.95,0:21:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學...學姊 再動的話就...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.78,0:21:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.45,0:21:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要...忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.65,0:21:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.45,0:22:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次從上面插進來
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.07,0:22:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.70,0:22:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.49,0:22:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.86,0:22:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部 射到嘴裡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.07,0:23:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.36,0:24:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 我還以為嘴巴也要懷孕了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.36,0:24:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看吧 你的量
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.53,0:24:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對...對不起 忍了很久...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.07,0:24:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞穗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.90,0:24:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.40,0:24:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳在吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.57,0:24:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 今天你先回去吧 下次再賠給你
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.03,0:24:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳叫我從哪裡逃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.07,0:24:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從窗戶能下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.03,0:24:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Carbonara很好吃哦\N從窗戶能下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.61,0:24:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Carbonara很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.40,0:24:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Carbonara很好吃哦\N來 鞋子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.78,0:24:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 鞋子
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.99,0:24:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來 這是你到車站的地圖
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.07,0:24:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳用了 什麼美味的培根嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.11,0:25:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.61,0:25:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是貓哦
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.03,0:25:07.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.95,0:25:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,學姊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.70,0:25:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳是怎麼看待我的呢


