I have...I have been blaming myself
for the whole mess...
He saw me like that... I am so ashamed!
Master!
No...Stop... please stop!
More, Move your hips, harder.
Bridget, how is it? You like that?
Bridget! I can't just watch you
suffer like this!
I don't deserve to leave with John!
"Vicious"
Episode 2
John!
Bridget! Why!
Bury her in the yard.
Excuse...me?
Hi! My name is Bridget and I am
going to start working with you today!
Hi John!!
How pretty!
Do you take care of this all by yourself?
How neat!
Come on! You can chop better than that!
You seem to like it like that!
Your pussy is flooding!
John! Are you done?
Please, would you say a prayer for Bridget?
Sure, of course!
Wa...Wait Angela!
Over here! Let's sit!
What?
Hurry!
Yes, what is it?
What's wrong? Aren't we lovers?
But...not after all that's happened today.
What are you doing?
Miss Angela.!
Look... I'm touching myself.
John.
Make me feel good.
Deeper...deeper!
Suck my nipples!
We'll be together forever.
You're the man I've been waiting for...
to take me away from my father!
Worthless woman!
Sleeping with Bridget!
Was it really an accident?
Bridget was not as broken
as the mistress....
John!
Yes!
Are you all right?
Y..Yes!
Go get me another piece of bread!
Yes, master.
She was suffering....
My father's a worthless scoundrel!
What did the master do to them?
Miss Angela!
I was in my room thinking
about you...couldn't wait!
It feels good.
It feels good!
John!
I have never been so happy in my life.
I love you, John.
Miss Angela!
How are your studies?
It's much more important to be with you,
rather than studying.
Angela, could I please ask you a question?
Go ahead?
It's about Bridget.
What about?
About Bridget and the master.
How long were you aware?
Aware of?
Well... uh...their relationship.
Relationship? You mean, like us?
Yes.
Want to know?
Okay. If you come here and do what I say,
I'll tell you.
Right...there!
Mother... before she died....
Father was forcing himself on her.
Please, stop!
Does it hurt? If it hurts,
here some medicine for the pain.
No!
Bridget liked it from the beginning!
Oh wait, I'm...coming!
Angela!
I'll visit your room tonight!
Lick my pussy more!
Oh...no! I'm...coming!
Wait! I'll get on top!
Oh.. I want... good...good!
I'm coming again!
John! Good night!
Father!
What are you doing?
I..I couldn't sleep, so I went for a walk.
In the rainstorm?
Just around the house.
It's not just today. The last few nights
you're sneaking around at night.
What are you doing? Answer me!
Don't touch me with your dirty hands!
What?!
You don't think I know?
You were sleeping with the maid!
You're a scoundrel!
My mother died because of you!
Shut up!
How dare you! You. my only daughter...
...show no appreciation or respect
for the finest upbringing I provide!
What! I hate you! I'll leave this place!
John is going to save me from you!
With John?! You haven't been...!
Master! Please stop!
John!
No more violence, please!
How dare you corrupt my daughter!
This is how you pay me back for rescuing
you from poverty five years ago!10
I am truly sorry, master! But!
Quiet!
Damn you!
Dead! He's dead!
Now it's just us.
I've taken care of the rest!
We'll live together, always!
I love you John!
She never know what love was.
She never received any,
so she never knew how to love anybody!
I was at fault...
I should have done something!
John and I will live in a beautiful,
white mansion.
He will look into my eyes
and tell me I'm his true love!
No one is going to get in our way!
I need to go rescue him!
Miss. It's time for dinner.
Yes.Our future together!
Nobody will get in our way!