[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub v2.1.2 RELEASE PREVIEW (SVN r1987, amz)
; http://www.aegisub.net
Title:(18禁アニメ) 淫笑う看護婦 THE ANIMATION counseling.1「Ｓ系眼鏡お姉様はお好き？」(DVD 704x396 WMV9)[CRC 029C]
Original Script:HKG..J99.. //歡迎訪問[HのSubs]:http://hsubs.kilu.de/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
Last Style Storage: Default
Video Aspect Ratio: 0
Video Zoom: 6
Video Position: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微軟正黑體,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H90DD8CC9,&H90DD8CC9,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,20,20,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.19,0:01:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雞雞的前端都滲出變態汁液了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.30,0:01:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.71,0:01:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會射的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.93,0:01:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雞雞光是硬梆梆地勃起還不足夠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.85,0:01:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然還想射出乳臭未乾的雞雞汁液
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.77,0:01:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個令人頭痛的變態小男孩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.35,0:01:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想射就射啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.52,0:01:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你是個把雞雞插到這小淫穴之後就一點都忍不住的變態
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也沒辦法…對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.92,0:02:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.38,0:02:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精液射進來啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.85,0:02:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕的小孩真不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.87,0:03:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 別…再弄了…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.09,0:03:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這小鬼真囉嗦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.09,0:03:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雞雞都硬成這樣還這麼囂張
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.64,0:03:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 有東西出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.60,0:03:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼色色的先發淫汁竟然這麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.77,0:03:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊…姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.15,0:03:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煩不煩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.73,0:04:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在醫院裡面要保持安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.99,0:04:07.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真臭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.08,0:04:10.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不把你這張囉嗦的小嘴封起來的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.00,0:04:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴上再怎麼不願意 你的小雞雞可是梆梆響哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.80,0:04:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是個舔著我那裡 雞雞就會勃起的變態小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.04,0:04:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣 能看得到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.00,0:04:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小鬼的變態勃起小雞雞要被姊姊吃掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.38,0:05:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 正在慢慢地被吞進去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把處男小鬼沒見過世面的雞雞吃掉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.76,0:05:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 姊姊快抽出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.64,0:05:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不斷膨脹的乳臭未乾小雞雞在我體內鬧騰著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.56,0:05:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快抽出去啊 我不要這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.61,0:05:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在已經太晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.11,0:05:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你童貞的雞雞已經被我淫蕩的○吃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.28,0:05:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美…咲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.29,0:05:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次想跟喜歡的女孩子做？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.50,0:05:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是可惜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.66,0:05:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處男第一次擠出來的汁液就由我全部美美地吞掉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.67,0:05:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好粗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.88,0:05:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又粗又硬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.34,0:05:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 別夾住啊 別動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.43,0:05:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.85,0:05:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要射啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.68,0:05:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啊啦 那麼快就要射精啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.10,0:05:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再給我忍一會
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.23,0:06:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經不行了 射啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.90,0:06:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你射了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.45,0:06:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我子宮的深處射精了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.24,0:06:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次做愛就中出
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.29,0:06:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是個變態雞雞小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.96,0:06:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起…對不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.61,0:06:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態護士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.36,0:06:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美和子…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.12,0:06:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫你檫了汗 連我自己也出汗了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.87,0:07:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好熱好熱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.97,0:07:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我汗水的味道怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.06,0:07:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能感受到性激素嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.14,0:07:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.69,0:07:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.94,0:07:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.40,0:07:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為姊姊給我看裸體了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.78,0:07:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 就是要歸咎於我咯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.36,0:07:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是壞孩子 要懲罰懲罰
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.32,0:07:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊…姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.41,0:07:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼來…每天…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.13,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算說不要 這樣子一點說服力都沒有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.26,0:07:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態小鬼光是看的話 是忍不住的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.43,0:07:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.31,0:08:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 都沾濕了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.57,0:08:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很襯你哦 變態小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.82,0:08:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態雞雞越來越大了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.86,0:08:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絲襪都快要被撐破了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.99,0:08:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可是我喜歡的內褲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.54,0:08:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別把你那臭臭的雞雞汁弄上去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.92,0:08:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很辛苦麼 變態小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.01,0:08:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭臭的先發淫汁又冒出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.05,0:08:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不行 要…要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.80,0:08:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…行…不能射在我的內褲裡面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.89,0:08:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態小鬼的雞雞和蛋蛋都很大呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.94,0:08:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內褲奇怪的地方都變形了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.24,0:08:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿著內褲 不能射出臭臭的精液哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.20,0:09:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊 變態小鬼的臭…精液噴了一褲子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.16,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來要懲罰多一點呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.84,0:09:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打攪了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.55,0:09:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美…美咲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.26,0:09:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄 我來探你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.60,0:09:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請稍等一下啊 很快就開簾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄 為了給你個驚喜 我沒事先打招呼就來了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.98,0:09:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.57,0:09:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請問現在是在檢查中嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.15,0:09:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打攪到的話 我很快回去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.66,0:09:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實也沒什麼哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.66,0:09:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的只是要取雄二的尿液罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.74,0:09:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.46,0:09:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尿…尿液…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.55,0:09:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不急 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.68,0:09:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 要快點好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.60,0:10:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.26,0:10:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.89,0:10:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 真想讓她看看變態雞雞尿尿的樣子再走呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.07,0:10:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可愛啊 我感覺年輕了十歲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.82,0:10:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情又要變有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.33,0:10:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.87,0:10:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然忘記把努力織的圍巾給他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.29,0:10:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是完全沒消退嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.67,0:10:35.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是因為那孩子走了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.17,0:10:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.59,0:10:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這絲襪都沾滿了臭臭的精液 我不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.44,0:10:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,積了那麼多變態汁 讓那孩子幫你發洩多好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.90,0:10:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.52,0:11:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄 不知道尿完沒有…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.02,0:11:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.22,0:12:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.23,0:12:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用奶子那樣弄的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.15,0:12:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣弄的話？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.73,0:13:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會…會射的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.24,0:13:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雞雞好熱 都快把奶子燒著了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.37,0:13:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 奶頭都嘎吱嘎吱地響
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.00,0:13:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶子漲得都快要爆裂了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.34,0:13:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我已經…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.05,0:13:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要…射啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.56,0:13:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態小鬼跟有偷窺癖好的變態女朋友很襯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.95,0:13:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去搞那個女的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.04,0:14:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雞雞都大成這樣子了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.67,0:14:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這變態雞雞男 會被美咲討厭的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.93,0:14:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.39,0:14:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這…這是怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.81,0:14:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲那裡的淫穢變態汁也涌出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.93,0:14:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.35,0:14:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄 別看
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.73,0:14:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄 你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.36,0:14:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是疼 是舒服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.24,0:14:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小雄可是喜歡被人這樣弄的變態啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.95,0:14:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小…小雄是 變態？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.70,0:14:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 美咲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.45,0:14:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為小雄是變態 所以得了雞雞變大的病
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.79,0:14:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去的話 不就連內褲也穿不了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.67,0:14:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲 來幫忙治好小雄的病吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.72,0:14:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.68,0:14:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在可愛的女朋友的裡面 就能把膿排出來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.64,0:14:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 小雄 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.81,0:15:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.78,0:15:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啊啦 現在就快出來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲 是治療變態雞雞的名醫呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.74,0:15:18.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要做這麼過分的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.87,0:15:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 小雄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.54,0:15:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.00,0:15:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面射精的話 就放了你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.88,0:15:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要 住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.93,0:15:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 在入口就射了嗎 變態小雄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.60,0:15:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼 好臭…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.77,0:15:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來變態小雄還沒滿足
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.24,0:15:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要好好中出才行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.16,0:15:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 都進去裡面咯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.66,0:16:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在裡面射出來吧 變態小雄
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.67,0:16:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好…好痛啊 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.46,0:16:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在美咲還帶有處女膜的小穴裡面 排出更多的膿哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.55,0:16:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.56,0:16:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 是不是很緊很舒服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.10,0:16:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.56,0:16:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 會在裡面射精的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.11,0:16:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 射吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.07,0:16:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往美咲的子宮 射得滿滿的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.79,0:16:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止了 淫賤護士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.46,0:16:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你們來幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.00,0:16:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是我們問妳在幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.96,0:16:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳這個 淫亂 變態 恬不知恥的護士
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.30,0:16:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是在治療當中 快出去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.26,0:16:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的「袋袋」或者說我們的容忍已經到極限啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.98,0:17:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.11,0:17:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變態護士 我們來給妳處罰
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.62,0:17:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 我不要這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.33,0:17:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別給我唧唧歪歪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.17,0:17:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 我才不要那些已經用爛了的雞雞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.21,0:17:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼不要 反正都是要插進去的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.97,0:17:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.94,0:17:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 全進去咯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.36,0:17:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動一動看看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.82,0:17:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好緊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.74,0:17:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.68,0:18:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面都在動 厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.22,0:18:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很快就要射了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.97,0:18:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 你也太丟臉了吧 這麼快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.98,0:18:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說這○很厲害啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 拔出去  拔出去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.15,0:18:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.53,0:18:42.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.12,0:18:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢貨 我們都還沒上 你他媽怎麼就射在裡面了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.50,0:18:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啊 一不小心就…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.07,0:19:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,葉月小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.12,0:19:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妳臉很紅哦 是不是發燒了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.75,0:19:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.21,0:19:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這…這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.81,0:19:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那話兒 跟乳臭未乾的小傢伙是不同等級的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.58,0:20:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我插
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.67,0:20:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,極樂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.72,0:20:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太大了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.22,0:20:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…被人強姦…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.64,0:20:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竞…竟然會有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.61,0:20:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別光含 把妳的舌頭用上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.70,0:20:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始舔人雞雞以後 妳的淫水可是越來越多了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.78,0:20:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然妳就喜歡那話兒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.29,0:20:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好窩心…為什麼我一定要吸吮這雞雞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.42,0:21:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡的是 還沒被污染的 年輕孩子的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.52,0:21:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 別用那種眼光看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.10,0:21:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要用那種看變態的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.36,0:21:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其疾如風
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.37,0:21:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要用那種看淫亂的女人的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.67,0:21:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看著一邊被強姦一邊吸吮雞雞的我…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.26,0:21:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要看我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.22,0:21:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侵略如火
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.56,0:21:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不動如山
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.87,0:22:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好幾十年都沒中出過了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.38,0:22:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.34,0:22:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直欺負你的可怕大姊姊現在都成這狼狽樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.55,0:22:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好報復吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.10,0:22:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.52,0:22:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 等一下 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.77,0:22:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也是這麼說的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.11,0:22:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了好多次「住手」的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.48,0:22:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對…對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.69,0:22:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會再犯了 所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.78,0:22:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 妳老是這樣強迫我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.71,0:23:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.42,0:23:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊妳有感覺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.59,0:23:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實被人欺負也是很舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.97,0:23:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不是的 不是那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.64,0:23:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊 跟我一樣 都是變態
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.52,0:23:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要…說我…是…變態
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.15,0:23:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 姊姊可是自己擺弄腰的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.28,0:23:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.79,0:23:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我打攪一下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.04,0:23:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不會吧 不行
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.13,0:23:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡 屁股那裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.10,0:23:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.31,0:24:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊妳 有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.44,0:24:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人侵犯 有感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.53,0:24:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也來一下
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.04,0:24:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊有感覺 快…快射了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.34,0:24:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了 去了 去了 快要…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.55,0:24:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.71,0:25:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給 這是祝你出院的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.92,0:25:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是…？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.43,0:25:14.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊…姊姊？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.30,0:25:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想欺負我的時候 就隨時按那個鍵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.60,0:25:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那再見了 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.14,0:25:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.65,0:25:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊…姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.46,0:25:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在炫耀呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.21,0:25:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙 明明只是個小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.33,0:25:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等美和子回來了 要懲罰
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.41,0:27:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一集 淫笑護士是
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.28,0:27:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟這一集不同 講笨蛋的主題的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.83,0:27:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥×妹妹 姊姊×妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.29,0:27:50.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做這種和那種事情
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.92,0:27:53.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為十分淫賤 敬請期待
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.38,0:27:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然是笨蛋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.75,0:27:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們在下一集再見
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.76,0:27:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙你的 我就不出場了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.18,0:28:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是沒問題 色情度我能作保
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.76,0:28:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 豎著雞雞等第二卷出來哦 知道沒？


