The blissful source of the greatness
of the universe.
If we take control of that...
...we can cross time and space...
...and manipulate the evil passions
of all people at will.
Tell us where the passage leading
to the Shikima brain is?
I don't know! Even if I did, I
wouldn't tell you!
Give in! Shikima King!
Hold it!
Fubuki!
Yaku!
Miko Mido!
Glory to the Mahoroba!
Ryokuga!
That's so good...!
I'm going to cum...!
More, more...!
Harder!
I'm going to cum...!
M-Miyu! I can't take it anymore...!
No. Not yet!
A little more! I'm about to cum!
I can't! This is it!
Cum inside of me! I want all of it!
I want all of it! Cum inside of me!
I want to feel it hot!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Hey, you can go again, right?
Look, Miyu! I wish you'd cut it out!
How many times do you have to
do it, and in my room!
How many times?
It's only been twice.
Isn't twice enough?
In any case, why do you have to
bring men back to my place?!
That's because this is the closest
place to my shooting location.
Miyu?
Miko.
Father?
What are you doing, Miko?
Have you found the passage
leading to the Shikima brain?
Don't tell me you've forgotten the
importance of the Shikima brain.
I haven't forgotten...
...what you told me, Father.
The Shikima brain...
...from which the entire
universe is controlled...
...is a holy place, considered
to be the origin of space.
If we can control that...
...we can cross time and space...
...and manipulate the passions
of all people at will.
Although we may have repelled
the Mahoroba clan...
...the brain will be the next target.
And so, Miko, in order
to protect the brain...
...you must find the passage
that leads to it.
I'll leave you to find that passage.
Well, see you, Miko.
I'll be using your bed again.
Hey! Wait a minute, Miyu!
We're here!
So, this is Miko's
and this is Yaku's and...
...and this is Fubuki's!
Why did you bring a computer
along, Fubuki?
It's about all we can count on now.
Nin-Nin, could you
get us refreshments?
Sure!
This is connected to here...
And then...
They're awfully carefree around me.
They don't even see me as a man anymore.
So, this is what they call a mouse?
Come on, Miko. Will you get
serious about this?
Have you forgotten the promise
you made to the Shikima King?
I haven't forgotten at all!
The Mahoroba clan attacked us...
...and we barely managed to fight
them off, but...
There!
We don't know when the Shikima
brain will be targeted...
...so in order to find
the passage to it...
...we're all hunkered down here
and working hard...
...to get as many leads as possible.
And we haven't gotten anywhere.
Maybe it's just not possible to find
the passage to the Shikima brain...
...just with the three of us.
Grandma's suggestion...
...was to get the survivors of the
Miroku clan to help us, but...
...that didn't work out either.
The Miroku have been
all scattered about...
...like blades of grass.
Even if we look for them,
we don't even have one lead.
That's right.
That's why we brought a computer.
We'll set up a web site...
...with keywords that only those
from the Miroku would understand.
These are modern times.
Miroku people who can't get in
touch with the clan might access it.
It'll be like killing two birds
with one stone...
...if we can get some leads on the
Shikima brain as well.
You're so amazing, Fubuki!
When did you become such a techie?!
Everybody knows this stuff.
This is the age of information
technology, after all.
The mouse makes his way
over the mountain...
Stop messing around, Nin-Nin!
Do you really think the Miroku
will recognize the web site?
We've got to try it, right?
We can keep jumping and
running around in circles...
...but we haven't been able
to get anywhere so far.
You're right. It's better than not trying.
As for the Miroku clan...
You're Shikima clan, right?
So the only Miroku left that we
know of are Nin-Nin and Yaku.
This all because of my negligence.
Anyway...
...even if just one from the Miroku
were to access the web site...
...that might be enough to give us
a lead to find the Shikima brain.
We're going to have to count on
you for this, Fubuki.
That's right. We're completely
ignorant about these things.
But I have to ask, Miko...
...do you have any college friends
who can help us with the web site?
Huh? I thought you were going to...
I'm still working on the whole
information technology thing.
Click, click... Click.
How dare you take advantage
of the situation, Nin-Nin!
And so, the way the human brain works...
...is still not clear in many respects.
In regard to the function of the brain...
...half of it isn't even being
used most of the time.
We don't completely understand
the human brain.
The Shikima brain is
more full of mysteries.
We can't even figure out how
we're supposed to get there.
Miko!
Ruri!
I finally got a hold of my brother.
He said he'll drop by after
the computer shop.
Really?
He said he'd be about an hour.
Wow, that really helps me out!
Thanks, Ruri.
Don't mention it.
It's really no big deal.
I'm just happy that we could
become friends because of this.
I'm happy, too, that we
could become friends.
I should ask for help more often.
There he is. Maho!
You were awfully quick.
Oh, Ruri.
What is this sudden feeling I have?
This bittersweet, weird feeling
that I'm overcome with?
What is this...?
I'm Maho, Ruri's older brother.
I've heard a lot about you.
Uh, I'm Miko Mido.
I'm sorry for making you do this.
What's the matter, Miko?
You're blushing.
Maho,just because you
don't meet girls often...
...doesn't mean you can
have your way with her.
How could you say such a thing
in front of your friend?
Well, I'll leave the rest with you, Maho.
I've got somewhere
I've got to go to, Miko.
I'll see you on campus tomorrow.
Uh, thanks!
But why?
I've never met him before.
But I feel a fondness toward him.
Here we go.
You just have to wait for a while...
...until the service provider
sets up your account.
What's the matter?
Is there something on my face?
Uh, no. Oh, I know...
...I'll get you a cold refreshment.
Miko!
Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm home!
Did you bring someone who's
going to do the web site for us?
What are you two doing?
Thank you so much for today.
Thanks to you, the other two are
all over the computer now.
Well, if that's the sort of help you
need, then call me anytime.
Thank you very much.
If you have any more trouble
with your computer...
...feel free to give me a call.
I appreciate that.
We did it, Miko!
I girl who seems like a Miroku
accessed the web site!
Really?!
That's right!
I used the keyword, '' Peach
blossom in the land of Miroku.''
And this girl sent in a question
asking whether...
...that was a reference to the name
of a Miroku ancestor.
As it turns out, she lives
right near here.
Nin-Nin's gone out to get her.
It was awfully easy finding
someone from the Miroku clan.
I'm back!
Come on in. Don't be shy.
Hello!
Miss Miko!
Are you the one who
got in touch with us...
...through our new web site?
That's right.
I'm Kanako, Miss Miko.
Miss Miko?!
This has always been
a dream of mine.
The day I would be summoned
by the great Miko Mido of the Miroku.
Miss Miko!
Cut it out!
Before my grandmother died...
...she had trained me
in the carnal arts...
...so that one day I'd be of some use...
...and able to offer my services
to the Mido family of the Miroku clan.
You've been training in
the carnal arts as well?
That's right.
But normally I'm a student
at a nursing college.
Kanako...
And I didn't know
how to get in touch...
...with the main house
of the Miroku clan...
...so, I've been alone all this time.
Is that right?
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't even aware that someone
like you was out there.
But I just happened to come
across a web site...
...and when I saw that keyword
only a Miroku would catch...
...I thought,just maybe this time...!
And then just like in my dream...
...I get to meet the adorable Miss
Miko Mido of the Miroku clan!
Miss Miko!
Kanako! I'm really not
into that sort of thing!
I wish you'd call me lover, Miss Mido!
Look, you...!
Miss Miko!
No...!
Why don't you just become
her big sister?
I suppose. Experience is the most
important thing, after all.
You two are horrible!
How can you think such a thing?!
What are you going to do, Maho?
Are you going to leave Miko Mido alone?
No.
Anyone who tries to get
near the Shikima brain...
...I cannot let alone,
no matter who they are.
I'll lure her into the usual place,
and eliminate her.
I see. Sounds all right to me.
So, we shall cross paths again.
Gimme a break!
Fubuki!
Tentacles from the computer?!
Yaku! Fubuki!
Look, Kanako...
Fubuki! How...?!
Fubuki!
Fubuki, what just happened now?!
It happened while I was in the shower.
Why would tentacles come out
of the computer?
It looks like she'll be all right.
But she doesn't seem to be conscious...
...it's like she's watching a dream
while she's awake.
That's what it looks like to me.
There's a specialist doctor at the
hospital where I'm interning.
The doctor's doing research
on sleep treatments.
I think we should take
her there right away!
Fubuki...
Anyway, we're going have to get
her to regain consciousness.
Right.
Kanako, do you think we can ask
that doctor to help us?
All right! I'll try to get a hold of her!
Nin-Nin, call an ambulance right away!
Right...
Just hang on, Fubuki!
She's probably being molested
in her dream.
If she's being molested in her
dream, there's nothing we can do.
Yes.
Kanako, do you think Fubuki
will be normal again?
I'm sure the doctor I'm interning
for can help her!
She's a world-famous scientist in
the field of sleep treatment.
She's highly respected by serious
researchers all across the country.
I see.
I just gave her a sedative.
She'll rest for a while.
I'll take this opportunity to determine
what is tormenting her.
Can you figure out what
kind of dream she's having?
Yes.
There are two different types of sleep:
REM sleep and non-REM sleep.
Fubuki is now dreaming
in a non-REM sleep state.
These dreams are called
hallucinatory dreams...
...and they seem very close to reality.
Hallucinatory dreams?
Yes.
World famous scientists,
like Nobel laureates...
...who make major scientific discoveries...
...or great minds who discover
truths about life and the universe...
...have often awakened from
hallucinatory dreams...
...gaining insights into truths that
they later reveal to the world.
Then, what Fubuki's seeing right now is...
...an experience as she nears what
it is that she is trying to discover.
You could say that it's like trial
run taking place in reality.
Miko...
Perhaps Fubuki's desire to find the
passage to the Shikima brain...
...has brought on the carnal
demons tormenting her.
Doctor, please bring Fubuki back
to consciousness.
I understand.
I'll do the best that I can.
Hello, this is Miko.
Hi, it's Maho.
Oh, Maho.
Miko, do you think we can meet?
Huh?
There's something I really
want to show you, Miko.
But I can't really leave where I am.
I'll send you an e-mail with the address.
I hope you come.
It's really important. I'll be waiting.
Uh, wait! Hello? Maho? Hello? Maho?
What's the matter, Miko?
Maho, who created that web site
for us the other day...
...insists on meeting me right away.
He said there's something
important he wants to show me.
He sounded really tense.
I understand, Miko.
I'll watch things here.
But, Fubuki's...
It'll be okay. Don't you worry.
I'll stick around and watch over Fubuki.
Yaku...
Thank you. I'll leave you with Fubuki.
Miss Miko!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Kanako, I want you to stay here
with Fubuki.
Oh, Miss Miko.
Are you going somewhere?
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to be apart from you!
Let me go with you.
Kanako, I'm asking you...
You're the only one I can trust
to watch over Fubuki.
Okay. If that's what you want,
I will obey you.
Now, let's see what this
nightmare is all about.
I really hope you can do it.
Fubuki, where are you right now?
Inside the great hall.
An appropriate sacrifice
to open up the passage.
I'm sure even the Shikima
will be satisfied with this.
What? What are these people
talking about?
We can tell with how she was
writhing in pleasure before.
We'll have to get her nice and wet
before we open the passage.
We'll summon the Shikima
with her moaning.
We'll have to make preparations
before that.
Summon the Shikima?
Who are you people, anyway?!
Wh-What are you doing to me?!
Who on earth are you people?!
Why are you doing this? Where am I?!
- Doctor!
- Are you all right, Fubuki?!
Yaku, I want you to tune into
Fubuki's hallucinatory dream.
Tune into Fubuki's hallucinatory dream?
Is that even possible?
This is an emergency.
If the torment of this hallucinatory
dream continues much longer...
...she'll be damaged psychologically.
Someone has to tune into her
hallucinatory dream...
...and go in and save her from it.
I understand!
Miko, get on the back.
Maho!
I didn't think you would actually
catch the last train.
I half didn't expect you to show up.
I'm so happy we are
meeting again, Miko.
Maho...
But why do I feel this way?
Why do I feel this way toward Maho?
What is this place, Maho?
Wh-What's that?!
Wh-Where are we?
What's happened to us?!
Maho...!
Stop! Please, no! No!
Fubuki!
Hang on, Miko!
Shikima are present as stipulated
in the contract.
Take the other one and
offer it up as a sacrifice!
Miko!
Maho!
Stop this! I am the daughter
of the Shikima King!
Never heard of him!
Who does she think she is?
Nice and tight. This is quality pussy!
How could they not know Father?
Aren't they Shikima?
Where on earth is this?
Miko!
No! Don't look, Maho!
No!
No, Miko. I mustn't get aroused.
Maho's watching. I can take
at least this much...
N-No...! Please, I beg you...!
Don't do this to me anymore!
No, please! Not there!
Not in front of Maho!
Please, not in front of Maho!
No!
I'm going to cum... I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum!
Miko!
No! Please don't watch, Maho!
I beg you!
No...! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Miko!
Maho...
Coming up next,
La Blue Girl Returns Episode 4.
Don't miss it!