The one who carries my thick blood...
...I have waited long for you.
Peace has brought complacency
and a disregard for carnal power.
Now is the time for revenge.
We lost our brethren at the hands
of the despised Maitreyas...
...who had joined forces
with the carnal sorcerers.
They butchered many...
...and we were driven off
the land of the Mahoroba.
The long-lost powers of the
Mahoroba gather again...
...and they shall now be restored!
Realize the hatred of the centuries.
And restore the power
and position of our clan.
Grandma, I'm sorry I haven't been
by in a while.
It's peaceful here, and I haven't
had to use my carnal powers...
...but I am continuing with my
training nonetheless.
So, don't you worry.
Since Miko's going to
lead the Mido clan...
...I'll be living a normal life.
I wanted both my fiance and I to...
...break the news about our
engagement, but...
He's really late, Miss Miyu.
...since he's been so busy with work...
...he said he'll come directly
this evening.
I've been so looking forward to
seeing him.
Oh, that's right. I guess you
haven't met Michael yet.
That's right. He's my dear sister's
fiance after all...
...so, I planned on checking
him out with my own eyes.
Oh, come on, Miko...
I'll check this out with my own eyes.
It's so hard to choose between them.
Michael's so busy flying off to New
York and L.A. all the time...
...so I'm sorry it's just me here
to tell you the news.
This is you we're talking about,
so I hope he's not some weirdo.
Don't you worry.
Michael's a music producer.
He has good taste and he's very kind.
Listen to you, so proud and all.
I don't think I can take it.
Oh, this view! I don't know
if I can take it!
So, is he, like, really handsome?
I've gotta get a shot of this.
You can take a good look
when you meet him.
Watch it, Miss Miko!
What are you doing, pervert?!
What?!
Miss Miyu!
How dare you jump on my grandma!
Be careful, Miko!
Watch sis for me, Nin-Nin!
Leave it to Nin-Nin!
I lost her!
That's very quick of you.
Who are you?!
Hand over the seal case.
Then I'll at least spare your life.
Don't be ridiculous!
Well, then.
Why are you after the seal case?!
Who are you?!
I am Kocho Kunoichi, the 69th
head of the Mahoroba clan.
A clan dating further back
than the Maitreyas.
Why does the Mahoroba want
the seal case?!
It's not for you to know.
Unless you do what I say, you'll
lose more than your clothes.
Don't you take me for a fool!
You're not getting away!
She's gone!
Where did she go?
Oh, no!
A Maitreya is nothing but a
helpless infant in our hands.
Submit to my carnal power, and
tell me where the seal case is.
Have a taste of the carnal
pleasure potion...
...passed down through
the Mahoroba clan.
Now, tell me the whereabouts
of the seal case.
Or you will die of pleasure.
Or would you rather me gut you
from here to your chin?
You'll never be able to use
your carnal powers again.
Look how stiff these are.
No, stop!
Look at the torrent
of juices flowing.
Are you sure you're a virgin?
No, I can't make it stop...
No, stop!
Stop it. I'm about to go crazy...!
Grandma, I can't take it anymore...!
I'm gonna die!
Do you want it all to stop?
Then tell me where the seal case is?
I can't let myself die like this.
I can't get it off.
It's burning me!
Miss Miko!
I made it...
You're okay now?
I'm not okay at all.
The blood is rushing to my head!
That sure was an amazing
trick, though.
When did you learn that?
I just learned it from
the Book of Secrets.
I see.
But you sure are nice
and wet in here.
What do you think
you're doing, Nin-Nin?!
Sorry...
Just get me down!
It's a bit cold, Miss Miko.
Just stop complaining, all right?!
You're never any use when
I need you the most.
But your juices sure
had a bite to them.
Enough, already!
Wow! Check out the fancy car!
Wow!
I wonder if it's sis's fiance's?
Wow! Check out the interior!
Miko. You're back.
Are you all right?
Yeah, but she got away.
Hey, hey, did your fiance
finally get here?
Yes. I'll introduce you.
This is Michael, my fiance.
How do you do?
He's superhandsome!
It's an honor to meet you.
YourJapanese is very good.
Likewise. It's an honor to meet you.
Wow! I shook hands with
such a handsome man!
I'm not washing my hands again!
Oh, is that a ninja costume?
Huh?
Well, uh, this is actually
Nin-Nin's clothes, and...
Look, you!
How dare you dress me like this!
But you're the one who took
my clothes from me!
You just shut up!
And that's Nin-Nin,
a bona fide ninja.
How wonderful!
Well, it's getting late. We'll
go see Grandma tomorrow.
I guess. He's a good catch.
Handsome and rich and all.
I do have my ways, you know.
Listen to you.
No...
Oh, come on. Look at you.
No, Michael. Miko's sleeping
in the next room.
What's wrong with that?
She can watch us make love.
Turn around.
No, it's embarrassing.
Forgive me, sis.
You're forgiven. You're forgiven.
Just give me a break.
Oh, that feels so good.
Miko will hear us...
I hear you! I hear you!
I love you, Michael...!
Go harder...
Oh, come on! Why do they
have to do this here?!
I don't know if I can take
any more of this.
It's a bit unbecoming of me,
but it is part of my training.
Yes, yes... More, more...
Michael...!
Just forget about me
lying here alone.
I'm going to burst, Michael!
I'm gonna cum...!
It's easy for sis to get all worked up
and cum like that...
...but I have to train to keep
myself from cumming.
Oh, that's enough now...
I just came...
How long are they going
to be at this?
How am I supposed to sleep?
Miss Miyu...! Wow...!
Look, Nin-Nin!
Where is the seal case?
Where is it hidden?
W-What?
I don't know. What are you
talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
I know you're a direct descendant
of the Maitreyas.
I don't know...
Still want to play games, huh?
You want me to keep going
until you're dead?
Stop! No!
Let go of my sister!
Who are you, anyway?
Miko, where is the seal case?
Must be a Mahoroba!
So, what if I am from
the Mahoroba clan?
This is...
...that pleasure potion...
My body...
It's starting to work on you.
Your carnal training shows.
It's getting nice and dripping wet.
At this rate, I'm going to be...
You can't fight it.
Even the best Maitreya will succumb
to my carnal powers.
Hand over the seal case.
Or your sister won't live.
Don't you worry about me.
I can't breathe...!
W-Wait...!
Nin-Nin...
...get the seal case.
You mustn't, Miko.
Don't give in to him...
Miss Miko...!
H-Here's the seal case.
If you'd given in at the start,
this would've been more pleasant.
It's the genuine article.
Let go of my sister.
I suppose.
But first I'll show you
the pleasure of this.
I'll take a rain check on that!
Carnal power! Hairpins!
You caught me off guard.
But I do have the seal case!
Hold on, you!
Now, the Shikima realm shall be
at our command!
Hold it, you coward!
What's this sensation in my body...?!
No, not in a place like this...!
But I can't help myself...!
Miss Miko's feeling
herself up outdoors!
Nin-Nin! What were
you doing, anyway?!
S-Sorry...
I finally got it off.
But, that Miko...
How can I not despise you?
How dare she cause me injury.
Goddess of the carnal world...
...although I succumbed to
Miko Mido's carnal juices...
...I will take control
of the Shikima...
...and bring the Mahoroba
to new heights!
Goddess of the carnal world,
give me the power!
Kocho...
...I shall awaken the power
within you...
...of our ancient clan!
That's...!
Miss Kocho!
Are you all right, Miss Kocho?
Do you have the item?
Yes. I have the seal case in my hand.
Well, good work.
We shall now be able to rule
the Shikima realm.
However, that seal is simply
a contract with the Shikima.
That Shikima King will not go so easily.
He's also Miko's father.
How would you like me
to handle it?
With only the two of us,
we cannot achieve our goal.
I will first go to the Shikima realm.
But the gates to the Shikima realm
will not open...
...without the power of Shikima.
I have a secret plan.
A plan that will restore the
Mahoroba at the same time.
I'm sorry, Miko.
It's all my fault.
But you didn't know
anything about it.
Don't worry about it.
But we have to tell Father that
the seal case was taken.
I feel that I can't show
my face to them.
But you have to come with me, too.
What?
I mean, if I leave you here alone...
...the Mahoroba might
come after you again.
I'll go, then.
It's almost eleven. Let's get going.
Wow! A double stack-o-pussy!
Double sister pussy...!
We masturbate facing eleven
o'clock, at eleven.
It just seems so embarrassing.
This isn't the time to worry
about that.
I mean, I'm embarrassed, too, but...
Let's begin.
Miss Miyu's is spreading wide
open and looking real tasty!
Go away, Nin-Nin.
I can't do that.
I have to go along with you.
I'll even help you!
How are we supposed
to concentrate, Nin-Nin?
That's easy to say, but
how can I ignore this!
I see.
That's the masturbation Miss Kocho
was talking about.
Miko carries the blood of the
Shikima king.
She has the power to open
a path to the Shikima realm.
At that moment, you must place this
into Miko's womb.
The source of my life.
My soul.
Miss Kocho, this is too much...
The metamorphosis is
only now beginning.
I need all of your seed.
I cannot withstand this.
You must set me on fire and melt
my body and soul.
How nice and firm, Ryokuga.
It's good...
Yes... Yes...
I can feel my life melting away.
Yes, yes... I'm melting...
I'm melting...
I cannot withstand it any longer!
Now!
I'm melting! I'm melting!
I'm melting away!
The soul of Miss Kocho...
...I will send her along with you
into the Shikima realm.
Oh, no...! I'm going to cum...!
Just a little more, sis.
They're about to climax!
I'm cumming!
This is too much!
Hey, Nin-Nin! What's with
this stupid parachute?!
It's my work of art??
You're looking pretty cute, Miko!
Why do you have a normal parachute?!
You have to stay still...!
Good luck, Miss Miko!
Are you all right, Miss Miyu?
I think I hit my bum a little.
Well, well, whereabouts does it hurt?
Around here?
Oh, my, my!
The important bits are glowing red!
Let's deal with that...
Nin-Nin!
You're really no help, are you?!
Oh, Miss Miko... What if
this becomes a habit?
I really do feel a bit sore down there.
Will you be all right?
I'm okay.
Now, let's hurry over to
our mother and father.
Carnal beasts that dwell
throughout the realms...
...I summon thee in accordance
with this contract!
We present ourselves to Shikima
under contract of the seal case.
I've long awaited your arrival,
comrades.
Did you summon us?
That's right. I, Ryokuga
of the Mahoroba clan.
Submit to my command in accordance
with the contract.
And what is our prey?
Them!
They are all to be captured as slaves!
Go!
Help!
It's been awhile since
I got some human!
Feel the pain. You will be slaves
to your carnal urges!
Foolish carnal beasts...
...you shall work to serve our ends.
It's been a while since there's
been a contract request.
Is that right? I'm a little worried
about Miko now.
I don't think anything grave
has happened to Miko.
Father!
That voice is... Miko?
Well, it certainly is!
Father... Mother...
Miko! And Miyu, too!
What's going on?
The seal case was taken!
Then you weren't the one making
the contract request?
It's the Mahoroba clan, Father!
The Mahoroba clan?!
Do you know them?
They were a ninja clan
that controlled...
...Soga, who was principal advisor...
...to the Japanese Imperial
court 1 ,400 years ago.
I think we studied that
in history class.
You mean the Soga who was destroyed
during the reforms?
That's right. Soga died in his
villa as it burned to the ground.
At that time, a Mido
ancestor served as...
...a secret councilor
to the Imperial court.
Shortly afterwards...
...there were rumors
that a number of...
...Mahorobas had managed
to escape to the sea.
So they've restored
their power, huh?
Michael was an American
ofJapanese descent.
Come to think of it, Kocho
seemed different too.
What's the matter, sis?
There's a sudden pain...
...in my stomach...!
Miyu! Miyu!
There's something growing
within her!
But what?!
What is that?!
It's Kocho!
My dear!
Maria!Just take Miko
with you and go!
Yes!
The Shikima realm must
submit to the Mahoroba!
Not so fast!
Don't make me laugh.
I shall also feed off of you!
Mother!
Are you all right, Miko?
Miko! You must flee for now...
...and devise a strategy!
But I can't run away and
leave everyone here!
The Mido Book of Secrets...
...should have a plan for
fighting the Mahoroba!
Go, Miko!
You must escape, Miko!
Come on, Miss Miko!
You won't get away!
So, they got away...
Hurry! Hurry! Miss Miko!
Wh-What's this all about?!
What's happening?
It is now time for another to take
the place of Shikima ruler.
I see.
Fubuki...!
Yaku...!
We must capture Miko Mido.
Miko's back,
and she's in trouble...AGAI N!
Don't worry about me. I'm getting
more powerful all the time.
I'll be fine.
Watch out monsters.
Miko Mido's coming to get you
with her carnal powers!
Coming up, in the next episode
of La Blue Girl Returns!
Nin-Nin's back and he's a 21 st
century ass-kicking sex machine!