Miss Miko!
I'm Kanako, Miss Miko.
Miss Miko?!
What are you going to do, Maho?
Are you going to leave Miko Mido alone?
No. Anyone who tries to get
near the Shikima brain...
...I cannot let alone,
no matter who they are.
I'll lure her into the usual place,
and eliminate her.
Yaku, I want you to tune into
Fubuki's hallucinatory dream.
This is an emergency.
If the torment of this hallucinatory
dream continues much longer...
...she'll be damaged psychologically.
I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum!
Miko!
Maho...
Fubuki...
Now, Yaku...
...I want you to tune into Fubuki's
hallucinatory dream.
By synchronizing Fubuki's
non-REM brainwaves...
...with Yaku's brainwaves...
...you will enter the same
hallucinatory dream...
...and will be able to rescue her.
All right.
So, this is Fubuki's hallucinatory dream?
No!
No, please...!
Please stop this!
Fubuki!
Carnal awakening!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Thanks, Yaku!
Miko!
Are you all right, Miko! Wake up!
Yaku...
We have interference.
The ones we called are gone.
We might as well disappear.
Miko!
What's going on here?
Where are we?
I was taken by Maho and...
...and I ended up here when I woke up.
This is Fubuki's hallucinatory dream.
I came here to bring you back.
That's when Miko...
Miko.
I'm sorry that had to happen to you...
...considering I'm here with you.
How did you bring Miko here?
Fubuki?
Yaku?
Fubuki and Yaku are gone!
There's nothing to worry about, Miko.
They just woke up from
the hallucinatory dream.
They're probably back
in the real world now.
Awoke from the hallucinatory dream?
Isn't this Fubuki's hallucinatory dream?
Why did you bring me here?
What on earth are you doing, Maho?
Miko...
Anyway, let's go purify our bodies
in the nearby spring.
I'll tell you everything then.
Maho?
You've awakened. It was a success.
Thank goodness.
There's big trouble, Kanako.
For some reason Miko has been
left in the hallucinatory dream.
What?! Miko is...?!
That's strange.
If she was in Fubuki's dream, she should've
disappeared when she woke up.
Which would mean that
it's not caused by her...
...but rather that she wandered
into someone else's dream.
In any case, we have to rescue Miko!
Doctor, please put me
into a dream state again.
Unfortunately, that's impossible.
We don't know whose dream it is.
I was able to trace Fubuki's
brainwaves to synchronize, but...
If only Miko was here...
...we'd be able to catch her brainwaves...
What?!
Then, Miko is...
Miko...
What a strange spring.
I feel like my filthy body
and spirit are being cleansed.
Now, tell me, Maho.
Where are we?
This is a hallucinatory dream.
The dream within the Shikima brain.
The dream within the Shikima brain?
Maho, what are you...?
First of all, I'll get us
something to wear.
Being like this could
become a distraction.
We'll have a long talk about this later.
Maho...
How would he know about
the Shikima brain?
Who on earth is Maho?
And what is that image that
appears in the back of my mind?
Miko...! Miko isn't coming back...!
My precious Miko!
The reason Fubuki was drawn
into the hallucinatory dream...
...should be hidden in this computer.
If we check it thoroughly, I'm sure...
There! I knew it!
It's set up so that the computer
activates it...
...after someone's been accessing
the web long enough.
But who can set up
a web site like that?
The guy who's with her right now!
Miko's...! Miko's in trouble!
You're making too much noise!
Just cut it out, Nin-Nin.
Ruri?
What are you doing here?
I thought is was strange my brother
left in the middle of the night.
I was following him, and I
wandered into this place.
As I wandered around,
I spotted you.
Is that right?
Where's my brother?
Maho said he was going off
to get some clothes.
Oh, perfect timing, then.
Now's our chance to get it over with.
Ruri?
But why, Ruri?
You're in the way.
That's why I want you to be
a prisoner of pleasure.
Huh? A prisoner of pleasure?
Ruri... What will happen to me...?
N-No...!
I'll tell you something interesting.
If you can cum in this place....
In this spring of carnal pleasure...
...you will be wandering in a state
of pleasure for eternity.
Ruri, I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to... I'm going to...
You can cum, Miko Mido.
Cum and become a prisoner
of the spring of carnal pleasure.
Oh, no... I'm going to...
I'm going to cum...!
- Ruri?
- Maho...
Miko Mido is now a prisoner
of the spring of carnal pleasure.
If you leave her there...
...her soul will wander aimlessly
for eternity...
...in the dream of the Shikima brain.
Isn't that great, Maho?
What happened to me?
Ruri cast a spell on you...
...and you became a prisoner of
this spring of carnal pleasure.
You were about to be sealed away
in here for eternity.
Ruri did?!
Ruri and I are descendents of a clan
that protects the Shikima brain.
You and Ruri are from a clan that
protects the Shikima brain?
That's right. All those who
approach the Shikima brain...
...for whatever reasons...
...I lure into this hallucinatory dream...
...and seal them away forever.
That is the duty of our clan...
...and our reason to exist.
Then, the one who lured Fubuki
into this place...
...and the one who
brought me here was...
If that's the case,
then why did you save me?
That's because you and I...
...are lovers from long ago...
...who were reborn into this world.
You and I were...
...lovers in a past life?
Miko. Look at this.
Try to remember.
Clothes you wore in a previous life.
Clothes I wore in a previous life...
Are you all right?
Thank you very much.
We fell in love with each other
that instant.
Who is it?
Good morning.
Wh-What's the matter?
Try and catch me!
All right!
I'll give you something nice
if you can catch up to me.
I'm going to get you!
Well, I caught up to you.
Then, I'll give you something good.
I didn't know that you were
the daughter of the Mido clan...
...whose duty was to search
for the Shikima brain...
...until that day.
Why? Why do you have to be
the daughter of the Mido clan?!
Why?!
What about you?!
Why do you have to be from a clan
that protects the Shikima brain?!
When we are born again
in another life...
...we will meet again...
No matter how many times
we are reborn, definitely...
...we'll meet again...
I'm sure... Definitely...
No matter how many times
we are reborn, definitely...
We finally meet again, but...
...this has to happen again...
Maho...
Miko...
I'm shy... Please don't look, Maho.
Why?
You're beautiful.
Maho...
I'm shy...
Maho... Maho...
Please don't tease my nipples.
Miko, look at you now...
You mustn't lick down there!
It's dirty! Maho!
Maho, I want you now.
Okay, Miko.
Th-This is the first time
I've been with a man, so...
...please be gentle.
I know, Miko.
Maho! I love you! I love you!
Miko! Miko!
Maho, I'm going to...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Miko...
Maho...
We've finally become one...
...after being reborn.
I'm so happy.
Miko...
What are you going to do, Kanako?
I enter the dream through
the same route...
...and go and rescue Miss Miko!
What? That's dangerous, Kanako!
Don't worry. I'll be sure
to rescue Miss Miko.
Kanako...
Good luck, Kanako.
I hope this sacrifice will
open up the passage.
Who knows. But at least
we can have fun with her.
Is this Miss Miko's hallucinatory dream?
No! Miko! Help me!
Hey, Maho...
What was that attacking Fubuki before?
They are the zombie demons of those...
...who sought the Shikima brain.
Zombie demons?
They sacrifice any woman
that comes their way.
Sacrifice?
In order to open a passage
to the Shikima brain...
...they must sacrifice the women
who are thought to be...
...the descendents of the Shikima.
Descendents of the Shikima?
That's right. By sacrificing the
women of the descendent clan.
N-No! Stop!
I already decided Miss Miko
was going to be the first!
No!
This woman! She is from the clan
of Shikima descendents!
It will open! The passage
to the Shikima brain!
Wake up, Kanako.
Were you able to rescue Miko?
I wasn't able to rescue Miko.
But something terrible has happened!
The passage leading to the
Shikima brain has opened!
What?!
Fubuki, we must use our magic
and go to the Shikima realm.
Right. We have to inform
the Shikima King.
This has to be the pleasure
center of this world.
I'm going to... I'm cumming!
Me, too... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Wh-What's this vibration?!
Shikima King!
Yaku! And even Fubuki!
Something terrible has happened, King!
The passage leading to the
Shikima brain has opened!
What?!
I see. That explains this convulsion
in the Shikima realm.
And Miko hasn't returned...
...from the dream we went into
to solve that mystery!
What should we do?!
But, now that the passage to the
Shikima brain has been opened...
...we cannot abandon
the Shikima realm.
I'm sure Miko can manage well.
Wh-What?!
What'll happen to Miss Miko?!
King...?
I'm sorry Miko. I hope you're safe.
Miko...
The passage leading to the
Shikima brain is opening up!
What?!
Don't tell me one of
the women sacrificed...
...was from the clan of
Shikima descendents!
The passage leading to the
Shikima brain has opened!
We shall gain the power
to control the universe!
We can now cross time and space...
...and manipulate the passions
of all people at will!
No.
At this rate those demons will
flood into the Shikima brain.
Maho!
Who is that?!
And we're so close
to the Shikima brain.
We must do everything
to break through!
Maho!
Maho...
Maho, you can do it!
Miko, listen to me.
The Shikima brain has awakened.
The Shikima brain has awakened?
That's right. Now that the Shikima
brain has awakened...
...this hallucinatory dream
will soon disappear.
Miko...
You've got to go to the Shikima realm
and protect the Shikima brain.
No! I have to save you first!
It's too late for me.
I'll disappear with this dream.
I doubt I'll be reborn again.
No. Please, Maho!
You've got to pull through!
I'm so happy that I was able
to be with you in the end.
But loving each other,
rather than killing each other.
Maho...? Maho!
After being reborn...
...and finally meeting again...
Maho... Maho!