Whose car is this?
What a mess.
The original story by
TOSHIO MAEDA
Does that mean the seal case
was stolen?
The original story by
TOSHIO MAEDA
The drawers haven't been touched.
This was no robbery.
What's this?
I knew it.
They went to the Shikima realm.
We should use our time travel
ability and go after them.
Miss Kocho, please
take a look at this.
I am and am not Kocho
at the same time.
I am Miyabi.
Descendent of the Mahoroba,
I am the ruler of the universe.
You shall call me Empress.
This looks like some
kind of a dead end.
But that does look like
an exit, though.
Are you sure this is the right way?
I'm sure there's no mistake, boss.
- Miss Miko, we'd better hide!
- Right.
They disappeared around here, boss.
Just don't call me boss.
Call me Future Great King.
Sorry, boss.
Give me a break...
The only exit around here
is the anus of the Shikima.
This is pretty weird.
I don't see them anywhere.
There's no sign that they
went through here.
Anyway, we'll seal it and
make it impenetrable.
Right. Good idea.
And you two stay here
and keep a lookout.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll go and make my report.
Hey, hey. Aren't we
important men now?
Yeah, that's right.
Then, it's okay to have our way
with those ladies, right?
Th-That's right.
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
Hey, how about having
some fun with us?
We are allies, after all.
All right. I'll show you the ultimate
in pleasurable sensations.
I feel all dizzy and horny!
You guys, we have other gates
to seal, too!
How could they? How pathetic!
It's an insult to the Shikima.
- I hope my father doesn't see this.
- Miss Miko.
There's a hole here that
we can go through.
Now's our chance while
they're distracted.
I suppose. It looks like they
sealed the gate up.
It's best that we get out of here.
Empress...
Once those new cocoons hatch...
...the Mahoroba clan shall be
completely restored.
We've lost track of Miko.
However, I've had Gamara
and his men seal the gates...
Never mind. If they
are trapped here...
...they will eventually make
their appearance.
What's happened to
the Shikima king?
Yes. Despite having lost so much
of his virility to your restoration...
...he is still alive.
Is that so? Quite amazing.
The prayers of the Mahoroba have
been answered after 4,000 years.
Not yet.
The true purpose remains
to be fulfilled.
Oh, comrades, there you are.
We sealed all of the exits.
You're in front of the Empress!
Get down on your knees!
Please excuse me.
Why are they such tight asses?
In order to control the
Shikima realm at will...
...we must find and take over
the brain of the Shikima...
...or our conquest will
not be complete.
The brain of the Shikima?
What is that?
It is a holy place, considered
to be the origin of space...
...from which the entire universe
is controlled.
Long, long ago, in order
to flee our dying planet...
...we had to locate
and travel through...
...a loophole in time
to another world.
Time did not exist there...
...and space had no bounds.
The clan succumbed
to a seductive aroma.
The clan had melted and
was turned into eggs.
Eventually an unknown force...
...caused the eggs to be
implanted in the wombs...
...of the first-generation
Mahoroba women...
...who became the source
of regeneration.
Then, that metamorphosis...
...that transformation...
That innate ability was turned
into a secret weapon.
However, it would succeed
only tentatively...
...affected by the life force
of the host organism...
...which limits the number of
those possessing the power.
So, are you one of them?!
However, we have come close
to that place.
The holy birthplace from which...
...we will renew ourselves.
Are you saying that the Shikima
brain is that holy place?
The blissful source of the greatness
of the universe.
If we take control of that...
...we could transcend
time and space...
...and manipulate the evil passions
of all people at will.
Incredible!
To think there was such a place
in the Shikima realm.
It seems like even you
weren't aware, Gamara.
Go, Ryokuga!
Search throughout the carnal world...
...and find the holy site!
Yes, ma'am!
What will I do?
That woman will be used as
a sacrifice to our renewal.
Use the Shikima king as
bait and lure out Miko!
Yes, ma'am.
Boss!
Don't call me boss!
What is it, anyway?
Intruders have entered
from the outside.
Who is it?
Friends of Miko.
The remaining Miroku, huh?
Interesting. I'll deal
with them myself.
Hey, are you sure this is the way?
- Of course...!
- Sh! Be quiet!
...I mean, the King's been
held in the appendix...
- ...so that Gamara is...
- Hear that, Miss Miko?
I see. He's being held
in the appendix.
Anyway, we'll have to get to the
stomach and meet up with Fubuki.
I really wonder if the psyche
call reached them.
I'm sure they're rushing
to our rescue.
But this passage sure is wet
and slimy. Creeps me out.
That's not so.
It's appealingly nice and gooey...
I almost want to stick
my face into it.
Hey, where are you looking?
Go ahead of me.
Come on. You shouldn't have
gone without panties.
Who are you?! Are you human?!
Don't you make a move!
That's not very nice of you.
What's with that attitude, anyway?
Or do you want to go at it
with me again?
This time it'll be nothing
compared to last time.
Well, excuse us, Miss Fubuki
and Miss Yaku.
Are you here for a reason?
Of course we're here for a reason.
Mere humans don't
satisfy you anymore?
Well, that's just a part of it.
But I don't think you'll be
of any use to us.
It would have to be like the King.
Would you like a try?
I don't care for that!
I know that Miko's here!
Let's see. I don't think
I recall such a thing.
Don't play games with us.
Someone stole the seal case,
you know.
I'm sure she's here to tell
the King about that.
What?! The seal case is
in the hands of a thief?!
Well, that's a big problem!
I think you've been playing dumb
with us all along.
Don't take my sense
of smell so lightly.
I've been smelling someone
other than you for some time.
Huh? What's this?
Who is it?!
So, you finally noticed.
I'll give you credit.
However, you are already under
the spell of the Mahoroba.
The Mahoroba?
Never heard of it.
I remember this smell
from Miko's house.
Fubuki, don't breathe this in.
Forget it.
That essence can be absorbed
through the skin.
Before the Mahoroba, even the
Shikima king could not resist it.
There's no way the likes
of you could resist it.
Where is the King?
He's being held prisoner
in the Shikima appendix.
You've sure done it now.
You'll regret it later.
Come to us, you two!
Find that your body is getting hot
and won't listen to you?
With all those love juices flowing
throughout your body!
This is too much!
- Stop...
- My body...!
Time for some fun.
No...!
Shove something into me!
More!
Seems you can't get enough of it.
I'll show you a pleasure that won't
even compare with the king.
Oh, my...! I've never felt this!
I'm sure. It's punishment
for underestimating me.
You're ripping me apart!
I'm cumming!
Miss Miko, we've come to a fork.
How are we supposed to know
which way to go?
This hole should take us
in the right direction.
How could I possibly pass through
such a small hole?
I suppose. You have been putting
on some weight and your ass is...
Nin-Nin!
- Are those the intruders?
- That voice!
The Miroku are hardly
a match for us.
Don't underestimate them. They have
defeated our ancestors before.
All right, guards. Lock them up.
Yes, sir!
Yaku! Fubuki!
The Empress has summoned us.
I'll leave the rest to you.
We only get to do boring shit.
Before we take them away,
let's have some fun with them.
What'd you think?
What?!
Come on! No!Just settle down!
That's the best of the carnal world
for you there!
There's no way he would've
resisted that.
Just shut up, Nin-Nin.
Miko, get us out of this, will ya?
We've captured the
remaining Miroku.
Well done. We'll use them
as a sacrifice as well.
And, have you found the brain
of the Shikima?
We're searching throughout
the carnal world...
...but we haven't discovered it yet.
There could be a secret
passage somewhere.
Perhaps the Shikima king knows it!
Even if he does, he won't be
so forthcoming.
All right, let's gather everyone
in the appendix.
We show them to the full power of
the Mahoroba and make him talk.
Yes, ma'am.
We have to find it
as soon as possible.
I will not last much longer
in this body.
I must do whatever I can
to realize my renewal.
We rub this ointment in, and...
I wonder if that would work
with such strong threads.
The fibers will turn to shreds once
the ointment reacts to the urine.
Urine?
I'll just have to take a little leak.
Wait a minute!
Don't worry about it.
Even your little prick comes
in handy sometimes, huh?
I wish you wouldn't say little prick.
Miko, over here, too.
What?! You mean right here?!
Guess I have no choice.
This is more embarrassing than...
...training in the carnal arts!
What a cool and beautiful sound!
We'll have to do something
about that Mahoroba spell.
Father said there's something
in the Miroku Book of Secrets.
But it seems all of the exits from
the carnal world have been sealed.
By Book of Secrets,
do you mean this?
Yeah! That's it!
Why do you have it?!
You just ran out without thinking,
didn't you?
You can be careless. So we thought
we'd take anything important.
But I was in a hurry.
Here it is. Love potion repellant.
Take the moss growing below
the rocks in the country...
...to make a concoction
and rub it into the skin.
It will neutralize the effect
of the potion.
You brought that too, right?
We didn't bring everything.
Is this what you're looking for?
I have it ground up
as a powder here.
I love you, Nin-Nin!
Then, Fubuki...
...I'm sure you can help me out!
Sure! I'll give you some good service!
Even a little prick!
But why did you have it on you?
I was hoping my premature
ejaculation would be cured...
Already?
Well?
The threads tighten as the
juices soak into them.
Dear!
Eventually, they will rip you apart.
You won't be able to endure it.
Tell us where the passage leading
to the Shikima brain is?
Where is it?!
I don't know! Even if I did,
I wouldn't tell you!
The Shikima brain is a holy place
that no one shall enter!
Judging by your attitude,
I believe you know.
Continue with the torture.
Has your proud penis
started to burst?
It's like some kind of lotion.
It feels so good.
You think. I'll tease you
even more, honey.
Look, you two. Quit fooling around
and get serious.
We've got to save my father.
We'll have to put some
in here just in case!
Lay off. I'll do that part myself.
At least with this, we'll be
able to neutralize the spell.
But, Miko. Isn't there anything on
how we're supposed to attack?
Actually, there's nothing
further written in this.
It really is completely blank.
Grandma, I have to go
and rescue Father.
Please protect me.
Miko, the secret of the Mahoroba
is in the Book of Secrets.
What?! But there's
nothing written!
It's just completely blank!
Concentrate hard and make
your love juices flow over it.
My juices from there?
Use your carnal abilities.
The road will then open up.
Wait, Grandma! I need
more information!
Grandma! Grandma!
Anyway, it'll all be clear once
you get those juices flowing.
But, why me?
Why do you think? You are the star,
after all!
That's not fair!
Miss Miko, just give it up.
Come on, get in the mood.
Yes, mood...!
I know, but I can't just like that.
We'll help you with
our carnal abilities.
Carnal pea breaker?
Oh, look. It's already
starting to happen.
Oh, please don't tease me!
Be gentle!
I'll have to tease these parts too.
It's not getting very wet.
You're really going to have
to put your mind into it.
Fubuki...! Go easy on me...!
Oh, please...! I'm going to burst...!
You're well trained.
You won't burst.
It's getting nice and gooey inside.
Doesn't it feel good?
I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to go crazy!
Good. It's getting
quite wet inside.
Concentrate... Now, Miko!
The words are coming out
of the Book of Secrets!
It's about the secrets of
the Mahoroba's body.
We'll concentrate a
little more on that.
Your own lust and
desire swell up...
...until your penis is ripped apart
by the threads.
I can bear this!
Don't underestimate the
Mahoroba's carnal power.
N-No...!
What do you think you're doing?!
It's like a torrent down there.
Maria!
This is incredible!
Once you smell the juices of your
beloved wife, you will give in.
How can you begin to understand...
...the long years of suffering
we've endured...
...hiding these beautiful wings...
...and being doomed
to the underworld!
Give in! Shikima King!
Hold it!
Miko!
So they make their appearance!
Fubuki!
Yaku!
Miko Mido!
Give it up!
All of your cocoons are being
burned by Nin-Nin right now!
You're going to pay for
what you've done!
Shikima! I order you under this contract
to capture these women!
Wh-What?!
Why?! What happened
to our contract?!
I've taken back the seal case.
This is used to summon the carnal
world. It's no absolute.
Take this!
That won't work on me anymore.
Then I'll fuck you myself.
I'll take up your challenge!
Submit to my power!
That's not going to be
enough to get me off.
You monster!
You're not one to call me a monster!
How dare you! I'll annihilate
you and all of the Shikima!
Here I come, Kocho!
Wh-What is this...?!
Carnal power! Lady pole!
That's nothing, Miko Mido.
Ah! That's not fair!
No...!
That feels so good!
Now. You must cum, Miko!
There's no way you can
beat my carnal power.
I-I won't lose this...!
Miss Miko! Your hairpin!
Nin-Nin! Watch my father
and the others!
Got it!
Take this!
I know the weak spot
of the Mahoroba!
Carnal orifice! Hundred seals!
Multiple strikes!
Now every single hole you have
will be sealed forever!
By your own allies, no less!
Why, you!
Stop it, you all!
Help me!
Have you all gone insane?!
How dare you!
How can it not work on Ryokuga?!
If I were not injured, I would also...
...have likely turned against you.
Ryokuga, I cannot blame the power
of my ancestor Miyabi...
...for everything I've done to you.
I just wanted to live in peace.
Stop that.
It's not as though the Mahoroba
clan has been defeated.
Koga, take care of Miss Kocho.
Miko!
I'm sealing this place up!
We have to get out of here!
All right, Father!
I'll use the last of my strength
and bury you all!
I'm taking you with me, Miko!
Farewell, Miss Kocho!
Ryokuga!
Glory to the Mahoroba!
What?! What's the sound?!
Damn!
The fluids are washing through!
Grab hold of the pillars so you
don't get washed down!
Miko!
Okay, Father!
It's coming!
Thank goodness everyone's all right.
What was that flood, anyway?
That was the bodily fluids...
...that cleanse the Shikima realm.
Just as a human has the ability
to regulate its body...
...the brain of the Shikima realm
possesses powers to do the same.
The brain of the Shikima...
Hey, Nin-Nin.
What do you think
happened to Kocho?
She was probably destroyed along
with Shikima's appendix.
I really wonder if that's so.
Now, we can go back to
our sweet life together.
Sweet life?!
Since when have we had
a sweet life together?!
When?! When?!
You're my manservant!
I'm a princess of the Shikima realm!
You're the princess...
That's right! I have to go and
get married at some point!
You better not spread
any malicious gossip!