Produced by Jewdan Subtitles
Translation: Jewdan
Everyone, quiet now!
Quickly calm down.
Is she taking a detour home?
She's been giving me strange looks lately...
She has also been home late,
Why has she been leaving school early?
Too go to this place?
The door is open.
Minna~chan, you are making better and better videos.
Your pussy is so tight and hot today, Minna~chan.
Minna~chan!
Renaane!
You... What are you making Minna~chan do?
Why are you in here?
She, she's like my sister even though
I'm her teacher!
She's here because...
Stealing.
It's just fair compensation.
Minna~chan actually stole such a useless thing.
If we told the school this would
be really bad for her.
Minna~chan!
No, I was forced to...
If these images leak out,
Minna~chan would be finished.
As her sister and teacher, I will...
Take her place...
Don't worry Minna~chan!
Loyal sister, huh?
You also have massive boobs.
I wish I had a teacher like this.