Well, this is what it means.
Does everybody understand?
You have to study
these subjects very well...
because they might be on the exam.
Alright, the rest of the
assignment is due tomorrow.
Does anybody have any questions?
All right.
Then this is it for today.
Uh... it's bright.
- Akiyama, got a minute?
- Yes.
You don't belong to
any college clubs or sports?
- No.
- Then if you don't mind...
I want you to bring this
printed material to Ms. Yoshifuku.
She's been absent from college
since she became a sophomore.
She just called me to tell me
she has a bad flu.
I would like to visit her, but I have
lots of errands to take care of...
so I can't make time for this.
I don't mind doing that.
Where does she live?
Oh, I really appreciate it.
Hey, leda!
Akiyama said it's OK for him to go.
All right, then we'll go together.
You saved my life.
I hesitate going to a woman's
place by myself. You know?
Yeah, I think so too.
But aren't your and Yoshifuku's
houses close to each other?
Yes, we're neighbors,
but she's just moved into town...
and we never taken
the same lecture before.
To be honest with you,
I don't know her very well.
But I remember
she was kind of hot.
Oh, I see.
You weren't in the same lecture
with her before either.
No, but I might have
seen her before...
since we go to the same college.
You must be very popular, huh?
You're very good at sports, and...
W-what are you talking about?
You look like the ideal type
for a woman.
Well, maybe if I belonged to some
kind of popular sports club.
It's suppose to be around here.
Ah... there it is.
- It's a really big house.
- I'll press the intercom.
Ah... y-yeah.
Maybe nobody's home?
- What should we do?
- Well...
Yes?
Ah... yes...
I'm someone who's taking the same
lecture as Miss Noriko Yoshifuku.
My Professor told me to bring
some printed materials for her.
Oh, thank you. Please come in.
I'll open the door right now.
Let's go!
It was gorgeous outside,
but inside is much more than that.
This is really spacious.
It is.
I'm sorry. I was taking a shower.
Please come in.
M-my eyes feasted on her.
What's the matter?
Ah... well... then...
Hey!
I heard you got the flu.
Are you all right now?
Can you wait here?
I will prepare some tea.
Sure.
I'm sorry, but nobody's home now.
Yoshifuku looks totally different
from when I saw her before.
Was she always that hot?
Hey! Akiyama,
what do you think?
W-well, I don't know about before,
but she is beautiful.
She said that
she was taking shower.
Yeah, she did.
Akiyama!
Weren't you just
imagining that right now?
- What?
- Yoshifuku taking a shower.
N-no I wasn't!
Oh! I should give her
the printed materials.
What are you talking about?
Nothing!
Oh... we still haven't
introduced ourselves.
This is Akiyama who is
also in our lecture.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
And I am leda.
These are the printed materials that
the Professor asked me to give you.
Thank you.
I guess you have already
recovered from the flu.
You can come to college
tomorrow then.
leda, isn't tomorrow
the fiirst Saturday of the month?
Ah, it's true.
It's not the flu.
I have a different kind of sickness.
Ah... s-sorry.
I didn't know that.
Yoshifuku...
I have this kind of sickness.
Yoshifuku?
I think dirty things like this
all the time.
Ms. Yoshifuku... what's the matter?
What are you doing?
Come...
Come to me... please...
Hurry...
leda...
Ah... no...
C-can I?
Give it to me...
leda...
C-come!
Please... come to me!
Akiyama.
- See you next week at college.
- OK.
I'll pick you up at your place
on Monday morning.
Thank you.
See you.
See you. Take care.
Akiyama!
See you.
She...
Don't you think her illness is...
the illness that anybody has
in their late teens?
Us too.
Akiyama!
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed for what I said.
You! You!
Ouuuchhh! F-forget it.
No, it's all right.
I understand that.
We have that sickness too.
I can't sleep.
- Good morning!!
- Good morning!
Good morning!
Good morning.
- Thank you for the other day.
- Well...
Yoshifuku, long time no see.
Yes.
I never knew there's such a
good-looking woman in our lecture.
I was in the same lecture
with you last year.
Do you remember me?
You've been absent
since the end of last year.
Have you been sick or something?
Sick...
I've been sick...
Well, well, everybody sit down.
Oh, Yoshifuku,
you've come back to college.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
- I'm glad you recovered.
- Thanks.
Let me take attendance.
- Akiyama.
- Here.
- Leda.
- Shinoda.
- Here.
- Nomura.
- Hashimoto.
- Here.
- Yoshifuku.
- Here!
Yoshifuku... I'm glad she's fine.
OK! Ready!
There are several rules,
but for now we'll just make it...
that if anybody in the outside team
circles around three times, wins!
If you step out from your line,
then you lose.
We will switch the teams when
everybody on the same team loses.
Ready, set, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Takaradon!!
- I'll go over there!
- Leave it to me!
Wait!
You did it!
Yoshifuku is really hot.
Akiyama, thank you.
W-well, Yoshifuku.
What is it?
I'm sorry. I'm a little nervous.
I forgot what I was trying to say.
Please let me know
when you remember.
And... can you come
and visit me again?
All right, let's play!
Let's play Takaradon again.
That was fun, wasn't it?
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- See you.
Uh... I wanted to be
with her little more.
Uh? What's wrong with me?
I really had fun today.
Can we do something
together again tomorrow?
Yeah.
Everybody was very nice to me too.
What's wrong?
This is where I live.
Wow, your house is
very close to mine.
- Then I'll see you...
- Yoshifuku.
I think there was nobody at
your place last time I visited you.
Is it the same today?
No?
Yes.
Uh... then... why don't you
stop by at my place?
It's kind of small, but...
Ah... great.
I'm home.
This is my room.
Can you wait a minute?
I'll clean it up quickly.
Brother!!
Hey!
I told you not to go in my room
without asking me fiirst.
Yeah, yeah.
This is my sister, Miyuki.
This lady is Ms. Yoshifuku.
We're in the same lecture.
Nice to meet you.
Is she your girlfriend?
That's not quite...
We're just...?
Y-yea...
Miyuki, when you go downstairs...
please ask mom to
prepare dinner for her too.
No, don't worry about it.
It's all right.
You have a nice sister.
Ah... yeah.
You have so many interesting
things in your room.
Sorry it's so messy.
No, I didn't mean that.
I have so many things I want to do.
I was in the basketball club
in junior High...
and I joined the tennis club
when I was in High School...
but I want to do other things too,
so time is important to me.
Do you belong to
any clubs right now?
Not at all.
I'm kind of easy going.
So I've already decided that
I won't join any club in college.
I envy you.
You can do the things you decide.
I can't control myself at all.
Yoshifuku...
Make love to me.
Do it as much as you want
this time.
Try to stay quiet.
Brother.
Do you hate me?
No, it's not that
I hate you... but...
You don't like women
who want to do this?
No... it's not that.
I do like you.
That's why I'm happy...
I like you too, Satoshi.
Look at this. It's ripe and juicy.
I'm sick.
Can you cure me?
I did it again.
I'm the sick one.
But... I can't forget about her.
I still can't.
See you tomorrow.
See you!
Of course it is.
Have a good afternoon too.
No, you can't!
Yoo-hoo! Akiyama.
Yoshifuku.
Let's go home together.
I'm alone today too.
What happened to leda?
He has to stay at college
for practice today.
He was selected as a member of
the ball game tournament.
leda is really good
at playing sports.
Akiyama,
you are often by yourself.
I kind of enjoy being alone.
I'm not so good at talking to people.
You must be bored
being with me.
I don't like that kind of
self-evaluation.
I'm a lot like that myself.
Ah... what?
What's wrong with me?
Akiyama, let's go to my place.
This is like a dream.
Since that first day
I was dreaming about this.
just the two of us
together like this.
I was waiting for this too.
We could've done this anytime.
But... I thought leda was...
leda and you are both my friends.
Important friends.
Let's do this again
with the three of us.
Yes.
What did you just do?
Here we go.
Oh, you!