Brother.
Brother, you and Yoshifuku are
having a relationship, aren't you?
Let's see.
How far has the relationship gone?
H-how far?
No, excuse me.
I asked the wrong question.
Yeah, what kinda question is...
Sorry!
I just wanted to ask
how you feel about her?
O-of course... I...
like her.
That's why
we're seeing each other!
Well... I have to study.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
And...
See you next time.
Sure.
Bye.
Yoshifuku.
Ah... yes... this is leda's residence.
Hello.
- Junichi?
- Yoshifuku?
I...
What's the matter?
Your voice is trembling.
I-I did... with your sister.
I'm sorry.
My sister?
Miyuki!!
Hey, Miyuki.
Miyuki, wait a minute.
Did anything happened
at Yoshifuku's?
Get out of here.
I'm going to take a shower now.
I wasn't expecting you to come here.
Miyuki... that's your name?
I'll get right to the point.
The man who you were just with.
Who is he?
Are you talking about
Satoshi Akiyama?
He is in same lecture
with me and leda.
We are all very close friends.
Close enough for kissing?
I saw you and him were kissing.
What did he come here for today?
What were you and he doing?
I hate such an attitude!
If you want to have relationship
with my brother...
please stop doing this.
Satoshi is...
Break up with him!
I don't want a person like you
for my brother's girlfriend.
But I have to accept it.
Because he likes you.
Miyuki...
Don't touch me!!
No... Miyuki...
Leave me alone.
It's not what you think!
I...
I hate you!
No!
Pervert!
Miyuki!
Where is my brother?
He went out.
He said that a friend called him.
Why don't you
eat dinner fast, Miyuki?
Ah, yeah.
I'm sure he went to see her!
I'm not the one he cares about.
Stupid brother!!
Hi, can I get the "A" set?
Here we go!
What's the lunch special today?
- I'll give you a big portion today.
- Really? Lucky!
Sorry to make you wait.
Yoshifuku?
I'm sorry!
What's wrong?
Something's bothering you?
Ah... I...
to tell you the truth...
I raped a woman.
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
I'm all right.
I'm just a little bit surprised.
- That means you did it with...
- Leda's sister.
She seems to know
about our relationship...
I was told to choose
either you or leda...
so I didn't know what to do.
Does leda know about this?
I talked to him earlier.
And?
He was surprised too,
and he took it so seriously.
He told me not to worry,
but I really hate myself.
I couldn't control
any part of myself.
Well...
What is she? Dirty and sick!
Did she suck my brother's...?
Brother...
Brother.
I'm the same as her.
I'm dirty.
I'm like her...
Brother.
I like you, brother.
I also...
want your...
Miyuki!
Can I come in?
Ah, Sorry!
S-stupid! Idiot!
Brother, don't you know
how to knock?
I don't believe this.
S-sorry. I apologize.
Do you know about Yoshifuku?
I heard that she's always
fooling around with men!
Hey, what's that?
She supposed to be having a
relationship with three men now.
Who told you that?
Tell me! Who told you that?
- S-sorry.
- E-excuse us.
What's going on?
With Miyuki, and Yoshifuku...
I'm really confused.
Yoshifuku...
Sometimes she's very cheerful
and sometimes serious.
At least I can help her
when she is upset.
Hey! Akiyama!
Is it true that you are
dating Yoshifuku?
W-well... we're just friends.
Well, then you're
dating with leda too?
I heard it was a rumor,
but we can tell it's true.
Akiyama is not a big deal for us,
but leda is very popular.
I agree. What's your
relationship with them?
Yeah, why don't you make it clear?
- Oh, god! Here we go.
- You have to tell us!
Yeah, tell us!
Stop it.
Well, what do you want to know?
W-we are just...
We heard she is dating
both you and Akiyama.
- Yes, it's a rumor though.
- She is not dating either of us!
He is right.
We're just close friends.
But that's weird.
Yeah, something is strange.
What kind of friendship
do you guys have?
We're...
Hey! Why don't you stop this?
I'm sure everybody has
some kind of problems!
Things you can't easily talk about
with other people.
Is there anything wrong
if we discuss our problems together?
Is that weird?
She found it easy to talk with us
about her problems...
so we listened and talked...
My problem.
A sickness, thinking about
dirty things all the time.
That's it!
What's going on here! Be quiet!
Let's begin the lecture.
Don't worry about that.
Cheer up! Noriko!
Arima is the only person
who's absent?
Let's start the lecture.
leda is a great man.
Everything he does looks cool.
You're acting like you're
the one who's in love with him.
Nice shot!
What?
Are you going home alone?
I'm sorry, I have to stop at
some places today.
All right.
Then be careful going home.
Yes, thank you for today.
No problem!
- See you!
- Take care.
Well, then you're
dating with leda too?
What's your relationship with them?
She's not dating either of us!
He's right.
We're just close friends.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. I always make
trouble for both of you.
I'm home.
Brother.
What's up?
Brother, you wanted to talk to me
about something, didn't you?
Oh... about Yoshifuku, right?
Yoshifuku...
She was just worried about you.
Brother.
M-Miyuki.
It's all your fault.
You and that woman,
Yoshifuku's fault.
I thought you were all mine
until I found out about her.
Miyuki...
Brother...
what do you think about me?
I really care about you.
So I wish I could accept
any kind of feelings from you.
Let's sit down.
But we shouldn't go beyond the border
of what a brother and sister can do.
There's something
we shouldn't express out loud.
I understand.
It may sound selfish, but...
You're not as selfish as I am.
I'm sorry, brother.
Brother, you'll be late for college.
I'm leaving.
I have to hurry.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Miyuki, good morning.
It's really nice day.
Hurry up, Miyuki.
Wait! Brother.
You're always slow.
- Brother and sister.
- Miyuki, come on.
Ah, sorry!!