Where there is light there is shadow.
Those born in darkness die in darkness...
...and there is no one to pick up the corpses.
The year is 199X, the end of the millennium.
The "ninja" are still assassins
and conspirators of the darkness...
...and live in a hidden village.
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl
Book 1
Escaped\NNinja's
Three-Way\NRomance
This way, Suzuka!
We will make it out, Suzuka!
Tsukikage!
Suzuka!
Tsk.
Sir Tsukikage, this is it.
Saint Fly
Suzuka, Tsukikage...
Why are you attempting to become Escaped Ninja?
Lady Youga!
Please turn blind eyes, Lady Youga!
We just want to lead a normal life in the city!
What?
You are leading a normal ninja life here, aren't you?
No! What we mean is...
...a little one-bedroom apartment, poor but happy.
We would go shopping together.
We would play computer games.
We would cook together.
We would share pajamas between the two of us.
A sweet, sweet life for just the two of us.
Right?!
And I'll enter you, just like that.
Enough, shut up! Don't say anymore!
Don't go on and on about stupid things!
Not one more word! Don't be
absurd! Don't even speak!
What, a sweet life? Just the
two of you? Share pajamas?
Cooking together... just wearing an apron?
You do this tonight, you do that tomorrow night?
You do this today, you do that tomorrow?
Be a bit more bold?
Day after day, night after night, fooling around?
Excuse me...
We didn't say all those details...
Shut up, shut up!
You two have succumbed to the
desire for an ordinary life!
You idiots!
Have you forgotten everything
I have done for you two?
Spineless idiot lovebirds!
Ninja girls! Show these two
the price of breaking our code.
Show them what will happen to their bodies!
Suzuka!
Stay still, Sir Tsukikage.
Watch and learn.
Take your eyes off her for a moment,
and Suzuka shall lose her life.
No, let me go!
We shall make an example of
you by shaming you in public!
Suzuka!
How do you like our clan's secret aphrodisiac?
No!
No. My strength is leaving me, yet...
...down there, my pussy is acting
like it's got its own will...
...as if it doesn't belong to me.
I'm going to lose it. No. Not like this.
Not while everyone's watching, including Tsukikage.
I can't hold back anymore!
Damn.
Tsukikage, it must be vexing to you to just watch.
Ninja art, bedchamber secret technique...
Oh!
"The Screw Hell!"
It will directly affect your spinal
cord, regardless of your will.
CENSORED
Fresh\NAutumn\NProduce
No!
Stop it. No, Tsukikage!
Stop it!
Even if I wanted to...
...the aphrodisiac has started to affect me.
No. This is too embarrassing.
Not in front of the others.
No, Tsukikage.
If you keep doing it, I will...
I must not, but it feels so good!
When everybody is watching me like this...
...even their gazes add to my pleasure.
No, no! No more. I...
No!
Have you learned your lesson?
Now that you've learned your lesson, you
had better not plan anything stupid.
Ninja
Do you think we've learned our lesson?
Ready!
Who is that?
Sounds enjoyable. Nay, it sounds demonic!
More, more.
Give me more.
No, more!
Lady Youga, it's Tsukikage and Suzuka.
Ignore them.
Lady Youga, the two of
them committed a shameless act.
Capture them.
Power\N\N\N\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hConnection\N\N\N\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTreasure
We have more victims now.
Find them! Tie them up and bring them here!
Hello, girls!
Look at me. Look at me closely!
They're out of control.
Those kids!
It's so good to be watched.
You two!
You two are banished!
Thus, we happily ended up as Escaped Ninja, and...
- Kuzu Bath House -
...we go to a public bath house every night.
Market
What should I make today?
Daikon - 300 Yen
Tsukikage will come home very hungry.
I'll make sure he will eat a lot.
And then, later tonight, again...
Excuse me!
Yo, Rookie.
Yo!
Come over here and help me.
Right away!
How can I help you?
Be careful, Sir.
Rookie, you surprised me.
Tsukikage has found a very suitable vocation.
A life without harsh codes or training.
On top of all that, I'm with Tsukikage every day.
What? I sense...
...danger!
An assassin. But, why?
Why me?
You're so slow, Suzuka. It took
you a long time to sense me.
You're infatuated with the outside
world. You're getting rusty.
Sagiri?
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl
Sagiri, why?
Can't you tell?
I've come to bring you back!
What?
Suzuka, get ready!
No! I said no!
Are you begging for your life? How ugly!
Of course not.
I don't want you to crack the eggs!
Dare not speak such nonsense!
I'm not kidding, Sagiri! Time out!
Welcome!
Would you like fries with that?
Just kidding.
There you are!
She used the transfiguration trick.
Why does she want to bring me back now?
Good, the eggs are safe.
Welcome home, Suzuka.
What kept you?
Sagiri! Where did you come in from?
Over there.
Please go home!
I have no intention of ever
going back to the ninja village.
Even if Lady Youga ordered me to.
This has nothing to do with Lady Youga.
Huh?
This is between you and me, Suzuka. Just the two of us.
The two of us? What?
How could you say that? You're so mean.
How could you become an Escaped
Ninja without telling me?
Without telling you?
Not only that, but you left with a man!
What?
Those days of ours, back in the ninja village...
What do you make of those days of love?
They were back then...
It was just because you were so aggressive.
I could say I was confused for the time being...
...or I could say I was just
curious at that awkward age.
You know?
How could you say that?!
Or, rather, I should say I was just young...
...or that it was my youth taking over.
You toyed with my heart and body.
Hold on a second, Sagiri.
You make it sound so bad, but, Sagiri...
Your guard is low!
Damn!
I can't move!
I tricked you, Suzuka.
I'll take my time, and remind your body...
...what it was like when your youth took over.
I will make sure you will never
be able to forget about me.
Then you will want to come back for sure.
All right!
Tie this up, and you can go home.
Okay.
Sagiri...
You like it here...
And here...
No.
No!
Don't attack all my sensitive areas.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I know all your weak spots, Suzuka.
No, no!
More, more.
No, Sagiri.
No.
Now...
Bedchamber secret technique, "Spectral Penal Shape!"
How do you like it?
I shall penetrate you with my mental energy.
No!
Do you like it, Suzuka?
You like it, Suzuka, don't you?
No more.
Hey, stop it, Sagiri!
It's already...
No, we've just begun.
It's about the time Tsukikage comes home.
Once I show you to Tsukikage like this...
...then you're all mine.
Suzuka! You prefer a girl to me?!
Abandoned in the big city, Suzuka,
you'll have only one choice...
Coming back to the ninja village. Back to me.
How does it feel to be raped on the bed...
...where you make love with Tsukikage every night?
No. Not like that. Not every night.
Every night and every morning!
You!
Do you think you're in any
position to talk back to me?
Here we go.
It sounds like he's back.
No.
No, don't come home!
What if Tsukikage sees me like this?
Go ahead, make noise to welcome him.
He will hate me!
- Suzuka, I'm home!
Suzuka?
No!
I'm home.
Suzuka?
This is it!
Suzuka!
Don't look!
Suzuka...
Threesome!
Sagiri! Long time, no see!
Tsukikage!
You two are having fun! Let me join you!
How dare you?
So you went for my Suzuka, Sagiri...
I compliment you for your bravery.
No, Suzuka is mine!
Shut up, shut up!
A woman dares to attack another
man's woman, lusty and sensual...
...skin on soft skin, is it a sigh
or a moan? This is a forbidden love.
Tsukikage, at your service.
I shall represent the Moon...
...and punish you!
Here I come, "Secret Sword, Shadow Destroyer!"
Ouch! Stop it, Tsukikage!
You're so heavy.
Soon enough, both of you will be coming under me!
Who would ever come for you!
We shall see.
I haven't wasted my days and
nights doing it with a ninja girl.
Hey, wait...
"Electric Light, Chinese Bamboo One-Letter Elimination!"
"Lightning Gravity Throw!"
"Electron Full Moon Strike!"
And now, "Plasma Twist!"
I have no idea what...
Sagiri, what is this slutty noise of yours?
No way. I won't give in to a man...
But what is this?
My core is undulating.
It feels like something is about to flood.
No. What's going on?
Sagiri's force is gathering.
Combined with Tsukikage's movement,
it's creating a huge tidal wave.
No, don't!
Tsukikage, I...
Come!
Tsukikage!
Damn! A defeat! But remember...
Ouch! My hip!
I won't let you get away with this.
Hey, Tsukikage.
Yeah?
Don't you want to ask me anything?
Suzuka, who do you love most right now?
You, of course.
Right?
So why not leave it at that?
We said goodbye to our past
when we left the ninja village.
We only have the present and the future.
Tsukikage!
Hey, you.
As for me, I've had ten or twenty ninja girls.
What did you say?
Twenty?
Ten or twenty?
In the ninja village?
No, I meant...
What do you mean by that?
It backfired.
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl
Book 2
Preview
It's me. Did you enjoy it?
Did I take my clothes off too much?
I'll rip her clothes off for the sake of art.
Now, a preview while I change my clothes.
To my surprise, Sagiri appears before us again.
And she's in love with Tsukikage!
She does this, she does that,
she just doesn't know when to quit.
Hey, Sagiri, keep your hands off of Tsukikage.
Karakuri Ninja Girl Book 2,
Ninja Girl Strikes Back: The Honey Hell
Ninja\NGirl\NStrikes\NBack
The\NHoney\NHell
Check it out!