Where there is light there is shadow.
Those born in darkness die in darkness...
...and there is no one to pick up the corpses.
The year is 199X, the end of the millennium.
The "ninja" are still assassins
and conspirators of the darkness...
...and live in a hidden village.
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl
Book 2
Ninja\NGirl\NStrikes\NBack
The\NHoney\NHell
Ninja
Saint Fly
Weird.
Lady Youga comes in and out from here.
There must be a trick door somewhere.
I shall search more!
I'm Haniwa.
I found them.
Fire\NScroll
Human\NScroll
Heaven\NScroll
Earth\NScroll
Found it.
Sagiri!
I knew you were not concentrating
on your recent training.
I also knew you were following me around...
...waiting for an opportunity.
What do you have in your clothes?
Is that a secret scroll...
...handed down from generation to
generation in this ninja village?
Or is it our secret treasure,
"Super Constipation Relief?"
If you want it, you may have it.
If you can get out of this village alive!
Follow her!
Listen, everybody.
While training here, you may not
have evil thoughts or delusions.
Our ancestors have bestowed
upon us hidden techniques...
...secret tricks, curses...
...even physical techniques, but
our presence as assassins of shadows...
...is only attainable if each
one of us strives day and night...
...never tiring in exerting ourselves.
To kill a person, you not only
need the appropriate technique...
...you will also need to learn to
shut out doubt, pity, even anger...
...and reach the state of absolute enlightenment.
If you cannot free yourself
from your own earthly desires...
...you are not qualified to stay here!
I won't stop you.
If you want to leave, leave!
Silence....
The "Body Switch Technique?"
Impressive.
Bath
Did I make you wait?
No.
I'm all warmed up.
Did you clean yourself well, Suzuka?
Of course!
I'm a little lady, squeaky clean
all over, and smelling of soap.
Tomorrow is Sunday, so let's do
it slow and thorough tonight...
Come on, Tsukikage, you're
always slow and thorough.
This is the best.
It's so warm, and it feels so good.
I'll make you feel even better tonight.
Tsukikage, that's all you think about.
What's wrong?
Someone is over there. Shh!
Sagiri?
Hey, Suzuka.
Why are you here?
Here she is again.
I am an Escaped Ninja now too.
Hey!
Sagiri! Sagiri!
Sagiri, are you up?
You surprised us last night..
...showing up all of the sudden
with your clothes in tatters.
You were lucky you were not hurt too badly.
Please!
Has your man been injured or something?
You guys have to be careful.
No, nothing like that.
Okay, here's the usual. It's on the house today.
Take care.
She remembers us...
Something's not right.
Why did Sagiri escape?
She is so full of herself, so
insolent, haughty, and brash.
Not to mention extremely self-centered.
How could she do something
that could endanger her life?
You just don't know when to quit.
You had to escape just to come after Suzuka?
You might want to give up this futile pursuit.
That's not it.
No, Tsukikage. I...
I love you, Tsukikage.
I just can't forget you.
I just can't forget that night...
...when you taught me the joy of being a woman.
You idiot.
Since the moment you lit up
the sensual energy hidden in me...
...I have lost all reason.
My heart is flip-flopping.
My body is writhing with desire.
So, Tsukikage...
Come on.
Come on, Tsukikage.
You will be mine.
Mine, mine, mine.
Something is indeed wrong.
Okay! I'm going to interrogate her.
I'm home. I got some medicine...
No! What are you doing?
No! Don't touch Tsukikage!
Tsukikage, you too?!
Say something.
Tsukikage?
What did you do to Tsukikage, Sagiri?
Guess. But soon Tsukikage will be mine.
Why do you have to keep on bothering us?
Oh no, it's Tsukikage's fault.
Step aside!
What are you talking about? No!
Hey! Stay away, Sagiri!
Step aside!
Ever since that night, my heart
has been stolen by Tsukikage.
So, in return, I decided to
steal Tsukikage from you.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Stay away from him.
Shut up!
Incredibly powerful.
I can do anything.
Love is blind. You can do anything for love.
And in love, the winner takes all!
You're wasting your time.
No! You must be kidding!
Look, he's so big for me!
Tsukikage!
No way!
Right! Ninja girl's secret hidden technique!
Devil Viper Aphrodisiac Technique
"Devil Viper Aphrodisiac Technique!"
After I suck him off,
Tsukikage will be my slave.
You are playing foul, Sagiri!
How dare you use techniques for this!
Who said we can't?
By the way, Suzuka, I want you
to enjoy it a little as well.
What did you do to me?
You will soon find out.
Right, Tsukikage?
How about it, Suzuka? Do you feel it?
The same pleasure that
Tsukikage is enjoying right now?
You will experience it with
Tsukikage as I take his backbone out.
Enjoy!
No!
No, not like this.
My body is responding.
Are you not happy now, Suzuka?
Finally, you are literally one
with Tsukikage, body and soul.
It will just be a minute,
so why don't you enjoy it?
Can you feel it?
How much Tsukikage is enjoying
my tongue and fingers?
Once he experiences this, he will
never be able to be without me.
She's not even touching me...
...yet she's licking my nerve endings directly.
Is Tsukikage feeling the same sensation?
Sagiri, what's the point of doing this?
Do you want a puppet with the face of Tsukikage?
Say whatever you want while you can.
Soon you will be swallowed in
waves of pleasure and be quiet.
Can you hold off until
Tsukikage falls for me, Suzuka?
I know I'm forcing this.
But how else could I come
between the two of you?
This is the only way.
I may not have wanted it, but he is my first man.
How could I ever forget him?
No more. I'm going crazy.
Tsukikage.
Suzuka is reaching her end.
Come on, Tsukikage. Come. Come a lot.
Come and be mine.
Come for me!
No, no, no, no!
You have to be kidding.
Tsukikage, why don't you come?
Tsukikage?
Enough already, Sagiri. You were awesome.
Tsukikage.
But I am no good unless it is with Suzuka.
How could you defeat that technique?
That was nothing compared to
the love between the two of us.
Tsukikage!
Corny...
Just kidding.
Romance begins when two hearts
are attracted to each other.
You just can't force your feelings.
It was quite close, though.
Yes, if you have to force your
feelings, you're still a child.
You can't use secret ninja techniques!
Say whatever you want!
Well, you have become
an Escaped Ninja, after all.
Why don't you take your time
to look at the world around you?
This is so discouraging.
I know a kind of job you might be good at...
...though it might be a bit hard
to find a man as cool as I am.
You're the coolest!
I am, aren't I?
Okay, okay, I get it.
I'm the fifth wheel. Okay.
What's the point of pursuing him? It's hopeless.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Sagiri...
Bye bye, Tsukikage.
Watch it.
Hey! You're getting slow, Suzuka.
That wasn't fair! You threw shuriken!
What are you mumbling about?
We have to do it for real, or you'll go soft.
You've been gaining weight, haven't you?
Ouch!
Just because you're an Escaped Ninja...
...doesn't mean you can spend
the days without working.
You are so not romantic.
I just wanted to spend time out here
enjoying the cherry blossoms with you.
Look. Petals lightly-colored,
floating against the night sky...
It's so romantic.
Speaking of romance...
Huh?
Tsukikage...
"Crimson flowers shower onto the soft bare skin."
This is a poem.
You...
Oh, Tsukikage. I'm cold.
Don't worry. I'll do this to you...
Oh, Tsukikage. I'm hot.
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl
I'm cold and trembling.
What? A cold?
Do I have one?
Tsukikage!
Is this where you introduced Sagiri for work?
Yeah, I introduced her there.
How come you know of a place like this?
How come? Well...
I was studying the custom of the ordinary people.
Hey, Tsukikage! You said I was the only one!
Are you listening to me?
Tsukikage! What's wrong? Tsukikage!
Welcome!
Mr. Teacher, please be gentle with me.
Hello! What seems to be the problem today?
Okay, let's perform an operation.
Attention please, thank you
for boarding Fuck-Pack Airlines.
So Mister, do you want the
first class special service?
So many men are way more awesome than Tsukikage!
Bigger, better lovers!
Could this be...
heavenly
employment
...my life's calling?!
Burn! Good woman!
I've known all this time!
surely a lewd fate
M  ♥  A  ♥  N
prostitution!
I haven't seen the two of them in a while.
I wonder how they are doing.
What? Colds? Both of you?
It's so nice out there and I came
all this way to play with you...
...but look at yourselves!
But we were up in the cherry tree.
It was so hot at night, so we
kicked off the blanket...
...and we were both naked so
we got colds in the morning.
The water was not hot
enough at the public bath...
You're so soft... How would I ever
know that you both used to be ninjas?
I know you two are passing the cold back and forth.
Tsukikage, your temperature is not coming down.
I'm done for.
Suzuka, you know something?
After a man has a fever for too many days...
...I heard his cock will no longer get hard.
No, no way!
No, Tsukikage, you have to cool yourself!
What are you doing?
You have to cool yourself, too.
This won't work. I wanted to play with them...
...but I don't want to catch a cold myself.
See you later. Take care.
Hmm?
Oh yeah!
I have a good medicine.
It's a ninja medicine, so it is
the best! Do you know about these?
I don't remember them well.
I rarely got colds.
Okay, take care.
It's bitter!
What was that?
I'm getting warm.
Not warm...
I'm...
Maybe that medicine was...
She tricked us.
I'm hot!
Something is weird about me.
Me too.
My body! Help me!
What's going on? We haven't done anything yet!
Suzuka!
Tsukikage!
I can't.
Already?
No! Not yet.
Awesome!
It's hotter than usual.
So hot. So hot.
Suzuka.
Again?
I think we have overcome our fever...
...but Tsukikage is not responding to me!
I think we just did it too many times.
"Dear Lady Youga, how are you?"
"What's new and exciting in the ninja village?"
"Tsukikage and I came out of
our fever and we are doing fine."
"Tsukikage works hard, and
I am a cute newlywed wife..."
"...but we never forget the
ninja techniques and pride."
"We train rigorously everyday,
and get along fine with Sagiri."
"We would like to visit you
and bring some souvenirs."
"Well, until then..."
"...goodbye. Suzuka."
Karakuri\NNinja\NGirl