As the years advance,
my hearing declines.
My legs are not
what they used to be.
I can't stop getting uglier.
The women I loved are getting
grey hair and wrinkles.
All this irritates me constantly.
If I go on living in this world...
I don't think things
will get any better.
Let's go!
THE SENSUALIST
by Saikaku Ihara
Planning by
Ren Usami
Producers: Ren Usami, Tsunemasa
Hatano and Zuza Hagiwara
Screenplay by
Eiichi Yamamoto
Animators: Tomoko Ogawa
Masaharu Endo and Hiroyuki Kondo
Music by Keiju Ishikawa
Sound by Susumu Aketagawa
Camera by Minoru Fujita
Edited by Kenichi Takashima
Directed by
Yukio Abe
Fashion Shop
"DREAM"
Hey, I'll go in for a bit.
I'll wait.
Ah, Juzo the Tailor!
Yes, that's me.
So, is the master in?
He is.
I'm leaving for Edo,
so I came to greet him.
Hey, go and ask
the Master, if...
Yes!
Please don't bother him.
Would you just tell him so?
I'll be back soon.
Juzo?
Yonosuke
(aged 54)
Manager!
Yes.
Manager?
Yes!
Give him some money.
Yes, sir.
Master, I didn't come for that.
I know. I just want to help.
Take this.
Thank you very much.
What brings you to Edo?
I'm going to sleep
with Komurasaki...
...the most renowned
courtesan.
Huh?
What?
I was drunk at a party...
I said I'd sleep with Komurasaki
at our first meeting.
Then the party host made me a bet.
At your first meeting?
Umm, yeah...
Uhei the Clown is with
me to watch the results.
Tell me, Juzo...
Yes.
What did you bet?
If I succeed, I'll get
one of the villas.
And if not?
Well...
What then?
Listen, Juzo!
Yes.
Those courtesans are special.
Once, they were only
for feudal lords...
They are well taught
and very proud.
They are versed in the arts,
very sophisticated.
Since recently, the also
receive us merchants...
...but certainly not into
their beds, right away!
No bed at the first meeting?!
No workers accepted.
Sorry to say, but you
can't even meet her!
He knew that and forced
me to bet my manhood!
Who is this malicious man?
He made me promise
not to tell his name.
What a shame!
Manager!
Manager, I'll accompany
him to Edo.
What?!
What?
His father had a silver mine.
He came to Kyoto
with a big fortune...
He liked wine
and women.
His name was
Mr. Dream.
He redeemed the courtesan
who gave him a son, Yonosuke.
Like his father, Yonosuke
was precocious...
At the age of seven he got laid...
At the age of nine, he started
learning business at a relative's...
He also learned homosexuality.
At the age of eleven,
he bought his first whores.
No night was spent alone, then.
Neighborhood girls, wives, whores...
As long as she was
a woman, he didn't care.
I came with you...
...because I pitied you probably
losing your manhood.
I thought I'd arrange that
you can see her, at least.
It sure won't be easy.
Even if you get
a chance and fail...
Accept your fate.
You know...
Y-yes.
Don't talk like that.
Behave like a rich merchant
in front of the others.
Yes.
This is the landmark tree.
The red light district
is over there.
So this is the famous gate to
Yoshiwara, the red light district.
Ordinary whores are
in every brothel here.
...but courtesans must be
called to a tea house.
Well, let's go!
Hey, wait for me!
You want Komurasaki?
Yes.
This gentleman has come
to Edo for the first time.
He wants her at any
cost to remember Edo.
We'll gladly be at your service.
However, Komurasaki
is so popular...
I'm afraid you'll have to
wait for four or five days.
We know that, right?
Y-yes!
At the age of 1 8, Yonosuke
was sent to the Edo branch
On his way, he bought a whore
at every post town.
He took a long time.
In Edo, he promptly
tried out all the brothels.
He went with boys and girls....
...and ended up staying weeks
at Yoshiwara.
Even his father disowned him.
So, he became a monk.
Be he wasn't religious
even for a week.
Lust overcame him.
He called peddlers and the like
into his temple day and night...
Gentlemen, the courtesan is
on the way here.
It won't be long now!
Thank you.
Welcome.
Yuzo, are you ready?
Yes.
I'm ready.
Not that. I mean the shroud
for your thing.
Are you wearing the red loin cloth
and rosary I gave you?
Yes.
Show me!
Here?
Yeah, go ahead!
Here, sir?
Great!
I'm leaving.
But Sir...
Brace up.
You're the customer.
At the age of 20, still disowned,
he went to Osaka...
...Ieading a poor laborer's life.
Lust didn't leave him alone
all this time.
He then started 15 years
of roaming.
At the age of 22, he was
peddling fish...
Whenever he wasn't
frequenting brothels.
At the age of 25, he worked
in a gold mine.
But his dream of making a fortune
didn't come true.
He roamed through Northern Japan,
making love to all kinds of women.
At the age of 27, he forced
himself on a shrine maiden.
As a penalty, half of his hair was shaven
off and he was thrown into jail.
He was released on amnesty
after a year.
Wow! This is real happiness!
You two are very beautiful.
Why is the courtesan so late?
What?
You mean me?!
All right! All right!
I'm afraid he is drunk.
Did you like that?
I'm generous!
My money!
Hehehe...
Oh, my!
Ahahaha!
I won't mind.
Gentlemen!
The courtesan is here!
Well, have a drink?
Whisper...
She won't accept his cup
at the first meeting.
Go ahead, take this!
Huh! Oh!
I'll pour you some.
Oh my god!
Please do relax.
Would you continue while
I go and change my clothes?
At the age of 33, his father
died, forgiving him.
He was left with
a huge legacy.
His mother let him be.
He then, as it were, conquered
the red light districts of Japan.
He slept with every
famous courtesan...
...attaining the very zenith
of sensuality.
Since the age of seven until that of sixty
he knew as many as 3742 women.
Also the men he touched add
up to as many as 725.
He is sophisticated now.
Yonosuke leaves no posterity.
He frittered away his fortune
on sensuality with women and men.
What?! You had another
identical kimono!
What consideration!
What preparedness!
Sir!
Would you follow me?
This way.
Uhhh... Where
are we going?
Well, then.
Ummm... Well...
Well, then!
Huh? No! Wait a second!
Hold on!
I didn't... I didn't do
that intentionally.
You don't have to apologize.
Why don't you come closer?
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Funny guy!
Weird guy!
Come closer.
Fashion Shop "Dream"
Edo Branch
Here!
So, the courtesan wrote this
on your loin-cloth.
Yes, as proof!
"Hereby, I admit that I slept with
Juzo. Signed Komurasaki"
Did you witness that?
Yes, sir.
Are you sure?
Both my honor and manhood
have been saved.
Thank you, sir.
I'm impressed...
Thank you very much.
Look, Komurasaki...
Yes?
You agreed to sleep with me only
at our third meeting.
Why did you favor Juzo?
He seemed simple enough to
accept a foolish bet.
I hated the one who put him on.
That's why I gave him
a special favor.
You were right. I also helped him
out of spite for the one.
You have sharp eyes,
Komurasaki.
You're beautiful, smart
and spirited.
You're the best of all,
I think I'm in...!
Love me now,
Yonosuke!
Komurasaki!
You want more?
Yes!
Me too!
Even if we end up in hell,
we'll be together forever!
Yes!
Yonusuke...
Sorry.
As the years advance,
my hearing declines.
I can't stop getting uglier.
The women I loved are getting
grey hair and wrinkles.
All this irritates me constantly.
If I go on living in this world...
I don't think things
will get any better.
The boat is ready, sir!
Good.
Let's have fun all the way.
There may be no returning.
Where are we going?
We'll go find
a women's island.
You shall have all the women
you like there.
Fine! I won't mind dying there,
after using up my juices!
That will be real pleasure
for a man!
Let's follow the master!