No!
That hurt!
Stop it!
No!
Princess 69, Lesson 4: Last Stage
Where there's light, there's dark.
Ask the light, and the dark will answer...
Tomomi, you're the last member
of the Dark Gymnastics Team!
No!
It's time for initiation!
Make sure to speak
clearly and carefully.
What's the matter, huh?
Turn your head towards the mike.
Let's begin the last stage!
Hold it tight, or else you get shocked.
Come on, hold it deeper than that!
It feels great!
Niku, take a look at Tomo's pussy!
Her pussy is soaked just
from sucking your dick!
What a perverted girl you are, Tomo!
You're being forced into this
and you're getting turned on...
Girls like you are called masochistic!
You're a pervert!
She's really tight!
You feel good, don't you, Tomo?
We'll make you feel even better...
...with our Dark Gymnastics!
Tomo is really feeling it!
Don't close your eyes!
Let Niku see your
cute slutty face, Tomo.
You're so cute, Tomomi!
It feels nice and cold, doesn't it?
I'm going to keep giving you more.
It's Niku's semen cocktail.
Wow, her stomach is bursting!
What's the matter, your
mouth is slacking off!
This is great, it's like having
a electrified meat puppet!
Oh, Niku, push it deeper!
I'm getting great pictures!
Are you happy Tomo?
Tomo, you're dripping!
Niku, punish Tomo some more!
You got it!
I'm going to give you plenty
of my come, don't worry.
Tomo, I'm jealous.
Give her all of your come, Niku!
Tomomi started sucking on
her own and won't let go!
Give her more, Niku!
All right!
I bet you love the feeling!
You little slut!
Tomo's about to come!
Tomo can come just from sucking dick.
She's a real slut, all right!
With such a cute face,
how low can this girl go?
She wanted my cock
from the very beginning!
You were destined to be punished!
Get a good shot of it!
Got it, Niku!
Leave it to me!
O-Okay, here it comes!
Tomomi is really coming from that!
Gross!
Tomomi, you are a real slut.
Niku, we got the shot!
Tomo looks like a fish out of water!
We can sell this for a lot.
Feel good, Niku?
Yeah, It's like nothing I've ever had.
It's amazing...
That's great, Niku!
You have to press harder on her stomach.
She's really good at resisting.
You better give up and shit yourself.
If you hold it for too long,
you'll hurt your stomach!
I'm about to blow here!
Already, Niku?
Go ahead and release.
That's a lot, Niku!
Her pussy is so slippery.
She's ready.
What is it?
If you have something to
say to us, we're listening.
Be gentle...
Please...
Please be gentle...
I don't like pain...
Please, Nikusuke...
I have to poop...
Let me go to the toilet...
Please, let me go to the toilet.
Please, Master Nikusuke...
Miku, what do we do?
I never seen Tomomi like
this, it's a little freaky.
Niku, you got a lot
to learn about women.
It's okay.
Tomo loves this, and she's
always wanted to do this...
In other words...
Do it.
No!
Please, don't hurt me!
That's true, Tomomi is
a true slut after all.
That's right. Everyone's like that.
Well it's settled then.
Please don't!
Here we go!
I told you stop!
No, Nikusuke, please stop!
We did it!
Now Tomo is a woman!
Aren't you glad, Tomo.
Her insides are so hot!
It's awesome!
I finally screwed the
daughter of the Shirakawas!
Now all I have to do is get the bitch
pregnant, and then it's life on easy street!
Not inside!
Please!
If it's a boy, Nikumaru,
if it's a girl, Nikuhime.
No!
Okay, I'll just come a little.
There you go!
No!
I'm being sucked in!
I never...
I'll never give birth to your child...
Oh yeah?
How long will you be
saying that, I wonder?
Too early to go to sleep.
Miss Tomomi should
almost be ready to shit.
Make sure they get that on tape.
Stop!
Here, here!
No!
I don't want to!
My stomach hurts!
Give it up, Tomomi.
Let it all out, Tomomi.
It feels great.
Come on...
No, stop!
No!
Come on, what's the matter?
I can't hold it!
T-Tomo...
You finally accepted it, Tomomi.
It's coming.
It's all coming out.
Good, you're being honest.
I'm about to blow too!
I'm coming!
Oh, Mistress, breakfast
will be ready soon.
I can not come to the phone right now.
If you wish to leave a message,
leave it after the beep...
Papa...
No one can come to the phone.
You have 30 seconds after the
beep to leave your message...
Mama...
Yu Aizawa, Wakana
Sakurai, Madoka Senya...
...Stupid Niku, Miku
Haoka, Kozue Morishita...
You are out of power. Please recharge.
I'm revived!
M-Mistress!
Mistress!
We were worried, did
something happen to you?
Round up all the girls of
the Dark Gymnastics Club.
Now!
Yes, ma'am!
Go!
Hello, this is Sakurai.
I see Shirakawa's asking me to...
Sure, no problem.
I-I'd love to!
I see, Tomo...
I gotcha, it starts tonight...
Count me in.
Nikusuke Doguro
Oooh, no!
Don't, Nikusuke...
I-I can't take anymore!
Ouch!
Let's do it!
Come on, Nikusuke, we are waiting.
Of course you're going
to love me, right?
Doguro, I can't wait anymore.
I switched to contacts for
you, Professor, do you like it?
This man is mine!
Don't you lay a hand on him!
Hey Kozue!
I'm first!
Feel my pussy!
Shut the hell up over there!
We're sorry!
Have a nice day!
Let's go Professor.
We're going now.
Have a nice day.
Okay, time to clean.
Laundry, laundry...
Did you see how Nikusuke looked?
Hey, Tomo?
Tomo, how do you feel about Niku?
I don't know.
I thought that I liked Niku.
Or rather I was trying to like him.
No matter what was done to me, I
always wanted to be on his side.
That's why I'm here now.
When I do that, I'm a little happier.
I wonder if it's same for them.
I don't know...
Hey, Tomo, what do you think?
Why are you here, Tomo?
Do you want to know why I'm here?
It's simple.
It's because he's in love with me.
That's why I'm here.
That low life couldn't think
of any other way to get women!
I accepted his true nature,
so he has to accept mine.
I'll completely turn him into
the kind of guy that I like.
I see.
So that's it...
That's right, everyone's like that.
I see...
That's why everyone is...
Now, Professor Doguro, we're
starting your new diet today.
No more carbohydrate as of today.
Especially those beef bowls.
So that's it, that's why everyone is...
All right!
You two!
Yes!
Instead of staring off, can
you two please help me here?
Sure!
Fine, fine.
Coming!
Where do we start?
Rape is a crime punishable by law.