Unforgivable...
A student and teacher
doing such a thing...
Doing such a thing...
How cute.
So, do we know who this boy is?
Yes
Who?
That is a picture of the 32nd All
Japan Gymnastics Competition Champion...
...who also won the first place
in the individual male section...
...Nikusuke Doguro.
This is Nikusuke?
Yes, that's right.
Mistress?
I-I see...
This is N-Nikusuke...
I've gotten a good idea!
Princess 69, Lesson 3: Virgin Rondo
No good!
I don't know what I should do!
I know Wakana wouldn't
go like Kozue did...
Guess I have no choice
except to talk to Tomomi...
Niku!
Oh, Miku, what's up?
I'll make breakfast for you.
I'm going to borrow your kitchen.
H-Hey, Miku...
If you're going to
come, at least tell me...
D-Don't tell me you came all
the way here dressed like that.
Sure did.
H-Hey Miku.
I told you...
I'm on your side.
You can... give it to me harder.
Please make me your slut.
I haven't seen you in a while,
and you've gotten quite naughty.
You must've missed
me badly, haven't you?
You can come inside me!
Give me your sperm!
Shoot your load inside me!
W-Wow...
There's so much!
That was good...
But, Miku, you're
really an amazing girl.
You're really starting to
understand what a man needs.
R-Really?
I'm so happy.
But still, you need a bit more
work, so we'll continue training.
Okay!
M-Mistress...
Katsuragi!
I suddenly don't feel very well.
I wonder why...
Take it out.
Huh?
The car, you idiot!
Y-Yes, miss!
That idiot.
I was going to bring him
something, but forget that.
He can go eat a beef bowl
with that little poor girl!
Hey.
Yes!
What are you laughing at?
Huh?
Don't irritate me further, or
I'll have my father fire you!
Drive faster.
You're going to make me late.
Yes, Mistress...
Miku is absent today, again...
So is Yu...
Um, Professor?
Yes?
I have something I'd
like to talk to you about...
Of course, what is it?
Not here...
Um...
I understand.
Then, come to the Student
Council Meeting Room later.
Is that okay?
Y-Yes...
It's not that...
I wanted to tell you...
I don't expect you to
forgive me for what I did.
But I...
I really like the professor...
That much?
I don't know.
I just don't know.
But, but...
Well then...
That's more of a reason
to do something about him.
If we don't do something, Nikusuke
is going to be a slave for life!
Yu...
It's true!
I saw it!
Something very terrifying...
Please, contact the police!
Wait, Madoka.
Give me a little more time.
This is a very delicate situation
and needs to be handled carefully.
A slight mistake could
lead to terrible results.
Why are you protecting Professor Doguro?
I'll do this myself.
Oh.
How convenient.
Did you tell her?
Did you tell someone besides Wakana?
You saw, right?
I haven't told anyone
besides Professor Wakana.
But you won't get away with this!
I have to find out the truth.
Katsuhiko...
Please, give me courage.
So this is Wakana's fiance.
Pretty pathetic.
Look who's talking.
So, you sure she'll come?
She'll come.
She's an idiot.
I am going to ruin your marriage plans.
I'll give you the best wedding ceremony.
Is anyone here?
Professor Wakana!
T-Tomomi...
What are you doing,
standing around in the dark?
And what's...
This?
Isn't it beautiful?
It's designed by Coco Chanail.
It's custom made, and
special ordered by my dad!
Wow, it's gorgeous...
I think it would look great on you!
Me?
Yu, come on!
Yeah yeah.
K-Katsuhiko?
I think your fiance is a little pent up.
"To My Dearest Darling...
I'm in a special mood today.
So tonight, I'll give you
what you've always wanted.
I'll be waiting at the usual
time after work, behind the gym.
Your Wakana.
P.S. - I love
you Ka-chan!"
I sent this mail, and
the guy came running!
What an idiot!
Tomo!
What?
This guy is so hard he's about to blow!
If we don't let him come
soon I'll feel sorry for him.
Not yet!
We just started!
Make him wait for it!
W-Why...
Why did you?
I know that I'm not the best teacher...
But I've been trying my
hardest for all of you!
We spent time together on this campus.
I wanted to give you as many
good experiences as possible...
...so you'd grow up to be
role models from this school.
That's all I wanted!
It's true!
Professor Doguro and I were
only thinking about your future!
Nikusuke!
Yes.
Oh, hello Professor
Wakana, long time no see.
Wow, I'm proud that you
think that highly of me.
Sure makes me glad I'm a teacher.
Hey, Madoka, say hello
to Professor Wakana.
Professor...
Help me...
No!
No, please stop!
Please stop doing such horrible things!
That's fine...
...but you are not to say one word
about the Dark Gymnastics Club.
Yes, of course!
And in exchange...
...we'll give you a wedding ceremony...
...right here, right now.
What?
But not to your current fiance...
But to the man you used to love!
Professor, you look beautiful.
Now listen, don't let go of the dress.
It's really expensive,
so don't get it dirty!
If you stain it, even a little,
I'll make you pay for it...
...30 million yen.
And you over there!
You get to tease the one in glasses.
If you don't do well, that
girl is going to bite it off.
Here, now use these.
It's okay, I'll teach you how.
No!
This tiny lump I feel on my fingers...
You must have a very sensitive G-spot.
She may have an innocent face but
I'm sure she masturbates at home!
N-No, I don't!
I don't do that!
Liar!
She's still holding onto
Nikusuke's picture after all.
I bet she's screaming, "Nikusuke,
I'm coming!" at home at night.
I see, I see!
Poor Wakana's frustrated.
There's nothing normal
about how wet she is.
Look, it's a flood down there!
Damn that Wakana!
She betrayed me!
Two can play the game!
Damn it!
You little bitches!
I'll show you!
No!
Stop Katsuhiko!
We're ready over here.
W-What are you doing?
Bad girls must be punished!
Here's some more!
Nice reaction!
You look like you
want to pee, don't you?
That's great, you're
sexy as hell, Wakana!
Don't look!
I'm going to...
Stop, it's coming out!
I'm going to pee!
Don't look, please!
Here's the big finish!
You were very cute, Wakana.
The judges would definitely
give you 10's for that!
Silly Niku.
Put some more into it!
The loser will be punished!
At times like these
your daily practices pay off.
This is a lot more practical
than practicing for the club!
Come on, Madoka!
You can do it!
If you lose, you'll become like Yu!
Please, give me your come.
Shoot inside my mouth!
G-Good, I'll give you plenty!
Amazing, Madoka is definitely a pro.
Way to go, Madoka!
I'm impressed!
I think we found out who'll be punished.
Look at her pussy,
it's wet again already!
You just want to do it
with Nikusuke, don't you?
Niku, this guy's at his
limit, he's about to come!
So I see.
Okay, Kozue, prepare the punishment.
Gotcha!
Professor, you can't make Niku come
unless you take him deeper than that!
Well, which will it be?
Give it to me.
I want your come, Professor Doguro...
Wakana, how could you!
Over here too!
Okay, Kozue.
Who won?
L-lt's a tie!
Well...
Then you both get punished!
What is with this girl?
Her pussy is dripping.
She is definitely a true masochist.
Wake up!
Come here!
It hurts!
No, that hurts!
Amazing, my hips won't stop!
I can't stop, either!
My meat puppet feels great!
It's like a dream come true!
It's so tight...
This one, too!
She's amazing!
I can come inside her, right?
Stop!
Someone please stop him!
Don't worry, we'll pay
for your abortion.
100,000 yen should do it, right?
Niku, you're amazing!
Nikusuke, you can shoot off
as many times as you want!
Give it to her!
No!
Pull out!
Please, I'll get pregnant!
All right, switch it up!
Let's really get started!
This is great, I can go all night!
Here I come!
How do you like a taste
of reality, you bitches!
We're going to give you a reality check!
How do you like my grind technique!
From now on, I get to
do this whenever I want!
Today's lesson is over.
You can go home now.
Hey, Wakana, come to
my house early tomorrow.
I want you to come wearing
nothing but a frilly apron!
Be sure to practice your
blowjobs before then!
I got a great picture, this is perfect!
I'm going to hurry home
and masturbate to this!
Niku.
Yeah, I know.
Yu!
Gotcha.
Hey, that's really bright!
What are you trying to do?
A question for you...
Someone among us hasn't been initiated.
Who could it be?
A hint...
She's a virgin.
What's the matter?
Looking for something?
You know what it means to
oppose me on this campus, don't you?
Niku, or the baton.
Choose one or the other.
Which takes your virginity?
To be continued
There's no one in this school
who would dare to defy me.
So what do you think
you're trying to do?
You think you're going to
start ordering me around?
I won't allow it!
I've never even been scolded by
my grandfather or my own father.
Nikusuke, you're part of this, too?
No, stop!
I don't want to be punished!
Princess 69 Lesson Four.
Decadent Dance, Last Stage.