Hey...
We don't see Miku on the train anymore...
She doesn't come to
morning practices either.
Didn't you know, Yu?
The story about the training!
Professor Doguro is making
Haneoka take some secret training.
It's just a rumor, though.
Secret training...
Now, suck out the rest of it.
Yes...
Good, that's it.
Don't just swallow it, but savor it.
Yes...
Is it good?
Good, don't spill any.
Yes...
It's very thick today, isn't it?
Y-Yes...
Are you happy?
Very happy...
Slowly, savor the taste of it.
Y-Yes...
Professor, can I sallow it now?
I see, you want to taste it that badly.
Y-Yes...
Okay...
Let me inspect to see
if you have it all.
Open up.
Yes.
You did very well.
Go ahead and swallow.
O-Okay...
Now, what do you say?
It was delicious.
Good girl, now come on.
Yes.
I'm proud of you, you're
a very fast learner!
Thank you very much.
Now, we'll begin our morning training.
Yes, Professor.
Princess 69 Lesson 2,
Flower Garden of Leotards
God...
Damn it...
What the hell...
It feels so good!
My clit feels so good!
My dad will be so angry!
I better clean up...
Damn it, I'm so irritated!
Good job, Miku, 100 points!
Amazing, Miku is very
good at swallowing!
Professor Nikusuke!
You despicable bastard!
I never thought you'd be the
type to do that, Professor!
Serves him right.
You two were doing it whenever
you please, what did you expect?
It's almost a miracle that
you didn't get caught sooner.
This is trouble, this
is going to be a problem...
Miss Tomomi!
Please, ask your father
to help on this matter...
Our next target is the
flat-chested, Yu Aizawa.
Figure out a way to get
that endurance freak alone.
Otherwise, this sick feeling
in my stomach won't go away.
Um...
What?
Can I count on you about
the Wakano incident...
Figure something out by yourself!
My father is very busy!
He can't be bothered
over trivial things!
Instead, why don't you
think of a way to get Aizawa!
If Tomomi turns me away
what am I going to do?
Konhei...
There we go...
You sure are lucky, looking
like you don't have any worries.
Utamaru!
You jerk, don't be mean to Utamaru!
I-I know, you want Utamaru
to be part of your training!
What?
No!
M-Miku...
Y-You...
P-Professor Doguro did
something to you, didn't he?
Don't lie, you're hiding something!
Tell me!
What's this secret training?
Yes?
What?
Right...
So they saw you.
Okay, got it.
Where's Niku?
Oh well.
Listen very carefully to what I say,
I think I know how to solve this...
The Dark Dog Gymnastic Techniques?
That's right!
It's the most highly effective exercise
that develops your technique and senses!
It's an Ultra A Rank technique!
B-But I've never heard
of a technique like that...
Kozue, you are definitely slow!
That's because you haven't
refined your talents with training!
However!
If you take my secret training...
You have the ability to become a
super elite of Dark Dog Gymnastics!
What do you want to do?
Y-Yes, I'll do it!
I want to be a Dark Gymnast!
Here.
T-Thanks...
Yu.
Well, today...
There's a special training
session after school...
If you don't want to, it's okay.
I'll go with you!
Miku's pretty good at this.
Now to call up Niku...
Kozue, you seem to be very used to this.
You don't have a boyfriend, so
you must be practicing alone.
H-How did you know that?
I've been practicing blowjobs
for when I meet a guy I like!
Yes, I know.
The Professor knows
everything about his students.
See...
...and back here is the hymen.
Stop Professor, I'm going to pee!
My pee is coming out!
Good, you're a natural.
Now, I want you to pose
just like a dog.
O-Okay...
Like this, Professor?
Oh, very good, now for Dark
Dog Gymnastics training part one.
I'll show you a secret.
Yes!
Not like that, you have
to become more like a dog!
Bow wow wow!
Good, let's begin training!
Good, it's all in!
How's your first time feel?
It hurts!
You have to bark, remember?
Bow wow!
It hurts!
Idiot, I told you to bark like a dog!
It hurts...
Bow wow!
It's that good, huh!
Then I'll go even deeper!
Ow, it hurts!
My pussy hurts!
Take it out!
Oh man, I'm about to come!
No, I'll get pregnant!
I'll make sure you'll
have healthy puppies!
No, Professor!
I don't want to!
No...
It's coming out...
Your sperm is really coming out inside...
Now, you're really one of us.
I'll take care of my pet from now on.
All right, one down!
Yu, welcome to the Dark Gymnastics Team!
Shirakawa!
Calling us at a time like this...
What kind of training is this!
Where there is light, there is shadow...
In the long history of gymnastics...
...there's always been a secret
way to improve your skills.
That sounds pretty stupid.
Aizawa, that story is true!
Nikusuke!
And Kozue?
Now, listen up!
This is one manuscript.
This legendary book is full
of amazing techniques that...
...I never got to do when
I was still a competitor!
I want to use this book to
train you to your very top level!
And what's that got to do with anything?
It's just a book you probably wrote
bitching about your unreachable dreams!
What's so fun about using that
to make slaves of everyone?
Shirakawa?
It's a chance to remove
the veil from the...
...forbidden teachings
of Dark Gymnastics!
Are you satisfied at your level, Yu?
Miku, show her!
Yes?
Show her our Dark Gymnastics!
Yes!
W-Watch me, Yu...
Look at my indecent form...
Miku...
Y-You...
This is one of 108 Dark Gymnastic forms!
Obscene Ball Gymnastics!
Look at the beautiful form!
And her passionate movements!
And her beautiful expression!
I want to become that ball...
You're all crazy...
Here!
Miku, you really do learn quickly!
Miku?
But Niku, Yu is watching...
It's okay, you want her to see, right?
Yes.
Niku, your cock is rock hard...
Y-You guys!
What the hell did you do to Miku?
W-What the...
Yu, sorry about this.
You will be reborn today
with the Dark Gymnastics.
You will take shape
into your ideal form!
L-ldeal?
Let's see!
Don't look!
Even a tomboy like you has a
beautiful organ to please your man!
You dirty bastard!
I wet it pretty good.
Ready over here too, Nikusuke!
Stop, what are you doing!
I'm getting it ready for
penetration, of course.
S-Stop it!
Please stop, Shirakawa!
Then you won't ever
oppose me from now on?
O-Okay, I won't!
You'll help with anything that I ask?
Well, answer me!
I will, anything!
What if the next target...
...was someone you knew well?
I really want to stick
my cock inside her!
What will it be?
Will you help, or not?
Stop!
M-Miss Tomomi, I can't
hold back anymore!
Can I do her now?
Yes...
Looks like Yu isn't going to help...
No!
Please forgive me!
So what will it be?
I will help you.
I'll help, so please!
Yu, don't be such a crybaby!
Don't look like that, I know.
Nikusuke, you can use her mouth.
Kozue, take her ass.
Don't touch anything else.
Yu's ass is well trained.
Don't tense up, or else
they'll split you in two.
See, Yu, it feels really good!
L-lt hurts!
I'm splitting in two!
Please help me!
Here, this one is real tasty.
Miku...
I'll get Yu's first
blowjob on tape, okay?
Good, now don't use your teeth.
Oh Yu!
This will feel better,
the more that you do it.
Does it feel good, Niku?
Niku, does it feel good?
Does Yu's mouth feel good?
Y-Yeah, it's great!
Oh, shit!
I spilled a little there.
Niku, you're fast!
Is it that good?
Yeah, it's the best!
How is it compared to my blowjobs?
I can't really compare the two...
She's got her own talents...
Yu, take care of Niku's
cock for me, okay?
If you hurt my Niku, I'll release
this video all over the net!
That would be bad!
Come on, Yu!
Suck that dick like a pro and
make Niku come in your mouth!
Look, her jaw is so loose!
Now I can go at my pace!
Great, this feels so good!
If you look at me like
that, I'll come again!
Wow, I've never felt this good...
Yu, I feel so good, I can't stop!
Is it good for you too, Yu?
Go deeper.
Here!
She is crying!
I want to see this girl's face completely
covered in Nikusuke's dirty come!
M-Miss Tomomi...
I'm...
Oh my, Nikusuke!
Go ahead and fill her
mouth up with your come!
All right, then I'll
give you plenty of it!
Make sure to catch it all!
Awesome, I got that on tape!
It's coming out of her nose!
Don't spill it the floor,
otherwise you'll be punished!
If I clip these on, your
nipples will come off!
Do as Tomomi says.
Ew!
She spit it all out!
What a thing to do to my chosen sperm!
Wow, that is really gross!
You're in so much trouble, Yu!
Yu must now be punished!
Kozue, get it ready.
Gotcha!
No!
Nikusuke, are you getting this?
Yeah, I'm excited!
That stupid face is priceless.
We have to get more embarrassing
shots of you, after all!
Here!
That hurts!
What is with this girl?
Miku, Professor, look at this!
Wow, Yu, you're completely wet!
No...
Wow, that's amazing!
Did you get excited?
No, that's not true!
But Yu, your pussy is really twitching.
No!
Miku!
Come here and help torture
this perverted girl.
But...
Just come here!
M-Miss Tomomi, what about me?
Not you, Niku!
Why not?
Because if you go out of control
like last time, we can't stop you.
Today, your job is to
record this perverted girl!
Sorry, Yu.
Look closely, isn't that a filthy sight?
Feel good, Yu?
No Miku!
What a reaction!
Yu, you pervert!
Don't do that, stop!
How is it, Yu?
Losing your mind?
If you admit you're a dirty
piggy slut, you can come!
You are about to come, aren't you?
You are being tortured,
yet about to come!
If you hold back too much,
you really will go insane!
Go ahead and leak your juices all
over your precious Miku's face!
Yeah, go ahead and cover my face!
Miku!
She's coming, you dirty lesbian!
Nikusuke, did you get all that...
Nikusuke?
Nikusuke!
Not again!
Stop it, you idiot!
Don't you hear my orders?
Hey Nikusuke!
I'm coming!
To be continued
A woman's happiness comes
from a stable marriage...
That's why I've been trying to
fall in love with one person...
Why are you doing this to me?
No, don't look at me!
I don't want anyone to see me like this!
Princess 69 Lesson 3, Virgin Rondo
The Dark Gymnastic Team is unmasked!
Rape is a crime punishable
under criminal law.