Producers
Syuuta Biwajima
Chikara Niki
Damn... This is my second
year as a salary-man.
I didn't think it'd be so rough.
Director
Suginamidaifuku
No new hires,
and people are getting laid off,
but the work just keeps coming.
Screenplay
Yuuta Takahashi
I barely make it on the last train,
come in on the weekends...
I just go home to sleep.
I haven't even had time
to jerk off lately.
Xpress Train
Part I
Awesome!
Women Only Train
Out of all trains... Jeez...
But, it's kind of nice.
What the...? S-Stop...
That feels good...
No, don't do that.
If you do that, I'm going to cum!
This is the last stop.
You're...
If you don't get off, you're going
to get stowed with the train.
You're wet.
Um... Are you all right?
I'm fine!
Spring has sprung?
I wonder what's wrong?
Is she not feeling well?
I've never seen
a pervert in action.
I can't believe someone would
do something like that.
As a man,
I can't let this happen!
Lucky bastards.
I'd like to try it too.
I wonder how they do it,
exactly?
Hey! Trying to get away,
are we?
Huh?
What do you mean, "Huh,"
after doing all that?
I didn't do it!
That old man did it!
Where is he, then?
Huh?
Give it up!
Do you have proof
that it was me?
Then how do you
explain that?
Banish Pervert Busters
Handguns Initiative
I confessed to the groping.
If I admitted it
and paid the fine,
I could get released
immediately, but...
If I continued to deny it, I could
be locked up for weeks, even months.
Long, hellish years of battling it
in court would have been waiting.
It would take a lot of money, and it
would affect my family and company.
That's how the detective
convinced me.
And now I'm fired
from my job.
Damn it!
That old fart!
Come to the police with me!
You have to catch pickpockets
and molesters in the act.
How dare you!
You've ruined my life!
What an idiot. You deny it even
if you did it. That's the rule!
I didn't do it!
Then why did you admit it?
You're just as guilty as me
for looking the other way.
Same rule goes for bullying.
What?
Listen, groping...
is an art form in itself.
The Way of Groping.
Same as the Way of the Samurai.
It's a serious battle
with your life on the line.
Way of Groping?
We are hunters
who feast on our prey.
Hunter?
Try it! It'll change
the way you think.
Don't insult me!
I'm not like you!
Aren't you angry that you've
been wrongly convicted?
Have your revenge
on the women of the world.
This is insane.
Something isn't right.
I have to stop him.
For social justice and
for world peace, I have to stop him!
Is he going to fuck her?
No way!
He's inside a train!
Why isn't anyone noticing?
Do it! Go ahead and do it!
How could I? But...
No, I shouldn't.
This is wrong.
What's this rush?
I've never experienced
anything like it.
I never knew
a rush like this existed.
Anxiety and tension
are getting mixed up.
The lady getting felt up...
She is nice and wet.
She's tight, too.
Yes... Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
No... I'm going to cum.
What the...?
What is that?
You fucking pervert!
You pervert!
I'll beat the shit
out of human scum like you!
You'll never be
able to function!
No... Wait... It was...
Shut up and come with us!
That was a very flashy debut.
Who are these men?
My apprentices.
Apprentice Number 90.
I'm Number 135.
I'm Number 202.
I'm Number 407.
And you are...
my 500th apprentice!
You have that many?
He is the God of Groping.
Exactly. He's the man who touched...
God rest her soul... Teresa's ass!
I thought it was Helen?
You have a knack for groping.
No, perhaps you have
a hidden talent for this!
Coming from the sixty-year
veteran God of Groping,
you must have talent.
You just need to master the
Art of Not Getting Caught.
Well? Want to learn?
But, I...
Didn't it feel good?
Please guide me!
Welcome to the
Wonderful World of Groping!
Look.
It's a hidden camera.
It's Number 90's fetish.
Number 130 is...
Just watch.
And lastly, creaming on them.
Number 202...
He only does anal.
Number 407...
His forte is the vibrator.
Okay...
Let's get into formation.
It's a team sport.
Look.
Shall we do the Berlin Wall
or the Great Wall of China?
Let's go with
Operation: Surround the Prey.
Surround the Prey?
Also known as
the Battle of Odawara.
No...
Now it's your turn.
What am I supposed to...
The most important spot
has been saved for you.
Give her a taste
of your gold finger!
No...
I can't, anymore...
Okay, my turn.
When you become seasoned like me,
you'll be able to...
differentiate between the women
just by looking at them.
Look for the most
demure one around you.
You can tell by
looking in their eyes.
Stay way from women
with a piercing look.
They'll definitely
come after you.
Listen to me. Don't go
after the women on cell phones.
Women traveling in groups
are dangerous.
Make sure
you don't touch them.
Why do you keep going
after the dangerous ones?
I want to challenge
the impossible.
You said yourself that it's
the pinnacle of the Way of Groping.
Keep it up
and you'll get caught.
I've passed
my apprentice stage, right?
You still have
a graduation test.
Number 407 got caught!
How did that happen?
Undercover agents!
Well? Can you do it?
This is my graduation test?
Go do it!
Here he comes.
Another predator.
I'm going to wait and see. Once he
goes in, I'll nab him like always.
He's pretty good.
A worthy opponent...
What's happening?
He's... so good!
No, I'm feeling it.
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
That was awesome!
You're amazing!
You've definitely graduated.
I can't believe
you graduated before us.
Okay. This is
the real graduation exam.
You must grope
someone you know.
It requires technique, and you need
to control their emotions.
It's like a dream come true.
I get to spoil this angel...
with my very own hands.
What am I saying? This is what
you wished for. Let's go!
What just happened? She's reaching
for my dick willingly!
An innocent-looking woman
like her is a pervert?