Calling Car A, begin the operation.
Car A, roger, beginning operation.
I almost forgot.
This is supposed to be important...
Princess 69 Lesson 1, Indecent Stretch
Ew, it's Professor Doguro.
He is looking over here!
My luck today is awful!
I wonder if he washes that jersey...
Yeah, he's so gross!
Totally!
Oh, Professor Doguro...
Good morning.
Here we go...
Are you going to be
watching us again today?
It's so hard to turn
in that performance.
But we have to master it
by the next tournament...
Would you get the ball?
The star of the gymnastics
team is definitely Miku.
Miku is sparkling!
Keep it down, Tomomi will hear you.
Who cares, I'm just stating the truth.
I think they're both so beautiful...
It's true, they're both
about even in their beauty.
But if we're talking about
who has the better technique...
Oh, Nikusuke, you're already so big.
I'll squeeze your milk out
with my secret technique.
Come on, Nikusuke, shoot it
all out into my dirty mouth.
See, don't I feel better than her?
Relax and enjoy.
Oh, Nikusuke, you're delicious!
You're about to come, right?
Give me a face full of it!
No, I want some of Nikusuke's come, too!
Oh...
Well, looks like you two tie today.
Oh, my face is so full of your come!
My face is completely covered!
Oh, that's not good...
It's because he's thinking
perverted thoughts!
Freak!
Gross.
Oh man, that hurt!
What a wuss.
Creep.
Mommy, that hurt!
I'm sorry Niku!
I'm sorry, please forgive me...
It wasn't on purpose.
You okay?
Just keep still.
Pain, pain, go away!
Better, Niku?
See, you're all better now.
Get better soon, okay?
S-Sure!
Don't worry.
I'll always be on your side.
See you, teach!
I didn't know Miku was in love.
M-Miku sure has weird tastes...
If she's so nice to him now,
it'll become a problem later...
T-Then, M-M-M-Miku's
going to get p-pregnant!
Listen, you...
Calm down.
Listen, you understand, right?
She's the first one.
I want her to get really messed up!
The Dark Gymnastics Team will
unveil itself after school.
Just you wait!
I'll show them who's
the boss on this campus!
Okay, Niku...
Nikusuke, I don't care if you
peek at those peasants' panties...
...but you aren't worthy of
peeking at my elegant ones!
Die!
I'll give you specific
instructions later.
Go wait at the usual place.
Damn it, that bitch...
I'll make her my slave, someday...
Hey, don't look!
Where did you get that one?
So cute!
Well, I don't think Niku
will stay quiet about it.
Huh?
But it was already decided
at the council meeting.
There's nothing Professor
Doguro can do about it, now.
Besides, bloomers are just
the tip of the iceberg.
He's lucky no one mentioned the jersey.
Madoka's becoming a revolutionary!
Oh, Tomo!
What do you think of the
new suit my dad bought me?
Those star sapphires are real, you know.
Professor Doguro!
Will you say something to her?
S-Shirakawa... nice suit...
Isn't it?
It came from Paris this morning.
It's spectacular!
I wonder if this high-class
sense isn't lost on you, Nikusuke.
Of course, I get it!
Especially if you make the fabric
around here even tighter, it'll be...
...much more artistic...
Jeez, you're pathetic, Niku!
Hurry up and confiscate it!
W-What?
You mean I can strip her?
Shut up, beggar.
You have no tits, it
wouldn't even fit you.
W-What?
No tits, huh?
Maybe I'll talk to my father, and make
being flat-chested against the law!
Why you little...
Yu, stop it!
Miku?
Please, Yu, forgive Tomo!
What?
What's the meaning of this?
Do you think I'd lose to her?
I-I like the honest Tomo...
Huh?
What the...
Tomo, let's all be friends.
As we planned, I invited her
to the classroom after school...
...so I'll leave the rest to you.
You sure, this is okay?
Of course, I'm the leader
of the Dark Gymnastics Team.
I'm the Queen, and you're a servant!
You're my slave, get it?
R-Right...
Glad you understand.
What does she mean,
"Glad you understand!"
I swear, I'll make her my toy, someday.
It is now time for
after school activities.
T-Tomo, I'm so sorry I'm late!
I had to go and pick
up my little brother...
I wonder if she went home already...
A ghost!
I'm not a ghost, it's me!
P-Professor Doguro...
You scared me...
W-What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
M-Miku...
Sorry about this!
L-lt hurts...
No, it hurts Professor...
Why are you doing this?
Sorry, Miku...
I just can't go against Tomomi...
Tomo?
Ouch!
If I don't this, the student
council is going to fire me.
Yesterday, some people
broke into my apartment.
If I don't do this to you,
they're going to revoke my license.
At my age, I can't find
a new job so easily.
If I went to the cops, those guys are
going to keep coming after me.
You pissed off Tomomi...
Y-You're lying...
What are you doing?
Stop!
No!
No matter where you go, you can't
get away from the Shirakawa Faction.
Please don't!
And besides, I've always liked you.
P-Professor, please stop...
Please, not today...
We can't do this...
My mom will be so angry.
Please, I won't do anything bad to you.
Just help me...
Tonight, I'll train you
in the new gymnastics.
New Gymnastics...
What we call the Dark Gymnastics.
W-What?
Here we go...
What's that?
If you drink this, you'll become one
step closer to the Dark Gymnastics Team.
Go on!
O-Oh, I know!
You want me to do it like they
do on all your favorite shows!
You're completely hopeless.
Don't, Professor, that's dirty.
It smells and tastes great!
I can barely stand it already!
No, you pervert!
W-Where are you touching?
Don't!
It's so fluffy and warm!
Quit it!
Now then...
Oh, looks like you're a bit wet here.
Y-You're wrong, that's...
You're making some awfully nasty sounds...
S-Stop, I-I really
don't feel good today...
C-Could this be...
No, don't look, professor, please!
This is the first time I'm doing it
with a girl on her period, I'm excited!
No, stop!
Professor, you jerk!
Tomomi is fine too, but
this innocence is nice too...
There we go!
Let's go!
Your form is truly excellent!
Please, stop it...
Well then, let's dig in!
No!
And now for Miku's secret garden!
Don't look!
It's really starting to twitch...
Let's see how it is inside...
That hurts!
Wow, it's really tight!
And there seems to be something
sticky coming from inside...
N-No, you're lying!
Then what is this stickiness?
I don't know, please stop!
It's not urine, is it?
Do you want to pee?
I see, so you wanted to pee.
Stop, what are you...
Peeing should be done
in the toilet, right?
A-Are you serious?
I-I don't want to, it's embarrassing!
You want to go, right?
I'm sure that drink you had
before is taking effect too.
You feel like you're going to go?
Y-Yes...
What should I do, should I say no?
D-Don't...
Don't drop your skirt.
Let's go!
Stop!
Ah, what a waste!
Delicious, very tasty!
Professor, please don't do this anymore...
...or I'll...
What are you saying,
your pee is delicious.
No, stop Professor, please!
No, it's coming!
It's coming!
Stop Professor, please!
Go ahead and let it all out, Miku!
There you go...
It's raining...
There's supposed to be a storm coming...
That's good.
Now you have an excuse to be late.
Tomo...
I...
Where there's light, there's shadow...
Welcome to the Dark Gymnastics Team.
What took you so long, Nikusuke?
Sorry, it took a while to
get her into the leotard.
Whatever...
Miku, do you want to
keep being my friend?
If you say no, then our
friendship is of course, over.
I'll completely erase you
from the Shirakawa Campus.
But if you're willing to accept
Nikusuke's training course...
What are you going to do, Haneoka?
No!
Okay, now we're ready to go!
So this is the ancient
Chinese technique?
Right, this is the
pussy training program!
Shows quick results, and makes
you more sensitive, or so it says.
So all I have to do is pull the string?
Please...
It hurts, please stop it!
This is so fun!
Just pulling lightly
gives her so much pain!
Tomo...
That's it!
Just keep pulling and letting
go, and change the rhythm.
Like this?
Yeah like that!
Boy, aren't you feeling good, Miku?
Why, Tomo...
Aren't we friends?
Yes, we're friends!
That's why we're training you!
No!
Now, Miku, dance!
You're a member of the Dark
Gymnastics Team, aren't you?
Good girl, Miku.
Just do as I say, and
I'll take good care of you.
I-I'm your friend...
...so I'll take the training...
I-I can't stand it!
Nikusuke said he couldn't stand it.
Why don't you take care
of him with your mouth?
Yeah, please suck me!
No!
You idiot!
Oh, sorry.
Be happy, I didn't take a bath today,
just so I'll have the right scent.
Now, don't be shy and
get right in there!
No, get that thing
away from me, Professor!
What did you say?
Go on, how do you like that manly smell?
Stop!
What's the matter, Miku?
Help him out.
Come on, now...
N-No, Tomo, please help!
We're friends, aren't we?
So what?
Listen, Miku...
Aren't you supposing a bit too much?
There are a lot of
different kinds of friends.
Your naive concept of friendship...
...is something I don't need!
T-Tomo...
Don't bother giving me the puppy eyes!
Stop, it hurts!
You know what you have to do, right?
Or are you just to stupid to do it?
Tomo, Tomo!
Just give up, you don't want
Tomomi to hate you, right?
What you need in sports is
endurance, and competitiveness.
Good, now then...
See, you can do it if you try.
Now try licking.
Yeah, that feels great...
Now put it deeper in.
I-I can't breathe...
Miku, you are a very quick learner.
As your reward, I'll turn this on.
Come on, Miku, no time to rest.
That drink I gave you before, should be
showing another effect on your body now.
What's the matter, Tomomi!
Pull that rope for her!
R-Right!
O-Okay, Miku, you did well.
You cleared the first step!
The ability to sway men
is the first step on the...
...road to the Dark Gymnastics Team.
You're now one of us!
You can't turn back now, understand?
Y-Yes!
Here I go!
I'm going to come...
I'll spray it inside you now!
Incredible, I'm getting sucked in!
Professor, stop...
It hurts, it hurts!
You're finally starting to talk again.
Soon you'll be my woman.
Pull it out!
Thank you, Miku.
You're the only one who
accepted a dirty outside like mine.
You're the only woman for me...
I'm coming!
To be continued
That pig teacher Nikusuke
made Miku a woman?
And I'm the one they're after next?
Hell no, they won't get me!
Miku, oh no, what are you doing?
What's going to happen to me?
Princess 69 Lesson 2,
Flower Garden of Leotards
No one can stop the
Dark Gymnastics Team!