Sakajou...
A-Aoshima, good morning...
Are you reading archaeological
books in the library again?
Y-Yes.
You really like archaeology, don't you?
The Aoshima that I admire...
If it was him, I won't
regret giving my virginity.
I want to be loved by him...
I want him to love me...
I want to love him...
Kenichi! You're here?
We need to hurry up and get
back, class will start!
Sorry, sorry.
Stop shouting, Miho...
Sakajou, I'll see you after
school at the club room.
I love him this much, but
in his heart is always...
Archaeology Club
One day, during summer break...
...a mysterious "festival artifact"
suddenly started to glow.
I, who happened to be there, was
showered by the light and fainted...
Then I dreamed of
being loved by Aoshima...
It was blissful...
The one I love
was making love to me.
His thick, hot, hard thing was
sicking into me and stirring...
It was scary and it hurt, but...
...I was happy...
Kenichi!
N-No! That's me?
That's not...
That's not me!
What's going on?
Akiyama?
I'm Akiyama?
Why?
He didn't choose me?
No! That's not right!
No!
I-I love you the most...
BODY TRANSFER: Episode 2
Was that a dream?
But why am I in the library?
What was that light?
I have no energy...
Aoshima...
No! I'm at the academy, not my room.
Hikaru...
I can't stop myself...
Aoshima...
Aoshima, you were wonderful...
But if it was my body,
it would've been more...
What's happening?
Why am I Kenichi?
What in the world just happened?
Aoshima!
W-What are you doing? Sakajou...
I want you...
I want you to...
Aoshima!
Wow, Sakajou's touching
herself right in front of me.
W-What?
Don't tell me Kenichi's getting big?
T-This is Kenichi's...
Wow, something like this is on
Kenichi and it's growing?
It's hard and pulsating...
It feels good...
I can't think...
It was bigger...
I remember Aoshima's was
thicker, harder and hotter...
Aoshima! Aoshima!
No, I shouldn't be doing such
a thing with Kenichi's body...
But I can't stop it!
Oh no, I can't stop
listening to Sakajou's voice.
Help me, Kenichi...
Aoshima!
I'm going to come...
I-I'm gonna come!
Something's coming out!
Kenichi!
Yes, yes!
Oh my God, I'm coming...
So much is coming out...
A-Aoshima!
Um, not, I'm not...
This isn't what you think, Sakajou...
I'm sorry!
It's not Aoshima?
Wait, maybe because of that artifact?
So another person is inside Aoshima?
Miho?
I don't think you should come closer.
See? I think you should
stay away from it.
Shall we go to the club room?
Maybe everyone's back in the room.
So let's go, Aoshima.
I knew immediately
that you were Aoshima...
...and also Miho is inside him.
Not fair...
Nurse's Room
What's gonna happen to me?
Who is it?
It's me.
Sakajou...
Aoshima, why are you here alone?
Um, Ms. Touko said that guys
should sleep in a different room...
I see...
You must be lonely.
S-Sakajou!
W-What are you doing?
I'll do it with my mouth...
You were doing it by
yourself before, weren't you?
While watching me masturbate...
That was...
S-Sakajou...
It's already hard...
Sakajou, no...
Does it feel good?
S-Sakajou, stop...
Relax, Akiyama...
S-Sakajou, you knew?
I'm always watching Aoshima...
S-Sakajou...
It's not fair, I want to touch
Aoshima's thing too!
So, how did it feel to
masturbate with Aoshima's body?
Don't say that...
While watching me touch myself,
you were stroking his like this, no?
And then, you came
so hard, didn't you?
Stop it, Sakajou!
My body's aching...
Isn't it pretty low? To do something
nasty with somebody else's body?
Stop it, please...
I gave my virginity to Aoshima.
With your body, Akiyama...
It's kinda strange, isn't it...
I'm sure he made love to me...
I remember the pain and happiness...
...but my body's still a virgin...
W-What?
Then, that wasn't a dream?
S-Sakajou, no...
N-No, I can't think...
Kenichi...
Kenichi, I'm gonna come
again with your body!
You're back...
I was surrounded by light and when
I came to, you were making love to me...
...as Akiyama.
W-What?
Wait a minute...
I was happy, but
troubled at the same time.
Because I was in Akiyama's body,
even though I was inside her...
I want you to make love to the real me...
When I thought that, I
was back in my own body...
Please, Aoshima...
S-Sakajou!
Aoshima, I want you so bad...
Look, I'm already...
S-Sakajou...
Aoshima...
It's so thick and rough,
I can feel the veins, too.
Much larger than when
I did you in my mouth...
S-Sakajou, why are you so wet?
Because just thinking about
doing you makes me wet...
It's so soft inside.
Now, please go deeper.
Please feel me!
Sakajou, it's so squishy...
I'm so ashamed...
It feels so good!
Harder! Harder!
I'm one with Aoshima in my own body...
I'm giving my virginity to him...
I-I'm gonna come!
Ladies' Showers
I'm inside Akiyama's body again.
Sister!
You're weird! What's going on?
Why did you do something
like that with Yukino?
No!
No, stop it!
I don't want this!
You can't listen to your older sister?
N-No!
Konomi's private place
that doesn't know men...
It's so pretty I'm jealous...
Stop it! Sister!
If you can't listen to your
older sister, you'll get this!
Ow!
If you don't want to get hurt, be
a good girl and listen to me, okay?
O-Okay...
There you go, good girl...
If you stay like that, I will
do this to Konomi's nipples...
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
N-No...
You're feeling like this from
your sister, you're pretty naughty...
I'm not like that!
I'll let you feel even
better, stick your tongue out...
Sis!
Sister!
No, Sister,
I feel strange!
I can't take it anymore...
Nurse's Room
Aoshima...
Miho?
No, Sakajou...
Aoshima, I'll show
you something amusing...
Is it Miho?
Does it feel that good? Akiyama...
Yes, it does...
You're gonna come again?
Yes, almost there...
I see, then come really hard.
OK!
OK, Akiyama, come
really, naughty hard!
In front of Aoshima!
K-Kenichi!
Kenichi, don't look!
If you don't want to be watched
by Aoshima, why don't you stop?
No, I wanna come...
Let me come!
Then come in front of him!
Here!
Oh no...
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
Miho...
I can't move...
This is the body a girl who's just came...
How was it? Akiyama...
How does it feel when Aoshima
watched you come from masturbating?
N-No...
No!
It's understandable...
Being watched by somebody you like...
S-Sakajou...
That artifact has the power
to release people's desire...
Why in the world...
It doesn't matter what the reason is...
What's important is that
we want to feel good...
Can't you hear that sound?
We will eventually be
swallowed up by that wall...
We can't run away...
So, let's do what we want to do...
Don't you agree?
Miho...
Miho!
Aoshima...
It can't be me?
Does it have to be, Miho?
I love you so much...
I love you more than anybody...
Aoshima...
Miho!
Kenichi, you're back in your body.
What are you doing here?
I can't take it anymore...
You saw what kind of girl I am...
It's not just that.
I did things to your body as well...
M-Me too!
But it couldn't be helped.
It's all that light's fault!
I'm becoming something
that I'm usually not...
I'm becoming more and more like the
me I didn't want you to see...
I can't bear it anymore!
Miho...
Don't come, Kenichi!
I've always loved you, Kenichi...
I should've said it sooner, before
something like this happened...
Miho...
Kenichi, I was happy
when we were together...
...even when we fought, it was fun...
Miho...
While I'm myself...
Bye-bye, Kenichi...
Miho!
I love you too!
Kenichi...
I love everything about you!
Even if I'm not myself, the most
important feelings don't change!
I will not let go until the last moment!
I will be the one who loves Miho!
Kenichi...
Miho!
Kenichi!
Miho...
Kenichi...
We're back in our world...
Yes, that's right. We came back.
Kenichi...
Miho...
Miho, let's do it for the
first time again...
OK...
Kenichi!
Miho, you're really pretty...
It's embarrassing, Kenichi...
Don't look!
Kenichi!
Does it feel good here?
Like an electric shock?
Don't ask something
like that, you meanie!
If you do that, I'm gonna come!
Miho...
Right here, it feels good, right?
I know...
Miho, it feels good!
It's gonna blow!
I'm putting it in, Miho...
Yes, please come, Kenichi...
Miho...
Kenich's so hard and hot...
Yours is great too. So
soft and it wraps around me...
Kenichi...
Kenichi!
Miho...
Miho!
Kenichi!
Kenichi, I gonna come!
Please, let's come together!
Miho, I'm coming...
Miho!
Kenichi! Kenichi!
I'm coming!
Kenichi's coming inside
me, so hot and so much!
Kenichi, hug me tight...
Miho...
Kenichi, I want this forever...
Yes, let's be like this forever...