The Devil's violin, AKA Canne.
lt sucks up the ecstasy
from young women...
And turns it into evil power.
lt's a devil incarnate...
This Saint Cecilia Girls
Academy was created...
ln order to seal the
devil's instrument for good.
But someone appeared
and broke the seal...
And made a deal with the devil in
order to satisfy his own desires...
ln order to save those that were
possessed by that devil's violin...
l need your help.
What should l do?
The only thing that can
seal the devil's violin...
ls the angel's violin Cecilia.
lf you can use that violin...
Me?
Anal Sanctuary Vol. 2
Kozuki-san.
Asahina-san, Mr.
Yashiro wants to see you.
Mr. Yashiro?
Nanahara-san.
Ms. Tachibana?
Yukina-san wants to see you.
My sister?
No...
Stop it!
Asahina-san, l want you
to scream more for me!
No!
No...
Stop it!
Nanahara Mizuho-san.
lt's time to take a walk.
No, no, no!
No!
Why me?
Please Kozuki-san...
Stop it...
l can't do that Asahina-san.
You're gonna be my toy.
First, l want you to release
yourself in front of me.
What?
Please, stop it...
No.
We're just getting started.
No...
Let me go to the bathroom...
This Saint Cecilia Girls Academy
used to be a church for the heretics.
We keep many of the
evil instruments here.
One of those instruments happen
to be a violin called the Cannone.
Cannone has taken
control of Yashiro Akio ...
...and it's gaining greater power
by sucking ecstasy from the girls.
l can't do anything about it.
But you, Yukina Nanahara...
Maybe you can stop the devil's violin.
What's this?
Angel's violin Cecilia.
Cecilia...
l have to use this to...
What's this?
Yukina-san...
Don't look at me...
No.
Stop it...
That's not right.
Stop it you two.
She's supposed to be virtuous
but she needs to be punished...
...for acting like a slut.
You know what Yukina?
Maybe you should worry about
yourself before worrying about others.
Mizuho-chan!
No...
Sensai, please stop this.
No!
Mizuho!
Yes.
Stop it.
Sensai...
Mizuho...
Stop it.
There's no way for you to stop
me without the angel's violin.
Sister.
No.
Stop it.
The angels have forsaken us, and
we were captured by the devil.
We regret being born as women, since
what waited for us was dirty and ghastly.
lt was like a dungeon play.
We couldn't do anything
against the devil...
And he kept on violating
our bodies over and over.
Then...
Sensai, please let me down.
Sensai, please...
Let me go to the bathroom...
Then swear that you will
be mine, Nanahara Yukina.
This body of mine wants you.
l'll take good care of you.
Please, anything but that...
Do it Yukina...
l really love you.
l want you to love me too.
Sensai...
l love you too...
l love you Yukina.
Here l come Yukina.
Sensai...
Yes...
l want you to do me more.
Sensai...
l'm coming Yukina.
l'm coming.
l'll come, l'll come...
l'm defecating too...
This is it.
l'll get everything l want
with this devil's violin.
Sensai, l want you to give me a reward.
l want you to give this
perverted Yukina an enema.
Let me climax with an enema.
l see...
l'll climax...
lt feels so good...
Do me more...
Look at it more...
Look at my private parts...
Watch me release myself...
There's so many people here...
No, the vibrator...
More...
This position looks dirty...
l can't hold it in...
Sensai...