We're here earlier than expected.
Yusuke-kun.
Yeah.
Um, sorry, but don't talk to me until we stop.
Note: The symbol on the rear windscreen represents a driver who just acquired the license.
Oh, Yusuke-kun!
Too far. Stop, stop!
Phew, we're finally here...
Yusuke-kun, good job. You're sweating.
Thanks.
Orisaku-san and I...
I meant Akira and I are newlyweds as of today.
We had many obstacles, but we're finally starting a new and exciting life.
It's like a dream!
This is our treasure.
Yeah.
But, you are my most valuable treasure now.
Yusuke-kun...
Tonight, would you like to take a bath first?
Dinner?
Or... me?
Yes, this is our first night together!
Waiting in bed feels awkward.
Feeling a bit shy...
Soon... I am nervous!
I'm sorry.
There was a lot of work so I couldn't wash your back.
Don't worry about it.
We're going to spend the rest of our lives together.
I wanted to...
You're right, good job today.
Uh, well... you too...
She must be tired.
I was hoping we would... but can't blame her.
Yusuke-kun, are you already sleeping?
Yes! I, I meant no, I'm awake.
I'm tired, but also very nervous and...
Well, I'm finally your wife.
And when I think you're finally my husband, my sleepiness went away.
You too, Orisaku-san?
Hey, you called me Orisaku-san!
I'm now Oshima Akira so call me Akira.
You're right, I'm sorry.
Um... Akira.
Yes!
Akira...
Yusuke-kun...
Akira!
It's OK...
We're grownups... it's fine, right?
So this is Akira's...
It hurts!
I, I'm sorry!
This time, gently...
I'm sorry I laughed.
I'll hold it in, so continue...
We were waiting for this day...
So please...
Yeah.
I can't... hold it!
Akira...
No...!
Don't stare at it.
So cute...
I'm going to stick it in... OK?
Huh?
Yusuke-kun... we have to make yours wet too...
I feel it!
...Why?
It's starting to feel good...
Sorry...
No, you were tired, Yusuke-kun.
Don't worry, there's always tomorrow...
If not, there's always the day after so don't worry.
Day after tomorrow...
Cheer up Yusuke-kun, fight!
Honey...
Wake up.
You're finally awake.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yusuke-kun.
Breakfast is ready, let's eat together.
You have to go to the studio today, right?
That's right, I can't be late!
I better dress.
This came out of the boxes, but who is she?
She's an old friend of mine who is a few years younger than me.
She was very sick and had to move to America for treatment.
Of course, I haven't seen her ever since.
I kept this picture as a memento.
I see, well I'm not worried...
Oh, are you jealous?
That's not it! And hurry up.
Yusuke-kun, we're going to get married one day.
Alright, Akko, I promise.
I'm going to work.
Take care.
Yusuke-kun, lets do our best tonight.
Don't mind!
I'll do my best!
I am a housewife as of today.
Fight!
My dreams have come true, going to work on a movie!
Oi, Yusuke!
You must be happy!
This person saw my 8mm movie and liked my work.
He even offered me a job here. He is the Vice President, Fujimiya Shizuma-san.
Go easy, Shizuma-san.
Hey, I'm not going to go easy on you.
By the way, how is that white house?
It's good, thank you for letting us know about it.
Well, how is your sex life with Akira?
Well...
What to cook tonight?
Maybe something with meat?
Ma'am, today we have a big sale on steak.
Ma'am...?
Aren't you? I mean that ring...
Oh...
I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
But I usually get housewives here so I sense these things.
Um, well...
I knew it, movie directors are so demanding.
If I don't bring the actress, I'll get yelled at.
Misaki-san.
Please hurry to the studi...!
I'm sorry!
You must be new here.
You're lucky to see the naked body of an actress.
No...
I, I'm sorry.
You see!
You're still looking!
Uh, well...
We're going to start now, so please hurry!
That was close.
Better be more careful...
But, she had a great body...
Hey, I have a favor to ask you.
See you guys later, I gotta go.
I'm here.
Misaki-san, what is it?
Bringing me here all of a sudden?
How much do you know about me?
Huh?
What the...?!
You're Yusuke-kun, right?
What does she want...
I better hurry home to Akira.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Honey.
Would you like to have dinner first?
Take a bath?
Or me?
Orisaku... no, Akira!
I did my best coordinating for you.
So, what would you like to have first?
It's obvious!
Not here...
Don't mind!
Here comes Yusuke!
Yusuke-kun!
Let's try again tomorrow.
What is it?
What!?
Good morning, Assistant Director.
Why are you here, Misaki-san?
Is it me?
Wow, you're friends with the actress Misaki Atsuko-san?
But why are you here?
I thought you're going to help
her practice for the part, Yusuke-kun?
What?
Yusuke-kun, that's great! I'll cheer you on.
I'm counting on you, Director.
That's assistant director, besides what about today's shooting?
You didn't hear?
The director cancelled today's shoot.
What, really?
Sorry, but looks like the paparazzi got a picture of us yesterday.
I wanted to apologize to you and asked them to cancel today.
What?!
Well, I have some errands to run, so see you guys later.
Sorry about that.
I can't bother you.
This is the first step in your career.
I can't get in the way.
What do you...?
What!? This is...
This is the sacred grounds of husbands and wives.
So it has a meaning to me...
Stop it!
What are you thinking!?
I am an assistant director and just got married with Akira.
There may be some unspoken rules in this industry, but please don't drag me into it!
Besides, I thought you came here to apologize...?
Aren't you a man?
Show me what you got.
No, not right away...
Isn't this what you wanted!?
You're...
Please, continue...
OK...
Going to cum...
So am I!
Going to cum!
Akira!
So it was your first time... Atsuko-san.
I'm sorry, it's been a while I had some so I came inside...
What are you talking about, you do that with your wife all the time.
If you get pregnant, I can't take responsibility.
Since you seduced me.
You're so cold now.
Hey, do you...
Yeah?
No, it's nothing.
I'll be going.
I'm sorry to dirty your sheets.
Oh...
Let me use the shower.
I don't feel right staying at home.
But there's nothing at the studio...
There's nothing to do...
Um, excuse me.
Yes, who is it?
I'm a reporter from a station.
I have some questions about Misaki Atsuko's relationships...
I'm new here so I don't know anything!
See you!
Sigh, there's nowhere else to go but stay at home...
I'm home...
What happened!?
Yusuke-kun...
I slipped while cleaning.
Are you alright, are you hurt?
Be careful, I don't want you to get hurt.
Yusuke-kun...
Akira...
Akira!
Your clothes will get wet!
Akira...
Yusuke-kun.
Fine then.
The fire within me ignites like never before.
I can't control the beast within me...
Yusuke-kun...
Amazing, I feel strange, Yusuke-kun.
Me too.
Great, I'm going to cum...
But this time, I'll cum inside...
A lot.
But we have to plan these things...
We can overcome everything with love.
Yes, our love...
Don't be afraid, relax.
OK...
Here I go, stay still.
It's inside, Akira. It's inside!
Yusuke-kun!
It's wet and warm, feels good.
I'm going to move.
Akira, I love you. I love...
Me too, I love you, Yusuke-kun...
Feels good!
Yusuke-kun, it's hitting deep... deep inside!
Akira, you're so tight!
I'm glad you're mine, it's like a dream having sex with you everyday!
Me too... I'm glad that I'm yours!
I'm going to cum, inside!
Give me, give me your little babies!
I have to thank Atsuko...
Good morning, Assistant Director.
Good morning, Atsuko-san.
There was one thing I wasn't pleased about with our practice.
Wasn't pleased?
Help me again.
I can't.
But I do have to thank you for making things smooth.
Anyway, you better keep your promise.
Promise?
As promised, I will marry you one day.
I will take you away from your wife.
Let me know when you're ready.
Akko?
Can't be...
I'm not giving up...
Akira, I'm home.
Would you like to have dinner?
A bath?
Or me?
You of course!
Good!
Yusuke-kun.
Yusuke-kun!
Akira!
I can't betray Akira.
I love her deeply.