http://www.hentaiparadize.net
Subtitles by Yoshkid.
This... this is...
Did you come to your sense, Shuta? My name is
King Lividoll, the head of the Lividoll Kingdom!
King Lividoll! Why on earth are you doing this!?
Such a pitiful question... I do this for the... Lividoll!
Lividoll is nothing but the lust all human beings have!
You mean...
That's right... you too are a Lividoll. No, you are
beyond the average! I'm sure you felt the presence
before... In fact, you are the same as me...
Bull! You are evil, I am not!
You really think that?
This... is my favorite game.
Doki-doki Memorial Club
Shi... Shishi... Shiorin.
I wanted to see you.
T, to, to, the tongue... this has to be a trap! Soft lips...
My favorite girl in the game a reality... feels good...
This is King Lividolls trap...
I'm a bit embarrassed, but I'll lick you. Ok, Honey?
Ho... ho... Honey!?
Let me explain! Level 1. Mr. Todokoroki. Level 2.
Shuta Level 3. Honey
In this game, when a girl calls you Honey, it means
she really likes you...
Honey... you're thing is big.
Crap, this is too great... I'm going to cum soon...
Feels so good!
Manager~~~~
What are you doing?
That is! The Legendary Black Pudding!
Legendary?
Black Pudding is th eresult from the negative Emo-
Motion. Her smile definitely does not mean
happiness!
This version of Shiorin has a self destruction
mechanism. A slight touch will make Shuta's little
private go KABOOM!
Pudding, I don't care what happens to me! Please
destroy the Lividoll!
Manager~~~~
I already know about that.
Pudding and her friends are fighting waitresses. They
will fight to bring smiles to many people.
Welcome.
Yes, Ok. One Pudding, Four sets of Alamode Combo,
Two tiramisu. Is this everything?
Hmm, I wonde rwhat that dream was about...
Pudding... can't be...
Harue?
Yikes!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry. I...
I'm sorry too... I didn't mean to surprise you like that.
Harue, didn't you have a day off today?
Yes, but I wanted to create a new dish for the
upcoming festival. Don't want to loose to our rivals.
A new dish?
She cares about the restaurant more than I do.
It looks like a breast...
I though of a great dish!
Please let me know! I will make anything... I'm so
clumsy... I'm not cute... so I at least want to be good at
cooking.
Don't say that. You are very cute, Harue.
You are so kind, Manager...
Welcome home, Honey.
I'm sure who ever marries you will be happy
Harue being my wife...
Welcome home, Honey.
Manager, I will do anything... so please tell me!
Please tell me your new dish!
Are you sure?
Yes.
It's embarrassing, but I'll do my best...
I've done what you told me to do, Manager
Alright, stand still until the silicon dries out.
Yes, but... well... can you please come here... and take
a look at it?
Harue? What's wrong?
I feel a bit uneasy, can you please rub my back.
I see...
Alright...
Like this?
Uh, little bit more below...
Below?
Yes, a little more...
Right here?
Yes... There... thank you very much. Please keep that
up for a while.
Alright...
Oh, it feels good...
Someone told me you have Emo-Motion unlike
others... the rumors are true.
Your hand is so warm and comfortable.
Really? Thanks...
Can you continue torub me, but a bit more below...
Harue... like this?
It's so wet, I can't take this.
Manager... more...
What, more? Does she mean...
Hey, the silicon must be dried soon.
Um... I can't take these off myself... can you help out?
Uh, ok...
A, are you ready?
Yes...
Huh? They are stuck.
Manager, watch out!
I'm glad... you're safe...
Ha... Harue!
Oh, Manager!
Manager... Manager, I...
Yes, I... feel it.
This is... my... first... time... ohh.
Great, so great... I'm... embarrassed... so
embarrassing...
More, more, give me more! I am really a dirty little
girl! Yes, I feel it... it's great!
I'm going to cum, I'm cumming!
It's done.
Tadah! A breast shaped pudding!
Wow!
See, it's delicious.
Manager and Harue... they seem happy together...
Pudding?
Pudding, I am here... It's Shuta. Where are you
Pudding...
What's wrong, why did you bring me here?
Manager, um... well...
Stupid me... I can't ask about Harue...!
Danger! Pudding's Emo-Meter is in the negative
range!
What! That... what does that mean?
Um, my mom...
Huh?
My mom heard that you live by yourself... and asked
me to invite you over for dinner before the festival
What, your house!? Of course, I'll go! I will definitely
go!!
I'm home!
Manager, please come in.
I, I'm finally here. I'm so nervous.
Where are you Mom? Strange, I though she was
home today.
Welcome!!
Wow!
Huh, what!?
Mom! What are you doing!
I'm sorry... I meant to surprise you two, but... So sorry.
Who is... she?
I'm so sorry, I was a bit childish there. Thank you for
always taking care of Pudding.
Um... nice to meet you.
Mom, don't embarrass me.
I'm so sorry.
Same hairstyle, same face...
You two look... so much alike. Pudding you must look
like your mom...
Oh, I'm not that young!
Mom! No one said anything about being young.
Oh, I'm so sorry again.
I'm so sorry about earlier. I made lots of great dishes,
so eat up.
Mom, shesh...
Shuta, let me feed you. Say, Ahhh.
H, hey, wait. Mom!
Oops, I'm so sorry. He's your boyfriend.
Um, well... not really... a boyfriend...
I see...
Who would've thought I've spend the night at
Pudding's house. I'm so nervous.
Excuse me, Manager!
Wow, wait, hold on a second! I'm not ready yet!
She called me Manager... she must be Pudding? But
she looked like Mama Pudding for a second.
Manager, don't look at me so much. It's
embarrassing!
Thank you for treating me nice everyday... let me give
you a reward.
Um, ok, thanks.
He's nervous... so cute.
How is it, Manager?
Great...
Pudding, you have to be more pushy with the guy you
like... alright, Mama's going to ignite the fire for you
two.
Yes... It... feels good...
I'm so sorry.
Pudding, Pudding!
Wow, he's so energetic... and big.
Does it feel good?
Was Pudding always this forceful?
Oh, I'll make you feel even better.
Wow, Pudding... Pudding...
Manager, your thing is so... big.
This is great... Pudding is sucking on mine...
Pudding can really use her tongue... I never thought
Pudding is so...
N, no... I can't take this... I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
No, don't cum yet!
Manager, lets continue in my room.
Pudding said such things but... I'm very nervous to go
in her room. But she did tell me to come in her room
...I must be brave.
Pudding, it's me.
Pudding, are you not here? What!?
Kinky light settings, see through lingerie, a bed like
from a love hotel...
She has to be welcoming me!
Yes, the plan worked!
In fact, you are the same as me...
How stupid can I be... although she did invite me over
If I continue, I'll be the same as a Lividoll.
I'm sorry, Pudding.
What, Why? Pudding and Shuta were suppose to
get it on.
Hmm, Manager...
Huh, Pudding!?
Where are you going? I'm so lonely...
Because...
Manager, I want your hot thing...
But I though you were asleep.
No... I was shy and just pretended to be sleeping.
Are you sure it's ok...?
Yes...
Your lingerie seems different?
Oh, this? Um, well... I though you might like this
better, Manager. Do you not like it?
Well...
Alright... I'll take them off then.
Pu, Pu, Pu,
Pudding!
Don't need to rush... Manager.
Pudding, Mama is gonna get Shuta into the mood.
Once he's up hard, I'll switch places with you while
he's not looking.
Oh, don't need to rush... lets enjoy this slowly...
What, Pudding giving me a tit job?
Was Pudding always this forceful?
Crap, this is great!
She's even giving me a blowjob at the same time...
I'm going to cum...
No, wait... if you're goingto cum, cum inside me.
A, alright! Here I go!
It's deep inside me... it's inside, inside...
Manager, you're thing is so big... more, more... give me
more. Give me more of your big thing!
I'm cumming... I'm going... to... cum...
Huh, why are you here, Manager?
Pu, Pu, Pu, another Pudding? Wha, what is going
on!?
Oh, I see! I'm just having sex with you. I see... good
night...
That's right, I'm Mama Pudding!
That means... the bath incident was also...
Yes... I'm so sorry.
It's just that Pudding is such a baby when it comes to
this... and I just wanted to help her out.
I was going to change places with her, but the sex felt
so good and, well...
What am I going to do... Pudding saw me...
Oh, look at you. You're trying to deny it, but you're
still hard.
But still...
It's ok, Pudding won't remember a thing about this
when she wakes up. Lets have more fun.
Yes, it's so big...
Good morning... last night... I had a really kinky
dream!
Everyone should be here soon. Look at the people,
looks like they are having fun.
Yeah, lets take a brake.
Yes! Everyone looks like they are having fun...
No... people will see us...
I don't mind... actually this turns me on more.
No, not right there...
Um, well...
Pudding...
To be honest, I was very lonely.
I thought maybe something happened between you
and Harue... I'm also not sure if that incident last
night was a dream...
There's no way I can tell her the truth...
Please tell me one thing! Do you... do you care about
me!
Of course, I care about you the most!
Are you telling the truth?
Yes, I'm being very honest with you. I can't lie to you!
Then... please have me as you wish...
Yikes! I... I must have fallen asleep!
Looks like someone had fun.
Manager, please wake up! Wake up!
Harue... your breasts feels nice... Oh Mama Pudding
...if you continue to lick me...
Manager... Manager, I hate you!
Manager doesn't care about me at all.
Huh, what happened?
Misuzu?
White panties...
Shuta... I've always...
Hated you!!!
You made Pudding cry!
Alright, lets get ready. Lets forget about this bastard.
Manager, are you ok?
Are you hurt?
Nako... Harue...
Sorry, I have to go.
Pudding, I am so sorry. It was all my fault!
Pudding, I need you...
Pudding!
Pudding, lets head back. Everyone is waiting for us.
Pudding transformed into Black Pudding!
Let me explain again! When Pudding's Emo-Motion
reaches to the negative peak, she becomes Black
Pudding!
What do you need?
In fact, you are the same as me...
Pudding, I am so sorry. But I'm not lying by when I
say I care about you the most!
I see...
I know apologizing isn't going to help, but I do not
bend my words.
You said you care about me the most...
Yes, I did say that. You are and I am not lying!
Even if I do this to you?
Of course.
I see...
Even this?
Yes...
Not yes. You mean Yes, Ma'am!
Y, Yes, Ma'am!
Prove me that you care about me. I'll believe you if
you can make me cum.
Make Pudding cum? I am happ... no,
Yes... Yes Ma'am!
That's right...
Takashi, it feels goo...
I'm going to cum...
Me to, Chiko!
A monster!
Crap, it felt so good that I lost my concentration! Oh
well, stay quiet!
Noo!!
Halt!
Fighting Waitress, Jelly!
Parfait!
I am Panna Cotta!
Tiramisu!
Don't bother me!
Crap, he is strong! We need backup!
That's right... squeeze them tighter...
Looks like Pudding is getting closer to orgasm.
Manager, the Lividolls are attacking!
Where are you? Please answer! Can you hear me!?
I'm sorry, but I'm busy right now.
What, Manager? Manager!?
I have to do something about the Lividoll, but Pudding
is more important! I'm sorry, everyone!
What's wrong... you... can't make me... cum like this...
So you say... look at you... you are so wet...
Hmm, looks like Pudding is loosing some of the
blackness.
What, Pudding sticking my thing inside herself!?
Crap, Pudding might make me cum before I make her
cum!
What's wrong boy... can't you do any better?
Yes... Ma'am!
I can feel it all the way inside! I can feel it!
Yes, stir me more! Make me cum!
Crap, this is just too great!
Yes, yes, yes...
I'm going to cum... I'm going to cum!
Me... too! I'm going to cum... cum!!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!
This is the legendary Pudding Cutter!
Justice always win!
Justice?
Damn it, I almost had them! Crap...
Pudding, I'm so sorry!
Sex Warrior Pudding and friends won their battle over
the Lividoll Kingdom, but this is only the end. The real
battle and real true love is just about to begin! Don't
loose, Pudding! Do you best, Pudding! Oh... and you
to, Shuta.