Yes, that's it.
More.
Let me hear you play that vulgar tune.
Yes, you're almost there!
l'm coming!
More...
l want more!
What a beautiful sound.
Anal Sanctuary Vol. 1
See you tomorrow!
Damn it!
Why?
Everything was going perfectly...
Why couldn't l move my fingers?
Excuse me...
l don't know what happened...
But you shouldn't get your violin wet.
Your violin will get damaged
due to dampness and water.
l'm sorry. l know it's
none of my business but...
You're right.
lt's not the violin's fault.
Umm...
Here...
But what about you?
lt's ok, l live around here.
l never thought l'd see her here...
l'll never use that on her.
Stop.
l just can't do it to her.
Excuse me.
Kozuki-kun right?
l'm done with your lesson for today.
l have to ask you something.
What is it?
What do you think of my performance?
l can see you're trying.
You should keep on practicing.
That's not good enough!
l want to get much better.
Much...
Better than her...
l want to be better than Shion-san!
Asahina-kun huh?
She's in a different
league than you are.
You should give up.
No!
l just can't do that!
Please! l want you to
teach me how to play.
l'll do anything to get better.
You're willing to get
better at any cost?
Yes.
Hold this.
What?
But this is your important violin.
You just have to put your hand on it.
Try to learn it by feeling.
Y-Yes...
Sensai...
Concentrate on your playing!
Yes.
There are rare instruments that
show the performer an illusion.
Stradivarius is one
of those instruments...
But the instrument
you're using right now...
...is called the devil's violin.
A devil?
Are you afraid?
But if you play this rare instrument...
...you can feel a different type
of sound than you normally would.
Plus this will provide you
with a keen artistic sense.
No...
Are you embarrassed?
Then l'll stop...
No, please continue.
Fine.
You still have some feeling left
over from the devil's violin.
Try playing it on your violin.
This is just...
You're just going to quit?
l can't believe you're
wasting all your effort.
l should've just let Miss
Asahina experience this.
No!
Please continue.
Then spread your body out.
Feel the sound of the
violin with your body.
Yes.
No...
Sensai is watching me but...
lt's my first time...
l can't believe he's watching me...
Moaning like this in this
embarrassing position.
No...
But what happens if l resist?
What's the matter? Your body is tense.
Yes...
l can't let him see me wet.
This is a very important lesson.
No...
l'm feeling it.
That's good.
Now what do you do
in order to feel more?
l think you know how.
l can't do such an
embarrassing act on my own.
But...
You're confused.
That's the correct answer Serika.
No, it hurts!
Please don't look at me...
lt's an important lesson.
You're feeling it a lot
and loving this very much...
No...
l'm not...
Stop...
How do you feel?
Explain it to me in detail.
Yes.
My entire body feels hot.
Especially my boobs and...
They feel numb...
What feels numb?
Say it loud so l can hear it.
My crotch hurts and it's numb...
But it feels so hot.
Every time they go inside
me, it feels like...
No...
Not there...
Stop...
No...
Are you sure?
lt looks like you're enjoying it.
Please don't look at me...
l can't believe it feels so good...
This is cruel...
lt's just cruel.
No...
This is not right...
Let me see your face.
Suck on it.
l understand.
No. lf l quit right now...
My effort will be wasted.
Here l come.
Where am l?
Music room...
Then that was all...
Hey, she's awake.
l wonder what she'll do tonight.
What are you embarrassed about?
People are here to see
you play the violin.
But l can't play like this.
Play.
Yes, l understand.
She's completely naked
and playing the violin.
How erotic.
l hope she looks this way all the time.
Don't look at me.
She's feeling it.
Please stop looking at me.
This is cruel.
lt's just too cruel.
You sounded good Serika.
What?
Your skills are finally
starting to bloom.
After getting sexually aroused,
your playing is so much better.
Am l better than Shion?
Yes, of course.
But in order for you to get much better
you need to...
...experience more embarrassing things
and be sexually stimulated.
Can you handle it?
Embarrassing things...
Yes, l'll tolerate any
kind of embarrassing act.
Good girl.
What's this?
No, l'll wet myself...
Stop pushing...
l'll...
Wet myself...
Please stop filming me...
Are you kidding?
This will be an important
material for my teaching.
You should be happy.
What...
No!
lf you move that violently...
l can't take it...
Wonderful.
l can't believe you can do
this without any hesitation.
They must really like your stuff.
They're eating it.
lt's terrible.
Kozuki-san was struggling
so much in the past...
l heard she got better because
of Mr. Yashiro's special lessons.
Wow, l'm jealous.
l want to take Mr.
Yashiro's special lessons too.
What a beautiful sound.
l feel like getting sucked in.
No, my body feels hot.
Why am l getting wet?
lt's like l'm...
No, it won't stop.
Sensai...
Excuse me...
You can't get up?
l'm sorry...
You made such a mess in
this prestigious school!
l'll have to punish you...
Please forgive me.
l'm begging you.
No.
Do you realize that was a
sacrilegious behavior on your part?
Please forgive me.
l'm begging you.
No...
Ouch.
Who's there?
Kozuki-san.
How dare you look away
when l'm talking to you!
l think you need to
be punished even more.
We're just getting started.
Nanahara-san...
Let's clean out your stomach.
No, no, no!
Are you ready Nanahara-san?
No...
Stop, l can't hold it in...
l can't take it anymore...
l can't breathe...
Hey.
Yes.
Nanahara-san, l'll treat you real good.
No!
Stop it.
Not there...
lt feels good...
No...
Don't do her there. We're
supposed to punish her.
l'm really sorry.
This is...
No...
Not there...
No!
lt doesn't hurt.
ln fact, it's rather hot
and it feels strange...
lt tickles.
No, it feels so good...
Hey, what's wrong?
Your ass is twitching.
No, don't...
Don't say that.
Are you feeling good?
Unbelievable. She
enjoys getting punished.
Why don't we use that stuff?
That stuff?
Oh yeah.
Don't look at me.
l'll go crazy.
This is just...
Yeah, l guess this really
doesn't count as punishment.
Even if we put this into the anus...
His delicate fingers are entering my...
Sensai, use this...
You're very attentive.
Thank you very much.
No, please stop it.
Take a look at yourself...
You've never seen
yourself like this right?
Kozuki-san, why?
Sensai, use this now.
Yes.
No, don't...
Stop it.
What's wrong?
No.
You look very stiff. What's wrong?
Please stop this.
You make me want to touch
you more if you say that.
l'll do anything you say.
You'll do anything?
Yes.
Then Serika, let's move on.
What...
l'm begging you.
l need to go to the bathroom!
lt's hot and my stomach...
No! l can't hold it in!
Please!
Nobody's gonna help you, Miss
Nanahara.
There's no point in begging,
you'll just have to do it here.
No...
Why...
lt's so hot.
lt's hot and getting numb...
lt's embarrassing but...
More, more...
Tease me more...
Please...
lt's embarrassing.
No...
l...
This is the school's church?
Then that was all a dream?
lt wasn't a dream.
Yukina-san.
Elaine-san?
You're alright now.
The nightmares are over.
But this is not the time to cry.
Yukina, l need your help.
Me?
Yes.
ln order to save those that were
possessed by that devil's violin...
l need your help.