Koutaro...
Koutaro... wake up...
Mom...!?
I'm sorry, Koutaro...
I'm so lonely after your father passed away.
Mom...
You remind me of him...
I know we're not blood related, but I'm sorry...
It's OK, Mom...
Ever since I saw you, I was in love with you... so
Thank you, Koutaro.
You are the only one I can rely on...
Mom... I have never...
It's OK, let me...
Mom, your tits are big and soft...
It's OK to breast feed... you are my son.
Alright...
Koutaro... harder...
Koutaro...
Koutaro, how is mommy's breast?
Delicious...
Please... stick it in me... Koutaro...!
Mom!
Me having sex with Mom... it's a dream come true.
Koutaro, it's great... great!
Better than your dad's!
It's not fair that dad had you first.
Don't say such a thing...
Mom, I'm going to cum... inside!
I'm going to cum too... cum... together!
Mom!!!
Koutaro!!!
Bro!!!
Bro, the store!
Where's mom!?
Mom?
Huh, I did her in my dreams?
Did what?
That's right, I have to open!
Wow, hey, stop it!
You pervert!
Your fault for being in my room!
Die, you pervert!
Ouch!
Sakura Market
The store Dad left behind.
A very important treasure.
I will protect this store, Mom and Nagisa!
Hey!
How's the store going, oh Manager?
What do you want!?
Have you reached the agreement of million dollars?
With this small store, I think not.
You better be ready to pack up.
I will never take an advice from a traitor like you!
Taiyo.
Mom!
My, my... hello Minato.
Call her Mom! She has too much to
worry about now that Dad is gone!
Koutaro...
We are doing the best we can right
now so please don't bother us, please!
What beautiful family love.
You guys really accept each other as family?
Shut up!
Whatever, do your best.
By the way, even once we own
this store, we won't disown you guys.
Don't forget that Mr. Kaneshiro is a generous man!
Come Manager.
Lets do our best as usual.
You're right, Mom.
Welcome!
We have lots of fresh food, Ma'am!
Wife with Wife Part 1
- This is a Housewife Supermarket -
Cabbage... 248 yen
Lettuce... 198 yen.
Welcome!
Think straight, Manager!
How much is this?
Y, Yes!
Well, how much?
Big ones are two for 350 yen
Excuse me.
Manager?
What's wrong?
Hey Touko, how are you?
Fine.
I was checking up on something.
This is wrong.
There is one zero missing.
What? I'm so sorry.
This one too.
I'm so sorry...
Touko, please come to my office.
Yes...
Hey, Koutaro, wait...!
Koutaro... my son has gotten the fever and
I was taking care of him until late and...
Touko, call me Manager at the store.
I'm... sorry...
What are you doing?
No, this it's still working hours...
If Kou has a fever, it means you're
not feeding him much.
Mmm, the smell of thick milk.
Koutaro...
That's Manager...
Yes...
Touko, this is your punishment for that mistake.
Manager...
I have to teach you some discipline.
The fun is just starting.
Manager, not here!
That's why...
This is very exciting...
Here I go...
The pussy that recently gave birth...
My cock goes in so smoothly.
Don't say such mean things...
It's so wet and feels so good!
I wonder how Mom's feel...?
M, Mom!?
Let your mom wash your back, Koutaro.
That's not... a good idea...
Why?
What if Nagisa sees...
Huh? Nagisa went to karaoke with her friends.
Besides, we're family.
We are, but...
Is it because we're not blood related...?
No, that's not what I meant...
Please... wash my back...
Koutaro...
Koutaro, you have your father's back.
It is very manly.
Ummm...
Don't move.
Hey...
Hmm?
Why did you marry my Dad?
Well...
Especially with us bothers as luggage...
And I have Nagisa.
I do want to tell you something, later...
One thing for sure is that we
were madly in love with each other.
That is the truth.
Mom...
Mom!?
I love Choichiro so much...
Choichiro, why did you leave me behind...
Why did you...
Mom, calm down...
Choichiro... you are so... cruel...
Mom held me tightly and let all her stress
out on me...
That one incident made me look
at my Mom differently...
It's so great!
Right after that incident, that's when I met Touko...
That's a good little boy.
Miss, looks like you need a hand.
Hi, Manager.
If you can wait a bit, I'll deliver them to your house.
Hi, it's Sakura Market, I'm here with your items.
I'm sorry, I'm in the shower.
Can you please leave it on the kitchen table?
Sure, not a problem.
Alrighty...
Thank you.
No...!?
Hey, take a rest.
My son is asleep and I'm bored.
Lets do something fun.
Do you mind?
Ma'am, this isn't right...
You hard means OK, doesn't it?
Ma'am, your son...
Kou won't even wake up in an earthquake.
Kou?
His name is Koutaro.
Ma'am, your husband...
My husband is always busy with his work.
I haven't had any in a while and I need some now...
I need more excitement...
Ma'am...
My name is Touko...
Your big man hood fits perfectly between my chest.
It's so soft and great...!
My hubby has a small one and it's boring.
It's big, so big! I like it!
Ma'am, this is great, really great!
Please call me Touko.
Touko!
You came already? Too quick!
Well... this is my first time...
Great, I got your cherry!
I haven't had a big one for a while...
I'm so happy.
This is sex...
That's right, sex...
Better than masturbation?
Yes!
Touko chose me to relieve her stress.
I accepted her so I can keep
my mind away from my Mom.
It was a great happening to relieve my needs...
I hired Touko as a part time for my sexual needs.
I thought this would help keep my
mind away from Mom.
Touko, it felt so good I came inside.
Please take care of it.
Am I evil...?
Yes, don't worry...
I hope Kou gets better soon.
Thank you Koutaro, you are so nice.
That's why I like you.
That's not true.
And call me Manager while we're working.
What are you looking at!?
Shut up!
Mom, Bro is perverted!
He got excited looking at me.
Shut up, who would get excited
with your premature body!
What did you say!?
Did you hear that, Mom?
Don't worry, he's just shy.
Shy?
That's right, because you've grown so beautiful.
Mom...
Koutaro, sorry...
Damn it...
Oh, Touko. How is Kou doing?
Thank you, he's doing well and
now he won't stop drinking my milk.
My nipples hurt because of it.
Hey, remember to save some for me.
Let me drink some later.
Yes, of course Manager.
Ma'am, wait.
Ma'am!
What is it!?
Can you please show me your purse?
Why?
Well...
Something wrong?
Uh, well...
I didn't see it happening.
I better think of something, quick.
What is it!?
Don't blame me randomly.
Ma'am you're loud...
Manager, problems?
Oh, it's nothing.
Ma'am, please come with me.
Hey, let go.
If I'm wrong, I'm sorry.
But if there is something, I would need to check.
Um... Ma'am? Ma'am?
Well, if I scream now, would there be
a problem then?
Stop it! Are you threatening me!?
Ma'am, please!
I'm so sorry!
I'm going!
Sorry!
Wait, I haven't got to the bottom of this!
Man, I quit school for this?
I'm pooped...
Please stop, let go!
Stop!
If you give up the store, I'll listen to you.
I'll give Koutaro a job and you Mr. Kaneshiro's wife.
And Nagisa my second wife.
What are you...!
You won't need to worry about
money as Mr. Kaneshiro's wife!
Bro, stop it!
A knight in shining armor?
Whatever, anyways think about it.
Are you alright, Mom?
I'm sorry, Koutaro...
I'm so weak...
No Mom, you were brave.
Koutaro...
I will protect Mom, Nagisa and this store...
I have to take care of Mom, the store... and Nagisa.
It's not easy taking care of two girls
and a store together...
Especially now that my little sister
is a grown woman.
And that incident...
What am I stressing about?
I should get a reward for working so hard.
That's it, I will...
Have her...
Nagisa...
Nagisa, I'm sorry...
Nagisa is still a virgin
However, Mom on the other hand...
Mom, I hope you were waiting for me.
This is where Mom and Dad...
W, who!?
Ko... Koutaro!?
Mom, not so loud. Nagisa is upstairs.
What are you doing, Koutaro!?
Stop it!
I won't.
I have already decided to sleep with you.
You're responsible for this too, Mom.
Mom, this tastes like honey.
I'm jealous that my dad had this every night.
Don't say such things!
Mom!
This isn't right...!
Listen to me, Mom!
Mom, Please!
Please understand my feelings!
Koutaro.
Mom, your breast are perfect for some tit fucking.
Isn't it big as my dad's?
Koutaro, no!
But you had sex with me in my dreams.
Dreams?
Here I go, Mom.
No!!
How is it compared with Dad's?
Please, don't say that Koutaro.
Well?
Please... don't talk about your dad right now...
So you mean, you're fine with this?
Mom, let me cum.
Mom, I'm going to cum!
Me too, Koutaro!
Can I... please...
What...?
Cum... cum inside you, Mom!
I want to remember this day forever!
OK... alright!
Please cum inside me!
Here I go, Mom!!!
Koutaro!!
Mom, I love you.
Koutaro...
Is this a dream or reality?
Am I the one who's betraying my Dad?
But I can't step back...
I have to love Mom as a woman forever...
With Nagisa...
The End