Yikes!
Slurpy, slurpy.
You!
Sick Pervert!
So it's you!
The rapist on the loose!
Slurpy slurpy!
What!? How did you? He's not human!?
Me tongueish a vibrator... sssllurpy!
No, argh!
Yikes...
Meish a Lividoll that brings you pleasure...
don't you love me slurpy?
Stronger...
Weaker...
You see? You pussy juice flowing like a river...
No...
I'm being violated, yet I like it...
This is so embarrassing!
What? The fun ish just about to start!
Hold it right there!
Whoish it!?
Spin!
Twirl!
We are here to take your order!
Sex Warrior Pudding are the fighting
waitresses!
They fight to bring smiles to the people!
Sex Warrior
Pudding!! At your service!
Twat!?
Sex Warrior Fever...
Flash!!
So, the Lividoll's true form is a mere doll.
Hmm, the Sex Warrior...
I'll remember that.
Wow, that must been hard on you.
But I'm glad you are safe.
Yeah, but those girls who saved me, I think
I saw them from somewhere...?
Haha, you are thinking too much.
But it's amazing that you are working as a
manager at Alamode,
the restaurant where your girl, Pudding,
works at. Huh...
Well, I...
This was really unexpected.
Where is this place?
Welcome.
To Alamode, Shuta...no.
Manager.
Huh? Manager?
Wow!
Wait, what is happening here!?
Think of this as a welcoming gift and our
obedience.
I'm sorry for the late introduction.
I am the assistant manager of Alamode,
Chiyoko.
Here...
This is from your late father.
My father?
Wassup dude!!
How ya doing foolio?
I'll make this really quick and simple for ya.
While I was experimenting new inventions,
I was also running this restaurant.
Well, now that I'm gone, you will need to
take care of this place!
Thanks dude!
Dude?
If you want the 411, ask Chiyoko.
I'll check you out later!
Father, wait! Wait!
Manager...
This restaurant, Alamode is also a
crime fighting organization...
...the World Defense Federation!
World? Defense?
Earth is being invaded by a mysterious group
of beings known as the Lividolls.
They are the culprits behind the rape incidents
that have been committing lately.
I don't know what you just said,
but this feels too good...
This is why Alamode was created...
To defeat the great powers of the Lividolls.
We need the power of "people's smile".
What can be better than a restraint to gather
these smiles?
That's the reason why your father was running
this place.
This story sounds a bit farfetched...
Damn, you're sucking me harder now.
Crap, I'm about to...
Cum!!
What?
Welcome Manager!!
Are you for real?
I am... I am the restaurant's...
Oh fuck, my dick!!
I am Pudding Nishimura, nice to meet you
Manager.
Manager? Me!?
That's amazing, a guy who plays animated
porn games all day long
in love with a real girl.
Misuzu, don't call it an animated porn game.
They are...
Bishojyo games!
So, what's it about her that you like?
Those big tits?
Nah, it's all about her smile. Not to mention
that cute voice and pretty face.
Manager looks so happy when he's talking to
that girl...
Excuse me.
Be right there!
What are you up too?
I'll show you that real girls can't keep their
smile all the time
like the girls from your games.
How may I help you?
Are you ok?
Um, yes, I'm alright.
I am sorry Manager.
No, it was our fault.
I'm glad you're ok.
This is it, the smile that I like.
Emoguage up by 30%.
Understood.
Please tell Manager to come inside the
Manager's office.
Chiyoko.
Are you sure this is right?
Yes, don't worry about it.
The manager and his employees have to share
their body and soul. It's a duty.
I don't understand it at all.
But...
Who gives a damn!!
This feels good...
Hmm, I want to try out the position I've seen
from the game.
Like it? Do you like it!?
Yes, I love it, Manager!
Your pussy it so tight!
Cumming...
It's ok, please, please cum inside me...
Wwhat?
A Lividoll is spotted at the park! He's violating
the girls around the area!
Everyone, get ready to dispatch!
Wow.
Sex Warriors ready to go...
Crap!! I totally forgot!!
Manager, please give the orders.
Yes, sir!
Rubby dubby.
No!
Hold it right there!!
Who is it!!
Sex Warrior
Pudding!
Jelly!
Pannacotta!
Such a beautiful view.
What the...!
I like this one.
Yikes!
Rubby dubby.
Oh no.
You girly boobies are great.
Sex Warrior Rod!
Hold it right there girly.
If you want this girly in one piece, you put that
thing down.
I'm the Lividoll's number one boobie rubber.
Boobie ruby feels great.
Hohoho, so you threw away your weapon.
Now I can rub your boobies too.
Raaaa, I will make sure King Lividoll gets his
pleasure!
King Lividoll?
Is that the name of the mastermind?
Argh... You are unfair...
How you like it! What I feel, King Lividoll feels
it too.
Good rubby dubby.
I rubby you more!
Oh no!
I can tell you really likey this.
It feels good...
Oh no, Pudding!
Chiyoko, I am going to go! I can't stand seeing
her like that!
Yes, please!
Huh?
What?
Wow!
Shuta?
Hohoho, ready to cum?
Are you ready to cum?
Yikes!
Are you alright, Pudding?
Shit, I forgot!
Manager!
I can not forgive you!
Pudding's Emogauge is now on max!
Manager, Pudding has a secret power that
no others have.
The only person who can activate this power is
you, Manager.
Huh?
The password is "Maid Up".
Maid...Up?
Maaaaid Uuu!!....
What's wrong Pudding?
I can handle this guy without your help,
Manager.
Frame Up!!
Emoload One, Power Frame Mode!
Pudding, you are disobeying orders!
Raaar, you are annoying!
Pudding! We have to work together and do
Maid Up.
I can...do it by
myself!!
Pudding Dynamic!
Damn it...
Not again!
Pudding!
Why... why didn't you do Maid Up!?
What just happened?
Pudding is a Sex Warrior?
Stop right there.
You passed, Ms. Terai, no, Tiramisu.
Tiramisu?
Why is Misuzu here?
The fight we had two days ago.
She was there looking at the whole thing.
I told her about our organization and decided
to test her abilities.
Misuzu a Sex Warrior?
Hey Pudding.
Manager, looks like you haven't been doing
well with Ms. Nishimura lately.
Yeah, I think she hates me at the moment.
I have a solution.
What? What is it!?
Have sex with her!
What am I going to do... well, I guess I should
start by talking to her.
Manager.
Wow, Celica, aren't you working?
I'm on break now!
Thank you for saving me. I was really happy.
Nako.
Celica! What are you doing? What if someone
sees!
This is only a small present for saving me.
Do you not like it?
I didn't mean it that way.
Great.
Do you hate small breasts?
No way, I like them!
Is this heaven!?
I know Manager helped us, but he didn't do
anything to me when I was naked.
Argh, stupid stupid!
Cheer up, Pudding!
I have to say thank you to him for saving us.
Pudding, this is... err...
What is it?
Well, umm, this...
Crap, Celica is sucking me harder now... this
feels too good.
I'm working right now.
Hey, wait!
I can't hold it any longer!
He doesn't even chase after me for leaving like
that...
My newest innovation is finally created!
The Sex Warriors are surely going to get it this
time.
I have combined Licker and Rubber together to
create!...
Rubby Licky!
Roooar!!
I think I saw Pudding going to the locker room.
Pudding.
Pudding, it's me.
Oh.
Misuzu...
Shuta, I meant, Manager.
This doesn't look right on me, huh?
No, it does.
I join this team not to save the Earth, but...
There's someone here that I like.
See, my heart is pounding so fast. A tomboy
like me...
Don't say that.
Wow, look at what I'm doing to Misuzu. I can't
stop!
Manager is already getting involved with
Misuzu, the new recruit.
What is this feeling? I have heavy...Oh, I am
wet!?
Why? Why am I so turned on? Pudding, no...
No, this is not you, but the hands will not stop!
Noo!
I'm going to rub you then lick you, rubby licky!
The women at the park are being violated!
Tiramisu, Jelly, Pannacotta, get ready to
dispatch!
Yes, ma'am!
What about me? I don't go with them?
You have disobeyed orders last time so you're
on parole.
You got that Manager?
Huh?
Yeah...
Yes, Sir!
Pudding!
Hold it right there!
Sex Warrior
Tiramisu!
Jelly!
Pannacotta!
Rooooar!
Yikes!
Sex Warriors in danger!
Already!?
Pudding...
everyone is in danger and we need your help!
But...!
You're the one who gave orders for.
Unless if we fight together as one,
there is no way to stop the enemy.
I want you to open your heart to me and go
help them.
I can't...I can't trust you anymore...
If I was a character from a game....
Alright, I should do the same.
I can't, I can't do it...
That's the wound from the time Manager
saved me.
Pudding, I'll be honest.
The one I love is you!!
If you don't love me, I don't care about this
planet anymore.
I want you to open your heart to me.
Well...
I am a bad girl, sorry...
Don't say that.
So please...punish me.
Punish...ohh...
Please...
Well...
You won't even do it when I'm like this?
Alright!
I'm going to punish you!
Alright? I'm going to stick it in...
It hurts...!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'll be fine...
Wonderful!
Hot...
It's big...
It's good...
No, I'm about to cum!
Pudding's Emogauge is to the max!
What!?
I don't know what happened... anyways, have
her dispatched!
Hehehe, this is the end of the Sex Warriors.
What is that?
What!?
Huh, what is this? I'm flying?
Oh, this is embarrassing!!
Wow! When two hearts become one, a great
power is born.
This must be the legendary Super Pudding!
Legendary?
I can't look like this forever!
Here I go!
Electrifying Pudding Kick!
You did it, Pudding!
The power of love... it's so powerful!
Love?
It's all thanks to you Manager. Really...
Pudding...
Don't touch her!
Pudding is! Pudding is!
That's right, Misuzu likes Manager.
She is mine!
Don't tell me that person is...
It's Pudding.
What the...
Damn those Sex Warriors!
Fuck.
Not fair... me too.
Stop it!
The war is not over yet. The battle of love has
just started.
You can do it Pudding! Don't be so discouraged
Pudding!
Oh, and you too, Shuta!