Alright! The main event is ready to start!
Here are the competitors for the "Wow!
Beautiful Waitress Swim Event."
First we have the energetic Celica.
Then we have the angel of smile, Harue.
Baby faced Nako.
And last but certainly not least, Pudding!
Pu, Pudding!
Looks like Pudding is on fire today.
Let's get the opening ceremony started.
Biiiiiiiitch!
Every stupid moron cheering for Pudding.
Hold on a second!
How do you like it? ...my beautiful body, great
assets, and this erotic swimsuit?
All the guys are now...
What the hell!
Pudding!
I challenge you to a duel!
No problem!
What the...!
Since you seem like you have great spirits, I
will allow you to compete in this competition.
Umm...
Our first competition is 100 meters free style.
Get ready, on your marks...
Hehehe, my goal is not to win Pudding, but to
embarrass her by taking off her bra.
No, this is embarrassing!
Get set...
Hehehe, little does she know I'm swimming at
her pace.
Now! What?
Goal! Pudding places first!
No, this is embarrassing!
Next time, I'll make sure I do it!
No!!
Oh, this is so embarrassing!
Hey...
I'm the one that is suppose to make you
embarrassed,
But you keep doing it by yourself!
Why are you such an airhead!
Yikes, I'm so sorry!
That's it. Just taking off her bra isn't going to
do it!
I'm going to take off her bottoms too.
This is the last event, the Calvary Fight!
Manager, thank you for helping out.
Yeah, sure, not a problem.
Will the winners be Team Pudding...?
Or will it be the new Challenger, Team Ai,
or etc?
What!
Etc!?
Booo!
Now, go!!!
Yikes no!
Oh no, Pudding.
Oh, I'm so sorry, my hands slipped...
Hehehe, take that! She must be humiliated
with all these people around!
Hurry up and whimper back... what!
I am not going to loose!
Oh, Pudding's secret bush is rubbing against
my head...
Take that!
I'm not a pervert!
That's what I thought!
Watch out, Pudding!
Is this... this is great... but I'm going to die...
Uh oh! Team Pudding is out of the game.
The winner is Team Ai.
Hold it right there, Pudding! I'll get you
next time!
But you won, how weird.
Sex Warrior Pudding are the fighting
waitresses!
They fight to bring smiles to the people!
No!
Shit!
Yahahaha! I ish called Fan Boy.
Let I wind blow and show I your panties.
Everyone! Let's use Sex Warrior Kick!
OK!
Alright!
Yaaa!
Se... x Warrior! Kii... ck!
Yahahaha, show I panties!
Fan Boy powers up.
Sex Warrior Kick Counter!
What!? Sex Warrior Kick does not work?
Hoho, you guys can still stand up after
I counter attack, hmm?
Yahahaha, looks like this girl can't get up.
I rape you!
Nako!
Shit!
Chiyoko! Nako is in!
Yes, Manager, please go save her!
Yaooo!
Yahahaha, if you get close, I ish going to kill
her!
Bastard...!
Yahahaha! You have cute tits. I like small tits.
No!
I rubbing, I rubbing.
Let's see over here... Yohoho, it's so wet.
Ahh, oh... stop...
I rubbing, I rubbing... you slut, you like it.
Sshit!
What can we do...!
What ish you talking about... look how wet her
pussy is!
Oh... Noooo!
Ish open, ish open. Yohohoho.
I'm so embarrassed, I have never shown
anyone.
Alright, time for the grand finale.
Huh!?
She's so tight that I can't push it in!
Whaaaaaaaaaa!
Wow!
Yohoho!
This guy... he powers up the Sex Warriors...
Power up!
I might lose...
I might lose... I ish no like...
Check you out later!
Hey, wait!
That Lividoll is smart...
Manager...
Na, Nako... What is wrong...
Nako...
I should go home soon...
Oh, sorry... I didn't mean to burst in like this.
It's just that you're here pretty late so I was
worried about you.
It's been a while since the restaurant closed.
You've been here all this time just for me?
Sorry, I will go back to the working ground.
Please don't go...
Na, Nako!?
You're in a kimono today... looks really great
on you...
My household is very traditional.
I've been raised to be polite ever since I was
very little
and I thought holding in your feelings was
quite normal.
But ever since I started working here and met
you, I have changed. I am happier now.
Then, don't worry about today. Smile and
forget about what happened.
Oh, I thought of something we can laugh
about.
Umm, can you please hold this?
Are you ready? Here I go...
Um, ok...
Wha... - t!
Was it not funny?
Hahaha, no, it was funny! But I told you to
smile not me.
I'm not good at smiling so I want you to smile.
That's why I want you to be my first...
No panties!!
Um, but...
I know. I know you like Pudding, but please for
now...
Look at me.
Na, Na, Na, Nako!
Oh, not this... it feels too good...
I can't hold it much longer!
Who, who... who can resist this!
Na, Nanana, Nako, here I go.
Ok...
Nako, are you still here?
If we don't go home soon, the last train will
leave.
Strange, I thought I heard someone in here.
I must be thinking too much.
It hurts, but my body is hot.
It's inside, it's inside Nako.
What have I done...?
Crap, crap... What if someone sees, but it feels
too good to stop!
Well, I better get back to work.
Phew, we're safe.
Just kidding!
Um, hahaha. Well, how should I explain this?
Hahaha, Manager, you are so perverted.
Sorry to bother you.
Pudding! Nako, sorry.
Hold up! Pudding!
I'm not going to wait!
Sorry, that wasn't right...
You don't need to apologize. I'm not mad at
you.
I mean, it's not like we're a couple.
Not couples? I...
...elieve you.
Huh!?
I can't believe you anymore... that you love me.
Besides... umm...
Its sticking out.
Oh crap!
Pudding.
Yikes, Manager, what are you doing?
I'll prove it.
No, don't... this... no...
Oh... Manager, please, stop...
No...
Are you sure you don't like it? You are so wet
down here...
This is how I feel about you!
I love you and I would always want to have
sex with you!
Argh... Pudding's inside is so warm.
Ohh, ahh, Manager, you're so...
No, I love you Pudding! I have to prove you
my love for you!
Ohh... ahhh!!
N, no... Manager, you're so rough, why, ahh,
my body!
Nako, why are you...
I'm sorry, Pudding. I was the one who seduced
him.
Manager was just trying to cheer me up...
Ahh, if you keep doing that, I...
But when I become one with Manager, I felt
safe...
Manager, please have do us as you will.
Pudding, you are going to be first!
My mind is so blank...
Nako, you're next!
I've never seen Nako so happy.
Ohh, Pudding, Pudding you...
Ahh, Nako, I am going to...!
Inside! Please cum inside me! Inside!
Yahaha, so you guys are here Sex Warriors!
Show me your panties again!
Assistant Manager! Nako's Emogauge is to the
MAX!
Manager, please have Nako do Maid Up!
Maiii... - d
Only a waitress that is totally in sync with
Manager can do Maid UP. That means Nako...!?
Up!
Enfeebling Scan!
There it is! Fan Boy, you are weak to...
This!
Oh crap... umph...
Another peaceful day thanks to the Sex
Warriors. To the battlefield, Sex Warriors!
Damn it.
My cute little Lividoll!
I'll get you next time!
Welcome! Please come by!
Hey!
Hohoho, how do you like my restaurant?
Who are you?
It's me, Ai! Remember me, god damn it!
Anyways, now that we are rivals, let's do our
best. Although at this rate.
Looks like your restaurant will go bankrupt,
hehehe.
Bankrupt?
Alamode?
That's unheard of, hahaha.
We're going bankrupt.
But that's not it. If we have no customers,
we won't be able to get the energy from their
smiles.
That means there will no longer be any
Sex Warriors.
That means we have to figure out something.
I wonder if it's ok.
Hmm... Maybe if we stick closer, we look like
couples, but don't get any ideas.
We're only doing this to find out their secret,
ok?
This is unique Manger...
Yeah...
Sorry to keep you waiting. My name is Betty.
Here you go.
No, I don't... that's not... well...
Don't say that.
Pu, Pudding!
How do you like our service, Shuta?
Ai!?
How did you know it was me?
Did you think that I wouldn't know?
Here's a house special ice cream just for you.
My, this looks so delicious.
Manager, don't please. I want to stop...
But I can't resist this!
Let me take a bite.
Aiyee, Manager is so perverted.
Hehehe, Pudding is so jealous. Now is the time
to finish her off.
Don't forget about the main dish.
Is it right to have her while Pudding is looking
at me?
Besides, what kind of service is this!?
Manager, don't. Ahhh!
When did you get such a thing, but... ohhh...
Shuta, see... Pudding is having a great time.
B, but...
Oh, I feel good...
Come...
Here I go!
Manager, Manager, No~~!
Its hot, it's hot!
Oh, it's hitting deep...
Ahh, no, ohh!
No, I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Your majesty, hurry...
Hmm, where do you want it? Say it.
I want it here. I want your majesty's big cock
right here.
You are a slut.
Ohh, it's big.
Ahh, it feels good...
How are the plans going? Did you find out the
Sex Warrior's weakness?
No, not yet, but Shuta is almost mine...
What!? I had sex with Ai!?
Is this for real, Pudding!?
Yes, it's true. I don't remember much.
But probably, I was part of it as well.
You!
Summersault
What in the hell did you go spying for!
Attack
You bastard!
Misuzu, wait! Don't blame him too much.
I was part of the orgy too...
That's what Trifle does so, please,
don't blame Manager too much...
Huh!?
What's wrong with me, hehehe.
Pudding is very depressed. It's all my fault.
Because of my actions, Pudding is...
Chiyoko, what are you...
There is something I would like to check on.
Chiyoko, what is the meaning of this?
When you came back from Trifle, you had a
strange odor.
If I check your sperm, I'm sure I can find out
something.
So please don't hesitate to cum.
I, I, I can't hold it in any longer!
This taste!!
Huh? What is it!
I do not know.
Anyway, I'll let the research lab take a look at
this. Thank you for your time.
Yes?
Shuta, aren't you coming over today?
Ai!?
I am very wet right now.
You hear that? Can't you hear that kinky
sound?
You promised you will come today. Let's have
fun together again.
I want your big cock, Shuta!
Ai!?
Ai!
Putting Shuta aside, we have to come up with
a plan.
Pudding, did you realize anything while you
were at Trifle?
Umm... We had sex...
Huh, where is Shuta?
I haven't seen him for a while.
I'm so happy.
Argh... I can't take this, but...
Crap, I'm under Ai's control. But, what else can
I do to find out Trifle's secret...
Don't cum yet... you have to give me a huge
load...
Yes, ahh... it's, it's good...
Shuta... do you feel good too?
Y, yeah...
To be honest, the best!
I'm so happy. Give it to me more... Shuta...
Like this?
Crap, I'm falling into her trap.
Shuta...
Huh?
You are the leader of the Sex Warriors,
correct?
Wha, what are you talking about?
Don't act like you don't know... we all know.
We know about you, we also know that
Pudding is a Sex Warrior...
Please tell me the Sex Warrior's secret...
That is...
I don't know! Even if I did, I won't tell you!
Strange... he is snapping out of it!?
Oh really?
Shuta, don't you like me?
Yeah...
Ai! Now, I know the secret of Trifle!
That perfume from that amulet is controlling
the people!
I won't loose to such a thing!
After all, I have Pudding with me!
Impossible!? Perfume Li'stunthome, isn't
working!
And it's bigger than ever!
The reason is this!
Pudding's panties!
I borrowed these panties from Pudding so that
I won't fall for another girl!
So I am fine, thanks to this!
I won't fall for your tricks any longer!
Ahh, no...
If you keep doing that... I'm going to...!
I lost!
Damn! That was so close too!
Shit!
Hey Pudding, what's up.
Yikes!
I'm so embarrassed!
Again, the world's peace was saved thanks to
the Sex Warriors.
Fight for the future, Sex Warriors!