Taketo! I don't like perverts!
We're beyond this, already.
You have to wait until
you become a proud and worthy man.
Good morning, Mr. Nogawa.
Your father is going to hire me
at his company.
He says he's going to make me
his private secretary.
Shall we talk in my office, Yumi?
-Why, yes.
-Dad!
What's this, Taketo?
Yumi....
Playing hooky from school
and taking another nap?
-What should we do about you?
-So what? Leave me alone.
As you wish.
Are you going out like that?
I'm going to work. W-O-R-K, work.
Aren't you embarrassed
about that outfit?
Or are you willing to do anything
for my father?
You're not man enough
to understand this.
That's it.
I raised them the same,
but they have different tastes.
Oh?
Hello?
I'm going to make him
recognize me soon enough.
Once I've prepared this bitch,
even better than expected.
Immoral Sisters
~Two Premature Fruits~
The First Night
"Madonna Debauched"
Side A:
"Yukie, the Lusty Wife"
Hello, this is Kitazawa residence.
Hello, dear.
Yes, it's me, Yukie.
No, nothing.
I'm a little....
...sick.
I'm sorry.
Really.
I'm all right.
The girls....
They are fine, too.
Tomoko.
Nice work, Rumi.
You, too.
-Good work.
-You, too. See you later.
-Tomoko.
-Rumi.
Tomoko, stop acting
like a scaredy-cat. It's a bad habit.
I'm sorry.
I have to drop by the Art Club.
Go home on your own.
Ouch!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
You look good in pink.
You are not hurt, are you?
Yes. Don't worry.
Yes.
No.
No, no, you're wrong.
Really, nothing.
Nothing. Really.
Yes, of course.
I love you, too, dear.
¥200,000?
No way! The cars barely touched
each other!
You can look at our actual estimate.
Even if the amount is accurate,
you're partly to blame for the accident.
I'll compromise.  You pay 70%
and I'll pay 30%.
Still, you owe us ¥140,000.
There is no way I can pay that!
Guess we can't settle this
out of court.
Please let me go home and...
...I'll talk with my husband.
I'm sorry. I'm a little dizzy.
Before you go home,
would you at least sign here?
What is it?
Your agreement to the settlement.
But we haven't settled
the amount....
We don't care, but you asked us
to settle it out of court.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Isn't your husband
a section manager at a trading company?
What?
¥200,000 in half a year may be
too much for you.
What are you talking about?
With your looks,
you can make money in so many ways.
A life can be so easily changed
with a piece of paper.
You don't mean.... Show it to me.
What is it?
My chest....
I'll make it easy for you, right away.
No, no.
All we need now
is to establish the facts.
No!
Don't.
No. Someone help me.
Dear.
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry, dear.
Don't cry.
I'll train you.
Soon you'll be making ¥200,000 easily.
Just to show Dad.
I'm home.
Mom's out, maybe?
She didn't even lock the door.
She is so careless.
Tomoko, stop acting like a
scaredy-cat. It's a bad habit.
I don't want to be looked at.
I'm not as pretty as she is.
She has a bad habit, too.
I wonder if it feels good.
It feels strange.
What was that?
Mother?
Mother, are you home?
Tomoko....
What is it?
Has something happened?
-Nothing happened.
-Are you sure?
This has nothing to do with you.
Mother?
Immoral Sisters
Ouch.
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Tomoko?
What's wrong with her?
Side B:
Rumi, a Madonna debauched
Who could that be?
What is this?
I'm changing! Get out!
-You're Rumi Kitazawa, aren't you?
-What?
You'd better not make noise.
You wouldn't want to
attract attention.
I should introduce myself.
I'm Yumi Okamoto, Secretary
to the President of Machikawa Industries.
This has to be fake!
Unfortunately....
My boss is waiting for you.
Would you come with me?
You'd better hurry.
My boss is an impatient man.
He'd prefer you just like this.
We got a permit to use the rooftop.
Then tell everybody to gather
on the rooftop in half an hour.
But none of us are in uniform.
We can change on the rooftop.
There won't be anyone to see us.
It's part of our duty to get used to
being watched.
Really?
When you're acting scared,
you will be spotted easily.
If they ever see me....
I hear you're something
of a school celebrity.
Good grades, athletic, popular,
all-around good student.
All girls' school students
love scandals.
I'm too old to be standing under
the winter sky.
You shall warm me up
right away.
What are you waiting for?
I'm talking to you, Rumi!
I told you.
My boss is an impatient man.
I could never do such a thing.
What are you doing?
I'm attaching your
mother's photo to e-mails....
Please don't....
You're asking the wrong person.
More than anything,
I hate to be made to wait!
What do you want me to do?
How could you not know? You're old
enough to have heard all about it.
Idiot.
Don't hit me! I'll do as you say!
-I'll even do fellatio.
-You mean, you want to suck?
I want to suck.
This time, use your tongue right.
Yumi, send out the e-mail!
Wait!
Looks like she's quite a good student
in this subject as well.
I agree.
Though she's not innocent
like you were once.
Good morning, boss.
Your father is going to
hire me at his company.
He says he's going to make me his
private secretary.
Shall we talk in my office, Yumi?
Why, yes.
It's been a while since I last
visited you.
I can cook something.
I've become quite good at cooking.
By the way, Uncle, please talk to
Taketo. He's acting like....
Good thing you've graduated
from those childish ones.
What are you doing?
Is it trendy to wear
these sexy ones?
Please don't.
You're not stupid.
You lost your parents early...
...and had no one else
to take care of you.
You knew I was not
acting out of charity.
What's with you bringing me here,
all of the sudden?
You must have been joking, earlier.
For a moment, I thought you meant it.
You are my uncle. For you to say....
Enough talking!
Remove your hands!
What? I don't want you to see....
I'm telling you to show me!
This is your job interview!
Spread your legs!
Raise your knees!
No. No.
Remember how you sat down to
pee, when you were a child?
Take that pose!
My son seems to like this.
I prefer this.
If you are not a virgin,
your application will be rejected.
No.
Don't.
No!
Please stop.
No, no, no.
No, no. Stop.
No.
No, no!
Swallow it all.
When you are done with sucking...
...the polite thing to do is to
masturbate for him.
Not my back.
You're such a slut,
you have to do this every day.
Please, forgive me.
How do you do it?
I'll do it right away.
Like this. With my panties on.
You like panties, don't you?
It feels like I'm being watched.
I think about how they watch me
in the club activities, and it's so good.
No, not my ass. No.
What a surprise.
What a slut.
She's already cum once,
but look at this.
Your panties are already drenched.
Now....
No, not there....
It hurts.
No.
Stop.
It hurts, it hurts.
Oops. Your precious panties are
covered with blood.
Listen, Rumi. You go home
wearing this.
Wow. Our rooftop is quite large.
Oh, no. Are we changing here?
Stupid! We should have changed
before we came up here.
What if
someone was peeking at us?
Look, change if you haven't already!
We're starting.
I enjoy thinking about
which pair of panties to put on.
Today we're cheering the tennis
players, so mine look like tennis balls.
-Nana's panties are slutty.
-Don't be ridiculous!
Nana color-coordinates her panties
for girl she's cheering.
I know!
Nana only wears this color
when she's cheering the tennis players.
Our tennis player Rumi Kitazawa
wears that color.
How do you know
Rumi's taste in panties?
I'm always watching
the tennis club practice.
Well soon, Rumi's taste in
panties will be red, right?