Forgive me.
¥200,000 is too much for me to pay.
Then you will be mine forever, just
like this, Yukie.
She's fallen, completely.
And the settlement money?
I'll suck it out of her.
Do it well, Taketo.
Yumi...
...am I bad?
Blood is thicker than water.
When it comes to this.
This? But, I love you.
No. Not now.
Not now?
You have not surpassed your father
yet, Taketo.
Immoral Sisters
~Two Premature Fruits~
The Second Night
"The Fallen Good Student"
Side A:
Rumi, the Good Student
Who are you?
This is who I am.
What if I showed it to your father,
away on his business trip?
The lunch time is over. I have
to go back.
Hey, we're still talking.
What do you want me to do?
In short, it's up to you.
Don't touch me.
Hey, hey.
What's with her?
Wait!
You are Tomoko Kitazawa,
aren't you?
Yes?
Rumi is so cold. Is she always
like that?
That depends...
But you don't look that cold.
I'm Taketo. Let's be friends.
I'm sorry.
Hey, wait.
What's with her?
Kitazawa, are you all right?
It hurts.
Tennis Club
Don't hesitate.
I have to do this for the family.
Rumi, so you did slip away
from the class.
I pretended to be hurt.
Good. You have an important
job to do.
Now, you have the school's
chairman to spoil you.
Coming.
Who is it?
Your master is back.
Your daughter and stepdaughter
don't know how to behave.
You haven't...
Bitches. Both of them
rejected me!
You take the responsibility.
What?
Take them off.
What's wrong? Didn't you say
you'd do anything I tell you?
Did you forget about the ¥200,000?
I still have the settlement paper.
Answer it. It's from your husband
again, right?
Hello, dear.
Yes, yes.
We're all fine.
Nothing's happened.
Dear, I miss you.
I want it.
That's why...
How could you...?
How long do you want me to wait?
I can't live like this...
Nothing you can do? But I...
I can't go on like this!
Great performance.
Turning the whole thing into
telephone sex, to lose your husband.
Forgive me, already. Please.
Then turn around and get naked!
Very good.
You're not bad, are you?
I don't do this, even to my husband.
Taketo, can I lick some more?
Wait, wait.
The fun has just begun.
Yes.
It's me.
I'm home.
Mother...
Mother!
Rumi!
Welcome home.
How dare you!
Because you were mean to me.
She's been taking care of me,
for you.
Here we go!
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
Leave her alone! Get away from her!
What did you say?
I won't let you touch her!
This is getting interesting.
Rumi...
Rumi, don't.
Please, don't.
You're good.
Rumi!
You, shut up!
But if I don't do this...
Don't worry about me.
You won't be the only one to suffer.
What a lovey-dovey family.
This is stupid.
Hey. Suck me well.
I'm doing it! I'm doing it
with interest.
Rumi!
That's good.
I can't wait anymore.
Already?
Yeah. And you want it, too.
You're ready, aren't you?
But...
Rumi.
Don't worry. I'm not giving in.
So, don't worry.
Shut the fuck up! You're
distracting me.
She's squeezing me tight.
I'm going to cum!
No! Don't cum inside Rumi!
We'll see.
Go ahead. I dare you to cum
inside me.
If I get pregnant...
You won't walk away free.
Idiot! Idiot! Why did he
have to cum inside me for real?
Rumi, I'm sorry.
What's the noise upstairs?
She looks so innocent,
but she's so wet.
She's at that age. She's been
interested, right?
Look.
She's ready.
Dad.
Please stop your son.
If we have to go on like this...
Do you want to destroy
your life?
If you just shut up and put up
with it...
...not even your husband
has to know.
You don't want to destroy your
fine family, do you?
Side B:
Tomoko, a Fragile Budding Flower
Damn Taketo. He's got to learn
how to complete a checkmate.
Why would I let go of
such jewels?
Rumi's like a lioness, and it's
so early in the morning.
Maybe something's happened to her.
She's not acting like herself.
Maybe she's lovesick.
Who are you?
This is me.
Don't touch me!
Before he can drop the
mother completely...
...he wants those girls I
had my eyes on.
I'm Taketo. Let's be friends.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Yumi.
You know who has to taste
those virgins first.
Of course. Let me handle it.
Kitazawa, are you all right?
It hurts.
Rumi. So, you did slip away
from the class.
I pretended to have been hurt.
Rumi...
Now you have my boss,
your school chairman, to spoil you.
Girlie, I'm all ready.
Why not try tennis clothes
today? I like them.
Good girl. Suck me well.
You have cute undies.
No! Don't photograph me like this.
Aren't you always doing slutty things
all by yourself?
Don't get me wrong.
I just want to help my family. That's
why I'm doing it.
Hey, don't take your mouth away
without my permission!
You dare say you want to
shoulder the settlement payment?
What an insolent child.
If you don't perform well, you'll
never complete your payment.
Or is it too much to handle
on your own?
Would you want Tomoko
to help you out?
No! Don't you ever touch Tomoko!
Shut up!
Where do these insolent words
come from?
From these tits?
Or from here?
Smells good.
Must be the sweet fragrance
of your virginity.
No, don't!
Forgive me.
You mean, "please forgive me."
Please forgive me.
Good girl. You shall receive
your reward.
Why?
No, I said no!
My, it looks like you're enjoying it
more than the last time.
You secretly like having this done
to you, don't you?
No! No way!
Yes, way. It's already become
habitual, hasn't it?
You're in fact enjoying it, aren't you?
No, don't say that.
If you say that, I'll cum.
I'm cumming, too.
Look, the school chairman's cumming,
too. Swallow it.
No...
I'm cumming!
Good girl. Doing everything
we tell you.
How did you like the school
chairman's milk? Tasty?
I won't let them touch Mother and
Tomoko, any more than this.
Yes, I'm the only one that
needs to be dirtied.
Why does Rumi do such a thing?
I'm so hot, I'm going crazy.
Mother's acting strange these
days, too. I don't know.
Why is my body acting like this?
Oh, no. It's getting habitual.
Yes, just a minute.
I'll tell you why.
I'll tell you why Rumi is doing
something like that.
If this gets known throughout the
school, you two will be in trouble.
Please, what can I do?
You're a kind girl who cares about
her family.
A girl like that has to fall.
What?
You have to do slutty things,
and satisfy a man.
That's the only way to save them.
Please don't!
Yumi, bring her along now. I
can't wait any longer.
I just got here. We're heading
your way.
Good. Finally, she's here.
Excuse me...
Shush! Looks like they're
enjoying it now.
What's wrong?
Let's not bother them. Let's go to
your room.
Or should I keep doing this?
Welcome home. A show is
about to begin. Care to watch with me?
Who is he?
I told you, if you want to save
the family...
...you have to sacrifice your virginity
to a certain person.
No way...
What are you waiting for?
The show is about to begin.
Tomoko, let's watch together.
Rumi, don't, please, no.
It's all right, Mother.
You won't suffer alone.
I won't let a bastard like this
touch you!
This is getting interesting.
Rumi.
Look, she's about to sacrifice herself
to save her mother.
Isn't she wonderful?
Don't look away. Don't you want to
save her, too?
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
Not like Rumi.
Why not?
- Because, because...
- Because?
I'm not as pretty as Rumi.
That's not true. You're beautiful.
Really?
What a view.
No! Don't look!
Wonderful smell.
The smell of freshly
washed underwear.
The smell of a virgin,
getting it wet.
This is the fragrance of youth!
No, no, don't look, don't look!
You can't fight it. I'll make you
cum, all the way.
Look, Rumi is taking the man's thing
in her mouth.
You want to take one in your mouth,
too, don't you?
This is all to save the family.
Can you leave it all up to Rumi?
Then why don't you become a
woman now, here?
She's all ready.