No, please don't.
Too late. Your cunt is crying,
craving it. "Give it to me, give it to me."
That's not true.
No means yes, doesn't it?
Your body is being honest.
No, please don't.
Beast.
See you.
Mother, get a hold of yourself.
Rumi, I'm sorry to have involved
you in this.
It's all right. Don't give up.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Mother.
See? You don't have enough
strength to resist me.
It's about time you lost
your virginity!
No, please don't push something
so hard in me!
Look at it! Your slit is already
ready to swallow me, all the way in!
No, no.
Give it up.
It's your chance to awake
into your womanhood.
Just like Yumi says.
I'm upgrading you into
a real lady! Here I come!
Not yet. I'm pushing all the
way in.
It hurts! It hurts! Stop, please!
What does it feel like to have
lost your virginity?
Does it hurt? Does it hurt so
much you want to cry?
Rumi. Mother.
Immoral Sisters
~Two Premature Fruits~
The Third Night
"Drowning in Love and Pleasure"
Side A:
Rumi and Tomoko in Love
You're still here?
Why are you here?
A house full of women
looks safe, but there are holes everywhere.
No way. Tomoko!
Tomoko!
Tomoko. Why?
She asked for it herself. She said it
was unfair she alone was left unsoiled.
Tomoko...
I am a failure as a mother.
It hurt, didn't it? I'm sorry I couldn't
protect you.
Rumi, have I become pretty?
What?
It's not bad to do those
things with men, is it?
You sure looked like you were
enjoying it.
What are you talking about?
It hurts, and I can't
breathe, but...
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Tomoko.
Rumi, sleep with me tonight!
Tomoko, don't be afraid.
I will stay by your side all
night tonight.
Yeah.
Forget about today.
It was just a bad dream.
- Rumi?
- Yes?
I was lonely.
You and Mother were suffering
so much.
But I didn't know anything. I
wasn't doing anything.
No, it was my fault.
I didn't want you to worry, so I didn't
tell you anything.
Because of that, I not only failed to
protect you...
It wasn't your fault!
You didn't do anything wrong.
Thank you, Tomoko.
I'm still hot.
Tomoko?
I'm throbbing and hot, like a man
is still inside me.
What are you saying, Tomoko?
When you do that with a man, do
you feel like this, too?
Don't be weird, and go to sleep!
Tell me, Rumi!
Tomoko!
I had my breasts touched like
this today.
Stop it, Tomoko! What are
you doing?
Your nipples are getting hard.
No...
You're sensitive, too,
just like me.
That's not true.
Where are you putting your hand?
Wow, it's just like Yumi said.
You're getting moist here.
Tomoko, don't move your fingers!
I may be a stepmother,
but a mother is a mother.
They must have been
hurt more than me.
I have to console them.
Amazing. You're getting
wetter and wetter.
Don't, Tomoko.
You keep on talking like that,
and I'll go crazy.
I've been peeking at you doing
this, so I know all about it.
You're sensitive here, aren't you?
Tomoko.
These girls...
Now, why don't you join them?
You!
Go inside and hold them.
But...
You're their mother, aren't you?
Mother?
Rumi, Tomoko, I'm a bad mother.
Mother!
Please don't cry. It wasn't your fault.
Why don't we all go to
bed holding each other?
Tomoko.
That's right, Mother. Let's
forget about the whole thing.
Thank you, Rumi.
What a beautiful family.
You! You come barging in again?
May I join your wonderful family
get-together?
I was like you.
My virginity was robbed by my boss.
Watching you reminded me
of how it was for me.
Now, I'm so horny.
Please. It's too lonely to
do it all by myself.
Tomoko, don't believe her so easy!
She's been blackmailing us...
It's all right.
Tomoko?
It's all right, isn't it, Sis?
Somehow, you two have matured
into real women.
I'm so glad to hear that
from you.
We're graduating together
next year, Sis.
Tomoko...
After we've graduated, let's
do more slutty things together, Sis.
You two are so close.
It's as if you were real sisters.
You respond so well.
You couldn't be satisfied by your
husband, could you?
Tomoko, what are you doing?
Do you like it, Sis?
Never seen this before?
Taste it, a little.
Incredible.
Tastes good, doesn't it?
You took two fingers in!
Does it feel good?
You're drenched.
It feels so good.
It's coming in! The thick one is
coming inside me!
This may be unfair to your husband.
Put it in!
So do you like it better than
your husband's cock?
You like it, don't you?
I love it!
Sis, more!
Yumi.
I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
Where are you going?
To work.
At this hour?
Yes. I like to thoroughly
prepare for revenge.
It hurts, it hurts! Stop, please.
What does it feel like to have
lost your virginity?
Does it hurt? Does it hurt so
much you want to cry?
Dad.
Taketo.
I suffered the same fate.
Side B:
Yumi, a Lady of Vengeance
Wrong password again.
Taketo? I didn't see you.
What are you doing here this
late, Yumi?
My boss is taking a trip tomorrow,
for an important business meeting.
So I have to prepare
documents tonight.
Do you enjoy working for my
father that much?
It's not like I'm working for
your father.
I'm working for myself.
Then, you're not in love
with him, are you?
Taketo...
Yumi, it's not fair!
You compare me with my father,
and laugh at me behind my back!
No, no.
Taketo, what are you doing?
Shut up!
I'll make you understand that
I'm better than Dad!
Ouch! Taketo!
Yumi...
Be gentle.
- Like this?
- Yes. Don't make me wait.
Taketo.
Do you love me?
Yeah.
We're graduating from this already.
You have to wait until you have
become a proud and worthy man.
Then, why didn't you rescue me?
Because...
When you have something
this manly?
You were afraid of your
father, weren't you?
Yumi...
My turn.
Taketo.
So good. Give me more.
Yumi, I can't wait any more!
Wait!
If I have a relationship with
you, your father will be mad.
Yumi.
If that happens, would
you protect me?
Of course. I will fight
Dad to protect you!
Can I trust you?
You're coming inside me, Taketo.
Then, I'll be on your side.
I will help you.
Yumi, thank you.
It's so good.
Yumi, show me better.
No.
No!
I can see us connected so well.
I can see so well, Yumi.
It feels so good.
I'm cumming!
Your father will be surprised when
he comes back from his business trip.
When he finds out you've been
robbing the Kitazawa family.
Checkmate, he says.
You have the settlement paper
somewhere safe, don't you?
Yes. Secure in Dad's safe.
I'll help. So, why don't you
give it a try?
Now?
It's a chance to get acknowledged
by your father.
You don't have money?
Then sell this house. It'll
be worth quite a lot.
I have to ask my husband. I can't
sell it by myself.
Ask your husband? Why do you
have to do that?
In the first place, you had the car
accident, not him.
Don't be mean to my mother.
If you want my body...
Idiot! We're past that stage!
Pay the full amount within two
days, before my father comes home.
That's impossible.
I'm not interested in slut
step-sisters my father has already raped.
You're horrible!
And you couldn't even
satisfy Rumi.
What?
You're a premature ejaculator.
What? Who do you think
you're talking to?
To you! You're less than
your father!
You!
Taketo, calm down.
We're talking business here.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Taketo, you were lying to me.
What?
These women haven't fallen at all.
That's not true.
If you can't satisfy these women, you
can't say you have weakened the family.
Yumi...
Maybe it does take your father...
What are you saying, Yumi?
What do you say everyone?
If Taketo can satisfy the three
of you by himself, we win.
If Taketo loses, the settlement
paper will be shredded.
Yumi!
I'll do it!
Me, too!
Show me you are stronger
than your father.
Harder!
Your father touched my
breasts harder.
Like this?
Make it harder. Harder than
your father.
Good. It's getting big.
I'll reward it, by sucking it.
I love young men's legs.
Don't lick my legs.
You came already?
Do you want me to suck out more?
So that's how to suck out
what's left inside!
Taketo, now that Mother is doing it,
you have to cum to the last drop.
Not yet, not yet.
The battle has just begun.
Get hard again.
It's so good, so good.
It's already morning.
The girls are not going
to school today.
It's a chance to have you
pamper both of them.
Why waste it?
I always wanted a big one like this.
At least give me breakfast.
I'm cumming again.
No, Sis, hold on.
Give me a break.
I'm not cumming yet!
I won't lose to Taketo!
Give it up and cum!
I'm going to wash you,
right here.
So give it to me later, Taketo.
Don't wash me there!
I'm cumming!
It's so good!
Yukie & Tomoko: More, more!
Incredible!
Please, Taketo, shake your hips!
Don't stop your fingers.
Move your fingers harder than
Rumi does!
Stop already. Stop, please.
Should I tear this up?
I tear it up, and it'll all be over.
No. Not that.
Then it will go on and on.
No, no. No more!
Be a man. Make up your mind.
Do you want to continue or not?
More!
Harder!
Don't stop!
As I told you...
...I've been pretending to do as my
boss told me to do.
Now that he thinks he's won, it's a
perfect chance for your revenge.
I see. I'll do it.
Me, too.
Wonderful! The step sisters are
servicing me at the same time!
Good. Suck me!
Finish each other
off, step-sisters!
Please, chairman, forgive me.
Resist me only when you have
paid off your parent's debt!
No! Chairman, please stop!
Good. Suck me all the way
down to the hilt!
Chairman, no. I can't do
it anymore!
You two are my slaves for the
rest of your lives!
Now, service me
again, together!
- Forgive me, forgive me please!
- Someone help me!
Hello, police?
I have some documents I'd like you
to take a look at...
...in connection with the corruption
scandal at Nogawa Industries.
Give it up! You can cry,
you can wail...
...but I'm the Chairman of the
Board at this school! Nobody can fight me!
One Month Later
Your father is in jail. You are free.
I lost to my father.
Yes, but we are the real winners.
Come on, make it bigger.
You've come over here as penance
for your father's sins, haven't you?
Now, it's time for me to eat.
Sis, don't take it all.
I want some, too.
It's early in the morning
but everyone's having fun.
Mother!
You want to join us?
I'd love to, but I have to go to work.
I'll take my time and enjoy it when I
come back.
Right, Taketo?
Yes.
Drive Safely