Nymphs of the Stratosphere Chapter One
Take it off.
Come here.
I like this one better.
Look how wet you are.
It feels great!
I want more.
Forever...
Forever!
What's this?
Look... What do you think of this?
Move your hand.
Oh...
You have nasty juice
coming out of your...
Smells so nice. Smells like fruit.
Hold on, I'll give you something nice.
I'll make you feel better...
A lot better...
I'm not finished yet.
It smells so good...
Let me see your pussy...
Stop it.
Nymphs of the Stratosphere
File No. 49
Those eyes were full
of lyrical ambiguity...
...but they tempt people to
return to their animalistic origin.
The concept's
presentation of "beauty"...
...oppositely located the
intrusive sense of value.
Not even a freckle.
White, white, skin...
The lips, as if drawn thin and
red, quiver only to desire ecstasy.
The body's flaw is not having a flaw
at all, reigned by the Golden Rule.
Is there a "soul" under those
slightly lifted swells...
...on either side that
persistently have peach nipples?
Bottom, rear end, buttocks...
Those words can't capture the...
...suggestion of noble,
round, twin hills...
...with sweet fragrance
pouring out from the depths.
It is a sequence of the crystal
of unprincipled pleasure...
...no way to know the selfish moral.
Sleeplessly hiding in the darkness,
...sticking her fingers
in and out of there...
...stirring her fingers there...
...plucking her fingers there...
Here eyes filled with
curiosity, wait for nightfall.
Seeking an outlet for her sexual desire.
File No. 08
My apartment stands, overlooking
the park with thick trees...
...that seem to encompass the lake.
I live with my parents in this 5-room
apartment close to the top floor.
It was bought when my father,
who's in commerce, living away...
...6 months out of the year, and
my mother is also never around.
I've been spending time by myself
since childhood. I attend a...
...well known academy that's located
one station away, since kindergarten.
I don't have many friends, even though
I've always lived around these people.
My classmates call me "gloomy", but
I never thought of myself like that.
I just feel it's stupid to be excited
about superstars and musicians.
It's probably because I have
sexual habits unlike normal kids.
I often walk alone on the
way back from the academy...
...to my house, which
takes about 30 minutes.
I walk through the park, towards my
home, but during these summer months...
...there are many couples
and doubtful people.
During dusk, I try to choose well-lit
places and hurry myself home...
...but one day, I saw a funny thing.
This person was perched
on a tree, like a bird.
It was on a branch more than 10 meters
high, not holding on to anything...
At first, I thought...
...it was a boy.
As soon as I noticed and
stopped to take a better look...
...it suddenly disappeared.
I thought it fell from the tree,
but it seemed like it didn't.
I never saw a ghost, but
I did believe in them...
...so I was excited because
I thought "I saw it!"
Because this person was really
beautiful, I wasn't scared...
In fact, it seemed like she was
emitting a warm, welcoming feeling.
A few days later, I was walking
home from school as usual...
...a little late in the day because
I was doing research at the library.
It was Friday, and there
were many couples...
...some of them making
noises in the dark...
That's when I saw it.
I don't know why I looked that
way, but I was drawn to it.
It was perched on a tree,
at the edge of the park.
I quickly hurried home.
At that angle, I could probably
see it from the balcony.
I ran into the empty room and
without switching the light on...
...I took my father's
electric binoculars,
...impatiently adjusting the zoom and
brightness, I ran out to the balcony.
I can see!
As I thought, the treetops were
blocking it a little, but there it was.
At first, I didn't
know what it was doing.
But, I've never been
this surprised in my life.
Because, like before, it
was high up in a tree...
...sitting, with its shorts
down, showing its butt.
And it was sticking its
fingers in and out of it.
It wasn't peeing...
...but a good amount of sticky liquid
was flowing out onto the branch.
The cute face was a little flushed...
...and you could almost hear the
sighs from her quivering lips.
And I noticed this being
was intently watching...
...a couple having sex.
She...
I'm sure it was a girl...
So she was on a tree,
peeping, satisfying herself?
And, when her panting lips looked
like she was going to come...
...the hat she had on floated up, and
from around her ears, appeared wings.
The wings opened up slowly...
...as if a young bird was about
the fly for the first time.
And she again disappeared.
What is she?
Where did she come from?
I, in many ways, don't
know anything about men.
And, I'm not even interested.
I want her.
File No. 72
The milky white mist, obeying its own
will, blankets the building's corners.
Even the creatures that were
ejected from the surface of ethics...
...which is called the
non-directivity of sexual desire...
...lacking in consequence,
mumbles while...
...they slowly get sucked in,
from the drain to the sewage.
The indifference of everyday life,
gives birth to the essence of collapse.
An illusion of being able to spin the...
...indulgence of one's own
original sin through knowledge.
The small delight from belonging to
someone is against a fragile appearance...
...only to form the affirmation
as a kind, that's a metaphor.
The shade of buildings...
The top of a tree in the forest...
The corner of a shed...
It's waiting for
nightfall in the shadow.
It appears from the maturity of
civilization and the boredom of culture.
Together with a vulgar scent of fruit...
Nymphs of Stratosphere