Floy...
Still no kiss?
I didn't care what Floy was...
...as long as she was close to me...
Besides...
If I tried to find out...
...I felt like I would lose Floy...
Nymphs of the Stratosphere Chapter 3
Next news.
Concerning the death of
a young woman at a hotel...
...in Shibuya, the
morning of the 21st...
...results from the
autopsy states that...
...this woman was infected
with an unknown virus...
Unknown...
Be quiet!
If you're good, I'll give you food!
Welcome to Nymphs of the Stratosphere!
Hello! Today's Fetigoro's diary!
Here are some pictures of my nymph...
I love my master!
Time for food!
Look how big we've gotten!
You've got mail!
Number of nymphs is 100
among them, 5 are defective?
"Defective Nymphs" can't shrink?
Hey, settle down!
Yeah, good girl...
Found a nymph!
What's this?
I see that's how it is...
Ta-Da!
Huh? Creepy...
Do you put it in here?
Okay...
Wow...
This is awesome!
I guess you're not satisfied yet.
How far will it stretch?
All the way to my wrist...
What a monster!
It's so freaky!
What the hell is this?
What a huge hole...
I can see inside real good.
I guess it's not fun as is...
...Ms. Nymph!
Ms. Number 2
What's wrong? Defective nymph!
Floy?
Isn't this a nice toy.
I got it just for you.
Teleport, huh?
But it looks like it's not perfect.
Boring. Let me have more fun.
You're not human, right?
Let me guess...
You are a sudden variation of
human's revolutionized version...
No, more of a poetic being...
...because you're so beautiful.
Here, lick it... good.
Okay, next!
All right, lick it...
It's in here...
If I pull the trigger, can you
imagine what's gonna happen?
That's it, more, be more frightened...
You're beautiful...
You really are a nymph...
Smells nice.
You taste good, too...
Good. I'm coming soon...
You come, too...
T-Together...
Come with me!
What's wrong? Floy?
OK, I'm off.
Are you okay by yourself?
Yes, mother...
Would you like anything?
No, mother...
Sure?
...I like my current doll...
Okay, let's start, my pretty doll
Let's see, we'll use...
...this.
Well, do it.
take it off...
Hurry...
Breasts...
Lower...
Yes, yes, slowly...
Yes...
Good...
You, too...
Nymphs of the Stratosphere
News! A new nymph revealed!
Solve the mystery of defects,
which exist 5 in 100 nymphs.
Defects don't have wing ears.
Defects can't shrink.
Defects don't have wing
ears, and can't shrink...
You are...
...a defective doll, huh?
Let's see, then...
...this.
This is boring...
I should've asked Mother
for something else.
Floy!
Floy...
I'm here...
I'm here for you!
Floy!
I told you to be quiet!
What, food?
You want food?
Here, food,
Foo-d.
What's wrong? Hey.
It died...
It melted...
Hmm, defects are no good after all...
Floy...
Floy, where did you come from?
Why are you so sad?
What do you think of me?
But I can't ask you any
of these questions...