I was...
...seeking something.
Something that will quench
this insatiable thirst...
I was seeking it.
What is it? This sweet
fruit-like scent...
I was seeking for something...
...something...
Nymphs of the Stratosphere
Nymphs of the Stratosphere Chapter Two
Here, I got you some food.
Yeah, thanks...
There's about a week's worth...
It's fine to be caught
up in something, but...
...you should get some
fresh air once in a while...
I'm not gonna let you
talk about my health...
So you were listening after all...
Indeed...
Excuse me...
l-I live here...
W-What are you doing here?
H-Hey, wait!
She was watching this...
Nymphs of the Stratosphere
Nymphs...
More interesting news! By Obelonlon
I've acquired some info about
the Nymphs of the Stratosphere!
She's really, really cute. On top of that,
she's really curious about sex, but...
A lame erotic site.
Dad?
Y-You are...
H-Hey!
H-Hey you, wait!
Huh?
Why she's here?
But...
She's so pretty...
I've never seen a
girl as cute as this...
...almost inhuman...
Um...
W-Wait a minute!
Sorry, because you suddenly...
Why in the world...
Why don't you say anything?
You can hear my voice...
Is it you?
Please look...
Let me see yours...
No! I can't...
You do it, too.
Do it...
Please, do it.
W-Wait...
What I was seeking...
It was a girl with
translucent, white skin...
Not here?
Not even a kiss?
I don't understand.
The more I want, the more I get scared.
Shou...
Well, I don't know anything
about you, not even your name...
Floy...
You're sure?
We don't have sex organs.
F-Floy...
Feels good...
Oh, right, I'm pretty sure...
...but rumor has it,
they don't have sex organs.
How do they do it?
No sex organs?
D-Don't tell me!
To Obelonlon, from the
little window of ChiruChiru.
I don't want you to tarnish the
nymphs with vulgar delusions!
I've heard that the Nymphs of the
Stratosphere have ears made of wings.
I'm sure they are sacred beings...
What am I doing...
Floy, I want to know more about you...
Without you, I...