I'll kill you, Jap!
Oh my God!
Supernatural Beast Battlefront
ADVENTURE KID
Sorry about the racket.
So, what's the game today?
Pacific war simulation.
You've got games
on the brain, Norikazu.
I did it!
Midori, I did it!
Boring...
Boring! Boring!
You perv! You were
looking at my panties!
White... I mean, I didn't see
anything! They aren't white!
Hey mister, you got
something buried here.
Oh great... I'm no good
with machines, anyway.
C'mon "Papa",
let's go in the house.
Hey! Norikazu?
NORIKAZU!
Oh, hi Dad. What's up?
Nice view. Very nice!
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
You dirty little boy...
That feels so good!
Oh no!
Okay, that should do it.
I heard there used to be an
electronics lab around here.
The Masago Research Center
or something like that.
I bet there is more of this buried.
That's gonna slow our work down.
Masago Research Center, huh?
Well, Norikazu?
Just check this out!
C'mon, work...
Okay, there we go!
Oh, shit!
Norikazu!
Norikazu,
are you all right?
Norikazu...
A little numb, but I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Hey! What was
all that noise about?
Nothing, Dad!
Well, be careful out there.
- C'mon...
- Coming, love.
Sorry, Midori.
Don't worry about it.
I'd better get home.
I'll meet you later, then?
Sure.
"Papa... "
Here I come!
Harder!
Okay, how about THIS?
Oh "Papa",
you're fantastic!
No, I guess not.
Norikazu! Norikazu!
Are you alright,
Norikazu?
Huh?
What happened to me?
I heard you
yelling up here.
Don't you know I don't
like getting "interrupted"?!
Oh, SHIT!
Look at the time.
Gotta run!
Hey! Wait!
Nothing but trouble.
Hey...
We've got the house to
ourselves tonight, right?
Why don't we pick up
where we left off?
Way to go, Midori!
You're a champ!
I'm okay, I guess.
Alright, next target!
Let's look sharp, guys!
This game's the best!
That's probably why it's
the most popular right now.
But man, Midori!
You kicked some major ass tonight!
Thanks a lot.
You know, I'm really thirsty.
Alright then,
let's get something to drink!
What's going on?
This isn't the place, guys!
You dumbshit!
Are you alright, Kazu?
Norikazu!
What was that thing?
How the fuck should I know?
This thing's headed
for the roof!
It isn't stopping!
Kazuya, what is it?
Outside! OUTSIDE!
Outside?
Kazuya, what's going on?
Would you stop?
How should I know?!
Sue, come on!
Norikazu, you okay?
Norikazu,
I was so scared...
What was that?
Nori! Run for it!
Midori!
Help me!
God dammit...!
Nori, you're the mechanical genius.
Do something!
Are... Are you kidding?!
You call THAT a machine?!
Kazuya!
Let me go!
That fuckin'...!
Kazuya!
You monster!
Stop it! Let me down!
Midori...
Norikazu, save me!
- Midori!
- Wait!
Don't just throw
your life away!
I've got an idea.
Come on!
Let me go!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop...
Stop it!
I'll give you something
to play with!
No more...
Well, I'd say we've had a
pretty crappy night, huh?
Too right.
But, how'd it happen?
Huh?
It just turned
on by itself!
Creepy!
Oh, please!
It's on a timer or something.
It doesn't have a timer.
Huh?!
I can't make heads or
tails of those numbers.
His brain's just wired
different from ours.
I'm getting something!
Help me!
Midori!
They're foreigners.
Where the hell are we?!
Dunno... It's like a
hospital, but not really...
Look, it's a tank!
Cool!
Wait... Where have
I seen that before...?
Relax! We're safe here,
no matter what!
Norikazu,
what's he saying?
"Where're you from and
what are you doing here?"
I was sorta hoping
he could tell us.
No!
What's he saying?!
Now's our chance!
Norikazu!
We're... We're in
the middle of a war...
Nori, snap out of it!
Come on and loosen these
ropes with your teeth!
Gotcha!
We've gotta find
Midori and Sue!
How can you
keep so calm?!
I'll kill you, Jap!
Oh my God!
Let's go,
while they're distracted.
Right.
At last I've found you,
Midori Asai.
Midori... Midori,
do you know this weirdo?
No! I've never
seen him before!
I'm not surprised
you don't know me.
But I'll make sure
you never forget me!
NO!
Norikazu, don't just
stop short like that!
I just heard
Midori's voice!
Come on!
Norikazu, wait a sec!
Now then, move aside.
What if I do?
Do I get to run away?
Ah, a girl with spirit.
Very well!
You alone may escape.
But what about these
other women here?
Please, you're after me, right?
Just let them go!
Midori, you're going
to get yourself killed!
But...!
Such a beautiful
friendship...
I despise people
with such feelings!
Sue!
Now then...
Your turn next.
Why you...!
Norikazu!
Midori!
Are you alright?
It was getting tight, but...
And like I WASN'T
in danger, too?!
Sorry!
You again... That's twice
you've gotten in my way.
But you won't
bother me ever again!
Look out!
Humans are so pathetic...
Norikazu! Norikazu!
Let me go!
Mi... do... ri...
Midori,
I love you.
I love you too,
Norikazu!
Now I remember. That officer
slashed me with his sword.
So, is this heaven?
Or is it hell?
Boy!
Welcome, Norikazu Hanyu.
Who are you?!
How do you know my name?!
You allowed me to see
your deepest thoughts.
My deepest thoughts...?
And how much you care
for the girl, Midori!
Midori? Where is she?
Where?!
This is a world
of my own creation.
All within this dimension
is decided by my will.
Even matters of
life and death...
So, am I dead?
If I am, can you
bring me back to life?!
Perhaps you are dead.
Perhaps not...
Then please, let me go
back there one more time!
And if you're killed again...?
I don't care! I just want to
save Midori from that monster!
Oh, so you care
for her that much?
Allow me to show you
something of interest...
Midori!
No! Get away!
Just where do you
think you can run?
There's no one left
to save you now!
Now then, let's get
a bit more intimate...
Kazuya!
Kazuya, speak to me!
Come!
No!
I'll give you pleasures beyond what
anyone of your world could know!
No... NO!
Somebody, help me!
Midori!
No... Stop it.
Stop...
Stop it. Please, stop...
You're quite well endowed
down there.
You're crying? Is this
really so painful for you?
I'll give you something
to REALLY cry about!
Growing quite well,
I see.
No... Stop it...
No more... Please...
Shit, he's gonna kill her!
Please, just send
me back to her!
Do you really care
for her that much?
I do! I love her!
Shall we proceed
to the main event?
No... ri... ka... zu...
Now then...
Lick it, and taste the depths
of your own degradation!
Now the fun truly begins.
No, don't!
I'll make a
real woman of you!
My little lovely...
Send me back!
Even if it means dying again?
After you were saved already?
If I don't save her,
who will? You?!
That I cannot do.
Then send me back!
She is fated to this destiny.
"Fated?"
The blood of Midori Asai
is already tainted.
What?!
She must atone...
Endless atonement in
this world I've created.
Then you're letting that
officer do this to her?!
Letting him?
I'm making him do it!
You son of a bitch!
You want to kill me?
Quite impossible.
In this world you're more
helpless than an ant!
Stop it... No...
Stop it... Stop...
Make him stop! Please!
Do it and I'll stay here
and atone with her!
I think you're serious.
As much as you love her,
she may not be faithful.
Can you accept that?
Very well. Only because
you released me from N3-C.
N3-C... That was the...
You're Masago!
- My name is Suhiro Masago!
- I knew it!
Now, show me how far your
memories of her can carry you!
Now then, for the
piece de resistance...
You're still alive?
Wha-?!
You thought you could
defeat me with that?!
What's wrong?
Finished so soon?
You're just in time. Now,
watch as I violate your woman!
Oh god, stop it!
No... NO!
Stop it, please!
Norikazu Hanyu, are your
feelings for her so limited?
Are they really so weak?!
This girl is all
I could ever ask for.
Now, watch as
I bring her to climax!
Midori...
LET HER GO!
Norikazu! Norikazu!
Speak to me!
Midori!
Where the hell...
Oh please, how boring.
I hardly touched you.
So, where'd you come from?
You're kinda cute!
Don't act so shocked.
Hey, let's have some fun.
Whoa, hold it!
It won't be so bad...
There is no escape from me!