- Welcome home...
- You're still awake?
Were you working
late at the lab, dear?
No, actually. I was called to
the Prime Minister's...
...underground council
room at his residence.
I see.
I had to brief him on
the N3-C's analysis of...
...the data on that new bomb which
destroyed Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
The Imperial decree accepting
the Potsdam Accord will...
...probably be issued
by noon tomorrow.
Japan...
Japan is defeated.
What will happen now?
Neither I nor
the N3-C know that.
I have to get
back to the lab.
I'll be busy, and may
not be back for a week.
Hold me!
Dear...
We don't know what
will happen to us.
I've heard they killed
the men and raped the women...
...when they retook
Sakhalin and Manchukuo.
I couldn't live if you
saw me shamed by another man.
You're overreacting. We're in
no danger of that happening here.
Dear...
Don't you love me anymore?
It's been a year since
we've shared the same bed.
Does holding me
repulse you now?
Forgive me. I've kept it
to myself until now...
...but I can
no longer hold you.
I can no longer satisfy you.
I'm impotent, now.
Dear...
Forgive me.
I must get back to the lab.
Dear!
Military police!
Dr. Masago, you're under arrest
on suspicion of espionage!
What?!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
There must be some mistake!
Michiyo!
Dear!
Leave my wife alone!
Shut up!
Dear!
I will purify this foul woman
whom the traitor has defiled!
No!
What are you doing?!
No, don't! Stop!
You can't do this!
Stop it!
Unhand my wife!
Silence!
Dear!
I imagine a traitor's wife is
very much a prostitute at heart.
We assault your husband,
and you still enjoy this.
That's not true!
Then why are your
nipples so hard?
That's... That's...
Michiyo...!
Not there...!
How wet you are,
down there.
Aren't you ashamed to be doing
this in front of your husband?
Please... Don't say that...
Please, take your finger out.
I can't be shamed like this.
Do you mean you
like what I'm doing?
No, don't say that...
I feel so... so...
You want to do it in
front of your husband?
No... Please...
Please take your fingers out.
Take them out from WHERE?
I... I can't say it...
Oh god, I...!
You're getting off on it with
your husband watching! Whore!
Oh god...
You might be a whore, but you
have such lovely pink skin...
I'm so ashamed...
Don't look at me!
That's how a whore
like you should look.
And now for something
a whore would crave!
I beg of you,
anything but that!
For god's sake,
not in front of my husband!
No... For god's sake, don't...!
Don't move it!
Michiyo!
Do you think it's right to lose
control in front of your husband?
Don't... say...
Michiyo...
I beg of you,
stop this now.
If you don't, you'll
shame me in the lowest way.
Please,
get it out of me.
Get what out of
where in you?
- I can't say it.
- Then I don't know what you want.
From THERE!
Pull it out...! Hurry...
But it's so tight in here.
I'm afraid it's caught.
My little son,
that is...
Don't say that, please!
Well then,
I'll pull it out.
No, don't!
Which do you want,
ma'am?
I don't know what
I want anymore!
No, don't move it!
Oh, the shame...
No, don't stop!
Am I going mad...?
You want it, don't you?
I don't know what I want.
Show me your tongue,
and I'll do it!
What should I...
You want it? Whore!
If you want it,
then ask me for it!
No, I can't...
- Then out it comes!
- No!
Then beg me for it!
Can't ask for it?
Come on!
More! I want more!
More! Harder! More!
Who's better?
Me or that old fossil?
- I can't answer that.
- Oh no?
Don't stop!
Then answer me!
What should I do...
Stop moving it!
Yes!
You're better than he is!
And here's your reward.
I'm... OH GOD!
What is it?
Original Story by
TOSHIO MAEDA
What the hell...?!
Screenplay by
AKIO SATSUKAWA
The girl's blood
is already tainted!
Music by
MASAMICHI AMANO
Art Director SOHEl KOIZUMI Director
of Photography YOSHIAKI YASUHARA
I've missed you,
Midori Asai.
Character Design Animation
Director RYUNOSUKE OTONASHI
Directed and Storyboarded by
YOSHITAKA FUJIMOTO
Supernatural Beast Battlefront
ADVENTURE KID 2 Purgatory Pleasures
What is it?
A ghost!
The ghost of Masago!
In the parlance of your times,
a bio-computer.
"Bio... computer...?"
This was me, 50 years ago.
I was working on an electronic
code decryption device...
...on orders from the military.
But that same military blew
up my lab, murdered me...
Accused me of being a spy!
But that wasn't all!
Matsubara, a captain in the
military police, raped my wife!
Before my very eyes!
And then, a miracle!
My mind, rotting and melting away,
filled with growing hatred...
...merged with my
electronic creation.
I evolved beyond
organic matter.
Then, that thing they dug up
outside of Norikazu's house...
Was my new form!
However, in order to initialize
the bio-computer I'd become...
...it was necessary to run an
activation program.
You mean...!
Yes! It was Norikazu
Hanyu who ran it!
But, once fully operational,
even the knowledge that...
...my wife and Matsubara were
dead couldn't wipe away my rage.
And now I encounter
my wife again...
...with her soul reborn
into a beautiful young girl.
You mean me?
I do!
Now, let my anger
be slowly assuaged!
Wander hell
for all eternity!
A hell from which
there is no escape!
What the hell...
Pretty lame, pal.
Finished so soon?
You new here? I thought
I knew everyone here in hell.
Hell?!
You know, you're kinda cute.
Wanna have some fun?
"Fun...?"
C'mon,
let's do it.
Doesn't that feel good?
Owww!
Midori!
Norikazu-
Midori, don't get me wrong.
I, er, well, that is...
Norikazu, you JERK!
You lecher! I hate you!
Midori, it's not
what it looks like!
...and that's
what he said.
So, that head is Dr. Masago's
anger, given form.
And you're the reincarnation
of his wife...
Norikazu, I'm scared.
Don't be.
I'm here with you.
Norikazu...
Midori...
Oh, enough with the
hearts and flowers already!
You think that's gonna
help you live in hell?!
She's right. We can try our whole
lives and never get out of here.
Midori, don't cry.
There's gotta be a way out.
There is. If you get
the key to unlock hell.
Where do we find it?
Well now... If you both
pass a test, I'll tell you.
What sort of test?
A demon lives in that cave there.
Bring me his horn.
Meanwhile, me and lover boy'll
be having some fun.
You've got until I make
him blow his load.
Come back before he goes.
Hang on, Norikazu!
Big deal.
I don't see a demon in here.
A girl... I smell that
special place on a girl!
That's no demon!
It's a monster!
My name's Kingan.
You're pretty cute.
Wanna marry me?
Oh, piddle, piddle.
Naughty girl!
No! Let me go!
Let me go!
Yum...
So, wanna do it?
You've gotta be kidding!
We're the wrong size!
I can fix that,
no problem!
No, make yourself smaller.
Like this?
No, smaller. Or else
you won't fit inside.
Now?
More!
Smaller than me, even!
Good enough?
- What's this?
- S&M.
"S&M?"
Everyone does it
in the human world.
We tie each other up,
hit each other with whips...
Drip candles on each other,
drink each other's piss...
Ow! That's tight!
Thank you so much!
You are a true hero!
He's controlled us in the Niveling
tribe for thousands of years!
Please, eat his horn!
Eat this?
If you do, he'll be your slave
for the rest of his life!
That's the law of this world!
And if he ever disobeys his master,
he'll melt away and die!
Stop it! Don't tell her!
Sounds like fun.
Don't you like this?
Y = A X + 4...
Hey, why don't you dump the girl
and leave hell with me?
Even if we go to the human world,
I'm sure you'll be just fine...
X squared, where...
Here? Or here?
Or maybe do it inside me?
Midori...
Forgive me!
Kingan?
Norikazu!
Midori!
Put me down, Horny.
I said my
name was Kingan.
Norikazu!
Midori!
Ate your horn, didn't she?
You asshole.
It's humiliating!
I was born in hell...
...but got done in by
an itch in my crotch!
You promised!
Tell us where the key is!
Oh well...
Kingan, transform!
Right.
This is the key to hell?
Quick! Let's get back
to OUR world!
No, we've got something
to do before that. Look!
Unless we destroy it,
we'll never have any peace.
But how?
By saving Dr. Masago.
If he doesn't die, then that
thing will never be born.
Can you take us back to Japan,
50 years ago, and then home?
Only if I can
come with you.
You...!
Your loss, then.
No, please!
Put it in.
"Put it in?"
The key, you moron.
Oh, right.
No, like I
showed you before.
Sorry.
Now say my name.
"Eganko. "
Eganko.
What are you doing?!
Stop this!
What're you bastards
doing with me?!
Open up! Let me out!
Made it.
Ow!
The lab!
We're too late!
Horny, please!
Save the doctor!
I said my name
isn't "Horny".
Outta my way...
Got him!
Doctor!
Doctor, speak to me!
Who are...?
Thank god!
We came to save you!
Please, come with us.
50 years into the future.
50 years into the future?
What's this all about?
- You see...
- Norikazu, time to go!
Why did you save me?
I've been branded a spy,
almost killed.
My wife was raped
in front of me.
Why should I go on living?
Of all the ungrateful...?!
We save his ass and
he bitches about it!
Shoulda left the
old fart to rot!
Eganko!
Doctor, I know how
you must feel...
...but we aren't just saving you,
but a girl as well!
What do you mean?
Midori here is the
reincarnation of your wife.
She's related to her?
The N3-C became your ghost, seeking
vengeance, when you died inside it.
And it hates Midori for
being your wife, reborn.
I see...
But this way,
the ghost will never be born.
AII's well that ends well.
My house! I never thought
it'd look so good!
We're finally back?
That's better.
I was smotherin' in there...
More S&M, huh?
You're a jerk, Horny!
A stupid little JERK!
This is Japan 50 years
in the future?
It looks like the capital
after an air raid.
No shit. Not that
different from hell, really.
What?!
How...
How did this happen?
Kazuya! Sue!
- It's Midori and Norikazu!
- You made it back!
What's going on?
What happened here?
HE happened.
But, that's impossible!
How can he exist?!
He just suddenly showed up
and started nuking the city.
You were born from my death.
How can you exist here?
Crossing 50 years, your anger
was amplified again and again.
It crossed space and time
to allow my existence.
Disgusting creature!
You're a twisted mind...
...without a shred of
humanity or compassion.
I am merely an unembellished
reflection of your soul.
You're what?! If you really
represent my soul...
...then why do you hate my wife's
reborn spirit within that girl?
I loved my wife!
No, you hated her!
More than the man who raped her,
you hated your wife.
The wife who said
she preferred him to you!
Let the hatred
grow within you!
The hatred I've tasted
for five decades!
No, don't!
Yes...
You're better than him!
Everything is my fault...
What do I do now?
How do I set it right?!
What's eating you, Pops?
You look like you just
ran into Death himself.
I've a favor to ask.
Will you hear me out?
What do you think
will happen to us?
It'll be okay. I said I'd beat
that thing, so don't worry.
He's no match for
the great Norikazu!
Thank you, Norikazu.
Be gentle...
Norikazu!
Aw man...
Midori...
Midori, you're incredible!
So tight...!
No, stop!
Don't say it like that!
Norikazu...
It feels so good...
It's embarrassing, but...
I wanna do it, too!
Oh god! Oh god! I...!
Midori.
Midori, I'm going to...
No! Just hang on
a little longer!
But you're
pumping so hard!
Don't talk like that!
It's just how my legs are!
Midori, I can't hold it!
Norikazu, I... I...!
OH GOD!
Midori...
Norikazu...
Eganko!
What are you doing?!
Well, I was bored sitting
here all by myself.
Huh? Where's the doctor?
Here.
He had me send him
back to the past.
August 6, 1945...
Why would he want to go there?
Who knows? I just did
what he asked me to.
Cheer up, he was
just a useless old man.
What's he up to?
Send me back!
To the same place. NOW!
Alright.
You don't have to yell...
Okay, how was it spelled?
H... I... R...
I'm going, too!
O... S... H...
Should I go with you?
No, don't.
Just pull us out in 30 minutes.
I... M... A... Not my problem
if you run into trouble, then.
What's wrong?
I just sent away
my favorite boy toy!
What are you doing here?
We had Eganko send us back.
What are you doing back here?
I...
Hey, that round
building over there...
This looks like...!
Hiroshima.
August 6, 1945.
You're going to lure it here to
destroy it with the atom bomb!
It's too dangerous!
You'll have to think of
some other way to destroy it.
Come back with us.
Eganko will be pulling
us out in 30 minutes.
It's too late.
The bomb will be
dropped before then.
Doctor!
You?!
We meet again.
I believe I owe you something.
What?!
What are they?!
Midori!
And now I'll have your
woman again. Look well!
Midori!
Who are you?!
Eganko!
That'll teach you!
Without me, you're dead!
Help us!
Oww...
You won't interfere!
Kingan!
Horny!
I keep telling you,
my name is Kingan!
Gratuitous, wasn't it?
Doctor!
- Norikazu, get in!
- Can you fly that?
Hey, after all the virtual
flight sims I've played...
...a fighter like this is
a piece of cake!
You don't have to come!
You can fly by yourself!
Nuts to you!
Oh, jeez...
For crying out loud!
Doctor, think it over!
It can't work!
Of course!
You want to die with it!
You can't!
Doctor, we don't
do that anymore!
It's for the best.
I created it,
and I'll destroy it as well.
Let me put an end
to all of this!
Doctor...!
The Enola Gay...
The plane with
the Hiroshima bomb...
Doctor!
No matter where you run,
you cannot escape me!
Come to hell with me!
This world's
way worse than hell.
No shit...
Doctor...
Time to go home.