The grounds
are really bright.
They're really bright for
this early in the morning.
Yeah...
I didn't hear from you for a while.
What were you up to?
Nothing special.
Like hell! You and Norikazu
went off somewhere, didn't you?
He wasn't at school
either while you were gone.
C'mon,
where'd you two go?
Midori, tell me where.
Midori...
Midori, what's with you?
I'm not saying!
Midori!
Oh, for Heaven's sake!
Good morning to you...
Professor.
How might I help you?
Yukimoto!
How could you write this?!
How could I write what?
Read it yourself.
Question: In 200 words,
discuss the basis of...
...the twelve note musical scale
of the late Romantic period.
Answer: Professor Saiki, as I
look at your figure from behind...
...as you administer this exam,
I write for you this answer.
Your long hair, your perfect skin,
your bewitching gaze...
Just thinking about them
sets my heart on fire!
Your lips...
Your lips, so carefully rouged
into so full a smile...
How many men have
longed for those lips?
That's not what you wrote!
That lewd little mouth of
yours was really asking...
..."How many men have
those 'lips' sent to Heaven!"
Oh Dean...! Stop it!
Oh god... Don't...
How did you...
How did you get that?!
Professor...
Would you please disrobe?
What did you just say?
Stop it!
Turn the tape off.
Professor,
please disrobe.
Professor, you're still
wearing something.
Yukimoto, please.
Don't do this.
Stop it!
Turn it off!
Yukimoto,
don't do this to me.
Please move
your hands, Professor.
Such large breasts.
A 36" bust, to be sure.
How many men have
squeezed them?
No, don't...
Professor, be so kind as
to move your other hand.
Now then,
spread your legs apart.
Why, Professor!
Getting wet so soon?
Please, don't say that.
Now then,
please play the piano.
Yukimoto, what are you...?!
Professor, your hands have a
job to do. Continue the recital.
Professor, your nipples
are this hard already?
Don't say that.
Yu- Yukimoto, not there!
Spread your legs, please.
No!
Now move your hips.
No... Stop it!
Professor,
your recital is suffering.
Yukimoto, I can't...
Yukimoto, no!
Professor...
How many men have
been inside of you?
No! Don't say
things like that.
Yukimoto, no.
A teacher and a student can't...
Please, stop.
But it's all right for a
teacher and the Dean to do it?
That was... Don't!
Professor,
I'm about to release.
No, not inside me!
Well, then you shouldn't be
holding it in so tightly.
Don't say...
Oh god, I'm going to...!
No! Pull it out!
I'm... I'm...
Oh god!
Good morning, everyone!
And now for the
morning announcements.
Very good, Professor.
How many men have
you practiced on?
No, you can't rest yet.
Here it comes.
No!
Midori...
I'm going to...!
Supernatural Beast Battlefront
ADVENTURE KID 3
Original Story by
TOSHIO MAEDA
You new here? I thought
I knew everyone here in hell.
You know, you're kinda cute.
Wanna have some fun?
Screenplay by
AKIO SATSUKAWA
"Fun...?"
Music by
MASAMICHI AMANO
Norikazu, you JERK!
Character Design RYUNOSUKE OTONASHI
YUJI TAKAHASHI Art Director SOHEl KOIZUMI
Animation Director YUJI TAKAHASHI
Director of Photography YOSHIAKI YASUHARA
You promised!
Tell us where the key is!
Oh well...
Kingan, transform!
Right.
Directed by
YOSHITAKA FUJIMOTO
Now say my name.
"Eganko. "
Eganko.
Supernatural Beast Battlefront
ADVENTURE KID 3 The Miracle Love Potion
I'm dying!
You're killing me!
Interesting idea, Dakiniten.
If you, a Lady of hell,
were to die...
...just where exactly
would you end up?
Sire, some news...
What?! My son is
a slave to a human?!
Look at this, Sire.
What?!
In addition, she refers to
him by the lowly name of "Horny. "
The noble name of
Kingan is denied him...
...and replaced with "Horny?!"
Unforgivable!
YES!
Mephisto!
Is Mephisto here?
So, Mephisto. You've been with
me for 500 years, haven't you?
And I am filled with gratitude
for your majesty's good will.
Here's your chance
to regain your freedom.
Go to the human world
and bring back the prince.
I must humbly suggest that Mephisto
is unsuited for this responsibility.
500 years ago, he allowed the
master demon alchemist to escape.
All because he was
distracted by a woman.
If you fail,
you forfeit your life!
Because I'll be sending
him after you, next!
But since Eganko's left...
...the doorway to the
human world is sealed.
Why don't I try to
break that seal open?
These thighs let Eganko into
this world when she was born.
Tell me, boy... Do you have
what it takes to get in here?
So, how does it feel to wear only
your birthday suit, Professor?
Yukimoto, please.
Give me back my clothes!
I've brought a wonderful
outfit for you.
Please put this on.
Yukimoto...! You seriously
expect me to wear this?!
Put it on, Professor.
The collar as well,
Professor.
Now turn around, please.
Yukimoto,
what are you...?!
Yukimoto...?
Stick it out a
bit more, Professor.
Professor, you're
already getting wet?
Don't...
It's embarrassing...
Professor,
a bit wider, please.
Professor, do you ever
play with yourself?
No, I don't do
things like that.
Well then,
do you play with toys?
What?
Yukimoto...!
Professor, liars always
get punished in the end.
Yukimoto, stop it!
No! Don't!
You seem to be enjoying this.
Why don't I leave it in?
Yukimoto.
No... Oh no...
Do you like it, Professor?
Shall I leave it like this?
No, Yukimoto...
Stop it...
No! Stop it!
I'm going to...!
Stop! Stop it!
I'm almost...!
I can't help it!
I'm... OH!
Professor, don't hog
the fun all to yourself.
I'd like a bit
of that as well.
Taste good,
Professor?
Here's your reward.
Please continue,
Professor.
Midori...
If only this
was Midori, instead.
Professor, I'm about ready.
Swallow all of it when it comes.
Professor...!
Midori!
Norio!
On your way home?
No, it's test prep
class, for me.
Killer.
And it's Summer, too.
Say, Midori.
Do you like the opera?
I've two tickets to
the Met for tonight.
Care to join me?
Sorry, but I have plans.
Today's Norikazu's birthday.
And I bet that's a homemade
cake for him you've got there.
Bingo!
Too bad. Guess I'll use the
other seat for my bag of textbooks.
Sorry I can't join you.
See you tomorrow!
Midori...
As much as I care for you...
What do you see in Hanyu?!
Hey... Cut it out!
C'mon, let's pick
up where we left off.
If she hadn't butted in that time,
we could've gone all the way.
But, that was just...!
Hey!
THIS part of
you's being honest.
Happy birthday-
Midori!
Oh, Norikazu.
Norikazu...
Norikazu, I HATE YOU!
Midori!
Norikazu, wait!
And he had so
much to give me...
Norikazu,
you stupid jerk!
Midori!
Midori, wait up!
We used to play together
when we were little...
I used to dream about growing
up and marrying you.
I've always loved you...
And now... Now...!
How dare you make
the mistress cry!
What the hell is that?!
You let Horny crawI
around in your shirt?!
But he asked if
he could ride in there...
And I suppose you'd let him
into your panties if he asked?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
You stupid jerk!
- To hell with you!
- Midori!
Midori...
Looks like she's asleep.
Poor kid.
Your highness, why won't you
come back to hell with me?
'Cause I LIKE this lifestyle!
Nothing wrong with being
this cutie's slave, no sir!
I get to slip
into her cleavage...
...and wander around in some
even more interesting places.
Lemme show you
something cool.
Umm, love that smell!
Lookit this!
God, I love
touching this thing!
Hey, wanna give this a try?
Do you wanna look in here?
Huh? Mephisto?
You saw me?
Jerk!
Eganko!
You're pretty well
in the mood, I see.
This is just...
C'mon... Let's pick
up where we left off.
- No!
- C'mon.
No! I only love Midori!
And thanks to you,
our relationship's shot to shit!
Get out of my life!
I hate you!
I never want
to see you again!
Norikazu...
The hell with you!
Mom!
Oh! Eganko!
Something wrong?
I just needed
to hear your voice.
I always feel better
when I talk to you.
- Where are you?
- The human world.
The human world?!
Have you been with the prince?
Prince? Oh, Kingan.
Yeah, I guess.
Mephisto's there
to bring him back.
Mephisto's here, too?
So, how are the men
in the human world?
Bet you've got 'em
lined up for you.
Well... There's this girl
who's screwing it up for me.
I think the potion should take
care of a human girl in one shot.
"Potion?"
Have you forgotten?
The miracle love potion...
...that's been in our
family for generations.
The miracle love potion...
The Sigh of Isolde.
That might work...
Thanks, Mom!
Good luck.
Just you wait...
With the Sigh of Isolde...
...I'll mess up all
your plans for him.
- No... Stop it!
- Oh, you like it.
I didn't come
here for this!
I know.
But is it so bad?
No...
Don't do that...!
You're good at this.
Pretty crappy roost
you've got here.
Eganko!
Wha-?! Who is she?!
What's going on here?
Uh... Well...
- I'm history, pal!
- No, please...!
Christ...
Serves me right!
Wait, come back!
Considering how you've come all
the way to the human world...
...I'd think you'd get
something better than this!
Not in the budget. Rent's
outrageous around here!
Liar. You just need a place
for your little diversions.
So, did you manage to talk
Kingan into going back?
The prince just
won't listen to me.
He likes being that
cute girl's slave.
There she goes again!
That little bitch is nothing but
trouble for ANYONE from hell!
Hey, Mephisto.
Why don't you help me out?
Huh?
If my plan works,
Kingan'll go home with you.
Well, in that case...
I know it's short notice, but I
need to check the Hell-Net database.
Gotta find someone who's got
the hots for that "Midori" girl.
Won't accessing the
base get us in trouble?
Keep quiet about
it and who'll know?
Norio Yukimoto, huh?
I'm bored... Lemme out!
I thought lookin'
in her panties was okay!
Professor...
Have you kept your promise?
Midori...
Why won't you acknowledge me?
My heart is drawn to you.
This horny sow is
only a substitute for you.
Professor,
I'm about to release.
No! Not inside!
Then don't move
your body so much.
I'm just... No...
Oh, yes!
Who are you? How'd you
get in here without a key?!
Oh please.
That's no trick at all.
So, you want
Midori Asai for yourself.
You want Midori Asai,
I want Norikazu Hanyu.
Norikazu's in your way,
and Midori's in my way.
You take her,
and I'll take Norikazu.
Like that'd work?
If we use this.
The miracle love potion:
The Sigh of Isolde.
"Sigh of Isolde?"
What are you...?
I just need a
little of your sperm.
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
No...
You're a naughty
little girl, aren't you?
Now, as an example,
we take this equation...
...in which we'll solve for
the variables x, y, and z.
We pay attention to the second
equation: x + 3y - 3z = 6.
We're going to leave the
x on the left side of...
...of the problem
while moving 3y and 3z...
You sure this
is going to work?
The blue one
is Norikazu's...
The red is the love potion
with your sperm added.
You're about
to see its effect.
Midori!
Professor!
Now watch. We rubbed that woman
of yours all over with the stuff.
Are you okay, Professor?
Who did this
horrible thing to you?!
Hanyu...
I can't take it anymore...
Please...
Squeeze my breasts...
But...?!
I... I don't know
what's wrong with me...
Please.
I can't take it anymore...
Hanyu, please...
Please, hurry!
Harder...
Hanyu, harder!
Yes! More! Harder!
Harder! Harder!
Hanyu, come into me.
- "Into you?!"
- Please.
B- but...!
This is a teacher's order!
Right...
Hurry!
Professor,
I'm putting it in.
Oh, yes!
Ow! What're you doing?!
What's your problem?!
Inside.
What are you doing?!
See? That's what your
boyfriend's REALLY like.
Someone who'd
do his own teacher.
Now it's your turn.
'Scuse me, Miss.
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
No! Stop it!
No! Stop-!
Don't...
Oh, YES!
Good luck.
Midori...
Don't!
No!
Midori, be true
to your feelings!
See? This part of
you already is.
I can't...
Midori, I love you!
Yukimoto, stop it!
That's funny. Any woman who
gets covered with the potion...
...should be drawn to the
man the sperm came from and...
...fall hopelessly
in love with him.
What?
I mixed up the
red and the blue.
You moron!
No! Stop it!
Midori...!
My body...
It feels so hot...
No... No!
I'm in love... with Norikazu!
Stop it!
What...
What the hell's with you?!
You think I'm not
good enough for you?!
Don't make me laugh!
You think any of
you are my equal?!
Compared to an elite like me,
you're all just insects!
You incompetents should fall down
on your knees in front of me!
No, stop it!
Save me!
Norikazu, save me!
Midori!
Norio, stop it!
Midori, don't
you really want this?
Hanyu?!
You son of a...!
So, we're "insects", huh?
He's getting away!
After him!
Midori...
Norikazu...
You saved me.
Midori, I-
It's okay.
Midori...
Norikazu...
Oh? I don't see
the prince with you.
Well, I...
You poor SOB.
I guess this is Doomsday for you.
So... He's coming, is he?
Sharpening his claws right now.
Wonder who's the unlucky victim?
He'll be there soon.
I'll be going to
Midori's house after this.
And after I get what I want,
we'll both die together!
Well, uh,
good for you...
But before that, I'm going to
beat the living shit out of...
...you and
that vampire chick!
Whoa!
Incoming transmission!
Shut up,
you fucking machine!
No!
He's coming in from hell...!
5... 4...
3... 2... 1...
The hell with this thing!
Now what's going to happen?