Hear me. Hear my voice.
And answer me.
Cloaked in red and a banner of
blue like the beasts of fury...
...commanding great power,
bringing good fortune upon thee...
...but then only to take it away.
Broadening the power deep within...
...the ones which bring to focus.
Thou great power of
meritorious deeds...
...the glory of thee and your
supreme valor.
Bring to me once again that
which was fulfilled in the past.
Grant me the power!
Know my intentions!
The enemy is before us!
Scorch them with the heat
of your passion!
Give countenance to my deeds,
spirits of heaven!
To the spirits of Ignis
and Framma...
...I need your power.
Gather forth in shining glory.
The valor that brings success
to my soul.
Show me and let me be
your sword!
Evoke Framma and Vintos!
Frame Window!
Only a female left.
So you can speak, huh?
It's telepathy. You pick it up
pretty good.
You've got a great body. Too bad
it wields a sword.
Don't mock me!
Oh, my.
Here goes...
Thanks for the fruit!
Help!
You! In the tree!
Help me!
I've got to save her!
Oh, no...
Meruru.
Charity is an investment.
A good deed will always return
with favor.
Hang on. I'll be right there.
All right.
Huh?
Oh, well.
The six gray horses pulling the
chariot of white gold.
The heavenly spirits of victory
galloping across the heavens.
Come to me!
To save the moment,
I must taketh from Tella.
And place it upon my palm.
To the spirits of Arel Vintos...
...I need your power!
Evoke Arel Levitation!
Oh...! No...!
Heh. How unreliable.
What happened to you?
Did some goblins get you?
Will you just untie me?!
You call yourself a warrior?
You're a novice, aren't you?
You're the one who fell
thinking you could fly!
You novice sorceress!
I have reached the Proficient Level.
No way! You sure don't look like
a full-fledged sorceress.
You're rude.
Maybe I'll just leave you here.
Oh, come on!
I'm worried about my sister.
Hurry up and untie me!
What?
I bet you train a lot.
You've got a great body.
This place?
Is this the power of the Ogre?
It's like a tornado went through.
Is anybody here?!
Anybody here?!
Meruru, let's split up and search.
Okay.
It's my sister's sword!
It must have been
a peaceful village.
What happened to the child
this belongs to...?
I can't...
...forgive them.
Are you ready?
No matter how much you study
the chants and practice sorcery...
...if you do not have the wisdom...
...as the saying goes, "the great sword
of goblins", the "slime and gold"...
...none will be of any use.
You will eventually fail.
Yes.
Think of the purpose for taking on
this dangerous power.
Study it well...
...the true sorcery.
What are you going to do to me?!
You're awfully cute.
I'll have to help myself.
I don't have anything
I can give you.
But you do.
The nice, firm body you've got.
I want it.
What are you going to
make me do?!
Don't be stupid.
I'm going to make love to that
hollow between your legs.
Make love?
I'm gonna spread your legs
wide open...
...and shove my member into you,
thrusting...
...and twisting it around
in all sorts of ways...
...and do the dirtiest, nastiest...
...things to you until your hips give out
and you can't take any more.
How can you...?!
No way...!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hear me. Hear my voice.
And answer me.
Grant me the power!
The enemy is before us!
Scorch them with the heat
of your passion!
Show me and let me be your sword!
Evoke Framma and Vintos!
Who do you think I am?
What'd you say?
Meruru the Sorcerer, who cometh
once in a century...
...is indeed I!
Lookin' good, Meruru!
Frame Window!
Thine spirit is at one with mine.
Spirits of heaven.
Hinder the intentions
of this scourge.
Cast judgment upon him
with indifference!
Reveal the power in the name of
thine greatness!
Evoke Ventum Spherics!
Why?
I practiced this so much.
Don't frighten me, cutie.
No...!
Let me go!
Looks delicious...!
No! Don't!
Let me go!
Since ancient times, the master
would send the novice on a journey...
...to be cast into a valley
of a thousand fathoms.
Forgive me.
Help me!
No!
I'll give you my love.
I said no!
Stop it!
I can't get enough...
No!
No...!
It hurts!
Stop!
We must learn patience.
I've had to learn that as well.
It hurts...!
Please, no!
It'll go too deep!
Nice and tight!
Ow!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'll twist it around.
No...
You're quite the woman.
Don't break apart on me.
Meruru!
Where did she go?
The light in the night shed.
Ogre Mountain!
You awake?
No! No...!
I'm Tia the warrior.
From the village.
Tia?! You mean,
Luna's big sister?
Is Luna all right?
I'm sure she is.
And who may you be?
I'm Meruru, from
the town of Hugh.
I'm a sorceress of the Wiz Sect.
A wizard?
Who are they?
They were taken from the village...
...as food for the Ogre.
Hey, lady. I'm gonna have you
instead of breakfast.
What?! No...!
You've got a lot of energy considering
I just popped your cherry.
But I'm gonna have
a little fun first...
...you cutie.
Well then, I'm gonna sink
my morning staff into you.
No! Stay away from me!
What a view!
No!
No! W-Wait...!
I...
I'm sorry, Meruru.
Oh, yeah...
Meruru...!
Lu-Luna...
Luna!
Stop it...!
Luna...
Are you okay?!
Wow, your sorcery was amazing!
My...
Frame Window!
My sorcery did...
Spherics!
Meruru, you must check first
with your own eyes.
If you do not understand
the resurgence of the soul...
...there will be no resurgence
in your power.
Observe the power.
As one who strives to attain
the highest level...
...you must remember that your
beautiful body is something very rare.
You really must be...!
...a once-in-a-century sorcerer...
That's right! It's the sorcerer...
...Meruru!
Meruru.
Luna.
I was so scared!
Well, there were some problems
along the way...
...but we did see some
impressive sorcery.
People become adults as they
face adverse situations.
Right, everyone?
Are you going already, Meruru?
Why don't you stay awhile?
I'd love to, but I'm in
the middle of training.
I see.
Then work hard and become
a great sorceress.
Thank you.
Meruru, I'll work hard to become
a strong warrior.
Yeah, let's both do our best.
Well, good-bye.
Good-bye, Meruru!
I hope... I hope we meet again!
We'll meet again. Sometime, I'm sure!