Luric Ruleek, the path of
no return.
Showing you the road eight times...
...those with courage
returning three.
What do you mean?
I have no choice but to go!
Why are the shriekers after us?
There're after women.
Human women.
What?!
I heard these guys...
...reproduce using human women
to plant their eggs in.
What?
I summon the protection
of the house of Yugdrasil...
...Ehwy Ahweh, Loki, oh, Loki...
...hear my voice.
The sword of Ruun,
show me a miracle!
It didn't work!
There's too many of them!
Muppa!
Take that!
Ew Woowy Neu Teel Teel,
grant me the power!
No!
When the power of the
constellation of Lukes...
...descends upon us...
...the evildoers shall be
condemned.
Evoke Lukes Anti Viru!
Ateriel!
Grant me the power!
In this moment in which
I possess the wisdom...
...thou shall strike down...
...the soulless scourge!
Evoke Ignis Fireball!
Hey, wake up! Hey!
You all right? Hey! Hey!
Thank you.
She seems to be sleeping well.
I'm glad my potion worked on her.
She's a sorcerer of the craftsman
level like you.
She is?
Yes. Frenieple Slaipny Sen.
She's our master.
My name is Liao.
I'm a monk of the Deepankala Sect.
I'm Meruru Sheckle.
Nice to meet you.
Is that insignia from Riledihaim?
Don't tell me you came all
the way from there?
It's the edge of the world...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it. It's the truth.
My home is in Selica.
I'm a barbarian from beyond
the edge of the world.
Are you awake? How do you feel?
All right...
I'm all right now.
What? You're after the Likuu
book of sorcery too?
Yes. I take it you are?!
I guess those going in for
sorcery are all the same.
Then you must be seeking
the Lanini monastery as well.
Yes, that's right.
Then, let's go together.
I'd love that!
The good will of travel companions...
...begets a party of
strong travel partners.
What a party! What a party!
How auspicious!
Ehwoh Eyaweh Yawoh...
...Ansaz Ansab, hear my voice.
We are your daughters,
Yellar Aluchis.
Come forth. We are your disciples.
Ehwoh Eyah Woh Yahwoh.
Ehwoh Eh Yahwoh, Ingis Ingis...
Lord, our father...
Come forth to Ruun.
This is no good.
I think we got lost.
Leave this to me.
As my spirit melds with...
...the spirits of the Vintos...
...grant me wings for my soul.
Evoke Vintos Locate!
Thunderbolt of Ruun!
Give me a miracle!
Jurido Blasting!
SAHAGI NA FALLS
The bridge must've been
washed out by the flood.
There's no way we can swim
to the other side.
I never learned Aqua Breaching...
...or Hydro Walking.
Levitation won't get me
across either.
We'll just have to go to the
other bridge upstream.
Let's just pray it wasn't
washed out too.
Liao!
Bolboi.
We're lucky this year.
We should be able to produce
strong babies with these bodies.
Babies? What do you mean?!
Don't play dumb.
We're gonna lay eggs
in your body...
...and we're gonna fertilize them.
And that baby's gonna eat
your bodies alive.
You've got to be kidding.
We're not some kind of shellfish!
I'd say you're pretty much
the same thing.
You guys, that's not
all there is to it.
How about the part about
coming in the mouth?
What are you talking about, Geri?!
How could I forget that!
In the mouth?!
What are you scheming?!
Listen, first you lick this here.
Then you take it in the mouth
and suckle on it.
Then you move it up and down,
side to side...
...until your jaw seizes up.
Then you take what comes
and swallow it all.
What...?!
Fellatio...!
How could they...!
No way!
Don't you get uppity with me!
What about you?!
It's your misfortune that
you came after us.
That's the spirit, Meruru!
Teach them that people aren't
who they seem at first.
Awaken!
The wise redeemers
of darkness and fury.
There's no green far and near.
May our fertility sustain us.
Deliver us from this ugliness
as our hearts deserve.
Evoke Tella and Teneble!
Metamol Fas!
What?!
It's because I don't have
my Charles Rod!
And my parchment was washed
away in the river.
Even without my Rod...!
Grant me, the miracle
of metamorphosis.
I shall then wield a spider web.
I shall dance, floating on the air,
and capture you in my web!
Evoke Tella and Vintos!
Magic Web!
Oh, no! Meruru!
They're nothing more than
mummies wrapped in bandages!
They sure fell into a hole this time.
No!
Well.
No...!
Get that ass up in the air!
No...
Freni!
Shut up! I'll do you in a minute.
Just sit tight and watch!
Here we go!
No!
Hey, Geri! Let us have a go at her!
Let me just finish up here.
Freni!
Oh, yeah! I'm gettin' pretty horny!
I'm about to come!
Now, it's your turn.
All right!
No...!
How about we give this one
a little bit of love?
All right, it's your turn.
Yeah!
No...!
What are you talking about?
It's only just beginning.
Please stop! Stop it!
Now, suck it! Suck it!
You idiot! Don't spit it out!
What's that look for?
All right, you swallow too! There!
My turn! My turn!
And you too!
Let it all out. All of it!
Now, we're gonna rip your arm
and leg tendons apart.
And then it's over.
Metamol Fas!
This must be...!
They must be down there somewhere.
Oh, Meruru...
You are already aware.
The thunderbolt that destroyed the
man-eating ogre, and this spell.
As long as sorcery lives in the Rod.
In other words, the secret effect
of the Spell Enhancer.
You know that it is not
your own power.
My Rod is there to save you.
However, Meruru, if you have the
will, you must carry on your quest.
To the deep bosom of your master.
We're saved.
But eggs have been laid inside us.
It's okay. I have a potion
that my master gave me.
If we take that...
Really?!
Hear me. Hear my voice.
And answer me.
Cloaked in red and a banner of
blue like the beasts of fury...
...commanding great power,
bringing good fortune upon thee...
...but then only to take it away.
Broadening the power deep within,
the ones which bring to focus.
Thou great power of
meritorious deeds.
The glory of thee and
your supreme valor.
Bring to me once again that which
was fulfilled in the past.
Grant me the power!
In this moment in which
I possess the wisdom...
...thou shall strike down the
repugnant and soulless scourge.
To the spirits of Ignis
and Framma...
...I need your power.
Gather forth in this place, and
show me your supreme valor.
Let me be your sword!
Evoke Ignis Fireball!