Any organization, large or small, has
their own share of dark human drama.
Greed may enter the picture, especially in cases
involving inheritance and life insurance policies.
In these types of circumstances, the true
colors of humanity reveal themselves.
The incident that occurred at Nonomura
Hospital is an example of this phenomenon.
NONOMURA HOSPITAL
One morning, the hospital president was found
dead, and I was privately hired to solve the case.
I infiltrated the hospital in
an inconspicuous manner...
...and managed to acquire some vital clues.
The president died while having sex
with a woman who has a beauty mark.
But, who secretly made that
phone call and for what purpose?
A woman with a beauty mark.
And, what secret is the security
guard blackmailing Rie Makino with?
In the midst of this tangled
web of relationships...
...I have begun to narrow
down the suspects.
What do you think?
Have you solved the mystery already?
This was a narration by Takumaro Kaibara.
Mystery of Nonomura Hospital
Episode 2
NONOMURA HOSPITAL
I didn't get enough sleep last night
because of that nasty recorded call.
Good morning.
Wash your face and I'll
get you some breakfast.
Great.
What's with that perverted
look on your face?
Um-no, nothing.
You're having dirty thoughts
again, aren't you?
Good morning.
Well? Any progress?
Oh, and your electric
wheelchair is here.
That's great, thanks.
This works great.
By the way, I hear that the late
president was really a horny bastard.
I didn't know and I don't care.
Someone's frigid.
Anyway, about the case...
It could be a woman,
possibly a nurse.
I'd like to get a full report in
the VIP room tonight at 9:30.
I'll be there.
Shimizu from room 409
passed away this morning.
That's the third one this month.
Apparently, it was a lot worse when the
old hospital president was in charge.
There've been a lot of rumors
about surgical mistakes.
Hey! Thanks for coming.
The police said it was a suicide,
but the case is still open.
I knew it.
The president was apparently addicted
to drugs. They're investigating that.
So, did the president accidently
inject himself with cyanide!?
Someone must have switched
it on the night of the murder.
Good morning.
Morning.
She's a charming girl.
Really cute too.
Her nurse is too.
This place has a ton of hot babes.
You should admit yourself.
God! Men are such pigs.
Oh and about Rie Makino...
That's her over there.
Six years ago, her parents
were in a car accident...
...and were admitted to
this hospital, but they died.
At the time, there was a rumor that the president
made a critical error during the surgery.
She was adopted by her
aunt and changed her name.
Something smells fishy.
I wouldn't want to name her
as a suspect. It's too tragic.
Apparently there have been many
mistakes like that at this hospital.
She's probably not the only
one who's holding a grudge.
By the way...
...can you imagine the
sound of a woman's moan...
...when she's having sex, just
by listening to her normal voice?
Don't ask me that!
Does that mean...
You're a virgin!?
W-what!? What do you
mean, "when she's having sex!?"
When I was in the VIP room, someone called and
played a recording of the night the president died...
...and there was a woman
moaning in the background.
What?
Really?
Why you?
Who knows.
It's our job to find out.
Yeah, but...
Then who, and for what reason?
I don't know. But they seem
to be watching us closely.
Then, am I being watched too?
You've been watched since
you accepted the case.
No way!
Ryoko, you find out how that
bug ended up in my room.
It might have been the same one
that was used at the murder scene.
Sure.
I'll see if I can get any more
information from the police.
Before you do that, I'd like to get
a wire tapping system for myself.
Staff Announcement:
Miss Mamiya. Miss Mamiya...
Please report to
the Nurse's Station.
I'll see you later.
Ok.
Hey!
Oh! Hi, detective.
Do you write in your
journal every day?
Yes. I'm writing a story.
Really!? That sounds interesting.
Will you let me read it?
I can't!
I haven't even let Chisato read it.
That's too bad! Aww, man!
You really want to read it?
Yeah! I really want to read it.
Really? You really want to read it?
Of course! I may not look
it, but I love Fantasy books!
To be honest... I'm having
trouble writing the rest.
Will you give me some feedback?
Sure.
Then... I'll lend it to you.
But only for one day!
Thanks.
Mr. Kaibara. This is the staff
assignment chart for that night.
Oh, thank you.
High cut panties!
Mr Kaibara! If you're done
here, please excuse yourself!
S-sorry.
Wild taste in undies for
a woman of her age...
A beauty mark!
Miss Makino!
Yes?
Chisato Mamiya and Rie Makino were both on
duty on the top floor on the night of the murder.
Miho Nozawa was on duty for the morning
shift, and the other nurse called in sick.
I've been waiting for you.
It's you!
Please go take a bath.
You smell like sweat.
Are you horny from
smelling my hot sweat?
You idiot.
WATER REHABILITATION ROOM
Want to join me?
This feels great!!
How's the water temperature?
Good! Good!
This is heavenly!
It was a joke! Don't take me seriously!
This isn't a co-ed bath!
I... I'm getting out.
But you're usually such a pervert...
That's all show. That's not really me.
Liar. You seem pretty happy.
Why are you...! Trying to distract me
from the investigation isn't gonna work!
Don't... mess... with... me!
I beg you. Please don't investigate her!
Who are you talking about?
You suspect Rie, right?
I'm not convinced yet
that she's the murderer.
Her motives are suspicious,
but there're other suspects.
Let's talk in my room.
I'd like to save Rie too.
I'm sorry... I... You're a good person.
You're really going?
Why did I have to act like a gentleman?
Rie and I lived together in the same dorm.
When I got dumped by my
boyfriend, I attempted suicide.
She was the one who stopped me.
If I hadn't had Rie, I probably wouldn't
have been able to get back on my feet.
Then you know about her parents, and the
president's mistake during their surgery?
Figures... you've already investigated.
Why do you think Rie is the murderer?
That day...
I was changing to go on duty
for my morning shift when...
...Rie came in crying.
I asked her what was wrong,
and all she could do was cry.
Later, I found out about the murder.
I thought that she'd finally done it.
What time was it?
Around nine.
Do you know about the security guard?
Huh? What's that?
I haven't mentioned anything
to Rie about it since then, so...
I'll tell you after I've thought
about it some more.
OK. You promise?
Yeah.
Tonight is the night I
will defeat the demon.
The prince gave me a vial of
the demon's favorite nectar.
I'm going to switch it with poison.
The demon always bathes
before the ceremony...
I was able to successfully switch the vial.
The demon came towards me
and raised me on the platform.
His serpent tongue licks my
black star in my pussy.
Your beauty mark in your
pussy makes me so horny.
I love it when you cry like that.
A black star!
The woman with the
beauty mark is Momoko!?
The demon drank the nectar as usual.
Then the ceremony begins.
But it's different this time...
The painful ceremonies will be over soon...
I must hold on... I must hold on...
The demon is dead.
The prince promised me he
would take care of the rest...
...before the witch, the demon's
queen, comes at dawn.
Could the prince be...
It's dated the night of
the murder. It has to be!
She had trouble handling her guilt, so
to cope with it, she wrote it all down.
I can't bear to tell the prince the truth.
I can't tell him I dropped...
...the vial before I switched it.
Momoko and the "prince" are both innocent.
The mastermind is someone else!!
Hey!
Can I have a little bit
of your time? Please?
S-sure...
FILE ROOM
This is...
Your true objective has been to locate your
parent's medical records in that room.
Am I wrong?
How did you know that?
A detective needs to think things through,
but they also have to follow their instincts.
You wanted to see your
parents' medical records...
...to see if there actually was a
mistake during their surgery, right?
That day, you witnessed Chisato
coming out of the VIP room.
It seems like you're concealing that fact.
Why are you covering for her?
When my parents died, it was
Chisato's father who took care of me.
What?
How am I supposed to tell people my
benefactor's daughter is a criminal?
That's what it was...
That morning I was in charge
of the linens in the VIP room.
I wasn't told that the
president was staying.
When I got off the elevator
to change the linens...
...I saw someone walking down the
stairs at the end of the hallway.
And that was Chisato?
I only got a glimpse,
but I'm positive it was her.
I thought it was strange, and
I peeked into the VIP room.
That's when...
Thanks for telling me.
What's going to happen to Chisato?
She's not the murderer.
Really?
Yes.
So if the security guard makes
any more advances, tell him no.
I assure you, you don't have to worry.
Mr. Kaibara.
Forgive me.
This is what you get for saying
you want to quit the hospital.
You're my slave forever!
No!
Or do you want me to distribute
that embarrassing tape!?
Stop please!
Ever since the president
showed you how to use it...
...your cunt has been enjoyed
by many of our customers.
Look...
You're so wet.
Please stop!!
Chisato has a beauty mark too.
Hello, this is Kawasaki.
I found the murderer!
Really? That was fast!
Come quick!
Just in case, contact the
police before you come!
This is front page news!
What did you say!?
A couple of the member tapes are gone.
Could that detective or his
assistant have taken them?
Unacceptable!
If that got out... It would
cause a scandal...
...that would rock both the
political and financial worlds.
Forget about collecting the life
insurance. We'll lose our funding!
Let's get rid of them.
The sooner the better.
We can do it tonight.
NURSE'S STATION
Yes?
Come here.
Chisato is...?
Akiko and Fujiki should be leaving
the president's office soon.
Sneak in after making sure
they've left. Got it?
This is Fujiki.
What?
Follow the plan.
The assistant is here.
It's Kaibara.
I've been waiting for you.
Please come in.
I've prepared the finest tea for you.
I'll gladly accept, since
I've finished the case.
Then I'd love to hear
your skilled conclusion.
It's just as you said,
this is a case of murder.
Momoko and Chisato, who were being threatened
by the president, plotted the murder.
But their plan was overheard by
others who had planted a bug.
Plus, they saw Momoko drop and break the
poison ampul meant to kill the president.
But they had also anticipated that, and
switched it with a poison ampul ahead of time.
You say it as if you witnessed it.
Then who's the mastermind?
Just in case, secretly destroy all of the
other illegally recorded member tapes.
As you wish.
And make sure you get rid of the one
that was taped that night, by tonight.
From the point when my husband gets in the
shower, to the part when Momoko comes...
Even the part when you
switch it, it's all recorded.
You still had it?
Seeing my husband being murdered doesn't get
boring, no matter how many times I watch it.
He used my family's connection to
the political and financial worlds.
He made a fortune prostituting
the nurses and selling illicit drugs!
It was a loveless marriage
only meant to use me.
If we hadn't managed to overhear
the nurses' murderous plot...
...you would have ended
up doing it yourself.
Yes.
And then they covered for each other.
The police had no choice
except to rule it a suicide!
I still want my husband's life insurance!
That's why I hired
that stupid detective.
Y-yes...
We're almost there!
It was useless to play that recording
to try to make me blame those girls.
You should have followed
the trail we laid out for you.
I'm not about to let you
have the insurance money.
If we investigate the route between
Momoko's room and the VIP room...
...we should be able to
find a chemical residue.
Well done.
Ryoko might have had faulty reasoning, but
she was dead on about the mastermind.
That stupid girl is about to disappear
forever into the incinerator in the basement.
What did you put in it...
Damn it!!
You just take a nap here
until Fujiki and I return.
Fujiki. Don't you think it's a
waste to just kill and burn her?
Do whatever you want. It
doesn't matter either way.
I'll make you feel good before you die.
My Lady!
Dear, dear. You haven't killed her yet?
I didn't think it would hurt to
let Tanaka have a little fun.
Hey. Hurry it up!
Wait!!
There's something I want to ask her first.
Fujiki!
Yes.
It's better to speak up.
Little girl, you're going to tell
me where you hid the tapes.
No!! I don't know anything
about any tapes.
Oh really? I wonder how
long you can keep that up.
W-what!?
The brakes!
Shit! I can't cut
the power either!
The elevator's open!
That fucking bitch!
Please stop!
Tell me where the tape is!
If I get thrown off...
...it's gonna hurt so bad!!
What a stubborn girl!
Takumaro, help me...
My Lady. Maybe she
really doesn't know.
Seems so... That stupid
detective must have the tapes.
I'm done with you.
I'll make your precious hole bigger.
Oh my! What a rude girl.
My Lady, um...
Sure, do as you please.
Clean her pussy for her.
Stop!!
Mr. Kaibara!
Stop me! Stop me! Stop me!!
Kaibara!!
Miho! Stop me
with your breasts!!
Carry me to the incinerator
in the basement...
No! Help!!
Hurry!!
Gotcha!!
Hold it right there!
Go Kaibara!!
You fucking pervert!!
You're all right now.
You idiot!
What took you so long!!
I was so scared.
Sorry.
Thanks.
NONOMURA HOSPITAL
Morning.
What's wrong? You don't seem like yourself.
Are you not feeling well?
Y-yeah...
Hey! You're acting strange today!
I don't care if I'm acting strange.
Thank you for saving Rie.
This is the only way
I can repay you.
You don't need to thank
me... but... your... umm...
My feelings for you are...
Here... Feel it...
I'm feeling guilty about your girlfriend.
D... don't worry about it.
She's my assistant.
Detective... Not yet... Not yet...
Takumaru, you asshole!!