NURSE'S STATION
I turned off the lights. Is this ok?
Let me take a good
look at your pussy.
You're shaking.
A stormy night is a
nice change of pace.
Your pussy always smells so nice.
There's only one left.
I forgot to restock.
You didn't need this so...
I'm going to go ahead
and help myself.
Yes... This is great.
Come, get on all fours.
Hurry, come on.
Lift your ass up.
You drive me wild when
you moan like that.
Mystery of Nonomura Hospital
Episode 1
TRASH SCHEDULE
THE KAIBARA DETECTIVE AGENCY
WORK!!
Hello, this is the
Kaibara Detective Agency.
HEY YOU JERK!! I've flnally got you on the phone!!
I want you to get out today and I mean it!
Thank you for waking
me up every day.
What?
I'm turning off all the electricity,
gas and water today! Just you wait!
I'm not listenlng to
your excuses anymore!
I'm coming right now
so you better not run!
It's gonna be a wasted trip.
Off to work I go!
But first, let's eat!
MILK TEA
Today's the day I finally
eat a decent meal!
Is this the Kalbara Detective Agency?
Yes, it is.
Is there a representative I can talk to?
My name is Akiko Nonomura.
I'd like to commission a job. Would it be
possible to set up an appointment?
Hold on. Let me take
a look at my schedule.
Oh, I have time tomorrow morning.
Then wlll you be able to
come tomorrow morning...?
...at ten to the president's
office at Nonomura Hospital?
Nonomura Hospital...
The hospital where the
president committed suicide...?
Yes. The police said it was a
suicide, but I'm not convinced.
And you are?
I am the late president's wife and
the vice president of the hospital.
I see. I will be by tomorrow.
Ow... Watch what you're doing!
That was dangerous!
Oh, it's Ryoko Ito.
It's been a while.
It's me.
Takumaro Kaibara!!
Nice to bump into you.
I'd like an answer today.
I absolutely refuse
to be your assistant.
I'm working at the industry's
top firm, Saijyo Detective Agency.
Why should I work for you?
Once you become my assistant
you'll find out how great I am.
Keep talking.
All you do is stick your nose
in cases and cause trouble.
Geniuses are never acknowledged.
Anyway!! What are you
going to do about my suit?
You better buy me a new one!
I'll replace the inside
of your skirt, no problem.
Y-you idiot! Where do
you think you're looking!?
Pervert!! You're an
embarrassment to the industry!!
Once you see me analyze
a case first hand...
...you'll want to submit
your body and soul to me.
Yeah right.
Oh, no time to waste.
I have to go see my client.
My leg...
...is backwards.
I think you broke your leg.
NONOMURA HOSPITAL
What!? Your client is here?
You were commissioned too?
Yes.
We didn't tell her what she wanted
to hear, so she voided our contract.
RECEPTION DESK
Takumaro Kaibara.
Please report to orthopedics.
That's me.
Hey, lend me your shoulder.
Where do you think
you're grabbing, you pervert!!
It wasn't intentional.
ORTHOPEDICS
God... I'm only helping
you to the examination room.
I'm going home.
Take care of my bike!!
Where are we going?
NOGIWA
You're being admitted.
The semi-private rooms are all
full, so I've readied a private one.
A private room?
I can't see your panty line.
It's better not to be hated
by the hospital nurses.
It's my job to analyze.
Call the vice president.
She's my client.
Tell her it's Kaibara. She'll know.
Then you're the new
detective she hired?
That's right.
If you're wearing any...
It'd probably be relaxed-fit
thigh highs with frills.
Guessing from your
personality, the color would be...
Yes! It's got to be...
Translucent red!!
If you want to heal, you'd
better keep that mouth shut!
Miss Mamiya, can you
take care of the rest?
Oh, sure!
I'll go inform the vice president.
Guessing from how pissed
she got, I was probably right.
Please, this way.
OK.
Make sure you hold
on to my shoulder.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
You're welcome.
This hospital is loaded
with beautiful nurses.
Is this how the murdered
president liked it?
Murdered!?
Please don't say such things.
The police said that the
president committed suicide.
It's my job to take
up the cops' slack.
What? Then,
you're the new detective?
Word gets around fast here.
By the way, are those breasts real?
These thingies.
She's got big tits but
she's demure and shy.
Use this. The vice president wants
you to come to the president's office.
But it'll be easier if
I use the wheelchair.
You have to get used
to using crutches.
What are you doing!?
Ouch.
Jeez.
Ooo!!
No whistling in the hospital.
There were so many cute
girls, I just couldn't resist.
There are some awesome perks
to being admitted here, huh?
Miss Nogiwa!!
Yes!
Quiet in the hallways!
Okay.
Young nurses these days...
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
It's Miho, I've brought Mr. Kaibara.
Come in.
What do you think you're doing!?
A cockroach flew into your skirt!
Stop it!!
I said stop it!!
I knew you were wearing panties.
I was dead on about the color.
Damn you!!
You pervert!
Please excuse us.
I'm Takumaro.
I'm Akiko Nonomura.
Nice to meet you.
What was the ruckus about?
Oh, I was just practicing
my deduction skills.
Anyway... I didn't think you'd
be late from being admitted.
This is more convenient in a way.
But I wonder if you'll be
able work with your leg like that?
Come on, a sharp mind is...
...all I need.
I have my outside
information sources.
On top of that,
I have a great assistant.
I'll get straight to the point.
I can't have my husband's
death ruled a suicide.
I need you to find the murderer.
Because you won't be able to collect on
the insurance if he committed suicide?
You're pretty sharp.
You're not so bad yourself.
Bring in the file.
Are they bringing the files from the
female detective who was fired, too?
You're quite quick at
collecting information.
The investigation started
when I accepted the job.
Give it to him, Fujiki.
Yes, my Lady.
Thanks.
So would you like some coffee?
Or would you like...
I prefer tea.
Queen Marie preferably.
Fujiki, get it for him.
As you wish, my Lady.
You seem picky about your tea.
Like Holmes, every detective has
something to help them think.
I'll make sure to send
nothing but the best to your room.
Just don't start playing
a violin really badly.
What else would you need?
A hospital map, a master key to all the rooms,
a list of all the doctors, nurses, and staff...
...a list of patients, a list of
contractors who come and go...
...and an electric wheelchair.
This hospital is huge.
I'll ready all of that. By the way,
how much will all this cost?
For now, necessary expenses.
I'll bill the rest to you later.
Milk first.
Please.
There.
Thanks.
Mmm... It smells great.
Score! This'll show my landlord!!
Anything else?
I'd like you to tell the
nurses to cooperate.
Of course.
Twice In one day!
That should be enough.
Leave the rest to me.
You seem dependable.
I can tell you're different from the other
detectives by the look in your eyes.
Your body's different
from all my other clients, too.
You flatter me.
MAKINO
I brought the flowers.
Put them in water please.
Yes, of course.
Ouch...
She was eavesdropping.
I want more Baby's Breath.
Yes Ma'am. I'll change
the water, too.
Hey.
No!
CONSERVE WATER!!
Why is she so scared of him?
STORAGE ROOM
Watch your teeth.
Yeah, use your tongue.
Please... can this be the
last time we do this?
I can go to the police
and tell them, you know.
No. Please!
Then... You know what to do.
That's right. You're
getting pretty good.
You're crying down here too.
No...
Turn around!
Please, not that...
Hurry up and get on all fours!
Hurry up!
Obedience is best.
No!
Stop!
Please stop!
No!
Stop...
This is great!
Rie is getting blackmailed for something.
Please! No more...
All right then.
See you next time.
Your face is really flushed. Are
you feeling all right, detective?
Oh, it's nothing.
H... hey.
Mr. Kaibara, your
room is on this floor.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Is that man a detective?
Yup.
I wonder if he'll be
part of my story?
Yeah, I wonder?
KAIBARA
I can't believe I let that
sex scene affect me.
I'm still green.
Please excuse me.
By the way...
Why do you call
Madame Akiko 'My Lady'?
I have been serving as her butler
since before her marriage.
One more question.
Why hasn't she been grieving
since her husband died?
I'm sure because it
was a bad arrangement.
I can't say anything else.
If you need to know, you
should investigate it yourself.
So you've decided to
become my assistant?
What!? I brought you your bike.
And yeah, I might still
interested in the case, but...
I say that Fujiki guy is suspicious.
So, you still think that the murderer
is someone close to Madame Akiko?
Yes.
She took a out huge life insurance
policy on her husband six months ago.
That makes her look
really suspicious.
You turned your client into the
murderer. No wonder you were fired.
I just wanted to
uncover the truth!
Then, be my assistant so you can
continue to work on the case.
I guess I have no choice.
I'll be your assistant this
time. But only this once!
Then let's have a meeting
downstairs at the café.
Give me your shoulder.
I'm not going to
fall for that again.
Bitch.
Being a bitch is fine with me.
Fine. I'll use my wheelchair.
What's wrong?
It's about time I
finally get to eat.
I wonder if Fujiki put it there?
You shouldn't be so suspicious.
There are other people
who know where my room is...
And I seem to have the
attention of a few here as well...
I think the vice president wanted
the insurance money so...
There has to be a reason why
the police believe it's a suicide.
I know a magazine reporter who's
got an inside source with the police.
I want you to deliver a message.
Here's how to reach him.
Benzo Kawasaki, huh?
Ok then.
Oh, and lend me your cell.
I left mine at the office.
Here you go.
So Miss Assistant!
Let's get moving!!
What!? You're making me pay!?
Talk about a VIP hospital room!
"The victim, Sakuji Nonomura...
...was found dead face-down on
the bed the day of the incident."
"The president sometimes utilized
this room for personal reasons."
"Status of the body when found:"
"The body was wearing a
gown and an undergarment."
"A used needle and
an ampul were found."
"The content of the ampul was cyanide."
"The estimated time of death was
between midnight and 06:00 AM."
"At 10:00 AM, Madame Akiko, the
first witness, became suspicious..."
"...when her husband didn't answer
the phone, and entered the room."
"At the time the body was found..."
"...Madame Akiko was accompanied by Fujiki,
the head nurse, and a security guard."
"During the estimated time of death,
her maid and personal driver..."
"...said Madame Akiko
was at the house in Kamakura."
"Outside entry is impossible."
"All fingerprints left in the room..."
"...Including the ampul and
needle, belonged to the victim."
"The official police
announcement declared it a suicide."
"It was supposedly
stemming from..."
"...the hospital's financial problems..."
"...and his country club's bankruptcy
when the economy began to decline."
FAILING HOSPITAL MANAGEMENT
NONOMURA HOSPITAL PRESIDENT COMMITS SUICIDE
COUNTRY CLUB DECLARES CHAPTER 11
It feels so good.
Your body feels great.
It's fantastic.
Look! My dick is so hard.
What is this!?
Who's doing this!?
Your beauty mark in your
pussy makes me so horny.
I love it when you cry like that.
You drive me wild when
you cry like that.
Hello... Hello!
Who are you!?
To Be Continued...
There's a murder case involving...
...the women at Nonomura Hospital.
There aren't very many suspects.
No one has a motive for the murder.
Embarrassing places are
searched and stretched around...
...right before my eyes.
Nice isn't it?
And then there's Ryoko,
caught up in the madness.
Fear not!
I'll solve the riddle that
gramps left behind!
But... just who is my grandpa?
Knock it off, you idiot!
Next time: The Mystery
of Nonomura Hospital
Hope you enjoy!