Cut!
OK!
- Well done, everyone!
- Well done!
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- Well done!
Sex Beast
Idol of Darkness
lkumi, do you often cook at home?
Yes. But because I live alone,
I eat out a lot too.
But on your days off, there must be
a certain someone to cook for you?
That would be nice! But I'm so busy
with work at the moment.
I'm picking you up at 6:30am tomorrow,
so don't sleep in!
I won't, Tanaka.
And make sure you're not late!
Good night.
Good night. Take care!
Graduation Day
lkumi.
- What the hell?
- Looks like the roof collapsed!
This shrine gives me the creeps.
Mm, let's get it over with quickly.
Right, ready for action!
Scene 36. Take 2. Action!
Good morning!
Sorry we're late.
I've kept you waiting.
Rie, this isn't good enough,
we've already started.
I'm so sorry.
But surely it's not time for me yet?
It's the supporting actress, isn't it?
Supporting actress?
She's the supporting actress more like!
She's a has-been. What a nerve!
Well then, shall we make a start?
- Don't pay any attention to her.
- I won't.
Right, get ready...action!
Ready for action! Scene 36. Take 2. Start!
No one's going to upstage me.
If it wasn't for that girl...
Cut!
OK!
- Rie, erm...where are you going?
- Leave me alone!
Are you the one
that woke me with your cry?
I will grant you your wish.
- Do you know what this is?
- Hm?
Well, well.
Drink, please.
Of course.
I'm so tired.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Everyone's been waiting!
Going out to ten million fans nationwide,
lkumi Murase's Spring Concert!
Make sure you come! Promise!
5th March...
- Give me a massage.
- OK.
How's next week's schedule?
What's the matter?
Well...
You don't have any appointments.
Isn't it the manager's job
to find me work?!
I'm sorry.
That bitch!
Gets a little popular and look,
so full of herself!
She can't act, she's a terrible singer,
and she's not nearly as pretty as me!
The lead actress should really be me!
She's the one they want now.
If only I could summon up the sex beast.
You are my faithful servant.
- Do you listen to everything I say?
-Yes.
There! Yes, there!
More, more!
That's so good!
I'm coming!
That girl's not been herself lately.
Well, boss, the truth is...
She's at a critical stage.
A scandal could ruin her.
- Will you have a word?
- Yes, boss.
Graduation Ceremony
Akira!
Can I have a moment?
I want you to
stop seeing lkumi for a while.
Why?!
She's at a very critical stage.
She's young and inexperienced.
From now on, she'll be working on
many projects and she must succeed.
Until then, love and romance
are out of the question.
You two had a bad argument
the other day, didn't you?
It's because she's so busy
you can't see each other, isn't it?
At the moment,
she's worrying about you.
She's in no fit state to work properly,
and that's a problem.
It'll soon be time
for her debut concert tour.
She must be a success,
for the sake of her future.
Just think about her.
I want you to disappear
from lkumi's life, now.
Akira!
lkumi.
No matter how long you wait,
Akira won't come.
What?!
lkumi, listen to me carefully.
You're at a critical stage. Love and...
I know that!
But...
Akira understands.
He'll disappear from your life,
he's promised.
Shit!
Oi, come here!
- You won't put up a fight, huh?
- Not a bit.
This is an lkumi song.
I hate this girl!
Pretending to be so innocent!
I find her so cute -
her and her big breasts.
Oh, my darling lkumi! Suck my dick!
She looked great in that bikini
in a recent magazine.
Yeah, she has that real innocent look
but with seductive eyes.
I'm dying to fuck her!
Wait!
You fucker!
What is this?
Hello!
Hello, this is Akira Kobayashi.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Don't scare me!
You go first.
Rie!
There it is!
(Voodoo chant)
Just as I was told!
Yabe, let's begin.
(Voodoo chant)
Boss!
lkumi has....
Ikumi has disappeared!
What did you say?!
(Voodoo chant)
lkumi Murase
Spring Concert
(Voodoo chant)
Yes, I've tried her friend's apartment.
I'll definitely find her.
Finally, the time has come
to wake the sex beast.
It's so good!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Sorry to keep you.
Thank you.
- Akira...
- I...
I...have been thinking about
what Mr Tanaka told me,
thinking about us.
Even when you become a star,
you are you.
And I am me. That's how it is.
As you get more and more popular,
you're going to slip away from me.
That's how I felt.
But even if you become famous,
you'll still be lkumi.
The lkumi the star on the TV
and the lkumi with me now.
I know that both lkumis
are precious to me.
Ikumi, you told me once
''I've got a dream where I'm a singer,
performing in front of loads of fans.''
So...sing for me.
I love lkumi the singer too.
Akira!
lkumi.
Your fans are waiting.
Ikumi!
I'll be watching the TV, cheering for you.
Sing one for me, lkumi the star.
Give it your best!
Give it your best, lkumi.
He told me where you were.
- He's a good guy.
- I know.
Let's go!
Good evening, everyone!
I'm so happy that so many of you
have come here to see me tonight!
Encore! Encore!
Encore! Encore! Encore!
lkumi!
Thank you for tonight, everybody!
You all made it a great concert!
I've really enjoyed it!
There's something I want to tell you.
There is at the moment...
there's someone I really like.
That girl!
Boss, let her be.
But...
She is doing fine.
Get lkumi!
This boy that I like,
he's in my year at high school.
I met this boy
when we started high school.
And I've liked him ever since.
He hurt himself saving me
during summer camp.
We went to the school festival
in fancy dress together.
We ran the three-legged race together
on sports day.
He's always by my side,
he looks after me.
He's no movie star
and he's a bit of a dope.
But to me, he's the most
important person in the world.
I'm so busy working,
I can't see him as often as I'd like.
So sometimes we argue.
But...after that last time that I saw him
I've decided not to worry about
these stupid things.
I've decided to trust him.
Whatever happens,
I'll be right beside him.
And...
Well, I don't know what I'm saying.
I've been too shy
to say anything until now.
I...
I'm in love with Akira.
- Go for it!
- Good luck!
Thank you.
I am blessed to have so many fans
out there who support me.
I'm so happy!
I - KU - MI! Go for it!
Thank you, everyone!
I will sing a song for all my fans
who have supported me
and for my boyfriend
who is watching at home.
In the hazy sunshine in my bedroom
I can almost see your smiling face
That white T-shirt you always wear
It's shining so bright
Are you sad?
That summer's day when we first met
And now
In my heart
I'll hold you again
And kiss you with passion
Don't you forget about me
I want you to feel my heart beat
I want to send my heart
Carried on the wind, softly
To you
lkumi!
There they are.
Am I out of gas?
Shit!
lkumi!
lkumi.
Ikumi!
Give her back to me.
Akira!
You died for me.
lkumi.
Where did you get that strength from?
I don't even know myself.
When I think about you,
I'm filled with a strange power.
Oh, Akira!
It's so...
Oh...there!
I'll be gentle.
Slowly.
It feels good, lkumi.
Me too.
Ikumi.
Akira!
I'm coming!
In the hazy sunshine in my bedroom
I can almost see your smiling face
That white T-shirt you always wear
It's shining so bright
Are you sad?
That summer's day when we first met
And now
In my heart
I'll hold you again
And kiss you with passion
Don't you forget about me
I want you to feel my heart beat
I want to send my heart
Carried on the wind, softly
To you
I'll hold you again
And kiss you with passion
Don't you forget about me
I want you to feel my heart beat
I want to send my heart
Carried on the wind, softly
To you
The end