It is a turbulent age of war...
I have infiltrated
the Takigawa territory...
...in order to steal our
enemy's hidden treasure.
There is a reason why someone like
myself, completely unskilled in the...
...martial arts has been chosen
to take on such a daunting task.
I happen to have one asset, one
area in which I have no parallel.
That area is...
Seduction!
I have risked my life to bring two female
ninjas from the enemy's side to climax.
In this way I obtained two fragments
of the map of the hidden treasure.
There is another reason why
I entered enemy territory.
I am on a mission to find
my adopted sister Sayo...
...who was kidnapped ten years ago.
At the time, I never imagined
that Sayo was in the custody of...
...none other than Muhousai Tenni...
...the man responsible for
the magic of the tattoo maps...
I still have no clue as
to Sayo's whereabouts.
I have to do something, that I do.
W-What the hell is going on?
How lovely!
And what a sweet and wonderful smell!
I feel really good...
Since you defeated both
Kochou and Shirohebi...
...I was expecting
a formidable opponent.
You've dashed my hopes!
Oh my, yet another babe!
I guess your eyesight hasn't been
impaired by the spell I cast on you!
Hm? Rain?
It felt so good, I couldn't help myself...
Y-You've got a lot of nerve!
Such a masculine aroma!
Let me water the flowers...
I can feel the spell fading...
It's not fair, you've been enjoying
yourself without me for too long.
What a huge one!
I've never had anyone this big!
It's that lovely aroma again!
My job is to control the scent of flowers,
but I can't resist this smell at all!
I can't take it anymore...
Hurry, take this and
rub it all over my body!
Your wish is my command!
Something's blocking the entrance.
Just take it out and throw it away!
Dumplings rather than
flowers, as they say...
It's such a shame, though, you've
arranged them so nicely, that you have.
I got it!
Since that space is occupied,
why don't I just go in from here...
Oh no!
You're too big!
Kochou did a fine job of
bearing the strain, that she did.
You don't want to be less
of a ninja than her, do you?
O-Of course not, how dare you
compare me to someone like Kochou!
The hell with it! Do as you wish!
All right, then please excuse me!
Does that hurt?
Not at all!
You're doing great, it feels amazing!
I think you might be even
better equipped than Kochou!
Do you mean that?
Unbelievable!
How can your anus be so wet?
That feels so good!
My body is bursting with a huge dick!
Oh yes!
Collecting the pieces of the map has
been an unexpectedly easy job so far...
...but Sayo, where the hell can you be?
I guess there's no
use thinking about it.
It's been a while since
I slept on a futon.
I'll get some rest tonight,
and resume my quest tomorrow!
Who's there?
Sayo?
It was a dream...
It was nothing but a dream...
I know I'm going to find Sayo,
I'll find her no matter what!
Sayo?
Sayo!
L-I'm sorry, I thought
you were someone else...
What's going on here?
You can't move about freely
in your dreams, can you?
What?
You wretched man!
I'll see to it that you get a
big dose of pain before you die.
You filthy worthless creature!
I can't move...
I can't even do anything
to defend myself!
Damn, if only this wasn't a dream...
...I could at least fight
my way out of these ropes!
Suffer!
I have to wake up...
Wait a minute!
There's a way, it just might work.
It'll be a little embarrassing...
What's this horrible smell?
No, it can't be...
I did it!
I wet my bed for the first
time in years, that I did!
And it was so uncomfortable I woke up!
Phew!
That's strange...
She's got to be around here somewhere
to cast spells in her victims' dreams...
Who are you?
L-I never thought you'd use such a
tactic to wake from your dream.
I know! I thought it was pretty
inspired myself.
You are not at all like
the one in my dream!
Ever since I was a child, I've been
bullied by men who called me gloomy...
That's why I've hated men all my life.
And that's what motivated me to get
through Lord Muhousai's rigorous training.
I swore to myself that with these
powers, I'd get my revenge someday...
I'd make men suffer at my hands...
So that's why you transformed yourself...
...into such a powerful woman
in my dreams and beat me!
I feel sorry for you.
You've never met a man who
would be kind to you, have you?
What?
I have defeated you in battle.
Normally, you would have no
choice but to die by my sword.
However, I'm not going to kill you...
One night is all I'm asking, I want
you to give me your body.
I swear that I will
not harm you in any way.
It feels so good!
How could any man be so cruel to a
woman with such superior equipment?
Just like a sweet syrup...
No!
There's no reason to be embarrassed.
Your body is seeking
pleasure, and that's normal.
Look, me too!
W-What is this?
You and I are having intercourse, and
so we can fulfill each other's desires.
By feeling compassion
for one another.
Compassion?
That's right, I want to bring you
pleasure and make you happy, that I do.
That feels so good!
I don't know what's
going to happen to me!
Surely one finger is not enough, is it?
I'm being sucked right in, it's like
you're begging me for more and more!
How embarrassing!
Wow, my fingers are all the way in!
Ow!
Should I stop?
No!
It hurts, but it feels good!
Don't stop what you're
doing, do it harder!
As you wish!
I cannot bring myself to beat a woman
with a whip, but I can at least do this...
A-Are you all right?
So lovely.
You are a very beautiful woman!
It's so strange.
You've been bullied all your life, yet
all you want is to be hurt or tortured.
My body just got
conditioned to all that...
...but this is the first time I've
ever experienced such tender bullying!
I've now collected four pieces
of the map, only one more to go.
But surely it's too much to hope
that my luck will last any longer...
More importantly...
Will I be able to find Sayo?
Saotome's spy, this is the end.
So you made it, huh?
You did not defeat four
of my disciples for nothing!
Which makes you Muhousai Tenni.
The one and only!
Sayo?
Do you two know each other?
Sayo, it's me, Matagoro!
Have you forgotten your brother?
It's true that I once
had a brother, long ago...
But my brother didn't come to save
me when I was being carried of f.
Despite his promise that he would
protect me as long as he lives!
Sayo...
It's not the tearful reunion
you thought it would be, eh?
Sayo, show this man who's the best
swordsman of all the Takigawas.
It will be a parting gift
to him before he dies!
Sayo...
What's the matter, Sayo?
I can't do it...
You're getting emotional, eh?
You still need a lot of
training ahead of you!
It doesn't matter now.
Get out of the way!
I already know that your
mission is to find the map.
And how you managed
to defeat my disciples.
But your weapon of choice
won't have any effect on me!
Die!
Lord Muhousai, I'm asking
you in the name of heaven.
Please spare this man's life!
What?
It would do nothing for our clan to
take the life of such a lowly man.
All we have to do is
take the map from him and...
...send him off into the wilderness.
Are you defying me?
Have you forgotten that it was I who
brought you up for the last 10 years?
No, I haven't forgotten that debt!
Still, that man is my only
brother, he's important to me!
Shut up!
I'm going to kill him now!
You feel that strongly about this man.
Thank God...
So naÏÏve of you, Sayo!
You might have surpassed me in
swordsmanship, but don't forget that...
...I have the wisdom that comes with
having lived for more than 100 years!
You know what to expect what
happens to those who betray me...
Die!
My brother!
Brother, are you all right?
It's just a scrape, that it is.
We'll have to take
care of that right away!
Sayo...
Thank you, for still being alive...
Brother...
Let's go home together,
Father is waiting for you, too.
You haven't changed,
even after ten years.
You did come to save me after all!
I see you're still a crybaby!
Brother!
Still, I feel a little
bitter, that I do...
What?
Well, I know I should be
happy because I found you, but...
...I only had one more person to go!
Just one more piece of the map, and
I could've found the secret treasure!
Brother, you can rest assured, you can
obtain that piece any time you want!
Hey, don't make it sound so simple.
I've just been lucky
until now, that I have.
Next time I go into enemy territory, there's
no guarantee that I'll come back alive.
There's no need for you to go
into Takigawa territory anymore.
The last person you're
looking for is right here!
Huh?
I have been waiting
for this day for years...
Sayo...
I love you!
I love you, too!
That tickles...
Oh, not there...
Don't worry, I will not cause
you any pain or suffering!
All right!
Sayo, you won't believe
what's going on down here!
No, how embarrassing!
Don't hold back, it's all
right if you raise your voice.
There's no one here but us!
My whole body's starting to
tingle, it feels kind of strange!
Y-You're doing great!
So this is your...
Starting from today, it's yours,
Sayo, do as you will with it!
You're doing a good
job, it feels so good!
Do you think it's time?
What?
For us to become one,
that's what I meant.
That feels so good!
My body's going to melt away...
I'm burning!
It's like I'm burning up inside!
You're the best woman I've ever had!
Your huge thing is banging
me all the way inside!
Inside my body...
It feels so good!
I'm tingling all over!
Sayo, I'm going to come pretty soon...
Then come, come inside me, all of it!
I'm sorry to make you do that...
Brother, you are wounded.
Anyway, I'm probably better at this
since I've been trained as a ninja!
That's true...
But you have to stop
calling me "Brother."
You are now the wife of Matagoro.
Yes, Matagoro!
All right, I'm going to open the door...
What the hell's going on?
I don't know...
What the hell?
What is going on?
Are these women the
hidden Takigawa treasure?
It's possible that they might be
what they call "Living Rewards"...
...which were given to valiant soldiers.
My master, please come
over here and caress me!
Master!
W-Who wants a treasure like this?
As long as I have you, I
don't need anything else!
Do you really mean that?
You never know,
someday you too might...
That will never happen,
I'm sure it won't happen!
Um, maybe...
Master!
Wait for us!