It is a turbulent age of war...
A man has nothing to rely
on but his own skills.
And only by using those skills to
the utmost can he hope to survive!
That's amazing...
I can't believe how delicious this is!
There's no need to hurry,
I'm not going anywhere.
But you're so popular...
I have no way of knowing
when you'll come see me next.
Well, since the war's been going on...
...I have more and more widows
like you to tend to, that I do.
It really can't be helped.
That's amazing!
L-I can't take it anymore!
That's a lot for you to shoot out.
But I don't want this
to be over already!
Never fear.
Haven't heard the rumors about me?
"Matagoro the Stallion"...
...and "Matagoro the
Bottomless Reservoir"!
L-It's huge!
You're going to smash me to pieces!
Not to worry.
This thing of mine is
nothing compared to a newborn!
My husband was killed before I
had the chance to get pregnant...
...so I don't know about that.
I am so sorry, that I am.
I shouldn't have said that.
It's all right...
If my husband were still alive, I
wouldn't be having such a good time now!
So please, I want you
to thrust even harder!
Just pound me to smithereens,
and make me forget everything!
T-That's amazing!
I'm in heaven!
Not yet...
I don't know what's happening to me!
Not yet!
I feel like I'm burning up inside!
I feel amazing too!
It's like a stallion's,
it's so big and hard!
And it's all the way
inside me, hitting my spot!
You are wonderful.
You are such a beautiful
woman.
That makes me happy!
That feels great!
I want more!
I want more! More!
Whatever you wish!
That feels so good!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming...
I'm going to come!
Can't take it anymore,
Then let us come together!
Please, come!
Who the hell are you?
Filthy wretch, don't come near me!
Please, I need to see
Lord Akiyama right away...
According to my spy,
there's treasure in Takigawa...
...buried for generations...
If that's the hidden goldmine
we've heard so much about...
...it might bring an end
to our long-standing war.
But how much truth is
there to this information?
With your spy now dead, we have
no way of verifying his story...
He said that the tattoos of...
...certain female ninjas would
form the map of the treasure.
It's too preposterous for words!
Not only that, but he also said that
the only time these tattoos were...
...even visible was
when the women climaxed!
Are we supposed to believe
such a ridiculous story?
Wait!
I've heard that it was a trick
devised by Muhousai Tenni...
Sir!
If a monster like Muhousai
is behind all this...
...we can't very well
dismiss it as a fabrication...
My lord, Muhousai died 150 years ago.
I would caution you against
sending forth troops based on...
...unreliable intelligence, especially
at such a time of financial strife.
I see...
Sir, if I may...
What is it?
Lord Akiyama, I have an idea.
I ask that you leave this matter to me.
Stop!
Come back here!
Hey, I said come back!
All right. Leave Sayo alone.
I'll take you all on!
You think you can beat us
crouched over like that?
Who do you think you are, anyway?
Bring it on!
You asked for it!
Big Brother, help me!
Help!
Father...
What do you want from me at this late
hour?
There's a job that no
one else but you can do!
All my life you've said I was a
failure both as a scholar and a warrior...
There's no job in the world that
your bumbling son could accomplish!
Actually, there is!
We Yoshimuras have long
been regarded as outcasts...
...but this is the chance of a lifetime!
If we do this right, it might even give
us the opportunity to bring in a bride.
Huh?
Tomorrow morning at first light,
you must head for Takigawa!
That's ridiculous!
I'll be killed with one stroke
by the first enemy I run into.
And besides, why does it have to be me?
Well, son...
Father, are you serious?
Well, I suppose I am the ideal
man for the job.
Even so...
Listen, Matagoro.
I'm pretty sure that
Sayo is in Takigawa...
Sayo!
While you're fulfilling
your mission there...
...you might be able to
find out something about her.
It's been ten years since
those enemy spies kidnapped her.
If you're going to look for her, this
might be your last chance to do it...
Sayo is my younger sister.
But since she was adopted from distant
relatives, we're not related by blood.
Even so, we had a relationship far
stronger than that of brother and sister.
Nobody doubted that someday...
...she and I would marry and take
over as head of the Yoshimura clan.
Big Brother, help me!
Sayo, I'm coming right now!
Big Brother!
You're safe now!
Big Brother?
What?
Big Brother, will you always
be there when I'm in danger?
Of course, I'm going to protect you
for the rest of my life, that I am.
I promise!
Of course, that's assuming
Sayo is still alive, of course...
Sayo is still alive.
I know she's still alive!
Matagoro...
I can't make any
promises about my mission...
...but I'm going to find
Sayo no matter what it takes!
And with those words, I shared
a farewell drink with my father.
I should have crossed the border by now.
According to our spy, there
should be a female ninja...
...around here somewhere on guard...
Okay, where did she go?
Hmm, what a piece of...
Uh, I wasn't peeping.
Oh yes you were!
You don't look like a
member of the Takigawa clan.
But why are you cutting through the
woods instead of taking the pass?
Oh, I just lost my way, that I did.
You have no reason to suspect me!
Here, I'll prove it...
See?
I don't understand...
You're far too much
of a wimp to be a spy!
L-I told you already! I'm not a spy!
Then who are you?
Where did you come from?
Um, before I tell you, is there any way
you could put down that horrible sword?
L-I'm trembling, I couldn't
talk if I wanted to!
Enough, lame-ass!
I usually just get rid of
suspicious characters like you.
Die!
Such magnificent breasts!
You fool!
So you're burning with desire
even as you're about to die!
Oh my, how embarrassing!
I should've made sure I
tightened my loincloth!
But is it supposed to get like this?
W-What is this?
P-Please, forgive me!
Got her! Now I'm in control!
On second thought, it would be too pitiful
for you to end your life so abruptly.
As a parting gift, let me indulge you!
I can't believe there's still so much
left when you're all the way inside!
That feels so good!
I knew you weren't just anyone!
Yes!
Oh really, it's nothing special...
M-My God!
I have endured the
most Spartan training...
...and here I am, wrestled to
the ground by a man like this...
As long as it makes you feel good,
there are no winners or losers!
It's hot!
I feel as though I'm going to
burst into flames any second!
This fire is going to melt me away!
Amazing...
Unbelievable!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to come!
I'm going to come now...
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, I could die...
No, you can't die
yet. See? Look at this.
See how much energy I still have!
H-How can that be?
If you've worn yourself out down
there, why don't we use your other hole?
M-My other hole?
Your penis is way too big!
Too bad, because I'm going
to do it anyway, that I am!
Ow that hurt!
Didn't you say that you'd
gone through Spartan training?
I'm sure this is nothing compared
to that! You really shouldn't whine.
B-But!
That training really did you a lot of
good, you're amazingly tight, that you are!
See, it doesn't hurt anymore, does it?
It still hurts!
My body's going to rip apart!
I guess that's enough for today...
This is what I was looking for!
I managed to get one of them...
That was just luck...
I got this piece of the
map by accident, but...
...how am I going to get my hands on the
rest when I'm no good at martial arts?
The most important
thing is Sayo, though...
She must be all grown up by now.
Just thinking about
it makes my nose bleed!
Calm down, calm down!
Life isn't that easy, after all!
I'm going to sleep.
I have some long days
ahead of me, that I do.
Someone's there...
What a fool to invade my home!
I said I was finished...
Come on, let me get some
sleep, for god's sake!
Another female ninja!
Not to mention another babe!
Who the hell are you?
I was suffocating.
I thought I was going to die!
I'll ask you one more time.
Who the hell are you?
L-I'm just a traveler, that I am.
I'm spending the night here, that's all...
I'm not going to let you
make free with my home!
Oh, I understand!
I'm very, very sorry, I'll be on my way.
So if you'll forgive me...
You wish!
I wish? You mean you'll let me stay?
I've never before allowed anyone under
my spell to leave this place alive!
Oh, so you mean...
...I'll have to kill you!
Suffer!
Suffer, and bid
this world farewell!
Your mangled flesh and bones
will be all that's left of you.
I'll feed you to my darling children!
C-Can't take it anymore...
Wait, I can't just give up!
Didn't I promise to find Sayo and return
home with her, or was that just a lie?
Somehow I've got to find a way
to escape from this monster...
There just has to be a way!
Wait a second...
I've got it!
Snakes are the same as humans,
they must have erogenous zones too!
L-Is this the end?
So she and the snake are one?
I see, that's all I need to know!
That feels amazing!
What delicious juice you're secreting!
Not only that, but
this smell is so divine!
Y-You're full of it!
That's what you say,
but you're turning red!
You like it, don't you?
I'm so embarrassed!
Yes!
I can see you're a lot
more naÏÏve than you look!
Look at me.
See? Your juice is all over my mouth.
What a filthy body!
Put me into your mouth...
I can't do that...
Oh, then you want me to stop right now?
No! No!
You can't stop!
Well, make up your mind!
L-I want this...
What do you mean by "this"?
I mean this!
You'll have to say the word!
I don't want to!
No, I actually I do!
What are you talking about?
I want this, put it in me now!
As you wish!
This slimy texture...
How reptilian!
A burning snake is
slithering throughout my body...
So amazing!
I can feel it...
It's so huge, I can feel it inside me.
Go ahead and do whatever
you want to yourself.
Don't stop, just turn around...
I'm about to come...
Oh, please come!
Please, I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to explode!
That makes two...
Another one...
Another one of my disciples
has fallen, I hear.
Whose doing is this?
Someone has been
disturbing the peace here.
It must be one of Saotome's spies.
Since I've lost two of my
disciples, I cannot let this go...
Hanakage!
Sir!
Mugen!
Find this man and kill him!
Yes, sir!
You've improved immensely.
All that rigorous training I put
you through has come to fruition!
You have made Sayo very happy with
your words of praise, Lord Muhousai...
How many more pieces do I
need to get the whole map?
More importantly, Sayo...
I have to find her as soon
as possible, that I do!
Who will next try to thwart
him as he continues on his way?