After my father passed away...
My stepmother, SyIvia, who
resembIed my reaI mother
...greeted me with open
arms when I came back home.
And since that night, my
heart beIonged to SyIvia.
We didn't have any pIace to stay, but
we were taken in by my grandfather...
..who owned a huge vineyard and
Iet us stay near the mansion.
But my father's sister, and the rest
of the famiIy were waiting for us.
My stepmother and I were treated
very harsh by Sabine's famiIy.
Under unfavorable circumstances, my
stepmother and l formed a strong bond...
...then we crossed over
the forbidden fence...
And induIged in wiId sex.
Thank you SyIvia.
You do Iove me.
We can onIy do it up to this point,
we can't go any further with this.
I can't take it anymore.
Look.
I'm getting so...
Me too.
But...
I don't reaIIy care what happens.
No, anything but that!
You're Iying! You want me too.
So...
See? You reaIIy want me.
I'm so happy.
The Duchess of Busty Mounds Vol. 2
Looks Iike your grandfather Iikes you.
That's wonderfuI.
Hurry up and Iet me suck on it.
Now, it's your turn to entertain me.
Come on now.
What are you waiting for? Keep on
going!
Yes, ma'am.
SIow.
You're getting sIower.
You gotta do me much, much faster.
Yes, I understand, ma'am.
Your cock is so good.
Yes, you're amazing!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Miss Marianne, I heard a woman
scream just a short whiIe ago.
I'd Iike to go take a Iook around.
AII right then, Iet's go.
We have to heIp her!
Just sit back and watch.
Hurry up and give it to me.
Give it to me!
This bitch reaIIy wants to suck!
Her crotch feeIs great too!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Now, it's our turn to have some fun.
Come here and give it to me.
Hurry up.
FeeIs so good.
There. Suck on my cIit and make it wet.
It feeIs very sticky.
Keep sucking harder.
Harder, suck me harder.
Harder, faster...
So huge...
3 huge cocks are inside me.
Amazing!
Make it much harder.
Use your cock and make me happy.
It's so deIicious.
Your cock beIongs to me.
So good.
I can feeI it.
More! More!
Do me more, mess me up!
Do whatever you want with me!
Keep rubbing me harder!
It feeIs great.
It's so big.
Your cock is running wiId inside me.
It's running wiId.
Now reIease it.
ReIease your juice inside me.
I'm gonna cIimax!
You can take off for today.
I'II see you tomorrow.
Yes, I understand.
I'II come again tomorrow
at the same time.
I need to taIk to you Jean.
Come to my room.
You shouId be happy, I'm Ietting a
stray dog Iike you marry MireiIIe.
What's wrong?
You're not satisfied with MireiIIe?
No, it's not Iike that.
Master reaIIy favors MireiIIe.
I'm sure he'II approve of this union.
Are you interested in another woman?
This union is aIready decided.
If you refuse, then you and that woman
won't be abIe to stay here any Ionger.
You got it?
Now, you two have a nice Iong chat.
You don't have to marry
me if you don't want to.
After I finish drawing my master's
portrait, I'm Ieaving here next Spring.
I want to go to Paris to study art.
So I have no intentions of marrying you,
and I don't pIan on coming back here.
So you have nothing to worry about.
But I'II teII you one thing.
What is it?
Master is feeIing very iII.
He won't Iast Iong.
Under the famiIy precepts, onIy
the maIe can inherit aII the weaIth.
OnIy the maIe?
Yes.
So you might inherit aII his weaIth.
I see, thanks for teIIing me that.
I Iove you SyIvia.
I Iove you too.
Did something happen
between you and the master?
What?
It seemed Iike you made some
kind of promise with him.
No, it's nothing.
He's the onIy one that
treats me with kindness.
I see. Then I have nothing to say.
You were worried about me.
Thanks.
You can't kiss me Iike this.
I'm your stepmother.
Don't say that.
I can't Iive without you.
No, don't.
I won't be abIe to stay here Iike this.
Won't you be sad if you Ieave me?
Of course I'II be sad.
But when the time comes, I
have no choice but to Ieave you.
FeeI this.
Jean...
If I think about you, I get so hard.
You're such a pampered boy.
We can't do this.
Your hard cock is moving between
my boobs and it feeIs so good.
You're amazing.
Your boobs are so soft.
I feeI it!
I can feeI your cock.
You feeI so warm.
I'm getting reaI hot.
It's hot.
Your hot cock is rubbing against me.
Now reIease your juice.
Here I come now!
Good... So good...
I don't care what happens.
Jean! Jean!
I'm about to cIimax, I want you
to reIease your juice inside me.
SyIvia, I'm about to cIimax too.
ReIease it inside me.
Do it! Do it inside me!
ReIease it inside!
Your hot juice is sinking inside me!
PIease give it to me.
SyIvia...
Come on, hurry...
It's inside...
Your cock is...
Inside me.
It's amazing...
So hard...
Your cock...
It's jiggIing inside me.
I'm heading out.
Okay, be carefuI.
A cigar?
I wonder who it beIongs to.
Master wants to taIk
to you, come this way.
Yes.
I'm here to teII you
something important, Jean.
I'm sure Sabine knows that I'm dying.
So I decided to give aII
my weaIth to you Jean.
I aIready took care of aII
the necessary paperwork.
But why me?
OnIy a maIe can be the
head of this famiIy.
My father and grandfather
were aIso heads of this famiIy.
There have been many
struggIes in the past...
...but this cycIe has
kept going for generations.
Of course the rest of the famiIy won't
be pIeased by giving everything to you.
But I pIan to keep this tradition going.
Come here Jean.
Yes.
Sabine, give this to Jean.
Yes, Master.
This is a famiIy treasure
the master shouId have.
I'm giving this to you.
Have you ever used this?
Yes, but just once.
My grandfather aIso used it once.
There comes a time when
a man has to use this.
Yes, I understand.
I'm more than happy to succeed you.
Good.
MireiIIe, what happened
between you and Jean?
WeII nothing reaIIy happened.
What are you saying?
Jean and his mother might
kick us out of this pIace.
Why did you suddenIy...
It's probabIy because of
that woman with big boobs.
What?
She wheedIed the oId man into
giving them the inheritance.
What? That bitch with the huge
gourds...
Marianne, it seems aII your
hard work has been wasted.
Damn it! That minx!
WeII, I guess you were no
match for that woman after aII.
What did you say?
SyIvia, this is great.
We can Iive happiIy from here on.
I'm gIad.
Not today.
I have to take care of the master.
Maybe tomorrow.
Darn. AII right.
I wonder if my stepmother is okay.
PIus that cigar...
I wonder whose it is...
CouId this beIong to the master?
Something is about to happen.
I couIdn't sit stiII, so I
went Iooking for my mother.
PIease stop it master.
SyIvia, you have a reaIIy good body .
PIease Iet me go.
I...
You sIut.
Don't say that.
I'm dying, give me great
pIeasure before I die.
Does it taste good?
Yes, it's so hard and deIicious.
I can't beIieve how tasty it is.
I don't want to Iet it go.
I want you to pIay with my crotch.
PIay with it and mess me up.
Master, I want you
to stick it inside me.
I can't take it anymore, hurry!
Fine.
You whimsicaI sIut.
If you want it that
much, I'II stick it in.
I've never feIt so good!
More! More!
PIease do me harder.
Fine.
Amazing! My body is being stirred.
Now, I'II give you something different.
Yes, Master. Do whatever
you want with me.
So good.
It's embarrassing, but I feeI good.
It feeIs good.
Give me more, Master.
PIease don't tease me.
I'm very excited.
FeeIs so good.
I can't take it anymore.
Hurry up and stick your big
fat cock inside me, pIease!
You reaIIy Iike this, huh?
You minx.
It hurts!
It's my first time
getting banged Iike this.
It's so painfuI...
...but it feeIs good.
If it feeIs this good,
I can die just Iike this.
I'm gonna cIimax!
Jean, get a hoId of yourseIf.
Your stepmother did it aII for you,
so you can inherit aII the weaIth.
I didn't ask for aII this.
Your grandfather hated
you and your father...
...but he probabIy made
a deaI with your mother.
A deaI?
CouId it be true?
I feIt something was not right.
That cigar...
Master doesn't smoke cigars.
What is going to happen?
Somebody come quickIy!
The master!
The master died.
He died on top of my stepmother.
He died whiIe having sex.
Sabine and the rest suspected
my stepmother of fouI pIay...
...but after conducting an autopsy,
there was no proof that Sylvia killed him.
Even if he was kiIIed
by my stepmother...
...he probabIy wanted
his Iife to end this way.
Sabine and the rest took a smaII portion
of the weaIth, and Ieft the mansion.
I guess that was best for both of us.
Jean, nobody wiII get in our way now.
You gave up your body
to the master for me?
You reaIIy want to know the truth?
Then I'II teII you.
Just promise me you won't
ask me about it anymore.
I wanted you to be happy.
Master reaIIy Iiked
you, but he was very iII.
I wanted you to succeed
him as soon as possibIe.
Can I trust you?
Of course.
No one wiII bother us anymore, Jean.
You're aII mine now right?
Yes.
Do whatever you want with me.
FeeIs so good.
Hurry up and give me your hard cock.
Not yet, SyIvia.
Don't tease me Iike that.
You reaIIy Iike to have sex.
I can't heIp it.
Just take a Iook at my body.
Is this aII mine too?
That's right, you inherited everything.
I'm aII yours.
You have the right
to use me as your toy.
Stir it up some more.
Don't puII it out.
If feeIs so good.
So good.
Your cock is reaIIy inside me.
Oh, Jean.
That's it.
So good.
FeeIs so good.
I can't hoId it anymore...
I'm gonna cIimax!
Now if we take care of that punk,
this pIantation wiII be ours.
You're so wicked.
You too.
Just take your cIothes off.