Even just remembering what
happened makes my heart ache.
What do you mean?
It's best for both us.
I think we've tried enough.
That's not fair! You're always
deciding everything on your own.
You're terrible...
Nimura, you idiot!
He said it was best for
both of us, and left me...
It's spring outside.
Although I've been constantly
haunted by that dream...
...a new season will be a
new beginning for me...
...and I'll meet new people.
Starting today, I'm going to be a nurse.
NAUGHTY NURSES PART 1
AOSHIMA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Your blowjobs are always so good.
Oh stop. You're the one who coached me.
Plus, it's not just my mouth that's good.
Good... Good... This is why I can't leave!
Because there are fantastic nurses
like you that keep me going.
If you're this energetic, you
should go back to work.
How am I supposed to look forward...
...to congressional sessions
with a room full of old men?
I wish the voters could hear you now.
That's politics for you.
I can't believe I get to do this with nurses.
You're so wet.
Because it feels good.
Then how about this?
I can't take that many fingers at once...
But you're not letting my fingers go.
Oh stop!
It feels so good...
More... More...
Here I come!
I can feel you all the way inside! Yes!
Me too!
Yes! This position feels so much better.
No... It feels so good... I
think I'm going to go crazy!
I can't... I can't hold it anymore...
Go ahead... Cum inside me like always.
I'm cumming!
Me too...
You still want more...
I can't keep up with young
women these days.
Speaking of young women...
I hear there's a new nurse coming in.
So? What if there is?
What do you think? I want her to care for me.
I understand. I'll do
something about it, then...
In return... I want you to make me cum again.
Everyone quiet. I'm sure some
of you know already, but...
This is Mayu Mizuno. She will be
joining our team, starting today.
I'm Mayu Mizuno. I'll do my
best. Nice to meet you all.
Nice to meet you too.
Satsuki, will you show Mayu
around the hospital, please?
Yes ma'am.
I'm Satsuki Aoyagi.
This job isn't always easy, but
let's do our best together, okay?
Right!
She's so pretty.
So, you've only been at
this hospital for a month?
Yup, so I'm pretty new too.
Why did you leave the
last hospital you were at?
Nurses have to move on, too. Get it?
Sort of...
You keep saying you want to
become a good doctor, but...
...we all know the real reason why.
What's that?
Because doctors get all the babes!
Not just humans, but every
living thing's goal in life...
...is to reproduce and leave descendants.
You're a pretty handsome guy.
I'll show you the ropes of being a doctor...
...and how to get with girls, too.
Thank you, but my heart is already set.
I don't have a boyfriend! Plus,
I have my heart set already.
I'm going to be married to my job!
What?
Nimura!
Mayu! Why are you here?
That's my line!
Is she your friend?
Sort of, not really...
I never heard from you,
and I was wondering...
...what happened to
you. So you were here...
Do you have any idea what I went through?
I was young, and I didn't know
what was going on, myself...
And now you're a doctor!
I'm still a resident.
It's the same thing!
Okay...
I think you'll be a great doctor.
Satsuki.
As long as he listens to me, he'll be fine.
You shouldn't teach naughty things
to such a respectable young man.
Dr. Hattori.
What's that supposed to mean, Satsuki?
I don't know.
I've still got a long way to go!
Damn you...
I can't believe I bumped into Mayu here...
She looked like she was really angry...
I left her after that incident, as if
I was running away from her...
I'm sorry... I can't...
You don't love me... Is that why?
No! It's just... I'm not sure myself, and...
I've never been so insulted...
You're so pathetic.
Hey there, pathetic boy.
Satsuki.
Mayu told me everything.
I thought the stories about
you were pretty cute.
I can't believe you're still afraid to have sex.
Mayu, why'd you have to do this...?
Why'd you have to tell
Satsuki, of all people...?
But... I understand why you're
like that. I kind of like that.
Really?
Yes. Can I sit next to you?
So, you've never had sex.
Well, Mayu and I tried a
couple times, but we never...
How embarrassing.
Does that mean you're impotent?
No, I'm just scared... I think...
Do you think you'll be
able to have sex with me?
How about me?
It's not who I'm with...
Satsuki is so cute...
I'm joking. I'm joking.
You still love Mayu, right?
Then you should try it with her again.
I bet she's waiting for you, too.
Ryoko.
Thank you.
Well? Have you gotten used to this place?
Yes. Everyone is so nice, and very helpful.
I see.
Thanks again for the coffee.
I'll go.
Mr. Ishigami?
Is something wrong?
Nurse, lately, at night...
...this is embarrassing, but
my penis suddenly gets hard.
I see...
So I'm having a lot of trouble falling asleep.
It's like my body is on fire, too. Isn't
there something you can do, nurse?
Please talk to your physician
about these things.
I haven't been a nurse long, so I
don't think I can fix your problem.
If you don't have any other
problems, please excuse me...
What the?
What's wrong? Nurse? Oh, the
medicine must be working.
Medicine? But when did I...
Mayu's probably... Right around now...
I wonder if she's having fun?
There's no use trying to fight it.
This medicine works really well.
You had this planned all along?
Communicating with your
patients is part of being a nurse.
Getting to know their body is especially
important, and also the hardest.
But I'll show you first hand.
Don't worry. I've readied
another uniform for you.
Yes... It feels so good... It's so
amazing. Nimura... It feels so good...
Right there... Harder...
Fantastic! A young woman's
body is magnificent!
Please stop...
Stop...
I can smell your pussy. It smells
good. Let's see how it tastes.
Your pussy smells and tastes great! It's great.
You shouldn't wet a patient's bed like this!
Come on. Treatments are important.
You need to be thorough.
We've only just begun...
You need to move too.
You're pretty good! I can't
believe you're new here!
Please... No more... Please stop... Please.
Didn't I tell you? We've only just begun.
Well? Don't you think I'm much better
than any young man you've been with?
No...
We still have a long way to go.
Oh my... Are you
masturbating with my penis?
I can't believe it... I never knew I
was such a perverted woman...
I'm shaking my own ass... I can't stop!
Well? Doesn't it feel good? Say it.
It feels great. I think I'm going to die!
Let's finish it up!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to die!
Make me cum... Make me cum! Please!
I'm gonna cum!
Nimura, you're the best! It feels so good.
You're fucking me so hard, I...
What's going on? My dick
is... What's going on?
Is someone still here?
No, not here...
Then, why did you come here so late?
How many nurses have you gotten with?
Who knows... I can't count
them with both hands anymore.
What's this stain?
Why do I have to be hard now?
Because you're touching me there...
My penis...
What do you want me to do this time?
I want you to touch it...
My penis...
What's wrong with it?
It's amazing. Your pussy is great!
The color, luster, feel...
Everything about it is better
than any nurse I've fucked.
How many doctors have you fucked with this?
No one...
Then that means I'm your first.
No, it's dirty there...
Human bodies are dirty everywhere.
I feel so strange... it feels so good.
I bet your mouth wants some
attention. Right, Satsuki?
I never thought you'd like to
have such wild blowjob sessions.
I can't hold it anymore! Let me fuck you!
It's so big... It's so big, doctor!
Savor it, Satsuki.
I've never had one so big. It's
amazing Dr. Hattori. Yes...
I'm proud of my dick, too.
Once a woman tries it, she can't get enough.
Yes...
It feels so good. My body... I'm so
hot I think I'm going to catch fire...
Yes! I've never had sex that was so good.
You're having sex with a
doctor in a sacred hospital.
What are you going to
do if someone sees you?
I don't care! Look at me! Look at me!
Naughty nurse...
I want your sexy breasts to make me cum.
Yes...
They're so soft...
My breasts feel good, too...
Your penis is... looking at me...
I'm gonna cum!
Yes! Cum!
Did you do this at the
last hospital you were at?
I wonder?
What's wrong? You look down.
Every beautiful flower's
roots are covered in dirt.
What's that supposed to mean?
You don't seem to be happy, yourself.
Covered in dirt, huh?
NURSES STATION
We're going to operate on
Moriyama from room 305 at noon.
NURSES STATION
I want Sudo and Karino to assist me.
Right!
NURSES STATION
Oh, and Yamauchi, also from
room 305, will go into surgery...
...as soon as we can take CT scans.
Hey, has anything happened
with you and Mayu?
Waiting isn't going to solve anything.
Don't wait around, or some
other guy is going to take her.
The men at his hospital are assertive,
so she'll be taken in no time.
Nimura, are you listening?
Shut up! You slut!
Someone's in a bad mood.
Oh, good...
He wasn't saying it to me...
My new life couldn't have
started off any worse.