Welcome back, Lord Estilgar.
How go the arrangements?
Quite well, sir. At this rate,
we'll be done in 3 days.
Oh, so she meets expectations, Garius?
I believe she's a rare find, sir.
I'm looking forward to this.
Yes, endure. Stand up to it.
Endure it until lust
controls you completely...
...then you will be a sex slave!
It was like a nightmare.
It went on unceasingly
for hours. A nightmare.
They shall appear in the humblest of forms.
Superior to man or woman,
their advent in this world...
...will herald the defeat of all the evil ones...
...and bring shining prosperity to all!
SLAVE WARRIOR MAYA
You there, wait!
Me?
Hmm... I sense an extraordinary
destiny within you.
I'll read your fortune for you.
Sorry, but I don't have any money.
Compensation is unnecessary.
Now come closer.
Now, the ball. Look into the crystal ball.
Clouds... What happened to me?
M-M-Monsters!
No! Stay back! No!
You are foreigner, Miss?
Those are some really wild
clothes you're wearing.
Wh- What are you things?! Where am I?
Why do you look so weird?!
No way...
You wanna talk about it, Miss?
My name's Maya Mizutani.
My, you have a really wild name, too.
Oh, yes. My name's Heckle.
And my friend here...
Jaekel, Miss.
So, Miss Maya, tell us about yourself.
Um, well, I live in Seitatani,
Tokyo and I'm a freshman...
...at St. Canary University.
The school's about 20
minutes from Shibuya...
...by the east rail line, so it's a little far...
...but there's the CD store
and the pachinko parlor...
...that I like in front of the station.
I live with my mom and dad
and our dog, Pusuke, and...
Okay, I got it. Miss, you're from
the other world, aren't you?
Other world...?
This is Valserius galaxy, star
system Goodwin, planet Estorida.
You don't know, do you?
The sorcerers do this.
Sorcerers?
Exactly.
It's not that rare for them to
forcibly bring people here.
Oh, no... Then what will I do?
What'll we do, Heckle?
What do you think? There's only
one thing to do when this happens.
Yeah, there's no escape.
Anyway, what you do is...
Um...
Oh, uh, no worries, Miss Maya!
Yeah, yeah! We know a
way to get you home.
Really?!
But we're businessmen, so we
can't just tell you how for nothing.
Um, what should I do?
First, could you take off all your clothes?
No way! No way! I couldn't do that!
Let's go, Jaekel.
See you later.
All right, I'll take them off.
Will this do?
Still got some on.
Yeah, ditch the other things.
No way!
Let's go, Jaekel.
Right with you.
All right! I'm desperate.
It would be for some lizards, too...
Satisfied?
Hey, cut it out! That hurts!
What's going on?! What's the big idea?!
Don't talk. A naked woman in
the mountains isn't human.
She's an animal!
Now that you've taken off your
clothes, you're just an animal.
You live or die on our say-so.
Oh, no...
No!
Get one to really get some!
And now, the final bargains for today!
Step right up, folks! We've got
a lovely woman for you today.
First cleaned up for you in the city of Maar!
She was born an aristocrat...
...but, sadly, caught in the flames of war.
She lost her home, her family!
Forced to live alone in the outback!
Her virginity is intact!
Innocent! Upright! Beautiful!
Her chastity developed over several years!
And, with all the things she's seen...
...she is a woman of many contradictions!
With a body as passionate as hers...
...she isn't even guilty of pleasuring herself.
Now, then, everyone. For this virgin...
...let's start hearing the bids!
Will you pull out that
wonderful money of yours...
...and give some of it for her?
Okay, let's start the bidding at 200!
Give it a try! What's to lose?
203!
206!
I'll see your bid!
And there's one more feature to show them.
220! 250!
230!
300!
360!
Five million!
Five million.
F- Five million?! Anyone
else want to see that bid?!
W- Well, then, sold to Lord
Estilgar for five million!
She got picked by one of the elite.
No! No, stop it!
I see... The gloss of your skin
shows you really are a virgin.
Not there! It hurts!
Oh, is this what it is to be a virgin?
You've never even pleasured yourself.
My God, you'll be amazing as a sex slave.
Please! Please don't hurt me! Please!
What are you saying?
With your wet little hole...
Garius, I leave this to you.
As you wish.
And, to become the sex
slave they wanted...
...my body gradually began
to change Into a sex fiend's.
Maya! Maya!
We came for the other half
of your slave auction price.
We heard you were down
here and came to see you.
Man, you've really got it rough!
And whose fault do you think that is?!
Please, forgive us.
Yeah, forgive us.
It's your fault that I... I...!
Wow, you really pack it in.
Yeah, that's incredible.
No, please! Don't move it!
Miss Maya?
You don't seem to want us down here.
If that's the case, then...
...we're outta here!
Wait! I know something you want to hear!
Something that'll make you money!
What, are you gonna try to
trick us so we can save you?
It's true! I saw where this
castle's treasure room is.
The treasure room?!
Yeah. You see that lever over there?
If you pull it, it'll open the
door to the treasure room.
What'll we do, Heckle?
Hmm... We may never
have this chance again.
Right. If you don't, you'll regret
it for the rest of your lives.
True, but I still think you're trying to trick us.
You really did trick us!
Now we're even.
W-W-What'll we do? If they find
out, there'll be hell to pay!
We've got no choice! We'll
have to take Maya and run!
Come on, Maya! Let's go!
Something wrong, Maya?
It won't come out! It's stuck!
You're a lot of trouble, you know that?
An escape! A slave's escaped!
Maya, it's okay now.
Wait!
What's wrong?
My... My tail...
Tail? Oh, yeah. Hey, that
looks pretty funny...
This is no time to laugh, you idiot!
Forget me, I give up. You
two escape by yourselves.
Heckle, is there something
weird about this room?
I don't see anything.
Just take your glasses off!
Wha... What the hell?!
Heckle, where are we?
I don't know...
Maya! Warrior Maya!
Who's there? Who are you?
Maya? What's going on?
Maya!
Heckle, what was...?!
Who the hell are you?!
Maya! Listen to me, Maya!
Who is it?
Who's calling to me?
Take the sword, Maya!
Take the sword and smash them!
Smash evil!
Smash Zotos' ambitions!
This is it!
We're going to die!
What the hell...?!
Could that sword be...?!
That... That's impossible!
This planet is where the
prophecized one appeared?
Yes, Lord Zeon. We will
Be entering orbit shortly.
Estorida, third planet of
the Goodwin star system.
But I don't believe it.
A Druid warrior on a frontier world like this...
I heard you were born on the
frontier as well, Lord Zeon.
Lady Miran.
I believe that's what planet Marina is.
Good Heavens... But, for a holy warrior...
A legendary Druid warrior
to have appeared here.
Do you doubt the god Romus, Lord Zeon?
Forgive me. So long as
I can, I will serve Him.
Very well. To be honest, I, too,
used to doubt the legend.
Until just now...
Lady Miran...
I felt it. I felt the warrior's awakening.
What? The awakening?!
Yes, Lord Glassmeyer. Without a doubt.
It was definitely the legendary warrior!
Estilgar, it seems I was
wrong to entrust you...
...with maintaining the seal on that sword.
The circumstances were embarassing.
Never mind. What will you do about it?
I've already dispatched a pursuit team.
She may have awakened, but
she's not at full strength yet.
And my slave torture
device is still functional.
Those dogs in the Republic Forces
will be sniffing around here soon.
I'll try to suppress any rumors...
...but the Emperor doesn't
tolerate failure from his servants.
Go to it, Estigar.
As you wish.
Heckle! Maya's awake!
Oh, good.
So, you can't remember anything?
Y- Yeah...
Maya, you were incredible!
You sliced those knights
down one after another!
And the way you busted
out holding that sword...!
I'm sorry. I can only remember
up to where I heard the voice.
I'll give you a special, on the house!
So, what is it?
How do you like this?
Hyper-heavy armorwear!
No way! I can't move in this!
Well, how about this?
No way! It's too embarrassing!
Well, then, how about this?
Would you knock it off?!
I thought it looked good on you.
Well, maybe this'll do.
Okay, now to deal with your tail.
Isn't there any other way?
Maya, we already went over this.
The only way to Ransberg is
through the Forest of Eral.
Right...
Maya, does your tail hurt?
Well, you'll just have to put up
with it till we get to Ransberg.
We'll find you a good
armorer and get it pulled out.
Maya, what's wrong?
Didn't you just hear that?
Not me.
I didn't mention this before...
...but they get apparitions around here.
Apparitions?
Like spirits.
I hate ghosts and spirits and things!
That's not the way a warrior should talk.
But...
What happened to all that strength before?
You were incredible, Maya!
You took out all those
soldiers, slice, slice, slice!
That's right. I saved
Heckle and Jaekel before.
Maya! Maya!
Yeah, I'm a warrior. I can't be a coward!
Wow! Incredible as always, Maya.
I thought we were done for!
I was so scared...!
As expected of a Druid warrior.
Who's there?!
Wait for your chance and
then hit them where it hurts.
I compliment you on your plan.
But, will it work against me, Garius?
No way...
Maya, you can't show weakness here!
Show'im who's boss!
R- Right!
Hey, you villain! Come and get me!
If you don't mind, I mean...
You don't have to be polite to him!
Maya, what's wrong?
My vagina...! No... No...
Hedonay!
Maya! Uh, Heckle?
Jaekel, in this situation...
RETREAT!!!
One who has our slave torture
device implanted must obey us.
Now take off all your clothes.
No! Don't look at me!
Look at yourself! This is
what you really are now!
Such a lovely body. I'll make
you the ultimate sex slave.
Your face when you
awaken will be priceless.
Once we make your body
something to be ashamed of...
...you'll lose the desire
to return to your world.
A Druid warrior... How pathetic.
Let's begin.
You called, Lord Glassmeyer?
Republic Forces members will be here soon.
If they do anything suspicious,
you know what to do.
As you wish.
Once the transformation is complete...
...the legendary warrior
will be a mere sex slave.
I wonder what the Republic Forces
will say when they see the new you?
Full power!
What do you think they're doing to Maya?
Dunno...
I hope it isn't anything too horrible.
What's a Republic Forces ship doing here?!
I think something major's starting.
Yeah, a Druid warrior...
I heard about it when I was young.
My mom used to tell me
the story over and over.
The legendary warrior. The
holy sword of the Druid.
You mean the sword Maya had?
Yeah. They shall appear
in the humblest of forms.
Superior to man or woman,
they will save the world.
Maya, what's going to happen to you?