Masaki, I love you!
Miyuki, I love you! I love you so much!
I'm so happy! I love you! I love you so much!
Masaki...
Don't let go! Don't let me go!
Help me. Get me out of here. Please!
Miyuki, I'll save you. I swear!
A dream? Who's Miyuki? I don't
know a girl by that name.
Am I horny or what?
Next stop, Rakuganji-Mae. Rakuganji-Mae.
My bag!
Hey, wait!
Hey, you thief!
Damn it!
Oh, what the hell is this?!
And the train's gone, too.
My wallet's gone!
And so are my tickets!
Okay, the next train's...
Shit! Three hours?!
But I can't ride it without money.
Maybe I can ask the station master...
What the...? There's no one here!
I don't have an ATM card...
Not that there's a bank here, either.
Shit!
Hey, this thing's so old it's...
It's an earthquake! Oh, for God's sake!
For crying out loud.
My name's Masaki Hoshino.
I write for a news magazine.
I'd come to this area to do a story.
And here I was, stuck at an
abandoned train station.
Man, I have the worst luck.
Hey! What are you doing?
What do you mean?
Waiting for the train, of course.
You can wait forever. The train won't come.
What?
The earthquake just now caused a
landslide that blocked the tracks.
No one has worse luck than me!
And what are you planning to
do without money or a ticket?
Well, first I have to contact my editor.
Then find someplace to stay.
Oh, well.
I'll let you stay at my place
till the tracks are cleared.
Thanks. But is that all right?
There are just women there,
but it's okay. I'll ask Mom.
Thanks, really. You're a lifesaver.
I'm Masaki Hoshino.
And I'm...
Miyuki, right?
How did you know?
Oh, it's written on my sketchbook.
Oh, uh, right. By the
way, where's your home?
My home's over there.
I'm home!
This way, Mr. Hoshino.
I got my mom to okay it.
She says you can stay.
Here, please take this room.
Sure. Thanks.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh, nothing.
Thanks, really.
You're a lifesaver.
Well, I'll call you when dinner's ready.
Why...?
She's the girl from my dream.
Miyuki told me about you.
I'm Ryoko, the oldest.
This is Mayu, the youngest.
She's still in school.
And our maid, Kana.
I'm sorry, but mother's been
sick in bed since yesterday.
What brings you here, Mr. Hoshino?
Oh, well, I was doing a story
for the magazine I write for.
Oh, so you're a magazine
writer, Mr. Hoshino.
So, what sort of article are you doing?
Oh, well, I'm still writing it, so...
What magazine is it?
Weekly Spe.
Oh, I've seen it!
It's that obunism magazine, right?
That magazine carries all sorts of photos...
...including nude ones.
Yeah, well...
Have you ever taken any nudes?
Oh, no. I'm just a writer.
I'd be no good at that.
Uh, this is really good!
Did you make all this, Kana?
Yeah! Do you really like it?
I'm glad! Do you want more?
Kana!
Excuse me...
Pardon me. You have plenty
of food already, don't you?
Yes, thank you.
Oh, Sis. You shouldn't yell like that.
I can't tell if I was lucky or unlucky today.
No, definitely lucky!
I get to stay here with
three gorgeous women!
And their maid, Kana, is really cute, too.
Sir, how's your bath?
Oh, shit! It's Kana!
I'll wash your back for you.
Uh, well, sure...
If you want to.
K - Kana...?
Oh, so big already?
Why...?!
Miss Ryoko's orders.
I'm to take care of you.
No one here knows that I'm here.
Just relax and enjoy it.
Not even Ryoko?
Well? Like it?
Oh, yeah...
More! Give me more!
Yes! Oh, yes! Please,
give me more. Fill me up!
Please! Come inside of me!
But...
It's all right! Inside me, please!
Now! Make me come!
Was it... a dream...?
Kana, who said you could have sex?
Looks like I'll have to punish you severely!
No! Please forgive me, Mistress Ryoko!
Maybe we should try 600 cc today.
No! Don't! Please forgive me!
There we are. In it slowly goes.
How many minutes can you hold out today?
Mistress Ryoko, if you do that, I'II... I'II...!
Oh, there'll be no forgiveness. Not
after I brought our guest here.
A maid is supposed to please guests, right?
No! No! Please don't look at me!
Silence!
Please, come in. You'll get a better view.
Oh, God! It's coming out!
Well, shall we play with her together?
Morning! Breakfast time!
What, aren't you up yet? Your
breakfast's getting cold.
Miyuki!
What the hell happened last night?
Was it just a dream?
You're Kana, right?
Yes!
Thanks for last night.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
But Ryoko really punished you.
Nobody punished me!
What, you're still eating?
You're looking for a story,
right? I'll show you around.
There, you see? It all collapsed.
The road and the train
tracks are both blocked.
Wanna go for a closer look?
What's with you?
What? Oh, nothing.
Let's go!
What do you do for a living?
Me? Right now I just help
with the housework.
Oh? But you've got a maid, don't you?
What I really want to be is an illustrator.
That's why I always walk
with my sketchbook.
I stop and draw whatever catches my fancy.
What sort of stories do you
want to write, Mr. Hoshino?
I really want to write a
novel, but I haven't tried yet.
Well, when you write a novel,
be sure and send me a copy.
Hm? Oh, I promise I will.
Miyuki...
Help me! Get me out of here! Please!
What are you doing?!
Um, sorry, I just...
What happened to me?
I just suddenly felt this
incredible sense of closeness.
I just wanted to seal my promise to her.
Mina!
Mayu! If you don't give it back, I'll just die!
I just can't stand it!
You have such a cute little
snatchy-watchy, Mina.
Mayu! If you do that, I'll just lose control!
What the hell...? What's with this family?!
Um, er, well, that is...!
Mister, I feel so horny!
Do you want to play with us, Mister?
Mayu, why aren't you in class?
How can I go to class
when the train can't come?
C'mon, Mister! Play with us!
Uh, hold on!
Let's hide it and make
him try to find it, Mayu.
Do your nipples feel good, Mister?
Mister, I...!
Oh, you make me feel so good!
It feels so good!
No fair, Mayu! I want a piece of him, too!
Your clit feels so nice, Mina!
If you keep doing that, I'm going to pee!
Mister, hurry!
He's in me!
Oh, that feels so good!
Come with me, Mister! Come with me!
Mistress Reiko, please forgive us!
Ryoko! You had some fun with that
man when you punished Kana!
Please forgive me! I won't do it again!
Silence! You think I could forgive you?!
Wha...?! This is pretty fucked up right here.
Mayu! You had him join in while
you and Mina were doing it!
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
That's "Forgive me, Mistress Reiko!"
It seems someone needs to
be punished a little more!
Please!
Miyuki! Tell me what you did
with him when you went out!
You miserable little slut!
Please, forgive me!
He and I didn't do anything!
I hate lies! Tell me the truth.
It is the truth! I didn't do anything wrong!
Stubborn girl.
I guess the usual punishments
are no longer effective.
Kana, fetch the thorn lash.
Yes, ma'am.
No! No! Not that! Anything but that!
All we did on the beach was kiss!
Oh? You just kissed?
Yes. We just kissed.
I was so embarassed when he did it...
Oh, no! Miyuki, have you fallen for him?
No, never!
Tell me the truth!
Mistress Reiko, please
stop it! You'll kill Miyuki!
Please! Please!
Stop it!
Oh, no! Not until she confesses!
Stop it! It's true!
We really didn't do anything!
Well, well. Your prince
has come for you, Miyuki.
No! Don't look at me! Turn away!
Miyuki...
How can you treat your daughters like this?!
My daughters?! These women are
all servants I have to play with!
She's nuts!
On my orders, Kana lured you
out onto the station platform.
And Miyuki started talking to
you to lure you to this mansion.
Now, then! From now on, you are my slave!
Like hell! Why should I obey you?!
Why indeed?
If you don't, who's to say
what will happen to Miyuki.
If you lay a finger on Miyuki, I'll kill you!
Masaki...
Well? Wanna give it a try?
What?!
Did you enjoy your bath yesterday, sir?
Kana and Asami are twins.
And my most loyal servants.
Their job is to keep watch over these girls.
Well? How about a little
contract between you and me?
If you agree to join me,
I'll forgive Miyuki. Well?
If you resist, I'll beat
Miyuki to death right here.
Which do you want?
All right!
What a cooperative boy!
Well, what shall we do first?
What a good look for you, young man!
I know. Since you like each other
so much, I'll give you a treat.
Come on, Miyuki! Come over
here and show him everything!
I can't! Please, don't make
me do this, Mistress Reiko-
Stop being an idiot! Go on!
Did you not hear what I said?!
Masaki... Look at all that I have.
How honest!
But you won't have him, Miyuki.
Ryoko!
Yes, ma'am.
That smell!
It's an aphrodesiac to help
you get into the mood.
Those who can't handle it will fall asleep.
If you can handle it, it helps immensely.
Then those weren't dreams!
Let me tell you something.
When you'd fall asleep...
...it was Miyuki who'd bring you in here.
Yes, Mistress Reiko.
And what do you want to do with me?
C'mon, Mister. Let's play
some more dirty games.
You're incredible, Masaki!
Your nipples are so small and cute!
I'm not used to this.
Sis, lemme have a lick.
Mistress Reiko, could you
give me the big one, please?
How adorable. You just love the big ones.
Kana!
Okay, there's the first one.
And let's get one for your ass, too.
Oh, that's great! Wonderful!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
Mistress Reiko, me, too!
Oh, that's great! Wonderful!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
Mistress Reiko, me, too!
I'll give you the candles.
Well, well, Miyuki. You really
seem in the mood now.
Miyuki's really as much
of a slut as the others.
Understand that, kid?
No...
Miyuki, now I want you to piss on him.
Masaki, look inside of me.
Drink it all in.
Oh, I won't let you come now, Miyuki.
No, please! Let me come!
Let me come! Please!
He belongs to me!
No! Masaki!
Oh, wow! Cool! I'm really coming now!
Get me out of here. Please!
Miyuki! Miyuki, run!
Hurry!
MIYUKI!
It's not safe here! Run!
The mansion's collapsed.
I wonder if any of the others got out.
Thank you. You got me out of there.
But I promised you, didn't I?
In the dream, I swore I'd save you.
Thank you...
And thank you, Miyuki.
A train.
The tracks must be clear.
Miyuki! Miyuki!
Still here...