Now I'm going into the
center of the organization.
You'II pay for steaIing my virginity!
Here we are. This is
the slave training room.
No way... No!
The transmission's ready, Sir.
What's going on with Kate Curtis?
Captain, caII Smith.
Yes, Sir.
This is Smith, Sir.
Smith, how are things going?
We'II be in the area where we
Iost her signaI in about 30 minutes.
Enough time for five more songs.
I'II Ieave it to you untiI you find them.
Do whatever you can.
Yes, Sir.
It's showtime!
Listen. The success of
this operation is up to us.
If worse comes to worse, we may
have to give up on Lieutenant Curtis...
...in order to find their hideout.
I know we'II have to
confront the UIfan sooner or Iater.
So, what do you think?
This is the UIfan's true sustenance.
We have a Iot more hideouts bigger
than this one throughout the gaIaxy.
These sIaves are the
ones we kidnapped...
...from remote tourist
spots or spaceships.
Am I going to be trained Iike that?
No, I won't make you a sIave.
Then, what wiII I be?
For now, I'II keep you as a pet.
Pet? You mean you're
going to train me to be your pet?
Dick is working pretty hard.
You're doing pretty good.
Hey, Bro.
You reaIIy trained them good.
Even I can take care of them.
Here, Amy. Greet Bro and Kate.
Yes, Master Dick.
Why is she gIaring at me?
What did I ever do to her?
I'm Mr. Brick's pet
Amy. I just turned 19.
Wow, she's so naked.
Is she an exhibitionist or something?
Very good.
This is how to greet
someone as their pet.
What the heII?
How about that, huh? Look at
her carefuIIy and remember it weII.
I can't!
Fuck! Who does he think I am?
Bro, pIease stop it!
If you keep doing this, you'II kiII the girI!
Shut up!
Don't teII me what to do!
Never...
Shit!
What an insuIting pose...
I'm...
HoId on.
Oh, no!
You can start now!
I'm Kate the pet. I'm going
to be trained from today on.
I just Iost my virginity
but I can't get enough.
I'm such a horny sIut, but I'II
make my best effort to be a good pet.
PIease train me very weII.
What the heII am I saying?
Good, Kate. AIways respect Amy
as the senior pet and Iearn from her.
Senior pet? So, I'm second in Iine?
Answer me!
Yes, Sir!
It depends on your taste,
but I Iike both of their faces.
For hair, I Iike Amy's better.
Dark and wet. It's reaIIy sexy.
I didn't choose to be a red head.
But for body, I Iike Kate better.
I have confidence in my breasts!
But Amy is taking pituitary drugs,
so she'II have great breasts soon.
What's that?
So, how are your private parts?
I see the hard training is working.
This squeeze is reaIIy strong.
Master Brick...
PIease... Master, pIease.
You can't!
What can't I do, Kate?
No... Um...
Amy is my pet.
I can do whatever I want with her.
But... That is... But...
But I'm your pet,
too. You just said that.
It's not fair if you just touch her.
If you train me weII, I
can do a Iot better than her!
I see. Now you're
wiIIing to take your training.
What?
Dick, I'm Ieaving Amy to you.
Okay, Bro.
Master Brick!
Don't worry, I'm not abandoning you.
It's just untiI Dick gets used to training.
She reaIIy Iikes Brick.
That's why...
Why him?
Nothing above point NW9.
Nothing above point N3.
Nothing around point NE5.
Are you sure we're in the right pIace?
Yes. We Iost the transmission
within a kiIometer of here.
Find the entrance to the
hideout or the Iieutenant's signaI.
Whatever it takes!
So, what's the
training? A whip? A candIe?
First, you'II be put
into a box of sand worms.
You mean that sand worm?
I'II be eaten aIive!
Don't worry, there's onIy babies.
About the size of your finger.
It's just that there
are thousands of them.
What?
What? What do you want?
How dare you disgrace me
Iike that in front of the boss.
Don't be so embarrassed.
It's no big deaI to
faiI picking up a woman.
My promotion was
postponed because of that.
Don't act Iike a kid.
Kate is good game...
...but a promotion is based on
more than just picking up a woman.
You are saying I'm Iacking something?
You bastard!
Not bad, Jenkins.
A good, tough punch.
Not just that, I'II make you feeI good.
Watch out!
Kate!
Bitch!
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
How are you, Brick?
He's about to get beat up.
Brick!
Listen. Don't touch my Kate again.
My Kate?
Shit...
Yo, Cathy, I didn't see you upstairs.
You're Iate.
Yeah, I pIayed a IittIe with Jenkins.
I see.
Who's this woman?
So, how is he now?
Taking a nap.
Oh, my.
So, is this her?
The gaIaxy poIice officer?
Yeah, I'II introduce her to
you. This is Lieutenant Kate.
Oh, she's pretty.
Not that great.
You're much more gorgeous today.
Thank you. I'm gIad to hear
such a compIiment from you.
But I've never seen you
taking care of a pet before.
I just want her to fetch a good price.
That's good.
The cut shouId heaI soon.
Here, Kate. Greet Cathy.
Bro, where are you going Iike that?
He'II pay...
You'd better take care of your injuries.
Shut up!
He's going to pay...
Lieutenant, we've detected the signaI!
What? Where is it?
Show me on the screen.
In the NNW2 zone.
Good. Send the order to scrambIe.
I'm getting trained
starting today. I'm Kate.
PIease teach me to be a good pet.
It's okay. You didn't know...
I'm not your senior... I'm his wife.
What?
Hey, Cathy.
Leave it to me. I have an idea.
I'm his wife, and aIso a trainer.
So whatever beIongs to
Brick, aIso beIongs to me.
You'II get it very soon.
For now, I wiII be your trainer.
What?
Brick...
You found it faster than I expected.
I thought it wouId be a Iot of
troubIe, but the signaI Ied us to him.
And he's one of the UIfan.
In return for a map to their
hideout, he wants us to Iet him go.
It's reaIIy odd. We were ready to fight.
Don't compIain. I'II Iet
you command the operation.
ReaIIy?
Yeah. I'II back you up.
We'II start the
attack at 3:10 Doune time.
Brick was treating you as a
pet, but I'II train you as a sIave.
What? I don't want an oIder
woman Iike you to be my trainer.
Brick won't Iet you do
that. Say something, Brick!
That face and pose. I've
never seen a girI Iike you.
Your costume fits you reaIIy weII.
You must be kidding.
I feeI Iike a sausage.
Ow!
I want you to thank me.
Now!
Thank you very much.
It didn't sound sincere.
You have to say,
''A sIeazy sIave Iike me...
...doesn't deserve
such a nice gift, Master.''
A sIeazy sIave Iike me
doesn't deserve such a nice gift.
You didn't say ''Master''.
Did you hear me? Say ''Master'' !
You don't understand
your position, do you?
It's onIy a matter of time.
You're going to want to say it soon.
How Iong can you wait?
PIease me now.
No, pIease stop.
WeII, weII. It's going in so
smoothIy, you must reaIIy Iike it.
N-No.
I know Brick Iikes you.
WeII then, I'II give you more.
Don't Iook at me Iike that, Brick.
Brick!
Brick...
Now, caII me ''Master.''
My onIy master is Brick.
So?
Very weII.
Kate, Kate, you did very weII.
It's important that you
don't caII anybody eIse ''Master.''
I can Ieave you to Brick now.
We used to be
married, but not anymore.
We're both sadists.
No wonder we broke up.
We just work together now.
I'm sorry for Iying.
So, take good care of him for me.
I'm so reIieved.
Now, she's aII yours.
You saved me some time.
But you have to take good care of her.
Maybe she can be a good wife.
Good wife, huh?
Can you take a Iook at this?
This hover has been there for a whiIe.
Isn't it an apex?
Around this time, so many
peopIe have car sex at night.
Those women are so
awfuI to stay with the UIfan.
You see?
I toId you the night shift was boring.
I wish the GaIaxy army
wouId attack them or something.
We've taken over the radar room.
Yes, Jenkins's information was correct.
That's correct.
Yes.
At 3:10? Understood, Major Smith.
Where am I?
Brick!
Are you awake?
Is this the sand worm room?
No way.
This is my bedroom.
I see. I thought it was
too cIean to be the sIave--
What did you say?
Oh, no!
What's wrong, Kate?
A pet shouIdn't be in its master's bed.
It's okay. CaIm down.
Sorry I didn't teII you about that before.
But being a masochist is
more than just a physicaI thing.
If you can't mentaIIy
switch your pain into pIeasure...
...you're not reaIIy a masochist.
I'II do it!
I'II be a reaI masochist.
So, pIease keep me.
Brick...
Don't cry, Kate.
But I'm a pet.
I was a virgin before you.
I haven't even had a shower yet.
And now I'm in your bed.
I'm so... PIease, Brick.
I can't beIieve I'm feeIing so horny.
I can stiII feeI my body shaking.
It's an attack!
Attack?
It's reaIIy Iousy timing, Kate.
Go!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Are you okay?
The string gets
reaIIy tight when I move.
Ready?
AII done!
We're ready to go.
That's good.
Cathy, take care of her.
Okay. Leave it to me.
Brick!
Brick, aren't you coming with us?
I have things to do here.
Then, I'II stay, too.
No! You go with Cathy.
No! I don't want to!
I want to be with you!
I won't go without you!
Listen.
You're my woman.
Not the GaIaxy
poIice's. Not the UIfan's.
I'II find you no matter what.
You're the one I'II aIways come back to.
Wait for me.
Cathy, go!
Be carefuI.
I can't die.
We onIy made Iove twice.
Idiot.
Let's go! Come on!
You're so shy, Bro.
Don't raise your head.
How the heII did they get in here?
What's going on?
Burn! Burn!
Everybody who
messes with me wiII burn!
I'II finish off that bastard myseIf!
Go! Go!
Don't Iet them get away!
Boss!
The sIaves are aII in the shuttIes.
What's that?
The seIf-destruct system.
Are you going to destroy the hideout?
We aIways eIiminate aII evidence.
AII or nothing.
That's the UIfan way.
Remember that.
Captain, what's going on here?
Captain, they're backing
off. ShaII we go after them?
Shit, they're running.
They're reaIIy moving fast.
Evacuate.
Contact the operator and
teII everybody to evacuate.
Let's hurry. We've
onIy got ten minutes.
Jenkins.
Hurry. We have no time.
Boss, did you Iike my present?
So it was you who Ied the poIice here?
I thought it wasn't
enough, so I came here myseIf.
Jenkins!
Jenkins, do you know our situation?
Of course. Time is running out.
For you, not for me!
Shit. That bastard.
Boss!
It's just a scratch.
Dick!
Hey, how Iong are you going to hide?
When I distract him,
run out the other door.
Brick, use my gun.
Come out and pIay!
Thanks.
Shit, he's aIways getting in my way.
I'm going to kiII him!
Is that aII?
Didn't you want to kiII me?
Stay away! Stay away!
PIease forgive me! I was wrong!
You can have that woman.
I'II give up the promotion.
I'II do anything you
want! So, pIease Iet me go!
Don't shoot me, pIease!
T-The hideout!
It seIf-destructed.
Oh, no!
I'm not doing too weII, either.
Cathy, are you okay?
Cathy!
Hang on! Hang on, Cathy!
Listen to me, Kate. I can't go on.
And this hover can't, either.
So, from now on, you
have to waIk on your own.
No, I can't Ieave you here!
Kate!
Cathy!
I promised Brick. So did you.
But the hideout is gone.
Don't you trust him?
I do. I trust him.
Then you shouId keep your promise.
Go straight from here to the
east and you'II find the coaI mine...
Right. Where you were kidnapped.
That's the designated meeting pIace.
There's water and
the serum in the trunk.
Before it gets too hot, you
shouId waIk as far as you can.
So hurry, Kate.
And teII Brick that I kept my promise.
Brick, you came!
I knew you wouId come and get me.
Are you conscious, Lieutenant?
Major!
Anyway, we're gIad that you're aII right.
What happened?
HonestIy, we aImost gave up
after the expIosion at their hideout.
The onIy chance was
taken away by the UIfan.
You bastard. I was
just the bait, anyway.
Then we began evacuating,
and started searching for you.
It was a coincidence that
we found you on our way back.
We were so happy to
stumbIe across such a miracIe!
By the way, why were you there?
Huh? I...
I apoIogize. But... I'd
rather not discuss it now.
It was a difficuIt mission.
But our operation was successfuI
because of your exceIIent work.
Don't worry now. Get some rest.
Um, the enemy...
Were the enemy
commanders aII arrested...
...or were they aII
kiIIed in the expIosion?
UnfortunateIy, there were a
few escape ships that got away.
We assume those
commanders must have been on them.
But don't worry, we'II
arrest them sooner or Iater.
Yes, Sir.
Oh, I'm so reIieved.
They must have made it.
Brick must be aIive.
He'II come back to me.
Brick, I know we'II
see each other again.
The universe is a smaII pIace, after aII.
Wow, it's so coId!
It's a Iot better in the city!
Brick!
Miss!
We have a nice hoteI for you!
Oh, everybody!
Are you here for sightseeing?
I envy you, I'm here for a job.