Let's go! Hurry!
Now, l get to take your clothes off at last.
Pearl: ''No! After this, please no more!''
Makoto: ''Hehehe! Don't move around so much!''
Pearl: ''l love you! l'm never letting you go!''
Makoto: ''Wait a minute!''
No! l was all set to see a naked woman!
Why did l waste so much time on this, damn it?!
What's wrong with Kenta?
Saiki, don't stop...
My peak sexual years are being wasted at this rate.
Goddess of Happiness, please rescue me from my celibacy!
Can Can Bunny
Extra 1
Long time no see, Kenta.
Who are you?
What? You've forgotten?
l am Suwatee the Benzaiten Goddess.
Suwatee?
Still living in the same tiny apartment?
Always playing dirty games on the computer and never studying.
Am l dreaming?
See for yourself.
l didn't feel anything!
We can only be seen by the pure of heart.
And those with very strong faith.
So, which am l?
You finally reached enlightenment.
Yes, the moment you realized you were an idiot.
l'd like to wake up now!
Who the hell's he talking to?
Keep your mind on me.
Who cares what he's doing?
But he's my friend.
Then, drop in on him later.
Yes, Wakaba.
You want to move in with me?
Commuting from the other world is a pain!
Please, Kenta.
But, hold on...
For your trouble, Suwatee will grant you a wish.
Grant me a wish?
Anything?
Sure...
l see...
What is it?
Something l've wanted for a long time.
You want me to help you get laid by beautiful women?!
Not so loud!
Don't laugh! lt's not like l'm a complete loser.
lt's just hard for me to meet girls.
Well, if that's what you want...
Alright. l will grant you your wish.
You will?
Your wish...
...Suwatee grants!
W-What the hell?
Suwatee! How could you?!
What if Emperor Shibi finds out?
Wow, what the hell happened?
l caused fragments of the Seven Great Northern Stars to fall to Earth.
Kenta, you will have the chance to meet seven beautiful women.
Really?
But, you must sleep with each of them,
or they will forget you ever existed.
l don't see that as a problem!
Now the world will see what a lady's man l can be!
Poor Kenta, lack of sex has driven him crazy.
Oh well, back to screwing Wakaba.
So, can we stay with you, Kenta?
Please, it would be my pleasure.
l don't know what Suwatee sees in this guy.
lt's a hard one to figure out.
Seven women.
l wonder what they'll be like?
Maybe someone like her.
Or a traditional girl like her.
A school girl would be nice too. l can't wait!
Kenta, can you handle this?
Your taste in men is terrible!
Shuree!
Hi! What have you been up to, Suwatee?
Why did you summon the fragments of the Seven Stars?
l wanted to make Kenta happy.
Jeez! What if that pervert, Shibi, finds out?
Why didn't you ask your dear cousin for advice?
What good is it if the one you love can't touch you?
Actually, if l have my way, he will touch me.
The power of this fragment will allow me to take on human form.
Once he sees me as a woman, Kenta will love me as one.
You're getting ahead of yourself, aren't you?
Okay, but l must see what kind of man this loverboy is.
Sorry! Pardon me!
Please, let me go.
What's wrong with having fun, little girl?
You like to have fun, don't you?
Come with us, and we'll show you a real good time.
But...
l'm sorry, can you excuse me for a second.
Sorry l'm late. We better get going.
Hold it!
Oh, uh, we're late for our date.
Don't even try to lie to me, you pathetic loser!
l see... nothing else l can do then...
Run!
Kenta!
Jeez, l can't bring myself to watch.
Are you okay?
l'm fine.
l hate it when a little puke screws with my evening plans.
Kick his ass, Abe!
That's a good idea.
Now, hold on just a second!
Get outta my face!
Hoshiro!
Y-You...
l did it again...
That's it?
Man, he's a lost cause.
Oh, l get it, Kaori! You're trained in martial arts.
Still, you were the only one who tried to help me. Thank you.
Well...
What a moron.
Why you...
Use my name. lt's Misao Aoyama.
Okay, so why was Misao being so mean to little Kaori?
Abe thought Kaori was shy, so we were taking her to a disco. That's all.
That's it?
You think that was reason enough for you to treat her so badly?
lt's all right, Kenta.
Misao, isn't your mother Yoko Goto, the famous rock star?
Oh, it must be nice being the kid of a big celebrity like that.
lt's not like l had a choice in the matter!
l don't know why we bothered with her.
Who'd want to dance with an old hag, anyway?
So you think l'm an old hag?
What do you think, Kenta?
l-l would never say that!
Are you saying l don't have rhythm?
All right, let's go!
l'll meet your challenge on the disco floor.
Oh boy, here we go.
You've got really good moves!
You have some too.
Kaori is really hot, but Misao turns me on too.
Why choose when l can have both?
What do you mean ''both'', you dork?
Who are you?
l am Rakusho, the Kishouten Goddess. Suwatee is my cousin.
Everyone calls me Shuree.
Suwatee's cousin?
W-What?
From what l've seen, you are definitely a low-life.
Why you!
Shouldn't you be eyeing your prospects?
And now the main event!
Who will be tonight's Dancing Queen?
The next number is ''Don't Walk'' by Yoko Goto,
the best hit of this week!
Let's dance together, Disco Goddesses!
This is your mother's song.
l'm worried.
Kaori rules! She's the best!
Looking good, Misao! You can do it!
They both dance great.
Who are you rooting for?
You dance well.
l guess dancing to your mother's music makes it easier.
Festival dancing suits you better!
l don't like the looks of this.
l sense a fight brewing.
You have no idea how awful it is to have a famous mom!
You spoiled brat! You just want to suck your mom's milk until you die!
Oh boy, here we go.
Don't take that, Misao! Show the magic kick!
Let her have it. Try the hurricane punch!
Man, this is getting serious. Hey, Shuree...
You want me to break it up?
Would you, please?
Alright...
ln the name of the Kishoten, rulers of Light and Darkness, l command thee!
Spirits of the air, wake the spirit of light that sleeps in the dark depths!
Unleash your energy!
W-What the hell?
Jeez, l shouldn't have involved Shuree.
Misao, why don't you take the bed?
She said she prefers the couch.
Oh...
l acted like a child tonight.
Still, you're a very sweet girl.
You could have beaten her up.
Misao has a hard time sharing her mother with the world.
That's why she hangs out with those thugs to relieve her loneliness.
Well, time for bed.
l'd better head home.
Don't go.
That is...
l guess she's attracted to blockheads.
He is not! He's very kind!
Sure, sure... l guess you see something l don't.
Please, turn the lights off.
No, l want to see your beautiful body.
But, l'm shy.
Quietly...
l can't help it...
Misao will hear me...
No... not there!
l can't...
Someone help me.
No, give me more!
l'm losing it!
So good!
l'm so wet!
Harder! Even harder!
Please stop, l can't control myself...
No... that's embarrassing...
No, now we're doing it doggie style!
My back, my back... please...
l'm dying! l'm dying!
Harder! More please! More!
No, no, l can't...
lt feels so good! Please help me!
This feels so good!
So good...
Kaori!
l can't hold back, l'm cumming!
l'm cumming! l'm cumming!
Together! Together!
Hey, wake up!
Come on...
You can't sleep...
Huh?
Kenta?
Who did you think l was?
That's right, you stayed the night.
Get up, sleepyhead.
Okay, let's go.
Huh? Where?
Here, take a look.
Wow! Tickets to the dinosaur exhibit!
Did you get these for me?
Kaori suggested it.
Kaori? Where is she?
She took off already.
She works as a tour guide at the exhibit.
Trying to get into this one's pants too?
Shuree...
Shut up! l'm trying to patch up their friendship!
So you can have a threesome?
N-No!
Kenta, why are you talking to thin air?
No! Um! lt's so early l must still be dreaming!
Goodness, he's such a prude.
l figured he'd be banging her already.
Kenta isn't that kind of guy!
Sure, sure, whatever you say, Princess.
Those guys again?
You came at a good time.
The exhibit isn't crowded on weekdays.
Oh wow, l can't believe they're real!
l'm glad you're having a good time.
Hey, can l touch one of them?
No, it's not allowed.
You're so stingy.
What's the matter?
Kaori, l gotta go...
Down that hall.
Excuse me for a second.
He's such a funny guy.
Now, let's see what that tough girl is doing.
The same jerks as before?
Can you keep your knees from shaking?
Hey, l can do it!
Oh? Who fell on their ass last time?
Shuree!
Kenta!
How cold. You didn't even call or anything.
What do you care?
Hey, we're just worried about you.
You can stop worrying!
Stay out of my life!
You're the one who wanted to hang out with us.
Now then, show her.
A rape video starring Yoko Goto's daughter should make us a fortune.
l-l won't let you!
Any luck, Kenta?
She wasn't there.
l don't like the way this looks.
l'm scared.
Let's split up and search.
Alright.
l didn't know you were a virgin.
That'll make the tape even more valuable!
She's all lubed up. Let's get some real action going!
Who are you?
What the hell are you doing to her?!
Oh, it's the pussy from yesterday.
Eat this!
Come on, how can you save Misao when you're lying down?
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
He's getting his ass kicked again.
Kenta!
Your wish...
...Suwatee grants!
Creatures in extinction, sleeping in eternity!
ln the name of the Kishoten, rulers of time and space, l command thee!
Walk through time and resurrect!
Save us!
Mommy!
What's their problem?
Wait! Where's Misao?
l'm sorry. l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
Calm down.
But, l...
Please do to me what you did to Kaori last night.
You were awake? l'm sorry.
Don't be.
l was so jealous of Kaori.
Kenta, please.
Are you sure?
Please, be gentle with me.
That's right, this is your first time.
l want it to be with you.
Wait...
Your fingers, the feeling's so strong!
You're more sensitive when it's your first time.
l can't help it. l can't help it.
Oh, so he ends up bagging her too.
So, why don't you join them?
l'm only kidding!
Oh no, not that!
l'm too embarrassed... don't look...
Your mouth feels so nice.
You're so wet.
l bet you finger yourself constantly.
l do not...
Admit it. You were at it last night, right?
l was... l was!
Because l was so lonely.
Naughty girl.
Misao is naughty.
Please shame me for my wrongdoing.
No, not yet!
Hurt?
A little.
Want more?
Oh yes.
l feel you. l feel you sliding inside me.
So hot and nice...
Push it. Push it in deeper.
lt's so... lt's so...
What should l...
lntense, feels so intense!
So big. You're so big, Kenta!
Kenta, l love you so much!
l feel strange...
My pussy is so soft and wet.
Your cock is stretching me out!
l can't believe it feels so good.
lt's amazing... so amazing!
You're tightening up!
lnside me... all of it... it's okay...
Let me have every drop.
Hey, here's the big stud.
You didn't do too bad for yourself.
A guy like me can always score!
You really are happy about this, aren't you?
What's wrong, Suwatee?
l don't know.
You don't know? That's a little strange.
Snap out of it-
H-Hey, are you okay?
l'm so sorry.
ls she next?
Seems like it...
This is fun!
Kenta...