l'm Kenta Ochiai.
l'm just a regular guy, an average student.
But since l met Suwatee, Shuree and the Gods of Luck, my life has changed!
l've been getting as much action as l can handle!
Ah! Life is good!
Then this gorgeous nurse, Haruna Sakamoto, appeared.
l want to share all the happiness of life with her...
Oh! l've never been this happy!
Can Can Bunny
Extra 3
Seiryuka Hospital
Haruna's missing?
Yes, she didn't come home last night. Mr. Okamura is very worried.
l'll help look for her.
Hey, wait!
We were the last people to see her.
She's probably out playing somewhere.
After all, she is a little girl.
What do you mean by that?
What's wrong, Shuree?
What's that?
l think it's...
This is the cross that Haruna wore.
Her grandfather Sakamoto and l were best friends.
He left this cross to her.
l feel strong spiritual energy coming from the cross.
ls it...
lt's the same presence l felt yesterday in the garden.
Does that cross have some kind of story behind it?
This cross belonged to my old lover, Kyoko Kawashima.
Fifty years ago, this was an army hospital.
Sakamoto and l worked here.
We had no hope for the future then.
We nursed people while waiting for our own deaths at the front.
Then she appeared in front of us... Kyoko Kawashima.
She was working in the same hospital as us.
l fell in love with her.
Kyoko and l made a promise that after the war, we would be married.
But while l was visiting my family,
Kyoko was killed.
Sakamoto took the cross from her neck.
lt was then l finally realized he also loved her.
The war finally ended.
Sakamoto found a woman who looked like Kyoko and married her.
Haruna strongly resembles Kyoko.
The only things that remain are the flower garden and fountain.
l see...
There's no mistake. lt's the same spiritual signature as the cross.
Then, Haruna was here?
Kyoko, forgive me! Kyoko!
The spiritual energy is getting stronger! Kenta, be careful!
l will, but where is she?
Haruna!
Kenta, wait!
What is it?
There's something dangerous here.
But, Haruna is...
Help me! Uncle, help me!
Kyoko, stop it! Haruna!
l must go! Haruna! Kyoko!
Haruna's in there. l'm going!
Wait!
Help me! Help me!
Haruna!
Kenta, behind you!
Kenta!
O spirits of the air around me!
Spirits that rule time and space, in the name of Kishoten, l command thee!
Combine your powers with mine!
Kenta, it's coming from where the old man is!
Kyoko, you can't! Kyoko!
Kenta, don't leave me!
Kyoko, forgive me! Kyoko!
Mr. Okamura!
Hold on! l'll call a nurse!
l'm fine. Take me to the garden!
Kyoko is the one who kidnapped Haruna.
lt's her anger.
Why?
When l went to visit my family, Kyoko was already pregnant with my child.
But l was forced into an arranged marriage by my parents.
What?
l didn't tell Kyoko what had happened.
When l didn't return, she forced Sakamoto to tell her the truth.
The night Kyoko was going to come after me, she was killed.
She must have hated me...
No, she had every right to!
Since then l've dedicated my life to this hospital.
l beg you, Kenta! Please take me to the garden!
l will.
Kyoko, you're there, aren't you? lt's me! Do you understand?
Takeshi?
Kyoko, please let that child go!
Kyoko!
Takeshi, l've been so lonely and sad.
But l believed that you would come back, so l've been waiting all this time!
No, you're wrong!
Aren't you coming back to me?!
Stop! Haruna has nothing to do with this!
Mr. Okamura!
Kyoko, it's my fault.
l'm the one who betrayed you.
lt's too late to ask you to forgive me, but that child is innocent!
Kill me instead!
l won't let my child go!
You're wrong. That child is Sakamoto's.
Kenta, l'm taking us back to the past.
Fifty years ago, Kyoko died here full of hate.
We'll take the old man back and have him meet the living Kyoko.
C-Can you do that?
There's no other way if you want to save those two.
Spirits of present, past, future!
ln the name of the Kishoten, l command thee.
Spirits of the air around me!
Come to my hand and set free the substance of space!
Relive the past!
This... This is fifty years ago!
Haruna!
Haruna, hold on!
Kenta, l...
Kyoko! Kyoko!
Don't die, Kyoko! Hold on!
Takeshi, is it you? My eyes! l can't see!
l'm here.
You didn't come back. Sakamoto said...
Kyoko...
The baby... l didn't know what to do.
l wanted to see you and...
lt's hard to breathe. Dearest!
Kyoko, l...
Don't leave me. Stay by my side always, please. The three of us...
Kyoko, wait! l still have things that l need to say!
Mr. Okamura!
Kenta.
Where are we?
lt's all right. lt's over now.
Mr. Okamura is safely back in his hospital room, too.
That mysterious woman is really powerful, isn't she?
No, no, no. That is...
lt's okay. l won't tell anyone.
Now l understand why Grandfather cherished that cross so much.
And why Uncle Okamura treasures me.
Kyoko was wonderful, wasn't she?
Beautiful and kind...
Haruna.
l was so scared! So very scared, Kenta!
lt's all right now.
Haruna?
l...
Oh no! What am l doing?
Haruna.
Please, Kenta.
What's wrong with me?
l've never felt these feelings before.
l really like you, Kenta!
Haruna!
Why doesn't he just go for it?
Kenta, l've never...
lf you don't want to, Haruna, l...
No, l want to be with you, Kenta.
Okay.
Kenta, l'm scared.
lt'll be all right. Leave it to me.
Haruna, you're wonderful.
Kenta!
No!
No one's ever...
Your first time?
Haruna, relax your thighs.
Kenta, hurry. l can't wait.
Just a little while longer.
Are you okay, Haruna?
Yes.
Kenta's being extra gentle.
Maybe he's really fallen in love.
Huh? What's this?
Haruna, you're very beautiful.
l'm embarrassed, Kenta.
You must think l'm disgusting.
That's not true.
Kenta! Kenta!
ls it okay, Haruna?
Why does my chest hurt? Kenta, l...
Haruna!
Did it hurt?
lt's okay. Go on.
She's so delicate!
l'm afraid l'll break her if l move!
Please stop, l...
Haruna, l can't hold back...
lt's okay, Kenta, go on.
Why can't l stop crying?
l'm sorry. Did l hurt you?
No, it's okay.
lf l made you happy, then l'm happy.
Haruna.
What a lousy day! lt's pouring down rain!
Hey, Kenta, have you seen Shuree?
lsn't she here?
l thought she was with you.
l haven't seen her since last night.
What's going on?
Now that l think of it, you really are quite beautiful.
That stupid guy has me all confused.
Suwatee, why do you love him?
l don't understand it myself.
You don't?
Why don't you confess your love to Kenta, tomorrow?
Hey, l'm home.
Huh?
Suwatee, are you alone?
Where's everyone else?
Kenta, what would you do if l weren't here anymore?
What would l do?
Would you be lonely?
What are you talking about?
Hey, do you have a crush on me or something?
What if l do?
lf l did, would that bother you?
You're crazy! You can't be serious!
Even if l liked you, we couldn't do anything anyway.
That's true.
Hey, wait!
Suwatee?
So did you tell Kenta how you feel?
And...?
Why? Do you plan to marry that old man without even touching the one you love?
Even if l touch him with the power of the star, the memory will be erased.
lf l could be with Kenta, love him...
l'd rather die with all those memories than live without them.
lf you don't do something, then l'll take him!
He's someone l wasn't supposed to love.
l didn't turn on the computer.
Hey, Kenta! You insensitive bastard!
W-What did you say? Hey!
We're going back to Heaven.
So this is goodbye!
Hope things go well with all the girls you laid! Later.
Hey, wait! Shuree!
Here Come the Gods
Take care of yourself! See you!
Don't get lonely when we don't see you anymore.
Not see me?
What about Suwatee?
Kenta, l'm sorry. This is goodbye.
Suwatee, where are you?
l really loved you, Kenta.
But there are others who love you.
So you'll be okay without me, right? So...
Suwatee, wait!
Suwatee...
Soon you'll marry the Emperor.
Are you okay, Suwatee?
Suwatee?
l don't want to!
Don't want to? But now it's...
Shuree, save me! Save me!
l don't want to leave Kenta after all!
lt's okay if l can't touch him!
l want to be by his side!
Well, aren't you a spoiled princess?
ls it really enough just to be by his side?
Yes...
Then give the piece of the star to me.
You weren't the one who stole the piece of star. l was.
l'll get married for you!
No! No way! No!
Suwatee...
Suwatee, it won't do you any good.
Give it to me.
No! No! No way!
l won't let you go!
Stop it! Stop it!
No! Be quiet now.
This way you can be by Kenta's side.
Now stop crying.
Suwatee, be good to Kenta, okay?
Goodbye!
Shuree...
Kishoten, huh? What do you want?
Emperor Shibi, look at this!
l am the one who stole the piece of star.
What was that?
So, l'm saying l'll be your wife!
Or don't you want me?
Very well.
Though your beauty has a different flavor from Suwatee's.
So, can l ask you one favor?
What is it?
lt would be hard to say no to a beauty like you.
What's happening to this room?
What's going on?
S-Shuree?
What is it? Did you forget something?
Yeah, l forgot to say something important.
What if l told you that l liked you, Kenta?
What?
Even if that were true, we couldn't...
That's true!
Sorry, Suwatee.
O spirit of the star, mirror my form!
Hide what can be seen, show what is hidden!
Your powers to me!
l can touch you!
As usual, your hands are faster than your brain.
What do you mean by that?
Kenta...
Shuree, what's happened to you?
ls this for real?
Sorry! l'm sorry.
l... l didn't know what else to do!
Hey, Kenta, don't you like me?
Well, l...
lt's okay. l understand.
l was so mean to you.
But when you said that l was pretty, it made me so happy.
l meant it. You really are pretty.
lt's okay even if you don't like me.
Just this once, make love to me.
Shuree, are you teasing me?
Believe me. l really love you, Kenta.
Suwatee, it's your own fault, because you waited too long!
Kenta, look at the real me.
l'm embarrassed after all, Kenta.
Shuree, l do like you.
l'm so happy!
Kenta, let me love you.
S-Shuree, that's...
Shuree, that's so good.
Kenta, l can't wait any more!
Kenta?
Shuree, you look so cute.
Be good to me, please.
Kenta...
Kenta, l love you!
Shuree...
After this. After this, l can forget him.
Yes! More! Kenta!
lt feels so good.
Kenta, that's...
Kenta! More! Don't stop!
Shuree...
Kenta, l'm coming. You, come too.
Let's come together!
Shuree, you were wonderful.
Kenta...
Shuree, are you crying?
Kenta, this is for you.
But you always wear this.
Yes. Don't forget about me, okay?
Please, don't forget me. Don't forget me.
Shuree! Hey!
ls that all you're going to say?
Pearl: ''No! After this, please no more!''
Makoto: ''Hehehe! Don't move around so much!''
Pearl: ''l love you! l'm never letting you go!''
Makoto: ''Wait a minute!''
l guess there's such a thing as too much love.
lt can't be!
lt's been a while, Kenta.
S-Suwatee!
Ahh, this time you do remember me!
Suwatee, why are you hanging out with this loser?
Shuree, you came back too?
Hey, Shuree, what do you mean by loser?
You're sure friendly. Who are you?
Hey, this is mine!
Why is it here?
You gave it to me.
What are you talking about?!
Don't you remember that time?
So when was ''that time?''
That time when you came here.
Me? Why would l come here?
ldiot! l can't talk about it!
Well, say it, you creep!
Did you really forget?
Shuree!
Don't tell me you used the
star's power with Kenta?
What are you talking about?
Unfair! You did!
l don't know what you're talking about.
Kenta, you ignored me, but you did it with Shuree!
Kenta, you idiot!
Now Suwatee is getting upset.
Looks like she's headed for a love triangle with Shuree!