I need to ask you a favor, Yusuke.
WouId... WouId you be
my private tutor, pIease?
PIease! It has to be you. PIease?
Yes! I'm ready for it!
Let's do it!
Right!
This is so unfair.
Reina, I want you to do the
questions in that bookIet.
Yes, Sensai.
Reina, I'm a tutor, but
there's another side to me...
I'm a boobie-loving alien!
I got you Reina!
What are you doing Sensai?
N... No...
You're amazing, Reina. Your
boobs feeI Iike marshmaIIows.
This is too sudden...
Your boobs feeI so good. Come
on, Reina. Move them yourseIf.
Sure... Like this?
Reina...
Sensai...
Reina, if you keep doing that... I...
So much cum came out of your cock...
It tastes so good...
Yusuke.
Yes?
You fucked Reina yesterday, didn't you?
Mitsuki, what are you taIking about?
I know everything.
She feII in Iove with you when she
saw you at the schooI festivaI.
That's why she asked
Yoshio to introduce you...
...and asked you to be her private tutor.
You took Reina's virginity, didn't you?
No, I haven't fucked her yet.
I'm surprised. You're so timid down here.
Momma Mitsuki's breasts... They're so big...
No!
Don't caII me Momma
Mitsuki. CaII me Mitsuki.
Yes Mitsuki!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Yusuke.
Yes?
You can onIy do this with me, okay?
If you cheat on me with
Reina, I won't forgive you.
To my Iife with giant breasts! Hurray!
It's so hot!
What are you going to teach me today?
We're going to do math today...
Is that aII we'II do today?
Of course it isn't!
Down there? You mean here?
She's just as sensitive down
here as on her breasts.
Sensai, it feeIs so good.
Sensai...
I'm coming in.
Reina, I'm going to cum.
Yes... I'm going to cum too!
Reina, I brought you some tea.
You two...
ANYONE YOU CAN DO I CAN DO BETTER
Part 2
Reina, what's the meaning of this?
The meaning of what?
I'm asking what you two were just doing!
Can't you teII? We were having sex!
What did you say?
Right, Sensai?
Oh... Sure...
Get off of each other!
Mom, what are you doing?
What are you taIking about? That's my Iine!
Yusuke!
Yes?
Which one do you Iike more? Me or Reina?
This is too sudden. I can't answer that...
The adorable Reina...
Or...
The sexy, sultry Mitsuki...
I can't pick one over the other!
Jeez!
Yusuke, if you can't make up your mind,
choose between us based on our breasts!
WeII, Yusuke?
I'm not going to Iose!
I understand, but I can't
decide just by Iooking, so...
I'II decide after I fuIIy enjoy them.
I'd better check the fIavor too.
Yes, suck my nippIes harder!
They taste great, Mitsuki.
You're paying too much attention
to mom. Suck mine too!
Of course I wiII.
Sensai!
Your breasts are so soft and fIuffy.
Sensai, do mine taste good?
They're a IittIe sour, but they taste good.
I have nothing to complain
about, as far as the flavor goes.
Their firmness and softness are great as weII.
I can't decide based on just breasts.
It feeIs great. You're both
using your tongue reaIIy weII.
How is it Yusuke?
Are you going to cum?
Yeah, it feeIs so good I
think I'm going to cum.
No fair. We want to feeI good too.
Right there...
It feeIs good there...
You're sensitive inside...
I Iike it inside. Stick your tongue
in more. Fuck me deep inside.
I feeI Iike it's vibrating aII the way inside...
Your big cock is inside me.
Look, Sensai. My pussy and your dick...
...are fucking each other
and making dirty noises.
Mom, are you feeIing good?
Yes, I feeI so good... Yusuke knows
how to use his tongue so weII...
My dirty juices keep fIowing from my pussy.
Your cum tastes so good, Mitsuki.
It's so big... it feeIs so good.
Mom...
Can I...
Come here.
Okay.
Mom... Does my pussy taste good?
Your pussy smeIIs sour
and has a distinct smeII.
Stop it! Mom...
I can't anymore, mom... I'm going to cum.
I think I'm going to cum too.
I can't anymore...
Me too!
Sensai! Sensai wake up!
Wake up!
Okay...
Sensai, which one did you Iike better?
Me, right?
What are you taIking about, mom?
Of course he Iiked me better!
Yusuke wouId never pick such puny breasts!
Sensai Iikes perky breasts
Iike mine better than yours!
What did you say? What is
that supposed to mean?
ExactIy what I said!
Don't act Iike such a wise
ass because you're young!
You're just jeaIous!
What are you taIking about, you brat!
Mitsuki, caIm down...
Reina, you caIm down too.
My Iife surrounded by giant boobs is...
This is getting strange...
Sensai, which one did you like better?
Me, right?
Sensai likes perky breasts
like mine better than yours!
What did you say? What is
that supposed to mean?
Exactly what I said!
Don't act like such a wise
ass because you're young!
You're just jealous!
I wonder what's going to happen to my
fabuIous Iife surrounded by giant boobs?
I wonder who it is?
Yes? Who is it?
Reina.
What are you doing here this Iate?
Sensai!
Sensai! I ran away from home!
PIease Iet me stay here!
My Dad came home and was
Iike, ''What's with that short skirt?''
''You're showing too much skin!''
He hasn't been home in a whiIe...
...and he stares at me. Isn't that terribIe?
Yeah, that's pretty bad. But Reina,
that has nothing to do with this.
Sensai, you're interrupting me!
Oh, sorry.
Then he said that's how I seduce
men and bring them into the house.
He got me so angry that I Ieft home.
So pIease Iet me stay here tonight.
Then I guess you can... No way! Reina!
Mitsuki must be worried... so
you need to go back home.
No? I'II make Iots of yummy
food for you. PIease?
But that's not the... You're reaIIy
going to make me good food?
Are you making fun of me? I'm
actuaIIy a great homemaker!
Stop it. Not here... I won't be abIe to cook.
Come on. You'd better pay
attention, or it'II be dangerous.
But I can't...
Reina, you're not cooking.
But you're...
You're aIready wet.
Stop! Don't say it out Ioud!
Come on. Keep cooking.
Sensai.
You're so dirty.
You're dripping your dirty juices...
But it feeIs good.
Right there!
Reina, you've gotten so much better.
Reina, it feeIs good.
Reina, wiII you show me your breasts?
You have sensitive breasts, right?
Yeah... My nippIes are sensitive too.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Stop it Sensai! I'm going to get wet
again if you're rough with them.
S... Sensai...
What is it?
I'm starting to feeI strange.
You're soaked.
My pussy is aching and I feeI
Iike I'm going to go crazy...
PIease hurry and stick your cock in me.
Fine then.
Here I come.
I can't wait any Ionger... Hurry...
Yes, Yusuke! Harder! Fuck me harder!
You're aII the way inside...
Sensai, I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to cum soon.
I'm going to cum... I'm going to cum too!
Reina.
What is it Sensai?
I think it might be better for you to go home.
It's not good for a young man and a
woman to spend the night together.
Sensai, what are you saying?
You're not too convincing,
saying it after the fact.
Anyway...
Reina...
You're stiII hard. Do you want to do it again?
Of course!
Mitsuki?
Mom?
I knew you'd be here! How couId
you run away from home Iike that!
I won't aIIow you to get the upper hand!
No, mom! He's mine!
What are you taIking about! He's mine!
Ow! Ow! You two are hurting me!
It'II be fine if you just pick me!
Sensai, you Iike me better, right?
WeII... Um...
Make up your mind!
But it's not that easy...
Yusuke, you wanted my breasts, right?
I know your dick wanted
them. They feeI great, right?
Yes... it feeIs great.
Mom! That's not fair!
Have him fondIe yours. I'm going
to have fun with his dick first.
Mitsuki...
Yes, what is it? You want me
to move my boobs harder?
Sensai, touch my breasts! I
want you to pIay with them a Iot!
Lick my breasts! Tease my nippIes!
How is it? Are you feeIing good, Yusuke?
Yes, fondIe my breasts more.
I'm impressed you haven't cum yet.
I'II tease you with my pussy next...
No!
His dick is mine!
Fine then I'II...
Yusuke, suck it hard!
Yusuke, it feeIs so good!
No, I'm going to feeI better first.
It feeIs so good... Your tongue feeIs so good!
No... I'm going to cum first. Sensai's mine...
Reina, I'm sorry. I think I'm going to cum.
No, I'm going first! I'm... I'm going to cum!
I can't hoId it anymore!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Reina.
Mom... Did you cum?
Yes, I came. Yusuke was so good,
I... You had such a sexy moan.
You, too mom.
Reina.
Mom.
See you Iater Sensai!
Goodbye, Yusuke. We'II do it again.
The storm had passed and the two went
home wet. As for me, I was sucked dry.
Rain falls and hardens the ground.
They got wet and made up, but...
Am I heading for disaster? How could
such a lustful world be upon me?
I'm coming in.
WeIcome!
Sensai, do want some beer?
Want to drink our breast miIk?
Do you want a sandwich?
Of course you'd Iike one, right?
Uh... yeah...
Do my breasts feeI good?
Mine feeI better. Right Yusuke?
Mine!
No, mine!
I said mine!
To my life with giant boobs! Hurray!