Dear Utsui, remember this day, and promise me you'll study hard. From your Teacher
Sensei!
Utsui-kun...
l'm very proud of you, you're really into your studies lately.
Never mind that!
l want you to help Asada!
She's a slave for lshino and lizuka.
Slave?
Those two are always picking on her after school.
No, no!
l'll climax! l'll climax!
Go and climax over and over!
What are you people doing?
Stop it!
Let her go now!
You think you guys can get away with this?
Sensei...
What?
Where did you get that?
l heard you're really into sex.
l want her to do me, too.
What is all this Utsui-kun?
Nothing.
They both know everything that happened the other day.
They're my buddies.
What do you mean?
You guys were both in on this?
So l want you to sign this.
Slave contract?
Then we won't pick on Asada anymore.
Are you stupid?
Stop fooling around!
Put your clothes on Asada-san.
Panty Flash Teacher Vol. 2
Results of the pop quiz were horrible.
You have exams coming up soon.
lf you don't get serious, you're all going fail.
ls that what you want?
At least try to write your names in kanji.
Fine.
l realize you folks don't like to study.
But you people are the ones who'll regret it later on!
l can't just let you people go on like this.
Hey Asatsuki-kun!
Your head, your head!
Ouch, ouch!
The answer sheet!
Asatsuki-kun...
ls there any reason why they pick on you?
No, not really.
Are you taking the heat for someone else?
Now, now Natsukawa-sensei.
lt's probably lshino and lizuka right?
You parted from your buddies?
He's one of Utsui's subordinates.
You have nothing to worry about.
But this is just way too much for a prank!
Asatsuki, just go home, okay?
Yes.
You don't have to deal with them.
Looking good there Asatsuki!
You don't want to do it with me?
l don't want to do this.
Stop complaining.
l don't want to do this anymore.
You're just like a girl.
Stop it!
Wow, it's like watching girls getting it on with each other!
Cute wiener!
Hey, take off his briefs.
lt got bigger!
Very stretchy!
Wow, his foreskin is so long!
He's got the world's longest foreskin!
Can't you tie up the ends of that?
But isn't this dirty?
Why are you people doing this?
That's because Asada isn't here.
You're the new toy.
Toy?
We'll treat you good.
Like this.
lsn't it great?
She's good at making guys climax.
She'll make you climax even if you don't want to.
So fast!
He climaxed already?
What the hell?
Premature ejaculator with a small uncircumcised cock...
...but it gets bigger after climax?
ls this possible?
But it's amazing l've never seen this before!
You!
Move!
You like to show off your big cock that much?
Then make her come!
Yeah, make me come!
So big...
Never had such a big one before...
So tight...
lt's too big and it won't fit...
Ouch!
Amazing!
Yes, l can feel it up in my uterus...
You!
Why do you look so happy?
Take that!
You bastard! Don't get carried away!
You're not the only one who's dying to do it!
Then why don't you let him suck your cock?
That sounds like fun.
Hey, crouch down!
Here!
You might be bigger than me, but mine's harder than yours!
No, l'm not doing this!
He's really serious!
ldiot, l'll never let a man suck on it, l'm kidding.
Hey, you and me should do it.
Yeah.
Yes, yes.
l think l'm going to faint.
l'm coming...
Please climax...
lnside...
Release it inside!
l can't!
Here l come Asatsuki!
Of course, you can count on me.
Here.
Thank you.
lt's like a dream to see your daughter serving us alcohol.
l can't believe she was that little girl l remember.
Thank you.
Election is almost around the corner.
My daughter Machiko will be joining me on the election car...
...and will greatly appeal to the voters!
l, Yoshiaki Natsukawa will do my best to win this election.
Once again, l thank you folks for your great support.
Cheers!
Let's beat Utsui!
That's right!
Utsui...
Natsukawa's probably regretting the fact he's running against me.
He didn't think you'd step down before the recall and come back again.
For this election, you have so many supporters backing you up.
No one can compete against you.
lf you get re-elected, no one will find out about your wrongdoings.
That stupid Natsukawa will stop interfering with us.
You'll be in power for a very long time.
No, let's head straight for the capital!
Now you're talking!
l'm home.
You look happy father.
Hiroshi.
We're just celebrating in advance, care for a drink?
No thanks.
Sensei...
Looks like you might be signing your name on this very soon.
Asada!
Help me Asada.
You can't just leave your buddies!
They're not my buddies.
Hey!
Wait!
Ohba told the teacher that l'm one of Utsui's subordinates.
l just want you to tell the teacher that l'm being threatened by them.
That's the best thing to do.
Please Asada.
Do it for me.
No!
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Stop it!
Hey Asada!
You're pathetic!
She turned you down?
Do you want to get away from me?
Do you remember who saved your family business...
...when it was doing bad?
But if you do what l say, l'll let you go free.
What?
This is serious.
You'll do it right?
lt's hard to make a living in this world.
Mayoral candidate Yoshiaki Natsukawa has come...
...to speak to you all.
We're doing our best to win tomorrow's election.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for supporting us from your cars.
He exposed the wrongful acts of the previous mayor.
He's the one that will completely change your city.
He's Yoshiaki Natsukawa!
l'm his daughter and l'm also supporting this campaign as well.
He's a reliable man. He's an honest man.
She's got such a nice ass.
He's Yoshiaki Natsukawa!
What the hell is this?
Ouch!
What happened?
What is this?
lt's a vicious way of interfering with our election.
lto!
Yes!
Take them off!
Take off every one of them!
Call the police as well!
This was in the letter that we just received from an anonymous person.
What the hell is this?
To Utsui?
Student teacher relationships are against school policy...
...but you got involved with Utsui's son?
Please.
The election is almost over.
You keep your mouth shut!
What do you want?
An assembly is in the gymnasium.
You created those dirty posters, right?
Posters? What are you talking about?
Stop fooling around!
That was taken at your house...
Did anything happen at my house?
l don't remember.
Don't accuse people without having any evidence.
Besides, you have other things to worry about.
What?
Oh no!
Asatsuki-kun!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Let me go! Don't try to stop me!
No! Don't do this!
Why are you doing this?
Sensei...
...if l keep going like this, lshino and lizuka are gonna end up killing me.
They forced me to create your posters.
What?
l see.
l don't want to cause anymore trouble for others.
That's why l tried to kill myself...
Asatsuki-kun...
Sensei!
Wait Asatsuki-kun!
l really like you Sensei!
So please!
But l'm your teacher!
l can't...
Shut up!
You had sex with Utsui, didn't you?
How did you know?
You did it with Utsui, but you don't want to do it with me?
Do you hate me?
Wow...
lt's so big!
Sensei!
lt's not like that!
Then what is it?
You like having sex, right? Utsui told me so.
What...
How many people did you do it with?
Why do you say such a thing?
Because you're so wet!
No! Don't look!
Amazing...
We're not done yet.
Asatsuki-kun...
So big!
l never felt like this before!
Slower...
Move slower...
Today's school assembly will take place in the gymnasium.
Please get there as quickly as possible.
Sensei, l want you to do me a favor.
l'll do anything you want.
l want to see you climax on your own.
You masturbate too, right?
Yes.
Show it to me, then l'll never contemplate suicide.
Fine.
But promise me that you'll never do it again.
Mic check. Testing 1 , 2...
Sensei, use this.
What's that noise?
This is great...
lt feels good...
Everyone go back to your rooms at once!
Hey technical crew! Turn this off!
Much deeper, deeper...
lt's inside really deep...
lt can't be...
l did what you told me to do.
Good job.
Natsukawa-sensei?
Natsukawa-sensei!
What?
What are you doing?
l see, so you're the one responsible for this.
Way to go!
Best is yet to come.
You're very bold.
You didn't have to broadcast your...
Stop!
l'm worried about you, Sensei.
After what you did, you think they'll let you teach at this school?
Even if they tried to keep it quiet it'll be very hard for you.
But there's one way out of this.
What?
You have to be my slave.
l'm sure you won't be satisfied with that, so l'll play this nice and fair.
lf my father gets elected, you'll have to be my slave.
What do you think?
Stop mocking me!
You don't think you're father will win?
Those dirty posters were quite popular.
lf your father loses, it'll be all your fault.
Think about my offer, panty flash teacher.
lt's not increasing.
We're not getting many votes from places that had those posters put up.
They really attacked places that were full of conservative people.
lt's over.
lt's all my fault.
Natsukawa-sensei.
Ohba-sensei...
Right now, the school is in chaos.
Everyone's trying hard to cover up your mess.
Let me ask you again.
What were you doing in that room?
Come on, you can tell me.
Let's go somewhere else.
What?
Let's go to a hotel.
Stop messing around!
Excellent.
Do you know what you're about to do?
l don't know.
Can't you guess?
You'll touch my body and remove my panties.
And?
You'll get me naked and suck on my nipples.
You'll also stick your fingers in my cunt.
Then you'll take your cock and...
You're wrong!
lt's a bit different.
You'll have to beg me to do those things.
Hurry!
Utsui-kun...
Sensei, you're wet.
No!
Now, what do you say?
My...
My dirty cunt!
l want you to play with my dirty cunt.
Well done.
lt's so wet.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
That's nice to hear.
And what do you want me to do next?
Hurry up and tell me.
l want you to take off my panties...
...and stick your cock into my wet, dirty cunt!
Then take your clothes off.
l'm cold...
lt'll be warm soon.
Are you ready?
Please.
You're still teaching right now because of my father's influence.
Don't you forget it.
Yes.
You're mine now, right?
l'm your slave.
lt feels good, Utsui-kun...
lt feels good...
More, more...
Sensei...
Utsui-kun...
You're looking real cute.
No!
Yes!
lt feels good!
More, more!
l'm coming!
We're just getting started, panty flash teacher.