Hurry! Hurry!
Hey! Hey! Wait a minuite!
This way! This way!
Teacher! Teacher! Hurry up!
Nagahashi-sensei!
Ezaki Hinami, what are you photographing?
A picture for the schooI newspaper of a student-teacher standing in a fieId of sunflowers!
That's nice...
l can see your panties.
What?
Yaaaaah!
Obscene, dirty, sex-crazed, pervert teacher!
What are you grinning about?
Nothing...
Where's Sakaguchi-san?
The desk editor isn't here.
Huh?
His bad back laid him up.
A bad back?
So... Senpai, please go out with me.
Go out with you?
It's for research! research!
That was hard work.
Senpai, you're getting old.
Why the hell, do I have to be in charge of a project Iike ''Best Date Spots"?
It's just until the desk editor's back is better.
Until then, you get to go on dates with the beauty of this century.
And, the company pays for it all!
You should consider yourself lucky!
Dummy, l'm going home.
Wait! Senpai! There's still one location left!
There's more?
Yes!
Um... the climax of the date is a "petite hotel".
What the heIl is that?
It's what they call a love hotel.
For Senpai, the pIayboy, it should be a great pIace!
Owww! The least you couId do is to make a sarcastic comment before you hit!
So, this means what? That you're going with me to a love hotel?
Well, of course, it's understandable that an over-sexed man like you...
wouldn't be able to control yourseIf
if you went to a love hotel with a super cute and sexy woman Iike me.
But! This is research! research!
Huh?
Forget the super cute, and let's finish this.
But, I don't want you to forget...
Waaah! Senpai, take a look!
Hey, why did you pay to get in here?
You got permission to use this for the story, right?
WeII, that is... it's what's known as a undercover report.
Dummy.
There's no point to getting in here undercover.
What are you planning?
Planning? Noway!
Is that right? Well, go ahead and finish this yourself.
Aaaaah! Wait, Senpai!
Give me a reason.
Um... Well, I thought a place like this might get you in the mood.
Huh? In the mood?
A lady can't just say "seduce me".
You just did.
l-l've played around a lot, too, you know!
This is nothing!
But, I wanted you to feel important so...
Waaaaah! Senpai!
Wait!
Then let's do it, Hina-the-pIaygirl...!
You're beautiful, Hinami.
Trust me, and reIax, okay?
Thank you Senpai, l'm really happy.
l am, too. l was waiting for this day.
That's a nice pose, Hina-chan.
ls this what lovers do together?
I didn't know...
WeII, damn, you want to quit already?
l'm perfectly fine! l've done this a million times.
That aside, you're covered in that stuff.
Senpai, you really are nice.
I almost believed you weren't.
Hmm...?
There you go!
Senpai, you're terrible!
Am I?
Please be more considerate.
What are you doing?!
I'm going to shave this damn hair. lt doesn't suit you.
What? Oh, no...
Don't move, or something important might get cut.
Oh? Did you like that?
No! That's not it!
Aaah! My hair...
l can see everything.
It's nothing to Iaugh about. It's too embarassing...
Now. Even if you've played around, l bet you've never had this inside you.
Of course, not! Please, turn off the microphone!
But, you're making some good sounds.
Now, I'm putting it in.
Hey! Wait! Time-out!
Ah! Wait Senpai! l'm sorry! l'm sorry!
What is it Hina-the-playgirl?
You already know!
Know what?
It's my first time to have sex.
You should have said that from the start, you and your stupid pride.
I'm sorry! I thought if l said I'd played around, it wouId be Iess pressure on you.
lts all the same to me.
You're a brute! A heartIess beast! You're going to rape a virgin like it's nothing?!
Who asked who out?
I did...
It hurts!
l didn't know it hurt this much! It was a mistake in my pIan...!
They will see you soon
This coffee is coId.
l'm sorry, I'II bring you another!
She's kind of nasty...
Hinami. Did a writer recommended by Professor Akiyama, come by?
Senpai!
lt's been a long time, Shouma.
Ayane! Why is she here?
Oh, didn't you know? Right now, l'm an assistant for Professor Akiyama.
Senpai! ln a place Iike this?!
A place like this can be a turn on, too.
You're a real sex maniac.
Your mouth isn't working.
You're easily aroused.
How would l know when l was aIone?
I'm cuming!
Drink it all.
Good girl. l'll give you a IittIe extra.
Huh?
I can't believe you were a virgin untiI just the other day.
l'm embarassed.
Looks like youre grooming yourself down there.
I'II give you a prize.
Yes, please.
It's stiIl tight.
ln time, it will be perfectly my size.
That makes me happy.
Ayane, what are you thinking?
But, people dont change Shouma...
You are the same as before.
The reaI character of a person can't change.
You can't Iove another person.
Shut up!
Because you can't trust anyone.
Shut upl You whore!
W-wait!
AII you're good for is a hole!
That's mean.
I don't want to. PIease, no more!
Shit! Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
I can't hold back anymore, cum inside me, cum inside me please!
That's why the Japanese music world must continue to change.
Will that do?
Thank you. lt should make a good story.
And, the photos are great, too! Looking like a nice intelIigent oIder man type.
Make a quick withdraw.
Yes, sir!
By the way, Narahashi-kun. Can I have a IittIe of your time?
Yes?
l have something l want to ask you.
Huh. Aren't you Ezaki-san? What are you doing?
Shibazaki-sensai...
Me? But that is...
I think this is a good opportunity for you.
How about it?
Please, give me time to think about it.
There's not a Iot of time. I hope you'lI give me a good answer.
Excuse me...
What?
Why are you still here?
No reason I was bored.
She was supposed to become my sister.
Supposed to?
My mother and her father were going to get married...
but in the end, it didn't get as far as marriage...
How about you? What are you doing?
I'm waiting for Senpai.
That's his sister.
Looks Iike you were dumped.
What are you saying?!
I work under him, so I can't just leave without him.
That's why l will always...
Since both of us got dumped, why don't we go have a drink?
That why I said...
Both of us got dumped...?
Probably, Shouma is going to America
Don't call him "Shouma'' like that! You don't know him!
His kindness is just a mask to hide his true seIf.
The reaI Shouma is not kind at all.
PIease, don't do anymore, Shouma...
l leave you tied up for onIy one day, and you're aIready begging.
You just pissed where you sat... It's perfect for a whore Iike you...
Don't say that. l was bad, Master Shouma. Please touch me kindIy...
What a sight, you whore. I'm gonna do you thoroughly!
Why are you acting all cool at an Oden shop?
Senpai is always mean to me, and enjoys it.
He's not the least kind... But, that's really...
is way of showing his love for me, Not!
She can't hold her liquor.
What about the beautiful sister...
No way he's leaving his cute little Hina alone and going to America.
You don't know anything, do you?
Hmmm... if you look closely, she's actually kind of pretty.
Huh? Shibazaki-sensai...
Stay still, and l'll make you feel good.
Good?
That tickles!
Hmmm... ls that the way it is?
l've thought of an interesting idea, Shouma.
But, it was a relief that it wasn't so bad.
lt is so bad. l have to stay for a week.
But, since you're here, Iets have them check you completely, okay?
Kuu, you're mean.
Nii-sama...!
Huh?
They want somebody over there.
l wanted to recommend you, who was one of my top students.
For you to stay in Japan not using your talents is a waste for the entire music world.
Ahhh! I'm finaIIy home!
I'm home again, front door!
She's over doing it.
lt can't be heIped. She was supposed to be gone a week, but it turned into a month.
It was to be expected when the test resuIts were bad.
Anyway, Chi-chan is better, so tonight we'll celebrate with a party!
America? At least a year? Nii-sama just came home. l don't want him to go...!
Last night, Chisato was reaIIy excited.
Yeah
What's the matter?
You saw us Iast night, didn't you?
You've turned into a bitch in heat, Kuu.
Don't say that...
You've completely turned into my bitch.
lts so embarassing.
Hinami! What's the meaning of this?!
You've caIIed in sick for two weeks! That devil of a desk editor made me do your work!
How fierce! Sounds like you really like this girl.
Ayane...!
l'm cuming! l'm cuming! l'm cuming! I'm cuming...!
Ayane! What are you doing here?!
Just what it looks like.
The same thing you're aIways doing.
That hurt...!
I dont know what you're thinking, but stay away from Hinami!
That's rich, coming from you!
Shut up!
Don't ever come here again. Understand?!
Egotist...
Wow... You must be really good at photography.
That's a manual camera, isn't it?
Ah! Can you teII?
That's a good angle, and you've framed it weIl. Ezaki, you may have taIent.
Hinami... Hinami...!
Wake up. Hinami...
Senpai...
Shouma... People can't change their true selves.
Neither you... or l...
Yeah, I remember now.
Yes... The reason l became a photographer was because you praised me.
Of course, since it was my first love who paised me, I was traumatized.
Do you know the correct meaning of trauma?
Did l make a mistake? Wait, don't you feel something at the "first love" part?
Not really.
This man is my first love, l have the worst luck.
l'm thinking of going to America.
Senpai is making Iove to me tenderly...
Tenderly for the first time...
Senpai...
From now on, where ever he might go
or what ever might become of him, I have
and l will always
No matter what, Senpai will...