Lord!
Guide us Crusaders to
the Holy Land, Jerusalem.
Lord.
Where is this ship going?!
Isn't it going to Jerusalem?
How foolish!
You're going to be sold
as slaves on the Ivory Coast.
You're mistaken!
We're going to Jerusalem
as ordered by the Pope!
I am the leader, Hans.
You've been sold by the Pope.
Wanna see the contract?
What?!
- Hans?! What is going on?
- Tell us!
Lord!
We believed in you. Is this how
you treat us in return?!
Lord!
Johann! Pierre!
Marco!
Michel!!
I no longer believe in God!
For my friends who've been
betrayed...
...someday...
...someday, I shall take revenge!!
I will become a fallen angel...
...and dispel our disgrace!
Working hard as usual, I see.
Old Sage!
Has there been any change
in your wife's condition?
No, thanks to you.
Except for her eyes,
she's doing quite well.
I've obtained a good herb.
I'll come by later on.
Thank you so much.
How peaceful...
How truly peaceful...
Indeed.
Since the Amakusa Restoration...
...the world has never seen
any wars.
It's as if time has stopped.
Oh, no.
The eternal flow of time rushes
forth with certainty.
As long as there is no
countercurrent...
What?
Oh, nothing. Just talking
to myself, that's all.
Say, isn't today the anniversary
of the Amakusa Restoration and...
...of those who served the cause,
the St. Michaela Female Crusade?
Oh, that's right.
Well, I should go offer them
a flower or something.
Excuse me.
This world, without national
or religious divisions...
The world without wars
amongst peoples...
This is the fruit of the Amakusa
Restoration, initiated...
...by these Female Crusaders of
St. Michaela's College.
However, after the Restoration,
the history has been erased...
...between the Great War of East
Asia and the Shohwa period.
Am I the only one that knows
this lost history?
The Restoration literally turned
back time in the process.
Thus, whoever remembers even
a shred of the lost time...
...must be terminated.
No matter who it may be.
Yuki?
Daisuke... died in battle...
Yuki.
Calm down, Yuki.
Who's Daisuke?
Died in battle?
There is no war anywhere.
The Restoration in Amakusa was
the last such thing.
You're right.
The Female Crusade overturned
the feudal government.
Then, the Roman Catholic Church
and the Holy Roman Empire...
...were also destroyed.
That's right. No more religions
and no more nations.
No more rotten wars that put
people against each other.
All thanks to
"Amakusa Hans" Aiko.
I don't know what's gotten
into me.
All I do is cause you trouble.
But... for some reason...
Every year, when I hear the bell
that marks the anniversary...
...I get such a headache.
...As if some unknown being is
shrieking deep inside my head.
But, I'm all right now.
I'm so sorry.
Why? Why is it?
Aiko, how's the wound?
Kozue.
It's healed a great deal.
I'll be back to my old self
real soon.
I'm embarrassed to have
failed you.
But you haven't.
After the uprising at
St. Michaela's College...
we've waged war in Amakusa,
then against the feudal army...
...and on and on till we finally
took the Edo Castle here.
We thank you for pushing
the battle front.
Sorry you had to get hurt.
Nothing to be sorry about.
St. Michaela's College...
Even after all this, I can still
remember it like yesterday.
Pardon me, but I'm Aiko Mimura,
the new transfer student.
You have some gall,
my dear new student.
Where is your crucifix?
Dyed hair is against college
regulation!
So are those shoes and socks!
Not to mention piercing!!
Everyone's all alike?
Wouldn't it negate identity?
Defiance calls for guidance!
Wow! An S & M show?
Ah! Hit me harder, please!
Oh, harder! Right there!
Mimura!
Aiko Mimura!
You have violated regulations
and rebelled against the Sister.
Therefore, in the name of
the Female Crusade,
we shall penalize you!
In the name of the Crusade,
No way... It's a joke, right?
It must be a joke...
A penalty will be served!
I couldn't believe how fierce
Rika and everyone were.
That's how we got acquainted
for the first time.
No sooner did I join the college
than I was on display...
...as an example of bad behavior.
But that's how I got to know
the Dean's right-hand man...
Daisuke Karino, and learn about
his plot against St. Michaela's.
And...
Devil!
You've come to ruin the sublime
mission of the Female Crusade.
You're the Devil!
The Devil?
Does the Devil...
Does the Devil have...
...these on her back?
Wing marks...
An angel?!
I confided everything to Rika.
I told her that Aiko Mimura...
...is an alias for Hans,
the leader of the Crusade...
...and about the tragedy of my
fellow crusaders back in 1212.
The same thing is about to
happen at St. Michaela's.
Using the name of God...
the Dean purports to prepare
you women for acting careers.
But in fact, it's a front for
a secret military mission...
...carried out by Daisuke Karino,
called the Michaela Project...
whereby you will be sent to the
battlefield as sex slaves.
That's a lie.
If I showed you proof I am
Hans in spite of being a woman...
would you believe me?
An androgyny...
Love is born out of freedom.
Forced celibacy is a feigned
myth borrowed from religion.
Come on...
You're an angel?
I'm not an angel blessed
with the grace of God.
I'm a fallen angel...
here to abolish God!
Now I need your help, Rika.
Hans...
No... Aiko!
Thus began our battle.
I am Hans Heilner!!
Then, in the battle against
Shiroh of Amakusa...
Please accept my warm welcome.
I am Shiroh Tokisada of Amakusa.
What do you want us to do?
In this part of the world,
I am God.
Let's fight together.
Paradise is near.
No!
We have killed many gods! No god
is exempt anywhere in the world!
I see...
Let me show you my godly power!
You impostor!!
There is no God.
Don't be fooled!
Rika!
Rika!!
Hans... I love you.
At least, I can die
knowing a first love.
Thank you, Hans... Aiko...
Rika...
RIKA!!
Rika Ikeda...
That's my name?
I don't know.
Together with Hans Aiko, Rika
revolted at St. Michaela's...
...and died in Amakusa.
You're her departed spirit.
Died in Amakusa?!
I died?
Does that mean I'll never see
Aiko... or Hans, again?
I want to see Aiko,
my first love...
Do you want to see her?
Do you want to see
"Amakusa Hans" Aiko?
Who are you?
How is it?
The back of the pupil
is damaged.
Here, gramps.
If this doesn't heal it,
it might just be incurable.
I don't care if my eyes ever
return to normal again.
Oh, stop it.
You mustn't think like that.
Your condition, one might say,
is psychological.
It depends on your attitude.
My attitude?
There's something you don't want
to see. That's your problem.
Something I don't want to see?
Right.
Old Sage, what could it be?
You shouldn't brood over it.
Right, Yayoi?
Yes. Sooner or later, you will
remember. Just wait and see.
Do you think so?
Sure.
Say... may I ask you
one more thing?
What is it?
The dead...
Is it possible to raise the dead?
Raise the dead?
It's not impossible, but
it's a pain in the neck.
I can communicate with the dead.
I recalled a certain woman
of college age.
Her name is Rika Ikeda.
Rika Ikeda?
The one who went from
St. Michaela's to Amakusa...
...and died for the cause of
the Female Crusade?
Yes, she served the Restoration.
Alongside the leader,
"Amakusa Hans" Aiko...
she became a much respected figure.
Why on earth did you?
When I recall her, I feel as if
I'm with the "me" of old.
Dead before fulfilling her love,
she seems unable to pass on.
Though I've consummated my own,
there's another "me" inside...
that has lost her first love
and is crying, as it were.
Do you use a particular
mediumistic incantation?
Yes.
I've tried to revive her but
she disappears like a phantom.
Because the spirit has no flesh.
Her consciousness is intact
but her body is long gone.
Then I can't?
When you don't have the body,
you provide a substitute.
For instance...
Here's something that could
replace the body.
A soulless but mobile doll.
If I could recall the spirit
and plant it on the doll!
Yes, but...
It is only a substitute,
the spirit won't live long.
Besides, Yuki...
One wrong move, and your own
soul could be taken.
I don't care.
Humor my one and only wish, please.
A living and vital ghost.
Thy name is nothingness.
Out of nothingness cometh
nothingness.
However, nothingness hath life.
By forces yet unseen,
I shall bestow life in thee.
Non cogito, ergo non cogito.
Non sum, ergo non sum.
How much longer must thou
sleep on a lotus a bed?
The evening of the Sabbath
hath now expired.
The dead, raise thyself slowly,
as it is thy wish.
Dear dream!
Dear dream.
How much longer will thou sleep
on the bed of nirvana?
The banquet of Sabbath
is all but through.
The Devil, raise thyself slowly,
as it is thy wish.
Dear dream.
Do you recognize me?
Wake up! Say your name!
Rika Ikeda.
Do you recognize the name
"Amakusa Hans" Aiko?
"Amakusa Hans" Aiko...
St. Michaela Female Crusade...
Aiko!!
Aiko Mimura!
Daisuke!!
I want to see her!
I want to see Aiko!!
Oh, no! Calm her down, Yayoi!
Yes!
Aiko Mimura... Daisuke...
It was not a mistake.
My memory was not mistaken.
Aiko...
Yuki, what are you conniving?
I want to recover the lost memory.
No, I want to know the truth!
You mustn't!
You said to remember
what I don't want to see.
I would give up my soul for it!
But...
When do I surrender my soul?
"Time, be still.
You are beautiful."
The moment you feel that way.
Time, be still.
You are beautiful.
But I won't let you! Yayoi.
Yes!
Wait!
What an evil-natured woman...
What you wish to know
and are afraid to remember.
What lies in the turmoil
of conflicting emotions.
It is the other history.
The other history?
This time, you'll have
to fight me.
You know the other history.
Please tell me what really happened.
Please answer me, Old Sage.
Gotten old.
Rika Ikeda...
Rika Ikeda, can you hear me?
Rika Ikeda,
do you recognize me?
Yes...
Kozue, what's on your mind?
The same thing that's on
yours, probably.
What?
That our mission isn't over yet.
When we revolted at
St. Michaela's...
...our plan was to take the time
tunnel in the chapel...
...in order to help Hans save
his fellow crusaders, no?
Back to Rome in 1212?
No can do. Aiko's still recovering.
I know that. She's spent.
We can let her rest awhile.
You mean?
We can go without her.
Kozue, don't forget
Aiko is Hans.
What do you mean
"we can go without her"?
The St. Michaela Crusade has
already proven its worth...
...through the success against
the feudal government.
I disagree.
I'm staying.
Well, whoever wants to stay
should stay.
I'll take my group with me.
What's the matter, Mayumi?
It's about Kozue and her group...
What about Kozue?
They left for Rome.
Rome?!
Johann!
Johann!!
Pierre.
Hey, Pierre. I knew
you would volunteer, too.
I'm Marco.
Nice to meet you, Pierre.
Nice to meet you.
I'm gonna be the first to get
to the Holy Land, Jerusalem.
Only if you can beat me.
Pierre...
Isn't Hans with you guys?
He's the leader.
He must've arrived ahead of us
to take direct orders...
...from the Pope.
He's the leader?!
Among the men in all of
the Holy Roman Empire...
Hans is the most faithful, after all.
Besides he's...
...also the most skilled!
Oh, let me introduce you to
Francois from the Frank Kingdom.
Hi, I'm Francois. I won't be
fazed by the male majority!
She's a peppy one.
I'd have to be, to enlist
in the Crusade.
You're right.
My dear faithful.
On this very day, I am
overjoyed to receive you all.
As you already know, there have
been many crusades to reclaim...
...Jerusalem, which has been
taken away from us...
...by the Seljuk Turks.
The reason I have invited you
younger adults at this time...
...is because you are
righteous and pure.
That is, you are angels who
have been blessed...
...with the grace of God.
Older adults have failed to
take back the Holy Land.
But, not you!
You are angels, therefore
God's servants.
To prove it, you have wings
on your backs.
Those with little faith may miss
them, but I can see them!
This Crusade is certain
to succeed!
Go directly to Marseilles!
Marseilles gives way to
the Mediterranean Sea.
There, your virtuous prayers
will be answered by God...
...and the sea will part.
Just as the Red Sea did
for Moses.
Do not have fear.
The Lord is with you.
The parted sea will lead to
the Holy Land, Jerusalem.
It will guide you all.
Now, I will introduce you
to your leader...
...Hans Heilner!!
- That's our Hans!
- Hey, Hans.
- That's Hans?
- Our leader.
The Lord will always watch over us.
Together, we shall win
the holy war!
the holy war!!
In the name of Love and
the Holy Ghost...
...may glory be with the Crusade!
May glory be with the Crusade!!
Someone named Gonza wants
to see Aiko.
It's been awhile.
What brings you here, Gonza?
Yuki seems to have awakened.
She has?
Has she been here?
No.
I can't find her.
I thought she'd definitely
end up on this side...
Where could she possibly?
I'll be damned!
You know?
Kozue's group is in danger!
Prepare to leave!
Aiko?
Get everyone ready!
We're charging into
the Holy Roman Empire!!
Oh?
Rika.
You'd better keep up, Misayo.
It's Rika. Rika!
No way. In Amakusa, she...
But, look!
Rika!! You were alive!!
When I came to, I was being
looked after by a fisherman.
That's why we couldn't find you.
It was a deadly war.
There were bodies everywhere.
Hard to tell who was who.
But, I'm so glad to see you.
Sorry I caused you such trouble.
But, how did you get here?
Yeah, how did you get here?
I heard you took the time
tunnel from Amakusa...
...and overthrew the feudal
government.
So, I knew that Aiko...
...or rather, Hans would bring
you here to save his fellows.
Sharp thinking as usual, Rika.
With Rika, we're unbeatable.
What a boost to our morale!
Absolutely!
Did you see Aiko Mimura?
She's not there.
She's not?
But Kozue Takemiya and her group
are headed toward the Vatican.
They are planning to join
the Crusade.
I knew it! That's why.
What do you mean?
If I put together your story
and what I know...
the Amakusa Restoration impacted
the whole world...
because Aiko was Hans Heilner,
the leader of the Crusade.
The World Restoration must have
been led by the students...
...of St. Michaela's.
Miss Yuki...
What?
Why do you obsess about
these things?
You need only do as I say.
- But...
- BUT?!
Rika Ikeda! You've died once,
have you not?
Don't forget you owe me
for reviving you!
Yes, ma'am.
Your second life won't last
very long.
When your mission is complete,
I'll allow you to live freely.
I shall infiltrate the Crusade
as one of the soldiers.
You stay with the students
of St. Michaela's.
Everything is my fault for leaving
it up to Daisuke.
If I myself had fought,
we wouldn't have lost the war.
Daisuke?
Miss Yuki?
I am Aaron.
I am a soldier of the Crusade,
Aaron.
Aaron?
Everyone, we finally make
our departure tomorrow.
It is imperative that
you act responsibly!
I've already relayed your order.
Don't worry!
Hey...
Looking like a real leader, Hans.
I've been trusted with the duty
to bring every last one of you...
...to the Holy Land ofJerusalem.
Hans, did you know?
We've been joined by a support
troop from Japan today?
A support troop?
They say they're students of
St. Michaela's College.
All female, to boot!
All female?
Must be a courageous bunch.
Where's Japan?
It's an island in the Orient,
they say.
I see... Is it farther than Mongolia?
Come to think of it...
The one who came here yesterday
is also from Japan, isn't she?
Excuse me.
I'm Rika Ikeda, from Japan.
I'm Hans Heilner. How do you do?
Hans... You are Hans.
But, right now, you don't
know me yet.
Rika!
You're here already.
Hi there.
We got separated on the way.
We were worried.
I knew we would find you here.
Just as you said, Kozue.
Allow me to introduce you
to my friends.
This is their leader, Hans...
Hans Heilner.
That's Hans.
The Hans before he came
to St. Michaela's.
The Hans who doesn't know us.
Well... so you are Hans.
Wow!
You know Hans?!
That's incredible!
The word about Hans has
reached the Orient!
Oh, I'm Michel.
Pierre.
Johann.
And Marco. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kozue Takemiya.
Kumi Aoike.
Misayo Hagio.
Watoko Yamato.
Welcome to a faraway land.
I must tell you...
We have come all this way
with the intent...
...to dissuade you from going
to Jerusalem.
On the contrary, you shouldn't
even go to Marseilles.
Why?!
It's a long, long way to
Marseilles.
You would be faced with fever
and disasters.
Nonsense! We have accepted
those challenges!
Hardship is the path
we've chosen.
Suffering is the Way of the Lord.
It's the way of Love.
Do you support us or not?
We do.
Then, why?
If you insist on going, we'd go
with you, of course...
What are you trying to say?
Right now, this is all
we can tell you.
Excuse us.
Go figure.
Some support troop.
Aren't you going with
your fellows?
Well, no.
What could they be thinking?
Do you know?
Yes. Well, no...
Who's there?
My name is Aaron.
I've enlisted in the Crusade.
I have something very important
to tell Your Holiness.
Come in.
What is it you want to tell me?
Will you please trust me?
I'd have to hear you first.
I shall offer my body to you
so that you could trust me.
You...
You are!
An androgyny!!
"An eye for an eye" is one of
the heathen sayings, naturally.
But I find myself up against
vicious treacheries...
...of the Devil's own
androgynous servant.
The Devil's servant?
The Devil is coming to hinder
the expedition of the Crusade.
No matter what happens, you
must get them to Jerusalem.
Or, at least, to Marseilles.
For your own good...
What exactly do you know?!
Everything!
That is why I am offering
my body to you.
What do you take me, the Pope...
I...
I know all about your secret
interest, Your Holiness.
My lips are sealed.
So, please, enjoy my body
to your heart's content.
My life is on the line.
The end justifies the means.
I trust you... trust you...
Even if I have to discard
this body of mine...
I shall consummate my true love.
Daisuke...
I promise you I will bury
all the Aiko Mimuras...
...of the world.
Yuki!
I won't let you have your way!
Marco and his fellows...
And our own St. Michaela's
fellows...
I won't let them be sold
to slave traders!!
Let's go, everyone,
to the Holy Roman Empire!!
Yeah!
As long as I... and Hans... can
escape death by you...
...for the sake of this world
I have built...
I declare war, Yuki!