Since I was very young, I had been a cry-baby.
I had always followed someone's back.
Suddenly, I lost that back to follow.
Onii-chan
Wait just a minute...!
Wait for what?
Um nothing. Please, go ahead?
"Go ahead"? You.
No!
It's so strange. Is this what they mean by "feeling it"?
You can't! A place like that.
If this is no good, then where would be good?
But...
l didn't know it would feel like this.
l can't believe it.
Onii-chan's finger is moving around.
What's happening to me?
lf you do it so hard!
You're wet. It's pretty good, for your first time.
Don't say things like that.
He can tell, things like that.
It's embarrassing
Onii-chan
You're putting it in?
It hurts!
Onii-chan! It hurts!
He's entering me. Onii-chan is inside me!
Onii-chan. Onii-chan. Please I...!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan. Onii-chan. Onii-chan!
Is it finished?
Was it painful?
Not as much as l thought.
Something is still inside me.
Um nothing...
Someday, l knew this would happen.
From that time when I saw him again so suddenly.
Was Brother any different?
Yeah
I understand
l'll come home early today.
See you.
So he's back.
You're the one who asked me to play, so why are you behind me?
Because, l can see your back.
What?
That because
Onii-chan
So I can see your back.
Brother?
That hurt!
You hit me with your fist!
You hit a delicate Iady with your fist!
Senpai! Look at the bump on my head! Here, right here! Senpai!
Kuu?
What the?
Ten years, you never even wrote.
Then you suddenly appear?
Tonight was supposed to be a heart felt reunion, and it's ruined!
''Suddenly appear", like a bug?
lts your fault for working where l had an interview.
How can you say that to a poor working student?
What is it?
Kuu, you've changed a lot.
You use to be quiet and cried alI the time.
Well of course.
Anybody would after being Ieft behind for ten years.
Okay, okay.
But the truth is.
The truth is l haven't changed at all, Onii-chan.
Geez, She's out after having her fun.
She was happy to see you.
We waited such a Iong time for you to come home.
Kuu and you as weIl
Made me realize that ten years is a long time.
Neither of you seem like the two I left behind.
Nii-sama. Which do you like better, the new or old me?
It's not what l like or not.
But I always want to be the Chisato that you love.
Kuu will catch cold.
Oh, you're right.
What, it's wet, oh no, why?
Hey Kuu! Are you still sleeping?
Don't come in without warning!
What? Are you sleeping in the nude?
Don't say stupid stuff like that!
Hurry up and come down. You'll be late.
Brother!
About that...
I'll go warm up the engine.
Aren't you lucky, Kuu?
Yeah
Kuu?
What's wrong with her?
l'm surprised that you're a student here.
What's wrong with it?
You used to like art better.
Oh? Did I?
Yes, you did. The only music you listened to was my violin.
I found that my talent was in music instead of art.
You said it, not me.
What is it?
Teacher
Kanoko?
Aren't you Kanoko?
It's been three years! How are you?
Yeah
How is the professor?  Tell him I said hello.
Okay, l'll tell him.
She is Professor Akiyamas only daughter. l used to be her tutor.
She's a good girl, but shes got a phobia about foreigners.
She's afraid huh. I see.
It's my day off, but I spend it shoveling snow.
We did it all ourselves while you were gone, so no complaining.
When it's a Iittle warmer, I'll go with you on a drive as a thank you.
That's just you wanting to go for a drive.
You could say so. But it's okay, right?
To me a day off is just that, I'm off.
A drive? No way.
Geez! Tightwad!
Hey!
This goes in the trash!
What a waste!
You smoke too much!
I haven't seen you for awhiIe.
About five years?
I heard your were working in Sakaguchi's editing department.
And you also got two lovely relatives.
What do you want to say?
We're alone, so you might as well tell the truth.
Do you Iike your new toys?
Shut the hell up.
It hasn't changed. This is the same too.
I was asked just to drive you home. I'm leaving.
It's just like you to pretend not to understand.
Stop it. l've changed from how l was.
Are you serious?
You are the same as before.
The real character of a person can't change.
You can't love another person.
Shut up!
Because you can't trust anyone.
Shut up! You whore!
Whore? How can you say that.
You calIed me just because you wanted me to rape you! You nymphomaniac!
That's right. See, this much.
Since l saw your face.
Wait! Not so rough!
Don't think you can controI me, Ayane!
No! Wait! Please!
You might act stuckup, but this part of you is as loose as ever.
Don't say things like that.
I'll rape you.
Ayane. This is what you want, right!
Wait!
AIl you're good for is a hole!
How can you!
No
I don't want to. Please no more!
No!
Damn it! Damn it!
That's right. People don't change, Shouma.
Onii-chan!
Chi-chan?
Onii-chan?!
ls this all?
Yeah. It's not much, is it?
Oh my are you moving?
Yeah. Kuu suddenly decided she wanted to live alone.
Geez, when she has such a nice place to Iive in.
It'll be lonely without you.
l've been thinking about it for awhiIe.
Since brother came back, it's a good oportunity.
Kuu
You can come back anytime. This is your home.
Yeah, l know. I'm sorry for being selfish, Chi-chan.
Let's get going.
Yeah.
Kuu...!
l'm sure she'll be back.
Yeah. She can't cook anything except stirfried noodIes.
Even though its a furnished apartment, you'll stilI need to buy a lot of things.
You want to go tomorrow?
Sure. Here's an ashtray.
Bought it the other day, very considerate of me huh?
I thought you would tell me to stop smokeing.
Because
I thought you wouIdn't come visit me.
Kuu
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan
I did something bad, didn't l?
Chi-chan really needs you.
That's why when I think
Kuu
When I think that because of me, Chi-chan might suffer.
When I think that l...
lts all right if Onii-chan loves Chi-chan.
Because l will love that Onii-chan.
lt should be around here.
Huh? You're Kanoko-chan, right?
Yes
I just got here myself. l wonder where those two went?
Sorry
It's ok.
Why don't you try studying abroad.
Studying in a different environment might be good for you.
Study abroad...
Hey! Lets go to the sea.
Let's go with Brother for a drive.
With teacher
Kinda earIy in the year to come to the sea.
But, I can't believe he agreed to it.
I used Kanoko-chan as bait, and got him in one try!
Bait?
How is Professor Akiyama?
Daddy is aIways nice, but it's just all fake.
Fake?
Yeah
Since l've been back, l havn't gone to see him.
Please tell him l'll come by soon.
Okay
Brother!
Kuu! What are you doing?
A student going to school is normal.
l guess you're right.
How about you?
l went to say hello to Professor Akiyama. l hadn't seen him for awhile.
Did something happen?
l was asked to tutor Kanoko.
Hey, wait!
Since we met, can't you say something Iike "I'll treat you to dinner"?
Sorry for not noticing. Well let's go to the noodIe stand by the station.
Whaaa!
l like that face.
Thank you very much.
lt ended up costing me again.
Thanks for dinner!
Now...
Going home?
Well...
Really? Here?
You don't want to?
At a place like this? lt's a Iittle perverted.
If not, lets go home.
I didn't say I won't, but...
They can't see us from above.
l wonder if they really can't see us.
Wait
Do you want to stop?
N-no. That's not it.
l don't have a change of clothes.
ln a place like this. Even though someone might come. l'm feeling good.
l'm really wet. Maybe l'm a little perverted too.
Even more than before, l'm really, really feeling it.
l want Onii-chan to move more and more.
Onii-chan, please. l don't want to finish Iike this.
What's the matter?
l can't see your face. I don't like that.
Oh
Like this?
Thats right.
l have to put it in myself.
lt's entering me. This is really.
What do l do now?
Do as you like.
But I don't know what to do.
Like this?
Yeah. But a Iittle faster.
l'm moving all by myself.
No, you can't do that.
It's all right if I don't do it too hard.
It's increadible! lt's in so deep!
No. Don't...
Onii-chan! l m scared! I'm scared!
I... l...
l don't like this.
You'lI just have to bear it.
What is this? Deep inside me. Something is coming, it's coming! l'm cumming!
l'm so happy Onii-chan!
It's mine.
Hello?
Is this Shouma-san? Chisato-san is, Chisato-san is...!
Chi-chan
She suddenly fainted in the garden.
According to the doctor it was an unexpected attack.
Thank you for everything.
Depending on the test resuIts, she should be able to go home.
So please don't worry too much.
Thank you.
It's no problem...
It's the same as that time.
That time when l didn't like Chi-chan taking all of Onii-chan's attention.
So l wished Chi-chan wouId go away.
Then there was a sound of breaking glass...
lt's all my fault!
Because l did something bad. Chi-chan is...!
l guess it still hasn't changed.
What?
That Chisato.
She didn't want to make us worry, so she pushed herseIf.
Her being stubborn and unyeilding is stilI the same.
And so is your being a cry-baby. It's just the same.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan! What am I supposed to do?!