Mayu!
Oh, it's you.
What's the matter? Why are you
acting so formal all of a sudden?
Mayu, I finally realized.
You're the only one for me.
I'm a man! I'll change and be the
man you want me to be, so...
W... wait! You're jumping ahead of yourself!
I don't know what came over
you, but calm down, okay?
I'm not the pathetic man I used to be.
This is what you wanted,
right? Mayu, let's fall in love.
N... no...
Mayu!
No!
NURSES STATION
What do you think you're doing, you idiot!
Mayu.
Yes.
R... Ryoko!
If you're going to take a nap, do it quietly!
Okay...
It's been a week since I've started to
work at Aoshima General Hospital.
A lot has happened, but...
...with Satsuki and Dr. Hattori's
encouragement, I'm doing well.
But lately, something has been bothering me.
I dream about Nimura
almost every time I sleep.
What does this mean?
NAUGHTY NURSES PART II
MOKUSHIROYA BAR
MOKUSHIRO YA BAR
Cheers!
PRIVATE PARTY
Drink! Drink!
Chug it, Nimura!
Okay!
Look at him go.
He can drink all he wants,
but he's still pathetic.
Hey, I think Nimura has
been avoiding me lately.
Did he say anything to you?
I wouldn't care if he had anything to say.
Chug another one!
Right!
I wonder if I did anything to make him angry?
One more, Nimura!
I, Shunsuke Nimura, want to
announce that I love Mayu Mizuno...
...who also happens to be here with us!
When we get married, we'll
have about five kids...
But I wonder if I'll have
the energy to do that...
That's it! If she has quintuplets
that'll solve everything!
Good job picking the right
place to heighten the mood...
Men are such idiots!
What he said... Was he serious?
Mayu... The time has finally come.
Dr. Nimura?
Great. We're back together again...
Now, we'll get to know each
other more than before.
Dr. Nimura!
Dr. Nimura... It's almost time...
Come.
Does it feel good, Doctor?
Yes.
Your cock is so hard, Dr Nimura.
We've only just begun, Doctor.
It's so yummy.
Ryoko...
What is it?
Are you going to fall in love with me?
Wh... why are you saying
that, all of a sudden?
Drunken resident... You just killed the mood.
Are you wet?
I'm wet... But if you give me
some loving... I'll be dripping wet.
I'm going to fuck you.
Nimura... I've been waiting for this day...
I can feel you throbbing inside me...
I can't anymore... I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum...
Was I wearing that bra?
What are you talking about?
Are you still asleep?
Ryoko! W... W... What are you doing here?
Did you forget what happened yesterday?
This isn't a comedy punch line!
Well, you were plastered, so...
I was surprised, because
you were so passionate.
Your dick got so big, and...
You made me cum so much.
You're so cute! Let's do it again sometime.
Want to have another round
before we go to work?
This is a nightmare...
It's getting hard!
What? Why don't you sit down or something?
Okay.
I wonder if she knows?
Whoa. She looks like she's
in a really bad mood.
Are you angry at something?
I bet she knows...
Is it about last night?
I knew it...
She knows about me and Ryoko.
This isn't good. She totally
hates me. Women are so scary.
I don't understand how you feel.
When you did that yesterday...
That was...
Were you serious?
Of course I wasn't serious!
Do you honestly think I could do that sober!?
Oh, so it was a joke.
I was thinking about it all
day. How stupid of me.
If you're not serious, then
don't tell me you love me!
But... You weren't talking about
me and Ryoko at the hotel?
Noooo!
What am I doing?
That wasn't cute.
Do you ever feel nauseated?
Nope.
Do you ever feel fatigued,
or have headaches?
Nope.
You're recovering nicely from the
surgery. You'll be able to leave soon.
But that's no fun. I finally got to know you.
You shouldn't stay if you don't need to.
We can't have you stay here like some old
geezer who sexually harasses the nurses.
Plus, your doctor is Dr. Hattori.
I hate that doctor!
He's always staring at my chest.
Well, I don't blame him.
Hey! You looked too!
Sorry! But it means you're that attractive.
I wouldn't mind it if it's you,
but I want you to love me lots.
Maiko?
Maiko, what's wrong?
Doctor... Do you feel my heart beating?
I feel it, but...
I wonder if I'm lovesick?
It's your fault. Please fix it.
I'm hard!
You're excited, too!
My body is hot.
I'll fix you first.
Your tongue feels so good!
I can do it!
The way Maiko's acting...
It must feel really good.
I could never bring myself to
do it, but I bet I could now!
Maiko!
Here I come!
Doctor... Your cock is so big.
Thanks.
I want you to stick it in my pussy later.
Maiko, you're so wet.
I... I think I'm going to go insane.
Fuck me! Fuck me with
your big cock! Give it to me!
It's inside of me! You're inside
me! Your big dick is inside me...
Does it feel good?
Yes! More... Fuck me more
and make me go crazy!
Doctor, you're fucking me
too hard... My body...
I'm going to cum.
Me too!
I've never had such great sex...
Really?
Yeah. It was super-good.
I can do it! I can do it!
AOSHIMA GENERAL HOSPITAL
NURSES STATION
Hello. Nurses station.
Huh? I understand. I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Nimura just told me Mr. Ishigami's
condition has suddenly gotten worse.
Off I go!
Mr. Ishigami, the man who left the hospital
this morning, is in critical condition?
It means that he's finally mustered up
enough balls to tell her to her face.
I don't know what happened,
but hopefully it won't backfire.
Nimura...
Nimura!
That was fast.
Where's Mr. Ishigami?
He left this morning, remember?
Are you making fun of me?
I'm sorry.
Can I leave if you don't need me?
I'm busy, unlike some people.
Well I called you because
I need you, of course.
What?
I want us to be together again.
I'm not the pathetic man I used to be.
This is what you wanted,
right? Mayu, let's fall in love.
That dream!
Mayu, I finally realized.
You're the only one for me.
I'm a man! I'll change and be the
man you want me to be, so...
Nimura, are you serious?
Mayu, will you...
No! This isn't right! You're
not acting like yourself!
Will you please go out with me again?
Just like back then... Of
course, that's if you want to...
I'd really like us to be together again.
I broke up with you like that, and if you
say you don't want to, that's it, but...
...It's like I've finally realized how I feel...
I know I'm being really selfish, but...
...I really love you, so...
...If I was going to have
regrets again... Mayu...
Nimura...
Y... yes?
Are you drunk?
Of course not! I'm sober!
Really?
Yes!
Really, really?
Huh? I wonder what's
wrong? My tears won't stop.
Huh? Why am I...
Mayu.
Come on. Let's enjoy a
passionate night to ourselves.
You're beautiful.
Stop.
I'm not in the mood.
Oh, come on.
Maybe I wasn't meant to be with doctors?
What are you talking about?
You and I get along great!
Satsuki... You... Are you in love with...?
Don't tell them, okay?
Are you nervous?
A little... But I'm fine. I'm
not the man I used to be.
You're beautiful, Mayu.
I'm so embarrassed, Nimura.
You like to lick.
Yeah.
Next is here...
Wow. You're so wet already.
You're embarrassing me.
It's silky and it tastes really good.
You're going to go down on me too?
You made me feel so good. This
is my way of saying thanks.
Plus, it's unfair that you only
get to see me in pleasure.
Wow! It's so big and hard!
Thanks.
Why were you running away from me
when your dick could get like this?
I can't believe you're giving me a blowjob.
You taste really good too.
I'm going to stick it in.
Okay. I want you inside me, Nimura.
We're finally one!
Mayu!
Mayu, you feel so good!
You too! I can feel you all the way inside me.
Mayu!
Right there! Right there! More!
Fuck me harder! Right there!
Yes!
Nimura!
Mayu!
Yes... Yes...
Mayu! Mayu
Nimura!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to go insane... Nimura!
Inside me... Cum inside me!
Days have passed, and
something sad happened.
Satsuki suddenly quit her job at the hospital.
I'll see you later!
Hey, did you know?
Satsuki was engaged to the hospital
president's son at her last hospital.
Really? Why'd they break it off?
He cheated on her. He apparently
cheated on her with another nurse.
Doctors are all the same.
Come on. Not all doctors are like that.
And apparently the patients were all
weird, so she had trouble there too.
All the patients here are nice.
Yes!
On top of that, the Head Nurse was
screwing the hospital president!
Things happen with nurses
too, you know... Right?
This hospital is on the brink, too.
What are you talking about, Mayu?
We're going to protect
the peace at this hospital.
Peace, eh?
That's right.
I... No, I mean...
We will build the future of Aoshima
General Hospital together.