That's...
Daisuke Karino...
...and Sister Yumiko?
Yuki, I regret to inform you...
...that my St. Michaela Project
has failed due to the uprising.
To save Japan, I've joined
the special attack unit...
...and am set to leave for
Okinawa tomorrow.
Daisuke...
The fate of our empire will be
decided upon this mission.
I have formed this special
attack unit...
...to carry out a most heroic act
of courage.
You must promote the tradition
of the glorious Royal Navy.
Be an example of honor for
the next generation to follow.
Wipe out all of the enemy fleet!
Thereby building the foundation
of an immortal empire!
This is the end of Daisuke
Karino? But... how on earth?
Kumi.
Who's there?
Kumi Aoike of St. Michaela's
College...
Now, at last, I shall avenge
Daisuke's death!!
Kumi!
- Why?
- Who did it?
It's horrible.
Miss Yuki...
Right now, I am Aaron.
You killed Kumi Aoike, didn't you?
I did.
I hope you're not planning
to kill Aiko. Are you?
Not so loud! Come.
Rika Ikeda.
You seem to have forgotten
you're living on my terms.
I could easily banish you
here and now.
Please spare me that, Miss Yuki!
Strip down.
Let me get it through to your
body that you're my servant!
Aiko...
You'll let me have your body but
your soul is reserved for Aiko.
Miss Yuki, if you kill Aiko...
Then what?
I will commit murder-suicide
right here.
Don't worry. I don't plan to
do Aiko any harm whatsoever.
My objective is to send
the Crusade to Jerusalem.
No...
Stop...
Send the Crusade to Jerusalem?
Then why do you oppose my fellows
from St. Michaela's?
Their objective is the same.
Quiet! It's just...
Yes?
Just as you love Aiko, I, too,
have someone I love.
Go on. We're leaving tomorrow.
Yes...
Daisuke...
Yuki...
Before my departure, I'd like
us to have a wedding...
Daisuke...
DAISUKE!!
If only Aiko Mimura hadn't
come to St. Michaela's,
my dear Daisuke would not
have died...
All I have to do is kill Hans.
Then he can't reincarnate
as Aiko Mimura.
Nor can he come into our time.
Please wait, Daisuke...
I'll do everything in my power
to protect your life.
Miss Yuki intends to kill Hans.
I must do something, or Hans...
rather, or Aiko's life will...
Lord...
Please guide us safely to
the Holy Land, Jerusalem...
That voice... Hans?
I must tell him.
If we're destined to unite,
I shall swallow my shame...
...and use my body to...
...so that the wind will be
calm over the ocean.
Lord, keep your loving hand
of guidance upon our journey.
Amen.
Hans.
You are... Rika Ikeda.
What are you doing
looking like that?!
One of my fellows has died...
a woman named Kumi Aoike.
What?!
What is happening to us will
happen to you as well.
Our Crusade has become one with
your Crusade.
Someone is also targeting you.
What are you driving at?
Will you cancel the expedition?
Not again...
I've told you.
I have a mission to accomplish.
About a year ago, someone stood
at my bedside and said:
"Go to Jerusalem."
I believed I heard the Lord.
Do you believe in the Lord?
It is you, Hans, that I want
to believe in.
Me?
You've taught me a way of living
that I had not imagined.
When? I've only just met you!
But we have met before.
To be precise, we will meet
hundreds of years from now.
We were lovers.
Do you mean to tell me you've
come backwards in time?!
Yes. I don't blame you for
not believing me.
But I did fall in love
for the first time... with you.
Love?
We even pledged our love once,
like this...
If this is fate... our destiny...
your body will know that I am
telling you the truth.
It's immoral!
With unspoiled purity
as our shield...
we the Crusade must rise up and
proceed toward the Holy Land.
How dare you!!
I will protect your life
with my own!
Get out, you filth.
Hans!
If you don't, I will!
Cover yourself!
How else can I?
What a disaster!
Hans and the Crusade have
already departed!
- What?!
- Why did they?!
How would I know?
We've got to follow them.
Everyone, get ready and gather
in 30 minutes!
Marco, is everything okay
with your carriage?
Hi, Hans.
Your order was so abrupt I just
grabbed everything and ran.
I had received a revelation
from God.
We are protected by the Lord,
after all.
Franćois, you are supposed to be
riding way back there.
Hey, I don't see the support
troop from Japan anywhere.
I'm sure they'll catch up.
There's no need for support.
We can manage fine on our own.
Right?
Recently, I've heard rumors of
bandits that prey on pilgrims.
Let them try if they dare.
We'll hand them their due
punishment, right, leader?
We'll spare no one that
stands in our way.
That's right!!
What's that?
What happened?
Bandits!
Get them, bums!
No! Stop!
No!
Franćois!!
Shit! Stop it!
No! Stop!
Beast! No!
Please stop.
Lord...
Shit!
Charge!!
What?
That's the support troop
from St. Michaela's.
Don't underestimate us ladies!
We're the Female Crusade...
...the veterans of a hundred
conquests...
...who wiped out the warlords!
Aiko!
Mayumi.
We just missed them. The Crusade
left early this morning.
Kozue's group also?
They were led by Hans Heilner.
Aiko, that's you...
Let's go. I know the route
they're taking to Marseilles.
To Marseilles!
To Marseilles!!
You're here at last, Aiko...
No, Hans!
Hans...
Leave me alone...
Franćois!!
What?
How awful!
Don't just stand there!
Take her down!
Give her a burial!
It is against the Lord's word
to take your own life.
Hans, do you still believe
in the Lord?
Trials are also God's will.
We shall overcome all obstacles.
The Holy Land, Jerusalem, shall
indeed be ours!!
Are you alright, Marco?
Yeah...
You're burning up!
Hans!
How's Marco?
We can't get his fever down.
Misayo is making an herbal remedy
with river water.
Thank you.
It's amazing how you predicted
the fever that's ailing Marco.
Rika?
This is Aaron.
He's been sent directly
by the Pope to aid Hans.
Perhaps you are God's messengers
capable of prophecy?
Oh, no. Nothing like that.
We've denied God's existence.
Right?
Right...
Okay, it's done.
Just enough for now.
Rika, why don't you bring it
to them?
Yes... May I, Misayo?
I'll be over as soon as
I make some more.
I've got to make enough
to get to Marseilles.
Pretty handy, huh?
I'm like the medic of
the St. Michaela troop.
You can save someone else's life
but I bet you can't save yours.
Why?
Misayo!
Look!
Hey, look.
Misayo.
What happened?
Misayo has been killed.
The killer is amongst you.
What? You suspect us?
Misayo said "the Crusade"
and drew her last breath.
What?
Let's stop this! This is no time
to make enemies of each other.
Rika... Are you taking
their side?!
Watoko!
There is no greater insult!
Stop it, every one of you!
Marco, you should be in bed!
It's my fault. If only I hadn't
caught this fever...
...Misayo wouldn't have...
...it's all my...
Misayo!
Marco...
Misayo!!
Everyone, let's give Misayo
a proper burial.
So we've failed to keep them
from advancing to Marseilles.
Kumi's dead. So is Misayo.
If we hadn't left Aiko behind,
maybe they wouldn't have died.
Watoko, what do you mean?
It's your fault, Kozue.
We should have waited for
Aiko to recover!
Too late now...
Kozue!!
Punk!
There's nothing I can do
about it now, is there?!
Aiko...
Everyone, we're almost there!
We're not far from Marseilles.
Hang in there!!
Yeah!!
I must avert Yuki's evil plot.
Or else, I will evaporate.
And the undivided world after
the Restoration would not come!!
I smell the sea breeze.
The sea...
The sea! Hey, it's the SEA!
I can see the Mediterranean!
We finally did it! Jerusalem is
just beyond this sea.
God has seen us through
our journey.
Thank you, Lord. And thank you,
Kozue and fellows.
And now, you're on your own.
What? Do you still hold
a grudge against us?
Hell, no.
The Mediterranean, I'm afraid,
will not part.
Nonsense.
There will be no miracle.
That's when you'd finally
realize you've been betrayed...
...by the Pope.
What?!
Rather, you've been betrayed by
the very religion you cherished.
Liar!
You're going to be sold
to the slave ship!
Waving a contract with the Pope,
the traders will take you all...
...to Africa!
Are you mocking us?!
I've heard enough!
Stop it!!
We must pray.
A miracle will happen.
The sea will part.
We will get to the Holy Land.
As long as we believe in Him,
the Lord will hear us...
...and answer our prayers!
That's right! Hans is right!!
Let's pray.
Our Father who art in heaven...
We the Crusaders have come here...
...to take back Holy Jerusalem
from the heathens.
Lord, please open our way
through the Mediterranean.
Amen.
Look! The sea is swelling!
The sea...
The sea is parting...
The way to the Holy Land
has been opened.
Let's proceed to Jerusalem!
To Jerusalem!
Wait!!
Kozue, you have nothing more
to tell us.
The sea has parted.
The promise has been fulfilled.
Those slave traders you feared
are nowhere in sight.
This can't be happening...
It's impossible...
This must be some sort of
a trickery!
Don't be deceived!!
Listen carefully.
These women have only pretended
to support our cause!
Aaron!
Remember what they said?
If the sea doesn't part,
it proves to us...
...that the Pope has lied
about everything.
But the sea did part!!
After witnessing a miracle,
why would they still deny it?
Because they are fallen angels
trying to destroy the Pope!!
They're the Devil's servants!!
What?!
Leave them to me to handle.
Hans, lead your fellows
across the sea.
Rika.
Let's cross the sea together.
Hers is the true faith
in the Lord.
Let's go, everyone!
We're crossing the sea!!
Yeah!
Kozue, forgive me. I'm doing
this for Hans... no, Aiko.
Aiko.
Watoko!
Eiko!
Kozue!
What about Kumi and Misayo?
All wiped out... most likely...
Can't be...
Yuki... I presume?
Right. I've been waiting for you,
Aiko Mimura.
You would disrupt the peaceful
flow of time just for one man?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand...
You intend to resurrect...
...the dreadful Michaela Project
once again?
I wouldn't expect
the Michaela Project.
What you're trying to do is
to recall the dark history...
...on behalf of Daisuke Karino,
is it not?
Which means...
Daisuke belongs to me alone.
I will keep him from going
to St. Michaela's.
That is impossible.
In any case, it doesn't matter
what you do.
The uprising at St. Michaela's
will be a springboard...
to the Amakusa Restoration, then
the World Restoration here.
Eventually, Daisuke Karino is
doomed to disappear...
...in the tide of a new history.
On the contrary!
It's you who will disappear!
Kill them!
Aiko!
They're not who they used to be!
They're just zombies manipulated
by Yuki's voodoo!
Kozue!
Kill or be killed.
It's no use fighting back.
Iwadate!!
Mayumi!!
Now, Aiko Mimura, you're
the only one left!!
Be a good friend and follow
the others to hell!
So that's it!
Try manipulating them now!
Why, you!
Aaron!
Are you all right?
We got worried, so we came back.
Pierre... Johann...
Marco... Michel...
Who are you?
Guys! It's me, Hans!
Pierre, Johann, Marco, Michel...
Rika?
Aiko...
I didn't know you were alive...
There she is. I'm finally seeing
Aiko again...
Rika.
Aiko.
Everyone!
She is the leader of the Devil's
support troop, Aiko Mimura!
Destroy the Devil!
Stop! Don't do it!
I don't want to fight you!!
Shut up and fight!
Michel!
Fine! I'll just have to knock
you out awhile.
Hans!
Johann! Marco! Pierre! Michel!
Hans, let me explain!
Did you do this?
Who are you?
I'm Hans Heilner.
That's me!
You are me.
The Devil!
Stop!
You mustn't hurt me.
It'll be a catastrophe!
Please, Hans.
She is your own self.
You are!!
Aiko!!
I did it! I did it at last!!
I destroyed Aiko Mimura!!
Daisuke... I'll fly over to you
right away.
Daisuke...
Here I am, Yuki.
Daisuke.
So we finally meet again.
735 years from now,
I shall live out my life with you...
That is impossible.
I have sunken to the bottom
of the southern sea.
No, you won't die this time.
We can go back to the time
before our wedding.
It's impossible, Yuki.
There... Look at that...
But that's?!
Yes, the World Restoration
has begun...
The World Restoration?
You're not Daisuke!
Who are you?!
It's me.
My dear!
Then, Daisuke...
Daisuke Karino has disappeared.
Now that the World Restoration
has become a reality,
his existence has no place
in this particular space and time.
I can stop this vile
World Restoration!
Yuki!
Your Holiness! You're unharmed!
You're... Aaron!!
I see, this is your doing!
What do you mean?!
The Crusade headed for Jerusalem
has returned to attack us...
...because of a contract they
found on some slave dealers ship.
This must be some sort of
conspiracy that you instigated!
I tell you, he is an androgyny.
He's a Devil's messenger!
What are you?
Stop it!
An androgyny!
We mustn't keep it alive.
We must kill it!
Why, you wretched creatures!
You should all burn in Hell.
Forgive me.
Please don't kill me.
Please spare my life! I beg you!
Die!!
Devil...
Ridiculous. It is you who will
end up in Hell.
The Restoration has been
completed.
That voice!
Old Sage... You were alive.
You've just done it yourself,
dear Yuki.
Now you've completed
the Restoration.
What do you mean, Old Sage?
All the events were preordained,
Yuki...
...from the founding of
St. Michaela's College...
...to the student uprising...
...as well as the Amakusa
Restoration...
...all the way to
the World Restoration.
All played a fateful part
in the history of this world.
Now, now, Yuki. Try to remember.
How peaceful and plentiful was
the post-Restoration world...
But for Daisuke...
Don't be foolish.
Those who are tied to the dark
history are doomed to perish.
But, Old Sage, your explanation
doesn't convince me!
Yayoi... You were alive?!
Aiko Mimura! Rika Ikeda!
No way...
No way! This is ludicrous!
Miss Yuki, even you can't
touch Hans-Aiko now.
I have become one with Hans
completely...
...thanks to Rika and Yayoi
over there.
We, too, have been rescued
by Yayoi.
Somehow, I don't remember ever
being killed, though.
Well, I had to tweak back time
a little, you know.
Old Sage, who on earth
are you two?
Yuki, you even forgot that, too?
Yuki...
My dear!
Come on, Yuki. Try to remember.
Remember those who have lived...
...deep within the dark and
oppressed history.
Gonza!
But your appearance!
Indeed, Gonza has reincarnated
for the better.
He is precisely the one true
symbol of the World Restoration.
I suppose it's time now for me
to make claims on your life.
Old Sage!
"Time, be still.
You are beautiful."
Don't say you don't remember
our pact we made that day.
But I have yet to meet Daisuke.
Yuki, just like Indra's net, all
the worlds are held together...
...by the reflections they cast
on each other.
Now that we have fulfilled
our mission...
there's no need for us
to stay in this world.
You can understand... no?
But... I want to... have to
see Daisuke...
Old Sage, brace yourself.
Yuki!
Damn you, Aiko Mimura!
Still won't get out of my way?!
Rika!
I protected the one I love
in the end...
Aiko, I love you.
RIKA!
This is the end of you, Yuki!
Daisuke, I'm coming to you now.
Time, be still.
You are beautiful.
Daisuke!
Yuki!
Daisuke... Here we are at last!
We shall be together forever.
Rika!!
Rika...
Aiko...
Rika, hold on!
I'll ask Yayoi for medicine...
You don't have to.
Now that Yuki is gone, my second
life, too, is about to expire.
I have no regrets.
There is no greater joy
than to die in your arms.
Rika, my heart will always
belong to you alone.
I'm happy.
Rika?
RIKA!!
I won't forget you,
I promise, Rika.
As long as this world goes on...
you'll keep on living
in my heart forever.
Forever.
Come on, here we go!
Yeah!