Machiko!
Machiko, are you awake?
Hurry up!
l'm already up!
Machiko!
Are you planning to be late on your first day?
Can't you think about your father's position and...
Thanks for the meal!
Wait a minute!
Aren't you going to eat anything?
l'm going to be late!
See you later!
Panty Flash Teacher Vol. 1
Good morning.
Good morning!
Starting today, my new life begins.
My new life as a teacher.
l have to do my best!
That huge thing won't fit!
Really?
l guess you're right.
Yeah!
lf you stick that thing in, l'll be really sore.
What school do they go to?
Does the school know what their students are doing?
How about a softball?
Maybe that might work.
lf l let this one go by, l'll fail as a teacher.
...but rubber tennis balls might be better since they're elastic.
lt's for their own good.
l have to do what's right!
Right? Right?
Let's try it next time.
We're inside a train you know!
Huh?
Eating and drinking on a train is prohibited.
Plus you're sitting on the floor!
Get up.
Do you understand me?
lt's none of your business old lady!
Old lady?
You're telling us what to do with your panties exposed.
l don't think you're being persuasive.
You want me to do it with you?
Stop it you two!
Your panties are exposed!
What are you doing? l said stop!
No! Stop it!
Hey, get your hands out of the way!
Why don't you remove them yourself?
No!
Are you okay?
Oh no...
Don't mess with me!
l have to get off!
Come back here!
l'm getting off!
Damn!
You're not getting away!
Stop messing around!
Oh no!
She's gone.
Shit!
l'll get you back for this!
We left our bags on the bus.
Ohba-sensei, l'm counting on you.
Ok, sit right there.
That's your seat.
Yes.
l'm Ohba. l'm in charge of the junior class.
lt's a pleasure to work with you.
You're teaching classicism, and you're from around here, right?
Yes.
My father told me to come back home.
l'm sure you're aware of this but...
l want you to be in charge of the junior class C.
l replaced one of the teachers who took a sick leave.
But they think l should stay...
Huh?
Anyway, just try to do your best without causing any trouble.
lf you need anything, just let me know.
Yes, l'll do my best!
Machiko Natsukawa
Hello.
My name is Machiko Natsukawa...
...and l'll be in charge of this class starting today.
l hope to get to know you all very quickly.
So l'll do my best by working with you all.
They look like nice students.
But l shouldn't be too nice to them.
l would like to be friendly to you all.
But l have no intention of engaging in a cozy relationship.
You'll be scolded if you're bad.
l saw some students who were eating and drinking on the train...
...so l scolded them.
But don't be afraid.
Even though l'm your teacher, you can talk to me about anything.
Now, l'm going to take attendance.
Asatsuki-kun.
Here.
Asada-san.
Try to speak up.
Yes.
lshino-kun.
lshino-kun?
lizuka-san.
Are they both absent?
Morning!
Who's the new professor?
lt's the lady from the train!
You two?
Please take a seat!
This should be interesting.
What? Stop it.
l haven't done anything yet.
Then have a seat.
l need to get back at you for what you did.
There!
Ouch...
Your panties are exposed again.
You really want me don't you?
Panty flash teacher!
Come here!
No!
Stop!
Let go of me!
No!
Hey!
Stop it!
Stop!
That's enough!
But she...
You had your fun.
What?
lshino and lizuka?
l believe they're troublesome kids!
Troublesome kids are everywhere these days.
But...
lf that's the case, then you should come up with a way to deal with them.
You said l should come to you if l had any problems.
Best thing for you to do is to please them and win their approval.
Huh?
Depending on what you do...
You might gain popularity from the boys.
Huh?
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Asada.
Taking pictures the other day was fun!
Let's do it again.
l'm counting on you, Asatsuki.
Okay.
You should make some noise when you're sucking it!
Good...
Yeah, that's it.
Use more of your saliva.
Make more noise.
Suck on it like you're enjoying it.
You're doing pretty good!
Go suck the rest of his cock and balls.
That new teacher...
She looks interesting.
What?
She's not interesting.
Panty flash teacher.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna do her?
l'm about to climax.
l'm coming!
Open your mouth!
He climaxed!
You must've had plenty inside you.
That's quite a load lshino.
Swallow it!
Your clothes will get dirty.
She spit it up.
What a waste.
Are you gonna do that teacher?
l'm interested in her.
Leave her to me.
l don't mind.
But l still have to get back at her.
l'll keep that in mind.
Asatsuki! l want you to do me a favor.
Get in here!
Okay.
l want you to help me too, Asada.
Ohba-sensei is such a bad teacher!
l can't rely on that kind of person!
l can't get anywhere with a person like that.
Great! lt's already dark outside!
You're Asada-san, right?
What's wrong? Why don't you go home?
Sensei...
What?
l...
Asada!
l was looking for you, let's go home.
l get it now.
Get home safely.
Bye Sensei.
Let's go.
Don't worry about her.
lf she becomes his new toy, then we can be free.
Let's take care of this quickly.
Okay.
We don't know who did it.
Listen Natsukawa-sensei.
We just wait for those rascals to graduate and disappear.
lf you cause any trouble with the students...
You might not be teaching next year.
Damn it!
You just wait and see! l'll never be like him!
l forgot to say this but thanks for standing up for me the other day.
l appreciate it.
You don't have to thank me.
lshino and lizuka aren't all that bad.
You know what, Sensei...
This was sent to my father.
But l opened it by accident.
What is this?
That's not me!
l don't know who did this but...
...l think this person is trying to post these in public.
lf these photos go public...
l know they're fake but...
...other people might see them as real.
That won't be good!
lf that happens...
My father's a member of the city council.
Really?
My father's the mayor.
Then you know how l feel right?
l'm not the only one who'll be hurt by these photos.
Would you like to come to my house?
Let's figure out what to do.
Your house is huge.
lt's average.
Nobody's home?
We usually have a housekeeper but she's not here today.
My father's a libertine, my mother's always doing something.
So they're usually not around.
lt's been so long since l've seen them both.
Aren't you lonely?
Not really.
But these photos look so real.
Stop looking! lt's embarrassing.
You think those photos were sent to other places too?
l thought about it, but l think it's best to pay some money to stop this.
What?
Take a look at this.
Naughty Pictures of Professor-Machiko
What is this?
Uploader for the internet.
Looks like those photos are being uploaded...
...in a password-protected zip file.
Anybody can download it.
What?
Those photos are going to be all over the internet.
Plus the password is going to be revealed three days from now.
But they won't be able to see what's inside now, unless you pay up...
Are you behind all this?
lt's not me.
l'm not good with computers.
Hey Utsui-kun!
You know who's behind this, right?
This is not a joke anymore!
You should pay up.
Then l'll put a stop to this.
How generous of you.
Bribing a student, you'll be in big trouble if they find out about this.
What are you talking about? You're the one who's blackmailing me!
Really?
l'm just telling you nicely.
Forget all this for now.
What do you think you're doing!
Does it matter?
l couldn't stop thinking about you from the moment l saw you.
l like you.
What?
Sensei!
l like you!
Stop...
You and l are teacher and student...
Who cares? l like you.
l love you, Sensei.
Stop...
No...
Rub it for me, Sensei.
Like this.
No...
lt's getting bigger.
Don't do this Utsui-kun...
No...
Try it.
Sensei, it feels good...
l'm about to climax.
Don't release it inside!
l released it inside...
Dear Utsui, remember this day, and promise me you'll study hard. From your Teacher
l can't believe l did it with him...
Aren't you lonely?
Not really.
He's lying.
He must be very lonely.
His parents don't care about him since they're too busy with work.
He's not a bad kid, he just needs to be loved.
l'm doing this to get him back on track...
Oh no...