It spreads Its wlngs and salls away.
TIII It reaches the sun burnlng In the sky.
And I belleved It could make It there.
Only the young are so reckless that...
...they keep charglng at It,
gettlng hurt agaln and agaln.
I turn back and I can
see you standlng there.
Destlny.
Those burnlng angel wlngs
are embraclng both of us.
That holy angel's love Is burnlng brlght.
As though the sun were
shlnlng... In the nlght!
Good work! You were great out there!
Thank you!
That was a great show. Now
we have a press conference.
Hi, backstage here.
Huh?
Rina, something's happened. Your father...
Your father collapsed. They're
taking him to the hospital.
My father...!
Idol Fallen Angel
RINA
It's that serious?
How could it have gotten this
bad without my knowing it?
Why...?
The boss was desperate
to fix up the company.
It all started when his
capitalization attempt failed...
...and he turned to illegal financing.
The debts started to snowball...
...until he lost his stock
and his credit rating.
No...
The boss used to say "Don't
worry Rina" like it was a mantra...
...so we hid his failing health from you.
Father...
Miss Rina Yuki?
Hm? Y- Yes. Who are you?
Kurosaki of Angel Productions.
I'd like to talk to your father.
I refuse!
My father's sick! He can't discuss
my signing with someone else!
And what does my contract
have to do with him?!
Now, calm down, Rina. You
may not be aware of this...
...but your father owes our
production company a lot of money.
It's part of a mob-related conglomerate.
He owes you money...?
You're the only one who can
help your father now, Rina.
Come now, you're a top-line idol singer.
Sign with us and you'll pay
off that debt in no time.
Think of your father. You don't
want his name ruined, do you?
Now then, what's your decision?
Hey, did you hear about this?
Yeah, I heard! I heard!
And I really liked her, too.
Sorta weird, though. It's
causing a real uproar.
Yes, and I'm grateful to
everyone who's helped me.
But I'd Ilke to try to do what
I couldn't do up tlll now.
So...
No! How many times do I
have to explain this to you?!
You haven't been moving at all!
But...
Don't talk back!
All right, take it from the top!
Right...
What's with that leotard?
Kinda revealing, isn't it?
I can't believe they sell those things.
Look how it's riding up into her.
Isn't she embarrassed by that?
I can't wear this thing!
Oh? And why not?
The company wants to change your
image for a more adult appeal.
I thought I explained that to you.
But, this is...!
Put it on and you'll be fine.
So, you're Rina Yuki, huh?
Forgive me for not introducing you sooner.
He will be taking care of you from now on.
Your manager: Takuya Kenzaki.
You have an overdeveloped
sense of modesty.
You don't want to be known as
some virgin idol forever, do you?
But...
You agreed to follow the company's orders.
It's for your father's sake.
Just make the best of it.
What are you daydreaming about?!
I'm sorry!
All right, let's start again!
I can have Rina Yuki, the virgin
idol, to do with as I please?
So, when can I have her?
We're still training her to
be a satisfactory partner.
Please wait a little longer.
Sure... It's something to look forward to.
Okay, here we go!
C'mon, look over here!
Yeah, that's good.
C'mon, smile more.
Right, okay!
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Okay, let's go for a bolder look this time.
Yes, sir.
That's it. Raise your butt a little higher.
Yes, sir...
That's it! Great!
Everyone's looklng at me. At
me, In thls embarrasslng outflt.
Hey, is that really that virgin idol, Rina Yuki?
Check it out! It's so sheer,
you can see everything!
I used to be a fan. This is such a shock!
Are you sure this sort of image
change is good for Rina?
She wanted this.
I wanted her to protect her
old image a little more, but...
Hm... She wanted it.
Maybe that's the reason she
signed with a new company.
She never let on about it, though.
Okay, spread 'em as far as you can!
Oh, yeah! Great!
Absolutely atrocious.
The expression, the pose,
the tension... All wrong.
We can't use any of this.
But, I just can't wear such
embarrassing outfits...
You promised to obey the
company's decisions, right?
Yes, sir...
From now on, this is what
you'll normally wear.
At least let me have some underwear.
Oh, no. You have to lose
those inhibitions first.
Besides, you soaked your underwear
at the photo shoot before.
Did having all those people
looking at you turn you on?
No! That was just sweat...
I wouldn't figure you for
being an exhibitionist.
No! I'm not that kind of a girl!
Just let those Inhlbltlons go.
These are just human feellngs.
Once you do, you'll feel much better.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kenzaki.
Something's wrong with the car.
Shall we go some other way?
I see. Oh, well, let's take the subway.
With me dressed like this?
Can't we take a taxi?
Just cover your face and
no one will know it's you.
After all, the world still
thinks of you as a virgin idol.
Hey! Do you see that?!
Ew! What's with her?
Nympho. Totally.
Oh, I like her style!
Man, you can see her whole ass!
What's wrong with kids these days?
Isn't she embarrassed to wear that outfit?
Probably likes people to look at her.
No... Stop it, please!
Mr. Kenzaki!
Mr. Kenzaki, help me!
No! Somebody, please...!
You're a nympho, aren't you?
Look how wet you already are.
Naughty girl...
Stop it, please!
No! Not in there!
Don't do this!
Stop it...!
No!
How could you?! How could you do that?!
I couldn't save you in that sort of crowd.
Besides...
...it looked to me like you were enjoying it.
No, I...
I didn't like it.
Oh? Then what's this?
No! Don't!
Don't look! Please don't look!
No matter.
Anyway, we need to clean you up.
You can't walk around like that.
Here, use this.
Where are we?
You have a lot to do.
You need to buy a lot of things.
Like clothes. You want more
than one outfit, don't you?
What's wrong?
No...
It's nothing.
What's wrong wlth me? I've been
feellng so hot Inslde for a whlle.
What's golng on? My vaglna's throbblng.
I'll buy you a vibrator if you want one.
Oh... It suits you.
I can't wear this as normal clothing!
Is it that strange?
Then why don't we ask the
other people in this store?
No!
Tell me, do you think this suits her well?
Absolutely magnificent.
Isn't that...? No...
Excuse me, but aren't you Rina Yuki?
Does she look that much like Rina Yuki?
But, I mean, that's her!
She's a Rina lookalike I
scouted for a porn video.
That virgin idol would never
come in here, would she?
No! I never make mistakes like that!
You're really Rina, aren't you?!
No. I'm not Rina Yuki.
I'm... I'm a porn video girl.
She a masochistic exibitionist.
Look. See how excited she's getting?
All of you looking at her is turning her on.
Well? Aren't I right?
Yes. I'm a masochistic exhibitionist.
Today we're doing a
promotion for your porn tape.
Let them do whatever they want.
I won't forgive you!
How dare you ruin my image of Rina!
You say you want to quit?
There's nothing worse
than breaking a contract.
What about your father?
If we add a contract breech
penalty to his debt...
...you'll never be able to pay it back.
Well, there is one other way.
Your father has a rather
substantial life insurance policy.
We could have him killed.
It's done all the time in the underworld.
Besides that...
If these pictures ever
get out, you're finished.
What's goin' on?
You miss your vibrator
when it's pulled out, sister?
Yes. I miss it.
You want it?
Yes. Please give me your-
I can't hear you! Say it clearly!
Yes, sir! I want...!
I want you inside of me!
No!
You got one in here, too?
Why don't I take this end?
No! Not that!
You're rubbing me raw!
You're rubbing me raw
inside from front and back!
Don't you like it, you little slut?!
Say you like it! Go on!
I like it!
I like it! I like it...!
Now try to piss.
Go on.
Do it on all fours, one leg
up, like the bitch you are!
I'm golng to pee Ilke a dog
In front of these people.
It's no use!
I'm a horny bitch who gets turned
on by you all looking at me!
I'll even piss for you! Watch this!
80 million!
90 million!
100 million!
Anyone else?
120 million!
Is that the final bid?
Then the twins are sold for 120 million yen!
It's almost time.
It reminds me of when I bought you, Ayaka.
Yes, sir.
Next up is our prize for the evening!
The virgin idol, Rina Yuki!
She's a true masochist who
will play any game with you.
Though she still has a
strong sense of modesty...
...she's ready to try new games anytime.
Rina Yuki will now introduce herself to you.
Look, everyone. Look at my pussy.
Look how soft and pink it is.
Just me thinking about what
my master will do to it...
...has made me this wet already.
Someone, hurry!
Make me a horny slave for my master alone!
Now, then, Rina Yuki will be available...
...as a sex slave for a six-month contract.
Let's open the bidding at 100 million!
Well done, Kurosaki.
And you, too, Kenzaki.
She's come a long way under your care.
I'm very satisfied and look
forward to future business.
Thank you, sir.
Rina Yuki is sold for 580 million yen!
Those burnlng angel wlngs
are embraclng both of us.
She turned out to be a
good buy, didn't she?
Yeah... I wish her father
had collapsed sooner.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm so happy so many of you showed up.
Tonight, I want you all to see the real me.
You see, I'm a very naughty girl.
See? Just having all of you
looking at me like this...
...has made me so wet.
Well? Can't you hear it?
Someone, make me come.
Hey, somebody, stop her!
It doesn't matter who.
All of you, make me come!
She's lost her mind...