l'm Kenta Ochiai.
Distracted by thoughts of girls in bikinis,
l got tricked into a part-time job at a resort hotel.
lt looks like it might collapse at any minute,
and it's run by some old loser.
To top it off, l can't even pick up girls, because Suwatee and Shuree came along.
l was attacked by the Amazon Gang and got beat up by a gangster.
lt sucked.
Then l met the adorable Mahoko!
l can feel waves of love in my heart!
Just don't let them become tidal waves!
Hey, everyone, come and get it!
Everyone who's hip eats hamburgers!
Kenta, two strawberry and three melon snow cones, please!
Okay! No problem!
So that kid is the rich old man's grandkid? Big deal.
Typical Kenta, drooling all over her!
Yes, Mr. President?
Miss Namiya, come to my office immediately.
Thanks! You really helped out today!
lt's been a long time since l had this much fun!
ls it okay if l come help tomorrow too?
Of course! l'd love it!
Okay, Kenta, see you tomorrow!
That Mahoko. She's such a nice girl!
So sweet and cute too!
Don't you think?
Suwatee?
Shuree, what're you doing?!
You idiot.
You need a cold shower, so you can think about how much you just hurt Suwatee!
An enormous typhoon is steadily growing stronger...
...and is headed toward Hokuoku lsland at 20km per hour.
ls that typhoon headed for us?
Yeah. lt'll be here in four days.
We should get ready for it.
Suwatee, watch your step...
Are you all right, Mr. Sanada?
Seriously, for a moment...
Mr. Sanada, that's...
''Seiichi Sanada - Champion, All Japan Surf Competition''.
Mr. Sanada, were you a surfer?
Yeah, l was.
l thought it was a great way to pick up girls.
That's cool! You shouldn't be embarrassed!
Why?! Why can't l help Kenta and his friends?!
l put everything l have into this hotel.
l also invested considerable money on the beach.
Sanada is the only one who stands in my way.
Helping them and their hotel is betraying me.
You're so narrow-minded!
l'm not a kid anymore! l can do what l want!
Sir, she's at a difficult age.
lt may not be wise to try and control her too much.
Be quiet. This is between my granddaughter and l.
lt's none of your business.
Hey, Suwatee, cheer up!
They're having a Summer Festival at the temple.
Want to go with me?
She said she's not going, so leave her alone!
Kenta, why don't you and l go together?
Okay.
Let's go!
Tricked you!
ldiot! Now she's really mad!
Seems so...
Ta-da! How do l look?
l'm surprised.
Surprised?!
l asked you how l looked!
Don't you think l look good?
Ah, yeah.
Fine...
You're beautiful! Beautiful!
Jeez...
What?! Shuree took the best and cutest yukata!
That was the one l wanted!
Poor thing, l didn't know that was the one she had her eye on!
She can't wear the same one as Shuree!
Hey, Suwatee, can l come in?
Yes!
l was cleaning out a box, and l found this.
Would you like it?
l think it'll look good on you.
lt's beautiful!
Can l really have it?
lt's just gathering dust. You take it.
Thank you very much!
Clumsy...
Do you want me to buy one for you?
Really?
What do you want from me in return?
Nothing, it's just to be nice.
Just kidding! Sorry.
Yes, l'd love one.
Pick out the one you like.
Let's see...
You didn't have to get the cheapest one.
l wouldn't have minded spending more.
lt's not that. l just liked this one.
Sometimes you can be so cute.
Really. Spare me the sweet talk.
And l still deny anything happening between us!
What are you getting upset about?
l'm not upset!
Suwatee.
Don't blow it this time, lover boy!
Hey, Suwatee...
Can l buy you some takoyaki? Or maybe some cotton candy?
l'd like a snow cone.
They're such a pain in the ass.
That old guy was the All-Japan Surfing Champion?
l thought he was just some loser.
l was surprised, too.
Good! Those two are getting along well.
All it needs to be perfect is a little music.
Well then, how about we help them out?
Here goes!
What?
l'm hoping you've finally cheered up.
Kenta,
do you think of me as a little girl?
lt's okay to be honest.
l know l'm childish sometimes,
but l'm ready to grow up.
Don't rush things, Suwatee.
We're all overwhelmed by our feelings sometimes,
but basically life is pretty simple.
When you're unsure,
you can always find the truth in your own heart.
Kenta...
And so that's that.
Now how about we get it on?!
You totally ruined the mood!
He's sure no Prince Charming.
Hey, Kenta!
M-Miyuki?
l hear you're chasing little Miss Mahoko.
l knew you were dumb,
but that's really stupid even for you!
Uh, no!
lt's nothing like that!
She was really upset about her grandfather.
That's the problem!
He's really pissed that Mahoko is working at your hotel.
They got into a huge fight over it.
Remember, he's really protective of Mahoko.
That's right!
Mahoko.
Hey, Shuree? Are you still awake?
Maybe Kenta and l aren't meant to be.
He's always got some other girl and doesn't even notice me.
Maybe the gods are telling me to just give up.
Hey, Little Miss l-Used-To-Be-A-Goddess, what are you saying?
You can't really believe that.
But...
So, you'll just give up?
Forget him just like that?
lf not, you'll just have to try harder.
Shuree, why is it so important for you to get us together?
Shuree, you aren't...
For the last time, l am not interested!
He's not my type at all!
Now, let's go to sleep! Good night, Suwatee!
Good night, Shuree.
Another long day at work...
Do you have a boyfriend?
l hope not. You're so cute!
What's with them? Those guys are all over her!
Why don't you come out with us?
Hey, guys!
We're free tonight. Pick us up later.
Score! Yeah, okay!
Shuree, what are you doing?
lt's brilliant!
Make Kenta jealous by going out with another guy!
Pick us up here at seven, okay? Don't forget!
Okay! Pick us up here at seven, okay? Don't forget!
Okay!
Hey, Suwatee, what do you think of this outfit?
Jeez...
Quit worrying!
Right now he's so worried about you, that he can't think straight.
Sorry!
lt'll be okay!
You guys ready for the next outfit?
Hey! This isn't a fashion show!
Kenta...
Suwatee.
You're going dancing with Shuree, right?
Have fun!
But, l really...
Hey!
Hey! Suwatee, hurry up! Let's go!
Suwatee, hurry up! Let's go!
Suwatee! Suwatee, hurry up! Let's go!
Hey!
Suwatee!
Suwatee, what are you doing?
Hurry up! Suwatee, what are you doing?
Hurry up!
Grandpa, how could you transfer me to a different school without even asking me?!
Seika Girls Academy is very strict.
lt's perfect for you!
l won't go!
That girls school... l'd rather be here, at the beach!
Mahoko!
Miss!
Sir, that was too much!
Damn it! What have l done?
lt's them. lt's their fault that Mahoko...
l'll make them pay for this!
l hate eating dinner all by myself.
Mahoko?
Kenta!
Hey, what's wrong?
So, your grandfather really did that?
l understand his feelings.
My parents died when l was four.
l'm the only family he has.
lt's not that l'm not interested in our hotel.
l just don't think we have to destroy everyone else!
And...
Mahoko...
lt'll be okay! Just try talking to him.
But he treats me like a baby!
There's no helping that... you are still a child.
You too, Kenta?!
You're awful!
Sorry.
Mahoko...
Kenta...
l'm not a child anymore.
l... lt's my first time.
Don't! lt feels strange.
No, don't stare at me!
lt's beautiful, Mahoko.
Oh, no!
No! No, l...
Mahoko...
Kenta...
Please be gentle!
Mahoko, you're so hot.
No, l'm so embarrassed!
You're such a drag!
There's nothing as depressing as a woman in love.
You're worried about Kenta, right?
l'll stay here with the guys. Go on home.
Shuree...
Thank you!
l can't argue with a woman in love.
Mina...
What was that about?
l'll walk you home.
Cheer up! l'll help you talk to your grandfather.
What is this?
Grandpa!
That guy's your grandfather?
Kenta!
Suwatee...
Hey, what's going on?!
You're the one interfering with my Mahoko!
Sagashi tsuzuketeta
You have the one bright smile...
kagayaku sono egao
...that l've always been looking for.
Yume ni made miteta
These arms of yours that hold me tight...
dakishimeru sono tewo
...l have only dreamed about.
Subetewa hajimatte ita
l remember when it started...
deatta shunkan ni kizuita yo
...the day l saw you standing there.
Kono sora no hate ni
We stretch our wings to the sky,
tsubasa hiroge FLYAWAY
take wing, and then we fly away.
Futari tobitatouyo
Soaring off together.
Eien he tsuzuku
We share an endless love...
owaranaimo LOVE
...that lasts for eternity.
Futari nara, ame no yoru mo
Two together through the rain...
samui asa mo mitsukerareru
...through the cold, holding each other.
Still the moment...
eien he tsuzuku
...from here to eternity.
NEXT TlME
Kenta's a jerk, doing it with that girl!
And now there's a surfing contest!
What are you going to do, Suwatee?
l'm tired of waiting!
l'm going to risk everything! l'm going to take a stand!
l won't let anyone else win Kenta's heart!
Next time, Can Can Bunny Extra.
Goodbye, Suwatee. Goodbye, Kenta.