Mr. Fujisawa?
Sorry I'm so late.
It was only 2 or 3 minutes, Rieko.
I've got our table reserved, so let's go.
Before we go, Mr. Fujisawa,
let me introduce you.
This is my daughter, Ayana.
How do you do?
Shook hands?
Yeah. Not really the usual
way to introduce yourself.
He was probably playing around.
Anything besides the handshake?
One other thing. He has
REALLY huge hands.
So, he's a real he-man, huh?
Yeah. Hard-boiled. A real authority figure.
A crime prevention
detective, huh? Is he cool?
Yeah, I guess on first
glance. He's just so big!
Go in!
So, she's remarrying a
detective. That's sorta unusual.
He's sort of famous, too.
They say he's a hero.
Have you seen his, you know...?
I have. I've even held it.
Really?! That's so cool!
But he brought it home.
Mom was out and he was cleaning
it on the dining room table.
I hated it, but just had to watch.
It was yesterday.
Now don't be so tense.
Relax your shoulders a little more, Ayana.
Invite me over next time!
I can't do that.
All right, then, I'll just have to get bigger!
Forget it!
Now, where did it go?
I didn't tell anyone about
the Yellow Star case. Relax.
What the hell is this?
Don't be too showy when you sell it.
I hear you.
I have one left over. You can have it back.
You can keep it. It'll come
in handy for something.
I'm sure.
Yeah.
So, Fujisawa, how's the new family?
Must be fun everyday.
We only just got married.
Haven't had a chance yet.
She hasn't seen what an animal you are yet.
See this?
My new daughter.
Cute...
Call us next time and
let us in on the fun, too.
When I get the chance.
STUDYING! KEEP OUT!
Please, just wait a little longer.
You always do this just
as we're getting ready!
After exams... We can do it then.
Will you keep your promise this time?
Maybe...
Ayana!
Don't look at me like that!
I'll keep my promise, Kohei!
God, she's cute!
You better keep it!
If you don't, I might have to force you!
If you did, you'd drown
in here from all the tears!
Well, see you tomorrow.
Has he gone home?
You were home?!
But mom said you'd be home late tonight!
I wasn't feeling well and
slept in my basement office.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Finals are coming up. Do your best.
I'm working on it. Don't worry.
A promise, huh?
Ayana, do you remember your promise?
I do.
I'm coming over today.
All right.
She'll be out of the country for a week.
Mom's such a workaholic.
I'll enjoy it.
Won't you be lonely by yourself?
Nope. A wonderful show is about to start.
And the stars are you and me, Ayana.
What's that supposed to mean?
You'll know soon.
He'll be here soon!
Exams are over, right?
Yeah, but Kohei and I will be
studying together tonight.
He's coming over?
I can't let you.
We're going to have some
fun downstairs, Ayana.
Wh- Wha...?
It's a mild hallucinogen with a stimulant.
It'll just take away your
strength for about an hour.
Don't worry. You'll be back
to normal in 4 or 5 hours.
Today, for sure!
No!
I can't stand it... You smell so good!
Please, let me go!
No!
Does it feel nice?
I can make you feel even better.
Yellow Star magnifies
the feeling several times.
She's not home. For crying out loud!
You've got a nice body.
Way too nice for Kohei.
Wet so soon, Ayana?
No!
First, the fingers...
Don't!
No!
No! No! No!
Forglve me, Kohel!
I'm coming!
This is our little secret.
Got that?
I came by yesterday.
Something came up. Sorry...
What do you mean something came up?
Can I come today?
I'm busy today, too.
What's with her?
Swallow it.
Do it.
Don't let your teeth hit it.
Your tongue. Use your tongue.
That feels good.
Where are we going?
For a change of pace.
This is strange. Aren't we
going to have sex like usual?
There are special relationships
to keep up in my sideline.
They're complaining about
me keeping you to myself.
Swallow this.
Who are you?!
Have I got a sight for you two.
We've been waiting for this, Miss.
I can't do that again.
You reacted like you always do.
Especially when you're with me.
Because of the drug.
Should I call your boyfriend next time, too?
Lt'd be funny to tell him about
our warm little relationship.
Next time we should try
doing it in front of him.
You took my gun... Are you nuts?!
Give it back.
Are you serious, Ayana?
You...!
Oh, you're shittin' me...
MYSTERIOUS EXPLOSION
ROCKS APARTMENT BUILDING!
POLICE SUSPECT DRUG RING
DETECTIVE KILLED IN EXPLOSION
It's not like it was your fault.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
Right... Kohei, he and I...
It's nothing.
Thanks for coming today.
What's keeping him?!
So, here you are. Remember us?
What, you can't recognize
us with our clothes on?
This time you'll be partying with us.
For a long, long time.
Huh?