Kenta Ochiai here.
Oh no, the old man found out about me and Mahoko!
Now what do l do?!
Sir, please stay calm.
l will!
Now, Mahoko, come here.
What? What's going on here?
Mahoko, come home with me now!
l won't go! l'm staying here with Kenta!
Hey, Sanada...
You're playing awfully dirty, aren't you?
You set that boy on Mahoko, just to get at me!
You've got to be joking! That's crazy!
Grandpa!
Mr. Sanada and the others have nothing to do with this.
l'm in love with Kenta!
W-What did you say?!
Mr. President!
Sir, are you all right?
Old man! Old man!
Don't come any closer!
Namiya!
Stop!
Just a little squeeze...
No!
That's it, Mahoko!
lf you don't come home,
l'll kick Sanada and his friends off this beach!
Old man, give it a rest. Sanada...
Hold it, Kenta!
Arisugawa, l don't want to fight with you,
but this beach is my home.
No matter what you say, l'm not leaving.
What?
Grandpa, stop it!
Alright. l'll go home.
Then you'll leave Kenta and his friends alone, right?
You don't have to go home, Mahoko.
Old man, Sanada was the All-Japan Surfing Champ.
lt's not about money for him.
He loves this beach.
All-Japan Surfing Champ?
What's so funny?
All-Japan Champ, you say? Don't make me laugh!
Just because he has a trophy doesn't make it true.
What do you mean by that?
We happen to have a champion surfer at our place too.
He won the Hawaiian Tournament.
So what?
Well now, how about a bet?
lf you win a surfing contest,
l'll let you keep your hotel on the beach.
But if we win, you have to leave immediately!
No, l...
You've got a deal! No, l...
You've got a deal!
We'll see you on this beach tomorrow at three.
Don't chicken out!
Don't worry! We'll be there!
Kenta?
Suwatee, after we win this contest,
the hotel will be safe!
Kenta!
Tell me the truth!
What is that girl to you?
Oh boy, now l'm in trouble.
l won't do it!
l'll never surf again.
lf you want to win, you'll have to do it yourself.
But, Mr. Sanada!
Mr. Sanada...
Suwatee...
Why do you keep that surfboard?
Because...
You still love surfing, don't you?
What happened, Mr. Sanada?
Fifteen years ago, l killed my lover.
l had just won the championship that year.
There was a typhoon coming, but l took her out onto the water anyway.
lt'll be fine. Don't worry about it.
But l was overconfident.
She was swallowed by a monstrous wave.
Mina...
lt was an accident.
Mr. Sanada, it's not your...
No, l shouldn't have taken her out!
l'm sorry.
Sorry.
l don't have the right to go out on the water anymore.
l see. l didn't know goofy old Sanada had such a dark past.
Now what, Kenta?
lf you tell Arisugawa the story, maybe he'll reconsider.
Like that old man would listen to any story!
But there isn't anyone else who can surf.
l'm going to do it!
You?!
Yeah, you know it's hopeless.
Hey, Shuree!
Shut up and watch me!
l practiced all night, so l'll be fine!
l'll win that contest and get Mahoko back.
Damn it...
Suwatee!
Kenta, you moron!
Could Kenta and Mahoko have...?
Why can't l make up my mind and do something?
But if Kenta doesn't change his ways, there's nothing l can do.
But, l don't want that.
l don't want Kenta to be with another girl. l can't stand it!
Mina...
lt must be wonderful to be loved so much by Mr. Sanada.
l want to be loved by Kenta.
l want to become a woman that Kenta will love.
Shuree, do you think l'm a coward?
l envy Kenta. At least l do right now.
Kenta, are you going to be okay?
This doesn't look good.
Hey, look at that!
Old man!
What happened to Sanada?
l can't believe he's afraid of these waves!
Kenta, get yourself together!
Okay! Wait up, old man!
l'm coming!
Kenta! l'm coming!
Kenta!
l guess there's no helping it...
Guys, get ready to help Kenta!
You got it!
No, don't!
Suwatee, aren't you worried about Kenta?
Kenta would never cheat to win!
He's not that kind of person.
Believe me, l'm worried sick.
This contest is too much for him!
Suwatee, you...
What's wrong, boy?
You look like you're having a little trouble.
Damn!
Feel free to admit defeat any time.
No way!
Mr. Sanada...
Kenta...
ls that Mr. Sanada?
He shouldn't be out there, he can't win!
He's such an idiot!
He's trying too hard.
Kenta's getting by on dumb luck.
But it's about to get dangerous.
Be careful, Kenta!
Just watch, boy!
This is how you ride the waves!
Wow! Grandpa's so cool!
l could beat you in my sleep!
There's no way l'll lose to you!
This is nothing.
Kenta!
l need this!
Come on, boy! ls that all you can do?
Sanada?
Well, you're pretty good.
Grandpa, be careful!
Wow! Mr. Sanada!
Mr. Sanada...
Stupid! l don't need your help!
No! Grandpa!
Mr. Sanada!
You guys better do something!
No problem!
What's going on? We're not doing that!
Mina...
Well, l have to thank you for that.
Arisugawa, you're a hell of a surfer!
You are too.
Kenta!
l'm so glad you're safe!
l'm fine. Nothing to worry about.
But...
Thank you, Mina.
l didn't know you were such a great surfer, Grandpa!
l haven't felt this good in years!
Mahoko, how about l teach you?
Yes! Of course!
Looks like it runs in the family!
Sanada! You're pretty good!
Well, yeah, kinda.
Want to be my coach?
Really?
Kenta... why?
You were acting weird this afternoon.
So that's what it was.
l'm bored with this job.
l'm going back to Tokyo.
You're lying. What's with you all of a sudden?
l don't have anything to say to you.
Later.
Wait!
Let me go!
The only thing l have to tell you is to take care of Suwatee!
Shuree...
Stop being so nice!
You...
l like you, Kenta.
And that... makes it hard...
...to be around you.
Shuree?
Please, Kenta...
Can l have one night with you before l go?
Shuree?
Shuree...
Now l remember.
l love Kenta...
Having his arms around me...
Oh yes!
Kenta, l want it in me.
Shuree, l can't...
Come! Come inside me!
So long, Kenta! Take care of Suwatee! -Shuree
So long, Kenta. Take care of Suwatee! Shuree.
That girl...
That wind chime sounds awfully sad.
lt reminds me that summer's almost over.
Don't be such a bummer!
Let's get moving! Faster!
Okay!
Hey, cutie, want me to teach you?
Get lost, cutie.
What a loser!
So, how am l doing?
You won't be beating me any time soon!
Jeez, grandpa...
Watch out!
Excuse me, Arisugawa!
Coming around you, Mr. President!
Hey, Sanada, keep your hands off my employee!
Looks like the president's a surfjunkie again!
Suwatee, let's take a break!
Okay!
You've really gotten tan.
You too, Kenta.
l wonder how Shuree's doing?
Hey, guys! Taking a break?
Welcome back!
Here, this came for you.
Hey, it's from Shuree!
Hi, it's Shuree! How are you?
l'm in Okinawa now...
l hitched a ride with a truck driver who brought me all the way out here.
l'm working at a beach bar,
and l think l've been pretty good for business!
l'm having a lot of fun.
But sometimes, when l watch the sun sink into the sea,
l think about you guys.
Suwatee, Kenta, Mr. Sanada: it was short but sweet.
Now l'm getting mushy! So goodbye until l see you again!
She sounds happy.
Hey, you two!
Take the day off!
You've been working hard.
Go have some fun!
Okay!
l guess summer's almost over, isn't it?
l can't even remember my life without you.
Suwatee...
l'm sorry, Kenta.
l want to...
But... but... l'm scared.
Suwatee, look at me.
Suwatee, l love you.
l've been an idiot.
lt's okay, Kenta.
Suwatee, you...
They're too small, aren't they?
No, you're cute...
Kenta, please...
Suwatee, you're beautiful.
You're really beautiful.
Sagashi tsuzuketeta
You have the one bright smile...
kagayaku sono egao
...that l've always been looking for.
Yume ni made miteta
These arms of yours that hold me tight...
dakishimeru sono tewo
...l have only dreamed about.
Subetewa hajimatte ita
l remember when it started...
deatta shunkan ni kizuita yo
...the day l saw you standing there.
Kono sora no hate ni
We stretch our wings to the sky,
tsubasa hiroge FLYAWAY
take wing, and then we fly away.
Futari tobitatouyo
Soaring off together.
Eien he tsuzuku
We share an endless love...
owaranaimo LOVE
...that lasts for eternity.
Futari nara, ame no yoru mo
Two together through the rain...
samui asa mo mitsukerareru
...through the cold, holding each other.
Still the moment...
eien he tsuzuku
...from here to eternity.