ln violation of the Tokyo nuisance control ordinance...
l hereby sentence the defendant Sakai Yuji to 6 months in prison.
What?
This can't be happening to me!
This can't be happening.
l'm innocent.
l'm innocent!
Gold Throbber
Vol. 1
My name is Sakai Yuji, 32-years-old.
l'm just a regular guy with a beautiful wife and two kids.
l graduated from a prestigious university and joined a company.
lt happened one summer, when everything in my life was going well.
No...
Please stop.
Keep it calm. l'll make you feel real good soon.
No!
No...
Don't...
l know it's hard to believe, but the people around me in the train...
Were engaging in crazy sex acts all the time.
This is just the tip of the iceberg, sometimes, we see things like this...
l'm always watching, but l never take part in any of it.
But...
This man is a pervert!
What?
Huh?
What are you saying?
Somebody! He's the one!
lt's not me!
He placed his hand inside my panties and...
What?
He's the pervert!
lt wasn't me!
Stop pretending like you didn't do it!
lt's horrible!
Have you no shame? She's crying.
You bastard!
Don't let him get away. Hand him over to the cops at the next station!
What?
You gotta be kidding...
6 months later
Sakai Yuji.
You were arrested for sexual harassment.
Your wife and kid left you and then you got fired from your job.
Now, you have no place to go.
lt's none of your business.
But it is my business.
Who are you?
l know you were falsely accused.
What?
My name is Sugimoto Kazuo.
People call me the God of Perversion.
The God of Perversion has no job, but was living in a luxurious apartment.
When you were arrested that day, l was on the same train.
Don't you want to clear up the charges against you?
Of course.
But why are you...
Listen.
Several other guys like you were falsely accused on that train.
12 cases have been filed in the last 6 months...
52 cases all together within Tokyo.
Something is happening within my territory.
That's a lot of cases but...
You were set up.
Don't you want to get revenge on the person who set you up?
Of course l do.
But l'm not a pro like you.
l don't know what to do...
They call me the God of Perversion.
That's why l can't let this one go.
l can't stand those who do unjust things in front of me...
The God of Perversion's arguments were incomprehensible.
You were falsely accused, so l want you to help me put them away.
That's my plan.
But do you have any proof?
Yeah.
The victims were all working for a company named...
...Heisei Construction Firm.
What?
The Heisei Construction Firm is just a suspicious-looking office building...
...that could pass for an ordinary apartment building.
Only the people going in and out were all women.
Plus they were very attractive women.
Okay, let's get her.
What? Get her?
They call me Kami-sama.
Frigid is not in my vocabulary. Just watch me.
So l decided to watch Kami-sama do his thing.
His target is a neatly dressed, beautiful office worker.
l can't believe he's doing this.
l don't think you should do this.
You just sit back and watch.
With my right hand, l can get any woman.
Nipples get hard and the clitoris will get big.
ln the end, she'll be very wet down there and will be dying for more.
There's no woman out there that can resist this hand.
For 15 minutes, it was like watching a miracle take place.
He's not even touching her, but she's getting excited.
Her body was getting very sensitive.
He was definitely the God of Perversion.
What's going on?
l can't believe what's happening.
lt's getting big and hard...
l want this.
l can't believe we're doing this in public.
l can't wait any longer. Stick it in.
Hurry up and stick it deep inside!
This is embarrassing.
My juice is flowing out.
My entire body wants your hard cock.
Give me more!
l'm releasing it inside.
Do it.
Pour your hot stuff into my womb.
As you wish.
Contract Pervert Prosecutors...
What?
Their clients tell them to eliminate certain people from society.
ln other words, they're an evil organization.
l heard about them from the previous head pervert.
But l didn't realize it became this big.
Previous head pervert?
My master.
l was surprised at the existence of this evil organization...
But l was equally surprised that his techniques were passed on from his master.
This proprietress...ls she the boss?
Tendouji Asuka. She has two subordinates.
Hirano Miyuki and Nakatsu Noriko, and...
Hey, she's...
The leader of special attack team, Suruga Rikako.
She's the one who framed you.
According to thie list, this organization has over 100 people.
l won't forgive them!
l won't forgive these women!
They're a disgrace to the art of perversion.
l'll destroy every one of them!
l'll humiliate them like never before!
Master, let me help you!
We're dealing with 100 people. We're evenly matched!
They're our enemy!
That's right! This is all out war between us and them!
According to the leather handbook, their target is the head of this school.
Their client is the assistant principal who wants to be the head.
Subordinate number one, Hirano Miyuki, is here in person.
Along with her is the leader of the special attack team.
Their target is the head of the prestigious school.
When l look at those boobs, l get very excited.
She's really a slut.
Look at her lips.
And that line that goes from her chest to her hips.
She has taste for men by nature.
Really?
That's right, you haven't had any action for over 6 months right?
Only masturbating.
You might get some action today.
lt's almost time.
l'm sorry.
What is this?
What is this strange feeling?
Your body is already feeling it.
You can't run from me.
Kami-sama's hand can hypnotize people.
When a woman is touched by his hand, she is captured by his energy.
She is unable to escape.
You slut.
l want you to tease me more.
Then suck my cock.
Yes.
Why are you...
Look, here's one more.
Kami-sama, l just love the way she sucks.
l haven't had sex in a long time, so it's very stimulating...
Suck it all up.
Did you get that?
Yes.
Yes! Give me more!
Yes, do me harder!
l'm gonna climax!
Don't worry, others are waiting.
What?
Kami-sama, thank you for treating us all the time.
You can do whatever you like with this woman.
l'm really into anal.
That feels good.
lt's embarrassing but good!
You're feeling it in your ass?
No! Don't...
Don't look at it!
Give me more and more!
l want you to give it to me hard and big!
Slut spotted at the station!
What the hell is this?
Why did Miyuki do this?
What happened?
l really don't know what happened.
You were with her, right?
Yes.
But l don't know why she did this.
lt's just...
lt's just what?
He's...
Are you telling me that Kami-sama is responsible for all this?
Kami-sama?
Yes, the 2nd God of Perversion...
l thought the Kami-sama died while having sex on the train...
lt's true, the first Kami-sama died.
But he passed on all his techniques to this man, Sugimoto Kazuo.
Supposedly, he has greater powers than the first Kami-sama.
But why is he after us?
l don't know.
But it's a matter of life and death for our organization!
Then why don't we just nail him before he gets us?
lf we underestimate his powers, we might end up getting hurt big time.
He has subordinates in the world of politics and finance.
lf we take him lightly, we might be in deep trouble.
But we can take countermeasures, right?
lf we win this battle, our name will be heard all over Japan.
l'm sure the perverts out there will be scared of us.
lf we work together, we can beat them.
l don't care if he's the God of Perversion or not.
This battle will certainly live on in the history books.
At least we got the big fish.
We have more work to do before we get their boss.
lt'll be easy with you, Kami-sama.
lf we go according to the leather handbook, we'll nail Suruga Rikako...
Let me take care of her!
She's the leader of the special attack team.
lt's dangerous.
Then teach me your techniques!
l can't teach you any.
But...
Believe.
ln order to master the art of perversion...
...you must believe in your strength and power.
lf you believe that you can get this woman...
...then you will be capable of anything.
And so, l began training to prepare for the battle with Suruga Rikako.
Kami-sama and l trained during the morning and evening rush hours...
By going after good-looking women.
You groper!
Pervert!
Are you okay?
Yes, l'll live.
My hand...
l can do it.
What's wrong?
Tomorrow's the day.
You're right.
My colleague was the one who framed me using Rikako.
He was having an affair with my wife.
l see.
But you shouldn't get sentimental.
A fight can end in an instant. Don't let your guard down.
Yes!
l'll tell you one thing.
lf you fail, l can't help you.
Then l'll have to abandon you.
Yes, l'm aware of that.
But l'll win this fight in order to master the art of perversion!