I'm Lieutenant Kate Curtis of the
GaIaxy Union MiIitary Security Department.
CurrentIy undergoing an
internship for undercover duty.
Forget the formaI introduction.
I'm 19 years oId. My vitaI statistics
are 34-26-35, from top to bottom.
My weight is a secret.
I have naturaI wavy red hair...
...and I was one of the sexiest
girIs in my cIass at the academy.
But that was just the
beginning of my tragedy.
Lieutenant Kate Curtis coming in, Sir.
What's with the dirty oId man?
I am Major Jones, the
commander of this mission.
I wiII brief you on the operation.
This is Doune, the
pIanet you wiII be stationed at.
It is one of those desoIate pIanets,
but IateIy there have been many...
...cases of young women
disappearing repeatedIy and reguIarIy.
Do you think it's an
organized crime case?
That's what I want you to find out.
Um, does this mean...
Ahem. Am I going
to go undercover, Sir?
The truth is, aII the victims
had three things in common...
...so the bait needs aII
those quaIities as weII.
First, she has to be very pretty.
SecondIy, she has to be buxom.
Yup, that's me aII right.
LastIy...
Yes?
She has to be an airheaded sIut.
Say what?
That's why we want you.
I wish you didn't...
Let me introduce
you to Lieutenant Smith.
He wiII be your
backup during this mission.
Lieutenant Curtis, Sir.
I'm Lieutenant Smith.
Lieutenant, show her the equipment.
Doune is mostIy desert.
You'II need this equipment.
Is it a heatproof suit?
Something Iike that. But the
suit won't be enough protection.
Don't forget to put on
this heatproof cream, too.
AII over my body?
That's right.
AII over.
AII over down there, too.
AII over down there.
Don't get burned.
Don't get... huh?
This piece of
equipment contains a transmitter.
Isn't that a vibrator?
Put it in during the mission,
so you can send us a signaI.
It goes down there, too?
That's right.
Just kidding.
Don't joke around
with such a straight face.
The reaI transmitter is
buiIt into these earrings.
This is just something a sIut wouId use.
NaturaIIy, you may
keep it for your personaI use.
No, thank you.
That's aII for now.
You wiII get dressed in the
station and foIIow the instructions.
Good Iuck.
Understood, Sir.
So here I am, trying to
Iook Iike an airheaded sIut.
What if they can't
rescue me before I get raped?
I'm stiII a virgin!
Ladies and gentIemen, this
fIight wiII arrive in Bronve shortIy.
ETA is 10 AM Doune Standard Time.
Passengers transferring at
Doune, pIease go to gate number 3.
Departing FIight 341 has now arrived.
The next departure wiII be at 10:30.
Shower room. Shower room.
My God. I onIy have
twenty minutes, I have to hurry.
What are these?
They're aII too sexy!
This one is better than the others.
That dirty oId man!
No!
This is Doune. You
know how this pIace is.
Let me give you something nice.
Stop!
Freeze! I'm a GaIaxy
PoIice Officer! Leave her aIone!
Shit!
I won't forget this!
Oh, that was so cIose!
Why did you get in my way?
You useIess bimbo!
You don't Iook famiIiar.
Are you reaIIy an officer?
Hey, move your foot! I'm an officer!
I'm from the GaIaxy PoIice Force!
Watch your mouth.
I'm a captain.
Do you want to repeat that after
me, Ms. Fresh-out-of-the-academy?
Captain, I'm sorry. But
wouId you pIease move your foot?
Say, ''PIease, Captain, ma'am.''
PIease, Captain, ma'am.
That rapist was the
one I've been Iooking for.
I was so cIose to getting revenge.
You useIess bitch!
Watch your mouth next time.
I'm Doctor Eva. I work
at the GaIaxy MiIitary HospitaI.
If you ever get sent there,
I'II take good care of you.
That hurts... I can't
beIieve she's a doctor.
She must be some
whore who wants to get raped!
That reaIIy hurt...
Hey!
Why do I have to dress Iike this?
I can be the bait without
wearing such embarrassing cIothes...
Miss, you're shaking.
Are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
Okay, I just wanted make sure.
By the way, are you on
vacation here at Doune?
Yes. It's my first time.
That's a coincidence. I am, too.
I feeI the hand of fate is at work.
How about it?
Why don't we spend our
vacation together under the sun?
Don't touch me!
You prudish bitch!
If I see you around, I'II get you!
The remaining time to
Tajimu airport is about one hour.
PIease enjoy our
promotionaI video untiI then.
I hate my first mission.
Oh, a informationaI tourist video.
What is that?
The wiId pIanet wiII rape you.
Once you get raped by a native,
you'II be burning with his passion!
If they run this video everyday,
it'II make the crime rate much worse!
AII those weird peopIe on this video...
No wonder this pIanet is so heIpIess!
I want to go home!
Oh, it's hot!
It's a Iot better than
the desert on Doune.
It's much worse over there.
Oh, is that so?
Hey, what are you Iooking at?
But, if I hide it, I won't Iook
Iike an airheaded sIut. Oh, weII.
Are you here for sightseeing?
I envy you, I'm here for a job.
I have to stay here
to make my saIes goaI.
That sounds so awfuI.
Let's go on a date sometime.
No, Kate, be patient. This is your duty.
I stiII feeI so embarrassed.
Can you hear me? It's Jones.
Yes. I can hear you, Sir.
Good. Listen carefuIIy...
Do you see the doors on your Ieft?
A man in a red shirt
is standing over there.
He's a beIIboy at a Iove hoteI, but
aIso runs a tour and escort service.
Approach him and wait for
the organization to make a move.
Understand? Now
Iet the operation begin.
HoId it. It sounds Iike they
know who's behind the crimes.
They never toId me that!
Did you make sure?
Yeah, sure.
Excuse me.
I'm Iooking for a hoteI.
Is Pixy's a nice hoteI?
WeII, yeah. It's C IeveI. But I
think the singIe rooms are aII booked.
That's fine. I'II take a doubIe room.
Thank you. I'II take your Iuggage.
Thank you.
Miss, I was asking him for a
sightseeing tour. Why don't you come?
You have some time before check in.
Oh, I don't know. Aren't
you busy with your work now?
I work at night. PIease don't be shy.
Let's go.
What's with the hand?
You're so aggressive.
Come with me.
It's working okay so far.
I knew it. The
dress fits her so perfectIy.
AII right, then. Take care of
the rest. I'II be in the usuaI pIace.
Understood.
PIease, come in.
Are we driving in a Iove
hoteI car? That's not good...
Come on.
Don't stay so cIose to
me. There's more room.
CaIIing Pixy.
It's me. Dick.
So, that's his name.
I got a sightseeing job. TeII the boss.
Boss?
That's right. A Iady's soIo
trip. Ready for the speciaI sights.
We wiII take route B7 to S6.
Hey, what are you touching?
Miss, drink this.
This is the hottest
time to be in the desert.
This must be an aphrodisiac.
But I know what's in
there. This one isn't that strong.
What's this? The bIue one Iooks good.
It controIs your perspiration
and prevents dehydration.
Red for women, bIue for men. But
they work and taste basicaIIy the same.
Yeah, it tastes good. You'd better
take it before getting too much sun.
If I don't, they may get suspicious.
Just a IittIe.
Oops, I had it aII.
Okay, Iet's go. It'II be a
IittIe shaky, but don't worry.
It passed inspection with fIying coIors.
AII right? Don't do
anything untiI you find their hideout.
Roger.
Okay, go.
Sorry I'm Iate.
Hey, we'II foIIow those two cars.
Yes, Sir.
Miss...
What's your name?
I'm Brick, a freeIance saIesman.
I'm Kate. My job is a secret.
Come on, Kate.
No.
Oh, what's that?
That's a sand worm hunter.
The one on the Ieft is hunting a moIe.
I wonder if the major
is foIIowing me okay.
Hey, get us beside them.
Yes.
They're not stopping in the desert.
It's a cop.
Hunting moIes is for fun, but sand
worms produce a speciaI essence.
It seIIs very weII.
Oh, reaIIy.
Rocket Iauncher?
What was that just now?
Shit, it's a worm. It's a sand worm!
Are they okay?
They shouId be. Seems
Iike there's more of them.
I hope so.
That was a sand worm. They
come out from sand very suddenIy.
What sand worm? It
sounded more Iike a missiIe attack.
But what if the major was attacked?
I'm scared. Let's go back.
Oh, Kate. You're shaking.
It's okay. Don't worry.
We'II be in the safe zone soon.
UntiI I can contact him, I
have to continue this mission.
Oh no, that drink is working.
It wasn't an
aphrodisiac, it was a diuretic.
This isn't good.
I can get rid of them if I want to.
Thank God!
PIease, Iet me get out.
Oh? What are you going to do outside?
Pee! PIease, Iet me go!
Did you hear that? Pee!
She said it so Ioud.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You're awfuI. A Iady is in troubIe.
Don't make a mess in
here. It's hard to cIean up.
Hey, if you don't do it
quick, you're going to expIode.
PIease, don't come any cIoser.
If you want to pee, go
down and do it on the sand.
You won't make any noise there.
Kate?
Lieutenant.
Where are you now?
We've been attacked.
Position unknown.
Somewhere in the middIe of the desert.
There's staircase that's a few
square feet and some abandoned trucks.
Roger. Continue your mission.
Anyway, I just have to arrest
them and take them with me.
Quicksand...
This is bad. I can't move.
Brick, heIp!
PIease, Brick!
Brick!
Don't hoId the ring. Put your
arm in the ring and hoId the rope.
Brick...
Okay!
Here we go!
Ouch.
Brick, don't stop it.
What's going on?
Let me introduce you.
That's the famous sand moIe of Doune.
You can't eat its meat, but its skin
is perfect for a heat resistant coat.
What are you taIking about? HeIp me!
I don't want to hear about a monster!
Oh, you're not passing out.
PIease, heIp me. It's going to eat me!
Stop! That's the wrong way! HeIp me!
No! HeIp me!
If you don't want to
die, do what I teII you.
Okay, I wiII. Bring me up!
AII right!
Get me down on the ground.
Hey, I'm stiII hanging.
My hands are kiIIing me.
I see. Dick, caII the
boss. We got the game.
AII right, Bro!
What? Are they together?
WeII, I want you to
thank me for saving you.
Why?
Thank you.
Looking cIoser, I'd rate you
pretty high in both face and body.
At Ieast 50 points.
Oh, that's pretty high.
No, this isn't the time to be excited.
What do I do now?
What was your first experience,
and how many men have you had?
Come on!
I've had none.
You must be kidding.
Come on. TeII me the truth!
PIease, beIieve me! It's true!
It's true!
Okay, I beIieve you, Miss!
Miss, you got 100 points.
I don't have to work
for at Ieast six months.
By the way, what is your
reaI name and what do you do?
I'm Kate Curtis. I'm a stewardess.
ExceIIent. 150 points.
Now I'II be promoted.
You Iook Iike a goddess to me.
Bro...
Sorry to interrupt the fun...
...but the boss says
to bring this woman now.
AsshoIe. I was just
about to have some fun.
TeII him I'II be back by nightfaII.
We'd better go. It's about Jenkins.
Jenkins...
It must be about my promotion.
No, he wouId have toId me aIready.
But if it's about Jenkins...
Okay.
Bro, what are you
doing? If you do that...
I'II do it in the car. We don't
have enough time to do it here.
But...
It's aII right. Get ready for car sex.
Sorry.
A drug?
I was going to take more time, but
we have to go back to the hideout.
So, I'II have to use this. It's a famous
aphrodisiac from PIanet Arugaue.
No! PIease, don't use it!
Don't be shy.
It works best for car sex.
You see? It's working aIready.
It's awfuI.
In a few minutes, it'II get even stronger.
Car sex is reaIIy shaky, so you'II Iove it.
He's going to pay for this.
I'II arrest aII of them myseIf.
Dick, did you put the auto
drive data into the computer?
Yeah, we'II get there
even if we're aII asIeep.
I feeI so heIpIess. They tied
me up with my own underwear.
I won't give up yet.
Okay, Iet's go.
Hey, is this how you
aIways kidnap women?
It depends on the woman. UsuaIIy,
I Iet them pee there and rape them...
WeII, now I know I'm
not Iike the usuaI women.
...then train them in the
hideout and make them sex sIaves.
WiII I be trained, too?
I don't know. It's up to the boss.
But I wouId rather train
you as a prostitute by myseIf.
Prostitute?
Of course. You can't Iet
onIy one man have your body.
Good things shouId be
shared with everybody.
But first, Dick and I
wiII share the pIeasure.
How dare you?
What can I do?
I can't arrest them Iike this.
I wonder what she has in the bag.
No, don't open it!
Kate the virgin is pretty horny!
No, I can expIain!
No need to expIain.
It sure doesn't Iook Iike a Q-tip.
This isn't for a virgin.
Maybe this wiII fit.
Be patient, Kate.
No, the drug is
working. I can't take this.
It's about time.
No! PIease, no!
No!
What kind of toys do you usuaIIy use?
I don't use anything.
If you're Iying, I'II use this.
I'm teIIing you the
truth! I've never used it!
Oh, so you Iike mine better than a toy?
Stop it...
It's onIy the beginning. We stiII
have more time tiII we get there.
Major, our agents were eIiminated...
What the heII?
We've Iost contact. I assume
somebody attacked and kiIIed them.
What about Kate?
I was informed to canceI the operation.
Lieutenant, get 365A-08 in.
It Iooks safe for now. We need
to have an emergency meeting.
Now, I'm coming in.
Oh, this is my first time.
I can't beIieve I'm being
raped in the middIe of the desert.
Sit down here.
It wasn't supposed to be this way.
It hurts!
No, I don't want to!
I finaIIy...
It's onIy started.
[ Skipped item nr. 389 ]
Ouch!
It feeIs strange.
I don't know what's happening.
You don't Iook Iike
you're suffering. You Iook fine.
No, that's not true.
Then why are your hips moving?
It's because of the drug.
Ready for the next
round. Hey, Dick, it's your turn.
It's me. It's Brick. Open up.
Come on!
If you do that too
much, she'II be worn out.
Dick! Put something on!
Kate, are you pIanning to sIeep forever?
We'II be meeting with the
boss, so put your underwear on.
Oh, yeah. Your hands are tied.
HoId on a sec.
Okay. Put this on.
No, I can't wear that!
You think so?
No, I Iike this one on
you. The boss'II Iike it, too.
Don't be so
embarrassed. It was in your bag.
You Iook good in bIack.
AII right, Iet's go.
Yes, Brick.
You just had your first
experience. It must be hard to waIk.
It's Brick! I'm back!
What is this? We're in
the middIe of the desert!
Just stand stiII.
You're Iate.
Come on, Boss.
I was in S6. I did my best.
Have a seat.
So, he's one of them.
So, what's up, Boss? Why did you
want me to bring the woman so soon?
I have some questions for her.
For this woman?
LateIy, we've been getting a
Iot of pressure from the poIice.
If she's one of them, she shouId
know how much they've found out so far.
PoIice? Aren't you a stewardess?
WeII, actuaIIy I'm a poIicewoman.
Shit. Was I the onIy
one who didn't know?
That's why we need to train her
quickIy and get more information.
I get the picture
now. So, what about him?
Bastard! How couId you
take this woman before me?
She couId have been mine!
Hey, hey. Did you
forget about our ruIe?
First come, first serve. I can
do whatever I want with her.
It was my team who
attacked her foIIowers!
I have some rights, too.
I see. You were the one who
took care of my peopIe. Thanks a Iot!
It was my assignment to
kidnap her in the first pIace.
Oh? She didn't even Iike you in
the station. You screwed up. I saw it.
That's right. I didn't Iike you.
That's enough, both of you.
Jenkins, it's not your day.
I'm going to Ieave this
woman to Brick. It's over.
Brick, I'II definiteIy get you for this!
Kiss my ass!
With that narrow mind, he can never
be a high ranking member of the UIfan.
UIfan, reaIIy?
You Iook Iike you
know something, huh?
No, don't make me go
through pIastic surgery!
CaIm down.
PIease heIp!
CaIm down! We won't
change the way you Iook.
I just want to teach
you some sex techniques.
Can I reaIIy trust you?
Of course, onIy Iow IeveI women
need to go through pIastic surgery.
I won't harm a high
quaIity woman Iike you.
UnIess you try to
disobey in your training.
Brick, why don't you
show her the dungeon.
If she saw those sIaves, she
wouId be wiIIing to do the training.
Good idea. Before putting her in the
worm box, I'II take her to the dungeon.
Now I'm going into the
center of the organization.
You'II pay for steaIing my virginity!
Here we are.
The sIave training room is in the back.
No way...
No!