No! No!
No!
Now to find a new blossom.
A butterfly!
Oh, another one got away!
Kirei, wait up!
If you run off like that, you
won't find your way back!
Oh, I said I'd be okay! You're
such a worrywort, Rui.
That wide-open sea! That
blue sky! That huge sun!
If you say that this all isn't
getting to you, then you're lying!
I...
Oh, you're too uptight, Rui!
You have to learn to enjoy the moment!
Easy for you to say...
Huh? What's that?
Who are those guys?
Must be locals.
Darn it, there are no
goodlooking guys around here!
Now that I think about it, there
aren't many tourists, either.
It doesn't look like this island
has much resort development.
Oh! Another butterfly!
Wait! Kirei!
Don't run too far!
What about those women?
That's what I call a tourist attraction!
Great bodies.
With gazongas like you wouldn't believe!
Kirei! Kirei!
Oh, Kirei... How far did you run?
This island's crawling with butterflies.
Why, you... Wait!
What's with this guy?
I ran into him, but he isn't saying anything.
Oh, well.
A strong-willed girl...
Excuse me!
Um, did a girl just come by here?
Rui?
Rui!
Another butterfly! This time for sure...
Rui, what's going on?!
Stop it! Let me go!
It looks like Rui wants to do it with you.
What? What are you saying?
That's why we gave Rui that juice.
Did you know that even our
language has a word for it?
Rui, stop it! What's wrong
with you? This is gross!
Lesbianism.
Rui, stop it!
What's going on here? Rui's acting so weird.
Just what happened when we passed out?
Spread it all over her, Rui. It's
a wonderful potion, after all.
Wait! Stop! This can't be happening! Rui!
Rui, stop!
Soon, this woman, too, will start
to show her sensual nature.
Even after all the ones we've seen...
...she really turns me on!
The potion's taking effect.
I think that's enough, Rui.
What's wrong, Kirei?
As it takes effect, you
should really start to feel it.
Man, listen to her moan! She
must like to have meat in her.
Nah, looking at her, I'd say
she's a masochist, Dabide.
Check out that look on her
face! She's really getting into it!
Kirei...
No... No... Rui...
You feel it, don't you, Kirei?
Nothing to be ashamed of, Kirei...
Let your feelings go.
Rui...
Before you woke up, the
warmth I felt from your body...
...as I was putting on the potion
was more than I could stand.
Dabide promised me. If
I can make you come...
I'll be rewarded.
Rewarded with his
huge... Hard... All I want of it.
You mean...!
Let it all out.
That's right. That's beautiful.
Like a flower blooming out of season.
Try rubbing breasts with her, Rui.
Quickly! Or you won't get your reward!
I don't believe it.
I don't want to believe.
Me
me
my
friend
me
this
place
my
friend
me
THESE MEN
this
place
But, the truth is
that I'm being raped...
...and I 'm enjoying it.
Kirei... Kirei...
Wake up, Kirei! Open
your eyes, Kirei... Kirei...
I...
It was real...
Rui?
You brought the key to those handcuffs?
Rui! Rui!
Rui, snap out of it!
Oh, God, what have I done?
Let's get out of here, Rui!
Rui! Hurry, run! Hurry!
Why? Why is this happening?
Oh, no...
Why...?
Kirei... I found a butterfly... A butterfly...
A butterfly?
A butterfly...
You...
Just where are you going?
The fun's just beginning.
Damned girl! How dare
you run away like that!
Kirei, snap out of it!
Rui...!
We don't need that one anymore.
Stop!
Rui!
Kirei, save yourself!
No... No...
NO!!!
Do it.
Rui!
You're next.
How dare you!
Shut up, you little bitch!
Do you hear me, Rui? You can
enjoy yourself down there forever!
He's insane!
Now, then...
To really give you a special punishment.
No! Let me go!
No! No! Stop it!
Stop... Stop it, please!
Please!
No!
Become even more beautiful.
Stop it!
No! NO!!!
No!
Don't! Stop it!
I couldn't believe it. Before I realized it...
...I was yelling with passion.
Before I realized it, I had
stopped asking him to stop.
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
More! Give me more!
I just love how she keeps asking for it!
You perverted bitch! Say it!
Well? Is it here? Do you want it here?
Yes! It feels so good!
You've shown me all that
is beautiful about you.