Welcome to the frontier, Lord Zeon.
Now, what can I do for you?
By order of the Ransford Roundtable,
we're here to inspect this world.
Oh, another tedious inspection.
The Republic Forces apparently
distrust Estorida's neutrality.
I'd like to stress that this
is for the sake of peace.
If you're insulted, let me apologize at once.
No need. Anyway, you must be tired...
...from your long journey, Lord Zeon.
Would you care to attend the
banquet we've scheduled and relax?
No, thank you...
...but we appreciate the offer
from the bottom of our hearts.
If you'll excuse us.
Brain-dead fool!
An inspection. Is that a pretext?
Only half of one. The Roundtable
gave me two missions.
First, to determine whether
the legendary warrior...
...really has awakened
on this world. Second...
To verify this world's neutrality.
To see whether the rumors
of Imperial collusion are true.
I have a feeling these guys have
cut some deal as appeasement.
There'll be a war, won't there?
Lady Miran, we have to find the warrior first.
Find the legendary Druid warrior.
I can only rely on you. Please.
SLAVE WARRIOR MAYA
Um, may I?
It gets cold at night.
This should help a little.
Um...
Excuse me.
Wait! I'm Maya. Won't
you tell me your name?
Please?
Leyna.
Leyna, thank yo-
Leyna, are you still here?
And what's this?
Don't you understand yet that
slaves don't need clothes?
No!
Nakedness suits a sex
slave, don't you think?
I'm Eluma, your trainer.
Stop it! Please, let me go home!
What are you saying? A
sex slave has no freedom.
I'll have to teach you that from now on.
With this dirty little body.
Well? How does my tongue feel?
Please... Stop it...
S- Stop it!
You still say that, when you're
wet right down to your asshole?
That's it. Perhaps you'll be thankful.
Thankful for Lord Garius' handiwork.
What? My vagina...
My vagina...! No!
Open your eyes and see.
No... It wasn't a dream.
It's still sensitive.
Not surprising seeing how it's newly grown.
I feel... I feel sick...
Hot... It's going to burst.
No... I'm going to cum!
No... No... NO!!!
Looks like you just popped your first load.
Now I'll take my time teaching you.
Of the joys of women. Of flesh. Of slavery.
We may be on the frontier...
...but the bustle of a marketplace
feels the same everywhere.
Really.
No trail, no starting point, and no leads.
So, where do we begin?
Lady Miran?
Lady Miran, what's wrong?
There's a familiar scent here.
Maya...!
I can't stop.
From Earth?
Yeah. It's another world,
totally different from this one.
My mom and dad are
there. Oh! Final exams!
I screwed up on my midterms
and have to do well this time!
And I have to return that CD to Yoshimi.
Oh, yeah! And the concert!
I promised Yoshimi I'd go with her.
I wonder if it's over. It probably is...
I want to go home. But
I can't with this body.
How could I face anyone?
With this... With this,
I'm not human anymore!
Maya, at least you have
a place to go back to.
I've always been here.
I'll live here till I'm old and then I'll die here.
Leyna...
Cheer up. If you don't lose hope...
...the god Romus will lead you.
You'll go back to your world!
Let's run away, Maya.
I'll drug the jailer tonight.
We'll use the chance and
slip out the back way.
This way, Maya.
If we climb this, the back
gate's just a few steps away.
Maya, run from here.
What's...?
I just switched keys, Leyna.
I've already told you that
slaves don't have to speak.
You must be punished.
Maya, do you know what this is?
It's a parasite from the
Rhodesia star system.
It's your new best friend.
Oh, look. It likes you.
No... Stop it, please!
What a fine view. I can see
right up into your uterus.
No...
Please! I won't run away again!
I'll forget about my old world!
I'll be a sex slave with all my heart!
Just, please, please stop!
Glad you've accepted it. But
perhaps I should put it in...
...so you can become an expert sex slave.
Once this thing's inside
of you, it becomes like...
...a reproductive organ and
controls your sexual appetite.
It'll take over your brain and...
...you'll crave sex all the time. You'll
become the perfect sex slave.
Isn't that lovely, Maya?
No! Stop it! Please, stop it!
Stop that and be a good girl.
Isn't this what you wanted?
Now, take it. Take it into you.
What's wrong, Lady Miran?
A dream...
A dream?
Lady Miran...
Forgive me.
Lady Miran, I think we've got company.
I thought so.
What?!
Is that really the great hero Lord Zeon?
Who's there?!
Here! Here! Right here.
Diana!
So, do your senses get dull
when you're around pretty girls?
Zeon, you ol' dog!
A Druid warrior, huh?
Yes. I'm prepared for anything.
We're trying hard to cover every direction.
As a spy for the Republic Forces,
have you heard anything?
Well, there's that one
about the holy sword...
What?!
Hold on!
These rumors show up on every
world once or twice, right?
Yes, that's true.
The thing is, I've heard
another warrior has awakened.
Diana, is that true?!
Yeah. I heard some guy
named Estilgar was after her.
Lady Miran...
But, the problem is that
apparently she's a slave.
Well? Did that excite you?
Maya...
Leyna, she seems to want to thank you.
Thanks to you, she's
become a fine sex slave.
No...
When the parasite destroys her brain...
...she'll be a prisoner of her desires.
No! Maya, please! Wake up!
You're wasting your time, Leyna.
Come, Maya. You must thank her.
Maya, wake up! Maya!
Please... do me...
Go on, make love to Maya, Leyna.
Go on!
What are you doing, Leyna?!
You know what happens
to slaves who don't obey!
Your tongue and teeth will be ripped out!
Your arms and legs cut off!
You'll be chained to the lavatory!
Just a lump of flesh for servicing men!
Do you want to become
a domestic animal slave?
No...
If you understand, do it!
No! Maya, stop it.
You're this wet? Liar...
Maya... Maya...
Who's there?
Awaken, Maya.
Stop it. Leave me alone. It feels so nice...
I just want to sleep...
Awaken, Maya!
You have a duty! A destiny to fulfill!
Stop it, please... Stop... Enough...
It doesn't matter!
Overcome your trials and tribulations, Maya!
Stop it!
Lady Miran, what's wrong?
Are you all right, Lady Miran?
I heard it. A voice.
The cry of a warrior.
And I saw an image, too.
An image of something about to happen.
What in the world...?!
Lady Miran!