l'm Kenta Ochiai.
lt's hard to admit, but l've never had any luck with girls.
But ever since Suwatee and her friends moved in, my life's changed!
l got to *BEEP* Kaori AND Misao, one right after the other!
lt seems like there's an endless supply of girls to *BEEP* *BEEP*!
Suwatee is sweet, and Shuree is a nosy loudmouth.
But l'm turning into some kind of animal!
No! No, no, no, no!
That's not the way it should be.
Love is a natural, beautiful thing!
Then a new girl stepped into my love life.
The girl who landed right in front of me is Chisato Sugita.
Ah, l feel destiny again!
Can Can Bunny
Extra 2
Welcome!
Chisato, are you feeling better?
Sorry. l haven't been sleeping much lately.
This comic is almost exactly like ''X-2''.
Did you write it, Chisato?
Do you watch X-2, Kenta? l'm a huge fan!
Space Detective X-2!
An otaku girl?
Be quiet, Shuree!
Ah, um... nothing!
Have you shown this to a publisher?
No, l'd be embarrassed to show it to someone l didn't know.
lt just so happens that l'm working part time at Shudansha, the comic publisher.
Chisato, l'll introduce you to the editor.
Amazing! l'm so lucky l met you, Kenta!
How fortunate, Kenta.
A girl who thinks she can count on you!
Good! Go, Mars!
Don't give up, Venus!
Five more girls...
Kenta, l wish you would realize how l feel about you.
What is this? What's going on?
This... this can't be!
Suwatee!
The Northern Emperor Shibi!
Suwatee, do you know why l am here?
Yes, it's because l stole the stars.
l'm really sorry.
You must return the seven stars before the full moon,
or else become my one thousandth wife.
Furthermore, lf you use the star to touch a human man,
you will lose all memory of him.
But...
lt's been awhile since l enjoyed a virgin like you!
Yes! Then l'll pick up the manuscript tonight. Yes.
What do you think, Chief?
The art and plot are fine, but...
Well...
Chisato, you're a big Space Detective X-2 fan, aren't you?
Yes.
Lots of people are following that trend in comics.
lf you want to be a star, you need your own style.
l see.
The deadline for our New Manga Competition is soon, but...
...you could enter a finished copy of this one.
Chief!
But still, it's such a surprise to see Kenta bring a girl here all of a sudden!
But l...
You're such a nice guy.
But, it is one of your best qualities.
l'm not going to enter the contest.
With exams next year, if l stop going to class, my mom will kill me.
But if l cut back on how much l sleep, it'll be like it was earlier today.
But, since having Aya see it, l'm feeling better.
Thank you for your help, Kenta.
Chisato, wait a minute!
Kenta?
You're awfully quiet. What's wrong?
Come on, tell your cousin.
Wait a minute, okay? lt's a mess.
Okay, come on in, Chisato.
Okay.
lt's not a great room, but...
What, is this girl with you?
Be quiet!
Did you say something?
Oh, it was nothing!
Anyways, please use this
room as often as you want.
But...
Hey, Kenta, are you back?
Well, well, a girl, you old wolf.
So? How many times have you done it?
Saiki!
Get out of here!
Yeah, yeah, sure.
But first look at this!
Ta da!
What's this?
l'm the lead actor. Come and see me!
Are you stupid? Only kids are interested in that kind of thing.
X-2! Wonderful!
Okay then, this poster is a present for Kenta's new girlfriend.
Wow! Really?!
Space Detective!
X-2!
So, you'll be there!
Now listen...
See you, Kenta! Have fun doing it!
Just hurry up and get out!
Our Earth is turning round in space.
The Earth is like a blue pearl in space.
A spaceman said this beautiful Earth is for you and for me.
ln this way...
That's a pretty lame disguise!
Kenta...
This imagery allows us to see the Earth as...
Jeez, she's been hard at work for three hours!
l'm sorry, Ma'am.
lt was all my idea.
l just wanted to give Chisato time to write her comic.
So, please don't tell her mother.
Don't worry. lt's no problem.
lt's so sweet of you to want to help.
But l feel a little jealous of Chisato.
When l see a happy couple, l can't help wanting to tempt the man a little.
Are you okay?
T-That's pretty tempting!
Oh, good grief!
l can't believe how much he gets laid!
Hey, what's with you?
You're acting so weird. What's up?
Nothing, really.
That's so good, Kenta.
Right there... deeper!
So good! That's it!
Not yet...
l think l'm going to come!
Pull out!
Please! Squirt it on me!
So much! There's so much!
Chisato, what's up?
Kenta!
All the comics you wrote got thrown away?
Mom found them while l was at school.
l had most of the new one in my bag,
but the deadline is so close.
l don't have time to both study and re-draw the missing parts.
You helped me so much, Kenta.
l'm really sorry. l feel-
Heads up!
Sorry!
Kenta!
Chisato, l'll help you!
You've worked so hard. lf we work together, we can do it!
Kenta!
Chisato, l've finished drawing that part.
Then fill in the colors.
Okay, sure.
What's with her?
She's determined to finish the comic.
He's going to exhaust himself.
He won't quit.
Good morning, Kenta!
l'm the first one here.
Were you here all night?
Yes, well...
You sure have stamina.
These days it's hard to find a man like that.
Aya!
So energetic!
That's so good, Aya!
Give it to me harder.
l can't...
l can't hold on!
Kenta!
Shuree, how's Kenta doing?
Come on. There's nothing you can do.
Shuree, l... l...
Let Chisato take care of him for now.
l'm sorry, Kenta. lt's my fault you're sick.
He'll be fine in no time. He's just tired.
Nurse...
He just needs to rest.
Kenta...
Seiryuka Hospital
Kenta, l promise you l won't give up!
How's Kenta?
Kenta, l finally finished it!
This is the comic for the contest!
That's fantastic, Chisato!
Hey, did you stay here with me all night?
Working on the manga, of course.
Thank you.
That's the best medicine l could get.
Suwatee, forget about Kenta,
and let's go home. Okay?
What about the promise Suwatee made to the Northern Emperor Shibi?
Alright you guys, what did you mean by that?
They told me everything.
Hurry up and tell Kenta it's over and return the stars!
Suwatee.
With the star l can make love to Kenta...
...but, l wouldn't remember any of it!
l thought if Kenta would treat me like a woman,
l would be able to leave everything.
But, l don't want to forget about Kenta!
l love him, but we can't be together!
l don't want to become Emperor Shibi's wife!
No! No! l just want to die!
Suwatee, calm down!
No, let go of me! l want to die!
Suwatee!
No!
Stop!
Suwatee, l wish Kenta would realize how much you love him.
Space Detective X-2 Show!
l can't wait to hear about the contest!
lf you win, what will you do?
l gave it my best shot. Even if l lose, l'm happy about that.
What's happened to X-2?
Why isn't it starting?!
X-2! X-2! Aren't you here yet?!
X-2! X-2! Where are you?!
Saiki, you idiot! You hurt your back?
Probably did it screwing some girl!
Who are you guys?
We're Saiki's friends.
Saiki's friends?
What?
Okay...
l got it.
You're Chisato, aren't you?
You're a big X-2 fan, right?
Saiki, you bastard. You set us up.
Here's hoping Kenta doesn't screw up.
Are you feeling okay, Chisato?
You haven't slept much lately.
l'm fine! l feel great!
l get to be X-2! Wow!
X-2! X-2! X-2!
Shut up you brats! X-2 has abandoned you all! Get them!
Hold it!
That voice!
Space Detective X-2!
Evil Spirit! l warned you not to hurt children!
D-Don't lecture me!
Get him!
Bring it on, evil doers!
Watch out!
This costume is so hot, and it's heavy.
l feel faint.
Chisato!
No... l must get up! l must get up!
What's wrong? What's wrong? Stand up, X-2! Stand up!
Kenta!
l'll handle this.
Shuree!
Spirits of the air! Gather to me!
Hide that which can be seen!
Show that which is hidden!
Lend thy strength... to me!
Kids, Space Detective X-2 is in trouble!
lf you cheer, he'll get stronger!
Shuree, why are you going so far?
Let's all sing the X-2 song!
With his hands...
...he banishes evil.
For the sake of the ones we love.
The sign of the galaxy...
l can't let the kids down.
They're cheering for me.
...Space Detective, X-2.
l can't lose.
l can't lose!
Chisato!
Waruda, you're next!
Get ready!
Dragon Star Punch!
Galaxy Kick!
Go, X-2!
Meteorite Drop!
lron Kick!
Chisato, that's good enough...
Super Special COMET BAZOOKA KlCK!
Shuree, that was terrible!
lt's out of my hands.
Hooray! X-2 won!
l did it, Kenta!
Well, that was unexpected.
Well, thanks for bailing me out.
Stop by the office later, and l'll pay you.
l'm sorry, Kenta. l got a little carried away.
Don't worry about it.
Well, you'll remember this day, won't you?
Yes.
l'll go change now-
Chisato!
Are you all right?
l feel a little dizzy.
lt's really hot inside this costume.
You'd better get out of it.
Thank you.
Do you feel a little better now?
Don't look at me. l'm embarrassed.
Chisato.
No...
Kenta, that's...
l'm sweaty. lt's awful...
lt don't mind... if it's you...
Don't do that!
ls it alright, Chisato?
Be gentle, please.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
lt feels so intense...
l feel kind of...
lt's so hot!
Chisato, l'm...
l'm gonna...
...come!
Seiryuka Hospital
How can they charge so much for two nights?
Kenta, you're paying for your fun.
What do you mean?
l feel a source of strong spiritual energy!
Out in the courtyard!
Oh, that's...
Wow! What a huge flower garden!
That's strange. lt's gone...
l can't believe how big it is.
That's not the point.
Who is it? Who's there?
Oh, Kenta.
And you are?
Who's that beautiful woman?
You're supposed to be invisible.
People with strong spiritual sense can see me.
What happened to Chisato?
Uh, she's no one special!
Oh, now l remember. You were my nurse.
l'm really just a student.
My name is Haruna. Haruna Sakamoto.
This is a beautiful garden.
Yes, my grandfather said there used to be a church here before the war.
A friend of his looks after the garden now that he's passed away.
Don't you have any...
Relatives? No.
Hey, Haruna!
Yes, Uncle Okamura?
How's it going? Did you find your lost necklace?
No, l'm still looking.
Okay, good luck.
l have to go have another test now.
Excuse me, l need to keep looking for my necklace.
Okay, see you.
You know, Shuree...
What?
Now that l think of it, you really are quite beautiful.
Stupid! What are you saying all of the sudden?
Like you don't say that to every girl you meet!
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
l thought l'd dropped it here.
Help me...
Help me!