My heart is turning to ice...
I'm being sealed in by ice that will never melt...
Thats what l thought on that day when I knew that I had really lost you...
His stay in the hospital is going to be even longer?
l'm all right. You don't need to worry.
Mom, l just want you to stay with dad.
Okay Bye
Oh... I have to put out the yard waste.
He trimmed a lot off those trees.
I wonder what Dad will say when he comes back from the hospital.
Nii-sama, do your best ok!
Yeah, well, l'm going...
You haven't forgotten anything? Do you have your handkerchief?
You know, l'm not in elementary school.
Hm?
Oh! Good Morning, Kuimiko-san.
This is Hashimoto Kumiko-san who lives next door.
Next door? Then she's the landlord...
Hi. l'm Narahashi Shouma and from today l'll...
l've already heard about you from Chisato-san.
Well, that makes things easy... well then, see you!
Ah! Nii-sama!
Geez!
He's that type of man... l'm sorry.
I don't really mind.
Then, just heat it in the microwave right before you eat.
I'm sorry, you have to helped me so much.
Cooking for a party is fun... a welcome home party for you brother, its realIy nice.
Yes... l hope you'll come too, Kuimiko-san.
N.. no...
I...
Kuimiko-san?
Uh... l won't tonight.
But...
It should be just family tonight... after all, its been ten years.
Let's have another party soon, it will give me more opportunity to cook.
Yes. Let's definately do that, Kuimiko-san.
Yes
What a stylish party! It's all for Nii-sama welcome home.
We're not related by blood, because he's the grandson of our adopted grandfather, who passed away.
Today...
The man who moved in next door...
He reminded me of you so much.
I was really surprised...
lt's strange, isn t it?
When neither his face or body looks like you at all...
Darling, Darling, l'm so lonely.
I'm not myself today...
Damn it, Kuu. Give me back my cigarettes.
No, and l mean it! You can't have it back until you finish shoveing the snow!
You can take a break without smoking, can't you?
People used to call a break, having a smoke you know.
That's got nothing to do with this! Oh! Kumiko-san!
Hm?
Hello!
Hm? Hey, Brother, why are you staring?
Hey Brother!
Dummy! You're embarassing her!
That's cause you're not listening to me at all.
Excuise me...
See you did it again, Brother!
Shouma-san...
When l look back... I think changes were happening inside me, where the ice had frozen everything...
Do you like things like that?
Shouma-san!
I'm sorry, did l surprise you?
You were looking at them so intently.
Uh...no... l'm sorry l yelIed like that.
Uh... um... it's a vase!
Huh?
Uh... that is...
l broke my vase...
And, I was looking for another.
I see.
l wish they had wrapped these flowers.
They look like green onions or cabbage in this.
Shouma-san, I heard you used to be a vioIinist.
That's in the past... presently, l'm just a poor editor for a newsletter.
l see...
What is it?
Um, I have a favor to ask...
Thank you for today.
Not at all. lt was just a perfomance by an amateur.
Your nieces are very cute.
It's the first time they heard a live performance of a violin.
They were so happy.
l'm... a widow...
What?
My husband was a musician, too... And, he used to play the piano for them.
Maybe that's why they love music.
Why am I doing this? Why am revealing myseIf to him like this?
We never made our marriage official, so my family name is still Hashimoto.
For some reason, my husband refused to fill out a marriage certificate.
My husband had cancer... I think it was because he knew.
That's why he never filled the papers?
He never ate much to begin with...
So I didn't realize that he was sick.
Oh? ls that Chisato?
Uh... Please let me off here. I have some shopping to do.
Nii-sama actually Iikes children a lot. l think he enjoyed playing for them.
l hope so.
Oh, that's right... Would you like some tea? We just got in some very good ones.
Yes, thank you, I will.
Chisato-san, you seem happier, recentIy.
It's all thanks to Nii-sama. I've been sickly since l was a child, and l've aIways thought that I would not live very long.
You shouldn't think that.
lf Nii-sama would stay. As long as Nii-sama stays... I can live on just knowing he's there.
I can live...
Chisato-san is in Iove with Shouma-san...
See you! We're going.
At some point I began to listen to what went on next door...
Unconciously, it was aIl so that I could see Shouma-san.
He's not my husband who passed away...
l know that...
I know that... but...
Shouma-san?
Hello
Did you just get back?
I had to pick up an acquaintance at the airport.
You seem tired.
l'm fine, really. See you.
Uh... um...
Yes?
lf it would be all right, I'd like to ask you to go out for a meal with me.
A meal?
To thank you for the favor you did for me.
Oh, right. Then how about this Sunday?
Yes
l'll look forward to it
Me, too.
Well, good night.
Good night...
l was the one who asked you, but you ended up treating me.
lt's all right. l'm satisfied with just your invitation.
Well, where should we go now?
Um... Anywhere is fine... whatever you want to do.
What?
from the moment I met you um...
Hashimoto-san?
Kuimiko's fine... that is... Please, call me Kumiko.
ln a place like this... what if someone comes?
Let them look as much as they like.
Eh?
l'm different from your husband or...
...do you want me to be like your husband?
Do as you like.
You have an obscene body.
Oh, no...
You didn't put on a bra... is that an invitation?
That's...
You have really big breasts.
Don't...
How about this end?
Oh, don't...
That's great, you're soaking wet.
Its embarassing... please, don't say it.
l'm going to make your wish come true.
Um...
What is it? Did you get scared?
No... um... in my bag.
Please, use this... l'm sorry.
You're well prepared... put it on me.
What?
You're doing it for yourself, aren't you?
B-but...
l don't care either way.
Yes...
Um...
If you want to use it, what should you do?
ls this okay?
You're very used to doing this.
lt's the first time l did anything like this... Ah! Please, don't be mean...
You're all melted inside.
lt seems you've been waiting for this a Iong time.
That's not true...
Please, give it to me... Pleasel
Do it yourself... Ma'am.
A man is entering me... I was sealed shut, but now I am being filled up.
I... can't think anymore...
This is the kind of man l am, ma'am. Do you hate me now?
The ice is melting away...
I believed most strongly at that moment...
That... nothing stays the same forever.
Shit! Why do I have to fix Hina's mistakes?
I'm sorry...
Hello?
l'm surprised that you would be the one to call me.
l thought you didn't like me anymore.
l'm sorry.
You don t have to apologize. Being honest to yourself is a good thing.
So, l'll be honet to myself as well, okay?
Yes...
Do you like it?
Now, l'II make you feel even better.
Please, put it in me... That... Please...
You want me to put this in?
Um...
Are you sure you want a toy like this... Ma'am?
Shouma-san's...
Please put yours in me...
All right. l'll give it to you.
You did that nicely, Ma'am.
Please call me Kumiko...
No... You haven't become completely mine yet.
That's not true.
Put it in yourself.
Yes
Shouma-san?
Hello
Chisato-san...!
Since Kuu moved out, l sometimes forget and make too much.
And, l did it again.
Nii-sama ate getting home today, too. lf he's making a pest of himseIf, please tell me.
l'Il keep him in Iine.
Chisato-san... You...
If l try to tie Nii-sama down, he'll no longer be Nii-sama, that's how l feel.
ls that strange?
I dont know.
Oh, no! I have a pie in the oven!
Shouma-san...
l'm in your debt.
If you hadn't been there, l dont know what would have happened to Chisato.
Not at all... I panicked, too.
l heard from Kuu-san. Chisato-san can go home next week?
This stay in the hospital was mostly for tests, anyway.
lt'll become noisy again, but l hope you won't mind.
l'm leaving this house for awhile.
What?
My father is in the hospital, and my mother has been staying by his side.
But, l can't let my mother do all the work.
It's a change of players.
Is that right?
lf I keeps going this way...
Hm?
l'll seriously start to want you for myself.
But l can't do that.
At first, l was seeing my husband in you.
But, you're not my husband.
That's why, we can't go any further.
Kumiko?
Please take me...
not in love...
but as just a man and a woman.
Then, I'll forget you, Shouma-san...
If thats what you've decided.
Let's just do it as we are, today...
What...?
Because, it's the last time.
l want to feel you directIy...
l never knew you were so hot... inside.
Inside me... together!
Its flowing... Shouma-san's...
Goodbye...