l'm Kenta Ochiai, a typical college student.
Lately l've scored with seven different women!
Some might say it's just because of Suwatee's magic,
but there's more to it than that!
Something about me makes girls crazy!
l'm a bad boy!
l've had this girl!
And this girl! And this girl!
They're all mine!
Hey, hey, hey!
They're mine! Mine! Mine!
He gets lucky for the first time in his life and he goes crazy.
What a loser.
You guys, give it a rest!
Damn! l can't believe you're running around in this heat!
How long are you planning to freeload off me, anyway?
You've been here two weeks already!
Well, what do you think, Suwatee?
Come on, it's alright...
We're all having so much fun.
lt's too hot! Don't come near me!
Hey, Kenta, you in there?
What is it, Saiki?
l need to ask you a favor.
lt's not something weird, is it?
No, it's a sweet deal!
l can't keep my resort hotel job anymore. Do you want it?
You get three meals a day, and there are gorgeous girls everywhere.
Seriously?!
The only man in a harem!
l can get laid every day all summer!
l've got a woody just thinking about it!
Substitute part-time job?
There's no one else who can do it.
l can't say no when my buddy asks for help.
What?!
You seem a little too excited to me.
l am not!
Oh, really? Then, l'll tag along with you!
No! No! l'm not going for fun!
This is definitely suspicious!
Shuree!
Hey, Taitei! What do you think you're doing?
ls this any way to treat your brand new wife?!
Silence, Shuree!
l know that you used the power of the star to have sex with that man!
Shuree! So you really did!
You knew how l felt, too!
You traitor!
Like l said, it never happened!
Kenta, tell her!
Don't be embarrassed, Shuree.
l still remember how you cried and confessed,
''Kenta, don't forget about me!''
There's no way l would say such a stupid thing!
Shuree, calm down.
l am taking away your powers as a goddess for a while.
What did you say?
Suwatee, the same goes for you.
For your punishment, you will both spend a little time as humans.
No way.
Please, wait a minute!
What is this?
How appetizing!
Thanks for the meal!
Don't get excited!
No!
Wow!
Gorgeous girls everywhere!
Kenta! Slow down and stop drooling.
Fine...
President Hotel, President Hotel...
Oh, that's it!
Welcome! Welcome!
Sweetheart! Come stay with us!
We have good rooms! How about it?
Excuse me.
Sir, are you looking for a hotel?
Uh, no... You're Sanada, right?
l'm Kenta Ochiai, the new guy.
You finally came! l've been waiting, partner!
Who are these girls?
They came along with me.
They want to work part time too.
Can you use them?
Well, it's pretty last-minute.
Please, Mr. Sanada!
We'll work really hard.
Pretty please.
Well, if you're that desperate...
Alright! l'll find something for both of you!
Thank you, sir!
Okay then, put your stuff in the car.
lt's beautiful here.
lt really is.
ls this the hotel limo?
Wait!
Amazing! This is paradise!
l'm so glad l'm alive! Girls...
Not that one! Ours is over here.
No way!
Saiki, you bastard! You lied!
You set me up!
No! No! No!
lf l give up now, l won't be able to accomplish my goal!
Girls, where are you from?!
Feels so good!
Mr. Sanada, this hotel is really quiet. Where are the customers?
An old miser named Arisugawa put up that huge luxury hotel...
...and stole all my customers.
My business is non-existent, thanks to him.
Hey, sweetie!
Want to go for a swim?
Miss, do you have a moment?
Let's do lunch.
Damn! No luck at all!
What's up with this?
You'll never score without our help!
What did you say, you midget?
Who are you calling a midget, you stupid mortal?!
You wanna fight?
What's with him?
ls he crazy from the heat?
That idiot...
lce cold juice! Beer! lnner tubes!
We also give oil massages!
Hey, Mr. Sanada, this is the Sunday Hotel's private beach, isn't it?
We'll get in trouble.
Shut it. lf we get caught, then we get caught.
Stop being so nervous.
But...
So our ''regular'' customer is here.
lce cold juice! Beer! lnner tubes!
This is bad, Kenta! Run for it!
Sanada, you again? Don't you ever learn?
Oh, she knows you, Mr. Sanada?
So hey, what's your name?
No! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
They're security for Sunday Beach.
They're the Amazon Gang.
Oh, l see.
l'm Miyuki Himuro. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Kenta.
Hey, Suwatee, what do you think of this?
What is it?
Swimsuit, a swimsuit. We're at the beach, after all!
But...
Hey, get me this swimsuit.
Huh?! But we...
Just shut up and do it!
R-Right...
Here goes!
Wow! This is great!
Hurry up and change too, Suwatee.
Okay...
Kenta might fall for you yet.
You have to at least give it a shot.
Do you think so?
Yeah, go for it! Go for it!
Are you trying to kill us?!
Stop it! Stop!
Stop it, please!
No charge for the towing service!
Kenta, where are you?
H-Help!
Are you okay?
Yes... somehow...
No! This is too embarrassing!
lt's all right, Suwatee! Have some confidence!
You look so cute, Suwatee!
Hey, guys! Welcome to the grand opening of our beach bar!
How about a drink with Shuree and Suwatee?!
Shuree!
Now, Suwatee... Business! Business!
Um... What would you like to drink?
What's your name?
How old are you?
Are you free tonight?
Shuree, do something!
Oh, all right.
Well now, little boys, if you don't behave, l'll close the bar.
So, Mahoko, you're that old miser's...
...l mean, the president's granddaughter?
But really, you guys have a lot of guts to compete against my grandpa.
He can't be that bad.
He's so eccentric and stubborn...
...and l'm totally bored.
Sometimes l sneak out like this.
But now l'll be on your side!
Please do! Please do!
lt'd be great if a cute girl like you were helping us, Mahoko.
Everyone's waiting! Hurry!
Hey, wait a minute, girls!
Where are you going, Mr. President?
lt seems rather lively in front of Sanada's hotel.
What's going on over there?
We've received information that he has hired three part-time workers for the summer.
What a pain in the neck.
l thought l would run him off this summer.
That reminds me, is Mahoko back?
No, she hasn't returned from the beach.
Surfing again?!
lt's all she does, morning to night!
Really? And who was it that first interested her in surfing, Mr. President?
This is definitely what you would call pennies from heaven!
Suwatee and Shuree have saved this hotel!
They must be the Goddesses of Luck come down to Earth!
Oh no, Mr. Sanada! How did you guess our true identities?
ldiot! Shuree, shut up!
Gee, this is fun!
lt's been a while since l've had so much fun! Look, l'm dancing!
l'm a really good dancer!
Hey, Kenta, were you hitting on some girl this afternoon?
See! Watch me!
So did you score?
You sure are a cheap drunk!
l'm Sanada the samurai!
So, maybe you wanna have a go at it with me?
Samurai Sanada!
Hey, Shuree!
This isn't what you promised!
Why are you two so upset?
And this is really funny!
Good grief! A drunken goddess...
Oh!
She looks so sweet when she's sleeping.
What was that?
lt felt so familiar.
Are you adjusting to life as a human?
lt's probably harder than life in heaven, huh?
No...
l always wished l could feel the wind and water like you, Kenta.
l thought about it all the time.
So...
l'm happy that l get to be by your side, like a normal girl.
That's...
Sorry, l...
Here it comes! Here it comes!
Hey, Kenta!
Hurry up and get to the store before it closes!
Yeah! Yeah! l know!
Why does that always happen when it's about to get good?
But you can't be too pushy.
Even though she has a real body now,
Suwatee is still a goddess, you know.
So, tell us the truth.
Do you like Suwatee?
l don't know, this is all very sudden.
Huh?
What's wrong, baby? Too scared to stick up for yourself?
Hey! Keep your filthy hands off me!
You spoiled brat! You making fun of me?
That big hotel of yours is killing our business!
Maybe you need to get off your butts and work a little harder!
Bitch!
Lay off, buddy.
Four guys against one girl...
He really never learns, does he?
Hang on a moment.
Real-life controller!
Go! Go!
What's with this guy?!
Get him!
Damn...
Bastard!
All that time playing video games wasn't a waste!
Are you all right?
l'm okay. Fine!
Thanks a lot. You really bailed me out.
Sometimes it's smarter to just run, you know.
But l shouldn't have to run!
l didn't do anything wrong.
You're feisty, aren't you?
Don't expect me to ignore your activities on the beach because of this!
Do you understand what l'm saying?
Yeah, yeah. l understand.
But l can give you a little ''thank you''.
Are you crazy?! That's dangerous!
S-Stop it!
Wow! You're so wet!
Because... l haven't gotten any in a while.
So good! lt's been too long!
l think l'm going to come!
l can't hold on!
Me either! l'm coming!
Mahoko, wait a minute!
Where are you going?
Your English teacher comes today.
Just out for a walk.
Don't tell such transparent lies!
You've been acting suspicious all summer!
You're grounded! No more games!
Grandpa, that's not fair!
Mahoko, someday you will take over the management of this hotel.
You need to behave like a young lady so that you can find a husband to help you.
lt's my marriage so l'll find my own husband!
Stay out of my life, Grandpa!
Mahoko!
She gets worse every day.
Hey, Suwatee.
How'd it go last night?
Not good, l take it.
You've got to make a move...
...before that idiot falls for another woman!
Excuse me!
ls there a Kenta Ochiai here?
Are you a friend of Kenta's?
Morning, everyone!
Kenta, good morning!
Mahoko!
l came to work with you guys, Kenta!
l want to help out!
Work with us? But it's so sudden...
You don't mind, do you? Please?
Please? Please? Kenta, please! Please?
Sagashi tsuzuketeta
You have the one bright smile...
kagayaku sono egao
...that l've always been looking for.
Yume ni made miteta
These arms of yours that hold me tight...
dakishimeru sono tewo
...l have only dreamed about.
Subetewa hajimatte ita
l remember when it started...
deatta shunkan ni kizuita yo
...the day l saw you standing there.
Kono sora no hate ni
We stretch our wings to the sky,
tsubasa hiroge FLYAWAY
take wing, and then we fly away.
Futari tobitatouyo
Soaring off together.
Eien he tsuzuku
We share an endless love...
owaranaimo LOVE
...that lasts for eternity.
Futari nara, ame no yoru mo
Two together through the rain...
samui asa mo mitsukerareru
...through the cold, holding each other.
Still the moment...
eien he tsuzuku
...from here to eternity.
NEXT TlME
What is with that girl, Suwatee?
She and Kenta seem awfully friendly.
No!
l know! Why don't you just give up on Kenta?
No! Not now that l can finally touch him!
You mean with a real body, you can do this and that with him!
No! Shuree! Honestly...
Next time, Can Can Bunny Extra!
Kenta, how do you feel about me?
Don't miss it!