lt's hot!
Stop it!
Come on, it's time to get ready.
Momomi, that's enough fun for now.
We're getting ready, Haruka.
Oh, a love slave with spirit.
Get off your queen routine!
Here's your chance to be strong!
Today we present a magnificent
new bondage painting.
And, on this first anniversary of the death...
...of domination master
Hiroyuki Sawawatari...
...l'd like to thank so many
of you for showing up.
Thanks to you, Takayuki has
become a worthy successor...
...and the deceased can
rest easy in the underworld.
Now, then, we've prepared
something fun for you.
l hope you all enjoy it.
This is just one part of
our party's entertainment.
Ladies and gentlemen,
feel free to have a taste.
Oh, yes...
This is ridiculous.
Big cock!
No, use your tongue more!
Your master orders you.
Do it!
Use your tongue more.
Now put it in your mouth.
Don't hesitate!
Yes... That's the way.
Stop it! Let me go!
Don't worry. You're going
to have a lot of fun.
No! Stop it!
l'll give you a taste of ultimate pleasure.
l'll make you feel even better.
Stop it! Please stop!
Please stop! l'm going insane!
Please stop! Please stop! Please stop!
Please stop! Please stop!
Please stop!
A slave must obey her master's
orders without question!
Pain and pleasure are one and the same.
Those tears will one day
become tears of joy.
An entertaining show, isn't it, Master?
Quite.
No, please! Stay back!
Now try it over there.
Don't be shy. Your master orders you.
Yes, sir.
lt hurts! Stop it!
Master...
Why did you have to die...?
And now, ladies and
gentlemen, tonight's main dish.
l present a magnificent sacrifice.
Please relish it till the very end.
lt's hot!