Rxxx: Prescription for Pain Part 2
l work as a physician at Misono General Hospital...
...one of the top-rated hospitals in Japan.
My skills as a physician have
been highly acclaimed...
...and l have been written up in several magazines.
l'm to the point where l can boast that l am the reputation of this hospital.
The president of the hospital is sick, and it's rumored he'll retire soon.
People used to say l was going to be the next president...
...and that the only thing standing in my way was my young age. Until that day...
Thanks for coming, everyone.
My daughter Serika has returned to us as a full-fledged doctor.
She'll join our team as a physician.
The meddlesome daughter returned...
But l haven't given up on becoming the next president of this hospital.
How do you like it?
lt's so good. l think l'm going to go crazy.
l'm cumming!
Me too!
You'll never be able to feel like this if you side with Dr. Serika.
Are you still going to choose her over me?
Master, l can't take it anymore... Please fuck me too.
Making us watch is like torture.
Fine. Come here.
l'll do anything to become President.
Serika... You have no choice. Either leave, or become my sex slave like them...
Your fate belongs to me...
OPERATING
Doctor? What's wrong?
Are you okay?
l'm fine... l'm fine...
Dr. Serika, would you like cream and sugar?
Neither, please. Black is fine.
Sure.
Here, Doctor.
Thank you.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
Dad... l don't know why either.
l'm getting enough sleep, but...
lt was a good choice you made, switching your shift.
Luckily Jyunichi was around.
Get some rest. You're exhausted.
Dad!
Serika!
Yes...
The President has decided that Dr. Serika isn't experienced enough to take over.
The administrators and nurses are leaning towards you again...
...for the President's position.
Good.
Blood pressure and vital signs?
Stable.
How's his condition?
He's stable.
Let's begin.
lt's started.
Look at him go.
As long as he's with us, the hospital is in good hands.
Yes, l guess...
You wield the knife like a pro.
Thank you.
You have amazing talent.
lt was an extremely difficult operation, and you were brilliant.
President...
As President, you make me proud.
Thank you very much. l'm also happy the patient will survive.
There you are.
Hi, Dr. Serika.
l'm impressed. The operation was amazing.
Are you being sarcastic? l was just marveling at how l'm able...
...to do such wonderful things as a doctor.
What a shame.
Shame?
lf you actually meant what you said...
...you'd be the best physician in the world.
Are you saying l'm lying?
How can l believe you, knowing what you did to me!
Whatever. lf that's really what you think, then that's your opinion...
Anyway, l heard you're not feeling well. Get well soon and get back on the job.
l'm working double time taking care of your patients.
Jyunichi Shiozaki... l don't understand him...
Jyunichi, are you eating out?
Yeah.
Living it up, aren't you? lt's not even payday.
l learned he was a sweet person...
...who was eating cheaply to send more money to his mother.
Who's the real Jyunichi? The sweet Jyunichi, or the...
Why?
No way! Really?
She's so lame!
She doesn't have any friends, so...
That's so sad.
Her?
l think she's the best prey for our next plan.
Not like that! lt'll unravel in no time!
Sorry.
Here, watch me. l'll show you.
Get naked.
Might as well show you how to wrap every part of the body while we're at it.
All right.
Okay? You wrap it like this. Not too loose, not too tight.
Right.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
l didn't know how much longer l could stall.
Very nice...
l haven't seen such a pretty pussy in a while.
Let's begin.
Look how modest she is compared to you guys.
She'll start screaming once you fuck her.
You think?
Wow... She looks like she's peeing.
Aya, your pussy is so firm. l love eating you out.
lt's like a fresh oyster. lt's my favorite.
You can play with toys by yourself, but you'll need me from here on.
lf you want to feel like this again, you have to become my slave.
You're feeling it. Your pussy is squeezing my cock and won't let go.
l'm going to cum.
The President was talking about downsizing the nurses.
Even if they do get fired, there's a shortage of nurses...
...so they'll be able to find another job.
Are you talking about me?
No, but a girl like you will probably have trouble...
...adjusting to a new workplace.
So, it's best for you to have him on your side.
"Him" meaning Dr. Shiozaki, the next President.
Of course, l'll look at your job performance, but l'm only human.
lf l have to make a choice, it's only natural to pick the ones who've been good to me.
Do you understand, Aya?
Yes.
l'm happy you're willing to work so hard, but...
...l'd rather see a demure girl like you writhe in pleasure.
Master, you're being mean.
Am l? l guess she needs some help.
Well? How does it feel?
lt feels good.
Feels good? You can do better Aya. Say "lt's amazing, Master."
Come on.
lt... lt's amazing Master.
Good...
Now l have one more slave.
l can't believe Dr. Serika would do that.
Don't you think it's terrible to do that to someone like Aya?
lt's scary... you never know what clever people are thinking.
What's going on?
Dr. Serika. l heard you raped Aya.
Stop playing dumb! l had so much respect for you, but not any more.
Aya, why are you lying? Did l ever do anything to you?
You're terrible...
Wait a minute. This is some kind of mistake!
Please believe me.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
This is insane!
l didn't rape a nurse! lt's a complete lie!
You know l wouldn't do that! l'm not a lesbian!
Of course. l believe you.
Then can't you say something? lf you talk to them as the President...
...the people who believe this madness will come to their senses!
Serika...
What?
What would you think about going to another hospital, and getting experience there?
What's that supposed to mean?
lf this was the only incident, it would still be all right...
...but you've made too many mistakes.
At this rate, the committee might say something. And if they do...
...you won't be able to take over the hospital, even if you're my daughter.
lt's best to keep some distance for now.
Don't worry, it'll only be for two or three years. lt won't be that bad.
l did it! l finally kicked her out of the hospital.
Master, please fuck me.
No, me first.
Shut up you two...
You two shouldn't be so selfish.
We're Master's slaves.
Yes.
l won! lt's only a matter of time until the President's position lands in my lap.
This is the best! lt feels so good!
Master's fingers are so amazing! lt's like they're magical fingers...
Master...
Are you planning to keep the same relationship with Aya that you do with us?
What do you mean?
She tends to misunderstand things, so l think it's best to stay away from her.
l see... l'll keep my distance then.
She's a loner. lt shouldn't be that hard to make her quit, right?
Yes. We'll start tomorrow.
This is going to be fun.
Hello?
lt's Aya.
Oh...
There's something l want to talk to you about.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
l've been informed of everything that you did to Serika.
lt's unfortunate. l wanted you and Serika to take over this hospital together.
Am l fired?
Under normal circumstances you would be, yes.
But considering all that you've done for this hospital...
...this incident will stay between us.
Submit a resignation letter and leave.
l'm not going to write a recommendation letter, but this should make it easier...
...for you get another job, rather than simply being fired.
Thank you for your thoughtfulness.
Hey, took you long enough.
What's wrong? Why aren't the lights on?
lt's past lights out. People would think it was strange if this room was lit.
True.
So, why did you want me to come here?
You know damn well why. Stop playing dumb.
l do. l'm the one who told Dad.
Was it Aya?
Yes.
l see. . . So it was her.
Dad is so sweet. He told you to resign, right?
lf l were President, you would have been fired.
l'm sure.
But ultimately, l was able to drive you out. l can see your approaching demise.
This room brings back memories.
This is the room l used when l was in the hospital.
The revenge l've been plotting since that day has finally been fulfilled.
What? Say something!
Seems like l lost.
You're awfully quick to admit defeat, for a guy who did such heinous things.
There's no point in fighting back now.
l'll admit defeat...
But l'll leave the battlefield after l wound my opponent once more!
No!
Damn it!
lt's all your fault that everything l've worked so hard for has been destroyed.
Are you enjoying this?
Don't lie! Listen to your pussy making all that noise.
Are you serious? lf this was the case, l should have done this from the start!
Why did you stop?
l'm not doing this for your pleasure. l'm doing this to hurt you, so it'd be pointless.
But...
No. lf you want me to fuck you, you'd better beg.
Please make me cum.
You left out "Master".
Master, please make me cum.
Good. l want you to suck on my cock.
Yes.
Yes... Your hard cock is all the way inside.
lt's so big l think you're going to tear me up inside!
lt feels so good!
lt's so good! My insides are getting hot... it feels amazing!
Same here...
l'm going numb.
Well? Does it feel good? ls it all the way inside?
Yes...
l can't anymore. l feel like l'm going to die.
l'm cumming.
Please cum... Please cum... Master, l want your hot white cum all over me!
l better go back to my room and start cleaning up.
This is goodbye, Serika.
l don't have a choice. The President told me to leave.
You of all people know that.
But there's a way...
A way?
The President hasn't told the committee.
Meaning, the only people who know are you, the President and l.
You mean...
l knew you were smart. Exactly.
l could care less either way. lt's not like my license was taken away.
l'll start over at a different hospital.
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
Since my father suddenly passed away last month...
...it has been decided that l, his daughter, will take up his position as President.
But l won't be able to handle this responsibility by myself.
So Dr. Shiozaki, who left last month, will return to us as Vice President.
Long time no see, everyone.
l hope to have your continued support.
Thank you.
Are you sure it's okay for me to be the President?
Yes. lt'll be more difficult to raise any questions...
...when l become President one day.
Plus, it'll be easier to do things my way.