My father passed away.
I received a Ietter from a
woman who married my father...
...whiIe I was away at boarding schooI.
In other words, it
was from my stepmother.
My father was the son of a weaIthy man.
But he Iead a Iife of debauchery...
...and my mother couIdn't stand
his drinking and wiId behavior...
...so she hanged herseIf.
I don't have any good
memories of my home...
But I Ieft schooI to see my
father's face one Iast time.
The Duchess of Busty Mounds Vol. 1
You're the onIy one I have.
Stay with me aIways.
Mother...
It's been 2 years...
Jean?
Jean!
WeIcome back!
Can't be!
Is this possibIe?
My stepmother SyIvia Iooks
so much Iike my mother!
And right then, it brought
back memories of my chiIdhood.
Your father got drunk and
feII off from his horse.
I saw his face, but I
didn't feeI sad at aII.
I knew he wouId end
up Iike this one day.
I'm sure SyIvia had a hard
time deaIing with his behavior.
She didn't even cry at the funeraI.
Mother...
Yes?
My name is Apache and I'm
the Iawyer for the famiIy.
I'm sure you're aware
of this by now, but...
...the Iate master disinherited
you, so you won't get any money.
AIso, this house wiII be
passed on to an outsider.
So my cIient, who happens
to be your grandfather...
...in other words, master CharieI,
the current head of the famiIy...
...wouId Iike to Iook after you two.
I don't think it's a bad idea.
And so, my grandfather who owns
a huge pIantation took us in.
I'd Iike to weIcome you two, but
we don't have any empty rooms.
For the time being, I want
you two to stay in a house...
...detached from the main compound.
Where's the master?
He's resting right now.
I was asked to take care of you two.
If you need anything, you come to me.
Yes, we understand.
To teII you the truth,
you peopIe are a nuisance.
If you want to stay here, you'II have
to work from tomorrow on.
Understood?
Yes.
We have a pIace for the time
being, so Iet's stay here.
I'm afraid we have no other choice.
Don't be so sad.
I'm sure things wiII
get better for you, Jean.
I'II be fine, SyIvia.
In these poor Iiving conditions, I was
embraced by my stepmother's scent...
...and I was feeIing somewhat happy.
WeII? What do you
think about my cooking?
It's reaIIy good.
There's pIenty of food
and we're Iiving together.
It's not as bad as I thought.
As Iong as I'm here with you,
I can bear any kind of hardship.
Good morning.
Sorry to interrupt, you two.
Yes, what is it?
What is it?
What an impudent fooI you are!
You peopIe are Iike
parasites, eating aII our food!
It's time for you to work!
Yes, I understand.
You go cIean the mansion. The
boy can go cIean the stabIe.
If you don't do a good job, our
master wiII kick you both out.
Who do you think Iet you stay here?
Your Iate husband Ieft
this pIace on his own.
And yet my mother feIt sorry for him.
Yes, I understand.
That's better.
You just treat us Iike your masters.
I guess we have no choice.
WeII, I'm heading over to the mansion.
You're doing a pretty good job.
I wonder how Iong you'II Iast?
What are you doing?
Is that how you taIk to your master?
Saucy feIIow.
Do you care about your stepmother?
There's Iots of hot-bIooded
workers here, you know.
Listen up, Jean.
From now on, you're my sIave.
You'II do whatever I say.
Understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Then I'II teII you
what to do immediateIy.
Now, come over here and Iick.
Over here.
That's it.
Lick me more.
I'm getting chiIIs down my spine.
Suck it, hurry up and suck on it.
Harder!
I can't take it anymore.
I want your thing!
So hard.
It's big and hard.
You're gonna serve me
everyday with this thing.
Now stick it inside me.
You're gonna make me
cIimax with your thing.
It feeIs good.
Do me harder with that thing of yours...
I can't take it anymore.
I'm about to cIimax.
Do it inside me.
ReIease that hot juice
of yours inside me.
I'm gonna cIimax!
Come here again tomorrow, got it?
Yes.
I'm home.
You sound very energetic.
Looks Iike you can work here after aII.
Where's my stepmother?
She's staying over at
the mansion for the night.
What?
Did something happen?
How shouId I know?
Since she's not here, I
was toId to make your meaI.
Thanks.
You can't keep worrying forever.
You just need to think
about your situation.
WeII, see ya.
SyIvia...
Good morning Jean.
Was everything aII right yesterday?
Yes, it took a very Iong
time to cIean the mansion.
I see.
Are you doing aII this on your own?
That's right. I have to work harder!
But it's gonna get dark soon.
You know what, I'II heIp you.
It's okay.
You have your own work to do.
That's right.
I'II give you something
to do if you're that free.
Go get some firewood from the forest.
Don't worry, I'II be fine on my own.
You just go and get some firewood.
You want me don't you?
AII the guys in the viIIage want me.
But I'II Iet you have me anytime.
Hurry up and do me.
I knew your cock wouId be the best.
Harder!
Your cock is banging me.
It's banging me!
No, I feeI Iike I'm about to pee!
Jean, you're Iate.
SmeIIs Iike Tina's perfume!
You did it with Tina didn't you?
I was forced to do it
with her in the forest.
Don't you ever do it with Tina again!
No, not just Tina.
Don't you ever do it with
another woman again, got it?
Yes, ma'am.
This beIongs to me.
WeII, Iooks Iike I'm done for today.
Sir?
You Iike books?
Do you Iike books?
Yes.
Books are good.
Your Iife wiII be so
much better with books.
You can go ahead and read
these books if you Iike.
But return them to their proper sheIf.
Yes. Thank you very much.
My grandfather was different
from the others I've met.
The pIantation has been
inherited for generations...
...but he was abIe to increase
the size of the pIantation...
And received so much
respect from the neighbors.
But he seemed somewhat
IoneIy in my eyes.
SyIvia...
I'm home.
WeIcome home.
You must be tired.
I'II fix your meaI.
I met my grandfather today.
Oh reaIIy?
Did he say anything to you?
Yeah, he said I can
read his books anytime.
That's nice.
You Ieft schooI, so this
might be good for you.
He must reaIIy Iike you then.
ReaIIy? I sure hope so.
I'm sure.
We'II be abIe to Iive
a normaI IifestyIe soon.
I'm sure your grandfather
wiII make it happen.
Ouch!
Jean, where did you get those scars?
From Marianne.
That's horribIe. I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were
having such a hard time.
I'm aII right now.
Stay stiII.
No, I'm your stepmother.
This isn't right.
No. I can't take it anymore.
I Iike you.
I reaIIy Iove you.
Thank you for teIIing me that.
But in order to Iive here, we can't
have this kind of reIationship.
You don't Iike me?
I do Iove you.
We're not reIated by bIood.
So...
No matter what we do, it's
not considered profane!
No!
SyIvia, your crotch is so warm and wet.
Stop it, Jean.
We're gonna Iive together
from here on, right?
You're gonna Iove me
no matter what, right?
Oh God!
Yes, I'm so happy.
More, suck me harder!
Thank you, SyIvia.
You reaIIy Iove me.
We can onIy do it up to this point,
we can't go any further with this.
I can't take it anymore.
Look how hard I've gotten...
I'm getting so...
Me too.
But...
I don't reaIIy care what happens.
No, anything but that!
You're Iying! You want me too.
So...
See? You reaIIy want me.
I'm so happy.