Welcome to the world of Virtuacall.
We've created it just for you.
Virtual Reality!
Enjoy it to your heart's content!
I'm Wendy, the operator.
Ask me anything, okay?
From here on out, everything depends only
on your charm and determination.
Put your heart into it, and
win wonderful love!
So I'll pray for your health, and...
Virtuacall 2,
Access 1.
Welcome to the World of Virtuacall
So everyone, please have a
pleasant summer vacation.
All rise!
Bow!
Emily!
I'm going to buy a patch on my way home.
Want to come along?
Sorry, I've got a prior appointment.
You're going to play with your
big brother again?
I volunteered.
After all, since he has tickets
to a live concert,
it'd be sad if there were no one
to go with him.
Well, bye-bye!
Hitomi, see you later!
That's what she says, but she's
having fun anyway.
Hot!
Emily, what are you doing?!
It's your fourth year of college, and
you're sleeping without a care?
What are you planning to do about
your first job next year?
You still haven't got even one
call back yet, have you?
No matter how much you worry, it's not
going to change a thing, right?
It just isn't in my character, you know?
That "Given enough shots, even a
poor shot will hit the target" thing
just doesn't work for me.
Really! Brother, you've got no
aptitude in these areas.
You're being awfully cheeky today.
As a relation of the landlord,
I am concerned about the future of
a tenant with no prospects.
Anyway, hurry up and get ready.
The concert will be starting soon.
I'll wait for you, so hurry up.
You're always such a pain, Brother!
Oh, that surprised me!
You really suck at this. But try harder.
But...
Don't give up!
The concert was good, wasn't it?
Let's go again sometime, Brother.
Besides since it's summer vacation
you have a lot of free time,
and you don't even have
anyone to date, right?
None of your business!
Besides, don't you have to go see
your parents in Los Angeles?
You haven't shown your face there
in about a year, right?
Yeah, but you know, they're always
flying off somewhere on assignment.
Even if I go, I'll only be in the way.
Really? It must be hard being a parent and
a newspaper's special correspondent.
Yeah, kind of.
Wait, Brother!
Hello?
Brother, are you asleep?
Geez, it's you. What are you thinking?
It's three in the morning!
You know I can't stand thunder!
Grandpa and Grandma are on vacation
with the Old Folks Association,
and they won't be home until
next week, and...
Please, don't hang up!
Hello? Hello?
Brother, hello?! Are you listening?
HELLO!
Brother?
Brother, you came after all!
I only have two weeks, Majhana?
Let me think about this for a while.
Please, let me have some time.
What is it?
I have a keen sense of smell.
My nose responds quickly to
a cute girl like you.
I'm in a hurry, so...
I'm sorry.
Field House
This is unexpected!
Is that kind of manly-girl your type, Brother?
Emily, why are you here?
A clumsy man's secret love!
Oh, I could just cry!
It's not really like that with her.
Hasegawa?
Oh damn!
Suzune...
Is that your girlfriend, Hasegawa?
She's cute, isn't she?
Oh no, you're wrong! Wrong!
This one's not like that!
They call me Emily!
My brother is always in your debt!
Idiot, don't say stupid things!
Well, Suzune, excuse us,
we'll be leaving now!
Thanks!
Bye!
That's good. You do have a girlfriend.
How long have you been with her, Brother?
Not yet.
I met her three years ago in the spring
at the commencement ceremony.
But she's cute, and her skill with the
long spear is on a national level.
It's stupid for someone like me to even
think about her being my girlfriend.
And, like just now, I get nervous, and
can't really talk when I'm around her.
That's not true!
Since I only have two weeks,
I have to work fast.
Brother, you can't do anything
without me, can you?
Two weeks?
What do you mean?
It's okay. I'll do something
about it for you!
I'll grant your wish, Brother!
Hey, Emily!
Leave it to me! See you!
What's got her in such a dither?
You're Kunihiko's Cupid?
Yes! So I want you to help too.
But Emily, don't you like Kunihiko?
Me? Brother?
Listen, to me that guy is like a
troublesome older brother!
Your naiveté is kind of scary, you know?
Geez! Don't make such weird
assumptions, okay?
Emily?
You have VHG at your house, right, Emily?
I do.
But what's this?
It's all the rage on the streets, a
Virtuacall Common Use Modem.
If you set this up, you can play in
virtual reality just like a video game,
but you can really feel it.
It's been THE thing lately.
Why don't you have Kunihiko get
used to girls with this?
Virtuacall?
But can Brother talk about things
he doesn't know anything about?
It's okay!
I'll have everything ready on my side!
If that leave falls, then the light of
my life will also disappear.
How fleeting a person's wishes are.
Sayoko, it's amazing how you can act so
miserable when all you have is fatigue,
because you were out too late at night!
Oh, it's you, Hitomi.
But no one will even come visit me.
There's nothing else to do but daydream!
I expected as much, so I
brought this for you!
The ultimate toy!
You have to be kidding! Why do I have to
let you meddle in my life?
You like her enough to become a rock
when she's in front of you, right?
Do you mean to keep quiet like this
until you graduate?
It has nothing to do with you.
That's okay! That's okay!
Put this on!
Hey, what're you doing?
Okay, Brother?
When a girl named "Sayoko" comes up,
you have to access that girl, okay?
Hey, Emily?
I've told Sayoko about you,
Big Brother, so...
Hi, welcome to Virtuacall!
From here on out, everything depends only
on your charm and determination.
Put your heart into it, and
win wonderful love!
Sayoko...
The progress of technology is amazing.
Virtual reality has come this far?
Sayoko, I'm sorry to involve you
in Emily's evil schemes.
It's all right.
I'm just a little nervous about
being alone with a guy.
Sorry, I didn't think you
could feel things too!
Hitomi told me that right now
your love is one-sided,
that you can't confess your love, and
you're worried about it, Hasegawa.
I've been sickly since I was little,
and now I'm hospitalized too.
When I listen to the other girls'
conversations, it all seems so fun.
But I don't know anything about guys, so...
Please keep this a secret from
Emily and Hitomi, okay?
I was thinking that since Virtuacall
is a fabricated world,
if it was Kunihiko...
Am I not good enough?
That's not true. You're cute.
Sayoko...
Kunihiko...
No!
Sorry! I just...
Sayoko!
Please...
Wow, it's so...
Good! It's good.
To think that you can feel so much
in a made up reality.
Good! It's good!
I can feel it!
I'm going to come!
Hey, Sayoko, are you okay?
Wow, it's been a while!
It felt so good!
All the way?!
Who said you should go that far?!
Can't breathe...
Hey...
Hey, Emily.
Isn't it expensive here?
It's okay. Just leave it to me!
You need clothes that don't hurt the eyes
when you stand next to Suzune!
I'll coordinate!
Emily, don't talk so loud!
Brother, I don't have time.
Pretty soon, I...
Pretty soon, I won't be here.
According to the customs of
our country, Welfenland,
you have been schooled outside of the
country until your eighteenth birthday.
I have come to Japan to help prepare
you for your return home.
My Lady, you are our country's only
eligible heir to the throne.
The people are longing for your return
from the bottom of their hearts.
Oh, Hasegawa?
Good afternoon!
Suzune!
Aren't you Emily? So we meet again.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Isn't this your chance?
Well...
Yes?
It's hot today, isn't it?
Yes.
Oh, it was you after all, young lady!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Suzune.
Well, shall we go, Suzune?
Brother, are you all right?
I'm okay. Okay!
It doesn't matter at all!
I need to go somewhere, so you
go on home, first! See you!
See you!
Brother...
That must be him.
Really? Some other guy got there
before him?
Since I tried to get his spirits up,
he's been even more depressed.
In that case, why don't you
go out with him, Emily?
A woman is the best cure for a heartache
caused by another woman!
Geez! I've told you so many times!
Brother and I aren't like that!
So you say.
Maybe it's that you haven't realized
your true feelings about him yet.
From a brotherly presence to a lover!
That kind of thing happens a lot.
What?! I'm asking for you help,
and you aren't being serious.
Beside, even if I did, there's no time left.
Hello?
Hello? It's me.
What is it?
I wondered what you were doing, Brother?
You don't sound well.
Not really. I'm the same as usual.
Hey, what's Virtuacall like?
I want to do it once too! I think I'll
try it now! Do it with me, Brother!
I really don't feel like doing that right now.
Oh, really?!
If some weird guy says something
perverted to me,
or something scary happens to me,
you don't care?!
If I become damaged goods, then I won't
want to live anymore, okay?!
I get it already! You want me to come
with you, right?! Right?!
There's no sense in doing
Virtuacall with you, Emily.
We live in the same condos.
Really!
Hi, welcome to Virtuacall!
From here on out, everything depends only
on your charm and determination.
Put your heart into it, and
win wonderful love!
Suzune!
Hasegawa!
Suzune, why are you so drunk?
So, you access Virtuacall too, Hasegawa?
Brother, where are you?
Miss, I have a keen sense of smell.
My nose responds quickly to
a cute girl like you.
No way!
This smell...
Have we met somewhere before, young lady?
Mizushima framed me so easily!
It seems he bet with his friends
he could do it with me.
Suzune...
Don't pretend that you're worried about me.
Guys are all the same.
And since we've met in Virtuacall,
let's have some fun together.
Her freshman year, the girl I like had
another girl confess her love for her.
She was surprised.
The summer of the second year,
she was commended for capturing
a pervert in the subway.
In the fall of the third year,
she began leaving notes for the girls
that confessed their love for her.
Hasegawa, I...
I've been watching you for
three whole years.
I... Hasegawa...
I can't do this. I feel sick!
Hold on, Suzune!
Brother, what were you doing?
Sorry, Emily, Suzune's in trouble.
Suzune?
I have to go!
Brother...
It's all right now.
He's so late.
Three years ago, Brother moved
into these condos.
I was separated from my family,
so I was really happy.
It seemed like I had a big brother.
At first I was a little shy, but
we soon became close,
and he played with me as though
I was his real little sister.
How are you feeling?
Thank you, I'm okay now.
Well then, I'll go home.
Wait.
Today, please stay by my side.
Suzune?
Nice!
That's good.
I...
It's good. It's good!
Good. Good.
I can't wait anymore!
Why does it bug me so much?
43th National Championship
Winner: Suzune Tenohji
What is this bad feeling in my chest?
Brother...
Before the day breaks
Even the moon sleeps
We passed through town in the car
A big bag
Is what you are carrying
The vision of you runs before my eyes
Sleepy, still a child
Hey, look
The fairy of winter
Is coming down in front of us
As if to guide us
The fairy lights the way, navigation
It's not on a map
Only ours
There's a side road
We'll be the first to fly out
So let's begin
The white shower
Of our breath
Again in the sky
Can become snow
For a long time, for a long time
Let's put our footprints in the snow
I can tell you
Gently, now
At the moment the sun begins to rise
Now, once again
Strongly, strongly
As you hold me close
I need you
Next Episode
Lady Emily has finally realized she's in love,
but it's going nowhere.
As for Kunihiko, he's wandering
this way and that.
Be honest and acknowledge your feelings.
And take those feelings and
go for it with Kunihiko!
Are you going to go back to
the Kingdom of Welfenland
with only memories of Japan?
You're almost out of time.
Lady Emily, good luck!