So, what can I get...
...for you?
Could I get a Gimlet, please?
He'll have the same.
Miss, could you maybe
do that in a hotel, please?
Look at that! Can you believe it?!
I guess that's what they
mean by exhibitionists.
Yeow! She's got her nipples
pierced! That looks painful!
But that guy with her is really cool.
You want to join them?
No way!
Oh, I can't look!
That's going too far!
Maybe this is a show or something.
They're leaving now.
I wonder what that was all about.
Still, it was interesting, wasn't it?
Huh? Ai!
Sorry, it's... I... I just remembered
something I have to do.
S- Sure...
I'll see you later.
Uh-oh. Maybe that was too much for her.
She's so innocent.
No, I mean she's usually such a neat freak.
No! Let me go!
I know you've been following us.
Why did you come here?
What did you think as you watched us?
I... I thought you were very pretty...
And you wanted to try it, too.
I... I don't know. I just...
Why would you lie?
I understand you. The same
blood that flows through us...
...flows through you as well.
No!
Come. I'll take you with us.
And we'll show you what
it is you're looking for.
You don't have to worry about these girls.
They're just furniture.
He likes you, you know.
Kiss that pierce on his chest.
No!
Go on!
Keep going.
Just do what feels right to you.
Come on, do it!
I... I...!
How is it? You've never sucked
off a guy before, have you?
Does it taste good?
I'm... I'm dolng such a dirty thing...
This huge thing... This huge, warm thing...
Inside my Iips...
It feels so good!
So pretty...
Fresh meat?
A horny bitch who was
wandering around downtown.
She's so cute.
Oh, I'm jealous. You're so popular.
Come!
Look. Everyone's staring
at how dirty you look.
No... Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
Oh, your nipples are so hard.
Are you that turned on?
It's so embarrasslng...
It hurts so much...
...but I like it!
What's happenlng to me?!
Oh, now I see...
She wants you when she sees
you. Go give her what she wants.
Yes! It feels so good! More!
Oh, yes! I'm coming!
More!
I'm not kidding!
No way!
By the way, does anyone
know what happened to Ai?
Yeah. I call and call, but she's never home.
I wonder what's up with her?
Hey, look! They're back!
Oh, wow! You can see her whole ass!
But...
Just ignore them.
God, that's so dirty! Look, he's
feeling up her breasts, too.
Uh, guys? Guys! Look!
What?!
Ai...?