DARK TOUR
BORABORA... AUSTRALIA-NEWZEALAND...
DEVIL PRINCESS TOUR
Matsumura is recuperating for a month.
Isn't he responsible for the Devil Princess Worship Tour?
What? Who's going to take his place?
That tour is coming up soon.
It's fully booked.
Um...
This should do...
Hey, Ann Naka!
You want to go?
Please don't kid me.
I heard ghosts really appear in the Devil Princess Worship Tour in Matsuzawa Village.
That story is a hoax.
The people in Matsuzawa Village came up with it to attract tourists.
But I can't handle scary things...
Too bad, Ann Naka. Your the tour guide.
What?
Reference material. Go over it.
DEVIL PRINCESS WORSHIP TOUR
Oh.
Isn't this is your first tour guide job?
Show some spirit!
"Show some spirit."
That's right.
I always wanted to be a tour guide.
Yes. I'll do it!
They're late.
Hey! Aren't we leaving?
Yes. Please wait a little while.
Is this the manager?
This is Ann Naka. Um...
I was just about to call you.
Those three groups have cancelled.
What?
Go with the remaining customers.
But...
It's less pressure for your first time.
It's better this way.
Well, okay.
This is a JSC promoted...
This is a JSC promoted Devil Princess Worship Tour. Thank you for participating.
Wow! Two girls! You're really brave.
Yeah. It seemed like fun.
Listen to you! You said it was going to be cool.
But it's a mystery tour! Uncool.
You can cling to me anytime you're scared.
What? No way!
What a horny dude.
We get off the bus at the entrance of Matsuzawa Village and proceed on foot to the hotel.
You shouldn't have applied for this tour.
You know I'm paranormal.
Why not?
Let's do it while ghosts watch us.
It's a turn on.
Let's have a real good time.
When we arrive, it's free time.
Then dinner...
Nevermind.
What?
Was it Ann Naka-san?
No one is listening. Why don't you take a break?
Yes, but...
Go ahead.
Yes.
Well then, just a little bit.
The usual tour guide had an accident?
Yes.
Could it be the curse of Tamiko?
Curse? Isn't the story a hoax?
I'm interested in the Devil Princess legend.
I've been on this tour numerous times.
Tamiko really existed. It's the truth.
The truth?
Yes. Matsuzawa Village always had few women.
To satisfy the desires of the men, women from neighboring villages were sold there.
One was Tamiko.
The main character in the Devil Princess legend.
The men of Matsuzawa Village
put Tamiko on a pedestal like a Princess,
and exploded their desires.
No!
Tamiko, who was sold to cover debts,
had no choice but to accept their desires.
But then appeared a man who was kind to her.
Tamiko loved this man and conceived a child.
The two tried to elope from the village.
But...
their plan was foiled and the man was killed.
Tamiko was violently raped on the spot.
And then...
She miscarried the child in her.
What?
That's horrible. That's too horrible!
That's too pitiful for Tamiko!
Ann Naka-san, you're kind.
What?
Well, what do you think happened after that?
She couldn't be with the man she loved
and she became a devil.
One after the other, she killed the men that raped her.
During sex, their nails shattered.
Their eyeballs popped out.
Maggots came out of their intestines.
No!
That's the legend of Tamiko's Devil Princess.
There is a doll in the room where Tamiko lived.
At night it...
Please. No more.
Let's go home.
What are you talking about?
We've come this far.
MATSUZAWA VILLAGE
Please pick us up tomorrow at three o'clock.
Thank you very much.
There it goes.
There's no way out.
Let's go. Follow me.
DEVIL PRINCESS INN
Welcome
I'm Sakamoto, the proprietor.
Please come this way.
I can't. There are ghosts here.
They're definitely here!
Yeah, yeah.
What's the matter?
He's not the usual innkeeper.
What?
Your rooms are on the second floor.
Please relax until dinner time.
What? Where's Tamiko's room?
That's after dinner and a visit to the cemetary.
What?
Ms. Tour Guide...
Yes?
Want to come to our room?
Let's play Mah Jong. You know how?
Oh, no. I...
All you do is hang with that intellectual. I'm going to sulk.
By intellectual, do you mean Saito-san?
Yes. We're all customers so treat us as equals. Alright?
This is paradise!
The fun is just starting.
What, Tamiko again?
More than that, aren't they bigger?
Hey what... Knock it off.
I'm getting out.
"All I do is hang with Saito-san..."
I didn't mean to. Being a tour guide is complicated.
Sorry. We haven't discussed business.
Oh sorry. I forgot.
Could you wait outside until I change?
Yes, of course. Well, then.
Let's see. Which was Tamiko's room?
Let's stick with the program.
Let's wait until then.
We came all the way here. You can't get this thrill anywhere else.
If only Kuroki-san was with us.
"You can cling to me anytime you're scared." Right.
He's not here when it counts.
Good evening.
Tamiko-san, are you here?
Stop it. It's not funny.
Rice and candles.
It's just to create a mood.
Hey, look at that!
It was in the brochure.
Isn't it the doll with Tamiko's curse?
Let's take a picture with the doll.
No way! That's not funny!
Hey, come on. Let's go to Tamiko's room.
I don't want to. Somebody's been watching us.
I can feel it.
"Feel it"? Cool. Like how?
Like this?
Or like this?
Useless!
Where are you going?
That's harsh!
What's with that guy?
So undependable.
I don't believe it.
Shit! That voice. It's that bothersome chick.
She might call someone.
Let's get this over with.
She's all wet.
This one's firm and pointy.
Are they getting off on each other?
Yeah! Get off on each other!
Alright. We go as scheduled.
It's terrible!
Hayashi-san, what happened?
Hands came out and there were screams!
From Tamiko's room!
Tamiko's room?
What are you surprised about?
This is Tamiko's house.
Nothing should surprise you.
The Devil Princess is watching you.
It was so sudden.
But I haven't been this thrilled in a long time! I love it!
Where are the others?
Katahiro-san and Hayashi-san want to eat in their own room.
How selfish. What about the girls?
It looks like they went into town.
That's what Sakamoto-san said.
They went down the mountain?
They shouldn't. It's dangerous at night.
Ann Naka-san, are they making fun of you?
What?
You're still a novice.
Thanks for dinner.
Don't worry. Selfish customers are at their own fault.
Rina-chan, you are doing a good job.
Who are you calling Rina-chan?
Please don't treat me like a child.
No. I didn't mean it like that.
Inoue-san and the others haven't returned.
I guess I'm a failure as a tour guide.
It's me.
Me.
Rina-chan looks depressed.
I thought I'd surprise you.
You called me Rina-chan again.
Oh. That's right. Sorry.
That's alright. I forgive you.
Rina is a nice name.
Anna Karina. There's a French actress by that name.
Anna Karina is in a lot of Godard's movies.
You know a lot about movies.
Yeah. I dream about making a serious horror movie.
What about Rina-chan?
Me?
Why did you become a tour guide?
Because I like to travel.
Going to different places, meeting different people,
and to make that my job.
That's wonderful.
But maybe I should have kept it a hobby.
Rina-chan...
Don't think that way.
Everything starts with what you love.
Saito-san...
Okay. Here's the main course.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry. Inoue-san hasn't returned.
Waiting is a waste of time.
Let's just go.
But...
That's right. If we don't worship, we're cursed.
Don't worry. When the two return, I'll bring them.
Alright. Then I'll leave it to you.
It's at the end of the tunnel.
I can feel ghosts.
I feel it too!
Oh, no. Is this part of the tour?
No, it's not!
Hey! What's that?
I can't take it anymore!
Tomoya!
Please wait!
Rina-chan!
You're in the way.
It's Tamiko.
It's Tamiko!
Tamiya!
Katahiro-san? Hayashi-san?
No good. I lost them.
Maybe they're back at the inn.
I'll go back.
You're a real horny chick.
Even though you said "no" in the beginning.
Take another rod.
Katahiro-san? Hayashi-san?
Kuroki-san, you're back?
We're alone at last.
What?
No!
Please stop!
What's with you guys? Don't come back.
You can't have her to yourself, Kuroki.
What's going on?
We belong to this village.
No!
No! Please stop!
This village was always short on women.
We were bored everyday.
So Sakamoto-san, the new mayor...
made a plan to snare women with this tour.
No!
It wasn't easy.
Making false reservations.
Hospitalizing a male tour guide.
It's better to have a female tour guide, right?
A cute one like Ann Naka-san.
No!
A weird guy sure got in the way.
I've been after you from the beginning.
No. Don't.
Stop it. Please.
Stop it!
What?
Rina-chan?
This is your favorite tour guide.
She's a nasty one.
Stop it! This is a crime!
A crime? This?
Rina-chan...
I want it in my mouth.
No choice.
Here.
This is her real identity.
Hey. I haven't cum yet.
This woman is great!
You're so tight!
What happened?
Don't tell me she's...
Hey! The doll!
Rina-chan.
Tamiko!