Stop it!
Marino Ohkura
She's a quiet woman, so comparative
training should be easy with her.
She's a virgin, which means...
...she should have almost
no sexual experience.
For a girl as unripe as Marino...
...it'll first be necessary to teach
her the pleasures of her own body.
It think it will be necessary
to drag her into this world.
I see.
Well, then, Master. We
should begin the training.
Yes, indeed.
First, would you start
by becoming a puppet?
A puppet...?
Ow!
A puppet doesn't speak!
No matter how I humiliate
you, you will not resist!
You must remember that you are my slave.
No!
Silence, Marino! You're a puppet!
Does it trouble you having your
breasts rubbed by a strange man?
Your master asked you
how you feel! Answer him!
Please, no...
You're a puppet. Don't talk.
You are a slave! How does
a slave answer her master?
Stop it! Stop it, please!
Yes! A slave must obey her
master's orders without question!
Come, let your body dance with ecstasy!
Someday soon, you won't mind
when I play with you down here.
You may cry, but they will be tears of joy.
Come on! Let's really hear
you moan with pleasure!
I swear, I'm going to enjoy turning
you into that sort of woman.
You take after your father.
Your father was a world
famous bondage artist.
But that was just his public face.
His true face was that of a
masochist female dominator...
...which he raised you very well to be.
Does she please you?
This girl seems to project
the image of tidiness.
Raping such tidy women adds
spice to the practice of S&M.
Hey! What are you doing?!
You're supposed to kneel
before your master and suck it!
Lt...?
Go on! Please your master!
Do it now!
Ow!
Now! Now! Now!
Ow! Ow! Stop it, please!
Now do it!
Don't insult your master!
Deeper!
Come on, make more noise as you suck!
You clumsy fool!
You'll never, ever satisfy
your master that way!
It wasn't my fault!
More! Suck it harder!
Ow!
Keep it in your mouth!
That's the way, just do
it harder! Suck harder!
Well? Now you know a
little about pleasing men.
No! No, please!
Don't do it! Stop it! Stop it!
Be quiet, or you'll get cut inside.
No!
Shall we have a little fun?
An aphrodisiac. You'll feel
very good when we use this.
It seems to be taking effect.
Does it hurt?
If it hurts, then do it yourself.
In front of your master's eyes.
Well? Do you see how
perverse you really are?
Look.
Come on, try it yourself.
What's wrong? Can't you do it?
Show me that dirty side of you I saw before!
No!
Help her, Saki.
Yes, sir.
Well? Feels good, doesn't it? Here, look.
How does your love juice
taste? Do you like it?
That's it. That's the way.
Masturbation gives a person the
best feeling of all, doesn't it?
Master, it looks like this slave
is only pleasing herself.
Shouldn't we punish her a little?
You have a point.
Wh- What are you doing?! Stop it, please!
N- No!
Help me!
If you can't take it, you
can always just let it out.
No! I won't do that!
P- Please let me go to the toilet.
Toilet? Your toilet's right in front of you.
That bucket is your toilet.
Don't be shy. Just let it out.
Holding it in? If you don't go,
you'll make yourself sick.
Stop it! It's coming out!
Don't look at me!
I... I'm sorry.
You think saying "I'm sorry" will help?
You must be properly punished.
Wh- What are you...?
I'm going to use this pump
to clean out your anus.
Nothing to fear. It feels very nice.
When I work the pump, your anus
will inflate like a balloon. See?
Go on, lick your mistress' asshole!
As a slave, you must be glad to do it.
I... I can't!
Pleasure must be shared. Now do it!
And make more sloppy
sounds as you lick it.
Like the bitch you are!
Master, since we've gone this
far, how about a little anal sex?
Good idea.
Stop it! Stop it, please!
If you don't relax, it'll hurt.
I'll let it out! I'll let it all out in your ass.
Looks like she's fainted.
Yes, it looks that way.
Today's training is over.
We'll resume tomorrow.