What do you call this, Emily?
To Kunihiko, Emily is just a child.
Because I was worried about you,
I introduced him to a Virtuacall
girlfriend, right?
I was just teasing you a little,
but what's so great about a guy
who just dizzily follows?
And you were saying that's he's
just a brotherly type?
Were you serious, Emily?
Good luck to the both of you!
If you don't hurry, your first love
will go away!
Emily, you waited for me?
Sorry! Sorry!
Was Suzune okay?
Yeah! She can't drink, but she drank a
whole bunch, and got dizzy, she said.
Good, I'm glad it wasn't worse.
Oh, and I thought I'd let you know...
I'm going to go out with her.
It's all because of you, Emily.
Thank you.
Really?
It's great that your feelings reached her.
This summer, you work hard, and
get a good man too, right?
If that happens, then dress smart,
and let's go on a double date!
I'm so sleepy! So sleepy!
Guess I'll take a nap!
Brother...
Virtuacall 2,
Access 2.
To You, My True Feelings.
Wow! That had a good ending, didn't it?
I guess so.
I guess that's what they call serendipity.
What's wrong, Emily?
You're upset that Kunihiko got laid, right?
It's not really like that!
"How unfair! I'm so jealous!
Give back my brother!"
That's written all over your face.
I don't care!
Well...
Don't come near me! GO AWAY!
Oh no, she is seriously in love.
I'm the boss here.
Suzune?
Yes?
Was the movie too childish for you?
No, that's not true.
It was pretty interesting.
Popcorn while watching a movie makes you
feel like, "I really watched a movie!"
And then I get really into it.
Oh yeah, I come here every once
in a while, but this shop...
This one, this one! The blueberry cake
and the cold mocha java are the best!
I've tried this too.
This combination is pretty good.
Do you come her a lot with Emily?
That Emily makes me go to
the movies with her,
and the course is pretty much
to go here afterwards.
If you turn her down, she gets mad.
It's really a pain!
That makes me a little jealous.
Hasegawa, when you talk about Emily,
somehow you seem really happy.
You're misunderstanding!
She's just like a little sister to me.
She's always around, so she just kind of
comes out in my conversation.
But it's not that kind of relationship.
That's okay. You don't have to get
so flustered about it.
Sorry.
Why the sad face, Brother?
My intention was to show
Suzune a good time.
It just seemed that the date
wasn't very exciting.
That time, we just got caught up in
everything and that happened,
but since then, we haven't even kissed.
Get a hold of yourself!
If you keep thinking that way, you'll just
make yourself insecure again.
I just get so weird when
I'm around Suzune.
Brother, are you sending her signals?
Signals?
Yeah, signals. Getting the hang of it is
important with things like that.
That's all wrong! That stupid face will
make her feelings calm down!
So look in the mirror, and do
some more research!
Emily?
What are you so mad about?
What's wrong with me? Why Emily?
Right now my head should be
full of Suzune.
I should be thinking about how to make
things go well with Suzune, and...
The Virtucall is still here?
All right, just once more,
to change my mood.
No, I can't! I already have
my heart set on Suzune.
How could I show such a pathetic
perverted character?
That Virtuacall thing...
Sorry, Suzune!
I'll make tonight the last time.
Hi, welcome to Virtuacall!
From here on out, everything depends
only on your charm and...
Enough with the explanations already!
Hello, I'm Kunihiko Hasegawa.
What's your name?
I'm Chisato Haragataka. Nice to meet you.
You don't look it, but you have a
very polite personality.
Hasegawa, what is your occupation?
Me?
I'm still a college student.
I'm in my fourth year, though.
Then it's an important time for you,
looking for a job and all.
Good luck, Hasegawa!
Oh, thank you.
This isn't good. I don't get the feel.
I think I'll change people.
Sorry, I just remembered something
I have to do right now.
Talking with me is...
It's boring, right?
Everyone says so.
They say I talk like a manual,
and that's boring.
Well, bye-bye!
Wait a minute.
I do have time now after all.
Shall we meet somewhere?
Hasegawa!
You're a stewardess?
Yes, that's right.
But time is scarce with that
kind of job, right?
There's not much of a chance
to even meet people.
Even if I do find someone I like, I can't
make time to see them as I wish.
Sorry, I'm getting depressing.
Tonight, let's drink!
Yeah.
Seen from here,
the airport looks kind of like a space
station floating in the galaxy, right?
Hey, lady!
My sense of smell has sniffed you out!
Miss, let's burn rubber in my Caddy.
Yeah, burn rubber!
Mizushima!
Oh? Is that you, Hasegawa?
Is she your woman, then?
It's not like that with her.
Then there's no problem if we
partake of her, right?
Miss, what is your name?
Quit it, Mizushima. She doesn't like it.
Stop using violence!
You... You can't be!
Hasegawa, you remember this!
Mizushima, she's dangerous.
I know that!
Take this!
Save us!
Sorry, that must've surprised you.
Eighty percent of my body is artificial.
Thank you, Kunihiko.
I feel refreshed after rioting a little.
Say, Kunihiko?
Do you want to have sex?
Sex?
I've decided to throw away the
boring me for tonight.
Don't worry.
That part is the twenty percent.
That part, you say?
Chisato, this isn't right.
I have a girlfriend, and this kind of thing...
Just an adventure for the evening.
And besides this is quite
engorged, isn't it?
My sense of reason flies away.
Suzune, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Good!
Good...
Hasegawa, from the back...
Harder, please.
Good...
I feel it, I feel it!
Good!
I... anymore...
Here I come!
Inside! Come inside me, please!
I'm coming!
My Lady, are you going to buy
something else?
It's cute, isn't it? What's the problem?
It's my gentle revenge on Papa and Mama.
Emily...
Suzune!
What's the matter?
You're buying quite a bit.
I'm leaving Japan soon. To tell the truth,
I was a foreign student.
Isn't Brother with you today?
No. More importantly, does Hasegawa
know you're leaving?
It's okay. He's just a neighbor.
He's clumsy, kind of dense and tactless,
but there aren't so many straightforward
nice guys like him.
Suzune, please take good care of Brother!
Emily, shouldn't you be more honest
about your feelings?
I'm just like a little sister, so...
Because of my homeland's customs,
my life in Japan has ended with
my eighteenth birthday.
I'm the only candidate to succeed to
the Welfenland throne.
I don't have anymore time!
Father, Mother and my
countrymen are waiting.
Who is it? It's open!
Geez! Who IS it?
Wait a minute, okay?
Yes?
Emily, what's up?
You...
Brother, let's go on a date!
Date? Even if you say so all of a sudden...
It's okay, it's okay! Hurry up!
I'm making my last memories, so...
Making memories? You?
Don't ask stupid questions! Now, hurry!
We're going! Going!
Emily!
Brother?
Oh, a yukata?
They still had sparklers.
Emily, did something happen to you?
It's strange.
All of a sudden, you dress up, cause a big
fuss, make me take you everywhere...
Is it something that you can't tell me?
Brother!
Emily?
The end.
I'm tired already today,
so I'm going home, okay?
Good night, Brother!
Emily...
Field House
It seems you've finally realized who the
person most important to you is.
Suzune, I've thought of Emily as
a little sister all this time.
To be honest, I'm hesitant.
It's something that happens often.
I finally realized it too.
Anyone who loves will have worries,
and become hesitant.
But I think it's really quite easy.
Bless your soul without any reservations.
Wonderful!
You say such beautiful things, Suzune!
I've finally opened my eyes.
What do you want with Suzune, now?
Think about what you did to her!
I'm not talking to you, Hasegawa.
It's all right, Hasegawa.
But...
The one I really like is you.
Suzune!
I wanted to speak with
this person once more.
And so that's how it is, Hasegawa.
I'm not so stupid that I'd make
the same mistake twice.
Hasegawa, before she leaves Japan,
you have to express your true feelings.
Leaves Japan? Who is?
What? You still don't know about
Emily leaving the country?
Leaving the country?
Making my last memories...
Suzune, thank you!
Maybe I acted a little too cool?
I'm pretty clumsy with people too.
Oh, what a beautiful foot!
Please pick on me some more!
Quit it already!
More! More!
Just a little more!
Emily!
My Lady,
the paperwork is done.
Shall we drink tea while we wait?
Yes.
Forgive me, Emliy.
I didn't even know your feelings!
I won't see you again, just like that?
Emily, you could have at least
discussed it with me!
Mister, I'll get off here.
Keep the change!
Sorry, about that, Sir.
Only twenty bucks?
Hey, boy! You're short ten bucks!
Ten bucks!
Damn, why was Emily silent?
Was that all our relationship was?
What was I to you?!
My Lady?
Shall we go?
Emily, where are you? Where are you?
...Welfendland, please gather at Gate 5.
Brother? Brother!
Emily!
Brother!
No, Brother!
Emily!
You idiot, why did you try to go
without saying anything?
I still haven't told you how I really feel!
Emily, I...
I like you.
I love you!
I like you, Brother.
No, I really like Kunihiko!
Emily, you're beautiful.
Please be gentle with me.
Emily...
It's hot down there!
It keeps getting hotter.
Good!
I can't anymore... I'm going to come!
Me too.
Kunihiko, me too!
As it turns out, I've been a freeloader
in Kunihiko's room ever since then.
Miraculously he graduated,
and we got engaged.
We'll have our wedding in Welfenland.
What an amazing castle!
I'll be the crown prince of a whole country!
Maybe even King?
Lucky! Lucky!
Welcome to Welfenland.
As ruler of the country, I welcome you.
You're the ruler of the country?
Kunihiko, what are you saying? Of course
Mama is the ruler of the country!
Leadership of Welfenland is based on
a succession of women.
The kingship is too, but the high-ranking
positions are held by women.
It's not a custom of putting men over
women, but rather women over men.
That's right, the custom of putting
women above men.
Woman
That's right, the custom of putting
women above men.
Exalted
That's right, the custom of putting
women above men.
Man
That's right, the custom of putting
women above men.
Lowly
That's right, the custom of putting
women above men.
Didn't I tell you?
Well, Kunihiko, it's good that you've come.
Now, I no longer have to feel so lonely
and low.
Putting women above men?
Don't feel so bad!
Yoake mae ni
tsuki mo nemuru
Kuruma touta shi
Okina nimotsu
kakaete matsu
Kimi no sugata hashiru
Neboke madako
Goranyou hora
Fuyu no yousei
Mai oritewa
Mishibiku youni
Michi o terasu navigation
Chizu ni nai
Bokura dake no
Nuke michi ga aru
Ichiban de tobi desou
Sa hajimeo
Shiroi shower
Futari no iki
Mo sore de mata
Yuki ni nareruyo
Nagaku Nagaku
Ashiato tsukeyou
Tsutaerareru
Sunaoni ima
Asahi ga noburu shunkan ni
lma mou ichido
Tsuyoku Tsuyoku
Dakiyose Nagara
I need you