Rxxx: Prescription for Pain Part 1
All right... How's the anesthetic?
We're ready to go.
Blood pressure and vital signs?
Stable.
How's his condition?
He's stable.
Okay, let's begin the surgery.
OPERATING
Doctor!
How was the surgery?
The surgery was a success. lt hasn't spread anywhere else...
...so we can relax for now.
Give him a month and he'll be back on the job in no time.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you. l know you're tired.
lt's okay. l don't mind.
About this...
Okay, can you pass this along?
Yes.
Dr. Shiozaki, l heard you were amazing today in surgery.
There was no need for me to do it.
lf it hadn't been Congressman Nakajima, l wouldn't have done it.
Would you like a massage?
Thanks. That'd be great.
The exhaustion after a successful surgery...
l can't express how much l love this moment.
Moments like this make me want to fuck a woman.
Doctor, what are you doing?
l thought l should return the favor.
D... Doctor...
Please stop!
You know you want it.
But...
No.
Feel how wet you are.
You're refusing, but your body is begging for it.
l'll scream!
Who's more important to the hospital? Me or you?
You're getting hot...
Your back massage was better.
You're supposed to do it like this.
Got it?
Yes.
You're getting the hang of it.
No...
Are you going to have your period soon?
No!
Maybe l should take a good look.
l see...
Your insides look healthy. You passed the test.
What is that?
This? Relax. l won't do anything bad to your body. l'm a doctor.
Doctor...
l'm filling up.
l... l can't hold it anymore! l'm going to pee!
Whoa!
Nice piss shot.
Let's see...
Good. Your physical exam was fine.
l just gave you a medicine that l created.
You'll start to feel things that you've never felt before.
Looks like it's starting to kick in.
lt's amazing! lt feels so good... l think l'm going to go crazy! Help me, Doctor!
Listen to me.
From now on, you're going to call me Master, except when we're on the job...
...or you'll never be able to feel this ecstasy again.
l understand, Master.
Good girl.
lt was water, but she totally believed it.
lt's so easy to brainwash naive women like her...
l'm going to cum!
Cum... Please, Master.
She'll never be satisfied with another man. She's my sex slave.
l work as a physician at Misono General Hospital...
...one of the top-rated hospitals in Japan.
My skills as a physician have been highly acclaimed...
...and l have been written up in several magazines.
l'm to the point where l can boast that l am the reputation of this hospital.
The president of the hospital is sick, and it's rumored he'll retire soon.
People are saying l'm going to be the next president, and that the only thing...
...that stands in my way is my young age, but...
Thanks for coming, everyone.
My daughter Serika has returned to us as a full-fledged doctor.
She'll join our team as a physician.
Hello everyone.
l'll do my best, and l hope to put everything l've learned thus far to good use.
The meddlesome daughter has returned...
l haven't seen her for a while, and now she's all grown up.
So it's not the other driver's fault?
Yeah, l wasn't thinking, and ran into the road. lt's totally my fault.
l hope you learned your lesson, and will watch out for cars from now on.
Yes Doctor!
l better get going.
Wait!
My dad really likes you. He made you my doctor.
You think so...?
He does! There's no doubt about it!
Yes, come in.
Hey.
Do you have a minute?
l have a chart that l need to review by tomorrow. Can you keep it short?
Why are you acting so cold? l just want to give you a warm welcome.
How dare you say that...
l'm sorry about that. l was young, l couldn't hold myself back.
Stop joking around! l haven't forgotten!
No! Stop!
N... No!
l'm going to cum...
Hey Serika...
Don't call me that.
Sorry. Doctor Serika.
What did you think of me before that happened?
Did you hate me from the very beginning?
That's...
At the time, l had just started out as a physician, and the stress kept mounting.
l took it out on you... l know l've done something l can never take back.
l'll make it up to you, even if it takes the rest of my life. l'll do anything for you.
Stop it!
Serika!
l'll never forget the humiliation l had to endure.
You're thinking about your next step...
Now that l'm back, your hopes of becoming the next president are fading...
...so you're trying to get on my good side, or better yet, marry me...
...all so you can control this hospital. Am l right?
W-what are you talking about? l wouldn't...
You'd better brace yourself! When l become President...
...the first thing l'm going to do is fire you!
You're going to fire me? The reputation of this hospital will go down the tubes.
The committee will never allow that.
Why do you think l chose the same field as you?
As long as l do better than you, there shouldn't be a problem.
You're going to leave this hospital...
...and don't even think about trying to get a job at a different hospital.
The medical industry is small.
No one will want to hire you and risk their relationship with us.
Then again, with your skills, you'll probably be able to get a job...
...at some hick village with no doctor, or maybe somewhere overseas.
lt feels so good! Just thinking about you looking at me, makes me wet...
Damn that Serika. She's still on a high horse because she has money and authority.
Damn it... That's how she was back then, too.
You're almost fully recovered.
l'll be gone soon. What should l do when l first get out?
lt's winter, so maybe l should go skiing in Canada.
Or maybe l'll go to our vacation home in Australia and swim every day...
Doctor, what do you want to do?
l'll ask dad to give you a vacation for treating me!
Let's go together!
l couldn't handle it.
She was so insensitive, oblivious about the hardships in life.
l couldn't forgive Serika, who grew up with everything l didn't!
No!
Nooo!
M... Master, you're so amazing today! This is the best... l'm going numb!!
Damn it! l'm not going to let her have her way! Just you watch!
You're the one who's leaving!
l can't do that!
You want more money?
Would you rather Serika become the next president?
That's not what l mean...
l think it'd be best if you were the next president.
But lying about malpractice? l can't do that...
Just pretend to discover it right before she injects the patient with it.
l'm a doctor. l'm not saying we should sacrifice a patient.
All l want is for Serika's reputation to be scarred.
l have to decline. l pride myself on being a nurse, so...
Are you sure?
Yes.
l see. That's too bad...
Are you awake?
lt seems l can't convince you with words, so l'll show you instead...
This is my way of convincing people.
Let me examine your colon.
Let's see...
Did it hurt? l guess it did. l didn't spit on my fingers and just shoved it in.
You're getting used to it. You're the one who's squeezing.
Why are you stopping?
What's wrong? Does it feel good?
Y-yes!
Make up your mind! l don't know what you want.
What do you want me to do? Do you want me to stop?
Doctor... Please fuck me!
Don't call me Doctor. Call me Master when we're not on the job.
Yes, Master!
Please... Please fuck me with your hot, hard cock and make me go crazy.
Fine...
Yes...
Yes!
Yes! lt feels so good...
l'm impressed. After all, you're the one who's in charge of the young nurses...
You've had a lot of practice over the years.
Thank you...
What's wrong?
Master, please.
Fine then.
lt's amazing! lt feels so good my knees are starting to get weak.
l'm going to cum!
M-me too!
PRESIDENT'S OFFICE
This is definitely Serika's handwriting.
l don't remember writing that. lt's so strange!
There's no reason to prescribe that!
You're right. lt's a good thing Miyuki caught it beforehand.
lmagine what could have happened.
The patient's condition wouldn't have changed with this, but...
...it could have been much worse.
ln a worst case scenario, the otherwise treatable patient might have died.
But l...
Dr. Serika must have been tired.
She's not used to the job here yet, and she's been working nonstop.
Go get some rest.
Yes. Get someone to cover for you this afternoon.
l'm fine!
No! This is an order from the President.
Dad!
l said no!
Please, l'm fine...
Good... But l've only just begun.
Dr. Serika is so wonderful. She's beautiful, smart and she's nice to us too.
The patients really like her, too.
The next president has to be Dr. Serika.
l wish l could be like Dr. Serika in my next life.
Hello, Nurse's Station.
Yes... What?
Yes, sure.
Come in.
Excuse me. l've brought the chart you requested.
Good job. lt must have been a pain to find.
No, not at all.
Huh?
l thought you were both off today?
Something came up...
Yes, something...
Nanami.
Yes?
What are you doing?
Well? Are you still planning to side with Dr. Serika?
That website run by nurses
that posts hospital stories...
You read it from time to time, right?
l'm going to send them this picture tomorrow.
Who knows if it'll get posted, but the nurses who run the site will see it.
Just think, if they're your old classmates, they'll know exactly who it is.
Don't do it! You can't!
This is all because you're being difficult...
You can't blame me for...
l see... Your body's made up its mind, but your mouth hasn't...
Your mouth needs a lesson.
Suck it!
Well? Have you changed your mind?
Switch!
What do you think? The real one's better, right?
Y-yes... lt feels so good...
You'll never be able to feel like this if you side with Dr. Serika.
Are you still going to choose her over me?
Take a good look, ladies. We're connected. How's Nanami's pussy?
l'm so jealous! lt's squeezing Master's cock.
Nanami is so wet. She's so excited. She totally wants you, Master.
You hear that? Do you still insist on siding with Dr. Serika?
Then how about this?
l'm going numb!
l can stop right now.
Are you sure you're not going to change your mind?
You can't stop!
You've changed your mind?
Y-yes...
l can't hear you!
l understand! l'll do whatever you ask me to do, Doctor!
Don't call me Doctor. Call me Master, except when we're on the job.
Yes, Master...
Um...
Master, l can't take it anymore... Please give it to me, too.
Making us watch is like torture.
Fine. Come here.
l'll do anything to become President.
Serika... You have no choice. Either leave, or become my sex slave like them...
Your fate belongs to me...