Madame, are you satisfied?
Yes... Somewhat...
Somewhat?
You're such a needy person...
She's become a slave to sexual pleasure...
She may look like a fool, but to me,
she's a most pure and beautiful being.
I... I'm in love with Madame.
I guess you're not
satisfied with my fingers...
Kayuki!
Yes!
I'm hungry. Can you make something?
Yes. I'll prepare something right away.
You're such a klutz.
Did you use these?
Sis? I didn't know she had it in her.
Who is she fucking?
It's all right. I'll find out for myself.
Don't worry about my food.
Clean this up and go to bed.
Yes.
Out of all people, he chose
my sister!? How dare he!?
I'm better than my sister.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
I saw it all. I saw you and
my sister having sex.
You've only screwed my sister, right?
I think it'll be worth your while
to explore my body, too.
Go ahead. Do what ever you want.
What's wrong? Are you
nervous or something?
That's so cute.
No matter what kind of rough
sex Madame and I have, there's
some kind of bond between us.
There's no way I'd do the same things to
this trashy whore that I do to Madame.
What was that for?
I'm giving you what you deserve!
Huh?
Why are you doing this?
You're the one that said I
could do whatever I want!
There's no backing out now!
Poor thing.
Your beautiful skin is completely ruined!
You need some first aid.
I'm giving you an ammonia
disinfectant treatment!
Aren't I nice?
I'm going to see your most
embarrassing moment, Lady Karen.
No! I don't want to do this!
Honestly I'd like to tape this, but I can't
have you causing trouble for Madame.
Come on.
No!
Excuse me.
Dr. Horibe is here.
I wonder what he wants? Let him in.
Yes!
It's Dr. Horibe...
I wonder why he's here?
Please stop!
We've already settled on our deal.
True, I received some
money to keep quiet...
...about your husband being
poisoned with arsenic...
So I have a right to demand something
for writing a false death certificate!
I'll pay you. How much
would you be satisfied with?
Don't worry about the money. I want you...
Yes... that's right...
We're both adults. Let's enjoy it.
I've always had a thing for you, Madame.
It's like a dream come true, that I get
to do something like this with you.
Please excuse me.
Madame.
It's fate that things turned out like this.
We share a secret together,
and now you're single.
I'll always be ready to
come over, at any time.
I really wish you wouldn't act so cold.
But that's the thing about
you that turns men on.
I'll be leaving now...
S... someone!
Did you do this?
Yes.
There was no need to kill him.
He can't cause you any more trouble.
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't let him have his way with
me so I could cover up for you!
The most important thing to me is to
protect this house from scandalous rumors.
Whatever the reason, at
the end you protected me.
Thank you very much...
Are you the one who killed my husband?
Forgive me...
It's fine. It's not like I was in love with him.
But why?
Why did you need to kill my husband?
Master was...
Juichiro Aoki was my father.
I was born between the maid and Master.
After I was born, I was raised in this house.
After my mother's death, I
remained here as a maid.
Then, one day...
You're starting to look like your mother...
Huh?
Your neck looks exactly like hers...
Master!
Your mother loved this more than anything.
Well?
I'm sure you love it too. Am I wrong?
Master!
Madame is...
You're mine. No one can tell me
what I can and can't do to you.
No!
Stop! Please!
Stop!
No!
Pull it out!
I couldn't bear the fact that my only
family in this world was a monster!
That's why I made him drink
the poison my mother left.
My mother loved Master...
That's why she committed
suicide when Master married you.
That's how I found out it was poison.
You said earlier that you know
everything that goes on in this house.
By any chance, do you know
about Ayamoto and me...?
Yes, I am aware.
I have a favor to ask about Ayamoto...
What is it? Go ahead and ask.
Can you please not
distract Ayamoto so much?
Are you in love with Ayamoto?
No, that's not it...
It's just that I'm worried.
He has such an amazing talent to become
a painter, but all he thinks about is you.
He hasn't picked up his brush at all lately...
I see...
Would it be possible if you could
make the initiative to put some
distance between you two?
When I married into this house, I
didn't come because I was attracted
to my husband's artistic talent.
I came for his money.
But if you care about Ayamoto, don't
you want to let his artistic talent flourish?
You're saying I'm in love
with a servant like Ayamoto?
Madame!
You should get back to work. It's
almost time to prepare dinner.
Ayamoto!
Huh?
You should stop seeing Madame!
Oh, you knew about that?
Do you really think that Madame loves you?
Love?
I don't think so... But I guess
it's a similar kind of feeling...
We both can't do without
each other. That's for certain!
You're wrong!
Huh?
You were only a convenient
man who was at arm's length!
You're not special or anything to her.
H... how would you know that!?
You don't know anything!
Ayamoto, I have something
to tell you! I'm in...
Good evening!
Y-yes!
Please excuse us for coming so late.
I am Sakuma from the
Jyohoku police department.
Is the Madame home tonight?
Mr. Sakuma. That girl is...
Yes.
So you're saying that Dr.
Horibe hasn't been here?
Yes.
That's strange.
He told the hospital that after he
finished a physical at the retirement
home, he'd stop by here.
Oh... But he really hasn't been here.
Is that so...
This is strange.
Dr. Horibe was here today.
Why is Madame saying that?
She couldn't have...
Hotter!
Burn my body!
You're such a selfish woman...
Do it to me too!
Pay attention to my sister, too.
I feel so bad for her when
you ignore her like this.
It's fine. Let her sit there.
The only one who's allowed
to be selfish is Madame.
It hurts! More!
Make it hurt more!
Let's see if your ass tightens up when
you have a fat one like this in you.
Karen...
Do it to Karen too. Please...
I'll deal with the vibrator for now.
If you insist, I guess I can't say no.
It's Madame flavor.
Be grateful. You get to suck it.
Thank you, sis.
I misunderstood you until now. I'm sorry!
It's all right, Karen.
Go ahead and let Ayamoto
give you pleasure.
Yes! I'm going to break!
Ayamoto! Do the same to me!
Madame!
Hurry up and do it!
More... More!!
Me too...
Do it to me too! Please!
Slice me!
Suck my blood!
Yes! More!
I'm covered in sweat! I'm going
to take a break and have a bath.
No! I'll lick your sweat off and clean you!
I won't forgive you if you take a shower!
Me too! Let me lick you too!
I wonder what it'll taste like if I eat this?
I want to eat the cock!
But that's...
Hello.
Um... Madame is busy right now...
Oh no, that's fine. I came
today to talk to you.
Me?
What terrifying siblings... Am I going to
be able to handle those two from now on?
Sis, I love you! I love you so much!
Me too, Karen!
So you're absolutely sure that
Dr. Horibe hasn't been here?
Yes.
Hmm... I see...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Something smells like it's burning.
Madame!
Madame!!
Madame! Hurry! Please hurry
and get out of there! Madame!
Ayamoto, come here! Hurry! Let's
do it together! It feels so good!
She's insane...
That's it!
What the...!?
Ayamoto, get out of there!
Ayamoto!
A few days later, Dr. Hoibe's
remains were found in the shed.
The murder case was closed, because the
detective witnessed the crazed sisters...
...and concluded that they
were the ones who did it.
Thus, Kayuki did not get arrested.
As for me, I spent the days absent
minded, while recovering from my burns...
...but thanks to Kayuki's devoted
care, I regained my health.
From that point on, I picked up my brush
and started to paint as if I was possessed.
Soon, I started to be noticed as
an up-and-coming new artist.
And now, I have regained
true stability once again.
I don't know how to
thank Kayuki for her love.
Kaoru, I love you... I love you so much.
I wonder if I'll be able to stay satisfied
with this boring sex life forever?
That hurts! What's the matter?
S... sorry...