Masaki Asakura is the manager
of the pop group Twinkle.
He has fallen in love with Saori, the
daughter of his step-mother, Emiko.
Will Masaki be able to
protect his dear step-sister...
...from the evil conspiracies
surrounding the entertainment industry?
SPOTLIGHT
Between the Realms of Desire & Envy
Episode 2
(YUNA SAOTOME)
I'm really sorry!
It's because I wasn't
paying enough attention...
It's my fault you got injured like this.
Oh, don't worry about it. It was my choice.
But I can't just...
What can I say? My
body moved on instinct.
Anyway, Saori is okay, right?
Aren't you glad?
Yeah... Thank you for saving
her. She's perfectly fine.
I really appreciate it.
A younger sister, huh?
Huh?
You're in love with Saori, aren't you?
Uh, well... that's...
You don't have to hide it. I can
tell just by how you reacted.
Anyway, you'd better be able
to protect her next time.
After all, you love Saori so
much that you came after us.
Well... that was a...
I did it in anger and...
I'm sorry. I've done something
terrible to you both.
I'll do anything, if you'll forgive me.
Anything?
Then...
Will you make love to me?
What?
I want you to do it gently this time.
I want you to make love
to me just this once.
Sure. If that makes up
for the things I've done.
Thanks to you, I can see
things more clearly...
But I must admit, it was
a rough route you took.
I just had to work harder.
Thanks for making me realize that.
See ya!
Erica.
May I have a moment of your time?
What do you need?
Masaki, remember the horrible
things you did to me the other day?
Y-yeah... I'm really sorry.
I really wasn't myself.
What are we going to do about
your overprotective sister complex?
Yeah, tell me about it.
There's something I want you
to do, to make it up to me.
To be honest, I was in love with you.
But you only paid attention to Saori.
I was so jealous.
That's why I was being a bully.
But it's your fault too, you know!
So make it up to me.
This time, I want you to make love to me.
Sure.
Thank you.
That was great, Masaki.
I'll remember this when I'm gone.
What did you just say?
Well...
So? What's going on?
Are you going to have
it all by the due date?
Yes, I'll definitely have it by then.
Well, just make sure you have
all one hundred million ready.
Rumor has it that your
talents are pretty promising.
It's only a hundred million. You should
be able to come up with it somehow.
We'll leave for now, but...
...you'd better have it next time.
Hey.
What's going on?
Your boss isn't returning our money.
So we came all the way here to collect it.
Anyway, ask your boss for more details.
As long as I get my money
back that's all I care about.
So, can you explain
what's going on, boss?
I was going to have to tell
you sooner or later, but...
...this company has a one
hundred million yen debt.
It's my husband's... Your father's debt.
The interest kept piling up, and now
it's reached the hundred million mark.
My father's?
Why haven't you told me
something this important until now?
I didn't know.
I found out when I had to
sign the inheritance papers.
Then it would have been better
to give up the inheritance.
But I made a promise to him.
I promised him that I would do my best
to see that his company succeeds.
Then, what are you going to do about it?
Asakuro Production doesn't
have the money to pay back
one hundred million yen!
We'll be fine if Twinkle can
become regulars on that show.
Their CDs will sell and commercial
jobs will hopefully roll in.
And if they don't get the position?
If you're going to cry, please do it here.
You can't cry in front of
Saori and the others.
I know...
...but, for now...
This is terrible. I almost gave her a kiss!
Yes...
Thank you, Masaki.
You're always so kind,
even to a woman like me.
Huh?
I only had sex with you
because I was so lonely.
On top of that, I was fantasizing
about your father during it.
I kind of figured as much.
Huh?
But in a way it's great. My step-mother
is still in love with my father.
I think I would have been
sad if it was anyone else.
You're a fool.
And there's something I need to tell you.
You're not alone.
You have Saori.
And, you have me.
We'll always be on your side.
Please don't forget that.
Yes?
Saori, there's something I
need to talk to you about.
Welcome, glad you could come.
You're a beautiful girl,
just like your mother.
This will be fun.
Oh? Mother, have you seen Saori?
Saori is at Kijima's place right now.
What did you just say?
What are you thinking?
You're terrible! In the end, you're
only thinking about yourself!
Damn it! I'll take care of Saori! You
can't have her anymore! Good bye!
Hmm? What's wrong? Hurry
up and take off your clothes.
Do you not want the regular position?
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
What to do...
Your mother was happy to service me.
Huh? Mother did?
That's right. You mother was
quite skilled at what she did.
I'm sure she's fucked many different men.
She didn't...
You have the blood of a slut
running through your veins.
Come now, entertain me.
Or would you rather have me force you?
Please hold that thought, Mr. Kijima.
Mr. Kijima, I recommend our Lovely Ladies
rather than a scrawny woman like her.
Now ladies...
...give Mr. Kijima a taste of Heaven!
Yes!
How the hell do you
expect me to eat this!?
W-what are you...
Mr. Matsuoka.
You have made a terrible mistake.
I absolutely despise wasting food!
B-but...
True, the Lovely Ladies seem amazing.
So I'll let them make their debut. But...
(NEW SENSATION ADULT)
(VIDEO SPOTLIGHT)
...as porno actresses.
(NEW SENSATION ADULT)
(VIDEO SPOTLIGHT)
Damn it. This wasn't how
it was supposed to be!
What the fuck are you doing Kibayashi?
Uhh... I was kind of, sort
of, thinking of joining in?
You fucker. What the hell are you thinking?
Um... Well...
I just wanted to try and get a
little something, for once...
You mother fucker.
Oh what a handsome guy!
Oh my! You said it sister!
I want the handsome with the glasses.
Then the grease hunk is all mine.
Yes? This is Asakura Production.
What? You've chosen our
girls for the position?
Yes. I understand. Thank you very much.
Yes? This is Asakura Production.
Oh, Yuna!
What? You're switching agencies?
You want to become an action star?
Yes? This is Asakura Production.
Oh, Erica!
Huh? You're going to become an actress?
But you can be one through us...
You've already decided?
Yes?
Saori?
What? You're not coming home anymore?
Good bye.
Glad you could come.
It's been rough for you, huh?
You finally got the 'Regulars'
position, and all your girls left you.
I'm all alone again.
They always leave me.
Do you know why Taizo died?
You were a pop star once.
There's a man who has
loved you since back then.
At first, he was only wishing
for your happiness...
...but then he started to
want you all for himself.
And he took your husband's life.
Knowing it wouldn't do anything...
I knew all along...
...that you gave the orders.
Then why?
Don't you hate me?
Even so, I have no choice
but to live for the both of us.
You're such a strong woman.
If I only had your strength
I would have taken you.
Although it wasn't any of my business,
I paid off your company's debt.
This is the only way I know to
express my love. Forgive me.
You're not alone. At least in
your heart, Taizo is there.
Forgive me.
I wish...
I was also...
...in your heart.
I'm sorry, Masaki.
It's all right. We were the
ones that were wrong.
You're the one that's right.
So, what do you want to do from now on?
I'm going to keep singing. For sure!
I'll write my own songs, and start
fresh with general auditions.
Okay then.
I'll fully back you. You just keep
doing what you think is right.
Okay!
And I have my first favor to ask you.
What is it?
Umm... I want you to make love to me.
I've been in love with you
since the first day we met.
Same goes for me.
Huh?
Masaki.
Is it all right if I take a shower with you?
Sure.
What's wrong Masaki?
Oh, I was just thinking
how beautiful you were.
I'm so embarrassed.
S-sorry.
That's so weird!
Wow. It ends up looking like this?
I can't help it. It's because
I saw your beautiful body.
Oh Masaki... you're embarrassing me!
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
You're so much prettier
than some pop star.
Um, Masaki? I'm a pop
star too, you know...
Oh yeah! That's right.
Sorry, my mistake.
Hmph! You dummy.
Anyway, I want to see your body more.
Nope!
It's so strange.
I was so afraid of Mr. Kijima's,
but I'm not afraid of yours.
It's not really helping me when you're
comparing me to an old geezer.
Was it shaped weird?
No, it wasn't that.
It didn't gross me out. I'm not
talking about how it looked.
Oh, I see.
On top of that, I've only seen yours
and Mr. Kijima's, so I really don't
know what a weird shape would be.
Then you're a...
Yes, it's my first time.
Oh, forget it!
Sorry Saori. It's my fault.
Let's make up.
Just forget it!
I was just nervous because I thought
I was going to make love to you.
It's like a dream come true.
Really?
Yes. Really.
But let's not, tonight. I
wasn't being nice to you.
No!
Please. I want you to
make love to me now.
My body is getting so
hot and I'm getting wet.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be.
You're so wet, it's great.
Oh, Masaki...
Saori.
I'm coming in.
Okay.
It hurts!
Oh, sorry.
No, don't pull out.
I wanna do this.
Okay. All right then.
Let's stop, Saori. That's enough for today.
Huh?
Okay...
I'm sorry Masaki.
But it really hurts...
Don't worry about it.
But it leaves you hanging...
Yeah, but what can you do?
We'll try again next time.
No, I can do it! I want
to make you feel good.
But...
You want to cum, right?
Well... yeah...
Honesty's the best policy!
You're really good, Saori.
Yes...
Yes... I'm going to cum...
I can't... hold it anymore!
H-hey.
Are you sure?
It's bitter, Masaki.
And my jaw hurts.
Thanks.
Uh-huh.
I'll practice more and get better at it.
Will you always stay by my side?
Oh my god. I'm so happy!
Let's spend our lives together...
Okay.