Madame.
I told you not to take a shower
for a week. Did you listen to me?
Yes.
It feels so good.
It feels good?
I'm not wasting my time
to make you feel good!
It hurts!
This is amazing.
Please stop!
I'm begging you!
Please make it stop...
Do it faster.
Faster!
Savor it in your mouth, just like wine...
You know what's going to happen
if you don't listen to me, right?
That's enough. You can swallow it.
His brush licking habit is creeping me out...
It's proof that he's concentrating.
And what is the powerful and sensual
energy that the picture emits?
It looks exactly like Madame.
Is it their secret pleasure session that
artistically inspires Master so much?
You're always working so hard.
Thank you.
I'm confident I can equal Master in skill...
But I can't draw something like that,
because I've never been with a woman.
Damn it!
It's not even a matter of skill anymore!
It's your fault for being spacey.
What were you thinking about?
I know! You were having
perverted thoughts, weren't you?
O... of course not!
You're blushing. It's
obvious, even if you deny it.
Hey...
I always tell you that I'll let you fuck me.
There's no need to be shy. Want
to come to my room right now?
Stop joking around.
I have an errand to run for Master.
What's so good about him?
After fucking guys like you all the time,
I want to fuck a virgin for a change.
Oh come on, don't say that!
We have more than enough energy.
We can even take on your sister.
Don't talk about my sister.
What? You're freeloading off of her
but you're not getting along with her?
I don't like her.
She's always been so snooty,
ever since we were kids.
But the high and mighty type
are also fun to deal with.
I'm not going to lose to my sister!
Especially when it comes to men!
Yes! More... Fuck me harder!
What a demanding girl.
I'll plug that wise cracking mouth.
The more I look at her ass,
the more I want to fuck it!
Her anus is twitching!
Stop talking! Hurry up and fuck me!
All right.
It's nice and tight!
Yes! My entire body's going numb!
Then I'll...
Harder... Harder... Harder!
Fuck me!!
It's almost time for a tea break.
Excuse me.
I've brought you some tea.
Master?
Master!!
S... s... someone!!
Master is... Master is...
JUICHIRO AOKI DIES OF
SUDDEN HEART FAILURE.
FUNERAL
I'll find another place to move by the end
of Master's forty-nine days of mourning.
This may be a selfish request, but
until then, please let me stay here.
You've done a lot for us, and this
house has many extra rooms.
You're welcome to stay as long as you like.
Thank you.
That Madame doesn't
look like she's sad at all.
Why would she be? She
married him for his money.
And I hear that her sister's a
whore, and people are always
talking negatively about her.
But they're from such a good family...
Wasn't their house a tea ceremony
house that was about to go bankrupt?
That's right. They finished rebuilding their
house, so they didn't need him anymore.
That's quite possible.
I think the younger sister is suspicious.
She's known as a trouble-making whore.
Everyone!
Seems like you're all discussing
amongst yourselves, but...
Could you please repeat what
you just said, to my face?
I didn't do it!
Well, even if I did, the doctor
said there's nothing suspicious
about the cause of his death.
You have no right to be
saying anything about it!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Kayuki!
Huh?
The bathroom...
Oh, sure.
That's Dr. Horibe,
Master's private physician.
Did Madame murder Master
like the mourners were saying?
She couldn't have!
Ayamoto!? Why are you here?
Madame.
I...
I can't hold myself anymore!
What are you doing!?
I... I'll scream and call someone!
Besides us, only Karen and
Kayuki are in this house.
Your voice isn't going reach their rooms.
Stop!
How could you do something so ungrateful
on the night of my husband's funeral!?
As Master's...
As Master's last apprentice, I
want to become a great artist!
And I absolutely need your
help in order to become one!
No!
I saw you hand money over to Dr. Horibe.
I won't tell anyone...
As long as you listen to me...
You can moan if you'd like...
Like when you were doing it with master...
It's like a dream come true,
that I get to do this to you.
So this is how you taste...
It's so warm.
I didn't know it was so warm inside.
I thought you didn't want
to, but you're so wet.
I bet I could fit more fingers in.
No! Don't!!
Does it feel good?
It feels good...
This isn't what I wanted to do to you...
It hurts!!
I'm not going to break it.
I don't like seeing blood, either.
Do it faster!
Faster!
Madame, I want you to suck the rest out.
Oh, you love it...
Lick it.
How does it compare to Master's?
I wonder which you prefer more?
I knew you were watching
my husband and me...
Huh?
It was a turn on, being watched...
Now, the one who was
watching is raping me...
More... Make it hurt more!!
More... Fuck me more!!
Fuck you more?
You may be my late master's
wife, but you need to ask politely!
Or else I'm not going to oblige!
I understand... More...
Please, do me more!
You should have just
said so in the first place.
Tonight is bamboo shoot
rice? I'm looking forward to it.
Ayamoto, you've been
in a good mood lately.
Huh?
Not really, but it's been all right.
Really...
This one's good. It's dense and heavy.
You haven't been drawing lately, though...
Huh?
I'm in a rut right now.
Are you really?
It hasn't been long since Master
passed away. What do you expect?
But...
But I think Master would like to see you
become a great artist as soon as possible!
I know that!
You're an outsider when it
comes to art, so leave me alone!
I'm sorry for intruding.
I feel like I'm going numb!
My insides are going to melt!
This isn't satisfying enough
for you, is it Madame?
N-no!
Then...
You're such a perverted woman.
You already have two fat ones in you,
and you just peed all over the place.
I...
More...