Miyu!
Miyuu!
"Wonder"-magazine (Lemon People) series:
Kittens of the restaurant
Welcome
How can I serve you
Wait a bit...
Whiskey, beer and fried noodles, please
I'll get them in a minute...
Anything interesting happening around here?
What do you mean by interesting?
Things like this!
If you could get that from
here it would be nice
You know what I mean
That was just a joke...
I have to go to the bathroom now
Hope, you don't mind
It's nothing, just go
Okay
Let's do this
Whaat!!!
Awesome!
This can't be real!
What the heck?
Where am I?
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
I'm the madam of this brothel
You don't look like a madam!
More like the girl of the brothel...
What would you like?
This girl is the number one
You kidding?
She's just fluttering there
Wait a bit...
Don't be so picky
They're all equally good
You know
What is this!
Not something I would want...
You can't mean that...
Little girls like this are your thing?
It's not like that, but...
Hey, lady
I'm for sale too!
Miyu!
I'll take this for sure!
Then she will yours today
Waiii!
You took Miyu?
When sun goes down there will be rumbling!
Anyway, let´s go up
Heh, okay
Wow!
What is this place?
This is not all that there is
I can change everything into more beautiful forms
See for yourself!
Isn't it nice?
Ofcourse you can have a bath here too
This way!
Okay, let's do it my way
Be a good girl
You should try to study
I hate... studying!
You're a mess, you must be drinking
so much that it makes you try things like this
Isn't it so!?
What the hell!
It's not drinking!
You know, I just need...
My medicine, it's nothing else!
Eeek!
Nooo!
Stop! Stop it!
Take this!
You should stop, you meanie...
You're too rough!
I don't like this!
No, I'm not!
Nonsense
Try it and you will pay for it!
Well....
This time I'll be gentle...
So bright...
Not yet!
It hurts!
Badly translated from Japanese by:
PeTA
But it won't end yet!
Now for the music video, Miyu just plays on the beach, enjoy it!
Aki-chan is more cute IMO, but Miyu is fine too
Guess what flag that is?
That's it, now is the time for the commercials
Lolita Anime I - "Beauty of the red snow"
Also on the same cassette, "Hardships of the Rose Girl"
Lolita Anime II - "Diary of what I'd die for!"
Also on the same cassette, "Sacrificial Altar"