Rati...
Sister Carrera.
Oh no...
Rati, sweetie.
Sister Carrera.
No, Sister Carrera...
I will come soon!
It's okay, come Rati.
Sister Carrera!
Sister Carrera, I'm coming!
VIPER - GTS -
Summons The Devil
Hi Alphina!
Carrera? You are late today.
I was playing with Rati.
Hasn't Mercedes come back yet?
No not yet.
Since she was summoned before me,
she should come back pretty soon.
Is that today's soul?
It's so small.
Yeah, the color is not good,
and it doesn't shine well.
These days the quality of
human souls is getting worse.
Really?
The souls you find are very rare.
Is that so?
I'm not interested in crystals.
What a waste.
Some rare crystals
can even create a life.
Don't tell that to anybody,
especially Mercedes.
Mercedes?
Why?
She is a serious one.
While she can't get good crystals...
...you always get rare crystals.
And you are not so serious about it.
Of course she gets jealous.
Since you guys are same age,
she's often compared to you.
I just want to do whatever I like.
I don't like the idea
that Mercedes dislikes me.
How long are you going
to keep me waiting?
Just a moment, it won't take long.
It's not a moment.
I've been waiting for 2 hours, Mercedes.
Oh, is that so?
This is not even funny, damn it!
It's done.
Here you go!
What the hell are you doing?
So sorry.
Let me clean up.
Well.
W-What?
I'm terribly sorry.
You must be starving.
I will make something again.
No, that's okay, I'm not hungry anymore.
Oh, really?
Why do I always make mistakes?
But I can do it.
I'm gonna beat Carrera some day.
Okay, I'll clean the bathroom now.
Huh?
Now what?
So sorry, I'll fix it right away.
Um...
I am so sorry.
Get...
Get?
Get the fuck out of here!
Welcome back, Mercedes.
I'm back.
Mercedes, how did it go?
Where's today's soul?
Mercedes?
Well...
You won't get it.
You will never understand my feelings!
Alphina, did I say anything wrong to her?
I don't know.
It's done.
This will summon the devil.
Then, with the devil's power, I
will kill everyone who put me down.
Stupid human beings!
Let the devils kill all of you.
I'm summoned.
Is it a summons?
Yes.
Be careful.
Well, I don't have to
tell you that, do I?
Thanks anyway.
Well, I'm off.
Here I go.
L-Is a devil coming?
Is this...
Is this a devil?
My name is Carrera.
I answer your summons
and come from hell.
Y-You are a devil?
That's right.
What is your desire?
If you sign our contract, I
will make your desire come true.
Are you sure? Anything?
To be rich, to be famous, or to
get revenge, anything you desire.
Anything I desire...
Anything...
Then...
Are you okay?
Well, I am fine.
Just give me a second.
Hmm, what's my desire?
Money?
Or perhaps I should ask for gold...
I don't really want
to be rich and famous.
What about girls?
Wait a minute, this devil...
Did you make up your mind?
You said anything would come true?
Yes.
Seriously?
Anything, right?
Well, I can ask for anything, right?
What?
Well, what if I said I
wanted to do it with you?
What do you want to do with me?
Um, what should I say?
You know, it's an "activity"
between men and women.
Oh, I got it.
If it's not okay, I will
think of other stuff.
It's okay with me.
I love your desire!
Are you in, Mercedes?
What do you want?
You said the wrong thing
back there, Mercedes.
I know, but...
Carrera is worried about you.
She's afraid that she
makes you feel down.
I know what you feel, but
Carrera also cares about you.
You should understand that.
Can I touch you?
Okay.
Wow! I-It's so soft.
Really?
Let me touch you, too.
Yes.
You have a really big dick.
I don't know if I can
hold this in my mouth.
If you do that...
What is this sensation?
It's hard, yet so gentle, a hot
tongue is slowly enveloping my dick.
Just like being caught in a
spider's web, escape is impossible.
I get sucked into it.
Her tongue tries to suck
everything inside my body.
Nobody, not even a professional,
has used her tongue like this.
This must be the tongue from hell!
That's a lot of come.
Sorry.
No need to be sorry.
We still have plenty of time.
See, you're getting hard again.
Hey...
I want you to make me feel good too.
Oh, that's it...
That feels good.
You're already so wet.
You wanna put it in?
I do!
Okay, go ahead.
Put your big dick into my pussy here.
Yes.
What is this sensation?
This pussy is all over my dick, as if
the pussy itself is a living creature.
Just like the Bermuda Triangle
that swallows the luxury liner.
The pussy tries to suck
everything inside my body.
This must be the pussy from hell!
This feels so good.
You are doing great.
I'm going to come!
Give it to me.
Come inside.
Come in the deepest part of me.
I'm coming!
Hey.
What?
You can do it again, can't you?
You came only twice.
We are gonna have real fun now.
I-Is that so?
If you say you're satisfied, I have to
take your soul according to our contract.
Are you satisfied?
No, not yet.
That's good.
I am not satisfied yet either!
So let's do it again.
Yes, ma'am.
Sister Carrera.
Sister Carrera...
Sister?
Sister Carrera!
Rati, what's going on?
Where is Sister Carrera?
She has been summoned for her duty.
Oh no!
I can't believe she left without me!
Hey, have you used this one before?
No, I haven't...
So let's try.
Really?
Of course.
Sometimes male devils have two
dicks, so I often use my anus.
Two dicks?
What kind of man is that?
Now quick.
Put your thick dick into Carrera's ass.
Well, if you insist...
So huge!
It's coming to my ass.
The big one is inside my ass.
What is this sensation?
Inside is soft but it's so
tight around the root of my dick!
It's just like the queen
of the fruits, Durian.
Once you taste it, you
will never stop eating.
This must be the forbidden fruit!
I'm going to come...
No not yet.
Hold it.
No, I won't let you come just yet!
Oh my!
This time I move.
This is so good.
Big and hard.
Oh no, don't move harder.
You'll make me come.
No not yet.
Don't come yet.
It's impossible.
It's so close.
No, not yet.
Don't come yet.
Don't tighten that much!
Did you come already?
Sorry...
I haven't come yet.
You can do it again, can't you?
Get it hard again quickly!
No that's impossible,
I can't do it anymore.
I won't allow it!
You can't stop it until I am satisfied!
Get hard at any cost!
No way.
H-Help me!
What a beautiful morning!
Well, I guess you are satisfied enough.
According to our contract,
I have to take your soul...
Uh...
Usually I will bring it back...
...but since I can't confirm your will,
I won't take your soul this time.
I had a great time, too, so...
Well, it's okay to make
a mistake sometimes, huh?
I hope my mistake
will cheer up Mercedes.
I'm back.
Sister Carrera!
Don't leave me here again!
Sorry, Rati.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Where is Mercedes?
She's in her room.
She's feeling down because of her work.
Carrera, where's the soul?
What?
Oh, I missed it this time.
This is a very rare case for you.
I'm not perfect. Sometimes
I make mistakes, too.
I see.
It could be good for you to
experience a cell for once.
What?
A Cell?
If you fail to take the soul of
the human who signs the contract...
...you have to stay in
the cell as punishment.
Didn't you know that?
What?
Spread dark wings,
fly out of the darkness.
The contract with the devil.
Do you wish an eternity of peace?
Save your spirits and your mind.
The words of darkness
summon a forbidden desire.
Save your spirits and your heart.
I don't want any fake feelings.
I only want the truth.