VIPER - GTS -
Sex With The Devils
These days, missing souls are becoming
more common in the human world.
Missing souls?
What is causing that?
It's under investigation right now.
We noticed that...
...there're distortions in space
barriers before and after the incidents.
The distortions?
Yes.
After research into the distortions,
we found a very similar case.
What is the similar case?
The gate of Hell.
The gate of Hell?
Which means...
Someone from Hell is taking human
souls from the Rules of Reincarnation.
The Rules of Reincarnation
are the rules of the universe.
How could they break that...
We need to do something immediately.
Punish the devils!
Defendant, Carrera.
Yes.
Despite the fact that you were summoned
and you fulfilled the client's desire...
...however, without any reason,
you refused to take his soul.
Even though you failed
in your duty, you came back.
This violates the three paragraphs of
Article Six of the Constitution of Hell.
And also this demoralizes
our society of Hell.
Carrera, do you have any objections?
No, sir.
Defendant, Carrera is guilty.
I order the defendant to stay
in the cell for five days.
Hi Carrera.
How are you?
Mercedes...
How do I look?
Well, what happened to you?
It's kind of strange to see
an A-student like you in here.
Don't you think?
What do you mean?
Even I make mistakes
sometimes, you know.
What? Mercedes?
Stop it!
Do you really want me to stop this?
Since you have been in the
cell, you haven't done it, right?
Of course not.
So then, I will do it for you.
H-Hey, stop it.
You want me to stop?
Do you, really?
But...
I think your body is more honest.
Oh, stop it.
Oh, really?
I don't know if that's
what you really want.
Your wet pussy is making
quite a noise, isn't it?
I can't help it.
I've been in this place like this.
Your pussy is really wet...
See? Look.
You want me to do it, don't you?
You say no, but look...
...your nipples are already so hard.
Oh stop it.
I'm so sensitive now.
That's why I'm doing it for you.
S-Stop it, Mercedes!
No?
You want me to lick somewhere else?
I see, then let me lick down here.
No, I didn't mean that.
No...
Stop it.
No, don't lick there!
You are such a liar.
How can you make your pussy so wet?
It doesn't feel like you
really want me to stop.
This must feel so good.
You should be honest.
Otherwise, I really will stop this now.
Hmm, no, don't stop.
Give it more.
That's better.
You want me to make you
feel better, don't you?
What do you want me to do?
What do I want you to do?
Something you want me to do to
make you feel good, of course.
If you don't tell me,
I won't know what to do.
I'm not an A-student like you.
I want to feel you in my pussy.
Oh, you want to feel
me inside your pussy.
But I'm a girl, I don't
have the thing you want.
What should I do?
W-With your tail...
Wow, how smart you are!
That's the A-student!
Is that how you usually do it?
I see, so you want my tail.
So you have to say, "Please."
P-Please.
Say "Please stick your
tail into my naughty pussy."
P-Please stick your tail
into my naughty pussy.
Oh, you make me feel great.
Carrera is begging me.
I suppose I have to fulfill
your expectations now.
I'm going to put my
tail into your pussy.
I'll put it in.
It's so big!
How is this? This prong
stimulates your pussy well.
My tail is sensitive.
This makes me feel good too.
This is great.
I'm doing the A-student.
Your pussy feels so good.
A very tight pussy.
Please, give it to me harder.
Harder...
Give it to me!
Oh I'm loving this...
I'm coming.
Go ahead, come.
You're a pervert who is coming from being
naughty with your friend in the cell.
Oh no, I'm coming.
I'm coming too!
This makes me feel empty.
Carrera, my dear...
I wish I could see her again.
Oh that was good.
See ya.
Wait, Mercedes. Are you
gonna leave me like this?
What's the matter with it? You're
going to be released soon anyway.
Bye.
Hey, Mercedes!
Good morning, Alphina.
Good morning, Mercedes.
Did anything good happen to you?
Well, yeah, kinda.
Where is Rati?
She's summoned and
she's in the human world.
She should be back soon.
I'm back now!
Please refine this, Alphina.
This is a good soul.
It shines tenderly.
Yes, he was a very kind person.
I can make a good crystal out of this.
Please take care of it.
By the way, Sister Mercedes.
W-What is it, Rati?
Didn't you go to see
Sister Carrera this morning?
How was Sister Carrera?
Well, she looked fine to me.
I see.
But she must be Ionely
alone in the cell.
Let me go and see her and cheer her up.
Excuse me.
So your good thing that happened
this morning was visiting Carrera?
Um, well...
Hear that? I'm summoned for my duty now.
See you, Alphina.
Okay, good luck.
Yes, it worked!
At last...
You've come!
My dear Carrera!
Thank you for calling!
I do anything from bathroom
cleaning to conquering the world...
I'm everybody's idol...
Mercedes!
I want to know your desire.
What?
He looks so depressed.
What is happening?
It's not you...
What do you mean?
You summoned me.
It's not you I wanted to summon!
What the hell did you just say?
What is wrong with me?
Carrera was so nice and kind to me...
Carrera?
My dear Carrera!
Her green hair shines...
She smiles like a goddess...
Her motherly love holds me tenderly...
I want to see her once more.
So he is the one Carrera
couldn't take the soul from?
Wow, today is my lucky day.
If I take the soul Carrera couldn't,
that means I am better than her!
Okay, I'm going to get
his soul at any cost.
Wait!
If I can't see her,
my life is worthless.
Let me die.
Wait a second, what am I supposed
to do if you kill yourself?
Anyway, don't you want to make a
good memory with me, before you die?
Memory?
Yeah, I can do whatever
you want me to do.
Anything?
Yes, anything.
Sister...
...Carrera?
Sister Carrera!
What happened to you?
Something with Mercedes.
Sister Mercedes?
Are you okay?
My dear sister...
No, don't touch me, Rati.
I just came a while ago, and
my body is still sensitive.
My dear sister.
No, stop it...
Rati, I'm telling you to stop.
Sister, you are so pretty.
Rati, this isn't fair.
You are taking advantage
because I can't move.
Sister Carrera, you
haven't been fair with me.
You always take advantage of me.
Even today, while I was working,
you had fun with Sister Mercedes.
So today I take advantage of you.
Rati, you have to pay for this later.
Yes, but you are all mine now.
Please enjoy the pleasure
of being played by me.
R-Rati.
Sister Carrera...
My pussy is...
My pussy is getting wet too.
Yeah, you're right.
Your pussy is so wet.
You must be so excited to play with me.
Um...
A-Are you free now?
Yeah, looks like it.
So Rati...
Ye-Yes, Sister Carrera.
Let's continue playing
since you are already so wet.
Oh no, Sister Carrera!
Hey...
This is embarrassing.
You said you would do anything.
But if someone sees
me looking like this...
That's funny. You devils feel
embarrassed being watched by humans?
Okay then, let's go somewhere private.
Where?
Don't worry, it's close to here.
Please forgive me.
I can't do this anymore.
What are you saying?
You are enjoying this.
What? No way!
But, look.
Your nipples got so hard.
That's because I'm nervous.
Is that so?
I bet your pussy must be wet now.
No, that's not true.
So, let me see it.
I want to see if your pussy
is wet, so open your legs.
You mean here?
Of course.
Can you check when we
go back to your room?
No, it must be checked right
now, otherwise it's meaningless.
But...
You said you would do anything.
Okay...
H-Hey, is that enough?
I can't see it clearly.
Open your pussy by yourself.
Yes.
Well, that is strange.
It's wet, you must be excited, then.
Not only you are a devil, but
you are also a masochist pervert!
Move your hand.
Let's see...
Wow your pussy stick around my finger.
You're naughty!
No, stop it...
Are you satisfied with fingers?
A masochist pervert devil like
you wants a bigger one, right?
If you don't want it, I'll stop now.
I want it.
What do you want?
I want a bigger one.
Where?
Please stick your dick into my pussy.
Okay!
But first, you gotta suck my dick!
It's huge...
Go on, suck my dick.
Y-Yes.
Use your hands too.
Yeah, that's it!
Hey.
Please give it to me.
I can't stand it any longer.
Okay, then hold the
tree with your hands.
Come on, quick.
Give it to me now.
Just a second, I'm giving it to you now.
Don't tease me.
Your big dick is getting inside me.
I have never experienced
such a huge dick before!
It's deep inside my pussy.
Your pussy is a little too tight.
Relax now.
It's getting better.
How about you?
This is great!
A big dick is inside of me!
There...
Please be gentle.
I should put out a show,
we have an audience here.
Oh no, someone is peeping?
If so, are you gonna stop this now?
But...
I don't think so.
It feels too good to stop, doesn't it?
You must get more excited being watched.
Because you are a little
masochist pervert devil.
Oh no.
I'm being watched.
Strangers are peeping at
me doing such a thing...
But why?
I'm so embarrassed,
but this feels so good.
Why does this feel so great?
Watch me!
Please watch me come hard!
I'm going to come!
If you do it harder, I'll come too.
Let's come together!
Come inside me!
Can I really come inside?
Yes, give it to me!
Give all of it!
Okay, I'm going to come...
Yes, give it to me!
I'm back!
Welcome back, Carrera.
How was your first stay in a cell?
It was fun, in a sense.
Don't you think so, Rati?
Y-Yes.
Where's Mercedes?
She's being summoned.
I see.
When she comes home, she
has to pay me back.
Did I fall asleep here?
What are you doing there?
Why are you drawing a magic square?
I'm trying to summon a devil now.
What the hell?
But I'm already here!
Well, you were okay, but...
I was "okay"?
You made me do such things,
how dare you to say that?
You are the worst jerk!
But I wanted to summon Carrera, not you.
C-Carrera?
I don't need this, I'm leaving!
The devil finally showed herself.
Punish the devils!
Hi Mercedes, you are back.
She's gone.
She was in a good mood in this morning.
It's a summons. Are you going to go?
Are you going?
Yes. It will be a good warm-up for me.
Don't forget to bring back the soul.
Of course, I don't want
to go back to the cell.
Yeah, finally!
It's Carrera!
Oh, you.
My dear Carrera!
At last, I finally got to see you again!
I wanted to see you so badly. You
have been on my mind all the time!
Really?
Uh-huh.
You are the first human
being to say that to me.
Thank you.
Then, you can do whatever
you want to do to me today.
What do you want to do?
Of course...
Stop it now, you Devil!
We won't allow you to violate
the Rules of Reincarnation.
We have to punish you
in the name of justice.
What the fuck is going on?
Who are you?
We are the warrior angels.
We protect the rules of the universe.
It can't be true!
C-Carrera!
It's a sadistic dream,
you are drowing in honey.
The whisper of the devil.
Do you wish an eternity of ecstasy?
Save your spirits and your mind.
Covered with an aphrodisiac,
you cross the charmed sea.
Save your spirits and your heart.
You don't need words,
all I want is a heart that never fades.