Tomoka's hurt because of me.
But... My feelings for Wataru-chan...
Tomoka?
Are you making fun of Wataru-chan?
Eh?
Playing around?
To..Tomoka!
Well.. If he's being played around with those huge breasts, Wataru-chan probably won't be able to recover.
Tomoka!
Ah... Sure is scary...
I wonder if Wataru-chan's gonna be abandoned.
Don't say that! I seriously like him, you know?
Uh...
Onee-san, you've finally admitted your feelings.
I really like Wataru-chan, too.
Isn't that good for both of us now?
Tomoka...
Well then, as for Wataru-chan, this means we're rivals with huge breasts.
Eh?
Yoroshiku.
Geez... Tomoka...
I was worried for nothing.
I won't be able to win against those huge breasts.
But I'm not planning losing for elasticity.
Me too, I won't lose for softness, you know?
Let me see.
Geez... Stop it already.
Coming!
Yes? Fusano residence.
Oh, Wataru-kun's father?
Ah... Sorry for calling all of a sudden.
Oh no, no...
Is Wataru-kun causing you trouble?
Everything's all right. He's being a good boy.
So, what are you calling for?
The thing is, I have a favor to ask of you.
Oh...
Yes...
Eh?
Eh?!
Translation: Red
Editing: ics
Milk Junkies 2
What are you saying?!
You must come to Arizona by the end of this month!
You're the one who's getting married.
Why do I also have to live in Arizona?
Living with my family has always been my dream!
Wataru-kun!
Ah, yes!
I'm hanging up.
It's now time for private lesson.
Aren't you done yet?
Hurry up!
That's why I'm telling you, I'm not going to Arizona!
Dad's always willful.
Besides... To be apart with Fumie-san and Tomoka-san...
Tomoka-san, sorry to keep you waining.
Huh?!
Uh... Fumie-san, why are you here?!
Am I not allowed to be here?
UH... no... but that outfit you're wearing...
Even Tomoka-san?
Come on! Good boy!
Tomoka-san? What's wrong with you?
Come, sit here and show your chest.
Okay! We're gonna begin the medical check up.
Medical check up?
Come on! Come on!
Please stop this joke, both of you. There's nothing wrong with me.
Well, let's see about that.
It's gotten this big already.
This is considered a sickness.
Wataru-kun, you're fallen in love with two girls at the same time...
That's why you need a medical treatment.
That's right.
Ah! Hold it!
There!
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...
Oh my, it's gotten this hard already.
You're aroused just by our boobies.
How sensitive.
Did you get aroused by my boobies?
You're wrong... It's aroused by my boobies, right?
Please be serious with us.
Who do you like?
Hey, if you don't decide, we won't give you any tittie fuck anymore, you know?
No...
But I can't choose!
You're so cunning!
We both love you and yet...
You want us to tittie fuck you here, don't you?
If so, you've got to satisfy us!
You're doing it right. Lick it more as if you're rolling it!
Suck it! Suck it more!
I'm about to explode already! Rub it against my dick!
We haven't done anything, yet it's so stiff.
Don't tease me. Wrap around it like you did before!
If so, make us feel good with this.
If you come before us, we won't forgive you.
How is it? Do my breasts feel good?
Mine feel better, don't they?
Your boobs both feel too good, I can't decide!
You can't do that!
You have to tell us while you're about to come!
That's...
If you move more than that, I'll...
I can't hold it any more! If you do it harder, I'll come!
Bear with it!
That wasn't manly of you to come early, you know?
You're mean!
How could both of you do this to me?
That's because you're going to Arizona soon, that made us want to tease you.
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...
Both of you knew?
We got a call from your father.
He wanter us to convince you to go and live there.
That's ... That's horrible!
Shall we let you rest on our laps?
It would be nice if we could stay like this forever, wouldn't it?
Yeah...
Are both of you fine with us being apart?
We're not...
We've been troubled by it, you know?
But, we can't be your replacement mothers.
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...
We only want to love you like man and woman do.
Playing mothers is over.
Because... you'll have a new mother.
Wataru-chan!
Can I do as I want today?
Sure you can...
You both can do as you like too.
Wataru-chan, you don't have to hold back.
We'll do it all together, okay?
Wataru-chan! You're intense!
It's my turn to make you two feel good.
If so, give it to me, too! Give me your hot stuff!
Fumie-san!
Wataru-chan! It feels so good!
Onee-san, you're not being fair...
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...
I can't hold it! I'm going to come!
I've also reached my limit!
Wataru-chan! Wataru-chan!
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...
I'm... I'm...
The three of us! Together...!
Wataru-chan!
Let's come together! Together!
I'm coming!
Are you taking this with you?
Oh, I don't need it.
Is that so? I bet this much won't fit.
In the end, I am going to Arizona just like my father wanted.
Living with my father and my new mother in Arizona...
I'm not that reluctant to agree to it, but...
Wataru-kun, I found it!
This is the English dictionary I used when I was studying in California.
It's going to be useful so take it with you.
Oh, Thanks.
...I was a little bit sad that Fumie-san and Tomoka-san seemed to be happy about me me leaving for Arizona.
Wow... Not bad, Onee-san.
What can I say?
...I was a little bit sad that Fumie-san and Tomoka-san seemed to be happy about me me leaving for Arizona.
Hoi Hoi... Come on! Hurry up!
The festival is already over.
Geez... Don't mind about that! Hurry, hurry!
We finally made it!
With you!
You're leaving soon.
Yeah...
I'm worried about you.
Eh?
That's why I was thinking of wishing upon the star.
Star?
Say, do you still remember this choker?
Ah, I gave it to you.
Yes! You gave this star-shaped choker to me as a lucky charm 7 years ago before you moved out.
Do you still remember what you told me that time?
You said, "If you feel lonely, make a wish to this star...
...it will make your wish come true...
...we will definitely meet again."
I was so happy.
Since that day, I've been making wishes, you know? That I'll see you again.
Then, 7 years later really got to see you again.
Arizona isn't that far.
Tomoka-san...
Tomoka-san... Tomoka-san...
Wataru-kun...
You can put it in between them.
Let's make it feel good for both of us.
Tomoka-san...
Wataru-kun...
You're intense!
You can come if you can't hold it.
I'll come after I let you come first.
That's the spot!
There! Feels good... Feels good!
I want it... I want it, Wataru-chan!
Tomoka-san... Tomoka-san...
We'll see each other again, won't we?
We will...
So, now it's your turn to make a wish upon this star.
That you'll see me again.
Tomoka-san... Tomoka-san...
Tomoka-san!
I want to see you again...
I want to see you again!
Me too!
Tomoka-san!
I'm coming again...
Thanks.
I'm somehow determined now because of you.
Do your best even if you're there, okay?
Yeah, I'll do my best.
"Ore"?
( Wataru has been using "Boku" which means "I" or "me" which is quite formal. This time he's using "Ore" which is informal. That's why Tomoka finds it funny )
It doesn't suit you somehow.
Say, shall we take a picture together?
Eh? At this place?
Come on! Smile!
Boku-chan!
Tomoka-san...
Thanks for your hospitality.
I see.
You're finally gonna leave tomorrow...
At least, it would've been nice if you could stay until the second term.
Well, my father is a stubborn man.
Do your best, okay?
Ah, yes.
Thanks for everything.
Ah, Fusano-sensei...
Sakurai's only gonna be here until today.
Oh, is that so? That's too bad...
Sakurai-kun, you must do your best even if you're there, okay?
Oh, yes.
I made you wait, didn't I?
No...
Tomoka's at home so...
I wanted to say farewell properly to you, so...
Fumie-san...
Shall we begin the class?
Won't anyone see us?
Everything will be fine.
I won't let anyone spoil our last lesson.
Yes... Yes...
Like a baby caressing his mother's body... Gently... Gently...
It's still to early for that.
You have to caress it slowly first.
Women will feel better that way.
Yes... That's the right timing...
It feels good... It feels good!
Whirl it!
There! More! More!
Fumie-san... Fumie-san...!
I feel good especially when you're licking my left tit.
Don't... If you do it that hard...
The milk will... The milk will come out!
I came...
A student and a teacher doing things like this in the class after school... is bad, isn't it?
Not as a student anymore...
Now you're talking arrogantly...
But before our private class is over, you're still my student.
I'll take care of you until you're sa-tis-fied.
It feels so good!
Really? It gradually feels good when my boobies are rubbing your dick!
I'm going to come!
You come now! Let it all out!
Fumie-san... Fumie-san!
You came a lot.
Fumie-san...
Wanna do it one more time?
Fumie-san!
No doubt, you're tits are the best!
You're different than before.
You're becoming more aggressive.
This is the first time I'm experiencing this!
Wataru-chan... Wataru-chan!
If you lick it that hard it'll be torn off!
I want to remember the taste of your titties!
Don't ever forget... my boobies!
I'll never forget... your boobies!
Wataru-chan!
Fumie-san!
Let me come on your boobies for the last time.
Sure...
Fuck my boobs with all your strength!
Thus, this summer, I've tasted the milk of two women.
Wataru-chan...
Eh?
These pictures are the proof.
Though it's a sweet and painful taste...
But it became the best memory for me.
Our deepest apology to the customers that the flight schedule has been delayed.
We would like to ask for your patience and wait for a while.
Both of them didn't come to see me off, after all.
Would you like to have a drink?
Maybe milk?
Tomoka-san?!
Sorry we're late.
Fumie-san!
Both of you came!
Uh... But we're inside of a plane.
Furthermore, those outfits...
We thought you'd be pleased to see us in these outfits.
Eh?
We're also going to Arizona.
Huh?
The truth is, we were invited to your father's wedding ceremony.
Sorry for not telling.
I had no idea.
It's more exciting inside of the plane if we didn't tell you, right?
Exciting? Don't tell me...!
Hey! We can't do this here...!
It's all right, it's all right!
Wanna drink some milk?
Ah! Hold it!
Geez... Wataru-chan...
Come with us for a while!
Doing something like that with these outfits on sure was thrilling, wasn't it?
Tomoka-san...
Fumie-san...
It's all right.
You can toy with our boobies like you usually do here.
The flight to Arizona is long.
Let's have all the fun we want.
You're doing great! Feels so good!
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san!!!
More... More!!!
More! Mess me up more!
Tease me more, too!
We will be taking off in a short while. Please return to your seat.
I still don't know which one of these lined up pictures will become an ornament for me in the future.
But, if ever the time comes for me to choose one of them, I think I'll grow more mature than before.
But now, all I should think of is...
Boobies!
Wah... Isn't this amazing?
Thank you... Thank you! I'm so happy!
Just as I thought, you're not that much different from your father.
Eh?
That's right.
What do you mean?
That your dad and you love boobs!
Fumie-san... Tomoka-san...!