You filthy devils violate the rules of the
universe and disturb the order of the world.
Although your sin is unforgivable...
...our merciful God will forgive you.
We, children of God, will
purify your dirty soul.
Everyone, let us purify this devil.
With our holy water!
W-What?
VIPER - GTS -
The Devil Has Risen to Heaven.
Oh my God!
Carrera is kidnapped!
What should I do?
Oh, I have an idea!
Thank you for summoning me.
I'm Rati from Hell.
Are you also a devil?
Yes!
There must be a lot
of girl devils in hell.
Because this devil and
Carrera are both girls.
Do you know Sister Carrera?
Then, I should treat
you better than others.
Tell me your desire.
My desire?
Let me see...
No, it's not about my desire!
What?
Sister Carrera was kidnapped by angels?
No, it can't be.
This isn't happening!
Listen, I think we should rescue her...
Yes!
I will help Sister Carrera.
There's no time to waste!
She's gone.
But she doesn't look
like a reliable devil...
Let me try again.
I'm Alphina, a messenger from Hell.
What is your reason
to summon me from Hell?
It's a male devil...
Is there any problem with a male devil?
What?
What I mean is...
I want you to help Carrera.
Rescue Carrera?
Sister Carrera, where are you?
Are you guys trying to stop me?
Then, I will send all of you to Hell.
Come on!
I see.
The warrior angels kidnapped
Carrera, and Rati went after them.
Yes.
Then, I have to do something.
Thanks for telling me. Let
me take care of this now.
Wait. Let me help you out.
No.
Why not?
This is a problem between
us devils and the angels.
You are a human being and should
stay away from this matter.
But what about the contract?
Carrera should be taken
care of by the devils.
This is not related to your desire.
It means that the contract will be void.
No way.
Let me request another contract!
My desire is that...
...I want to rescue Carrera by myself!
Are you serious?
Of course!
You want to rescue her by yourself...
Okay, let's make the contract.
What is this?
This can't be true.
Sister?
Sister Carrera!
What are you doing to Sister Carrera!
Stop it!
Silence, you devil.
We are in the middle of the
holy purification ceremony.
Purification?
Yes, you filthy devil.
You will be purified
with our holy water.
With your body, feel the
love from merciful God.
No!
Where am I?
We are in Hell.
Hell?
But Carrera is in Heaven...
There is a fellow devil I want to take.
A fellow devil?
Are you in there, Mercedes?
I'm coming in.
Mercedes?
What do you want, Alphina?
This is an emergency.
Can you give me a hand?
I told you I don't want to do anything!
Carrera was taken by the angels, and
Rati went after them to Heaven alone.
What did you just say?
Is that true?
Yeah.
He saw everything.
You are...
You're that jerk!
Oh, I see you are Mercedes.
Why are you here?
Do you two know each other?
Hmm, sort of...
Besides that, why is a
human being here in Hell?
All of us will go to
Heaven to rescue Carrera.
All of us will go to Heaven together?
That's his desire in the contract.
The contract?
Then, I wanted you to come with us.
I will go with you, of course!
No...
Let me start this.
Your breasts are small but cute.
Do you feel good?
I will make you really good now.
Filthy devils, I will
purify you with myself.
I can't believe you are so wet.
This is ready.
This is ready, too.
Let us begin!
What is going on?
What is it?
What are you gonna do?
You filthy devil, don't worry.
You will be purified now.
Receive the love of God to your body.
No...
It's too big!
Put up with it, it's
going to get better soon.
You will beg for the
love of God in the future.
That will never happen!
Is that so?
Open your eyes.
Look at the dick entering inside you.
That thick one is inside me...
I can't bear this,
this is so embarrassing.
Yes. I'm purifying your
dirty part right now.
Rati.
This feels so good.
This feels amazing...
I'm so excited by just watching.
I can't hold it any longer...
In contrast to what they said, the
angels are nothing but big mouths.
Just hang in there, Rati...
It's about time to start fighting back.
Wait for me, Rati.
Do you feel the love of God?
I will never feel such kind of thing!
Are you sure?
Thou shall not lie.
Your pussy is turning into jelly
and tightening around my dick.
You can't wait for my holy water.
Let me give it to you right now,
make sure to feel the love of God!
Oh poor thing, was it that good for you?
Stop it.
We just started your purification.
We will give you a lot more.
I will purify your mouth next.
So suck my dick.
You filthy devil!
Y-Yes.
Yes...
Yeah, that's it.
You will soon be able to
feel the great love of God.
Finally, we got outside.
It was a long underground gateway.
Hey, Alphina, this place could be...
Heaven.
This place?
To be accurate, this place
is the bottom of heaven...
...what the angels
call "the Dirty Island."
The Dirty Island...
Hey, Alphina.
What is it?
How can we find Carrera
in this vast heaven?
It's easy, we will lure out
the angels who took them.
Everyone, let us finish up here.
We will finish up the purification
of the devil with this God's tool.
You really have a bad taste for that.
What did you just say?
What is this?
These holy angels seem
to be deadly exhausted.
They are all out of holy water.
How could this happen?
I will never get satisfied
by this level of pleasure.
I'm very insulted.
Don't ever fucking underestimate
the power of the devil!
This is getting more enjoyable.
If you want to play with us that much...
...you will get your wish.
Prepare for it!
This indicates...
No, it can't be.
There's no mistake, it's him.
How could he be in heaven?
The white devil, Alphina!
They are here.
White devil, you showed up again!
You can't get away today!
I will get you!
They are coming!
They are coming, Ogawa!
In the darkness, you
separate light and darkness.
You are the hardest iron
and cold fire in chaos.
He disappeared?
Cut though the sky,
sword of the darkness!
This is a trap!
The sword of judgment...
He could cast such a spell...
Ogawa, you are a unique fellow.
I can't move my body.
What was the red light?
How could they forcefully
disarm our armed bodies?
Did you wake up, angel?
Human?
I have a question for you.
Where is the devil you kidnapped?
Where is she?
How do you like the double penetration?
They stimulate both your pussy
and ass. It must feel damn good.
This must be so good.
You even can't speak.
Your other pussy is tightening
around my dick so hard.
Even the cocky devil can't
help being obedient, can she?
Soon I'll make you feel
the ultimate love of God.
Just look forward to it.
You want to know where other devils are?
Asking the kidnapper is the
most efficient way to find out.
That's why you trapped us.
I can tell it's your
way, you white devil.
Are you angry, Ivy?
It was you who made the
first move, wasn't it?
But it's useless to do this...
...because I will never tell you!
We haven't met for long time.
Didn't you miss me?
You are not going to call me by my name?
What do you mean 'a long time'?
You are a fucking liar devil.
'AIphina' isn't your real name, is it?
All you said to me were lies...
Are you mad because...
...I haven't come to see you?
Whatever!
How could this be?
She's come so many times...
We may not find out where Carrera is...
You are wasting your time.
We, angels will never
trade with the devils.
It doesn't matter!
This is not about angels and devils.
I just...
I just want to rescue Carrera!
So please let me know where Carrera is!
You want to rescue the devil that much?
Yes...
I do!
Fine.
I'll tell you where the devil is.
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Oh I see. You really want it, don't you?
Well then...
Let me give it to you.
Why?
I already told you I would tell you.
But aren't you feeling good?
So let's come.
This is great.
Your dick is deep inside my pussy.
My pussy is so hot and wet.
I'm so wet.
Please, make us come together.
Let's come together!
This can't happen!
It looks like you are
the only one left here.
Do you still want to purify me?
Or...
That's gotta hurt.
My dear Carrera!
Carrera, where are you?
Oh, Carrera!
What are you doing here?
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I-I'm okay.
Thanks goodness...
Did you come here to rescue me?
Carrera...
What happened?
Hey!
Wake up, Ogawa!
No! Don't die!
This is how it's supposed to be.
I'm so happy now.
I don't want to spend my life
filled with hatred and boredom.
But now I could live my
life for the best moment.
I learned how great it is
to fall in love with someone.
And I did my best for my love.
I can see the light.
Am I going to reborn?
My next life will be the great one.
I can feel it...
Are you up?
Good morning. Breakfast
will be ready soon.
Why are you in my room?
Because we made the
contract in the park.
That's right...
But I made another contract with Alphina.
That's okay.
I made the contract before he
did, so his contract has no power.
Are you going to take my soul now?
No, I'm not.
Why?
Because if I take your soul,
I can't have sex with you.
Carrera, my dear!
You look like an idiot.
This voice is...
Mercedes!
What are you doing in my closet?
Because your room is so tiny.
What?
I can't believe four people will
be living in such a tiny room.
Four people?
Oh no.
What are you doing?
Good morning!
Good morning?
This is my show of appreciation
for rescuing Sister Carrera and me.
Don't you like this?
I didn't mean it like that.
You are good at it.
Really? That's good.
I have never sucked
such a big one before.
But I will do my best.
But...
I didn't know that Rati
was so good at blowjobs.
I don't know if I'm good or not,
but everybody likes my blowjob.
Let me suck it, too.
Wait...
Not there!
It looks like everybody is having fun.
C-Carrera.
You guys aren't too bad...
...but let me give him a real blow job.
Let's have fun.
We don't have to rush.
Until you get satisfied.
I'll be with you forever.
Oops, I came.
Everyone once dreams
of being stained in red.
The kiss of the devil.
Do you wish an eternity of life?
Save your spirits and your mind.
The words of darkness
summon a forbidden desire.
Save your spirits and your heart.
I don't want any fake feelings.
I only want the truth.