Translated, edited and timed by: feiX
Here... we're doing this one.
Y... yea...
Really?
Theeen... here... try to answer this one.
Are you that interested?
In boobs.
Are you interested in my boobs?
Do you want to touch them?
Ah... I didn't mean...!
How about... if you get a good score, I'll let you touch them.
Hey!
Don't be daydreaming now.
S... sorry!
All right, let's continue.
Since I was very young, I've never experienced tits.
The softness, the warmth, the pleasantness.
It's the 18th summer since my mom's gone to heaven.
I've been reunited with the bigo'titty sisters.
I wanna feel some tits...
Milk Junkies
Volume 1: Sisters Side
Thank you very much!
Ah... dad.
Wataru? You doin well?
How about yourself?
Are you eating properly?
Yea...
So how about it? Aren't you gonna come during your summer vacation?
The place I was sent to for my business trip has got nothing but bigo'titty ladies I can't handle 'em all!
No that's ok...
Ah? I need some of the Fusano Sister's giant titties!
I'm so jealous ahahaha!
While I'm away, I asked them to look after you, so you better not cause any trouble for them!
Geez I'm not a kid anymore... I'm hanging up.
Fusano Fumie
Tomoka
Why did you get in with me?
I don't have any time... it's all right, isn't it?
Geez...
Ah... your boobs are really big.
Stop it! It's embarrassing...
Our chests used to be the same size when we were younger, huh?
Hey... we don't have enough room for tits!
What do you want!
Hey!
Stop!
C'mone... stop it!
It sure is good to take care of them after all!
Stop it, Tomoka!
I'd feel good if I did it like this too, right?
I wonder if I should have Wataru-chan do this to me, too?
Stop playing around!
Onee-san...
Onee-san... you've liked Wataru-chan since a long time ago, right?
That...
He was our next-door neighbor at the time.
When his mother passed away, he was all alone wasn't he?
He didn't have any friends and he was bullied by everyone...
All he did was cry back then, huh?
I just wanted to be there for him.
But you know, it's been about three years...
...he's become stronger and a bit more of an adult hasn't he?
That's true.
I wonder if I should take him?
I'm going next door!
To Wataru-chan's place?
Yup! I'm his tutor after all.
Tomoka...
Don't be teaching him any weird stuff!
He's my student too, you know!
I wonder if that's how you think of him?
Bye!
Geez Tomoka...
Even though I said that I like him...
Hm? Where? Ah... that's right... you got it!
See you can do it if you try!
Yea... when you cheer me on I'm able to do it.
Oh? What a smart kid!
Whoo lucky!
Ah! How nostalgic!
You've kept this photo around.
Ah... yea.
I guess it's my... treasure.
We were so close and used to play a lot together, huh?
Come to think of it, whenever you were bullied at school, you'd never go back to your place....
but always came to ours instead.
So... I wonder who you liked better, me or my sister?
Hey, c'mone... don't be so cold now.
Ah... hu...
Since you like big boobs, you probably like my sister better, huh?
I guess I can't win over sis' big boobs after all.
What a shock.
T... That's not true!
Tomoka's are big and... wonderful too...
Thanks.
Well... since you answered honestly, I wonder if I should give...
Tomoka-san...
Take a look.
What do you think?
T... they're big...
That's all?
Beautiful...
Do you wanna touch them?
Eh? Can I really?
It's all right.
Try moving it.
What do you think of my chest?
Awesome...
They're soft... and warm...
Suck them...
Eh?
You can suck them.
More... Do it harder!
So these are... tits...
You're doing good Wataru-chan.
There... there!
It feels too good!
T... Tomoka-san!
You're already hard.
If you don't let it out, it won't go down, right?
Ah... that's...!
I'll give you a titty fuck.
How is it? Feel good?
It's really good.
I... I'm...!
Feel like cumming? If you're gonna cum, don't hold back.
Tomoka!
It feels good! It feels good! I'm gonna cum!
Go ahead! Cum all you want on my chest!
A lot came out... I'm impressed.
Hey... since we've come this far do you wanna go all the way?
Awesome... Tomoka's pussy... she's flowing like a stream...
I... I want to put it in...
Come then!
I'll... make you into a man.
It's big... it feels good!
Faster... more... play with my breasts!
It... it's so mushy inside... it feels good!
I'm... already...!
Cum! Let's cum together!
Looks like we did it.
Yea...
Wataru-chan... while we were having sex, all you did was suck on my breasts.
Do you like them?
I love 'em.
Geez... there you go again!
Hey... wanna go to the neighborhood festival next week?
Sure.
Now then... I wonder if I should call on somebody.
How about Saitou-kun? Try reading it.
Ok.
Since I slept with Tomoka-san, I haven't been able to look at Fumie-san in the face.
I... I like Tomoka-san but, I like Fumie-san, too.
Feels like if Fumie-san found out that we slept together, the friendship...
...is gonna fall apart.
Wataru-chan...
Fumie-san and Tomoka-san... which one do I really like...
Wataru-kun!
Wanna go home together?
Ah... sorry...
Her tits are softer than Tomoka-san's...
Hey... Wataru-kun!
Did something happen? You're been acting strange lately.
Nah... nothing really...
Cause you haven't been looking well. I'm...
Ah... rain...
C'mone... we're running!
Aah! It's really coming down!
If we don't hurry up and change we'll catch colds.
Look at you... you got so soaked.
If something's worrying you tell me, all right?
It feels like I've got your mother's aura, right?
You'll be able to take a shower soon.
Actually I...
H... hey! What's wrong Wataru-chan?!
Idiot! Stop joking around!
You shouldn't do that! Stop!
I said you shouldn't do that!
Stop it!
Wataru-kun! I don't know what's been going on, but you shouldn't do that to a girl!
Hurry up and take a shower and get changed.
Wataru-kun!
Fumie-san...
Geez... do you do this with everybody?
It's only cause it's you.
Wataru-chan...
It's all right just for a little bit, right?
T... that...!
Stop!
(falls back in his seat... "Whoa!")
We can't go on any further! Stop!
I... I can't hold it in anymore!
It feels good if I do this, right?
You don't have to... hold back either...
T... that...
You're really sensitive, huh?
You're pretty sensitive.
You like Wataru-chan, don't you?
I wonder if I should take him...
Wataru-chan...
Wataru-chan... Wataru-chan!
Your tits are really soft.
If you play with my breasts like that... I'll...
It stopped!
Looks like the festival will still be on!
I wonder if he'll be happy.
Like this?
That feels good!
Crazy... Tomoka-san's tits are soft and wrapped around me.
Can I move?
Sure.
Awesome!
Do my breasts feel good?
They feel really good!
Do you feel good, too?
Ah... I'm getting there...
Are you gonna cum?
Yea...!
Let it out! Cum all over my breasts!
I'm... cumming!
Wataru-chan's sperm... there's so much of it.
This time... it's your turn.
Ah... it... feels good there!
Hey... let's do it together...
Take your time just like that...
There!
Fumie-san!
No... don't be so rough!
It's... really tight inside!
Don't say that... it's embarrassing!
If you keep going... I'm going to go crazy!
Are you going to cum?
Yea...
Get on top... it's all right to cum.
More... Do it harder!
Fumie-san! Fumie-san!
I... I can't hold...
Let's cum together!
Cum inside me! Give ma all you've got!
Wataru-chan...
I was scared...
I... thought Tomoka was going to take you away...
I always felt a little uneasy.
But since we've become one like this... I...
Evening...
Let's keep this a secret from Tomoka.
Can we do it tomorrow, too?
We can't do this everyday.
Let's do it one more time then...
T... Tomoka!
Onee-san...
Translated, edited and timed by: feiX