No, please don't.
No, it hurts!
Once you cross the bridge,
you'll find yourself in a town...
forgotten by society.
In the rotten rain, cheetahs are fighting
for their territory...
hunting to satisfy their lust.
Surrounded by the river,
spilling with the virgin blood...
the town exists in a dream state
somewhere between day and night.
The Harvest Night
Episode 1: Rose and Poppy
It's a good place.
Please don't. What if someone sees us?
No one cares about the others.
Who are you guys?
No.
I told him I didn't want to,
but he forced me to come here.
What are you saying?
It was you who brought me here.
After messing with our sister,
what nerve you've got to talk like that...
old geezer!
Stop it!
That old man, he won't be able
to go home now.
He didn't have any money on him,
but with those credit cards...
we've got enough to last us for a while.
He won't report this to the police
after being caught with his pants down.
Hey, Masato...
I've heard Shinji's been stealing
some of our takings.
Where's Honoka?
Your sis?
- She's probably at her regular hangout.
- Is she?
I'm really bored.
Hey, Masato!
I hear you've been making
a lot of money recently.
Why don't you share some with us?
We've got no obligations to you.
Who taught you to talk like that, Emi?
You have no idea, have you?
Shut up, Wakaba!
You don't mean to resort
to brute force, do you?
Shut up!
Can't you give me a better price?
It wasn't easy to get them, you know.
Shinji, I can't change the going rate.
If you don't like what I offer,
go somewhere else.
Shinji. Hurry up, otherwise...
Masato will get mad.
Cut it out, Lisa.
All right, how about this. Look.
You were hiding that?
If Masato finds out, dude.
What about Masato?
Don't be such a scaredy cat.
If you're including that watch,
what about this?
That's not enough.
If you're scared of Masato,
I've got something you might like.
You know what? I don't want it.
Never lost a street fight, anyway.
It's not like I'm sad.
It's not like I want to cry.
It's just that I don't want to be
reminded of that time.
I just want to fall asleep quietly.
At that time all around here,
there were loads of dandelions.
When there was a breeze...
silvery cotton balls danced
across the sky.
In the middle of them stood that girl.
It was all a dream.
Just a dream.
That girl died at that point in time.
Now, everything. I loathe everything.
It's not like I'm sad.
It's not like I want to cry.
That shopkeeper's
taking advantage of me.
It's your fault, Shinji.
Stealing from Masato.
Your ass is so grass.
What's that girl doing here?
What are you looking for?
We'll be happy to help you out.
No, thanks. It's quite all right.
What are you doing?
You should accept kindness from strangers.
Shinji. Will you stop beating
about the bush?
Hurry up and just take her.
That's right.
We're all going to rape you.
Please don't.
We've found a nice gift
to bring back to Masato.
What? Masato?
Did you say Masato just now?
That's right.
Hey you, don't say
our leader's name so carelessly.
Honoka.
Honoka?
Is that you, Honoka?
What're you doing here, Ryoko?
It can't be.
What's the matter? Wakaba?
Look at this.
All of them are beaten up.
What a big mess!
Masato.
Is that you?
Why did you come here?
Shinji! You're late!
- I'm back with some good stuff.
- Can't believe it!
You're always away at a critical time.
You octopus!
Sorry about that, Emi.
Honoka! You okay?
Yeah. Ryoko, I'm glad you're okay.
What about that woman?
What's she going to do?
She's not going to stay with us...
is she?
It's good.
Hey, Masato.
Masato, let's go home with Honoka.
Wait! What are you?
No, don't!
Until they both agree to return,
I'm staying here.
Do as you please. Let's go, Emi.
So, what's that woman...
to you?
A childhood friend.
If that's all, that's fine.
Masato, I can't anymore, no...
I'm coming!
Honoka, will you please try
and persuade him?
I think he'd listen to you,
coming from his own sister.
Ryokyo, why don't you go back without us.
Why are you always so mean?
It's because of what you did.
No.
It's not true.
Sorry. I didn't mean to make you cry.
Honoka, you okay?
Honoka? No!
Dear, what's wrong, Wakaba?
Why are your tits so hard and excited?
Why is it so wet down here?
What a slut you are,
shaking your butt like that.
Looks like you want it really bad.
See?
Now you understand what happens
to those who're against us.
Do you see what I mean?
It's too late.
Does it hurt that much?
Sorry about that, Wakaba.
Poor girl.
Lisa always likes to go all the way.
Why are you so embarrassed, Lisa?
Damn it! What was that?
Hey, don't break her before we do.
I'm bored. Do whatever
you want with her. Who cares.
It must've been painful.
Rest assured, I'm the gentle one.
With your stomach full,
it's quite tight in there.
You can't really enjoy it like that
let me help you relax.
Yeah! It's getting tighter even.
Now, you can have fun.
Wakaba, why don't you let it all out.
Hey, don't be so reserved.
Don't worry, Honoka.
Everything will be just fine.
If you leave this untreated,
your life is at risk.
If you want to get cured,
you'd better leave town right away.
I'll take you to the doctor, right now.
You'll be fine.
Please forgive me, now!
Had enough!
I'm coming!
So, how was it, Wakaba?
You said, you wanted to go back
to the other side of the bridge.
Why don't I let you?
It's not like I'm sad.
It's not like I want to cry.
It's just that I don't want to be
reminded of that time.
I just want to fall asleep quietly.
At that time, all around here,
there were loads of dandelions.
When there was a breeze...
silvery cotton balls
danced across the sky.
In the middle of them stood that girl.
It was all a dream.
Just a dream.
That girl died at that point in time.
No.
It's that girl.
That girl, she's just like me.
What's wrong?
Do you want to leave town already?
Ryoko's well brought up.
We can get a good price for her.
Izumi, your boobs are so soft.
No, I'm not.
Why don't you join us?
The more variations we've got,
the more customers we'll have.
Hello? I got it. I understand.
I'll send her right away. Shima!
You're wanted!
All right!
So, Ryoko, think about it, okay?
Wouldn't that be good?
I bet we'll get along just fine.
Honoka! Where's Honoka?
Honoka. I saw her leaving with Shinji.
They've gone somewhere.
How come?
Isn't Shinji your boyfriend?
So, Honoka.
Wouldn't that be good?
Stop teasing and be my girl.
Bro Masato...
won't be quiet.
So what?
I'm not scared of Masato!
I get what I want, no matter what.
So, what?
Masato.
Wanted to talk about the job.
Shinji! I told you not to
mess with Honoka.
Okay?
Beaten up quite a bit?
That Masato.
I'll beat him up someday.
You know, Shinji.
It seems like Masato cares about...
Ryoko after all.
Emi doesn't say much
about anything.
I bet she doesn't like it.
You know, about the two of them.
See you again, mister.
What's up, Ryoko?
Have you found Honoka?
What's the matter,
cat got your tongue?
Emi! Hey!
How do I look?
Emi.
That man, just now.
What about Masato?
I love him. What about it?
Anyway, did you think about
what we talked about?
You can get six grand
for five photos.
Good old scanty for 15 grand.
Pissing for about 20 grand, I say.
Stop it!
Ryoko, you shouldn't do that sort of thing!
Ryoko, I want you to come with me.
What's happening?
You're so sweaty.
How's it here?
You're so excitable.
Ryoko, you're so cute.
Don't. Honoka, she's watching.
Not yet. I'll make you feel even better.
Stop!
Don't, not there!
You're so wet.
Ryoko, even though you don't
look like it, you're really a slut.
Don't say that.
Masato.
It's not fair.
Masato, please give me...
I'm happy for you, Ryoko,
that your wish has come true.
It hurts!
How daring are you
to work without permission?
You've got some nerve.
No! That's not it! We're...
Stop lying!
Lovers don't wander around this area.
It's true!
Please, believe me!
No!
Shinji...
a dirty girl like her, hurry up.
Just rape her already.
Is that going to be okay?
Without asking Masato?
Why do we have to get permission
from him for a thing like this?
So long as we clean up
after ourselves...
no one will know about it.
That's true.
It's their fault after all,
doing it here without permission.
Let's rape her, then.
No, stop!
No, please, stop it!
No! Don't!
No, please!
Now, Masato.
I'm embarrassed.
It's too late now. Look.
It's a gift from me to you.
No.
No don't look, Masato.
Masato, you're coming!
Really?
Masato!
I'm happy for you.
It's not your first time, then.
Don't!
Despite your innocent look,
you're pretty experienced.
So cute.
Don't!
You like it, don't you, Ryoko?
It's good.
It's good, Masato. It feels good.
You're almost there.
No don't, coming. I'm coming!
You liked it, didn't you?
Honoka, you should've joined us.
Honoka.
Honoka!