No!
- Please don't!
- Shut up!
No!
Don't touch me!
I've got a feeling that Tomoko will die.
No she won't, Moe. Tomoko...
Don't be so rough. It hurts.
It really hurts!
It's horrible.
Rie, we are your protectors.
That's the least the girls can do.
- Please, one person...
- Stop begging!
Don't expect a break from us.
Wasn't it you who volunteered
this to save Moe?
No!
If we take her outside,
we'll be discovered by the enemies.
Civilians are all softies.
Why don't you just get it over with?
Too deep!
That's too deep.
Hurry it up, Sergeant!
Don't hustle me like that, Hosokawa.
Please, don't be so rough.
Moe, don't look.
Sergeant, what if the higher-ups
at the main force find out about this?
Fukushima! Do you want Kiyone
to take the place of Tomoko?
No! I can't take it!
A good tight fit, you've got.
I'm coming!
It's okay. Tomoko's okay.
Don't worry about it, Moe.
Those assholes, taking advantage of...
Next! Go for it, Asano.
Hurry up!
Get down!
Damn, where is he?
Hosokawa, lower your head!
Fuck! This guy must've followed us.
At the end of World War II,
after dividing up the nation...
the countries that defeated Japan
failed to rule the island.
As a result, many independent powers
were established...
fighting amongst each other
and trying to seize control.
They developed a hatred
of one another...
leading the country into
a never-ending spiral of a civil war.
The women, whose families were killed
by the opposing powers...
began their miserable journey.
With the surviving soldiers,
they searched for the main force...
so that they could rejoin it,
but they didn't know where to find it.
Dark Shell: Lust in the Cage
When Paradise is Lost
All quiet from here
to the train station building.
Having these civilians makes it hard.
All right, let's go.
- I'm sorry, but, Moe...
- What, Tomoko?
I'm sorry.
Got to piss? Piss right here and now!
Hey, that's not nice, Hosokawa!
Leave it, Kiyone!
You shouldn't even dare to suggest that!
Hosokawa! Shut up!
It's nature's call. Not much we can do.
Do they know the danger we're in?
No more shots? Maybe he gave up.
Moe...
Kaoruko! Are you up?
As usual, that morning,
Keita came by on the way to school.
As if that event was a long-ago memory,
everyone had gone back to the old routine.
Although Keita was younger
than I was, he always said he'd marry me.
Both my father and my mother
loved the idea.
Well, he was a good man,
I didn't' think it was a bad idea.
Every time there was a battle,
we lost more friends.
Some of us lost family members.
Many of the older students
volunteered to fight in the war.
Get down! All of you!
Hold your fire!
Who knows when we can
find them the next time.
Just carry as much food as possible.
Rie, have you seen Kiyone around?
You want to know about Kiyone?
It's all about nature's call.
No, don't come in. Please don't.
I get the feeling
your wound a little tight.
Please don't, Hosokawa.
Right now, I'm going...
What fun!
You couldn't wait?
Let me clean it up for you.
Kiyone!
It's you, Fukushima.
You're here to fuck that woman?
Please leave Kiyone alone, Hosokawa.
Fukushima...
Don't you dare order me around!
Unlike you, I've lived through real battles.
What's going on!
Just a second, Yuka.
You're not going to intervene, are you?
No! Help me, Fukushima!
Kiyone!
It's okay. It's okay.
Soldiers...
Stop it, Kuroda.
We need some outlets.
Don't make me tell you that again.
Kiyone, will she die?
Never. No one will be killed.
Help me, Fukushima.
Don't be so uptight!
We can still have fun together!
Why don't you fuck that girl!
Let's go.
Fukushima!
You're lucky.
What a nice boyfriend you've got.
Stop it! I hate you! I hate you!
Is Kiyone...
Yuka!
Rie...
No! Stop it, someone!
Don't listen, Moe.
Don't watch! Not like this!
You smell a little ripe.
When did you take a bath last?
Stop it! You're gross!
Stop it! It's dirty.
No, it's embarrassing!
I'll teach you what it tastes like.
Tell me. Do you like the way
that you taste?
Stop!
No, don't take it off!
You pervert! I'll tell
everyone what you've done!
You know, I like obedient women.
Now, shut up!
What have we here?
Hello girls.
Your nipples are getting hard.
Let's give them a little lick.
Not there!
You're gushing.
Are you doing it with Fukushima everyday?
Don't touch me. Please let me go.
We're comrades. Don't hate me so much.
I'll make you forget
that weakling, right now.
Fukushima, help me!
It's so big, please!
No, don't move.
No, not there!
How does it feel
compared to Fukushima?
It's good!
You're big!
It's making me wild.
Fukushima, I don't want to feel it!
Help me!
How's that? Much better than him, right?
Yeah! Take it, take it all!
It's like doing it with a virgin.
More!
I can't bear it, it's so hot!
It's so great, I'm melting!
Getting hot enough for you?
It's so hot!
More.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Faster!
Sounds like Hosokawa had a lot of fun.
I bet that softy, Fukushima,
knows what it's like to be in a battle.
Let's go, Moe.
Hey, where you going?
There might be enemies around.
You can't just leave.
Kiyone.
I'm sorry, Moe.
I really didn't want you to see
the horrible look on Kiyone's face.
Are you telling me we'll all die?
No, that's not true.
We'll survive and join our friends, okay?
Please wait, Kiyone.
I can't turn against a veteran soldier.
Please understand.
Shut up!
Kiyone!
Kaoruko, will you help me over here?
That's my mom,
getting the laundry done...
in the bright sunshine
of an early summer's day.
The gentle breeze stirred the firm
petals of the rhododendrons.
Although everyday seemed to pass...
as if things remained the same,
our lives changed slowly and surely.
One day, Keita said to me...
"I'm going to join the army,
and I'll protect you, Kaoruko!"
I laughed and said, "How could you?
You're younger than I am."
"But all the adolescent boys
dreamed of being soldiers."
Having fun?
Kuroda, it's good, it's really good.
You're the best!
A lot deeper. Make me feel wild.
So, you lost both your mother
and father during that attack?
Yes. And Moe was raped.
Since then, her memory is messed up.
I don't want her to experience that again.
My job, from now on, is to protect her.
That's why you stepped forward.
To protect Moe.
Yuka, it's okay. You can cry.
Good. It's deep.
You're making me feel wild, good!
You're good too, Aki.
It's so good!
Kiyone!
Yuka, both your child and husband.
When the town was attacked,
we got separated. I tried to find them.
But I believe they escaped
and are with the main force.
Is it true?
Can we really join them?
The way it is,
we'll all either be killed or violated.
When push comes to shove,
let's escape alone without them.
Kuroda...
I can't take it anymore!
- It's tight!
- So hot I'm melting!
Come in deeper!
Kiyone!
Hey, you! Everything's quiet, right?
- All right then, it's my shift.
- Yes.
Kiyone's gone.
No need to keep it to yourself.
I just remembered.
Fukushima? Are you okay?
I was worried about you.
Rie...
You, bitch!
It was your fault that Kiyone was...
Stop it, Fukushima!
Please don't! Calm down.
Fukushima's been out there,
standing guard.
He's stressed out, don't interfere.
Moe!
All right, go for it, Fukushima.
Kuroda.
- No, I'm sorry. Forgive me.
- Kiyone's gone.
No, don't.
A pathetic man and a timid woman.
What a perfect match.
There was nothing we could do,
and I was scared.
Make no mistake about it.
Someone came by.
Crap! He's still following us.
I won't let him escape this time.
Let's split and search around
the school building. Don't lower your guard.
No, don't! Please don't!
Fukushima, please!
That's right. You won't survive
if you can't forget the dead.
Don't! Stop, please!
Fukushima! Fukushima!
Stop your whining!
If you don't lead me out of here...
- It hurts! You'll tear it off! It hurts!
- You're selfish, Fukushima!
Want to give up Moe instead?
Unless he goes all the way,
he won't calm down.
See, look at his rage.
It was my fault. I apologize!
Kiyone won't return.
- I want to go home! Mommy...
- Shut up!
Fukushima's finally becoming a man.
Put it in your mouth.
It's coming. Drink it!
You bitch! I told you to drink it.
I thought Fukushima
was the submissive kind. Guess not.
I'm sorry. I'll drink it next time.
I'm sorry. Moe...
No, don't come near me.
Yuka, help me. Help me!
No please don't, I don't want it.
What're you saying? I just got started.
Isn't it enough, Kuroda?
Fukushima says he just got started.
No, don't take it off, please!
- It's embarrassing, no!
- Shut up!
A loud woman.
Disgusting. Not at all like Kiyone.
No, I'm scared!
It hurts, please pull it out!
No, don't, it hurts!
Stop acting as if you're in pain,
instead, why don't you enjoy it?
Please pull it out!
Stop, please, stop!
Please, it hurts, please, don't!
No, not like this, no!
Fukushima, I love you!
I'm hot, it's good.
Fukushima!
Fukushima, push more, my body...
Disgusting, it's responding shamelessly.
Feels good.
I can't stand it! I can't stand it!
I'm coming!
They get me excited.
Why don't we have some fun, too?
- Let's go, Fukushima.
- Yes, sir.
We're all going to die, aren't we?
That's not true. If we're together,
I'll protect you. I will.
We must escape, get away from them.
- What's up?
- See there.
Hosokawa?
Keita and I visited a beach together.
It was our last trip before Keita
joined the army.
We did it because once
he became a soldier...
we wouldn't be able to
see each other very often.
I was surprised to see
his muscular body.
He was so gorgeous that it was hard
to keep my face straight.
An empty beach in the early summer.
When he held me tenderly
I felt like telling him to do...
what his heart desired,
but all he did was to kiss me gently.
Wait! Rie's...
Don't give up!
Before they catch up with us,
let's join the main force.
The main force, are we really
on the right path?
Rie, we've come this far.
We're almost there.
You don't want them to violate you
anymore, do you?
No.
What happened? Killed again?
Got killed on her own. It's not our fault.
Be quiet, Fukushima.
That's what happens
when you walk around without us.
Rie, she's dead.
In the next episode
In a dream, I was at a beach with Keita.
There was a cute little girl
who ran right in front of us.
"Hey, Keita," I said.
"Wouldn't it be nice
if we could have a girl like her?"
Let's see. Our girl's name
would be, how about Moe?
Recovering my consciousness
in the cold rubble...
I aim at the next target.
Dark Shell: Lust in the Cage.
Episode 2: Skin That Cries.
Dark Shell: Lust in the Cage
Episode 2: Skin that Cries