Honoka!
Come on! Honoka!
Hey there, Masato!
Treat the patient gently, will you?
Aren't you the doctor?
Can't you do something?
Masato.
Let's go.
Honoka.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I'm fine.
Honoka.
She wants to go home.
Why don't you take her back home?
We've got no home to go back to.
Masato.
The Harvest Night
Episode 2: Ashes in the Urn
It's not like I'm sad.
It's not like I want to cry.
It's just that I don't want to be
reminded of that time.
I just want to fall asleep quietly.
At that time around here.
Absolutely helpless.
I can't even protect my only sister.
Around here, there were
so many dandelions.
When there was a breeze...
It was...
It's you, Emi.
Hey, Masato.
Silvery cotton balls
danced across the sky.
Your mind's totally with Honoka.
Can't you look at me sometimes?
I'm cute too.
In the middle of them stood that girl.
It was all a dream. Just a dream.
Master, isn't this girl good?
Set a good price, will you? Please?
Unfortunately, she's already
experienced, I believe.
Too bad. I was sure
Ryoko was a virgin.
Let's see.
Some sort of used underwear
and urine like everyone else.
Girls with spectacles
are popular right now...
so if she appears in a video...
No. I don't want to.
- Because Ryoko, you're so cute.
- You'll sell a lot.
Very well, please sign here.
But...
No, don't!
Ryoko, you're not doing that.
I'm telling you.
Honoka.
Hey brat, will you stop interfering?
This is mine.
Hey, Honoka!
What about mine?
Masato prohibited me
from using yours.
It's not my fault even if Masato gets upset.
No, don't! Honoka!
Be quiet, Ryoko.
Honoka!
Come on, Honoka!
Honoka shocked me.
Can't believe it.
Even Masato's no match for that.
Stop talking about Masato when we're at it.
It's because you can't do anything, Shinji.
I'm the one who's got to work.
Stop pinching my tits so hard!
Don't get mad, Lisa.
I'll make sure to comfort you nicely.
But, you know...
Masato's acting weird of late.
Forget that.
Just continue, will you?
Can't you wait a bit?
What an appetite, Lisa.
Even your asshole's wet.
Come on in.
Just as usual, yours is really tight.
Shinji, hold me tight. I'm scared.
I'm really scared!
You mean, Masato?
No, of this town.
Lisa.
I'm sorry.
Don't need to apologize.
Shinji. Shinji!
It's good.
Shinji, it's good, really good.
Shinji, I can't. I can't, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Hey, Masato.
Of late, you're not involved
enough, don't yeah think?
Don't feel like it.
You mean, we're not going to take
that job tonight?
What?
That's going to work out
to be a real problem.
Haven't you heard,
the other gangs are getting a lot bigger.
Without Masato, it's uncomfortable.
It really is.
Unless we make our presence known,
they'll take advantage.
So, will you please, Masato,
will you come with us?
No, thank you, very much.
We can't count on you anymore.
Ryoko.
Don't tell my brother about that, okay?
I wouldn't really want him to know.
Yes, of course, I understand.
If I did, who knows
what will become of Lisa.
Honoka, please don't do that again.
Promise me.
Are you worried about me, Ryoko?
Thanks.
You know...
I thought I'd take Masato
and go across that bridge.
Please keep your promise.
Like you said:
I was jealous of you
because you could go near Masato...
without hesitating.
I didn't know how strong
the bond was...
between the two of you.
After all, I didn't know
anything about him.
Why are you crying, Ryoko?
We're already dead, you know?
Let go of me!
Let go of me, damn it, no!
No! Don't, no!
Shinji!
Motherfuckers!
Fuck all you bastards!
Fuck you!
Don't do that!
It hurts!
Stop it!
Without Masato, you guys are nothing.
Thanks for taking care of Wakaba.
No, don't, please!
Shit!
Don't you dare resist me!
Stop, it hurts!
Leave her alone.
Don't you dare touch Lisa!
What a nice pair.
Don't you look away! Here.
Stop it.
Leave her alone!
Take it in, deeper!
More!
More tongue.
All of it!
You're pretty good at it, aren't you?
You bitch!
Do you think it's that easy?
You fucking bitch!
What's that?
No, don't!
- Get away from her!
- Please, don't!
She'll get tighter.
That's fun! Right, guys?
Please, no!
What's wrong?
You're bored with your stupid talk?
Masato...
I know you want me dead.
What are you going to do?
Let's have fun, Lisa.
No, please don't!
No!
Stay away from her!
Just stop it!
You're too loud!
An unruly bitch has got to be
treated like this.
Stop it! You pervert!
They're all out late.
It's okay even if they don't return.
What?
After all, none of us can leave this town.
What do you mean?
It's all your fault, Masato!
Why didn't you come with us?
Will you tell him too, Honoka?
I'm leaving this town with Honoka.
Masato.
I know you're lying.
There's no way you'll leave us
behind and desert us.
You know I mean it.
You can't change my bro's mind.
Lisa's gone.
Agei, Shima and lzumi are dead too.
- Honoka! What's wrong?
- Honoka!
I knew you'd be back.
With this, there'll be no one
out there that can scare you.
I really hope so.
I wonder if Honoka's okay.
Worried?
But of course without Honoka,
you won't be able to leave this place.
That's not...
What are you talking about?
It's kind of too late, you know.
Ryoko...
Please, Emi, let go of me, please.
Don't say that.
Let's have some fun, Ryoko.
Honoka.
Not here.
Let's go, Honoka.
Ryoko!
Be careful.
Who's there?
No, Ryoko!
Emi.
Masato, you're a little late.
What did you do to her?
She seemed so lonely,
we all played with her.
I'm okay, I'm okay...
I'm okay, I really am.
No, no, no, Ryoko, why?
I haven't done anything yet?
Why did you go there alone, Ryoko?
We agreed that you wouldn't.
Tell me, why did you do this?
No need to cry.
I'll let you join her, Honoka.
So she says.
Don't touch Honoka!
Masato!
Don't move.
Here!
Don't think you're the big shot anymore.
But I won't kill you right away.
First, you've got to taste
the pain that Lisa tasted.
Masato, make sure you watch
this real well.
How smooth an inexperienced
girl's skin feels.
Her smallish boobs get me excited.
Let me see what she's like down below.
No, don't!
I bet she can feel a lot.
Her tits are hard and excited now.
She's getting wet down here, too.
I'll bet she's a virgin, too.
Of course!
With Masato protecting her like that.
We'll know as soon as we stick her.
No don't, please don't.
Look, how pretty down there.
There's a big difference
between hers and yours.
- You idiot! Shut up.
- Masato, please help me!
Honoka!
It's no good, Masato.
Will you just lie low?
No this'll make me mad.
Masato!
What a surprise!
She's got it in her pretty good.
It's about time for the real thing.
Did you hear, Masato?
Your precious sister's going to be a woman.
Watch that real well.
What's this?
She's not a virgin?
What a disappointment.
Not a virgin?
Then, Masato, what were you
protecting her for?
She's pretty tight.
Feels good, you know?
It's about time.
Let me try her too.
You perverts.
Just don't worry about anything,
and do her till she breaks apart.
It's enough!
It's too soon to be over.
We're not done yet.
It's not satisfying yet. Right, Lisa?
She's tightened.
Same here.
What the...
- Is she okay?
- How pathetic.
Why are you all scared now?
But she's not acting normal.
She might be dead.
That's fine. Now we don't
have to deal with it later.
Fuck!
I thought we'd have a lot more fun.
We'll throw you down the bridge.
All three of you together.
You must be happy, Ryoko.
Good bye, Masato.
It was fun doing it with you.
What?
Masato.
Hey, wait a sec!
No, Masato.
Don't come near me!
You fucking monster!
You fucking bitch!
Let's go, Honoka.
Let's go home now.
It's not like I'm sad.
It's not like I want to cry.
It's just that I don't want to be
reminded of that time.
I just want to fall asleep quietly.
At that time all around here...
there were loads of dandelions.
When there was a breeze...
silvery cotton balls danced
across the sky.
In the middle of them stood that girl.
It was all...
just a dream.