Where is the hostage?
Good job.
Captain.
Don't say anything.
Nobody cares if a pedophile dies...
I heard that she was the
only child to her mother.
Oh, and she had a puppy.
Looks like C.S. I has arrived.
Linda!
Mary!
Mary's team is on this case, huh?
Take her to the scene.
Yes, sir.
I can't stand this!
Yeah, her mother seemed very upset.
Of course, her only child was murdered
because she wasn't watching her.
It's terrible.
What is this dog?
Oh...
It's the victim's dog.
The pervert used the
dog to trick the girl.
Shoot!
Oh no...
Legend of the Wolf Woman
Part One
The Health Department announced
that...
...fifteen cases of the
dreadful disease were found...
...during the last week.
Vaccination is the most effective
way of preventing rabies.
All dog owners, please be aware.
Now, to the song...
Okay!
Are you ready, Mary?
Not yet, I need a couple more minutes!
Come on, we're just
going out for a drink.
What are you expecting?
It's not that simple for me.
You can say that because
you already have Brian...
...but what about me?
Okay, okay, take your time, Princess...
You always make fun of me like that!
Hey Linda.
Brian!
I saw the news, I'm sorry...
Me, too.
The captain was bummed even
more, he thinks it was his fault.
Tough job, I guess.
But we need you in this town.
Cheer up!
You're right, I've got to move on.
That's the spirit.
My princess...
Master, please give
another drink to Mary.
Kata!
What's up? You're done for tonight?
Yeah, I had an early shift today.
Then why don't you join us?
Sure.
Well, then Linda...
Oh, forget about Linda.
We're going to party
until the sun comes up!
Hey Mary, you're hurting me!
We'll drink until the morning!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Please be more gentle!
What a great view!
Hey!
Ouch!
H-Hey...
Please stop this, I'm serious!
I'll arrest you if you continue...
Brian, do you know what you're doing?
Do it by yourself...
You're already so wet...
You're lying!
I'm not lying...
You're moving your ass on your own.
Because...
Now I'm going to use...
This one!
Hey, it hurts...
Don't lie!
Look how wet you are!
It's going in too deep...
No, you're kidding, right?
Please, no...
Bang!
The egg exploded after
she put it in the microwave.
Okay, okay, now you sit down...
Master, give her a glass of milk.
Sure...
Hm? Where is the milk?
Hey, the condom broke
because you were so rough.
You spilled milk all over the place.
Stop it!
Linda...
Look what you did to my uniform...
You like playing dress-up, huh?
No way!
Don't make it sound like
I'm some kind of pervert.
I just love you in uniform.
You look so cool and tough
in your SWAT uniform...
We're always together...
Master, give me another one!
Mary, you've had enough!
Linda will be worried about you!
Ha, Linda always treats me like a baby...
I bet she is having freaky
sex with Brian right now!
You too, Kata...
Me?
You have such a great
body, I'm so jealous of you.
What happened to you?
Oh, could you check the cut for me?
Sure.
I got bitten by a puppy.
Bitten by a puppy?
Did you go to the hospital?
No...
The doctors around here don't care
about someone like me anyway...
Let me see, I might have something...
Wow! Are they all medicines?
Yeah, I carry this bag with me all the
time, because of my job...
I see...
But it's not normal, right?
Well, maybe a little strange...
Look at the time! I have to take
Linda home, we've got work tomorrow!
Linda...
Mary...
Dad, Mom, everyone...
I feel hot...
Case!
What is it?
Are you sure this is from the
subject who was affected with rabies?
That's right.
It's a sample from the crazy
Chihuahua that bit a baby two days ago.
It became violent suddenly
and attacked the baby.
People had a hard time
separating it from the baby.
They ended up kicking
the dog to death...
...right on the spot...
I see...
So this is definitely from the dog...
What's wrong?
I don't know what to say...
This is not the lyssa virus.
What?
This is the official
sample of the lyssa virus...
It's from our database.
Right.
And this sample is from the poor
Chihuahua, taken right after its death...
They look similar...
Yeah...
Here is the third one.
It keeps changing form rapidly.
Exactly.
The symptoms are similar but the
third one is a totally different virus.
I've never seen a virus like this.
Me, neither...
Lady, is everything all right?
Did you get a cold? You're trembling.
It's hot...
I feel so hot...
Huh?
I don't have any money,
are you okay with that?
Come with me. I know a good spot...
You look damn delicious...
Take it easy, girl.
Come on now, I can't wait...
You're so impatient.
Yes! Yes!
I'm coming!
What is going on?
What the...
I know that you're already
off the clock for today...
...but we have an emergency situation.
I need you to change back
to your uniforms again.
It happened about 3 o'clock yesterday
morning, and there are no witnesses.
The only clue so far is the way the
dogs and their owner were killed...
We will form several teams and
wait for further instructions.
Please stand by.
Dismissed!
Thanks for tonight.
I'll see you tomorrow, then...
What happened to you today, Kata?
Hey, why aren't you saying anything?
Manager, please sleep with me.
Why would I want to sleep
with a slut like you?
Stop it...
I said stop it!
Please, Manager...
I said stop!
Shit, now I'm wet...
Hey, if you really want me
to screw you, do what I say.
I'll let you have as
much fun as you want...
Hello.
Linda?
Me too...
I found something
strange about the sample.
You too?
I'm at the scene where
the incident took place...
Wow! It's so cool!
Cool, a real one!
Would you take a picture with us?
How did you get in here?
You shouldn't be here.
Isn't he dandy or what?
Yeah, totally!
Take pictures!
Would you take a picture with us,
Mister?
Yes!
Take a picture!
What's going on, Linda?
Linda? Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry, so what are you saying?
I said that we probably can't
make it to Tiger Eye tonight...
Oh, you must miss Kata.
That's not true.
Don't treat me like I'm baby.
I'm sure Kata is...
Hello?
Is something wrong?
Linda, I'll call you back!
Klutz.
Man, this is incredible,
the rumors were true.
I've always wanted to try this.
It's so tight.
Please, give me more...
Sure baby. I'll give you more.
It's so tight!
It can't be...
I said, I want you to find Kata.
Calm down first...
I don't get it!
Kata is in serious trouble!
Please Linda!
I need to find Kata anyway, right?
Hurry! She's infected by the virus!
Damn it, what's going on?
Damn it, Kata...
She freaking bit me, that bitch!