Don't move!
Raise your hands and put
them behind your head.
Walk toward me slowly.
Get down on your knees, now!
Legend of the Wolf Woman
Part Two
What?
I'm from the same tribe as Kata.
My name is Mustang.
How do you know that she's safe now?
I can tell because we all are
connected deep inside our souls.
But...
But?
It seems like she's being
haunted by a terrible dream.
And so is this city...
Yahoo!
Don't lose them!
Go check the containers, Frank!
You bastard!
I see one!
Damn it, stay still!
I can't aim...
Where did the other one go?
B-Brian?
It can't be!
No, it can't be!
Are you all right, Linda?
He went down there! Chase
them to the front door!
Kaboom!
What happened?
Oh my God, what is this?
They are human beings...
It looks worse than minced meat...
Yes? Uh, okay...
This is an emergency broadcast...
This video you're watching now has
not been tampered with in any way.
It's unbelievable!
It is not a fake, this
is a live broadcast.
People nearby, please stay
calm and remain inside your homes.
It's hard to believe, but this is real!
Where are they from? Why are they
here?
Colonel! Why did you blow them up?
We almost caught them!
What on earth are you thinking?
Remember those monsters were
originally human beings!
What are you talking about?
All I did was blow up the monsters
because you police are so unreliable.
I don't know what your plan is, but
we'll protect the people of this town.
Leave this matter to us.
No!
These monsters are ours.
I won't give them to you!
Did you find anything?
Yeah, some skin with hair follicles...
...but I'm not sure if it's theirs.
I guess we have to take
the samples back to the lab.
Linda...
Please help me...
Save their souls with
great compassion...
Keep that in your mind, Linda.
Let's go get rid of these
nightmares, shall we?
I thought she was a woman at first.
But it was definitely
a wolf that attacked me.
Or perhaps it just looked like a wolf...
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
I don't know either.
I must've passed out.
I might not have made it if
it weren't for you guys.
What happened?
He was attacked.
Are you all right?
As you can see...
And who is that big one?
Oh, he is a friend of Kata's...
Kata?
She's your friend
who disappeared, right?
Yes. We stopped by here to see
if you had any information...
We've been terribly busy
since these freaks appeared...
Linda, Mary, Captain...
I'll gather the
monsters in Central Park.
What do you mean?
I'll see you later.
Hey, wait a minute...
Case, are you still working?
Yeah, I wanted to hand you the
samples I collected at the scene.
Thank you...
Have you examined them yet?
Yeah, it seems like the
virus created those monsters.
You can't just conclude that without
examining the sample carefully!
Because Kata is also...
I already met her!
Kata is the one who attacked me!
What are you doing?
I found out why they
are attacking people...
No, please stop this!
They're returning to their
primitive roots...
This might be a new
stage in human evolution...
Humans should be true to
their primitive desires...
Like animals!
No!
Mary, are you okay?
The water in the river
constantly changes.
The water constantly changes its
shape, never stays in the same place.
The water is just like people.
Captain!
The monsters are acting strange...
Seems like they're all
heading somewhere.
It's Central Park!
They're all heading for Central Park!
What's the matter?
There has been an accident...
Mary, you were haunted by
a bad dream, weren't you?
A bad dream?
You mean, Mary is going to be like
Kata?
No!
Mary, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
No, please stop it!
No, no, no...
Wake up from the nightmare, Mary.
Oh no, please stop...
Please no!
Please don't do this to me!
You are all right now!
I can finish the treatment with Kata.
Really?
Yes.
Is Kata coming here?
I see...
Okay, we got him cornered.
Go over to the other side!
Catch him!
Hey, hold that side!
Be still!
Help!
Shoot her.
Put this talisman on
your gun, and shoot Kata.
Don't go there, come over here!
What are you doing? Capture him!
Damn!
Captain, we can't capture them, please
give us permission to kill them!
No, don't fire your guns!
What's this sound?
Charge!
Keep firing!
Kata, you don't remember me?
Kata, come down here!
I know somebody who can cure you.
She can't understand me anymore...
If you keep this talisman on
your gun, you can stop Kata.
Don't worry, in her current
state, she won't die from a bullet.
Kata...
Kata!
This is fun!
Let's go!
Colonel!
Stop right now!
Why?
Why would I want to stop?
This is such fun!
Colonel!
This isn't a game, stop this right away!
The fun has just started!
It's so heavy...
Oh, I'm sorry...
Where are we?
It looks like she came
to her senses too.
Kata!
Yeah, keep shooting!
Hey wait, you bastard!
Oh yes, shoot a missile or
two, make it big and loud.
Enough!
Just for you, I'll make it three!
Mary, come here and comfort Kata.
Don't worry, I'll hold her down so...
Number 5, number 7, number 10...
The time has come! Are you ready?
You are doing great...
It's your turn, Mary.
It's too big. I don't think it'll fit.
You are wet enough to take it in.
Who the hell was he talking to?
Number 5, number 7, number 10...
Fire!
Roger, firing number
5, number 7, number 10!
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
Excuse me, could I ask who is
speaking?
Who the hell are you?
We are the SWAT team.
We're trying to capture
the monsters in Central Park.
Central Park?
I'd get the hell out
of there if I were you.
What do you mean?
It's too big. I don't think it'll fit.
I don't think I can take this...
It's too tight!
No! Please don't lick down there!
My missiles are already on the
way. Take them as presents from me.
Don't cause any more trouble!
Order them to self-destruct!
Why?
Who would want to stop
this? It's so much fun!
What are you guys thinking?
Hey, the missiles are coming!
Get out of here!
It's too late!
We're saved...
We came...
So, is everything okay with you now?
Yeah, I feel like I was
having a strange dream...
What do you mean?
I felt like I was making
love with a chubby man...
Oh no, me too...
Captain!
Oh, you are all safe?
Are you all right, Captain?
I guess not...
This is nothing...
Did you see the news yesterday?
I did! Don't you think it's incredible?
So incredible!
I'll take pictures!
I thought we'd die...
Totally.
Hey, they're from the other day...
Excuse me, can we
take pictures with you?
Please, please, please!
Pictures, pictures pictures!
You're such a klutz, getting bit by a dog
the day before going back to Japan.
That dog was so cute!
You are dumb!
It really hurt!
Why don't you show some sympathy?
Stupid!