First Annual Vanilla People's
Choice Award, story by Tarorin
Huh?
Hey! Rio!
Open the door!
Is she taking a nap?
Here you go, honey.
Thanks.
Okay, let's eat.
Hey wait a minute.
Rio isn't here yet.
Oh, I didn't even notice.
You're right.
Can you go get her, Yuuki?
Okay.
Rio! Dinner!
Wake up!
Like Mother Like Daughter 2
Here you go honey, open wide.
Stop that.
Looks like Rio is sleeping.
Oh, were you watching us, Yuuki?
This is really embarrassing.
Looks like Rio came home and took
a nap.
But now she's sleeping like a baby.
That's too bad.
She must be tired.
Just let her rest.
Curry will still taste good
if you heat it up later.
But...
Eat more, okay?
Okay, I'll eat more.
You got some rice on you.
Oh no, it's embarrassing.
Hey, you have some rice on you,
too.
Stop playing with your food!
If you're not going to eat, then...
Thanks for the meal.
I'll eat with Rio when she wakes up.
You can just leave it the way it is.
Rio didn't wake up at all.
Plus...
I don't care. Do whatever you feel
like.
Even if I see him, it's not
like we're going to have any fun.
I wonder where Koichi is.
Looks like Koichi has to do
overtime.
It's too bad for Koichi.
I dished out a lot of money
for this special dinner.
I think I'll eat
Koichi's portion as well.
Here you go honey, open wide.
What's happening?
It just doesn't feel right.
Rio, what's wrong with you?
Something must be bothering her,
right?
Otherwise, she wouldn't be like
this...
Are you listening to me, Yukiko?
Yes, I'm listening.
You know what?
Koichi seemed kind
of different today, no?
How?
Well, I don't know how to say this,
but...
Well, he seemed flirtatious.
Why do you find that strange?
Koichi and I are a married couple.
Of course we flirt with each other.
You two are a married couple, but...
What?
We're a married couple.
We love each other from the heart
and of course, with our bodies.
Yukiko, you're...
What is it?
Well...
You're getting too close.
Hey Yuuki.
Do you want to know why Rio
locked herself in her room?
Sorry about that, Yukiko.
Do you want to know why?
Well, yeah.
But how did you find out?
Well you see...
You're going to release your stuff
inside me...
...'til I can't take any more, right?
No way...
What is this?
Yukiko?
Well, I've had moments
like that as well.
Yuuki.
After you did it with Rio,
did you take good care of her?
How did you...
Know about it?
I know everything that
goes on in this house.
Girls that age are very delicate.
So you have to take good care of
her.
Okay, Yukiko.
I just made that up.
So what should I do?
Let's see...
Yukiko...
Don't do this...
Why?
Your cock seems to be wanting this.
I have Rio...
Oh? You're still worried about her.
Then...
It's still rock hard.
Do you want to stick it inside me?
Nope.
You kept on calling me Yukiko.
I'm really hurt because of that.
Let's see...
Call me mother and I'm all yours.
Mother...
That's better.
I'll let you stick it inside me.
Yuuki's cock is going inside me!
Your cock is completely inside me.
Well?
Is it better than Rio's?
Don't start moving.
I want to feel your cock.
My pussy is stretching.
I didn't know your cock was this
good.
If I go up like this...
Look, it might come off.
I love your cock.
Your cock feels so good!
Your cock is starting to shake!
You're coming, you're
coming, you're coming!
I love cock juice!
I love cocks!
You released quite a load.
It smells like baby's urine.
So cute...
Why did you do that?
What do you mean?
Well, that...
You, Koichi, Gonzo, the three of
you...
Three of us?
What about us?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I saw you three having sex!
Plus...
You messed around with my Yuuki.
Messed around?
Well...
You were having sex with
Yuuki behind my back.
So many times.
Well...
we love each other and...
Rio and Yuuki are members
of this family...
...and they're allowed to have sex.
But why can't I have sex?
Well...
When you two were having
sex with each other...
I was all by myself in
this house feeling lonely.
Nobody really cared about me.
That's not true, I...
Liar!
You didn't do anything for me.
You just looked grieved.
Didn't you know that you
made me feel more miserable?
But I feel like I'm now part of their
family.
I wanted to show it to you too, Rio.
The sight of a happy family
today during dinnertime...
...and how happy I felt with Koichi.
You're right.
I didn't really care about you.
I have to admit you were
right about what you said.
But I can't forgive you
for messing with my Yuuki.
He's...
Yuuki is...
...the only family I have!
Listen to me, Rio.
You say that I stole Yuuki from you.
But both you and Yuuki are
my very precious children.
But, but...
Then why?
Yes, you see...
Your pussy looks so nice.
I envy your youthfulness.
Your clit is getting bigger.
Let's lick it.
No!
No, no, no!
Stop it mother!
Why?
You're salivating down here
and it's asking for more.
But, but, this isn't normal!
You're right.
But are we a normal family?
We're not normal, right?
No!
I climaxed on her finger...
I knew she would go after Yuuki,
but...
Are you listening to me Yukiko?
Yes, I'm listening.
Girls this age are very delicate, so
you have to take good care of her.
Okay, Yukiko.
Why?
Don't start moving.
I want to feel your cock.
Your cock is starting to shake!
I didn't think she would go after Rio.
This is just too good.
Let's keep going.
You can understand, right?
I like Koichi and Yuuki...
...but I really like you too.
Yes, I really like you too, mother.
This is amazing.
Stepfather?
Grandpa?
Well, I wasn't peeping or anything.
It's just that I heard some noises
and...
Stepfather, it's okay,
you don't have to lie.
We're a family.
Let's not have any secrets, okay?
But you can't join us like that.
Rio.
Go and suck on it.
Yes, mother.
I can't take it anymore!
Oh my, you don't last very long.
Or is it because Rio is very good?
Rio, let's climax together.
I really like you mother!
Great.
I can't believe this.
I have no strength in my hips.
If I keep going like
this, they'll suck me dry.
I have to rest for a while.
Koichi!
Yuuki!
It's shooting out like crazy!
It's so hot.
I think I'll burn myself.
Plenty of cock juice!
Bitter!
When you grow older,
it'll taste much better.
Only a blowjob?
Are you kidding me?
Somehow I made it.
I love your cock...
It's much better than a vibrator.
Rio is unbelievable.
It feels so hot!
Your thing is completely inside me!
Can you stop for a minute?
I have a great idea.
Do you mind Rio?
What is it, father?
What is this?
My ass...
My ass feels hot!
Now Koichi and Yuuki, start moving.
Hot!
It feels so hot inside!
Mother!
Hot!
Rio is so sexy.
I'm starting to feel it as well.
I'm starting to feel so good.
Can I do it harder Rio?
Yes, do it much harder!
You're so cute, Rio!
I feel it coming!
I feel it in my ass and my pussy!
Rio, you're such a nice cute girl!
I should escape now...
Stepfather?
Where do you think you're going?
Your cock is really amazing.
It's different from Koichi or Yuuki's.
It shouldn't be like this...
Hey Yukiko, continue where you left
off.
Yes honey.
Father.
Stepfather.
Old man.
Grandpa.
Is he running away?
Probably.
Go after him!
Yeah!
They'll suck me dry and kill me.
Come back here!
It was supposed to be like a harem.
We need more!
You see him?
No.
Since we became a happy family,
I thought we'd celebrate
by having an orgy.
Stepfather...
I wonder where he went.
This is wrong.
It was supposed to be
a much better place.
Why did it turn out like this?
Well, I'll try better next time.