Taka?
Yo!
Yo?
What are you doing in the men's shower room?
What are you talking about?
This shower room is for both men and women.
Stop worrying and take a shower.
Yeah, but...
You're a man, right?
Stand up straight and look sharp!
Y-Yes!
Hey hey!
Did I tell you to straighten your cock as well?
Well, this is just...
Whatever, so you got an erection.
If I don't do something about your cock...
...then I'll just be defying my style.
Style?
Looks good.
It's good to be young eh?
You still can't do a man's share of work, but you got talent.
It's not bad at all.
Thank you very much.
You're still inexperienced, but I guess it's okay.
I guess I'll let you stick it inside.
Huh?
What?
WHAT?
Women at Work
Let's see...
You got a really nice one.
Feels good to be inside me, right?
Well?
It's so tight...
I'm starting to feel good.
Well? Feels good right?
Are you about to come?
This is bad...
I'm about to come...
Yeah, yeah!
Come on! Come on and release it!
You did pretty good.
You came too fast, so let's do it again.
Looks like you can do some more.
All right then, I'll let you get off one more time.
What?
WHAT?
What was that all about?
I wonder how many times I came today.
I guess the only thing getting trained in this work environment...
...is you, little guy.
This is no good.
All right! I'll go back to square one and train hard from tomorrow on!
Now I'll go home and sleep.
Muscles, muscles...
Why do you look so surprised?
This way!
Sit over here.
Massage chair?
It's for a massage...
All righty then.
It's very comfortable.
It feels good!
What's going on?
Sorry.
You saw... But don't tell anyone my secret, okay?
What the hell?
What's going on?
Hey, just wait a minute!
It looks like a guy is sucking my cock...
But it feels good...
This is bad...
It's turning into a world of boys' love...
Hold on...
You like it rough?
No...
Oh no...
I'm starting to feel good...
This is bad...
This is really bad...
I'm gonna come...
I got off not too long ago...
I'm coming!
I got off...
I released it...
I can't believe I did that...
I released it inside a guy's mouth...
Please, keep my secret between us, okay?
Even if he tells me to keep this between us...
...it's still a man's world.
But that might not be such a bad idea...
Ugh! No way!
If this keeps up, I'll be sucked deeper into this parallel world.
Oh? You were still here?
Plus you're looking very bold...
You know what?
Do you want to see if that brown algae worked or not?
What?
You can do me any way you like.
Well, this is just...
Sorry! You'll have to excuse me!
Is he shy?
So cute!
Women at Work
What's going on?
What's happening?
Oh, it's you kid. You came at the perfect time.
What do you mean by that?
There's some building materials buried down there and...
...we can't get our work done unless those materials are cleared out.
You're right.
Normally, we'd use a machine to do this kind of thing...
but unfortunately, the machine is broken.
So we need to do it like the old days.
Use this and get the materials out of the way.
Me?
That's right.
Young folks like you should do this job.
We got another one here.
What?
Wait a minute.
All right then, we'll see in the next 35 seconds...
...which one of you can destroy the most concrete.
Okay, place your bets!
Thanks for what you did yesterday...
No problem...
Okay, this is a showdown!
Okay.
Showdown eh?
When I was young, I used to compete with other young guys.
The loser has to clean the shower room.
Got it?
Let's get it on!
Ready...
Come on, keep digging!
Use more strength!
Looking good there!
Come on, come on!
Time's up!
This guy is clearly the winner!
No!
Okay, let's share the prize.
Don't forget to clean the shower room!
Yes, I understand.
Thanks.
You took it easy on me.
I'll repay you for this some other time.
What?
I'll be heading back.
Oh no...
This is really boys' love...
Women at Work
Let's see, brush and detergent...
What the...
Harumi...
Oh, you're looking for something?
Yeah. A brush and some detergent...
Well let's see, I think it was under this thing...
I'm sorry, but can you get it yourself?
My hands are full right now.
But under what?
Here.
Can you see it?
I could see it, but how do I grab it?
You can reach for it by sticking your head between my legs.
I don't mind at all, so feel free to stick it all the way inside.
You say you don't mind but...
Hurry!
Excuse me.
What are you looking for Harumi?
A condom.
What? A condom?
Why?
There's lots of guys here.
So without a condom...
...both guys and girls are going to be in big trouble.
Boys' love!
I don't know what you're talking about...
...but you're rubbing against it and it feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I can almost reach it...
If you rub it that hard...
I'll get wet.
I can't take it anymore.
Hurry! Hurry!
It's inside.
Now thrust me real hard.
It feels so good.
I'm feeling good too.
When you climax, release it inside my mouth.
I think I'm gonna climax.
I'm coming!
Tastes like you need to cut back on salt.
Here.
I'll give you these so make good use of them.
You'll get more brown algae for lunch today.
Women at Work
Oh well.
I guess I have to do it since I lost.
I didn't know there was a door back here.
Lately, bad things have happened when I opened doors...
But I can't just keep them closed...
I knew it...
You're a rude bastard!
You burst in here knowing it was my personal bathroom?
No, it's not like that...
You're letting out all the steam.
Come inside.
Yes.
Oh my...
Wow...
Use this.
What?
You're not using the condoms provided by the company are you?
These were custom-made just for me.
This is only 0.01 millimeters in width, it's ultra thin.
Plus...
...it's covered with a special lotion and my favorite perfume, CN 17.
It feels natural and the colors are minutely detailed.
Now, let's get it started.
Hurry up!
Yes.
Here I come.
Moderate exercise after work makes your body more supple...
It's starting to feel much better...
Yes...
Make sure to rub them good...
Use your other hand.
Yes, right here?
Yes, feel that part...
Do it carefully...
Let's do it faster...
Yes.
You're getting dull.
Keep squeezing them more.
Yes.
You're pretty good.
I'm about to climax.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
It was pretty good.
But build more endurance until our next meeting.
Got it?
Women at Work
It is just my imagination?
The sun looks really yellow...
I wanted to get paid, work out and get a great body...
...get a girlfriend, and experience true love...
...but lately, it seems like I've been...
This is what sex is all about?
What is love?
What are women thinking?
What am I doing?
I didn't come here to do these
things.
Should I quit?
Watch it!
Be careful when you're up here!
Pay attention!
You're the one who's dangerous.
I'll tell you one thing.
Listen, don't worry about what happens in between.
Only the results are important.
Umm...
Don't speak! I can tell!
You came here because you had something on your mind, right?
Well, sort of...
If you're a real man, then you shouldn't give up so easily.
Look at blue sky.
That's right! Your answer lies within the blue sky.
I see...
Don't give up no matter what.
And reach for that blue sky.
I see...
That's right, you have to have a heart like that clear blue sky.
Heart like a blue sky?
I don't really understand...
Be quiet!
Do you always have to complain?
I don't really understand it myself either.
But the answer lies within that blue sky.
So that's how it is?
That's right.
Just remember this.
Women are the sea, men are the blue sky!
Right...