What?
I'm happy you feel that way but...
Plus you seem like a nice-looking guy...
Sort of...
But it looks like you're a wimp.
I see...
I'll pass.
Pass?
I'm sorry.
But it looks like you're a wimp.
Wimp...
You got huge muscles!
It's marvelous! Make love to me!
I've been dumped by my girl and she said I'm a wimp...
Men should be strong.
Who is this guy?
Weirdo!
Now Hiring
Workers wanted?
Workers wanted for a construction site...
Robust...
Body...
Gutsy...
High salary...
Yeah!
Times are getting better.
If I work at a construction site, it'll be much better than going to a gym.
I can really get a workout.
If I go to a gym, they'll charge me money.
But if I work at a construction site, they'll give me money.
This is a nice idea!
I can do this!
No, I can really do this!
Muscles and money, killing two birds with one stone...
Easy money...
Like driving a stake into sawdust...
Opps, my bad...
I'll workout like crazy and I'll show her what I can do!
I'll work and get a massive body...
I'll soon be attractive!
Just you wait!
Physical labor!
I'll show them!
Women at Work
My name is Hiroko Miike and I'm in charge.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I looked at your resume.
For the time being...
I don't see any problems.
But can you really work at a construction site?
You look like a wimp.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I can handle it!
You know something, boy?
You can't make it in this world on attitude alone.
Do you understand?
All right.
Then I'll be nice and give you a test.
Is that ok?
Really?
Thank you very much!
What?
Go and prepare for the test.
Now, you have exactly 10 minutes.
Go!
What do you mean go?
I'm just trying to test your strength.
Didn't you learn that in school?
We'll be conducting a nationwide exam starting next year.
Or are you thinking that you can't do it with me since I'm older?
No, of course not.
Stand up!
Yes!
It's really standing up.
Of course.
Wow, it looks strong.
Strong?
We'll begin the test.
Yes!
Test...
This is an actual test, right?
I have to do it if it's a test.
You passed the first part.
Now let's go with the second part.
Shove that mighty stick inside me.
I passed the first part...
Mighty stick...
Yes! I'll shove it inside!
Like this?
You can move faster if you want.
Yes!
Give it to me faster...
Faster...
Yes, that's it!
That's it, keep it going.
You got it?
Faster! Faster!
You're good.
You have more strength than I thought.
You passed the second part.
Thank you very much.
Now comes the last part.
Just do your best until the very end!
Yes!
He's good.
Go on and release it inside!
Are you sure?
I'm coming!
You're pretty good.
You're hired.
I guess I'll have you start working today...
Thank you very much.
Starting today?
If you can't, then I won't hire you.
No, of course I'll start.
I'll be happy to start working today!
Out of the way!
I'm sorry.
I was in a rush.
What's going on?
Well, I was in a hurry, and...
I got what you said.
So please...
Try not to talk with your mouth full.
I'll climax!
I'm coming!
Sorry about that.
I know this is none of my business but...
...you should get some iron in your diet.
I have to go now.
Excuse me...
Who was that?
Oh, you don't have to worry about her.
Huh?
Harumi Tanigawa.
I hired her to provide us with tea but, she's a bit...
...no, she's really a natural.
You'll find out soon.
Yo, what's up?
Yuck!
Did you just say "Yuck"?
Really?
All righty then.
But you shouldn't look so surprised.
You're very rude.
Seeing a woman work at a construction site might be rare, but...
Okay, okay.
Don't pick on the young workers.
Hey, introduce yourself.
All right!
I'm in charge of this site...
Harumi!
We needed more lunch boxes!
Don't eat me...
I'll eat you...
Hey rookie!
Let's go to work!
Yes!
People sometimes go through events that change their lives.
I honestly didn't believe that at all...
...until today.
I can't believe it's at a construction site in middle of a filthy city...
Women at Work
Now that I've been hired...
...I'll work like crazy to make money and train my body...
I know I shouldn't be whining like this, but...
...why are these bags so heavy?
Hey! What are you doing, you slowpoke?
Keep it going!
Sorry.
Aren't they heavy?
I can't believe they're making you carry those by yourself.
My name is Akira Hayasaka.
I'll be working with you from now on.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, I'm Akiyoshi.
Nice to meet you too.
No, no.
Am I going gaga?
I don't know if this is a girl or a guy... but I'm getting excited...
Yo.
Looks like you guys already met each other.
Sorry I couldn't introduce myself earlier.
My name is Minako Takahara.
Call me Taka.
She's very rough.
But she doesn't seem like a bad person.
Damn! Here she comes...
Who could it be this time?
Miss!
You always show up to work like a princess.
Hey, these are the rookies...
There's no need for you to introduce them!
She's really gorgeous!
I'm guessing she's the president's daughter...
...or maybe she's the president's lover.
Expensive workclothes...
I didn't know they made those things...
You look very weak.
Can you really work with a body like that?
Whatever.
I just hope you don't get in my way.
Her name is Mutsuki Oshima.
Also known as "the Princess."
You can tell her personality just by looking at her.
Don't you worry about her.
What a complicated world.
Maybe I'm lost in a parallel world...
Okay everyone!
Get to work!
We're behind schedule, you know.
Let's put some energy into this!
Women at Work
Time for lunch.
Hey rookie, time for lunch.
I'll be right there.
Here's your lunch!
Try to savor it.
I can't...
I'm too tired to eat...
Here's your lunch!
Thank you very much.
Make sure you get some iron, I put lots of brown algae for you.
Hey Taka...
About that public relations work...
Unfortunately, I can't make it this afternoon.
So I was just thinking...
Can you send that rookie of yours as a representative?
Oh, that public relations work...
But sending him is a waste of time.
As a matter of fact, he's unreliable.
But there's nothing else I can do.
Damn!
All right then.
Can you go?
Me?
Well, it's an easy job, but...
But when you say public relations...
...I have to negotiate with others, right?
I don't have any experience with that. I can't do it.
It's like route sales.
It's so simple that anyone can do it.
Especially a young man like yourself.
Huh?
They said it's somewhere around here, but...
I only see regular houses.
I don't see any office buildings.
I see...
Is it just my imagination? I thought someone was watching me...
I have no time to think about such things.
I need to find that company fast and...
Hey! How long are you gonna make me wait?
What?
I see the person in charge is really young this time.
Now we can really negotiate.
Anyway, come on up.
My name is Fumiko.
You can see what I do from the work that's in front of you.
Yes...
Are you the person that I'm going to negotiate with?
Huh?
If you can, can you
just tell me the details?
They didn't tell you?
Great...
I hope you can understand.
My job is to write mangas all night and then sleep all day.
Get it?
But since you guys started to do some work in front of my place...
I can't sleep with all that noise.
I see...
So regarding this noise problem, your Nekoyanagi...
...construction company and I decided to talk things over.
That's all.
They didn't tell you anything?
Your superiors are really mean.
Sorry.
That's just great.
But you'll do what you came here to do.
Start preparing for the meeting.
You're in charge of this right?
Let's begin the meeting.
Excuse me...
Basically, I want you to make me really tired so that I can fall asleep.
Well, it's just that, I...
Meeting is where a man's hips and the girl's ass goes bang bang.
They meet.
Well, they do meet, so that's why they call it meeting...
I see...
That's our agreement.
Since I can't fall asleep in the daytime due to your construction.
You people send over a strong man...
and make sure I can fall asleep after banging our hips and asses.
I see...
This is no time to be impressed...
Since you got it now, let's begin!
That's good...
Yeah...
Use your tongue more...
Lick the other hole as well.
Stick it deeper inside!
That feels good!
Okay, stick it inside.
Right here.
What? Are you sure?
Yeah.
If I get banged in this hole, I can fall asleep easily.
Now, don't hesitate. You're still young.
Yes.
Here I come.
It's tight...
Hey, that rookie seems to be doing well in his first meeting.
Yeah, he's got a nice tempo, too.
Yes! It feels good!
I like older guys, but I also enjoy the feeling you younger guys give.
It feels so good!
Go ahead.
Release it inside!
Women at Work
I finished the job.
Good job!
How did it go?
Take a shower and relax.
What a day.
Am I really lost in a parallel world?
Yeah, I must be.
Taka?