[ National Police Force ]
How about noodles, delicious noodles.
Don't you want to eat my noodles?
Nan-myu-ho-ren-gekkyoh...
[ Police Box - Japanese Off Limits ]
You are ordered to cease, desist and return to your homes!
This area is off limits to all Japanese.
We, the Japanese people, shall punish these countries for conquering our Japan!
[ The Republic of China ]
Riot in progress, area A4, level 3. Over!
Repeat, rioting in area A4, level 3...
Who's inciting in? The Abashiri family?
No, just frustrated reactionary elements.
I see. Quell the riot at once!
The life of a human has less weight than a piece of paper.
The family of Buddha shall come together and quickly flee.
The world was consumed by fire.
The time is near, when all the world shall disappear, disappear...
~ THE ABASHIRI FAMILY ~
Subtitles by A.D. Vision, Inc.
OCR by Inactive (Subs.com.ru)
Explosion of violence!!
We don't have justice!
They're shooting at each other too much. That's what delayed me.
Calm down, Naojiro. While the police are waching them, our work is easier.
Boys, today's target is that bank. Examine it carefully.
The money in there belongs to criminals of the worst sort, so there's no reason not to take it!
You know what to do, right? Don't screw it up!
Damn! You don't have to tell us what to do!
We go in the front door and BAM!
Then, we get the money, right?
Dead right, Kichiza, if a little extreme.
Goemon! What are you doing?
It's useless, brother.
I'm no good at this kind of fight. I'm good at sneaking, that's what I like.
The oldest son of the world famous Abashiri Family, and his speciality is stealing girl's underwear...
Poor, poor me.
Well, Kikunosuke, are you ready?
Okay. I'd like to say I'm ready but what you told me earlier wasn't what you just said now.
I know, I know. I know what I've got to say.
Children, listen to me carefully.
Today, after this job, the Abashiri Family will disband.
What?!!
What are you talking about?!
I have more to tell you!
Today, the Abashiri Family's greatest secret, guarded fro 16 years, shall be unveiled!
Today is a special day for us! Be prepared!
[ The Abashiri Family is coming! ]
I don't understand.
But it's time to work!
Charge!!
Welcome to my bank!
My, what a loud entrance! And who are our new clients?
Uh! You-you're... I don't believe it.
You got it. It seems cheeky to say our name after all that.
We are, of course, the Abashiri Family, here to rob this bank!!
Oh, the Abashiri Family! Welcome to my bank!
Today would have been my lovely wife, Omitsu's, 10th anniversary, but that's just a coincidence.
Today, as promised in my wife's will, is also the day I shall unveil my family's greatest secret!
Truly, a momentous occasion! Therefore, I must take a lot of money to in honor of the occasion!
What a memorable day!
The Abashiris, with a bounty of over $50,000,000,000.00 on their heads, all together at one time!
Well, I'll promise you something memorable!
It's useless.
I don't make exceptions for ugly girls. Not ever!
You'd better not move.
For your own sake.
He's right. Goemon has mastered the Abashiri method of pocket picking, purse snatching, and murder!
His eyes see bullets in flight, his fingers snatch at the speed of sound, and
with a flick of his finger, he can puncture an iron board.
Therefore, guns are useless against the Abashiris.
Don't underestimate my bank, Mr. Client.
I didn't know this bank had taken up heavy artillery. I'm impressed.
This operation is merely a front! Our real business is eliminating hard cases like you and establishing peace, order and development.
This bank is a branch of the National Police Corporation!
You do hear that sound, don't you?
Check mate, Oreg 2, location confirmed, the Abashiri Family is caught inside trap C-4.
Repeat, they are in trap C-4. Arrest them now!
I don't care if they're living or dead, but if you have to take one of them out...
don't destroy the bodies. We have to be able to identify them.
Don't underestimate them. The Abashiri Family is as powerful as an army.
Defcon 1 is engaged. Again, Defcon 1, Defcon 1 is engaged.
How do you understand? It may be a cliche, but you are completely surrounded.
All you can do now is die.
Thank you.
What?
I said thank you, for preparing a suitable stage for the end of the Abashiri Family.
Damn it!
Die!
Don't shoot!
Enema!
At long last, I've killed the Abashiri Family!
They may be vulgar, sewer dwelling crooks, but they're still human.
They couldn't survive a direct hit like that.
Hurry up and clean up the dead bodies.
That puny attack won't break my flesh and bones! Naojiro Abashiri is immortal!
What the hell?
That's right. The second son of the Abashiri Family is Naojiro.
His body is the ultimate armored cyborg, except for his brain.
Look at him! See his power!
There!
It itches...
Shit...
It's too early to be surprised.
Next is the youngest son of the Abashiri Family, Kichiza.
My turn at last.
When Kichiza Abashiri takes off his mask...
somebody dies.
Shut up!
A genius with explosives, Kichiza Abashiri wears special clothes made of gunpowder-based fabric.
That means his clothes really are dynamite.
Freeze! If you move, you explode.
Money! Money! This is money!
Well, those three were just the opening act.
The sole heir to the Abashiri Death Attack, Kikunosuke Abashiri is the main event!
The power, the shape...
A single blow is lethal with this technique from the Eight Gods martial arts school...
the Seven-Headed God-Dragon!
Kikunosuke is the master of this ultimate martial art, which originated in Vishupulana, India.
In addition, for 18 generations, only males have been born to the Abashiri Family.
Now, the 18th generation has born our first female, Kikunosuke!
What?!
Kikunosuke is...?
Fe...fe...female?
Did you say female?
You know, dad. I thought something was funny.
You've been giving Kikunosuke a lot of special treatment.
Like, Kikunosuke's getting his own bedroom and shower...
We're half-brothers. We all have different origins.
But we always swore our bond would be stronger than iron. Why?
You tricked me for a long time.
Shut up! That was the rule!
The greatest secret of the Abashiri Family, kept hidden for 16 years...
Today, Kikunosuke's 16th birthday, is the day we shall break the seals.
That's right. Our family has committed far too many crimes.
The first Abashiri, Sword Killer Choujuro, killed and murdered over a million people.
Perhaps the curse on our family comes from their ghosts.
We have enduredm yet no female was been born into the Abashiris.
Now, in our 18th generation, a daughter, Kikunosuke, was born.
I don't know why I was born with this Abashiri birth mark on my back...
but it means I shall be the Abashiri's next master, with our family's fate in my hands.
As the rules stated, I pretended to be male until my breasts grew, and I've done a lot of evil.
But it's over, as of today.
On this day, having been released from the curse of an all male family, the Absashiri Family is normal at last!
That's what I'd like to say. However, as evil is everywhere in our society, and since we need money...
It's nothing personal, but I have to kill you.
I won't let you live just because you're a girl.
A beautiful woman is better than gold.
You're strong. That excites me.
A murdere like you belongs in the Abashiri Family. Girl's shouldn't have blood on their hands.
No!
Just because I was born an Abashiri, I was born a criminal with a reward on my head.
Evil, greedy men stalk me constantly. If I didn't kill them, they'd kill me.
It's a rotten world and it's going downhill.
I'd prefer to have been born a pretty young girl.
What bull shit.
That's right. Murder's no job for a pretty young girl...
but once she's 16, she must become a woman.
That was the will of her dear, dead mother.
Hear me, Kikunosuke! You, alone, must end this curse!
It's the last crime of the infamous
Abashiri Family, feared everywhere for their wickedness and cruelty!
Now the family's fate rest on this single bank robbery... but this is no simple hold up!
An army of police have surrounded the Abashiris...
and in the center of the battle, an earth-shaking revelation!
Who suspected that Kikunosuke was a girl? the secret was so well kept that even her own family didn't know!
But while God may be forgiving, people aren't.
Is there a future for the Abashiri Family?
If you touch it, even a little bit, it will explode.
Kikunosuke's the main performer here! You boys stay out of it!
Oh, man! I never realized Kikunosuke was a girl.
I feel it. I feel it.
A pretty girl should be kept naked and used as a pedestal.
Never seen a woman before, you bastard?
I see women all the time.
But I'm not familiar with pretty girls.
Oh, you have grown up breasts!
What are you looking at? Don't get so excited! You bastard!!
I've finally caught you, little mouse! How shall I cook you?
Bastard!
Don't even think about getting involved. He's already dug his own grave!
Having lived as a boy for so long...
Kikunosuke's female side has been pushed into the deepest part of her heart.
If somebody touches those long suppressed feelings...
the incredible energy unique to the female Abashiris will be released.
I really don't like men looking at me like this...
at all!
You're annoying me!
The final attack! An Abashiri 8 God attack! Fire God!!
Fight's over!
Goemon!
Yes, sir!
The prize is ours. Now let's escape!
There!
Listen carefully, Abashiri Family! you're already surrounded by our most powerful troops!
Cease struggling and surrender now.
Shoot!
Our power is stronger than yours. Stop this senseless struggling and die.
The strongest weapon in the world isn't an arrow, a gun, or a missile. It's money.
Money...
Don't touch it! All mine!
Do you want more?
We always do this and we never get rich. Damn!
[ I'm BAD! ]
They're not worth being afraid of!
This is the true face of the National Force troops.
Hell! Paradice School
And I put the flowers like this...
Yes! All finished! it looks delicious!
Wake up, everybody! A delicious breakfast is ready!
Hurry up or the lovely meal will become cold.
Hurry up and get ready, you shit heads!
I've got a feeling...
[ Gallantly ]
Beautiful breasts, the size of my paws. A beautiful butt, so nicely shaped!
Really!
Ah, what a waste!
Oh, you don't need to hide them...
Oh, first, she wears a shirt and what next?! What?
What the hell are you doing in there?
What? Well...
you over there, too.
What are you guys doing?
What were we doing? Nothing...
Oh, that was a sight for sore eyes! What a beauty!
He's right. it's tragedy to hide your beautiful breasts with that cloth...
and you can trust me to supply the lingerie!
Your breat size is... A cup and 70 centimeters. I've got that size.
Choose whichever you like!
Enough of this!
I'll never wear girl's underwear.
If you don't like women's underwear, how about swimsuits?
Exercise shorts are the best.
Negligees, too!
Stop that!
Biys! I envy you for having spied on your sister changing.
After all, I'm her father and I haven't done that yet!
What did you say?
B..Breakfast is ready, everybody!
Now everyone, there's a reason for bringing you together today to share a meal.
According to the new rules, we will now be a normal family and contribute to our world and its people.
Therefore, I shall tell you how to do this.
But first, a question before my announcement.
How do we get money?
Pilfer...
Swipe.
Steal.
There's no way except to kill someone and take it.
Idiots! I guess you don't understand, but once people used to work hard to earn money.
To do normal work, I think you need to go to school and improve you mind...
What I have just described is the right way to do things.
First of all, Kikunosuke! Go to school!
Go to school and learn to become a polished young lady.
I don't want to be polished.
I've already finished the entire application process for a school.
Kikunosuke's not a suitable name for a girl, so I enrolled you under the name "Reiko Shiratori". Try this on.
Wow, a school uniform!
Looks cute!
Show me my sweet daughter, Kikunosuke.
Female clothes don't look good on me...
I'm 16 years old and I've already killed 160 people.
My hands are too bloody to become a pretty girl!
If you don't kill, you'd be killed. That's the world's fault, not yours.
No way!
Idiot! Can't you listen to me?!
I think this looks good on you.
I'm happy if my sister becomes pretty. Aren't you guys?
Kiku, try it on.
Don't make fun of me.
You let Kikunosuke go to school, but what about us?
Biys and girls have the same rights.
You guys will do fine, somehow.
But Kiku... Kikunosuke is different from you.
Honey, I wonder how many people this baby, Kikunosuke, will have to kill to live her life...
I suppose it's all right to Abashiri men to kill, it's our way of life.
But a female can not live like a man.
The Abashiri family should never have had a daughter...
What a fate! I pity this child.
Bullshit! Dad decided school because he's got a thing for the uniforms!
Well, shit happens. I'm doing this for dad.
I guess I can play a high school girl for a while.
What?
A hidden microphone?!
I heard you, I heard you!!
In the Abashiri Family, if you say it once, you have to do it.
Do you promise?
I'm happy you said so.
I'm so happy you've promised.
The burden on my shoulders will vanish when you become a nice, normal girl.
I'll be able to meet my third dead wife in heaven without hesitation...
I'll tell her that Kiku grew up and became a beautiful girl who looked just like her.
Papa...
Well, Kikunosuke, let me get another good look.
Like this?
Oh, a chance!
There!!
Great chance! Oh, beautiful.
Excellent, I can trust you. You passed.
What do you mean?
I was wondering if you still had a little female left in your mind or not.
Liar! You're a pervert, Papa!
The motto of St. Paradice School is that an all-dormitory education focuses the growth of a well-behaved student.
Here, students are separated from the world's decay. With God's grace, we will nurture love, trust and intelligence.
That's our school policy.
Your name's Reiko Shiratori, right? I can see there are some blank columns on this application.
We decided it was all right. You'll start your dormitory life today.
Excuse me, but I've got to ask you something, Principal.
Maybe it's my imagination, but I smell blood from you.
Vice President, please take Miss Shiratori to the Ladies dormitory.
Oh, what a happy day!
The Paradice School is the best, a most famous school.
There's an old saying, "Among the crimson, things become red."
I'm sure that Kikunosuke will be a gorgeous woman when she graduates.
What's the matter? Drink more, drink, drink!!
I won't see Kikunosuke for three years... My heart hurts.
Are you in love with Kikunosuke? Well, I guess I could let you marry her.
Really?
Fuck no!
This is a new student, Miss Shiratori.
She'll be your roommate, so teach her everything.
Everything.
Yes, teacher.
It's nice to meet you. My name is Yukiko Shirane.
The outside world is dangerous so I'm locking the gate now.
Oh, I have to tell you that we get up at 6 am. Don't be late!
[ Teacher's Room ]
Did you see her? The new student's pretty cute.
But she looks like she was a hard case.
We have to help her get used to the atmosphere of Paradice High.
Now we'll have more fun...
Damn, what a cheap room! Just like home.
The girl's dormitories are all like this.
Are you really a girl?
Why? Do I look like a boy?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But, you introduced yourself like a guy. It's strange.
Unfortunately, I've been raised in a rather low-class family.
Iron bars on the window, too...
I guess you really are suitable for this school.
No, no, please. Help me!
In accordance with school rule #4...
the execution will now begin.
- Help me!
- Do you have any last words?
Mother, I wanted to go to a normal school!
Somebody was just killed. Damn! My nerves are shot.
Oh, no! No, I've had enough! Stop it!
Shit! A Special Meeting! They did this without any advance notice.
Hey, wake up, hurry! Special Meeting!
Miss Shiratori! Wake up! Hurry!
Shiratori? My name's Abashiri...
Miss Shiratori!
You'll be in really big trouble if you don't wake up!
Are all the students here, A-building?
I'm really sorry, but room #5, Miss Shiratori isn't here yet.
What? Did you say Shiratori?
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
You understand what will happen to you, right?
Which do you prefer, being beaten or raped?
Cut it out, old man.
What?!
If you do any more to her, I won't stand by quietly.
Who the hell is she?
She'll be killed!
Of course...
You're new, aren't you?
I guess you don't understand what kind of place this is.
You've said too much already, pervert.
What?!
You don't know who I am, do you? I'm Chidoro, they call me Bull-killer.
I'm a teacher here.
That's ridiculous! How can a psycho be a teacher here?
Bitch, I won't let you live any longer.
Don't contradict a teacher or you'll be killed!
Shut up! It's too late.
You'll pay for this! You die!!
Gain wealth by killing people! A bloody world!
There are many cruel criminals, but the Abashiri Family is the most fearsome of them all.
A beautiful girl named Kikunosuke is a miraculous flower of womanhood blossoming in this family of men.
To gain a pardon from God she has entered the prestigious St. Paradice academy.
But is God dead? Where is Buddha? A storm of violence envelops Kikunosuke once more.
Doesn Kikunosuke even have a future?
You've said too much already, pervert.
What?!
You don't know who I am, do you? I'm Chidoro, they call me Bull-killer.
I'm a teacher here.
That's ridiculous! How can a psycho be a teacher here?
Bitch, I won't let you live any longer.
Don't contradict a teacher...
You'll pay for this!
You escaped my deadly straight punch! I guess you're not like other girls.
You call that a deadly punch? It was so slow that a fly on your fist could die of boredom.
Bullshit!
Keep your elbow closer to your body, or you'll be leaving yourself open, old man.
What's the matteerm old man? The fight's just started.
You bitch!!
I'll kill you!
Can't you fight without grabbing some silly weapon?
Shut the fuck up!
She's found Chidoro's blind spot. Who is that girl?
What's wrng, old man? Is the fight over already?
Oops, don't move!
That's not a good angle to be looking at me from.
I can't believe she beat Chidoro!
She'll be in big trouble after this.
Now she's done it! Run!!
What? What's wrong with everybody?
There's an old saying, "If you know nothing, you get nothing."
Well, try to live long, new friend.
Riot! A storm in the Paradice
[ I'll be killed. Mother, I don't want to die. I want to go home. This place is like hell. ]
I'll kill her, I'll kill her! That bitch!
I was watching the fight, Professor Chidoro.
I can't believe you lost to a student.
Wait a second!
Please, please don't tell anyone about this! Please!!
No!
It's time for a faculty meeting.
Shut up and wait for the results of the meeting.
No, please don't.
Forget it! As a teacher you're supposed to be a model for our students, but you shamed yourself by losing a fight.
I doubt whether you can remain a teacher of Paradice High.
[ Study Hall ]
What you did was crazy!
We'll all be killed.
You'll bring us nothing but trouble!
What's wrong with this place? Are all the teachers crazy and all the students worthless?
You can say what you want, but you shouldn't have done anything, even if Yukiko was raped.
If you hadn't done something, we wouldn't be involved.
You bastard...
Wait a second. I don't want to fight against you. You're too strong.
But if you listen to the truth about Saint Paradice, you'll understand why we're all so scared.
Please...
Please, help me!! I won't fail again!
The assembled faculty has already decided.
You'd better start running, as fast as you can, okay? Or else you'll die right here.
Please, please.
Shut up!
Help me!
Who'll kill him?
I will!
This is no normal school. It may look like a proper school from the outside...
but once you enter this place, you'll never be able to leave again, just like in a prison.
And that's not all! We have two curricula: Cultural and Technical.
Cultural is the same as you learn on other schools, but Technical is some really scary and bizarre stuff.
It's Murder 101, all different ways to kill people. This is a school for murderers.
Hundreds of new students are enrolled every spring, but only two or three graduate. Do you understand?
Everybody dies! The teachers are monsters.
I'll escape... escape!!
You're so close. You could have gotten away if you'd tried just a little harder.
Yes, all of the students arer killed. Students with low grades are used for target practice.
That means we're forced to kill our friends, using the techniques we're taught.
Stop it!
On top of that, some students are killed by teachers for disobedience, or for trying to escape this place.
Stop it!!
This place should be named Hell, not Paradice.
You did well, Professor Hitokui!
I couldn't let him live after his mistake.
This girl Shiratori, who won the fight with Chidoro...
seems to have a backbone.
It will be well worth killing her.
Yes, slowly and thoroughly...
The teacher you beat up was the weakest of them. I know they won't leave you alone.
New student and freshman scum Shiratori!
Report to the room of inner reflection immediately! Repeat, immediately!
We have nothing to do with this!!
No, don't go! This time you'll be killed!
Out of my way. I don't know what sort of monsters they are, but I can handle it.
[ Room of Inner Reflection ]
Good work! You're strong, but you're too impolite for a new student. I'd like you to reflect on yourslef.
Forget the reflection part, this place should be called the torture chamber.
We call it that, too.
You lice! I'll take you all out at once.
You're numb and you can't even talk, can you?
This point on your neck is called the "Bon no kubo", where all of your nerves meet.
When a needle is inserted there, anybody will be taken down, even a great big man.
Now you can't do anything. Well, well, you are a good looking girl.
It would be a waste to just hurt her.
Tastes good. Well, shall we start?
Your roommate's back.
Don't worry. She's still alive.
Tell her she should pray long and hard... and to be prepared to die at any moment.
Miss Shiratori!
Brother...
Wow!
Come to me, hurry!
Shut the hell up! You're too noisy, talking in your sleep.
I knew that was only a dream.
Mmmm... smells like squid...
I'm dreaming of her even when I'm awake...
I guess I fell on love with Kikunosuke!
I'd like to smell her, at least...
Inhale, exhale, inhale, exhale...
I said shut the fuck up, you bastard!!
My heart's full of pain, too much pain. I can't wait any more.
Kikunosuke, wait for me! Why don't you marry your loving brother?
It would be a waste just to hurt her...
Ouch!!
No, don't move. I wish I had some
sort of medicine. All I can do is to cool down the scar.
That guy stole my lips. That was my first kiss.
Shit! Ouch, ouch...
What? Why am I crying?
What?
Miss Shiratori, I was afraid when I first met you.
You were a strong fighter and I felt you were looking for blood...
But now I feel relieved. You're a normal girl.
That's he only good part of being normal. The feeling of wanting your first kiss to be with someone you love.
That's something special about being a girl. It's the only nice thing in this whole stupid world...
A charm of purifying impurity.
A charm of purifying impurity...
Miss Shiratori!
What are you doing?
No! You haven't gotten well yet.
Please, please get out of here, somehow.
I saw a teacher spying on this room.
They're competing to see who gets to kill you first.
I guess it's okay to be killed someday.
You know these teachers are professional killers.
Maybe, maybe not.
Then why?
It's my nature.
Miss Shiratori!
No, don't die! I love you, Miss Shiratori!
It's strange, us both being girls, but it's true.
Please, please don't die!
How...?
How did you know? I changed
my voice, I changed my body right down to my skeleton.
I know my disguise was perfect. How...?
Smell! Yukiko smells like beautiful flowers. You stink like a dirty feral dog.
Die!
I've seen this martial art before. It's the most evil in the world, the Abashiri 8 God attack!
Only one person uses this attack... I see!
What a surprise! I didn't know Kikunosuke Abashiri was a girl.
You're worthy of being feared. You're a natural born killer!
Yukiko! Where's Yukiko!?
This is the reason I can't quit this school.
What a perk!
Shirane, with your lousy grades! Shiratori, who tried to protect you, is now writhing in her own blood.
She'll die believing you killed her, hating you from beyond the grave!
You can explain once you meet her on the other side...
but first, we have a few more things to do with you!
Hey!
No!
Bad news! He's dead! Professor Biniku's been killed!
What the hell?
It's true. And what's more, I discovered something even crazier!
What's that?
That new student, Shiratori, is really the arch-murderer Kikunosuke Abashiri!
Biniku wrote a message with his own blood on the floor.
If that's true, we can't take her lightly.
Now that we know she's Kikunosuke, it's all over.
Yukiko Shirane? I don't know.
I'd guess she's being assaulted by the teachers.
Shit! I can win if I fight them one by one...
but I don't know about a mass attack.
That's it, collect an army! They're students but they've learned the techniques of killing.
With an army, we can win.
Please. If we all fight together, we can defeat a group of less than 30 teachers.
You're full of it! You beat a teacher, but just one. Don't get too full of yourself.
Give up and go back to your room.
Women should just quiver in fear in a corner.
And I'm a woman, huh? Well I say you're male piece of crap.
Anyone who hasn't got the guts to help their companions is nothing but shit!
What did you say?
Bitch! What gives you the right to talk to us like that?
Wait! Wait a second. While we're wasting time like this, Yuki will be...
It's not that we don't like doing things like this... Are you ready?
Wait!
One, two, one, two, I'll surprise her while she's asleep!
How does Kikunosuke sleep?
She's very masculine, so only in underpants?
No, kikunosuke is fearless, so maybe naked?
Maybe she'll be lonely, sleeping alone...
so maybe she'll reach down and learn the joys of being a woman.
Your brother won't let you do that!
What?
Leader, I'm sorry. The honor of the first taste should be for you.
Idiot!
Stop playing with her!
If you have time for stupid games, use it to listen to her.
Are you joining me?
You'd better stop acting like a man. It's not proper for a girl.
Hey, everyone, it's time.
Like she said, we don't have to obey the teachers forever.
Tell all the students! Collect weapons! We'll fight together, all of us!
We'll rise together against this school at sunrise.
I understand that she's dangerous, therefore I approve of her elimination.
Yes, Principal.
Still, what a pity...
Yes, sir. She's pitiful.
Idiot!
I dind't mean that Abashiri was pitiful.
I said that all of you are pathetic, scared of a child.
Riot! The students are rioting and Abashiri's in charge!
What the hell?!
The price of betrayal
We can win now!! Now it's our turn to let them taste the fear of death.
We can get new students.
I can't let these live after they've disobeyed the teachers of Paradice High.
Kill them all.
[ We're waiting for you a the old school building. Let's see how much power you have. ]
Shit, too late! They've escaped into the ruins out back.
Boys! Wake up, wake up!!
Wake the fuck up!!
What did you do, father, you bastard!
Nao! I..I think I had Kikunosuke enter the most insane school I've ever heard of!
Where's Kichiza? Where's Goemon? Why aren't they here?
My sense of premonition has never failed.
Something horrible will happen at the Paradice School.
Kikunosuke's in danger!
We can't undo what we've done, now that we've come this far.
Well, what'll we do?
The line is too long.
We'll separate into small groups. Girls supporting the others, each group fighting individually. Am I clear?
Yes!!
You're a great commander, for a girl! You're not just a girl, are you?
Let's go!
I can climb this wall, no problems. Can't be a great pervert, otherwise.
Here!
Wow! Great!!
I'm glad I came all this way.
Who are you?
Just a pervert.
Please Mr. Pervert, hurry up and help me...
I can't do that. This is a special chance for me.
Hurry. Please, or Kikunosuke will be...
What? Kikunosuke?
Who are you? How did you get in here?
I thought today was the day for the PTA to visit.
I'm a brother of Miss Abashiri and would like to see her class...
What? You're Abashiri's brother?
Well then, I'll let you watch Kikunosuke's execution to your heart's content.
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing. Now we've got more bait for the trap.
This is group 2. We haven't come across the enemy.
We're heading to point #2.
The enemy!!
I've been waiting for you kids. Welcome to hell.
Do you really think students can win against teachers?
It's strated! Everybody's going to be killed...
Shhh! Don't make any noise!
Something sneaking up on us, but I can't see it...
Where is it?
I don't want to die!
Don't get separated from us!
You're a pretty good fighter, the rumors were right.
I'm "Mademoiselle Honey". Everybody at Paradice High calls me that.
I didn't know there were female teachers in this school.
Answer me. Where's Yuki?
Don't worry. She's around here somewhere, along with another lure.
But I guess that's not really necessary, since you're going to die right here.
From where...
What speed!
Are you a master of the Abashiri 8 God martial arts?
You don't look tough enough.
The wounds from yesterday are still painful...
Finally, recognition dawns.
This is the smell of sweet honey, which makes girls more girlish.
You'll soon see its effects.
How are you feeling? Don't you feel something mysterious?
Sweet, painful and more... I'll guide you to the pleasures of being a woman!
Well, well, you've become so sensitive...
Don't you have any inclination to masochism?
Escaping me is futile!
Bloodlust has eneveloped this whole school. I can hear faint screaming...
I knew it, something really dreadful has been happening here.
Looks like it.
Kikunosuke is the most important person in the Abashiri Family.
I won't let her die!!
You can't get away from me. Do you know why I'm called Honey?
Let me show you why...
What sweet honey invites instant death?
What is the taste of this solution, which dissolves all?
Dissolve into nothingness!!
You can take your clothes off one piece at a time, just like that.
The game is over. Now, you die.
I've got to get closer to her to win!
I don't like to brag, but I'e got the best footwork in Paradice High.
You can't win.
Prepare yourself!
Die!
Honey! My honey, on my face!!
My face!
I can't believe it took so long to finish off just one teacher...
What's the matter? Come on, attack me.
That's what you came here for, right?
I'm scared! Mother!!
Mother...
Here you are, Mister Leader! You'd better surrender to protect yourself.
You've only half as many students as you started with.
I don't care. Students can be replaced.
Who are you?
I've cultivated these forces in secret. These seven are mine alone.
Uh.. my glasses.
You can't teach at Paradice High if you can't dodge a knife.
Uh! Where?!
Leader!
You're the cruelest of all teh teachers.
You laughed strangely every time you killed a student.
Can you laugh like that now?
If you laugh, I'll let you go.
You asshole!
Besides that, they are nothing. If we kill the Principal, they'll betray the school and join our side immediately.
I guess tehre are a lot of people who want to die in this school.
Hold it! It's pointless to attack that man...
no matter what your technique! He's Daemon Abashiri!
Daemon Abashiri!!
I could never forget that voice. Danjuro Namakubi, right?
Yes, it is I.
This is the third time we've fought, isn't it?
And there shall not be a fourth.
What bullshit! Stop babbling, old man!
Stop, Nao! You're no match for that one!
What the hell is this?
My body's becoming numb.
Naojiro!
I found out that the Abashiri Family did this. Just two of them did all this!
They're too strong... like monsters!
But why are the Abashiris here?
It's Kikunosuke, the one we knew as Shiratori!
She's the Abashiri's daughter.
Then, we'll have to fight the Abashiri Family too.
They're worse than the teachers.
Don't worry. I found some good hostages for the battle.
I see. There's no better way to use them.
It's strange. I haven't seen any teachers for a while.
It's too quiet...
Hold it, Kikunosuke! It's not necessary to fight any longer.
How the hell do you know that name?
Your family came and helped us. The outcome of the battle has been decided.
We won. Let's go!
Everybody's waiting to see you in the forest.
Naojiro!
How about the power of my hair?
Danjuro, how did you get that ability? How do you keep so young?
Evil. I sold my soul to Evil.
Maybe you'll meet this Evil in hell!
Yuki! Brother!
Kikunosuke It's a trick! We've all been tricked!
What?! Where's my father?
He's still fighting in the forest.
I'm strong, but I don't want to fight those monsters.
I'm hoping Father Abashiri and the Principal will kill each other.
You bastrad! You have a hidden agenda don't you?
They intended to take over the school from the beginning.
She's right. I'll be the Principal and these seven will teach.
I won't let you get away with this.
No, don't move! If you move, these two will die.
You bastard...
We're getting a little bored waiting for the Principal and the Abashiri to finish fighting.
Why don't you dance naked for us?
If you don't want to dance, I can make this one strip.
Animals! If you want to see it that bad, I'll show it to you!
Come on! You'll die tasting the fear of death.
What's teh matter, big-talker?
Show us your pink nipples!
Damn...
Why are these things stuck on my chest?!
Don't tease us any longer. Hey, hey!
Help her out!
Danjuro! Do you think you can kill me with this tiny electric attack?
It was as I expected, Daemon! But I wonder if you will be able to survive the next one.
The 1,000,000 volt attack won't leave even a piece of fried bone.
You ought to just give up, then we won't hurt you.
Take her clothes off, starting from the bottom.
I don't care about me. Stand up and fight, Kikunosuke!
What a nice ass!
No! Stop!!
I've got it. I've found the source of your strength!
If you're found my secret, it's time for you to die!
I don't want to die! Help me!
You, monster! Start writing your own eulogy.
She said stop! I guess there's some feminity left in you.
Stop it!
Wow! I'll get to see something exciting soon!
Do it!
Principal!!
Help me! He'll kill me!
There you are, Abashiri!
Papa!
Kikunosuke!
Shit!
You fuck!
Don't mover, Abashiri! If you move, your daughter will end up like that.
All right, listen carefully.
I ought to be suitable to become the new Principal.
You've got no objections, do you?
I guess you'll agree, since none of you could oppose me, anyway.
What good boys and girls!
We shall execute the Abashiri Family at the inauguration feast for the new Principal!
What's the matter?
Here I am, the last member of the Abashiri Family!
Explosives genius, Kichiza Abashiri!
What bullshit!
Do you want to die that badly?
Does it hurt? Are you in pain?
I won't kill you quickly.
The main event..
always belongs to Kikunosuke Abashiri.
Gang Leader! I won't have mercy!
Afraid of fighting without weapons?
Here's your weapon!
Shit.
I can't move!
Here you go!
The most deadly martial art, the Abashiri 8 God attack, handed down to only one child from our ancestors.
I don't even have to touch you.
When the God mark appears on Kikunosuke's back..
it's time for someone to go to hell!
It's all my fault! Please help me!
Useless excuses!
The pain you feel now is the pain of my companions!
And the next one is for Yukiko!!
Leader and his seven goons are dead! There's no one left to kill you.
You're free!
Ah, Kiku. We killed a lot of people again...
I..I don't want to kill any more.
I know, I understand. Don't give up on your life!
I'm sure that someday this world will become one in which you can live happily as a normal woman.
I don't care what you're doing, but stop using my head as a footstop, you no good father!
Let's go! Look at that, Kiku! What a beautiful sunrise!
What about us, Dad, you son of a bitch!?
Don't forget about us!
- Come back and fix me!
- Wait! Wait a second! Father!
- Help me! Father!!
- Come back and fix me!
Time passes slowly, leaving certain distinct footprints...
Are you ready, Grandpa?
The Abashiri 8 God attack, passed down from our ancestors to only one child in the Abashiri family!
Kikunosuke's so strong!
Oh, no. You mustn't be mean to your Grandfather.
No, no. I was just practicing my technique!
Mommy... Why is my name and your name the same?
It's a secret, isn't it, Grand-Papa?
Yes, it's a secret.
The peaceful scene of which Daemon had dreamed is here.
A dream? Yes, this moment may have been but a fleeting dream.
Even so, it's enough for me, thinks Daemon.
For now, at least, his time of satisfaction has come.
[ THE END ]
The umbrella's colored red because of the red light
I gave it to you and ran away at the intersection
You're always so calm, even if something's happened
I wanted to hold you from behind
I'm not gentle, with a smile on my face
I can't do anything for you and I'm puzzling
I won't love you if you don't extend your arms towards me
I like being a friend for now