After my mother's death, I was
raised at a convent where I was...
...subjected to indescribable disgrace.
During that time my ray of hope was...
...the brief moments I spent with
Andrew, the Prince of this country.
Later my uncle, Duke Dusse,
took me into his care.
Under my uncle's orders I
started the harsh training...
...to become a Love Doll,
the flower of high society.
My uncle's gaze upon me
can be as cold as ice.
But at times, it can
be unbelievably tender.
Several months have passed since
I came to my uncle's manor but...
...I have yet to understand him.
Love Doll Episode 4
Madame, the usual gentleman
is at the back door.
I see. Will you go get Marsha?
Her again!?
The gentleman requests
her so don't make a fuss.
Fine then.
Dear.
What a troublesome customer.
Mr. L, I have readied the usual girl.
Please, go upstairs.
Marsha, Mr. L is coming!
Get yourself ready!
I'm ready whenever.
Jeez!
Don't be such a bitch just because
you have a high paying client!
People are attracted to others of
equal or higher stature, you know.
A client like him
will be of good use.
It's my chance to regain
my elite status.
I'll do anything for that!
What would you like
to do today, Mr. L?
I had an acquaintance make
this. I want to test it out.
Oh what is that?
Get on the bed.
As you wish. Do
whatever pleases you.
It's amazing... that thing...
It's so good...
It's amazing, Mr. L.
Mr. L, I've been satisfied
more than enough.
It's your turn now.
Is your dick hard from
watching me get so hot?
It seems it's not hard yet.
Let me pleasure you with my mouth.
That's enough.
Do not worry. It's not because
you did anything wrong.
Will you come again?
Yes.
Mr. L, you're a great client.
But I've decided to exploit
your secret for better profits.
You hear?
Rachel.
The date for your debut as
a Love Doll has been set.
Yes.
It is a ball with the royal family,
appropriate for Lady Rachel.
I've heard that Prince Andrew
who has graduated from...
...the Royal University
will also be present.
I'm sure it will be
a glamorous ball.
Andrew!?
Andrew will be...
Lady Rachel...
...to fulfill your duty
as a Love Doll...
...I imagine that you will be bedded
with many different types of men.
Tonight's lesson is to
bear in mind...
...the man who will bed a woman
for the first time.
I'll get to see Andrew soon.
I could bear anything in order to...
I've been awaiting you, My Lady.
What's wrong? If you're so shy,
we won't be able to do anything.
S-sorry.
Can you take charge
from here, please?
Yes... you're doing great.
Okay.
It feels so good. It feels strange
down there. Like it's aching.
Please, don't stare.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're still hard.
It feels like you
can keep going.
If we stop here it would be
somewhat unsatisfying, wouldn't it?
If feels wonderful.
You're doing great.
Andrew.
When I think about seeing you soon,
I can endure any kind of hardship.
It's a lesson and I'm having sex
with a man I don't even know but...
...If I think you...
Rachel...
I love you.
Huh?
Andrew!?
Please, don't stop. I want
you to hurry and cum.
Okay.
Oh Andrew.
Excuse me, miss! What do
you think you're doing!?
I don't know how much you
spent to bribe the Madame but...
...it's quite bothersome if
you're going to work here!
Do you understand?
This place isn't for you!
You hear!?
Today will be the last
time you come here!
Rachel!?
Marsha!?
I heard about your house.
How unfortunate.
You say that but you're probably
thinking I deserved it, aren't you?
After all, your bully's
house went bankrupt.
Of course not!
I was really worried.
Well it doesn't matter, whichever way.
I was getting bored of living
in high society anyway.
Marsha.
In any event...
...why are you roaming around here?
I thought your rich uncle was taking
care of you? It's really strange.
Th-that's...
No difference between the rich and
the poor in shady business, I guess.
Oh yes!
My frequent client seems to be
a nobleman of high status but...
...his dick is useless.
I heard it's because of an injury
he sustained in the battlefield.
He may be a noble,
but that's pathetic.
I wonder if you're one of
those pathetic nobles too?
I'm trying to find out some
stuff about this man.
He wears a mask to hide his face
but I don't think that's all he's hiding.
He probably lost his right eye.
His right eye?
Isn't that a great mark?
Do you know of any nobles like that?
If you know something,
tell me. We're old friends.
It would be good of you to tell
me if you know something.
Seems like you're going
through tough times too.
He probably lost his right eye.
Uncle?
Rachel, do you...?
I'm sorry. I...
...have a carriage waiting, so I must go.
I'm glad I saw you. I won't
come here anymore.
I promise.
Uncle is...
...impotent?
Could it be?...
Miss.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The head editor is in the
carriage on top of this bridge.
I see. Thank you.
Hold on a sec!
I don't know why you
asked me to steal...
...the Aristocratic Registry List
from the newspaper company...
...but you've put me
in a real tight spot.
So if the information you're about to
give the editor is some stupid lead...
Rest assured. Your
efforts will be rewarded.
I'll be counting on it.
Sure.
It's interesting
information but...
...without any proof, you
can't expect me to buy it.
I understand.
He's supposed to come
tomorrow night at eleven o'clock.
Take your pictures or
whatever you need then.
Sounds fine. That'll
be the plan then.
I'll pay you afterwards.
Okay.
Anyway, is it true that a girl named
Rachel is at that Duke Dusse's place?
That's certain, but why do you ask?
Oh no reason.
Poor Rachel.
Your uncle is about to be ruined
and everything will fall apart.
All because of me.
You'll be out on the
streets, in the filthy world.
And I will make my return to
the glorious world of the elite.
Lady Rachel.
I have made the arrangements
about the whore.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
Please go ahead.
Yes, my Lady.
Marsha.
Forgive me.
Everything is for my uncle.
For my uncle...
Rachel.
Yes.
I need to talk to you.
Have you discovered...
...my secret?
Secret? W-what are
you talking about?
There's no need to hide it. What
the slut was saying is true.
That's all. Return
to your lessons.
Uncle.
What?
The story that you sustained
an injury in battle must be a lie.
If it was a physical injury...
...you can't expect it to heal
by going to a place like that.
Did you have some sort of mental
shock or did something else happen?
It did, didn't it?
Is that it, Uncle!?
Leave.
Uncle!!
Just get out!!
I don't understand. I don't
understand what you're thinking.
Uncle...
...you're the only relative
I have left in this world.
Please tell me, Uncle.
I...
I'm not afraid to know
what happened to you!
After going through the
lessons of a Love Doll...
...I've nothing left to fear!
No!
Get out!!
Why? Do you hate me, uncle?
That's not it.
Then why?
It's because...
It's because you resemble
my sister too much!!
My mother!?
I was in love with
my own sister.
I was in love with your mother!!
My sister was the most
important part of my existence.
But the day came when
my sister was to marry.
In despair, to distract my mind, I
was intimate with countless women.
But that was only an empty act.
To find a new meaning for my
life, I left for the battlefield.
I learned of my sister's death in a
letter delivered on the battlefield.
Since then, I haven't been
able to get an erection.
Poor uncle.
I'm such a fool.
Of all sins, I was in
love with my own sister!!
W-what are you doing!?
I was able to train as a Love
Doll thanks to you, uncle.
If I can help with the things I've
learned, I'll gladly do anything!
Uncle, please let me help you!
I swear I'll cure you!
I swear.
No!!
How can I be forgiven...
...for having sex with my niece
who's the very image of my sister!
But... Why uncle?
I just want to help you.
Uncle!
Uncle!!
Mother!?
Please, explain. Why is...?
After my sister's death...
I claimed her body and secretly
moved her to this room.
I had her body completely preserved
and gave her eternal beauty.
Rachel.
Forgive me.
Uncle.
As my only relative, you should
be living your life as an aristocrat.
But I have forced you take
the path of a Love Doll...
...knowing it to be one of
the hardest ways of life.
It was because you looked
exactly like my sister.
The strict training as a Love Doll...
...was meant to make
you into my ideal woman.
It was the method I chose to make
you into a reincarnation of my sister.
Uncle.
Forgive me.
There's nothing to forgive.
I'm overjoyed to find out that your
love for my mother was so deep.
You lost the drive to have sex...
...because of your grief over
the loss of your beloved.
You have such a tender heart.
Rachel.
Dusse.
I am not dead...
Come... If you love me from
the bottom of your heart...
...be strong and embrace me.
Sister...
For uncle, my mother holds the
same place as Andrew does for me.
Uncle!!
It feels so good.
It's wonderful.
It's so good, uncle.
Uncle.
What is it?
You're fingers are great but...
...I want your...
But I...
Don't worry, uncle.
Look. It's really hard now uncle.
Uncle, please come in me.
It's in me. Your dick is inside me.
Rachel.
It's amazing! The inside
of my body is getting hot!
It's so wonderfully
numbing... My pussy is...
Uncle.
Rachel... I'm going to...
Oh uncle... Hurry... Hurry...
Uncle.
Tonight I will make my debut as a Love Doll.
I have endured such harsh
training to reach this day.
I am sure my mother and
uncle are watching over me.
No!