In the town where I was born,
balls were held every night.
Lots of ladies wearing beautiful
gowns went to these balls.
They wore colorful dresses
and beautiful jewels.
They danced and they chatted...
And sometimes they fell in love...
I met your father at a ball like this.
Wow!
Do you think when I grow
up I can go to the balls?
Of course Rachel. You'll go.
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Mother...
I was only shedding tears.
I didn't even know what death was.
When I saw my mother's face in death...
I thought she was so beautiful.
Those with dirty minds
must be punished severely.
You can understand,
don't you Rachel?
Please... Forgive me... Please...
No! Stop!
Stop!
What a bad girl! Look how wet
Rachel already is down here!
What a little slut she is.
We'll just have to
punish her even more.
NO!
Please...
Stop...
Love Doll Episode 2
Rachel, I have been looking
so forward to meeting you.
Me too. I've been all alone
ever since my mother died...
I did not know anything
about you until recently.
If I had known...
...I could have arranged for
us to live together earlier.
This gentleman is...
... my uncle.
It must have been hard...
No...
I never want to go
back to the convent.
Even if the training to become
a Love Doll will be painful...
... this is the only place I have now.
I understand George explained
things to you on the way here.
Y... yes.
In order to prepare you for your royal
debut, you'll have to take many lessons.
But after you finish your training you will
have the honor of becoming a Love Doll.
My sister...
...your mother... had the same lessons.
I hear you've inherited your mother's
extraordinary talents and skills.
You are bound to become
the best Love Doll ever.
Love Doll...
What's wrong?
No... It's nothing.
We'll continue.
Yes.
During this lesson, I will tell you about the
rules you will have to follow in this castle.
First, the entire staff of this
castle are your teachers.
You must always listen
to and obey them.
Do not go to bathroom
or bathe by yourself.
Everything will be taken care by the
staff. That's one of your lessons.
Y... yes.
Next, all your lessons must
be attended and respected.
You may not leave the
castle without permission.
And remember...
...if you break these rules,
you will be severely punished.
And I don't want to have
to punish my dear niece.
Never forget that, alright?
Y... yes!
And one more thing...
Never enter the Rose Room of this castle.
Understood?!
Y... yes!
I understand, uncle.
Good!
She's extremely sensitive.
But she has talent.
I agree, but she's no good like this.
As a Love Doll, she will
have to give pleasure
as well. We must see this corrected.
You're absolutely right, sir!
We have everything
ready downstairs sir.
Good!
Done for now! But
Dusse's Castle is so big.
I've only finished
about half of it.
That must be Lady Rachel
who just recently arrived.
Lady Rachel...
Stop...
Uncle...
Open your eyes! Watch
what she's doing to you!
B... But...
All done.
Good.
Rachel, now masturbate for us.
I want to see just how dirty
you can be with yourself.
Lady Rachel your answer?
Y... yes.
Ah! Why do I have to do this?
He's my only relative. Uncle Dusse...
Why?
Nothing has changed
from before I came here.
Rachel, never become
overwhelmed by the pleasure.
You just did it by yourself.
But when you are with a partner you
have to think about their feelings too.
Think about balance and
come at the same time.
Never fake it! People in royal
circles are never fooled by acting.
Control your body!
Always show your partner
you're coming too.
Give them that feeling of conquest!
Now... the lesson continues!
No!
S... S... Stop!
A... Andrew!
Lady Rachel.
Because of the Northern
Revolutionary Army's uprisings
at the borders to the South...
...they were constantly at war.
It was snowing the
day this battle began...
...and that's why it became known
as the Thirty Year War of Winter.
But this is different from the
Thirty Year War of Summer.
Do you understand, Lady Rachel?
If you understand, answer
using your tongue.
Good.
Now review the part
I just went over...
Think about our history as
you finish me off and I come.
You're getting better.
Excellent! Now, stay there
like that. Don't move.
Lady Rachel, swallow it all.
Don't spill a single drop.
Good! Today's lesson is over.
The Rose Room...
What's in there?
Lady Rachel...
I'm coming!
Rachel, you're starving, right?
Well eat!
B... But...
What?
You've only been given water
for the last three days.
Don't be ashamed.
This... this is my meal...
Good. Good girl!
Rachel. This man is very thirsty.
Let him drink your piss!
What?
Are you fine with simply
satisfying your own hunger?
What are you doing?! Pee on him!
Lady Rachel, your answer?
Why? Why am I doing this?
I can't hear you, Rachel.
If there's something else you have
to do besides just peeing, let it out.
You don't have to hold it.
It's his favorite.
Give him all he wants.
Your meal was full of laxatives.
It should be about time now!
No!
Alsid! Alsid! Where are you?
I'm coming!
Lady Rachel hasn't come out recently.
Has something happened to her?
Rachel, you need to talk to me?
Uncle, why are you, my only uncle,
doing these kinds of things to me?
What? That's all?
That's all?!?
If you don't like it, leave!
But if you do leave, what
will you do all by yourself?
I... I...
I know all about what you
were doing at the convent.
Wherever you go,
wherever you run to...
...you'll still be a woman who
can't live without sexual pleasure.
You were born to
be a slave to sex.
No...
I don't lie.
I'm more concerned about
your happiness than anyone.
Once you decide to
embrace the sexual world...
...you won't have to be some
whore on a street corner.
You'll become a Love Doll
and live as a flower of royalty.
That's the only way
you'll ever be happy.
No! Stop!
STOP!!!
Uncle!
Is this...
... another lesson?
So you finally feel like doing it!
She wants to suck it.
More! More! Please! I want more!
She's so fucking horny!
It's like she's sucking
me off down here too!
OH! This is... This is...
AWESOME!
Excellent!
Today, we're going to get a
new party dress made for you.
Party? You mean my
royal debut is coming up?
I guess you could call it a party.
Henry holds a gathering
at his castle every month.
This will serve as your trial debut.
It can't be...
That... That was Andrew
and Beth. Why... are they...?
Lady Rachel?
Lady Rachel!
Alsid, we start early
again tomorrow.
See you!
Is that...?
You're Lady Rachel, right?
And you are...?
I'm the gardener, Alsid.
Alsid...
Lady Rachel, is something wrong?
I'm sorry. I saw you were crying.
If you don't mind, would
you like to tell me about it?
Dusse?
George, I've just
heard about Andrew.
This will be a good
opportunity for us.
I can't take it anymore.
I hate everything.
Please calm down,
Lady Rachel. Calm down.
Lady Rachel, I can only imagine what kind
of things must go on inside the castle.
You should do whatever
Dusse asks of you.
That's the best thing you
can do right now I think.
Be a little more patient.
Please don't cry.
Show me that beautiful smile!
I've watched you from the garden.
I like the bright Lady Rachel.
I want to help you.
Alsid...
This is absolutely forbidden.
Would you like me to retrieve her?
No. Let see how this plays out. I want
to see the results of all our lessons.
I never thought Lady Rachel
would do this for me...
I... I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Please help me forget everything.
Lady Rachel!
That's it.
Good Rachel. Free yourself
of your inhibitions.
But get him excited too. Keep
him satisfied until the very end.
You are definitely the one!
Alsid...
I've been waiting for you, Rachel.
What happened to your clothes?
Th... this is...
Don't make excuses!
You broke the rules.
You have to be punished.
I was depressed and he
was nice to me and...
Uncle! I won't do it again.
It was just a little mistake.
Of course that gardener will
have to take responsibility.
But I guess he already has...
You can't mean...
It's so cold! It feels so good...
No! Stay away!
Don't worry. I won't
kill my darling niece.
They've been very well
trained... given special training.
This is your punishment
for breaking the rules.
But still in the spirit of your lessons...
No... NO!!