Mommy, tell me that story again?
The story about the royal ball?
Yeah.
You really like that story?
That's where you and
daddy first met, right?
I wanna go to the
castle when I get bigger.
Rachel, you want
to be a princess?
No! I wanna go to the royal ball
and meet a man like daddy.
Mom... can I go to the royal ball?
Rachel, honey...
You're going to be
a beautiful woman.
But I don't think you should
go to the royal ball.
Why not...?
Someone might step on you
with their pointy high heels.
Did someone step on you?
I was the one who stepped on somebody.
I stepped on your father quite a few times.
Was daddy mad?
No.
I wasn't really well educated
and I couldn't dance but...
...I put on a pretty dress
and went to the ball anyway.
I just wanted to run
far away from there.
But your father helped
me through to the end.
His feet were so swollen though.
Daddy's so wonderful!
Yes, he is.
I wanna get married with
someone just like daddy.
Oh, no! I feel sorry for your groom!
Rachel, look! You're already
ready for a bigger size.
Look how big this one is.
The Bishop will be pleased.
Rachel, come with us.
No! I want to go home
with my mommy.
Your home is with us now.
No!
Mother! Mother!
Your mother has passed away!
Your mother is gone now.
No! Mother! Mother!
At first we could barely
even fit a finger in you.
But look at you now. You love
taking big ones like this, don't you.
You're a little slut now, Rachel.
Look how wet you get.
You're going to really enjoy this.
And it's too bad you'll never
be able to escape from here.
But we're finding your
education quite rewarding!
Love Doll Episode 1
We're gonna be late.
Rachel!
Rachel, what are you doing?
Hurry up, you'll be late.
Beth!
Already? But I have to
bring this to the altar.
I'll take it for you.
You get to class, okay?
Are you sure?
Yeah, don't worry. That's
what roommates are for.
Beth...
Sister Eva, how's
Rachel's education coming?
She's still just beginning.
I'm sure she'll be turning
men's heads someday.
Well, now I'm getting jealous.
Eva...
You are so amazing.
Be sure to educate her
in all your techniques.
"...and people began gathering
upon hearing the noise. Then
the apostles began to speak..."
"...using the language of the villagers. The
people looked on silently, as if in shock."
"They became suspicious and asked
'They are all Gallarian, aren't they?"
"However, they speak to us in our own
language. How do you explain this?"'
"One among us is a Paltenian and..."
Mother! Mother?
Where are you?
Rachel!
Rachel, look up.
Rachel, stand up!
Yes.
We're still in class here. If
you have something on your
mind, think about it later.
You were thinking
about men, weren't you?
N... no!
I think I'm partly
to blame, ma'am.
What do you mean, Marsha?
She was affected by
my perfect reading.
She probably heard the words
I was reading from the Bible...
...and thought that God
was speaking to her.
She's right. I'm moved by her reading.
You're right. It's so lovely.
I guess I have no choice.
Rachel, I will forgive you
this time, thanks to Marsha.
You can sit down now.
Yes.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to startle you.
I was walking in the woods
and I heard you singing...
No, I...
Are you alright?
Did you hurt yourself?
Ah... No. Thank you so much.
I'm sorry for coming
up from behind you.
You're bleeding.
Oh, it's nothing.
Th... thank you.
Can we meet again
here tomorrow?
I have to wash this and
give it back to you.
OK.
And I'd like to know your name.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I... I'm Rachel.
I'm Andrew.
You live in the convent, right?
I live near here.
Maybe we can keep meeting?
I'm sorry. I forgot...
...you're not supposed
to talk to strangers.
...right?
Ah... No.
I'm sure we can
see each other again.
Really?!
That's great.
I don't often get a chance to
meet girls who fall from trees.
Oh, Andrew, you're terrible.
I'm sorry.
So, I'll wait for you here
tomorrow at this time.
Okay. And I'll come down
from the tree again.
I'll bring a big cushion and
wait for you, Princess.
No.
Oh, here you are, Rachel.
I need to talk to you.
Do you have a few minutes?
Don't worry. It won't take too long.
As long as you
promise to behave!
No!
Please stop!
Why do always treat
me like an enemy?
Phew! What a revolting smell!
You have the same smell.
The smell of a whore!
Did you meet Andrew
in the woods today?
Trying to seduce Andrew
with your foul pussy?
Don't you think that's
being rude to him?
An elegant woman like me
would be perfect for Andrew.
Do you understand?
I am going to marry Andrew
and be Princess of this land.
The Prince with a whore?!
I don't think so!
Andrew is the Prince of the Castle?!
You should remember
what your lot in life is.
It would be so easy for
me to get rid of you.
Have you forgotten that the
only reason you're here...
...is because of the mercy of the church?
Is this big enough for you?
Andrew is... the Prince?!
Look at her. She came with a vase.
I can't believe her.
Andrew...
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't know
anyone was down there.
Rachel!
How horrible!
Thank you, Beth.
I'm fine.
Rachel...
Rachel, it's time for your lesson.
Come up here.
Yes.
Now turn around, get on your
knees and show me your ass.
Yes.
We haven't even begun yet
and you're already wet.
You can take it really deep, can't you?
But you have yet to open
your mind and enjoy all this.
Don't you like these nightly lessons?
Once you open your mind,
you'll enjoy your night life more.
You never know when
all this is going to end.
It would be much easier if you just
learned to accept this and enjoy it.
Here's a little something to
help build your courage.
It will also allow you to free
your mind of any inhibitions.
No!
No! I can't stop.
It's alright. There's nothing
to be ashamed about.
How does it feel? It feels good
peeing freely in the open, no?
Here. What do you want next? You want
this? You're dying for some cock, right?
You want to reach out and
grab it, don't you, Rachel?
Your dick...
Oh, Rachel! Good, isn't it?
You like the taste?
Take your time and enjoy it.
I love your cock!
Good.
I'm going to come, Rachel.
Come on me.
Blow a big load...
More! I want more cock.
Stick it in me.
You really are a slut.
Just as I expected.
Back then, it was easy to lie and
tell you it was all your imagination...
But until today, you've
suppressed the excitement.
...you felt that day you
saw sex for the first time.
That day... when you
first saw intercourse...
...bare flesh on flesh...
You'd never heard a women's
voice scream in erotic bliss...
You've been waiting for this day with
fear but also secret anticipation...
...waiting to enjoy this
pleasure with all your heart.
Marsha!
Where have you been
at this time of night?
Is it true you were with the Bishop?
I don't care what you're
doing with old men but...
...I don't want a slut like you to go
anywhere near my Andrew ever again.
Rachel?
Rachel!
What happened to you,
Rachel?! Rachel?
Your hair...
Good morning, Beth.
Is something wrong?
Wrong?! Your hair...
Ah... this...?
It's nothing really...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Rachel.
Beth?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Beth... what are you sorry for?
I... I knew about all this, Rachel.
I knew you were in trouble.
But I was so scared... I couldn't
do anything to help you.
Don't cry, Beth.
Thank you.
Rachel!
You have such big breasts, Beth!
No... I'm embarrassed.
Beth... You're wet.
Ah... Don't tease me!
See? I can put my finger in you.
Ouch! Rachel, it hurts.
Don't worry. I'll go slow.
Look how far in you I can go.
Ah... ah... It's in!
Beth, I know it feels good. You're
wet. And look how swollen your clit is!
Beth... do it to me now!
But...
Let's come together, Beth.
Rachel...
Rachel, you're so loose.
Ah... Beth, it feels so good!
So, what do you think, Rachel?
Wow! It looks great, Beth!
You think so?
Really! It looks much better than before!
Thank you, Rachel!
For forgiving me.
No, Beth. You don't have to say that.
Because... I... I...
You cry so easily, Beth.
Because... because...
I'm lucky to have a friend
like you to cry for me.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you, Beth. I'm going to
be more careful from now on.
I don't want you to worry
about me anymore.
Your always such a
sweet fuck, Rachel!
This soft and supple skin...
Ah... these sweet lips...
You'll be a woman who
can win any king's heart.
I'll make sure of that.
Rachel... today I want
you to use your hands...
Use your hands to make me come...
Come... come a lot...
Come all over me!
Good morning.
Hey, you got your hair cut.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Andrew, I... I...
I'm sorry. I didn't
bring a good cushion.
I'm glad I caught you
before you climbed up.
You won't need to use
this scarf again today.
Andrew... I'm sorry. I...
Rachel, I didn't come
to see a sad face today.
I came to see your sweet smile.
Oh, yeah! Can you come with me?
Andrew!
Rachel, hold the basket.
These look good.
Try one.
Delicious!
So, the princess approves
of the grapes I grew myself?
Wow! You grew these grapes!?
I didn't know that princes...
You know? I... I...
Please, just call me Andrew.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
Rachel, this is for you.
Really? But...
Take it.
I... I can't...
It looks good on you.
It's Rachel. You asked for me?
Come in.
Rachel, this gentleman has
brought very good news for you.
For me?
Yes.
You must be Lady Rachel. I
have come to take you with me.
What?
Rachel?
You are... Andrew, right?
You must be Beth, Rachel's friend.
I've heard a lot about you.
Andrew...
Rachel is...
Goodbye, Andrew.
This is from Rachel.
Huh? Wait!
Andrew... It's so hard to say
good-bye to you like this.
Rachel...
When you read this letter,
I will already be on a train.
I'm going to live with my uncle, Duke
Dusse, my dead mother's brother.
I'll never forget the day we first met and
the times we spent in the grape fields.
It is so painful for me to leave you.
Don't worry, Andrew. I've heard that
everyone in his castle is very nice.
I hope to surprise you by being a
lovely lady the next time we meet.
Andrew... can you wait for
me until that day comes?
Rachel?
Y... Yes.
This was made specially for you, Rachel.
It will be a long trip and
this will help you relax.
Duke Dusse wants you to become the
fairest of maidens as quickly as possible.
He asked that I begin your lessons
on becoming royalty immediately.
Is this okay with you, Rachel?
Yes.
Good. Why don't we begin by helping
you change into these clothes
we've prepared for you.
No! What are you doing?! STOP!
Here.
You will follow the program the
master has arranged for you.
These lessons were created to help
prepare you for your royal debut.
They will help you become the flower
of the royal circles... the Love Doll.
Love... Doll??!
Well... please start with your own finger.
It can't be!
These terrible things will continue?
Forget everything you knew before.
The good memories and the bad...
Leave all that behind you now...
Andrew!
You will forget everything and
give your life to Duke Dusse.
Andrew!
Excuse me.
Master, I brought you a drink.
Is something wrong, Master?
You look rather happy.
Is it that obvious, Carol?
I never knew I had such
a sweet, young niece.
Yes, she's really cute!
I want you to help
out with her, Carol.
Oh, I will be more than
happy to help, Master.
This is just the beginning,
Rachel. It all starts now.