I can't believe what's happened
to my life!
I can't believe my life
has changed so dramatically.
In just a few weeks...
My name is Jyun Amanuma.
My father relocated overseas for his job,
and also remarried.
I decided it would be best for me
to remain in Japan.
Since my father sold the house,
he rented an apartment for me.
I'm still going to school, and working.
MANAGER'S OFFICE
I'm back! Hey, Sumire!
I'm back from the store!
Jyun, you're back early!
I'm sorry, I didn't know
you were getting dressed!
Don't worry about it,
it doesn't bother me.
Come on inside.
Yes, yes.
Everything is fine.
It would be so cool to have sex with her.
If I could just have sex with her.
She is the owner
of the apartment complex.
I was originally going to just rent
a room here, but...
somehow, I ended up being roped
into becoming...
the assistant manager.
Can you get that?
Sure.
You must be the new assistant manager!
Yes.
Rei, good morning!
Good morning, Ms. Sumire!
Good morning?
It's almost nighttime.
Jyun is our new assistant manager.
I'll have him deliver your package later.
All right, nice meeting you Jyun!
Have a good night!
You too!
Can you deliver what's on this list
to her apartment?
Sure.
Room number 203.
I hear something...
from inside here.
The door's not locked, that's not safe.
I'll just leave the package right here
and leave.
I really should not be doing this.
I'm just curious.
Your cock is rock hard and ready.
Awesome blow job, Rei.
I'm about to come.
Not yet!
Don't you want your money's worth?
Holy shit!
I want to fuck you right now!
All right then. I'll do this
and squeeze hard just like this.
Shit, Put it in right now!
I really like teasing your cock
with my wet pussy.
Damn, you're soaking wet!
Yeah, I love it!
Rei!
Damn Baby!
Fuck!
I'm coming!
I have to get back.
You're a peeping tom.
Naughty, bad, boy.
Sumire!
I need to explain to you what this place is
about, because you need to know.
Rather than start unpacking...
it's really important that you know.
Sumire!
This is a sex service apartment complex.
Sex service?
Apartment?
Are you surprised?
Fetish.
Role playing...
S and M, bondage...
it's all available.
All the girls do this during their spare time.
They work their jobs during the day.
At night, they run their sex business
out of their apartments.
I only collect rent, and nothing more.
Touch me here.
Sumire!
Squeeze and massage them.
Yes!
I had such a hard time finding an assistant!
That feels good!
We're open 24 hours a day, so...
it's really helpful
that you are able to work...
as my assistant manager after school.
Do you like it so far?
Relax and enjoy yourself!
Wow!
She's dripping right through her panties.
He's ready to play!
I love them young.
Yes! Jyun, I love sex.
I make it a point to control my sex drive!
But sometimes, I can't control it.
And I become insatiable.
Fuck me.
Right now! I want your cock!
Yes, just like that.
Sumire, your pussy's squeezing me...
Yes, your lock fits my key,
yes, come for me!
Jyun!
You know, every occupied residence...
has a key, right?
Sure.
Just like people.
People lock up their heart and desires.
The girls that live here, too.
They do this simply
because they love sex...
but they keep it a secret.
You cannot tell anybody
about what goes on here.
You can't break this rule.
You can keep quiet, right?
Yes.
That was my first day
as the assistant apartment manager.
She is so hot.
She's coming!
There she is.
Goddamn!
What a babe!
Good afternoon!
Welcome to Mariner's!
Wow, she's cute!
Now I see why all the guys
come here to check her out.
She's got one hell of a body.
She must wear at least a D cup bra!
She's got such a tight little waist...
and a fantastic ass, too.
I'm back!
I'm sorry I'm late, this is for you!
A pie from Mariner's!
You got this just for me?
Actually, my friends wanted to show me
this really cute waitress there.
So they dragged me after school.
So was she prettier than me?
Well, no, I didn't mean it like that at all.
I'm coming!
What?
Wait, didn't I just see you
at the restaurant?
So Marina was the hot waitress
you went to see...
that works at Mariner's.
Well...
I heard I have a package
waiting here for me?
Yes. Jyun, please carry it for her.
You're the apartment manager!
Thank you for carrying this for me.
I'm just doing my job.
Could you carry it to my room?
Sure!
I didn't know Marina lived here!
Wait.
That means that she...
services clients here!
My god, are all these all uniforms
from restaurants?
Yeah.
Wow!
These uniforms are all brand new.
Do you like this one?
It's from a roller blade cafe, special order.
Shit, she looks so hot in that outfit!
I thought the smallest size would fit right,
but it's a bit tight on me.
I think it's kind of sexy, though.
Yes...
I'm getting really horny now.
I'm feeling kind of horny myself...
and you're hard already.
I'm wearing my roller blades, but I can tell.
I'm going to go back to the office.
You can't, I'm just dying
for a good fuck now!
Yes, it's big!
Don't. Marina.
Marina!
I love the way you taste.
Marina, you're really good!
Yeah!
It's a nice, big load,
and it's really yummy!
Don't think I'm done with you yet!
What?
See, my Mariner's uniform.
I know you really like it.
I like...
I saw you...
and your friends, staring at me
with raging hard-ons...
wanting to fuck me in my sexy uniform.
I can explain.
I like it, really.
Actually, it really excites me a lot.
Sometimes, I don't wear panties to work...
and see if anyone can catch a glimpse
of me without my underwear...
Was I wearing panties
at work today? Guess?
I don't...
I wasn't wearing any.
I wasn't wearing my bra, either.
Sumire saw my exhibitionist streak...
when she saw me at another store
I used to work at.
She recruited me.
That's why you live here.
During the day, I work at different
restaurants and collect uniforms.
After my day job...
I work at home.
I think uniforms are sexier
than being just naked...
My pussy is quivering so hard right now.
Yeah, I can feel that.
Yeah!
Fuck me, harder and rougher!
I love fucking!
I want it deep!
Fuck me, doggy style.
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
Let's come together!
I've got to ask, did you get all these
uniforms from work?
No, I've bought a lot of them.
I spend the money I make here
to buy more uniforms for me.
I really enjoy working
in the service industry...
whether it's serving food
or really hot sex!
Jyun, I need you to come back
to the office.
That's right!
Marina, my assistant is working right now.
Can't he stay longer?
The train during rush hour sucks.
No!
Her tits are pressing against me,
shit, I don't want a hard-on.
Damn it!
I don't want to have an erection,
but I can't help it.
It's just that your large,
beautiful breasts...
are pressing against me.
You don't have any fractures
or broken bones.
I'll give you some ointment
for the time being.
Okay.
Come back and see me
if the pain continues after 5 days.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It really was an accident!
Hi. I didn't know you were a nurse.
I'll pay for your exam today,
I feel so bad about this!
No, really don't, it's okay.
Ms. Aihara, this way.
Yes!
So, the pretty nurse's
last name is Aihara!
Maybe this is the start of something.
What is it, Doctor Aihara.
Please show me.
In this office?
I want to make sure
that your following my orders.
I'm following your orders, Saki.
Wait, you're supposed to call me Doctor
when I'm wearing my coat.
So you won't forget again.
Jyun Amanuma, I can't believe
he lives at this address.
Just maybe.
Looks painful!
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll still be able to work.
I can walk just fine.
Okay.
If you need to go back to the hospital...
It's not that bad of an injury!
Hey now, I'm just worried about your foot,
all right?
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to
laugh, but...
Hello, Manager's office.
A disinfection container?
Yes, we have one.
What else?
Sumire has a really unique personality.
Yes, all right then.
She can be very professional,
but she's also very spontaneous.
She's got such a beautiful body.
I think I'm falling in love.
Can you deliver these to room 302?
Hey, Jyun, are you listening?
Yes.
I'll go right now.
He's such a good assistant.
I want to ask Sumire out.
A date with her would be so cool!
But one of us has to attend
the office at all times.
Aihara?
Thank you, can you carry it inside?
Wait, you're my doctor!
Don't ask me any weird questions.
Let's just say I get to do things here
that I can't at the hospital.
Doctor, the room is ready now...
They must be sisters.
I want to apologize for my sister.
I do want to repay you!
She will need you to remove all clothing
and just wear the gown.
Why?
Just follow the doctor's directions.
What?
I injured my foot today...
and this does not seem
like a foot exam.
No, this is not a foot exam.
Here, I give special kind of exams.
You know that, Mr. Manager!
No!
Why do I need a rectal exam?
You can feel my fingers
moving inside you, right?
It's kind of gross...
and embarrassing, too.
Actually, I'm giving you
a legitimate prostate exam right now.
And if I massage your prostate...
Doesn't it feel good?
You can ejaculate without coming!
You're really sensitive down here.
Miki, please clean him up.
Me?
You said he might be
the one to help you?
So go on.
Yes.
Don't close your eyes like that!
Continue!
Yes, I'm sorry!
See, you really can do it, Miki.
Make sure to lick him clean
so he's spotless.
You need to know
what a man really tastes like.
I like it!
See, it's not scary, right?
Now, it's your turn to please my sister!
But, I can't unless she wants me to.
You're her treatment, mister.
She can't be a nurse
and be afraid of a penis.
So I make her wear this
so she'll be used to them more...
She's worked so hard to become a nurse.
She was still afraid
of the real thing, until...
the day she felt your erection
during the rush hour commute.
I see.
Maybe you can help her overcome
her fear of the penis.
I guess, if that's the case.
I feel it!
I like it!
You feel good.
I'm coming!
Thank you, that was great!
All right.
There's one more thing left.
What are you going to do?
No please, not that!
I'm back.
Thank you very much.
So Jyun, take off your pants.
I want to see something.
This is an order.
So they did shave you down there,
it's so smooth, like a baby's.
So cute!
Hey, come on,
don't make fun of me, all right?
He's awake!
Sumire!
I am happy to be the assistant
manager here.
Can I find true love,
or is sex the only thing I can ask for...
from the owner
of this apartment building?
Either way, I want to stay here
with Sumire.
Jyun, yes, like that, good!
More!