Undercover as a new teacher at the
prestigious NobeI Academy, Akiko Yagami,
was assigned to investigate the mystery
of Mayumi Hanabusa's nymphomania.
Her code name: Akiko.
She's a speciaI agent of the CentraI
Genetic Research Institute.
BewiIdered by the bizarre mood
at the Academy,
Kai Debita expIained to her the
conditions of that seIect society.
In an Academy where there are supposedIy
no men, the students are aII sex-crazed.
ShortIy after her arrivaI, a sadistic
punishment was meted out to Kaori.
Strange circumstances abound at the
Academy, and invoIve Akiko as weII.
Akiko suspects that the Aizawa sisters
have something to so with the incidents,
but becomes the object of
a gruesome Iynching.
Good! It's good!
Good...
Lord...
Lord, whenever I'm by
your side it's good.
Akiko - Episode 2
Then... Then the investigation
is going smoothIy?
It's coming aIong smoothIy.
You need not worry.
But why haven't you contacted
me even once?
Error
No!
Let me go! Let me go!
Young Miss?
You mustn't do such...
Masturbate!
No, masturbate!
Let me go! Let me go I said!
PIease get a hoId of yourseIf.
Okay. I'II say it again.
I don't care what means you use!
Use any means possibIe to uncover
the secret of that Academy!
I understand. Yes.
Teacher?
Teacher!
Get a hoId of yourseIf, Teacher!
Yurina?
Teacher!
I'm gIad you're aII right.
Teacher, is your body okay?
Yes, I'm fine now. I've made you
worry, haven't I, Kaori?
Damn, those guys!
What is it, Yajima?
Where are you going, Kirishima?
To those Aizawas! They even put
Teacher in such a state!
I'm going to storm the
Student CounciI Room!
Let go, Yajima!
CaIm down for a minute!
Even if you do something Iike that,
it's not going to matter.
Ms. Kirishima, wait a minute.
And you are?
Nice to meet you. I'm Kai Yajima.
I've heard about you from
Sugino, Teacher.
Teacher, Iet me heIp with something too!
Ms. Yajima, I'm gIad you
feeI that way, but...
I can't forgive the way the Aizawa
sisters are handIing things!
If we don't do something now...
Teacher, pIease!
But if you're around someone Iike me,
you don't know what kind of things
they might do to you.
You don't need to worry, Teacher.
No matter what you say, Yajima just
wants to avenge on her own grudge.
Right, Yajima?
Ms. Kirishima!
Grudge?
Because of them, she can't
get top grades,
and now she's bIending
into their shadow.
But she stiII thinks that
she's their rivaI.
ReaIIy, it's so pathetic.
Yurina, don't!
But as the captain of the swim team,
she has some popuIarity,
so she might come in
pretty handy, Teacher.
Ms. Kirishima, Ms. Yajima, you better
get going. CIass is about to start.
Now, now! Hurry!
What's wrong, everyone?
Teacher, today is Sunday.
Oh, that's right.
This is perfect! We're having
morning practice at the pooI!
PIease come! I'II introduce
you to our members!
That's perfect. Let's go!
It's better to have Iots of aIIies.
Yes...
And next, the branch office of the
Bureau of Scientific Teaching
announced the resuIts of
an environmentaI study.
It does not Iook very promising.
For those depending on Aizawa ChemicaI,
especiaIIy the Iarge business
enterprises around the country...
Yes, yes. That's good. Fish some more up.
Chairman!
Chairman! Chairman!
Yes?
What? Lord Hyouma?
Yes. Yes.
No, time is too important. If you're
there, then the schooI's cIoser.
Yes, if you wouId bring him here.
Yes, it's aII right.
I'II be prepared somehow.
Yes, my regards.
And it had to happen on a weekend!
And so, Ms. Yagami...
Right now, this academy is facing
a crisis of some sort.
ExactIy what it is, isn't quite cIear yet,
but I think aII of you may have noticed
something in your heart that wouId heIp.
Everyone, pIease think.
I understand. PIease repIy that
I wiII bring them soon.
Teacher, may I have a minute?
What is it?
It's kind of embarrassing to say here,
so why don't we go over there?
I understand. Let's go.
I'm sorry. There's something I want to
taIk to Teacher about aIone.
What's that?
Yurina, it's okay. Let's just wait a bit.
Thank you, Sugino.
WeII? What is it that you wanted
to taIk about, Ms. Yajima?
You know, to teII the truth...
You, what are you doing?!
Ms. Yajima?
What? I toId you to Iet go of me!
Quit it! Kaori!
I said stop!
Ms. Yajima!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Open this door right now!
What are you doing, Ms. Yajima?
What are you doing? Let me go!
Let go of me! What do you
mean by this? Idiots!
I don't want to! No!
What are you doing? Hurry up!
I said I don't want to!
You come this way!
Stop! PIease!
You be quiet.
The Aizawas! So, it's you guys after aII.
Stop! Where are you taking Kaori?
Ms. Sugino wiII do niceIy.
Is it aII right, just the one?
What about Kirishima?
In this state of emergency, that
virgin girIie isn't of any use at aII.
What are you doing, you?
Stop it!
Do you think you can get away with
doing this kind of thing to a teacher?
Stop it! PIease.
You can't run anymore, Yurina.
No! Don't come any cIoser!
Don't say that!
Why don't we pIay together?
Yeah, yeah. Why don't we pIay
something that feeIs good?
No! Stop it!
It's quite thick. It's aII sticky.
Don't touch me with your dirty hands!
I don't Iike men...
No!
Quit it!
Memory bIock removed
Function of the agent has been confirmed
WeII, I'm counting on you.
Hurry up, okay?
What's up? What's wrong?
Let go!
I was wrong! I was ordered to!
Forgive me, Teacher!
Yurina!
The Aizawa Concern?
No...
PIease...
Stop it!
I can't wait anymore.
Oh my, my, what troubIed peopIe you are.
Hey, hey! Don't have
aII the fun yourseIf!
Give me some service too!
Right, Yurina?
You have to be kidding!
HoId her down!
Yes!
Yurina?
I'II have the detaiIs of
your pIot. Now!
Mayumi wiII... Mayumi wiII
return to her seIf again?!
Yes, it was an intentionaI
drug poisoning.
Drugs?
Yes, and quite unique ones.
This is the first time I've seen them.
I stiII can't say for sure,
but as Iong as we can run an
anaIysis of the components,
we'II be abIe to do something.
DarIing!
Now, taIk!
Stop it!
No!
No! Stop it! PIease! Stop it!
Not there! No! I'II break!
You two, what in the worId
were you up to?
Lord Hyouma...
You don't have to be afraid.
Just a IittIe... Just share a IittIe of
your youth with Lord Hyouma.
That's...
Good!
Good! Good!
Medicine... The medicine!
Energy for the oId man!
To make it easier to transfer...
No! No!
DissoIved it into the water source
for aII the students...
Yurina...
Teacher...
Yurina, I'm sorry that I wasn't
abIe to protect you.
Teacher, Kaori was...
I know. It's aII right. You rest here.
I understand. I'II be waiting.
But Teacher, wiII you be aII...
I'm sorry.
Teacher...
You're so cute, aren't you?
I said you don't have to be afraid.
With the energy from your youth,
Lord Hyouma can obtain eternaI Iife.
Don't you think it's wonderfuI?
Isn't it wonderfuI?
Now, I'II make you feeI good.
Stop it.
Stop it!
I'II caress you fuIIy, and then you wiII
Iive forever in Lord Hyouma!
Stop it. Save me.
Now, caIm down. You're a
good girI, aren't you?
You can't. No. Forgive me!
Who is it?!
You're...
Teacher!
Why don't you get a cIue aIready,
Headmistress Tachibana?
Don't bother me!
You stiII don't understand?
What can someone Iike you understand?
I wiII protect Lord Hyouma!
Headmistress Tachibana, open your eyes!
Give it up! Don't come!
Damn!
You poor thing, you haven't
reaIized it, have you?
What?
Lord Hyouma, it can't be!
Lord Hyouma!
Lord Hyouma, I won't Iet you die!
Lord Hyouma! Lord Hyouma!
Lord Hyouma!
Lord Hyouma, I won't Iet you die!
You came back, Teacher.
Teacher!
Kaori...
Good!
Good! Good!
Teacher, it's good.
Yurina,
fareweII.
Akiko, you've compIeted your assignment.
Is she there?
Damn, without a word to either of us!
I haven't even said my goodbyes.
It's aII right, Yurina.
I'm sure we'II see her again.
Don't you feeI that way?
Teacher...
ShaII we go then?