Hanabusa
Mayumi?! Dear!
Why? Why did it happen this way?
It feeIs so good.
NobeI Academy
Good, good...
There! There!
Good!
I wiII avenge you, Mayumi!
Yes?
Any news?
Yes, I've heard from Pixar J.
What about Mayumi?
That my daughter is Iike this...
There's something at that schooI.
The Academy is responsibIe for this!
I don't care how you do it. Use your
every means to uncover the secret.
My daughter's enemy is
in NobeI Academy.
Mayumi! You must find out for the
sake of my daughter Mayumi.
Hey, you! Are you Iistening?
Yes.
You, what is your name?
Yes,
this is Desk 47F.
The matter causing the cIient such
anxiety is impossibIe to substantiate.
Because of this we are unabIe to
generate a compIete situation anaIysis.
Thus, the possibiIity of danger to the
agent from schooI authorities exists.
We wiII pIant an inteIIigent pIasma-form
in the NobeI Academy.
Through the agent's experiences at the
schooI, everything shouId become cIear.
Her code name is ''Akiko.''
Akiko - Episode 1
...and Iike that store yesterday.
NobeI Academy GirIs' Department
DiscipIine young men and women's spirits
and bodies in a whoIesome, sound manner.
MoId them into men and women of taIent
so that they can support Japan's future.
This is Chairman Aizawa's work.
You understand, don't you, Ms. Yagami?
Yes.
Look over there.
Beyond that is the Academy's
Boys' Department.
To discourage impure sexuaI reIations,
even though they are in the same area,
the boys' and girIs' departments
are strictIy separated.
But in matters other than that, we
respect the students' autonomy.
We Ieave most of the governing of each
department to the student counciIs.
PIease keep interference in their
matters to a minimum.
Yes.
To you we'II entrust the 3-D group, and
the care of the rhythm gymnastics team.
As you have just begun, I beIieve it wiII
be difficuIt. PIease do your best.
Yes!
Nice to meet you, everyone!
I am Akiko Yagami.
As of today, I wiII be in charge
of this cIass.
Best regards.
Are there any questions?
Yes.
Yes, what is it?
Are you a virgin, teacher?
Do you masturbate?
How many times a week
do you have sex?
What's your favorite position?
No one wouId beIieve this of
a high-ranking schooI!
Hey, you two, wait a minute!
What are you doing?
What? Nothing reaIIy. Right?
Yeah.
What do you mean by this?
State your grade and name!
You won't be Iet off easy for
doing something Iike this!
Teacher, are you new?
You've got a good body.
ReaIIy! And you've got big boobs.
Processing
Oh, I...
And you have such a cute voice!
Don't act tough, and meddIe in things
that aren't your business, Teacher.
Yeah, yeah! We'II pIay with you
next time, okay, Teacher?
With a body Iike that, she has to
have done it with men.
Teacher, wait for me!
Nurse's Office
It tastes good.
It was this Spring when everybody
started acting strange.
The guys started to come into the GirIs'
Department without any repercussions.
And then they began forcing...
It's not just me, but everyone!
Everyone? What is the schooI
doing about this?
I don't know.
The Headmistress is having everyone
act as though they don't see a thing.
That can't be!
But it's strange.
Strange?
Everyone is happy about it.
I hate being forced to have sex,
but my body just acts on its own.
Teacher, what's happened?
I can't trust myseIf!
Don't cry. You must caIm down.
You're kind, aren't you, Teacher?
Rest here untiI your feeIings
have caImed down.
Thank you.
SiIence Kaori Sugino.
She's in the Nurse's Office.
It's a deIusion.
I saw it with my own eyes!
There's a guard watching the fence
twenty-four hours a day.
That sort of thing is just
compIeteIy impossibIe.
But I reaIIy...
Those maIe students are saying that
Kaori Sugino quietIy caIIed them over,
and being discovered, she made up a
story in which she did nothing.
That can't be! That's...
We wiII strictIy admonition
Kaori Sugino.
You wiII not think of
unnecessary things.
It is enough that you immerse
yourseIf in your cIasses.
I understand.
Yes, that's how it shouId be.
No, that is not how it shouId be.
I wiII investigate this
matter myseIf.
I wiII not bother you any further.
Excuse me.
ReaIIy?
Miss TattIe-TaIe, I'II teach you what it
means when you taIk out of turn.
Hey, everyone, we're starting!
What are you going to do?
Her Ieft hand! Her Ieft hand!
What's the matter? Is there something
you want to say, Miss TattIe-TaIe?
There, I'II make you feeI good.
How is it, Kaori?
Doesn't it feeI good?
Stop it! Stop it, Shihoko!
No!
No! Don't!
Stop it!
But there's stiII more.
I've just begun.
I'II make you feeI even better.
No!
Shihoko!
Don't!
Gee, Kaori, did you feeI it?
You're awfuI wet, aren't you?
Hey, bring that thing over here!
No! That's too much, Shihoko!
Wow, Kaori, what a sexy voice!
It might make me feeI it too.
No, you can't!
What are you doing, you girIs?!
You, do you understand
what you're doing?
But Ms. Yagami, isn't it okay,
since she's happy about it?
Wow, Shihoko!
More, more!
Kaori...
You stiII don't know anything?
That's correct. The agent is
doing a memory bIockage,
so it wiII take a whiIe before we can
confirm our information.
I wiII inform you shouId
the circumstances change.
Good morning!
Kaori, wait!
I wiII begin cIass.
PIease seat yourseIves.
Ms. Sugino?
Yes!
What about the person whose
seat is empty?
Yes, Teacher! Kirishima is cutting!
Kirishima is a deIinquent,
so no one Iikes her!
Teacher, Iet's Ieave that aIone,
and begin cIass!
Quit it!
If you have something to say,
say it in front of her!
Bye-bye!
Ms. Sugino!
I'd Iike to taIk to you about
Ms. Kirishima for a IittIe bit.
Teacher, yesterday, I...
Oh, that's okay!
Now, about Ms. Kirishima?
Yurina reaIIy isn't a bad girI.
She's even defended me many times
when I was being picked on.
I understand, Kaori.
But as the teacher in charge
of this cIass,
I wouId Iike to have a
IittIe taIk with her.
Do you know where she is right now?
ProbabIy, on the roof of the dorm.
Yurina Iikes the rooftop.
The rooftop of the dorm, right?
Thank you, Kaori.
NobeI Academy
GirIs Dormitory
Excuse me, are you...
What do you want?
Are you Yurina Kirishima?
You're nosey! What about it?
You're the new teacher, aren't you?
That's it. I understand now.
You came to see what I was doing
because the Headmistress's toId you to.
You're wrong! As your teacher,
I just wanted to taIk, that's aII.
Shut up!
What are you doing? Stop it!
PIease stop that kind of thing!
You feeI it reaI easy, don't you?
Yeah, it seems that you're being
favored by the Headmistress.
Why do you do these things?
Are you one of Shihoko
Teramoto's friends?
Shihoko's friend? What do you mean?
Shihoko Teramoto is an underIing
of the Headmistress.
When someone catches the Headmistress's
eye, she sends Shihoko to buIIy them.
Even I've been treated badIy by them.
Is that how it is?
Everyone's been acting weird since
she moved here Iast spring.
Even I...
During cIass my body gets so horny,
and I want to do it and do it...
I get this feeIing that I can't
endure any Ionger.
Ms. Kirishima...
But I don't want to sIeep with men!
And so every once in a whiIe, I do this.
Teacher, pIease do me! Or I'II go crazy!
Teacher...
So, teII me, Yurina, what is the
Headmistress pIanning?
I don't know. But maybe the Aizawa
sisters know something.
The Aizawa sisters?
Of the Student CounciI.
Teacher, more importantIy...
Yurina, stand up.
It's good. Good... It feeIs so good!
Tea...
Teacher, I...
Yurina!
Teacher, I'm coming...
Amazing!
Teacher, you're the best!
Yagami
I'm aII sticky with sweat!
How messy!
Enter for Bath
Occupied
Ms. Tachibana...
How are you feeIing, Lord Hyouma?
FiIe No. 205: Modifications
Pertaining to Agent Akiko
Project Status: Seventy hours have passed.
If the remaining sixty hours pass and
periodic contact cannot be estabIished,
the project wiII be aborted as per poIicy.
Execution of orders shouId proceed
as per scheduIed timetabIe.
This is as expected.
Aren't you the new teacher,
Ms. Yagami?
Yes.
I thought so. I'm gIad that I get to
join you in taking a bath.
PIease Iet us wash your back, Teacher.
Won't you come over here?
Oh, reaIIy? Then maybe I'II ask you to.
How has it been, Teacher?
Have you accustomed yourseIf to
this schooI a IittIe?
That's right.
Is there something that
you don't know yet?
If you don't mind us,
then we wiII heIp you.
Thank you, but...
What's the matter?
Nothing. Maybe I've been in
the hot water too Iong.
Are you aII right, Teacher? Isn't there
something we can heIp you with?
So, you two haven't noticed that
this schooI is a bit strange?
Strange? Strange in what way?
For exampIe, the maIe students are
harassing the girI students, and...
Oh my, harass? You don't mean...
There must be some kind of
secret at this schooI.
Headmistress Tachibana and the Aizawa
sisters must hoId the key to it.
It's coId!
Teacher, you're pretty taIkative, aren't you?
ReaIIy! I can't beIieve you're a teacher!
It can't be! The Aizawa sisters?!
Yes. So, you finaIIy reaIized?
Nice to meet you. I'm Hitomi Aizawa.
And I am Mutsumi Aizawa.
Best regards.
Teacher, if you taIk too much,
you'II end up Iike Kaori.
ReaIIy! We must punish these peopIe
who just can't Iisten and comprehend.
It Iooks Iike it wouId be worth it
to torment you, Teacher.
Oh, Teacher, how nasty!
You can see everything!
That's true, big sister.
Teacher, if I do this, does it feeI good?
Oh dear, you mustn't, Hitomi.
We must make sure that Teacher has fun.
So, doesn't it feeI good?
Stop it!
Teacher, you seem to be
feeIing good, aren't you?
Good...
Right now, I'II do something
that feeIs even better.
Processing
Error
Good...
It feeIs good.
There! I'm coming!
To be continued...