Act 3: Goddess Rising to Heaven
So, you're next.
No!
A beautiful moonlit night.
And who is it that
tarnishes that moon...
with a virgin's blood?
I'll lay that to rest.
The Moonlight Knight... Angel Blade.
Things are starting to heat up.
I'll keep tabs on everything.
Defeat Chloe and Elaine...
and prove to me that you'll become...
a worthy rival to Nailkaizer.
Angel Blade.
Can I win...
against these two?
Sister Seiru.
I'll protect you.
I'll protect everything that I love.
Mother.
Father.
Give Moena some strength!
Huh, that's perfect.
I came by to find bait to lure you...
but you saved me the effort.
I'll take you... now!
Damn.
I won't let you escape, Blade.
That's...
Angel Blade.
- Hey now, let's party.
- Come on, let's go.
- I don't know...
- Come on.
Wh... What is this?
No!
Die Blade!
Run!
How long can you run for?
Blade!
This is not good.
If I f'lght here right now...
innocent people will be hurt.
Here we go!
I guess you've
reached your limit...
Angel Blade.
If I let them continue...
I'm doomed.
What should I do?
What?
The nail in the coffin!
You'll be all right.
A-Are you...
a Blade too?
You little shit!
You pretending to
be a real angel, Blade?
I won't forgive you for this!
I won't!
Angel Blade!
I will have your head...
next time...
I promise.
I promise!
You look like
you're fine, Blade.
You are?
I'm Angel Ender.
I'm your...
prototype.
Why?
Why can you fight like this?
What makes you this strong?
Blade.
Wow, unreal!
This was my only chance!
And I failed to see it!
What? What?
It was Blade, Blade!
I am so unlucky.
No luck for me.
I've only won the
lowest amount on the lottery too.
And I've got no boobs.
But what's that
got to do with it?
Huh?
What's this?
Hey, old man.
You sleep there, you'll catch a cold.
Are you caught up in this mess?
Are you hungry?
Hello?
He... llo!
To Seiru Tenmyoin?
Yes.
So that means
Tenmyoin is Angel Blade.
No, that's not right.
Huh?
I myself have determined
that she is not Angel Blade.
But you still want
to capture her?
She's the bait...
to entice Blade.
Bait?
She's the only one
in this school...
who's had contact with her.
Twice.
I see.
So maybe there's some
kind of connection with Blade.
You look happy.
You want a taste of her...
that bad?
N-No.
That's not it.
Well, whatever.
I'll entice Blade out tonight.
Just make sure you get the bait.
I'll handle it.
W... Wait!
Please, wait.
Ms. Nailkaizer!
What?
In order to ensure
our plan is successful...
there is something I
need to ask you, Nailkaizer.
Say it.
Yes.
I want you to give
me some more power.
So I want your...
You want a piece of me?
Y-Yes, please.
Fine. I'll give you
some of my strength.
Thank you!
Stunning!
What's wrong?
You want some, right?
You want some of
Nailkaizer's golden juices.
Y... Yes.
Student body president
Seiru Tenmyoin.
The headmaster wishes to see you.
Please report to the
headmaster's off'lce.
I'll repeat.
Seiru Tenmyoin.
The headmaster wishes to see you.
Please report to the
headmaster's off'lce.
Fantastic.
I had no idea you
had such a hot body.
Watching you through a monitor
doesn't compare to this.
Oh, the softness.
And such bounce!
Fantastic.
Headmaster.
You're awake now Miss Tenmyoin?
Why...
my headmaster?
What are you...
Ugh! No!
No, stop!
Please stop, headmaster!
Why?
Why do this?
You're getting stimulated,
Miss Tenmyoin.
Your nipples are getting hard.
No.
No... No way.
I don't approve of the
student body president lying.
You're rock hard.
Aren't you now?
No.
You're dripping wet.
I can see your shape
now that it's transparent.
Um, there...
No.
No, don't.
I can't believe you're
gushing this much.
More than I expected,
Miss Tenmyoin.
No.
You don't like it?
But this is screaming for more.
No!
Brilliant.
This is Seiru Tenmyoin's
soft savannah.
The pearl that glistens
ever so brightly.
The beautiful wave that
glistens honey.
Absolutely fantastic.
Let me get a taste.
N... No.
No... more.
Closed Temporarily. So Sorry.
Angel Ender.
What is going on
in this world?
What can I do?
So then...
time for the main dish.
How do you...
...like this?
Get ready to have this
shoved in you.
N-No!
No, don't!
Not that!
No!
Forgive me.
Forgive me!
Please, forgive me!
Here it goes!
God damn!
Nice!
Seiru!
Hurts.
It hurts!
My body.
Getting hot are we?
Why?
Why am I getting so hot?
And turned on?
Yeah, Seiru.
You're...
fantastic!
Sister!
Angel Heart...
Flash!
Motor Blade!
Sis...
Seiru.
Are you okay?
Sister... Seiru.
Sister.
What in the...
Sister... Seiru.
Sister.
Why does it feel...
so good?
This is a lot better
than when I do it alone.
I...
I'm coming.
S-Sister... Seiru.
I...
was with you, sister.
What?
A lesbian show by
the fighter for justice.
I've quite enjoyed it, Angel Blade.
This is thanks for letting
me watch something interesting.
Why?
Why don't I...
have any strength?
You feeling it yet, Blade?
Feeling it? Not me.
No.
I didn't think you'd
fall into my trap this easily.
Looks like you used up
all your strength...
to undo the spell I
cast on Seiru.
The strength you have now...
is the same as a commoner.
No.
My anus.
Don't do that so much.
You're called Angel Blade, but
in the end you are just a female.
The floor is drenched.
You're so wet.
I shudder to think you're
called the Moonlight Knight.
So then, let's have a look...
at all of you.
What?
No.
Don't spread me open.
Not like this. No!
Fantastic!
The color, shape, sensation, and smell.
I can't believe such
an incredible thing exists.
No...
Don't look so much.
I'm embarrassed.
Why now?
You've been parading around
in this outfit for a long time.
You can show this off...
but you can't stand someone
forcing themselves on you.
No.
I'm not okay with this.
I...
Thoroughly enjoy...
the skills of my tongue.
No.
Don't.
Angel...
Blade.
So then, time for
the glorious main dish.
What is...
this?
This is a man's...
It's huge.
It's pulsating.
This f'lts into me?
But...
it's no use.
I...
Father...
Mother...
Forgive me.
Here we go, Blade!
Let go of Angel Blade!
You monster!
Haven't gotten enough
of me, Miss Tenmyoin?
But you see, I'm just
about to have my main dish.
Be quiet and watch from there.
Sister... Seiru.
W-What?
Angel Blade...
take this!
What is...
this power? This speed?
Is this the true strength
of Angel Blade?
Beautiful.
She looks like...
...a real Angel.
How? How can this
happen to me?
Ultimate Dynamic!
N-Nailkaizer.
Please give me some strength.
You can't even save yourself...
and you lay hands
on your master's prey.
You're worth less than a dog.
The strength that comes
from the need to protect.
Do I...
have that?
The need to protect something.
The shadowy hands pierce
dreams with echoing screams.
And against it is beautiful light
that casts away the darkness.
The hidden skin is the mark of an angel.
As solitary tears take over the town.
I sing an uplifting melody as
beauty protects all that I am.
Evil lives and forbidden love.
But the form of the warrior
who cuts the darkness still shimmers.
You light the vision.
This woman...
is the test for Angel System.
Good job, Karin.
Miss Maina.
Hurry, my Angel.
The legendary day of celebration is near.