Before the beginning...
...there was no light or shadow...
...even time didn't exist.
In the beginning of everything...
...there was chaos.
Lord Zeus?
That Hera...
She slapped me really hard... Does she want to kill me?
Aww, you got a big booboo, poor Zeu-chu.
I was so close...
Fella caught you cheating again?
Oshime, how many times do I have to tell you?
Her name is Hera, not Fella.
I don't even want to mention her name right now...
You should stop having affairs in Heaven.
You're always using your divine powers to hit on angels...
...of course Fella will find out...
You shut your mouth!
How can I get close to young, sexy angels and...
...do all sorts of naughty things without Hera finding out?
Oh, I want to do it! I want to do it!
I want to do it with young angels!
I want to do it!
L-Lord Zeus, you might want to keep your voice down.
Everyone in Heaven will hear you.
Oh, it's the Chief Angel.
I've been looking all over Heaven for you.
This is a divine palace...
...you should watch your mouth and try to behave yourself.
Shut up!
Lord Zeus!
Are you going to treat me like an idiot, too?
So, what do you want?
Well, it's almost time, so...
For what?
H-Have you forgotten?
Today is the day of the angels' yearly promotional examination.
You guys go ahead. I'm busy right now.
Count me out.
Unacceptable!
The future of young angels depends on this test.
Do you understand your position as King of the Gods?
Okay, okay, I understand.
I'm tired of listening to your lectures.
Very well.
The angels who will be taking the test for...
...B-Class angel are, Hesperis, Euproshne, and Aurora.
Hesperis, Euproshne, and Aurora?
Those three...
As you know, the test will be to see how many humans they can help on Earth.
Their final score will be judged on virtue, generosity, courage, and intelligence.
We'll rank each category from A to D.
On Earth?
They have three months.
During that time, they have to...
I see!
Um, Lord Zeus?
Get out of my way!
Out of his way!
I'm just here to deliver a package...
Can it!
I'm sorry!
Come on, can you guys just leave for today?
What do you care? You have no customers in here.
No customers at all!
That's because you guys are here!
Hey now, don't try to blame it on us.
What?
It's not our fault that you can't sell any flowers.
You...
Hey now...
I don't approve of violence.
Me neither.
We could help you with closing the store if you want.
Why you...
Could I have some flowers, please?
I'd like these freesia too.
I want this lily!
Uh, yes.
In a minute.
Who the hell are you?
Will you move? You're blocking the flowers.
What?
You're scaring the flowers with that face of yours.
Yes, he is.
You had better stay out of it!
Why you...
And what if we don't?
Bitch!
That's enough!
If you're going to keep causing trouble, I'll call the cops!
You'll pay for this!
You will!
Will you take a rain check?
Land speculators?
Yeah.
After my grandma died, I've been taking care of the flower shop by myself...
...but recently those guys have been trying to close this store.
That's terrible!
They are such meanies!
But I will protect this shop from them, no matter what!
We will help you.
We will make this shop thrive!
Leave everything to us!
But why?
Because that's our test...
...I mean, our mission!
But we have one favor to ask you...
Can we live with you?
Live with me?
We haven't found a place to live yet, so...
Well, I guess it's okay...
Great!
We don't have to sleep outside.
This must be a divine blessing...
Excuse me...
Yes?
Welcome! How may I help you?
Well, I'm not a customer.
I just want to get a signature for this package.
My human name is Yuu Amamiya. My angel name is Hesperis.
Her human name is Miki Yuunaki. Her angel name is Euproshne.
And her human name is Chadoko Asagiri. Her angel name is Aurora.
Actually, we are angels, sent to earth take the examination for promotion.
Listen carefully...
You must make as many humans happy as you possibly can.
That's the task for the test.
But you cannot let anyone know that you are angels.
You are not to use any angelic powers, either.
Many hardships await you, but don't let that get you down, and do your best!
We know you can pass this test!
Yes!
Are these all the flowers to deliver?
Yeah, but is it really okay to ask you to do this?
There is no need to worry!
You can count on us!
That's right. This shop will be flooded with customers in no time!
Well, I'm not going to get my hopes too high...
That's not a very nice thing to say. Don't you trust my sense of art?
Well, we're off to make our deliveries.
Be careful, Yuu!
I'll see you later, Miki.
Where are you going, Miki?
I'm teaching a swimming lesson.
Well, well...
Hi, I met you at the store yesterday.
Oh, you are...
...excuse me, but have we met?
I delivered a package to the flower shop yesterday...
Oh right. You're the delivery man.
So, do you work here?
Yes, I just started today.
Do you work here too?
Yes. I work a few part-time jobs.
I'm Yorishiro.
I'm Miki Yuunaki. You can call me Miki.
Yes, Miki.
Okay everyone, we are going to do some stretching in the water first.
Move your body just like I do in the pool.
Now...
One, two, one, two...
One, two...
Next, stretch your side.
And the other side...
W-What am I looking at?
I'm working right now...
Yorishiro!
Are you okay?
Come on, grab my hand.
Um, I can't right now.
Huh?
Well, my lower body is...
Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt, but...
Go on, grab my hand.
O-Okay...
Oh no! This time I really got a cramp!
Is something wrong?
M-My leg...
Yorishiro?
What should I do?
He isn't breathing, I have to do something...
Oh my...
Well, excuse me.
What's this?
What is this soft feeling?
M-Miki!
Ooh, I'm the luckiest man on Earth!
Her lips are so soft...
That's right. Keep doing that.
It feels great.
What?
What was that? I just felt something really hot inside my body...
That's right...
What?
Go on.
Yes.
Oh, it feels good...
My goodness, what am I doing?
But my body is so hot...
This must be the test Lord Zeus was talking about.
Now, kiss me.
Kiss?
That's right, kiss me.
Yes...
Huh?
Miki?
Are you feeling okay now?
This is so boring.
There are no customers...
I arranged those bouquets with all my love, but there's no one to buy...
Those are the thugs from the other day!
Those are precious flowers!
You came out of nowhere!
You did!
What are you talking about? You jumped right in front of me!
I could take you to the police if that's what you want.
Or if you sold the shop to us right now, we would forget about this.
It's you again!
You had better give it up already, or I will have to teach you a lesson again...
Yes, he will!
Hey stop it!
You should not step on the flowers.
What's that?
Get lost!
E-Excuse me...
Thank you so much.
Can I see some flowers?
Yes, of course.
Minori, we've got a customer.
What a beautiful rose...
My late grandma took great care to grow those roses.
I'll take a dozen.
Thank you very much.
And that bouquet.
Huh? But this is...
Just throw it in.
Oh, thank you so much!
Thanks for your help.
Thank you, come again!
What a generous customer...
See? He totally understood my taste!
I wonder...
Wake up, my little angels.
Lord Zeus?
I'm speaking to you from Pantheon Palace.
I understand, Lord.
Will you wake Chadoko up please?
Chadoko! Wake up!
Hmm? Is it morning already?
No. Lord Zeus is here to talk to us.
Really?
Everyone, just relax and listen.
As you all know the test has already begun.
So, how did you do, Miki?
Well, I think I made someone happy.
What about you, Chadoko?
Yes! I did a good job!
Oh really?
And Yuu?
I failed miserably.
But it was because of those men!
Yuu, you cannot blame others for your mistakes.
Yes, Lord Zeus.
If you are to improve your efforts, you must blame no one but yourself.
Yes...
Don't let this get to you, Yuu. There are still plenty of chances.
I'll look forward to tomorrow!
Good luck!
SPECIAL EFFECTS HERO SHOW
BEAST WARRIORS
BIKI ANIMAL SHOW
I'm going to do my best and make up for lost time tomorrow.
I can't lose to Chado and Miki either...
Let me zip up and...
Ooh, this costume is really tight.
It's wedged in around my sensitive area...
Here I am! I'm Biki Panther!
Do I look cool, or what?
What's happening to me?
My body is getting hot...
Not only that...
...it feels like my body has become more sensitive.
Warriors of Justice!
We're the animal warriors!
Biki Animals!
Good show.
It was a great show!
Yuu, you were really great.
Thank you.
I'm wet... What's wrong with me?
No, I can't. I shouldn't do such a thing...
Y-Yes?
Yuu, can I come in?
Yeah, sure.
Yuu...
Are you feeling all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Good...
You'll feel better if I do this...
What?
You're so beautiful
No, it's embarrassing!
Stop it, Yorishiro...
I don't know what's going on...
...but I can't resist it.
Besides... it feels good...
Yuu...
Suck this.
It will make me feel really good...
Oh, it feels good...
This must be the test Lord Zeus was talking about...
It feels great, Yuu...
Yuu...
I'll put it in.
Lord Zeus, is this also part of the test?
Oh, it feels great! I can't hold back...
What the...
It's a Sex Beast!
Why is it here?
Yuu!
Damn it, if I use any more godly powers, Hera will find out about me...
I have no choice!
Yorishiro!
Come on, you monster! I will fight you!
Take this! And this! And this!
And this!
I'm not going to lose!
You're not going to beat me!
Take this! And this! And this!
Eat this!
Yorishiro, are you okay?
I defeated the monster!
Yuu...
I did it! I did it!
Hey, Yuu...
What was I doing?
Zeu-chu!
Are you sure about that?
Yes. I saw it with my own eyes.
But I don't understand...
Are they trying to invade Hell?
Persephone, go to the surface and find out what his real purpose is.
And if those angels get in your way, eliminate them.
Okay!