I want this lily!
You had better stay out of it!
And what if we don't?
Next, stretch your side.
That's right. This shop will be flooded with customers in no time!
I'm going to do my best and make up for lost time tomorrow.
I can't lose to Chado and Miki either...
Here I am! I'm Biki Panther!
Eat this!
There's no mistake about it. They are angels from Heaven...
But I still don't understand...
Why is Zeus training such low-ranking angels himself?
Is it possible that he's planning to use them to attack Hell?
I'm counting on you, Persephone.
Excuse me, Lord Hades...
P-Persephone!
Why are you still here?
Because, I wanted to talk to you about something important...
Something important?
Uh-huh. It's about this month's paid vacation.
W-What?
Now isn't the time to talk about it.
That's not fair!
I haven't had any vacation this year.
A-All right. Then I'll let you take a long vacation around the end of the year.
I'll give you a bonus too, are you happy now?
Really?
Yes! Now go!
Go out there and get in Zeus's way however you can!
Okay!
Hmm, it seems like everyone is learning pretty well.
This will be a lot of fun...
But I feel like someone is trying to get in my way...
Oh, it's just that kid...
Zeu-chu! Zeu-chu!
Zeu-chu!
What's the matter?
Where have you been?
I went down to Earth.
It takes a lot of divine power to descend to Earth. It's really dangerous!
I know, I know!
Hey, you're blocking my view.
It's Chadoko's turn...
Something bad has happened.
Oshime, will you move?
I don't know what's gonna happen to you.
Move just a little to...
Zeu-chu! Fella was...
I said move!
They're gone...
Did they finish taking a shower?
Okay!
Please stop right there!
Not yet!
Okay, now you can go!
I'm doing a great job!
Please stop right there!
Watch out!
What is going on?
It's not my fault!
Bad Luck
More bad luck?
Yorishiro?
Wow, is it you, Miki?
Yes.
I didn't know you worked here as a priestess.
I want to help as many as people I can.
I see.
You lost your memory?
Yes, something strange has been happening to me.
All of the sudden, part of my memory is gone...
...and I can't remember what was happening...
I wonder if there's anything wrong with me.
I will ask the priest here to give you the blessing of the gods.
Really?
I'm sure you will be fine.
Thank you so much.
How long do I have to wait?
Sorry I'm late!
Excuse me, but are you the priestess?
Uh-huh.
Well let's start giving you a blessing, huh?
Um, okay.
Well, take off your clothes first.
What?
You need to be naked.
B-But...
You want to feel better, right?
Y-Yes!
Then you gotta do whatever I say. Now!
I haven't had this in a while... It's delicious.
H-How is this going to...
The real ceremony hasn't started yet.
E-Excuse me, is this really a purification?
If you question it, it won't work.
O-Okay!
Yorishiro?
M-Miki...
Wait, um...
What's going on?
T-This is...
Um, Yorishiro?
This is just a purification rite.
Purification rite?
That's right. Would you like to continue the ceremony?
...I'll do my best.
It feels good...
It feels great! Oh yes!
What just happened?
There's no need to worry.
The purification is complete.
I was so close...
But that boy was kinda cute...
Thank you, and please come again.
Everything's going well today.
Yeah.
But I wish there were more customers...
Actually, Yuu...
Hmm?
Oh, hello!
Minori, how's the bath?
W-What are you doing here?
You don't need to be shy.
You want me to wash your back?
Stop it.
It's all right, don't be shy.
No, it's quite all right.
Suit yourself, then. I'll leave a towel here.
Wait, Yuu...
What is it?
You've been a big help.
What?
You know, with the flower shop and everything.
I'm glad that we could help.
But why do you want to help someone so much?
Because that's the test.
What test?
To become a high-ranking angel.
What?
I mean, to become someone who is kind like an angel.
That's why we're helping people.
It's not enough...
We can't reform this shop with so little money.
Well, don't be so discouraged. We've just started.
We have to keep working hard.
It's Lord Zeus.
Lord Zeus...
Oh my goodness.
Oh, girls. There's no need to be so formal.
We appreciate your kindness.
Thank you, Lord Zeus.
So how did everything go today?
Yuu?
Yes, Minori seems happy with our help.
And we also sold a lot of flowers today.
That's very good.
And, how about you? Chadoko?
Well, it didn't work out too well.
Um, okay...
Your answer is always very simple.
How about you, Miki?
Yes. I must say that I have failed today.
Yorishiro looked so sad...
I'm a failure as an angel...
There are so many things I must learn...
I see. Well, keep working hard.
Yes.
In any event, I'll give you an opportunity to make many people happy tomorrow.
Really?
We're going to get lots of points!
Thank you so much, Lord Zeus.
We will not disappoint you.
Look forward to it.
Play Lottery Here
So are we working for the lottery?
It seems so.
But why do we have to wear this? It's embarrassing.
I'm sure Lord Zeus has a plan in mind.
We must do what he tells us to do.
Let's get a lot of points!
You're right!
Oh, sorry.
You didn't win, but you get tissue paper.
Sorry. Here's your tissue paper
Sorry!
Sorry.
We can't make anyone happy like this.
Then we should make the red ones first prize!
No Chadoko. We must not cheat.
We'll just hope that someone will win.
But don't you think it's strange that there's no prize other than tissue paper?
Oh?
What's this?
It's a bathing suit.
It doesn't look like a prize, but why is it here?
It's also bit provocative, don't you think?
What are they doing now?
Like I care... I'm gonna go bother them anyway.
Yay! It's second prize!
Well, I guess I'll take this one then.
And I want you to wear it.
Huh? Me?
What do you mean?
Oh come on.
It says in right here that if I get second prize, I can ask...
...any one of the girls to wear a bathing suit I pick and take a picture with her.
What?
Thank you!
You gotta be kidding...
This is like a sexual harassment lottery.
Totally disgusting!
I can't believe he picked Yuu over us!
Chadoko, you're angry for a different reason.
So if second prize is this, what's first prize?
It says if you win first prize, you'll get a date with one of us...
What?
I'm not going to lose to you!
Oh, Chadoko...
What's the special prize?
One of the girls will be your girlfriend for a day.
And since she's your girlfriend, you can do whatever you want to her...
What?
You pick the special prize and make her into your girlfriend?
You're still young...
I don't understand.
You see, I have a bigger plan.
What is it? Tell me!
You'll see...
I feel so young again, thank you so much.
That's good to hear.
I gotta work harder!
Me too!
Congratulations! It's second prize!
It's second prize!
Let's roll that thing.
You!
You're those thugs!
That's not a very nice thing to call your customers. We're here for the lottery.
That's right, we are.
Okay, then, go ahead.
I'm going to win the special prize!
Congratulations! It's third prize, tissue paper!
What?
Here you go.
Damn...
One more time!
Third prize!
Here is your tissue paper.
What the hell!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Third prize!
One more time!
Tissue paper!
Third prize! Tissue paper! Third prize! Tissue paper! Third prize! Tissue paper!
One more time!
Oh that's too bad. You don't have any tickets left.
He doesn't have any left.
You idiot! You don't have to repeat after her!
This lottery must have been rigged!
What did you say?
How dare you say that!
Congratulations! You've won first prize!
I'll be your date for a day!
Why do we only get tissues?
Why?
Oh, now I know what you guys are up to.
Hmm?
Lottery, huh?
One lottery ticket please.
Oh, hello Yorishiro.
Oh, hi Miki.
And Yuu?
Are you here for the lottery?
Yeah. But tissues will be fine. I have a cold, so...
I hope you win!
Y-Yes.
Hey, that's not fair that only you two have a friend!
Are you going to introduce him to me?
Hi, I'm Yorishiro.
He's such a cutie. He's just my type.
Yay! You won the special prize!
Special prize? Me?
Congratulations, Yorishiro!
Congratulations, come this way, please!
Wait...
Hey, what are you doing!
Yorishiro!
You can't steal our customers!
Who are you?
For the special prize, you get to do it with me.
And the last one...
Your body is so delicious.
Where did they go?
But who was that woman that took Yorishiro?
I've never seen her before.
I bet she's going to make a ransom!
I will make you feel a lot better...
Not yet...
In a little while, all of your energy will be mine.
There you are!
Let Yorishiro go!
I was so close...
Don't they have manners?
Who are you?
What are you doing with Yorishiro?
I am planning to suck the life out of him.
What did you say?
You're in so much trouble!
No! We aren't supposed to use our angelic powers.
But Miki...
Well then, I'll go first!
Come out, my pretty babies!
That's the monster from the other day!
There are three of them!
Miki! Chado!
No!
Are you okay?
Hey you monster! Let us off!
Oh, calm down.
What are you going to do to us?
You've got spunk, young lady.
I guess you'll be a perfect play date for my babies.
What? What do you mean?
No!
No! It's disgusting!
Stop it!
Oh my goodness, look at you.
Stop it! You pervert!
What happened to your attitude?
Who are you?
Uh-oh.
Why are you doing this?
Who told you to do this?
I'm not telling you anything!
It's Hades, isn't it?
I guess you already knew...
That's right, Lord Hades ordered me to interfere with your plans.
I see...
...but what does this mean?
How does he know about my plan?
That's impossible...
Well, uh, I'll be seeing you soon!
Tell Hades that...
...he shouldn't underestimate my power.
That's no way to treat a beautiful woman!
You jerk!
Everything went great today!
Yeah, up until that big lightning...
But because of that lightning, we got the chance to save Yorishiro.
But who was the kidnapper?
I don't know...
She was very bad!
If she hadn't shown up, Yorishiro and I would have been together!
I don't think so, Chado.
But...
After what happened today, now I know Lord Zeus is...
...really looking out for us.
Yeah, I think so too.
Let's work hard tomorrow again!
That's right, my sweet angels.
I will take good care of you...
And what exactly does that mean?
You know what I mean?
No, I don't. Would you care to explain to me?
H-Hera...
Persephone...
What a useless servant...
Next time, I shall defeat them with my own hands.