Open up!
Unhand me!
Kousuke-sama!
Shizuka.
Kousuke-sama.
Just a dream...
Sorry.
I'm home, Kousuke-kun.
ANGEL by U-jin
No matter how naive we seem,
The way we talk is so real.
We know everything about each other.
We're out on the town,
And you're the one who suggested it.
So why are you being so quiet?
All you did was kiss me.
It's silly to say you're sorry.
Don't make things awkward for me.
You want me, and want you in return.
I have the courage to do that.
I have confldence that I can maкe things go mу way.
Don't stop our romance, continue our kiss.
Let me feel it.
Let me hear your words.
Let me have you romantically all to myself.
Love me
This town really hasn't changed much.
I'm glad.
I'm sure Kousuke-kun has grown up a lot, though.
I can't wait to see him.
Hey! You call that decent?
You'd better do something about that ridiculous hair!
Huh? But this perm was expensive!
Sensei, good morning!
Ah, be a good girl.
Hey! Fix your collar, idiot!
Sensei, good morning!
Good morning.
At least they've got spunk.
Oh, please.
Aw, come on, it's okay.
Hey, you!
School is not a place for lovers!
If I catch ya doing that again you'll both be suspended!
Got it?
Jeez, infuriating!
I heard recently that indecent relations
between teenagers are quite common,
Arihashi-sensei.
Exactly, Principal.
And I cannot tolerate that fact!
Yes, you are...
Good morning!
...exactly right
The last thing this school needs
is indecent relationships.
Good morning, Sensei!
Good morning.
Young students are beautiful because they
put so much energy into their studies.
Hi, Madonna-sensei.
- Good morning.
Arihashi-sensei, how did it go?
Did she say yes to your proposal?
Ah, well, keep your chin up.
Rui-chan, you get more intense every day.
This is the first time l've done acrobatics like this.
Love conquers all. That's why.
Don't cum inside of me, okay?
Oopsie!
So where did you find it?
In the city, sorta.
Did you actually go there?
Yeah, I did.
Um, are you Atami Kousuke-kun?
No, sorry.
Oops! I thought he was Kousuke-kun
because he looked strong.
I'm not myself today.
I'm sorry!
My mistake.
Hold it, dearie.
You're pretty cute.
Why don't you apologize with your body instead?
Cut it out.
She doesn't want to.
What?
How epic-looking.
This man must be...
Kousuke-kun!
Asshole! Don't get in our way!
Beautiful!
E-Excuse me!
Is it possible you're...
So that's where you were?
You fucking perverted weakling!
Let me whack your pathetic sense of pride into shape!
Don't avoid me!
You're gonna get it!
Whoa, wait!
P-P-Please gimme a break!
Please rescue me, Once-sama!
That boy is being mean to me!
Why you!
Get away from her!
I have no damn business with a weakling like you!
Say your prayers, Kousuke!
"Kousuke"?
So you're Kousuke?
Yeah...
And you're not Kousuke-kun?
N-Nope, I'm Kanji.
Oh, shit.
Wait a minute.
Who the hell is that girl?
But it's certainly rare,
to transfer because of your father's work.
Your grades are top of the class, too.
If you play your cards right,
we'll help you with anything you want.
Well, work hard, dear!
And that's what the Principal says.
Don't be late for morning homeroom,
and stay quiet.
Excuse me.
Really! Why did I come to this school anyway?
Hey, newbie, you're pretty tough, eh?
Wanna come with us for a bit?
Oh, Principal, looks like we have
another pretty girl here.
I can't contain myself!
Just look at this,
at all these files!
P-Principal, these are...
all transfer students?
Pretty girls just keep coming to
our school, one after another.
W-Wow! So many!
What about these?
Everything beyond this point is boys,
but we don't need more boys at this school.
No, sir!
Take it out already!
If you cooperate, well go easy on ya.
Say something, bitch!
I'm in a bad mood today.
Can't we do this later?
You've sure got some nerve.
Fine, should we take your virginity first?
Then after that, we've got a special.
Cut it out!
Hey you!
Ganging up three against one on a defenseless girl?
I won't allow it!
Don't worry, you're safe with me, dear.
Kousuke-kun?
Let's do it!
F-Full bloom!
Hey, hey, hey, you call yourself a man?
Do you even have a penis?
Cut it out!
You bitches, now you've really fucking done it!
Time to die!
Yuri!
Wake up, Yuri!
Hang in there, Yuri!
Hey! W-Wait up!
How did you know my name?
Tell me.
Kousuke-kun, don't you remember?
S-Sorry?
What's wrong?
No! Why? Why did you die?
Ah! You're the strawberry panties girl!
Don't kill yourself over that.
Look at me.
Cool!
Did you get that cool haircut?
No! These bad bullies at my school were teasing me.
I'm so sad I wanna die.
But if I die, it's all over!
So l'd better become stronger!
Shizuka-chan!
Let's promise we'll become strong together!
Okay? Okay?
Sure.
Promise, okay?
Just a week after I met you, my father
transferred, and we moved.
Shizuka and Kousuke
Ever since that day, I vowed to become stronger.
I never forgot our promise.
I see.
So you're that Shizuka-chan.
And so, after twelve years away,
she has returned to Tokyo.
This is Himenogi Shizuka.
Kids! Let's all make her feel welcome, okay?
Nice to meet you all.
Oh, shit!
Shizuka-kun was the top of her class at her last school.
So let's use this as incentive to study and...
There!
You should sit in that seat.
I'm in love.
Come back to my place today!
Let's catch up on the way home,
Shizuka-chan!
Dammit...
Well, since today is the start of a new semester,
I have something to tell all of you.
Lately, teens have been engaging
in inappropriate relationships.
Your duty is to study and learn.
In a time as crucial as this, indecent relationships
are the most absurd thing imaginable!
Be strong like Miyazawa.
Try devoting your lives to learning!
Right, Miyazawa?
Right...
Everyone in this class who is
currenuy dating, stand up, please!
What? No one in here?
You lying to me?
Hey!
Kousuke, I'm fully aware that you've been
engaged in lewd acts on this very campus.
Stand up!
There are more of you, I know it.
Is that all?
I hate liars.
There are more of you, right?
S-So many?
How sad!
I'm so sad for you!
I suppose this is a result of my
shortcomings as an educator.
When I was a student, studying was my life!
Boys and girls didn't even speak to each other!
You mean no one would sleep with you?
Shit!
You fucking brats get to have all the fun I didn't!
Listen!
Listen well.
Each and every one of you boys must swear that
from now on, you won't date until you graduate!
No way!
Yeah! No way!
Shut up!
Have you forgotten your place as students?
Suzuki! We'll start with you.
B-But we're serious.
You wanna be suspended then? Huh?
I-I swear to devote my life to studying.
Well said, boy!
Next up, Aida!
S-Sir! I swear I won't date Mine-san anymore.
Good. Next up, Nishiyama!
Yes, sir! I-I'll make do with masturbation.
Very good, very good.
Next up, Atami!
What's wrong with you?
Wh-What an asshole.
Want me to tell your parents?
They'll probably lose their faith in you over this.
Your fault for taking advantage of them.
I swear from now on, I'll...
Don't say it!
Who we date is our own fucking business,
not some ass-wipe teachers.
Are ya really so weak that the best you
can do is threaten to tell his parents?
Himenogi!
You're a fucking joke.
Wh-What did you say?
Himenogi!
Apparently, you still don't understand
the way this school works!
Shizuka-chan!
You're all taking responsibility for this!
You all have pool-cleaning duty after school!
But why?
We're not even using it until next semester!
Don't gimme excuses!
Everyone cleans the pool!
Don't leave an ounce of muck!
And as for you, Miyazawa,
come see me after school.
That is all!
Why is Hitomi-chan the only one excused?
Is something going on with her?
Attention!
Those remaining on the ground
floor, please vacate at once.
Floor cleared.
Ready.
Floor open! Floor open!
Water cover removed!
Confirmed.
Please enter to clean.
What a lucky break.
I had no idea you were this good with machines.
It's nothing, it's nothing.
Well then, I guess we'd better go clean it.
Shit, why do we have to clean it? Stupid teacher...
Well then! Now the real fun begins!
But I really wonder who made a neat thing like this.
Target found and locked.
This is it!
This is for the glory of science!
It's Shizuka-chan! Okay.
Yahoo! I got a shot of Shizuka-chan!
She's wearing silk panties.
Her panties are...
Huh?
Huh? I wonder what this thing is?
What thing?
This thing.
Oh, what is it?
Look, it moved!
It's great to be alive!
You don't get many chances like this in life!
This is it!
This is what I've been waiting for!
This all belongs to me!
All of it!
Sh-Shizuka-chan?
Shizuka-chan! Don't go!
W-W-Wait up!
Were you the only one?
Skipping cleaning duties and
doing something horny instead.
Aw, don't be so hard on me.
Though I'm sure hard...
You're coming home with me today, right?
We can "catch up," can't we?
Please?
Please, come on!
Why is it?
Why are you so cold to me?
I-I'm sorry.
Even if I turn an adult toy on, I can't turn you on.
Shizuka-chan... why?
To tell the truth,
I'd decided l'd give you my virginity, Kousuke-kun.
But Kousuke-kun... Kousuke-kun...
You're actually such a loser!
What are you gonna do about that?
About my virginity.
If I get more manly, will ya give it to me...
Shizuka-chan?
Promise me?
B-But...
Let's do it now!
Shizuka-chan!
Shizuka-sama!
What is it?
Shizuka-sama, we have a request for you!
Please let us be your slaves!
Stop the creepy jokes.
I'm just a normal teenage girl.
P-Please don't go, Shizuka-sama!
What a mess.
That's Hitomi-chan!
So I'll give up on Shizuka-chan for now.
N-No!
Please, mercy. I'm begging you.
Stop putting up a fight.
But you're my teacher!
I don't caгe that you're a student.
I don't caгe that you're the heir to a company.
No!
No. No...
H-Holy crap!
No!
Lookie, lookie, you're already so wet.
You're such a slut, Hitomi.
Why, Hitomi-chan?
No...
I saw it.
I wasn't really planning on seeing it, though.
You're a model student.
Why were you doing that?
You have a reason, right?
Tell me.
Don't cry!
Hey you!
Don't make a girl cry!
I-It wasn't me!
I-It wasn't.
What in the world happened?
Tell me.
That's mean!
You stay over there.
Huh?
Shoo! Shoo!
And so?
My grades in PE were really bad.
I wanted to improve them.
So Arihashi-sensei told me
he'd give me private lessons.
Not good enough!
Straighten your legs more!
Sensei, why won't you let me
change out of my uniform?
Don't complain about specifics!
Don't you want an A,
Miyazawa?
I do!
All my other subjects are A's.
PE is my only C.
Please help me!
Then do as I say.
Okay, I will.
This is your last chance.
Okay.
Good. Stay like that for 50 seconds.
But I can't do it.
Miyazawa, here's a proposal.
If you stay still and don't question anything I do,
I'll give you an A.
What do you think?
Okay! Please help me, Sensei!
What are you...
Don't look up.
I had no idea what he meant back then.
The blood had rushed to my head, so...
No! No!
No!
What an asshole!
Arihashi, you're fucking dead!
And who is getting off on this story?
But ya know, he did give you an A as promised, right?
So you both got what you wanted.
You're right.
But it didn't stop there.
He threatened to tell my parents
about what we were doing.
Every day since then, he's made me
do embarrassing sex acts with him.
No!
No! Stop it please.
There are many other students like me at this school!
I hear some even got pregnant.
I hate him!
But...
Leave it to me.
Taking advantage of his position as teacher,
and destroying a sweet girl's heart and dreams...
I swear I'll make him pay for this.
Kousuke-kun.
Hitomi-chan, don't give in.
Let's be strong together!
Okay? Okay? Okay?
After I beat up Arihashi, I'll be reborn as a strong man!
Shizuka-chan, watch me!
Okay. It's getting late. I'll walk you home.
Let's go.
Don't worry, I've got a plan.
That kind of guy, huh...
It's you.
When I was a kid, he comforted me like that too.
He's hopelessly horny.
But he's got his good points too.
If I take pictures with this camera and
prove that Arihashi is raping a student..
If this goes well, Hitomi-chan will love me!
And then Shizuka-chan will open
her heart to me and love me too!
Two birds with one stone!
It's busty Madonna-sensei.
That's strange.
Why is she here so late?
Fine!
Gymnasium Pool
Gym Storage Room
Who's there!?
Who called me here for a nighttime private lesson?
I-I did.
Himenogi? Why are you dressed like that?
Sensei, is it true that you give girls
good grades if they pleasure you?
Idiot! I'm an honorable teacher.
I'd never do that, stupid girl!
Not as easy as I thought. Guess it's onto Plan B.
Um... I... Actually, I'm frigid.
I can't get wet.
Not at all.
So, I'm very scared.
Sensei, how can I get wet?
Will you show me?
Th-That's a complicated problem!
I was worried at first because you
seemed to be so rebellious,
but now you seem to understand
how this scnool works.
Anyway, as long as you've learned your lesson...
Hope you're ready, Kousuke-kun.
I can't stand it!
How's that?
Oh, you still aren't turned on?
Yeah... Oh yeah...
Now you feel it, don't ya?
Why won't you get wet?
My finger technique has never
been unsuccessful before.
How humiliating!
What are you waiting for, Kousuke?
Awesome!
More...
Two at once?
Huh?
Out of film.
Oh no, Shizuka-chan!
How about now? How about now?
I'm good, aren't I?
Sensei, thank you. That's enough.
No, you don't.
There's one last thing.
Kousuke-kun isn't coming to help me. Kousuke-kun...
You jackass!
Hey, hey, don't move.
Who's there!?
Fucking pervert!
I'm sending these pictures to the school board!
This will put an end to your teaching career!
Kousuke-kun!
Atami! Hand over the camera!
I'll give you all A's if you do!
I don't give a shit about A's!
You're the worst scum on the face of the planet...
for trapping an innocent girl like that!
Atami! Hand over the camera at once!
Shizuka-chan!
Hey, you
Come back, you little brat!
Shizuka-chan, this way!
Why you!
Now you've really made me mad!
What?
I can see her pussy!
Kousuke-kun, do it now!
Okay! Just you watch!
Stupid teacher, take this!
No!
- At least let me finish this!
- Stop!
- Kousuke!
- At least let me finish this!
- Shizuka-chan!
Okay, full power!
Heгe we go.
Shizuka-chan!
Stop it!
How could this happen?
Let me finish.
Wait! Wait for me, Shizuka-chan!
Shizuka-chan!
Stop it, Arihashi!
Idiot! You think I'm stopping now?
Shizuka-chan!
Kousuke!
Cut it out!
Sh-Shizuka-chan...
Kousuke! Kousuke! Kousuke!
Kousuke!!
Sh-Shizuka-chan...
Prepare to die.
K-Kanji! C-Cut it out.
Fucking teacher.
S-Stop it!
Hey! Do something! Do something, will you!?
I'm getting trapped. I'm getting trapped!
Thank you for saving me.
Nah. As long as he becomes a man, I'm happy.
Hey, Kousuke, you alive?
The camera...
There!
And so, Kousuke-kun hasn't changed that much,
but he has become much more manly.
As for Arihashi-sensei, I guess something's
wrong with him. We haven't seen him since.
Even though we don't have the
pictures as proof anymore.
Apparently we fooled him.
So I guess the problem is solved.
Shizuka-san, I can't thank you enough!
Really, I...
If you want to thank someone, thank Kousuke-kun.
Kousuke-kun? Oh dear, what shall I say?
Still not fixed yet? You pathetic little wimp!
Don't tell me...
You bastard!
Damn you!
Got me again.
Uh oh.
Weren't you gonna become more manly?
Well...
That was your last chance!
Save me!
Wait up!
Punishment time!
Dance!
Promises create sounds.
Your gaze entices me to the dance floor.
Burn!
Sorry, but I think I'm the one
Who's more excited than you.
But you know, the flames so dangerously dose to us
It stings.
Can't stop dancing, can't stop feeling
I'm alive, wanna dance all night!
Just like in Bombay.
I want to show you the flames.
Let's break away and dance.
Staring away
I don't caгe if you discover my true colors.
END