The demons have awoken
to destroy Sid, the continent.
Alicia, the girl who is being sought
after by the Four Lords of Darkness...
saved us
with her mysterious powers.
There seems to be some sort of
connection between the two but...
who gives a damn!
They'll never have Alicia!
I can't have you defeated too.
- Let's go, girls!
- OK!
Ash.
Ash!
That's...
What is it this time!?
Lavialos!
Who the hell are you!?
Lavialos, there's no need for you.
Do you think you can triumph
over Alicia's powers?
Lucretia.
Anyway, why don't we tell them?
That Alicia is one of us.
That's a lie!
What the hell
are they talking about?
The power Alicia possesses is the power
that we, the Demon Clan, wield.
The emblem on her chest is
undeniable proof.
That can't be.
I'm a demon?
We have been slaughtering
the humans to find Alicia.
Then are you saying Sid became
stained with blood because of me?
Now, Alicia.
Come with us.
If I go, will the battle between
humans and demons end?
Yes.
If you wish for peace on Sid,
come with us.
Shut up!!
Enough of your babble, demons!
Ash!
Pests.
Without the help of Alicia's
demon powers, you are weaklings!
Stop! I'll kill myself
if you hurt Ash!
Will you promise me
peace over Sid?
I promise, Alicia.
Come.
Alicia!
Don't be fooled, Alicia!
Alicia! Don't go!!
Ash.
Thank you for everything.
Aliciaaaa!
- Can I get that one?
- Thank you!
Be careful.
I can't believe that
Alicia was a demon.
So is everything back to normal?
It's probably a short-lived peace.
The demons have tasted
the flesh of young women.
I can't bring myself to believe
they'll stay quiet.
I'm through with this job!
Elliege!
Are you all crazy!?
There's no way we can win
against an army of monsters!
Plus, that reward ain't
enough for this job!
Gimme a break!
But you gambled away
all your reward money.
What about Alicia?
Abandoning a job you've already
accepted isn't exactly praiseworthy.
Elliege, please!
We need your Magnum!
Sorry, Ash.
Briggan and Amon's crystal weren't
able to seal Alicia's powers, but now...
our Demon Clan will rule Sid.
Right, Lavialos?
No!
No.
Are you thinking about Alicia?
Ah... No.
Because I'm half-human,
half-elf...
I was bullied a lot
when I was a child.
When I went to the village, I was
told to leave because I was an elf.
Then when I went to the forest, I was
told to leave because I was human.
But I was fine with that.
Because...
my father was completely in love
with my mother who was an elf...
and my mother was also completely in
love with my father who was a human.
Asti.
Even if Alicia is a demon...
if you love her,
you should go and get her back!
You're sweet...
I don't want to see you
just moping around.
Have you ever made love to
someone who wasn't human?
A... Ast...
I don't know
any other way to cheer you up.
It's so strange.
Our hearts are beating
so fast together and...
Why does everyone want to
make such a distinction...
between elves and humans?
You can love each other
even if she's a demon!
Ash.
Asti.
I want yours too.
Asti, I'm coming in.
OK.
Ash.
Asti... Asti...
Ash!
There are tons of them.
There must be
a hundred thousand of them!
Bring it on!
I'll play with them!
They're not the
usual forest creatures.
An army of monsters...
- I've already made up my mind!
- Good!
Elliege!
- Elliege.
- Hey.
- You're late!
- You took so long!
- You came.
- I knew you would.
Geez! Without me
you guys are too dangerous!
They're coming!
Leave this to us.
Ash, go save Alicia!
Yeah, she's probably waiting for you.
When we finish here,
we'll head straight there.
Girls... Got it!
Let's do it!
OK!
Ash, hurry and go!
Take care! Everyone!
Welcome, mortal Ash.
Lavialos!
How dare you deceive us!
Show yourself!
Where's Alicia?
Don't be so hasty.
Since you've come to my manor,
why not relax, mortal Ash?
We've only started...
Why are you going so far
to save Alicia, mortal Ash?
I am the one to be asking questions.
Why are you after Alicia?
In this world, there are some things
that humans shouldn't know.
But as a human,
you are a promising one.
Lord Harctune, who was sealed
away by God, exists in Alicia.
God?
Harctune?
That light from her chest!?
In order for the Demon Clan to
rule this world instead of humans...
we must release Lord Harctune.
Enough of your selfish idealism!
What's wrong?
I thought you were going to
protect Alicia.
What's this! You cheated again!
Of course not.
Ash, you're home late.
Do you want some Puar tea?
Ash! Elliege is being sneaky!
Alicia's in the back.
Hey! It's my turn to pick a card.
This time
I'll keep a sharp eye out.
I'm counting on you, Fromage.
He's here.
Alicia.
Give me back Alicia.
Aren't we impatient?
I'd like you to stop giving
the worthless humans your time!
Ash, will you protect me?
Yeah, I promise.
And when my friends come,
we'll get rid of the monsters in a flash.
They're really strong.
Forgive us, Alicia.
We weren't able to protect you.
But please understand this.
Everyone fought all they could.
None of us ran away.
I want you to know that.
What?
Is she trying to break the barrier?
Ash.
Why?
Why must we kill each other?
Ash.
Alicia.
Our promise...
Will you protect me?
Yeah.
What?
Everyone, combine your strength!
OK!
Demon Slayer Sword...
Grand Cross!
Axe of the Holy Mountain...
Bramma Hacker!
Lance of Virtue...
Lune Breath!
Fist of Combat Destruction...
Heavenly Battle of Devastation!
Dagger of the Sacred Beasts...
Yashima!
Blade of Divine Secrets...
Kirisamemaru!
Demon Execution Bullets...
Daisy Magnum!
Take this!
Super Combination Power!
We have no choice if Lord Harctune
has chosen the humans...
Will you protect me forever?