Master Briggan, she is not the one.
Find her.
I need the girl with
an emblem on her chest!
You can have her.
I'm Ash,
a popular adventurer for hire.
As an adventurer, I'm paid to slay
monsters that have suddenly...
appeared on Sid Continent.
A monster hunter if you will.
My next job is for
the village chief of Tylling...
a small village
on the edge of the continent.
That way!
Cries of help call to me.
Come here my dear.
- Come here!
- Don't come any closer!!
Are you all right?
Y- yes.
Who!? Who are you!?
Big guys like yourselves shouldn't
pick on a girl, you know.
Go!!
G... Go!!
Damn it!!
This is endless!
See ya!
After them!
Don't let them get away!
And... you are!?
Me? I'm Ash.
Leave the monsters to me.
Ash!?
I've been waiting for you!!
I've come from Tylling to get you.
What!?
There's a shortcut
to the village over there!
- Let's hurry!
- Ok.
- Is there something wrong?
- Huh? Um... N... nothing!!
Ash, you're a pervert.
I'll navigate from behind.
Ash, please go in front.
Yeah. Yeah.
She called me a pervert...
Thank you for coming such a long way.
Welcome to the village of Tylling.
Sir Ash.
Father, Ash has already saved me.
Oh! Thank you!
You must be tired. Let us continue
this conversation at the manor.
Until now, the monsters...
stayed on Demon Mountain
and never came to the village but...
did you know...
long ago, there was once
another continent west of Sid?
Yeah. I heard
it vanished overnight.
The "Ancient Ones," from the legends,
built four Pillars of Light...
surrounding the continent
and washed everything away.
It seems the Pillars of Light
have been erected once more.
Are you saying the light
created those monsters?
A villager who barely escaped alive
says he saw the Pillar of Light...
deep within the caverns of
Demon Mountain.
Next is Sid Continent then...?
I do not know that but...
My concern is the monsters.
For some reason, they keep
abducting the young girls...
Now all that's left is Alicia.
If the legend is involved,
it's not the usual monster hunt!
I do know this.
All of my friends
have been abducted...
The other day
it was my childhood friend, Les.
Please, Ash!
Please slay the monsters!
Ok. I'll take the job.
Even I'll have problems
if the ground is gone.
But before that,
I'll need some time.
Hey!!
You girls were pretty fast!
You asked us to hurry,
so we came as fast as we could.
I see.
- Fa-Fa.
- Hi!
- Nagi.
- Hey.
- Asti.
- Hiya.
- Fromage.
- Hi!
- Tanya.
- Long time no see!
Where's Elliege?
We were together
up till now but...
She went straight to the bar.
Again?
Sorry, guys!
Seems like I win again!
Thank you! Thank you!
How about another hand!?
- Ou! Ou! Ou!!
- Who are you!?
I need to borrow her
for a minute, guys.
Fuck off, Ash!
We're just getting started!!
You can have this back.
What did you do that for?
Asshole!
- You probably cheated anyway!
- That bitch!
Pillar of Light?
This job is going to be difficult.
Hey, with everyone's weapons
and my magnum...
we can finish the job like always!
So what are we going to do?
We leave here
early tomorrow morning.
We infiltrate Demon Mountain
and kill their leader.
Until then,
everyone get some rest.
Why didn't you say so, Ash!?
Then off I go to get some rest!
Gambling's calling me!
It's an enemy attack!!
It's monsters! Run!!
Come to get killed, monsters!?
- I'm here to help!
- Nagi!!
As you can see...
Ash, come back! Alicia's...
Damn it! They're decoys!
Nagi, take care of this!
Let me go!
Let them go, you monster!
You're going to get it!
- Ash!
Alicia...
Forgive me, chief,
it's my fault.
It can't be helped.
Maybe this is destiny.
We leave for Demon Mountain now!
Nagi, stay with Elliege
and protect the village!
Why!? I'm coming too!
If the village is attacked, Elliege
alone won't be able to handle it!
Please!
I see. Be careful then!
You are the last girl.
You're not a village girl,
are you?
So what? You'll pay for this,
you buck-toothed pervert!
What a spirited girl...
Do away with her!
What's wrong, Asti!?
I hear Tanya's screams.
- Above us!
- Let's go!
Hey!
He hasn't changed one bit.
Asti, next time,
don't use the tomahawk...
Stop! Let go of Tanya!
Don't worry about her.
Now, show me
the sealed emblem.
That's enough, you pervert!
W... what!?
Now you're all gonna get it!
- Ash.
- You again!
Tear them to shreds!!
Alicia.
Are you all right?
Y- yes.
Ash! Buck-toothed pervert
is getting away!
Wait, you!
Master Briggan! Master Briggan!
What's with the ruckus, Ed?
It's terrible, Master Briggan.
Our troops have been annihilated.
- What!?
- There you are!
It's the Pillar of Light.
Seems like this is their stronghold.
It's them! How dare you!!
Master Briggan is
going to show you now!!
You must be the leader
of the monsters!
Yes! I am one of the
four lords of darkness, Briggan!
Are you surprised?
It's just some fat pervert.
- I hate those.
- It's not my taste.
The boss of perverts
is a pervert himself.
Hey! Why don't you act
a little scared! That's rude!
Then why don't you make us!
Foolish humans!
Graviton Wave!
Are you going to give me
any more lip?
My body won't move.
How dare you
hurt my dear monsters!
As punishment,
I'm taking your panties!
My name is Ed.
Not buck-toothed pervert.
One panty!
Two panties!
Three panties!
Stop! I'm a guy!
It's ok that you're a guy.
Stop!
Four panties!
Ed, make sure you hang them
in the panty collection room.
Yes, sir.
Playtime is over.
Offer your flesh and blood
to my sword!
Wait!
There're panties over here!
There you go!
There are two!!
And they're still warm.
Let's put them up!
Where should I put it?
That was a close one!
- Now!
- This is our chance!
Demon Slayer Sword...
Grand Cross!
Axe of the Holy Mountain...
Bramma Hacker!
Lance of Virtue...
Lune Breath!
Fist of Combat...
Heavenly Battle of Devastation!
Take this!
Combine Powers!
Master Briggan, maybe that wasn't
the right time to collect panties!
That's right! What ever happened
to the girl with the emblem!?
- It's going to collapse!
- Hurry!
Panties, panties.
Run!