As a demon hunter...
I was hired by the chief of
a small village called Tylling.
There, I met Alicia, who was
being chased by monsters.
- Are you all right?
- Y- yes.
Father, Ash has already saved me.
Oh! Thank you!
Came to get killed, monsters!?
Let me go!
Damn it!
Take this!
Combine Powers!
I thought this was going to be
an easy job, but I was wrong.
I was involved in an event that would
shape the future of Sid Continent!
He... he's a
powerful monster, Nagi!
Who are you!?
Amon.
The mortals call me the Fire Demon
of the Lords of Darkness.
I don't know
who you are, but...
how dare you set the village
on fire, you bastard!!
Why did you do this?
To exterminate the humans
from Sid Continent.
What the hell are you
talking about, you pyro!?
Don't you understand
the consequences...
when you talk to me like that?
He's coming, Elliege!
Take this!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Let go!
Normal weapons won't phase him!
Elliege! Nagi!
What are you doing, Elliege!?
Ash!
This is not the time to be gawking!
He suddenly showed up and turned
the whole village into flames!
He burned my clothes too!
Another monster?
What would you do
if I were?
Ain't that obvious!?
Ash!
It's useless.
The attacks aren't working!
That emblem on her chest!
Is this one Alicia?
Are you after Alicia too?
It wasn't just Briggan?
What?
You know Briggan?
We finished him off!
You defeated Briggan!?
We destroyed the
Pillar of Light with him!
Defeated by humans...
How pathetic.
Well... He did leave me
some amusement, I guess.
W... wait!
Let me award you
for defeating Briggan.
He's one of the Lords of Darkness
as Briggan was...
but he's no comparison!
That Amon!
This is beyond the job
of a monster hunter!
What is happening
on this continent?
To get any answers,
we have to save Alicia at once!
But we don't know
where Amon is.
I have an idea
where he might be.
A traveler who came over
the Mountain of Fire had said...
he saw an ominous manor
at the banks of Meda.
At the banks of Meda...
It is a manor that did not exist
until Amon appeared.
That's got to be it!
But Ash! If we go now, we'll be in
the same situation as we were earlier.
You're right, and I won't be at ease
until I find a stronger weapon!
I would like a skilled blacksmith
to forge my new sword.
Then you should visit
the town of Selenis.
Selenis?
There are skilled blacksmiths and
an array of weapons and armor there.
Let's do it!!
Only a rifle that can shoot a
demon slaying bullet is our hope!
Yes. There's no point in going
if we can't fight.
That will take too much time.
Then why don't we split
into two groups?
It seems that's the only way.
Noooo!
Why is Lavialos
interested in you?
You look like
an ordinary girl to me.
No!
Stop!
I want to see
what kind of powers you hide.
I don't know!
I don't know anything
and I don't have any powers!!
Really.
Nooo!!
Show me the emblem once more!
Come on.
The fun has just begun.
No...
Stop...
Stop!!
I've finally got her!!
Looks like we'll be able to get
weapons and armor here.
I want to catch up to the others.
Do what you need to do and
let's meet back here in an hour.
- Got it!
- In an hour then!
Well... A couple of hands
won't hurt.
The ones that defeated
Master Briggan are here...
getting weapons and armor.
Perhaps to save Alicia, who was
captured by Master Amon.
No matter what weapon or armor
the humans may equip...
they will not be able
to defeat Amon.
Punish those who
oppose our Demon Clan!
Yes. There shall be
no need to trouble you...
Mistress Lucretia, one of
the Four Lords of Darkness.
- Savia!
- Yes ma'am!
The mortals have decided to call us
the Four Lords of Darkness.
Do not think I am the same
as Briggan or Amon!!
But of course, my lady.
Well, we're here at Amon's manor,
but how should we attack?
What are you saying, Ash?
There's no point in strategizing now!
Here we are, so we should just
go ahead and take the orthodox route!
The orthodox route?
- Open up, Amon!
- Hey!!
Give us Alicia back!
Hey, you guys!
It's not that simple...
What did I say?
Where's Alicia!?
Damn pesky humans!
Sit there and watch!!
Let me go, you imbecile!
F... Fromage...
How shall I deal with you...
Stop it!
Damn it.
Ash!
Alicia.
I can't even get near him!
Let's combine our powers
and fight together!
Alicia.
Oh! You still had
some strength left.
Say your prayers!
Don't make me laugh!
We won't be able to defeat him.
Don't worry. Trust me.
Burn to a crisp!
What!?
This power...
What just happened?
Selenis is a lively town.
I wonder where they are?
Elliege is going to be so surprised
when we tell her we defeated Amon.
No doubt about it!
It's their comrades!
We've got to report this to Savia!
Elliege is probably here.
Have you seen
a girl gambler around?
Girl gambler?
She has chestnut brown hair
and wears a gun belt.
She was taken away
by Lucretia's soldiers.
Lucretia? Who's that?
I'll tell you, Ash.
Long time no see, Ash.
You had an acquaintance
in this town?
She's not just an acquaintance.
Ash is my dear little brother.
You're Ash's sister!?
We're not related by blood though.
She's more of a pain in the ass.
It's good to see you too.
Anyway, do you know about
Elliege and the others, Savia?
Don't be so hasty, Ash.
Let's celebrate our reunion.
Savia!
Don't worry.
Your friends are fine.
To our reunion!
Cheers!
Savia.
What kind of child was Ash?
Let's see. Ash was...
What's wrong, Tanya?
I'm getting really sleepy.
Me too.
So am I.
Savia!
You're still green, Ash.
You bitch.
What are you staring at!
Why don't I make you all
a really yummy, rich dish?
I think their dinner is us!
H- hey wait!!
What're you guys thinking!!
Are we going to be the
subjects of their amusement?
No, I don't want to!
Fa-Fa, are you all right!?
I don't think this is the time
to worry about others!
Stop it! Don't touch me!!
Fa-Fa.
Open the gates!
My Lady Savia is here to have an
audience with Mistress Lucretia!!
Have you brought them?
Yes. You can see the girl is Alicia.
The other one is Ash, who has slain
Master Briggan and Master Amon.
Are you Lucretia!?
Ash! But you drank
the sleep potion!
You're the one who's green!
Thanks for bringing me here!
Now, release my comrades!
They just had the time of
their lives with my demons.
What!?
Ash!
Stop defying Mistress Lucretia!
Serving guys like them!?
It's not like you!!
Brother and sister killing each other
is one form of entertainment...
Savia! Kill him!
But...
Hey, Savia...
What are you doing?
We're not kids anymore!
You can't beat me!
She's my opponent!!
My body...
won't move!
Savia!
What!?
Stop!
Saviaaaa!
Ash.
Sis.
It's been awhile since
you called me that.
I wish I met you not as a sister...
My lady!!
How were you able to move!?
I'm not going to forgive you.
You should be honored that...
a mere human like you
shall die by my sword!
Why are you doing this?
What does the Demon Clan want?
Why are you after Alicia!?
A lowly human like you would not
understand even if I told you!
We shall erase your foolish race
from this continent!
This is?
You!
You're awake.
Alicia.
Lucretia. I can't have you
defeated too.