Sex Marionette.
I forgot that my private school is closed today.
I even forgot to bring my cell phone and I can't contact my girlfriend.
I don't want to visit her house if she is not home. What should I do?
What's the matter with you?
Kei.
Hi. Did you see Suika?
Suika?
She is the girl who always sits in the front by the windows in Mr.Anzai's class.
I know her.
We are supposed to meet here.
I haven't seen her.
I was 10 minutes late but I can't believe that she is later than I am.
Are you seeing her?
Not really.
I am going home.
If you see her, you can do whatever you want with her.
Give me a break.
She is pretty hot but I guess she isn't your type.
I don't know. I haven't really looked at her face.
I will leave you alone anyways. See you later.
What? Where are you going?
I can't believe that he left.
I wonder where Suika is.
Oh no.
Suika.
Ouch.
Are you ok?
Thank you.
Ken went home.
What?
Oh Ok.
She looks pretty hot.
If you go now, you may be able to catch him.
Well, I guess it's too late.
Any injuries?
No, I am fine.
You are a little careless.
Call my name.
You are Suika, right?
I am happy that you remembered my name.
Yeah.
I am so happy.
If you don't mind, can we go to our classroom together?
The school is closed today.
I know.
Her eyes…
I don't have any other plans so I will go with you.
Why are we going there?
Well…
Private School.
Why is she breathing hard?
Why is she breathing hard? Is she excited about something?
Her eyes again.
You sometimes looked at me from behind in the class, right?
Did I?
You didn't even look at me in the eyes when we passed each other.
What is she trying to tell me?
You are finally doing it, Maya-san?
You want to have sex with me, right?
Fuck me?
I came here for that.
You shouldn't leave now.
If you insist, Maya-san.
Suck it. That's what you want, right?
Yes.
Your eyes say so.
You are good.
Lean against the desk next.
You are so wet.
Oh yes.
Don't look. I am shy.
You fuck around with Kei, right?
Your juice is coming out.
You love having sex, huh? Your juice is coming out a lot.
I will fuck you so well.
Oh yes.
I realized that I am a little jealous of Kei when I saw her face.
It's tight.
I don't know why it's not going in at all even though she is wet enough already.
It's tight. It's great.
It's so tight.
Please forgive me now. Please.
I've always liked you, Maya-san.
I've always wanted to tell you that I like you.
Because I like you a lot.
Suika.
I am not sure what I should do about her.
I've always liked you and wanted to tell you that I like you.
Because I like you a lot.
Right. Her eyes. I like her eyes.
But I have known Kei since middle school so I need to talk to him.
My parents are out now.
Why don't you dry your hair by yourself?
Can you do it, Kei-chan? Because we're so close. Please.
I am not a professional hair dresser.
You are really good, Kei-chan.
You've done it before.
I had no idea that he has this cute friend.
I love how you dry my hair because it feels so good.
Ok then. You have pretty makeup today. Are you going on a date?
No, I am not.
But I have someone whom I want to ask to go out with.
Is that right?
You sound uninterested.
You are right.
I guess men like a mature beautiful woman with makeup.
What are you talking about?
I always see a lot of mature beautiful women around you.
Yeah, I'm not really into younger girls.
Oh, I was right.
Mariko.
I look so childish. I am not attractive.
That's why you don't care about me.
But I am not a child anymore.
I can't believe what you've just said.
Mariko. You are wrong.
What?
Kei-chan.
What's going on?
Stop. Someone may see us. Stop.
It's going to be fine. Nobody will see us.
The curtains are shut. No need to worry about it.
But…
Just relax.
I like your pink color.
Oh my. I feel so shy.
You are so cute, Mariko.
It feels so good, Kei-chan.
Come closer, Mariko.
Take it easy. You are going to be just fine.
You can just get on top of me.
I've always wanted to hold you like this, Mariko.
I am sorry. I knew your feelings.
I was just being a coward.
That's ok. I know your feelings now.
I am sorry that I made you worried.
I am so sorry.
It's ok.
I can't believe what they were doing.
Kei.
My parents should be on their trip for another week.
Why is the light on?
I have to take care of this until the guy next door comes back.
I should be able to use this as long as I read the instructions.
This is the tampon.
I need to take off my underwear.
Is this the right place to put it in?
Oh no, what's going on? It's not going in.
Looks like it's stuck.
Uruna?
Shigeki-Oni-chan?
What are you doing here?
I look so childish and am still growing.
But I am old enough to get married.
I just asked you what you are doing.
I have to practice using a tampon that all of my friends have already used.
Practice?
Yes. Your mother and father left the house key for me just in case before they left for their trip.
That's why I am here for cleaning and cooking for you.
I couldn't practice using a tampon in my room because I am too shy but I can in your room.
Don't use a tampon in my room!
I had no idea that you were coming home.
Also, I couldn't put it in by myself.
Can you take a look at it?
Look at it?
Ok.
Is she serious?
This is…just like an injection.
Ok. Show me.
Like this?
Ready?
It's not going in. I have to open it wider.
It's very pink.
It's getting wet. It may go in a little now.
What?
I am not supposed to put it in deeper?
I am getting hornier.
Let me open it.
Let me open it. It's slippery.
Shigeki-Oni-chan.
Did you feel good?
What are you going to do?
I want to make sure if you can take something bigger than the tampon.
Go ahead.
Shigeki-Oni-chan. Don't stop.
It's pretty tight.
Please.
Let me touch here.
Yes.
It feels hot.
His dick is in.
Uruna. Sorry. I was just…
Don't worry.
My dream came true at last.
I am so happy that my first man was you.
Is this your underwear?
Oh no. Don't look.
Why does she care?
We just had sex.
Shigeki?
Are you still seeing Moe, Maya?
Why? Any problem?
I can't believe that you are seeing her because she isn't hot at all.
You think so?
You always like a girl who wears glasses with braided hair.
Why don't you change your taste in girls?
None of your business.
Is Shigeki kinky?
Is that why he still asks me to keep my glasses and braids?
He thinks that I am cute?
I won't forgive him.
She is late.
Shigeki!
Is that you, Moe?
What happened to your glasses and hair?
I changed it up.
Come here.
Why did you bring me here?
Because we can talk without interruptions.
We have nothing to talk about.
I have to do this then.
Are you ready to talk now?
No need for that, Shigeki.
Are you sure? You are already wet down here.
No matter what you say, I know your weak places.
You are such a horny girl.
I can't help it.
Don't stop, Shigeki.
Your body is so honest.
So wet down here.
Wow. It's so wet!
You are too loud!
Nobody comes up here anyways.
This is a a little treat for you. Put your knees down.
Suck it. I know you want it.
Ah. Suck it more.
Are you ready to talk now?
Not yet?
I will make you feel even better.
Don't stop.
Are you feeling good?
You are so kinky, Moe.
It's so hot.
It's getting tighter. Are you close to coming?
I am coming.
Are you really climaxing, Shigeki?
What? Were you listening to the conversation with my friend?
Yes.
That was because I don't want anybody to see your real cuteness without glasses and the hair.
What?
I want to be the only one to know the real you.
I don't want any other men to find out how cute you are.
Shigeki.
Because you are so cute.
Really?
I like your usual look with your glasses and braided hair.
It looks neat and clean.
I like your glasses so much.
I guess he has strange taste.
I haven't seen Mana for a long time.
Yes. Shigeki.
What are you doing?
I borrowed this from my work. Do I look cute?
Yes. You look great!
Really? Thank you.
Oh my goodness!
Be careful.
What are you talking about?
I can't make this outfit dirty because it's not mine.
I like your tail.
Are you listening?
Are you going to put your finger in my hole again?
You are so used to this, right?
Well, yes, I am.
Your body doesn't lie.
Your body doesn't lie. Your pussy is so wet.
You are so aroused.
Are you ready to take this yet?
What? ok.
Not my dick.
Really?
Yes, I am not putting it in. Can you suck it instead?
This is…
What?
This is hard.
It's like eating a carrot.
Is that right? Why don't you take my carrot?
Put your hands down and put your butt up.
Oh God. In my butt hole.
What's this?
It's a carrot.
What? Why?
I told you no dick.
Oh wow. Move slowly.
You like this, huh? Do you need more than this?
Oh yes.
You are cute. You are so cute!
Mana.
I am so sorry.
You are a liar.
I don't think you should wear that anymore, Mana.
All men will go crazy about your outfit.
Really? Just like you went crazy?
Please do not wear that in front of other men.
Does that mean…?
Of course.
I am so happy.
I just wanted to wear this in my room.
Actually, I wanted to wear this. Look at this!
I actually wear this for my work.
I like this too!
You are so horny. In my ass again.
I am here. I bought some veggies and meats.
Ok!
Oh shoot. I totally forgot about that.
Come on in.
My house isn't clean yet.
Hello!
When did they become friends?
How did you put on the outfit?
You look good.
Can I try that on?
You look cute!
I can't get out from here.
Oh no. My glasses!