SUSPECT COMMITS SUICIDE IN CUSTODY.
Dad...
l believed you were innocent...
l trusted you...
Go away!
Whoa!
Don't be so cold. We just want to pay our respects.
What are you doing!
What are we doing?
No! Stop!
Not here! Not in front of my dad!
There's no need to respect a murderer.
We're going to make an example out of you.
Your father died before the law could punish him!
No!
Hey, this situation...
Yeah, it spices it up...
Stop!
No... No... No...
These guys are being manipulated by the Atonement Newspaper...
By the power of my writing!
Stop!
Her ass is so loose now.
Your daughter is a slut.
Her clit is swollen. She's feeling it in front of her dad.
That's not true! That's not true! No...
That went far.
No!
What a sinful woman. You came in front of your dead father!
A terrible daughter like you...
No, stop...
You're really wet. lt's going to drip.
lt feels so good...
Did you hear her? She said it feels good. What a slut!
lt won't be good if the neighbors hear. Konishi, shut her up!
Okay.
l'm going to cum soon.
M... Me too.
More... More...
Has she lost it?
This is the real her.
More. Give me more. Make me go crazy...
You don't have to ask. The five of us will fuck you until you break.
That makes me so happy!
This is the real her? They're wrong.
l'm the one who made her a slut. lt's the power of my pen.
Yesterday, Nanase Hiramatsu engaged in sexual acts with several...
...male classmates, right in front of her late father's remains.
We must pray that she receives further punishment for her shameful act.
This is...
Stand! Bow!
Nanase, hey...
What is it?
Can l talk to you for a minute?
Yes?
This.
So it's true. Who is it? l want to help you.
l won't let you go through something like this again.
Damn that Nanase, she...
lt doesn't matter either way.
This might interfere with the punishment.
We need to take care of it before it does.
TENNIS CLUB
Who's there?
This is the female tennis team's room. Get out of here.
There's no need to snap at us. We're here because we have business.
Business?
To shut you up.
So you guys are the ones who did that to Nanase.
So Nanase didn't tell you? She's starting to understand her sinful position.
What are you talking about?
You guys are just rapists!
Ohbari, who cares, let's do it.
The tennis team will be here to get changed any minute.
lt's not going to go your way!
They won't come for another two hours. Too bad.
The team captain is quite cooperative.
Narumi?
That's right.
S... Stop... No!
Stop!
TENNIS CLUB
No! Stop it!
You're so sweaty, l can smell you.
l guess even hot professors smell sweaty too.
Hey! Let me smell too!
lt smells awesome.
Professor, you have a very distinct taste. l'm going to cum from excitement.
lt's nice and salty, so it's pretty tasty.
Help me... l'm sorry...
Say what? l'm sorry?
We're the ones who need to apologize. You don't have to.
Forget about the Atonement Newspaper Or else...
...there are going to be pictures and articles circulating about you everywhere.
l can't anymore. Let me fuck her first!
Wow! lt's so tight!
No!
Damn she's loud.
Shut up!
l can't hold it anymore!
M... Me either.
There's no time to relax, professor.
Let me elaborate further about what happened at Nanase's house the other day.
l plan to publish more editions like this in the future...
...so make sure to read those, too.
Who wrote this?
Narumi Aizawa can't write this well.
Judging from the content, it has to be someone who was there... Then...
Damn it, who wrote this?
What do you mean? You're saying we should quit?
No, but there's the possibility that other people know about it.
l think we should cool it a little.
That's not like you. Your father will take care of it if something happens.
Your dad's a politician. We've done a lot of stuff before...
...but we've never been in trouble with the cops.
l bet it's something else.
Well... Miho found out.
Miho?
l'm going to cum.
Cum! Cum!
You're not yourself these days. We only fuck once when we go to a hotel now.
l'm exhausted from thinking about my future.
l hope that's what it is.
W... What?
lf this was true, l'd be really pissed.
But l wonder if anyone else would have the balls to do something like this?
l don't know what you're talking about.
Whatever happened to
"Brothers before Whores?"
l'm out guys.
What do you think?
Anyone who would get in the way of the punishments is a traitor...
Ohbari needs to be punished too...
We're going to do it to Ohbari?
Of course. lsn't that our responsibility? You're the new leader, take charge.
M... Me?
Who else?
Yeah, we're counting on you, boss.
Boss!
l have to figure out who wrote that article no matter what.
We can't stop until l figure it out.
You know what's going to happen to you guys if you go through with this.
Shut up! You're not the boss anymore. Keep quiet!
Why you...
We said, shut up!
There you go!
Look at you now.
Kato!
This is for choosing a girl over your duty! You traitor!
Look!
Miho!
What's the meaning of this?
lt's payback.
Her clit's getting hard.
She's a horny pervert.
lt's holding on tight. Ohbari, l'm jealous you have a girl like her.
The cum dripped down to my hand... it's sticky.
She really likes it.
She tastes like Madoka Yuuki.
Mikimoto, l've been thinking... You like Madoka don't you?
No, l don't.
Don't lie. Here, suck her off.
lmagine it's Madoka.
Come on, just go.
lt's not good to hold it in.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about. Everyone does it.
She's going to pee!
Look at this! l think you're taking too much fluid.
Damn, it stinks.
lt's foaming.
Bring the ex-boss.
Ohbari, you must be thirsty since you've been tied up for so long. You can drink it.
Miho is more important than our friendship, right?
Drink it if you love her so much!
Drink it.
Look at him drink it!
lt's his girlfriend's.
l'm sure it tastes exceptional.
Let's fuck her.
l'll take her mouth.
l wouldn't expect anything less from our ex-boss's woman. She feels great!
Move.
l said move. Don't make me do all the work.
Hey, if you don't move, your boyfriend's gonna get it.
You want that?
Stop! You're going to kill him.
Then listen to what l say!
Moan!
Miho's really feeling it.
She's not doing it to save you.
l'm going to cum!
lt's this late already?
Let's wrap it up. l want to take a nap before the last period.
Yeah.
Let's finish up.
What should we do?
Don't worry about her. She's not going to snitch.
That'll just put her in a bad position.
You're right.
lt's not my fault.
lt's because Ohbari cheated on her. Yeah... That's why!
Run!
FEMALE STUDENT JUMPS OFF
BUILDING AND COMMITS SUICIDE.
Miho committed suicide because she was stressed about her future.
l want the professors to listen to the students, and make sure...
...to lock up after class is over. Also, l want all of the professors to guide...
But her body was covered in semen, right?
...the students of Akemi University. Our school has a long tradition...
Her family and the school are ashamed...
...they don't want to make it public.
...of sending the brightest students off into the world in every field, and...
lt's been a month, but our lives are back to normal as if nothing ever happened.
Everything went according to my plan.
The group's hierarchy shifted and now l can keep her all to myself.
The Atonement Newspaper's influence was growing.
Obviously l can't write about Miho's death...
...but l'm sure there'll be other opportunities in the future.
My main goal was to sharpen my writing skills with this newspaper.
One day, l'll become a world renowned journalist...
...and manipulate the world with my pen.
But one thing bothers me... Who wrote the other Atonement Newspaper?
When my father died, l changed.
l no longer have any family who will worry about my actions.
After l changed, l continued to act out the role of a rape victim...
...and published the Atonement Newspaper, to create confusion.
Now, l've obtained the secrets of all the future elites.
With this, l'll get the best life money can buy. l swear it...