What did you want to talk to me about?
l don't have time for this. l need to go home because my tutor's coming.
A personal tutor?
For the daughter of a murderer?
What is this?
This is...
As you know, our classmate Nanase Hiramatsu's father was arrested...
...for murder the other day.
We are sure having a criminal for a father...
...has affected Nanase Hiramatsu to some degree.
How can we let a classmate like her be amongst us like this?
We must punish Nanase Hiramatsu.
What? Stop it.
No!
Please stop. Stop! No! No! Please! Stop!
l said stop!
lt hurts!
Look at Nanase. She's refusing, but she's dripping wet.
You're right. lt's because she's the daughter of a murder. She's a slut.
Ohbari, hurry up. How long are you going to make me wait?
Calm down, we have lots of time.
Yeah... You're squeezing so tight, you're going to make me cum.
lt hurts!
l can't hold it anymore. l'm going to cum. l'm going to cum. l'm going to cum.
Cum inside her. Who cares, she's the daughter of a murderer.
Yeah. Yeah.
B... But...
l'm going to cum!
No!
Whoops. Sorry about that. lt felt so good, l forgot to pull out.
Okay, my turn.
No! No!
You know it feels good. Moan. lt's not good to hold it in.
Our country does not prosecute the criminal's family.
But humans can change quite easily.
lf anger is matched with subliminal resentment and desire, it consumes them.
And they will seek to release the pain through unsatiable lust.
l don't know who wrote the Atonement Newspaper, but it's well written.
lt's the voice of our class.
We need to thank that newspaper...
lf that didn't circulate we might have let a sinful woman like her roam free.
My experiment was a success.
The Atonement Newspaper manipulated them into doing this.
l... l can't anymore.
Me either.
No!
This is the power of the pen.
lsn't this the epitome of the phrase,
"The pen is mightier than the sword?"
And l am the one who wielded this power.
Looks like Miho and Ohbari are going strong.
l'm so jealous. Maybe l should get a boyfriend. Right, Nanase?
Nanase.
You're spacing out. Were you listening to me?
Sorry.
Miho Minakami. She's from another homeroom...
...so she doesn't know about the Atonement Newspaper.
And of course she has no idea...
...that her lover is one of the leaders of a gang rape group.
Madoka Yuuki. She's one of the most beautiful girls at our school.
She's completely out of my league, but l hope to make...
...some kind of connection with her, because her father is a famous journalist.
Yesterday afternoon, Nanase Hiramasu was summoned...
...by a few male students from our class and was sexually assaulted on campus.
She could have easily figured out what would happen...
...but she chose to step into a trap.
She willingly submitted herself, to atone for the sins of her murderous father.
Who can blame her for what she did, if it was to atone for her father's sins?
ls this for real?
ls this allowed?
Who are the "few male students"?
What's with the commotion? Come on, we're starting class.
Stand! Bow! Sit!
Let's continue from last time. Open to page forty-five.
Nanase is acting strange today. Something must be bugging her.
This is...
FOOD SCIENCES
Madoka!
Nanase, what happened? l was so worried about you...
No! Don't come in!
Where's Mikimoto?
He ran out, saying he forgot he had something to do.
What's going on?
What to do? The only ones who are allowed to be here are the punishers...
...and the ones seeking atonement. Madoka, which one are you?
Atonement?
Ohbari, you're wasting your time. lt's obvious she needs to be punished.
Yeah. That's right.
l see. l guess it'll make it more interesting.
Don't! Madoka hasn't done anything.
Leave her alone! Have your way with me!
No!
Madoka!
No. Stop.
l've got my future as a journalist to consider...
l can't join in on assaulting Madoka.
But l have the responsiblity of publishing the Atonement paper.
l must observe what happens.
No! Stop!
Tastes good...
This one too.
Let's compare and see who tastes better.
Good idea.
lt tastes different.
lt's hard to put an end to this.
Let's switch. l can't eat her out if you fuck her.
Fine.
l can't get enough.
Good eats!
Nanase's dripping wet and she's twitching inside.
Slut.
Madoka needs to learn how to relax.
Not there! lt's dirty!
lt's not dirty. The hottest girl in our class also has a great tasting ass.
Modoka's getting wet from her ass getting licked. She's a pervert.
That's great. A hot perverted bitch! We're going to have lots of fun.
Please stop...
Why am l...
l mustn't! l need to stop paying attention to Madoka!
l need to calmly observe the situation as a journalist.
What a great tool to have in the Food Science's room.
Fresh vegetables need good salad dressing.
You're such a pervert.
lt's too early to relax.
lt's our turn now.
Looks like you're feeling it.
That's right... You girls should be happy.
lt's a perfect time away from studying.
l can understand Nanase, but it's scary that they did this to Madoka too.
lt's best to stay away from what they're doing.
Madoka Yuuki? l wish l was there to punish her too.
l wonder who did it? Do you think it's Ohbari's group?
Who's writing the newspaper?
l see...
You're not that pretty. l wonder why the guys like you so much?
Narumi... What are you trying to do? Tell me.
l read the Atonement Newspaper.
That article said everything that's been on my mind all this time.
Madoka, you deserve to be punished.
Come on.
Don't move.
Don't move. l'm not a pro at this, so if you move l'll end up slicing it off.
l have no idea how many men you've fucked...
...but l doubt you'll want to fuck them again for a while.
l did a pretty good job. Hey, look!
Oh, cute!
But it looks gross when it twitches.
Why are you doing this?
Because l'm popular with the boys? Because the professors like me?
Who do you think you are!
Hurry up. l have relatives coming over today, so l have to go home soon.
Let me see.
lt's warm.
lt's foaming.
l bet the guys would happily drink this if they found out it was Madoka's.
Yeah, l bet we could sell it.
Hey, Madoka. Chug this.
l heard piss is good for you.
l guess your piss tastes nasty. That's too bad. We can't sell it.
Please no more... l'll never do anything to defy you girls...
Hey, do you smell that?
Yeah, l wonder what it is?
Ew! Madoka, this is pee. Stop joking around.
Madoka Yuuki was punished yesterday in a female lavatory.
lt was a justified punishment, done by brave girls...
...against Madoka Yuuki, who was acting as if she were the class queen.
Yesterday, an Atonement Newspaper was published...
...citing the punishment done by the women of the class.
That issue was a fake Atonement Newspaper.
Anyone who does not argue the content, lf another fake is published...
...will be punished just like Nanase Hiramatsu.
This is a warning.
Hey, Narumi... Was it you who wrote it?
So what if l did?
l'm scared. You might get punished.
lt's just a scare tactic. lt's just a peeping tom newspaper. lt's not real either.
l'll keep writing if it brings down Madoka's popularity!
No... No... No...
Good, Nanase. You came without wearing underwear like l told you to.
You're getting wet.
Look at all these people around you. You should be ashamed.
What?
Haven't you read the latest Atonement paper?
Hey, show her.
Here.
lt's a grave crime to publish a fake paper and create confusion amongst the class.
Meaning you're just as guilty and in need of punishment as Nanase.
Don't hold it in. Tell us how good it feels.
No... no!
lt's time to switch. lt's your turn to pleasure us.
There's still time until we arrive at the school station.
Make us cum at least once before we get there.
lf you don't, we'll just have to invite someone unrelated like Madoka again.
Nanase. Are you going to keep committing these crimes?
Narumi, how about you?
No, l don't deserve this.
You don't?
Are you saying this paper is lying?
You leave us no choice. We'll have to take the initiative then.
lt hurts!
You're too loud. Are you sure you want everyone to find out what's going on?
She's feeling it. She's such a slut.
Hey, l haven't cum yet. Let me at her.
Use her mouth. She's right there.
Good call.
Don't soil the train. We have to respect public property.
Swallow all the cum.
Let's see... l want to be satisfied a different way.
We're so lucky to have the daughter of a murderer in our school.
Yeah, if we did this to anyone else we'd get sued.
l'm going to cum.
Me too.
They're doing exactly what l want them to do.
My writing is maklng them do this.
Narumi Aizawa, how dare you write a fake Atonement Newspaper twice...
...even when l warned you not to!
You're no match for my writing.