My name is Shinji Tachibana.
l'm a college student, dreaming of becoming a painter.
One day, a beautiful woman appeared in my room, naked.
Her name's Yuria. This beautiful woman with huge boobs is...
...according to her, an alien.
She says she came to earth to look for her sister...
...who's been wandering around the universe.
lt's hard to believe, sounds like a plot from a cheap anime show...
...but since that day, Yuria and l started looking for her sister.
Alisa is, like her sister, a sexy woman with a humongous rack.
As the typical "indecisive main male character" that l am...
...l was powerless in front of these boobie sisters...
And there l was, easily seduced by her sister, Alisa.
Invasion of the Boobie Snatchers Part 2
Good morning.
We did it so many times last night, but look at this.
You've gotten so hard already.
You're amazing!
Oh, if you do that...
Now it's my turn.
Hurry up.
lt feels great...
There, right there...
Lick from my clit all the way up to my butthole!
You make me tremble with pleasure.
Shinji, it's not only your penis that's great...
Your tongue is amazing!
l've never felt like this.
Right there...
Oh, you're so good!
Harder! Grab my butt harder!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
l don't understand women...
Jerk!
Uh-oh!
l'm sorry, Yuria...
Damn you, Shinji!
Where have you been, leaving me all alone!
Where? Um, you know...
Didn't l warn you?
l told you to be careful with my sister!
You had sex with her, didn't you?
lt must mean ''yes'' if you can't answer me.
You jerk! Bastard!
You're not used to a human body, you shouldn't drink so much.
What are you blaming him for?
Did you already forget what you've done?
That's why l can't trust women.
Shut up!
Bring me more booze!
l'm so sorry.
Shedding tears now?
You're such an actress.
l'm sorry.
l'll do anything you want to make it up to you.
Really?
Yes.
Anything?
Then, here.
Delicious...
Do all earth women eat like this everyday?
This is mine. Okay, Shinji?
Yes...
What a great view!
lt feels great!
Oh no, l'm going to come!
l'm going to come!
That's pretty bad!
Shut up.
He'll never be an artist.
lt's none of your business!
Please, stop it...
Moan louder. Our customers like it that way.
Come on, suck it hard, or else.
Look, she's getting wet.
Hold on, l'm gonna shoot a hot load inside you.
No, please stop it!
So Tashiro, you say she never loses, huh?
Yes, sir.
l don't know how, but she knows which horse will win.
l see...
All right, bring her to me.
Well, Boss, she's not a normal woman, you see...
She has a tail.
Like this?
Well, kind of...
Perfect.
l was getting bored with earth women anyway.
She's probably a Plometeusian or something.
Bring her to me.
Y-Yes, sir.
l know!
What's wrong with me?
l just want to paint so bad for some reason today...
lt's done!
Wow! Shinji, that's great!
What is it?
Sis?
Thank you for ridiculing me all this time...
From now on, you'll be our slave.
There's some residue in this glass...
ls she drugged?
But...
Let's go find her.
Okay.
Don't try to do anything stupid.
The cuffs aren't going to come off so easily.
Croak. Croak. Croak.
Go ahead, Boss.
What?
She won't be useful after what l do to her, so l'll go last.
Let Shoji go first.
Hey, Shoji.
Yes, sir.
Can't you go any faster?
Can't you see?
With this traffic, local streets are even worse.
You can't go any faster, unless you fly or something.
But...
Ooh, what a great view!
This should be fun.
Shoji, put your big fat one into her as hard as you can.
Yes, sir.
lf you don't stop this now, you'll be sorry!
Tashiro! Tell them to stop!
Ma'am, l don't think l can do that. l think you should give up.
Oh no, l can't let you do that.
l've never even talked to anyone as beautiful as you in my life.
Come on, resist more.
That's enough, you pervert!
Good, l like that.
No!
Oh? Seems like he knows where to lick.
Croak. Croak.
l'll give you a bonus for every time you make her come.
Hmm, this is great.
Pervert!
What the... You really are sick!
You're awesome.
Now, this hole...
Why is this happening?
Oh no, l can't...
Ew! lt stinks! l'll never...
Stop it...
l'm not finished yet. Come on, lick it clean.
Wasn't it enough? Please don't do this...
No, not there...
Let's see how deep this goes in...
Oh? lt's going in deeper and deeper...
l can't hold it...
Hurry up and give it to me.
Yes! Oh yes!
Oh man, look at her.
Please, hurry!
l'm sorry, but l don't think we're moving anytime soon.
We're going fly from here, then. Bye!
UFO?
l can't hold it, l'm gonna come soon.
l'm gonna shoot it inside.
Let me know if you get pregnant with my babies.
No, you can't come inside!
No!
l haven't had a Plometeusian in a long time...
l'll put this inside you now...
Aw, they're here already?
Stop it right there!
Alisa, are you all right?
Yuria! Shinji!
Everyone, kill them!
Shinji!
Sis!
What took you so long?
How did you know l was here?
l smelled you on Shinji's penis.
Oh, did you?
But if you had a time-controller, why didn't you use it?
l needed some entertainment.
l was really worried about you!
He's wanted by the GP... Keroro Jean Galion.
Good job, Alisa!
Wait...
Now, he can't harm anyone anymore.
Maybe l should cook this like Goya champloo...
Come on, turn off the time-control, or they could die.
Oh right. We don't want to lose our dear Shinji.
Our Shinji? He's my Shinji!
You kidding me? He is mine!
You guys, this is no time for a quarrel...
One Year Later
Delicious. Your penis is out of this world!
Harder! Suck my titties harder!
My pussy is feeling hot.
Mine, too. Hurry, put it in.
We will be arriving shortly.
What, already?
We'll pick this up in the bathroom at the hotel.
l've got him first today.
You did it with him yesterday!
Oh yeah? l don't remember...
Sis!
Don't fight, you two.
We're outside the event hall where the genius painter of this century...
...SHlNJl's party is being held.
He recently had a successful art exhibit in MOMA in New York.
We believe SHINJI will arrive at the party hall any minute now.
Oh, there he is.
He's arriving in a luxurious limo.
SHINJI is coming out of the limo, escorted by the beautiful Kanai Sisters!
Somehow, l awoke my talent of painting...
...and the sexy sisters became celebrities in magazines and on TV.
What a strange world it is.
Space Prison
Hey, handsome.
l'm your cellmate, Jean.