So she's over there this time...
What in the world is she doing at the edge of the galaxy?
Why do l have to chase her across the universe for 300 years?
But if l don't bring her back, Daddy will yell at me...
l guess l don't have a choice.
So these are earthlings...
l hope they're as nice as this planet looks.
Invasion of the Boobie Snatchers Part 1
Oh, come on, Tashiro!
l'm about to come!
Thrust your hips harder, and deeper!
Yes, ma'am!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
Me too! l can't hold it!
l'm coming!
Come! Come inside me!
l must be really stressed...
W-What is this!
lt wasn't a dream?
She looks human...
Maybe it's candid camera?
But why would they do this to me?
Besides, l don't think that show is on the air anymore...
She's really beautiful...
And she's got big boobs!
Well, looks like she's breathing.
l guess she's not dead.
Well then...
l don't know what's going on, but l can't miss this chance.
Sorry...
l'm going to come soon...
Oh shoot!
Hmm?
Oh, hi...
Who are you?
Who am l? Um, this is my room.
What?
This is my room, and you suddenly appeared.
Huh?
Oh, right...
This might be hard to believe, but l'm from outer space.
Outer space?
Seriously?
That's right.
This isn't a dream, is it?
She must be telling the truth...
What should l do?
Shoot, it's Kanna.
M-Morning.
Good morning. l brought you a cake.
Oh great...
Will you wait here for a minute?
l'm gonna straighten up my room...
Don't worry about it. l know your room is always messy.
Um, it seems like she misunderstood something...
lt's too late...
l can't explain this to her...
l'm sorry.
Um, well, this is...
How would an alien know how to do this?
Like l care how she knows...
This is interesting.
l'm not sure if ''interesting'' is the right word, but...
Oh my...
She's not used to a human body yet. She must be tired...
Okay, looks like she can feel it...
l'm feeling strange...
l feel tingly all over my body.
Why?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Y-Yes, it feels strange down there...
Good, that's very good.
Oh my goodness...
lt feels so good.
An Earthling's body is so strange...
She's really sensitive.
How about this?
l can feel it!
l can feel something hard deep inside me!
How about this?
Um, wow. lt feels strange.
lt feels so good. l can feel sticky liquid coming out of me...
Okay, then if l do this...
lt's coming out! lt's coming out!
Since that day, Yuria and l started living together.
She's looking for her older sister who supposedly came to Earth.
Nothing's happened for a while now.
Entertainment on earth is pretty boring.
So you have to put this ball into the holes, huh?
Let's see...
Chance!
Invasion AcompIished!
Awesome!
Machine 108 hit a jackpot!
Cash your prize
Five thousand dollars from three pachinko parlors...
Aliens sure are amazing!
Okay, let's splurge, shall we?
Yay!
Don't you think the movie was strange?
lf that old man in white put the main guy on the falcon...
...and took him to the volcano, it would've been a lot easier.
But then the movie would end right away, and it wouldn't be any good.
lt's fun, because there are many adventures.
You think?
But l think it still doesn't make sense.
You'll understand it someday.
Here we are.
l had a lot of fun today.
Thank you.
Yuria...
Wait.
What is it?
That...
l want to try that too.
R-Really?
Yes!
Wow, so many!
So, which one do you want?
l want this, and that one and that one!
You want three?
Uh-huh!
l've never used one before, so please be gentle.
Neither have l...
Please, put it in.
lt feels like the time l was captured by Galionians...
Are you okay?
No! Don't stop!
When that spikey thing touches my clit...
...it tingles all over my body!
Are you ready?
Please, put it in my butt...
Please!
l've never felt this good in my life!
Please...
Please, love me more!
Shinji, l've never felt like this!
l can't think of a life without you...
Me too! l can't hold it!
45 times in 5 days...
l can't help feeling guilty...
lt's my sister!
My sister is in this hotel!
Thanks to you, l won today's race as usual.
l'm counting on you for the next race.
lt's strange, having these pieces of paper makes me happy.
lt indeed is strange.
Yuria told me it wouldn't be hard to recognize her sister...
...and she was right.
There's no mistaking her...
l'd love to spend the night with you again, if you'd like to.
l'm sorry, but l want to try someone different tonight.
l'll look for tonight's date on my own, so you can go home.
Too bad, but if you say so.
lf you need anything, just give me a call.
l'm sorry...
l think l had a little too much to drink tonight...
l don't feel good...
That's awful!
Guts?
Why are you here?
The Great King ordered me to keep an eye on you, Yuria.
Keep an eye on me?
l'm just trying to bring back my sister.
The Great King is worried because you've been gone so long.
Okay, l got it.
But why you?
Because l'm Galaxy Patrol!
Oh well...
But l'm worried about sending Shinji to get my sister alone...
l hear earthlings are perverts!
Are you okay?
Where are your room keys?
l'm sorry. The keys are in my bra.
Why do you keep them there?
lt feels good and cold.
Hurry up and get the keys, will you?
Oh, if you touch me like that, l'll start to feel good...
Oh no, l'm about to explode...
How dare you, sis!
And look at Shinji!
l can't believe he was seduced by her in a second!
That jerk!
Wow! l've never seen anything like this before.
Just looking at it makes my womb tingle.
So tasty...
l've never seen such a big, hard, and arched penis...
Where have you been all my life?
Hold on a second!
Ooh, l like that.
l can't hold it any longer...
What the hell are they doing?
l don't know why, but it feels different than usual...
Oh, l'm coming!
Now, use this. Put this inside me!
Wait a minute!
We should investigate what Alisa is doing on earth!
Daddy didn't ask me to do that!
We don't want her to know we're here.
We should find out why she's here first.
l'm coming!
l'm starting to feel weird too...
Let me help you then...
ldiot! l'd rather do it myself than use your softie!
Your penis is hitting right on my spot!
lt's hitting on the spot!
Oh no, l'm going to come again.
Your penis is still hard as a rock. You're amazing.
l don't know why it's like this either, l can't control myself.
l don't care.
Do me deeper, harder!
lt's going in deeper, it feels so good!
More! More!
l'm going to come...
Please, come! Come inside me!
l can feel your penis getting bigger and bigger!
Yes! Yes!
Are you all right?
What am l going to do with these sisters...