Blue transparent skin
For the love, she devoted tomorrow
The heart of the flower
in spring seems very shy
Her body is dyed red
Belladonna, beautiful woman
Belladonna, the woman in the love
Sad melody
We have not heard yet
Belladonna
Faraway ...
Long long time ago ...
He and kindhearted, young,
beautiful young girl
Together because of love
The happiness fills the air in the sky
Smile of the spirit
In two people are intoxicated and happy
two people,
Smile of the spirit
always two people,
Happy reunion, happy reunion
However, the story has just begun
Lord, I am your faithful servant
The wedding was not delayed,
has already been over
According to ancient custom and convention
The son-in-law wants to be responsible
for various kinds of expenses of the wedding
Dad, this is money which institutes brings
of cow that I have sold to my home
Please accept it.
Please entrust me with your daughter
Cow? What happened on earth?
I have only one cow.
ten cow,
you must give me ten cow.
Please help me,
I'm very poor, I can't do that.
help me.
Does this woman's high moral principle
satisfy the criteria?
She calls " Jia " now
She will marry somebody soon.
There is not a lascivious thing
about her definitely
People's trust of her order, very industrious,
she is a person praised by villagers
Do you love that man?
Yes.
and you?
Everybody, after finishing tasting the sumptuous
cooked food, we get together, savouring slowly
Let us forget all past events,
We left from now on
In the blue mirror,
What thing is shaking?
Not tear,
Not suspiration,
It's that disappearing aftertaste,
or,
woman's heavy body
In the black dusk,
What thing is weeping?
Not nightwind,
Not crow,
It's that sound of hope,
or,
woman's painful moan.
Please don't stare at me.
He's so tired,
Don't wake him up
Who are you? Where are you come from?
It's you call me come here.
Me?
I heard truly
"I need power!"
"Who can save me?"
Your heart is shouting ...
and you also said:
"If you save me,"
"I can give you anything,"
"even my soul. "
You are devil
I am you.
You are really an unwise person
What you gonna do?
For you,
" You"
You are so small ...
It's all your fault.
Me?
I can become more and more bigger,
more and more stronger,
all depends on you.
You are really an odd person
You laughed,
You were glad at last
I have really smiled
I do not think I will smile again
I know.
I have been at your side all the time
I all know your thing
I've said, I am you.
What you gonna do?
Where are you going?
If if you go on like this, you will die
You pray to the god it is useless too
Your husband
Honest and competent
He responding to the request
that in spirit more than everyone
It is downhearted to already begin
Is he ill?
You even don't know
if he would live till the next winter.
Please stop saying.
I don't want anything,
anything,
I just want save that man,
Please,
Let's save him.
If бн
Junnu holds spin to the city to sell
That year, the famine was serious
in the village
Even so, collected taxesing,
people have still imposed the tax
People are desperate and downhearted,
even strength speaking No
Among them, only Junnu is still working hard
in the city,
Spin of Junnu has been sold at a good price
Nobody wants to bargain
Great amount of tax which nobody
can afford to pay
Only husband of Junnu Jun can be paid
So people's mutual rumor,
that woman was possessed by devil.
Jun has paid much tax,
Collecting taxes of extraordinary happiness people
Appoint the taxation people
in the village of Jun
The poor farmer Jun
Outstanding officers now
Looking at the husband in splendid attire,
Junnu feels the heart beats arbitrarily pit-a-pat
However, Junnu is noticed
The villagers' attitude changing
Their uneasiness which feel deep
And begin to intend to avoid two people
It is dark to begin to burn
Invite me бн
very hot бн
It is dark to begin to burn бн
It is dark to begin to burn
Go away!
What you gonna do with me?
This is just the begining.
Yes, the agony of Junnu has just begun
The war has begun
The war needs to want the money
If win, the land will increase
You say to me I am an important person,
But you only give to my so few persons
but,you can give me more ...
Listen,only depend on drip
the waterwheel won't move.
Within three days, if the money
has not been received yet, you are finished
But lord, villagers have no money
Seem to don't forget the order ,
Let oneself known
I want to cut down your left wrist
You seem to be calling me
No.
I come to save you.
Do you want strength?
You are an unfeeling person
You are mine now.
Your body and soul are all mine.
No.
My soul is that man's
Devote to god and that person
lovely but stupid girl,
Do you also want to dispute with me till now?
Do you want to let me connect the limb for you?
Please.
Your husband has already courted destruction
What can you do?
in any case, you are mine already.
But, I want to let you agree
to this with your own will clearly,
give me your heart and soul.
if you don't,that man will become ...
My body, my lowly body
I will give you,
for saving Jun
but, inside my heart ...
I will never give you my soul!
Good,now let me give you a bit more pressure.
What,Junnu?
Junnu puts on the green night clothes
Walk to the street straight
Green is the worlds dominator's color,
so it's called "Devil's color".
Even collect taxes people do not borrow money either
Cunning persons who lend money at interest
Even he himself does not know the reason
He has accepted the instruction of Junnu,
lends much money to her
The persons who lend money at interest complain
That woman must be possessed by devil,
The men in any era all like the war
Hunter and army, and the farmer
convening it, all go out together
They always leave sad remembrance for the woman
The men had not come back for a long time
A few years passed,
Junnu has become new persons
who lend money at interest
Economy in the small town and village
is all grasped in her hands
Her all right using them heartily
Honourable ladies in the castle,
people fear and respect Junnu further
Glad will of complying with her
At she it is in when, who this there
is pieces of owners of country?
Me or that woman?
of course you, dear lady.
I didn't ask you.
Dear lady, you are often angry
The war will lengthen time for a long time
Strength without that woman
Even kitchen most likely we of castle
shut up!
You look at it just nearby
However, those people with higher
more identity than my husband
They wallow in the good wine every day
Suddenly, the hunters returned in triumph
Men that come back and the women
coming to meet are all extreme joy begets sorrow
They dislike seeing Junnu
They meet the hunters' and return
in triumph on the square of the village
Certainly, Jun has come too
A woman who has never seen
Lord, when you are out, this country
has put upside down from head to foot
What?
That woman has been possessed by devil.
Devil? That woman?
Now, people fear that woman most
She must be still stronger than you
Really?
Yes.
Devil,go to hell!
open the door! save me! husband!
save me!
Nobody kills her
Just, let her torment living by the soul
For that succuba which possessed by devil,
this is the best way.
Really, should remove as soon as possible alienly
but, if the soul was possessed by devil,
devil will bite into and does not put
Then anything hinder from?
If, in piling up the faggots of kind
of mountain into, a handful of fire has put
That woman's soul should give up
the proud self-esteem
In the flame burning, it has won, immensely proud
If that,
Even that woman's human body has already died
But her soul would never die
The scattered result will emerge
and expand flying instead
What I can do?
Your wife is put into the prison house
You hold the key
You want the constant human body to her to wreck
That woman will tell you she will have
a kindhearted and modest heart
Good, I accepted.
Bring me that woman.
In the dark trial,
What thing is burning?
Not suspiration,
Not confession,
It's that standing pose which
she still trying hard to keep,
and,
woman's bitterness.
In the white time,
What thing is waiting?
Not life,
Not grave,
It's that mirage in the sere soul,
and,
Woman's red blood
You came at last
Lovely girl
You are forced to the end, husband
has abandoned you too
It's too late, too late.
Junnu, you are my friend when being born in
You are my partner
You and I, we are predestined to be together
Evil soul is hidden deeply in your heart
There is glamour like devil
It's you pushed me down.
Touch me, burn me
in a hell like this.
That's right.
The black dog bites into me,
that is bad thing that you do
The tooth is shiny
Thistles and thorns stab me
That is bad thing that you do too
The thorn just like flame burning and burning me
That's right.
but, I saved you.
Save me?
I do not want this kind of innocent and unwise soul of
sacrificing your own interests for the sake of others of yours
Roar furiously desperatly
The god is hating, devil is being hated
Soul of revenging is what
our institute wants urgently
You did a good job.
Today you are very beautiful.
Your appearance, your soul
Your appearance and soul excite my desire,
let me become the god revenging
devil
Yes,that's my name.
My wife, what's your wish?
I can give you anything.
What you wanna do?
I want to do the bad thing
What?
Any bad things.
Your answer is very good, that's the real you
Junnu, you only make your soul
And just present that I hand over
In the lonely wilderness, time slipped by,
springtime came
Suddenly, I discover Junnu is not a lonely man
Because she is with merging together naturally
You are very beautiful
You are lying, I should fall into the hell
Here is the hell
I have sold myself to devil
I have no route of retreat
My hair is the border of the hatred
Skin and ugly frog are the same
Hatred is just like the pitch-dark flame
This kind of sample of mine is not true
I have been deceived
I want become a woman with surprising strength
become a woman which everyone wants to avoid
It is not all right that I do not do it in this way
I do not want to forget anger and hatred
Angry, hatred, regret, these are not ugly things
You become beautiful, Junnu
Yes,just like fall in love
Lovely woman
You are more beautiful than the spirit
On one hand, in the village is still
gloomy springtime
Now, peasant woman that Junnu got back
to in the past life
In the unalterable village
Darker death shade, close to this village silently
bubonic plague ----If someone suffers
from a sure to die a kind of infectious disease
I have already lighted a fire
Who are you?
I am Junnu enclosed the body by devil
Where's here?
Out of the world.
Really? When I am still alive,
I have been taken the car by others
I still remember I want to climb out desperately
You are the person who I see at first after dying
What you gonna do?
Feed to you and take medicine. You lie,
that is poison
The poison solves medicines too
Thanks to it, you could resume
this sample till now
Do you want to kill me?
Anyway you had already died
There is once
Has his disease been cured?
What happened on earth?
The spreading of successive famine
and malignant infectious disease
Villagers surviving are all very hungry
That cabin is administered by succuba
She will appeal others every night, kick up a fuss
It is a magic, the bad thing that devil does
People say quite surly
Their carrying the food and wine voluntarily
Pig and succuba
Does that woman still live?
Flower of such strong color
After drank the flower juice, because of having
difficult labour painful wife
She is even too cold to fear
Oh yes, Jun has really said, Belladonna
plants woman who calls " beauty " flowers
If my family increase children again, live soon
My day passes the hardships very much
And I am very sad
I and Junnu discuss
I agree to accept the god punishment
That is my mission
But, I, no matter which kind of punishments
are accepted, still very painful now
If we can be happy afterwards
I do not regret that no matter which kind
of punishments are received
I want to see the grandson dying during the war
It is said Junnu can make the person dying revive
After Junnu has listened to me,
have shed a lot of tears
And, she let me smoke cigarettes
She lets me drink the wine like blood
Has your grandson dying appeared ?
Do not have
Have you heard his voice?
I have not heard
Is not this swindling ?
I throw myself on my knees on the ground
Praying while crying
Generating heat like fire of body
Perhaps that is a dream
I pluck up my courage, raise my head to look
What happened on earth?
I see the hell crying loudly
For my grandson
Do you satisfy?
I am very happy
Very terrific, the betrayal of the spirit
It is the rebellion of Lord
That woman
Burn her to death
However, people are all supporters of Junnu
The woman has already fled from the army
Are you a master of this country?
In the near future, the enemy will show their weakness,
we can defeat them till that time
Let me do this
What happened to you, is it small and lovely ?
Do you want to be embraced by me?
Junnu, do not you know me ?
I hate your master
So I hate you
The person who will kill you at first one day
in the future sooner or later is me
Why?
Because I love my master deeply
You come to kill me
Junnu, rescue me,
Enable me to realize my hope
I want to let masters embrace me
However, I am a servant with humble identity
He will not see me later
Different identities?
The god has confirmed everybody's identity
If someone wants to do such a thing,
that is betrayal of the spirit
That is bad thing that devil does
But, even surrender to devil, I want to maintain
this section of loves
I know
Succuba, I have been injured
OK, let me rescue you
That woman
Can't be close to that castle
on even bubonic plague
But the castle was invaded by the strength
of succuba at last
Lord, tries every possible means
as soon as possible
Go to call that man
husband
Junnu
Long time no see.
Junnu, your present life is unhappy
Junnu, may we resume?
You do not do such a thing again !,
Become an ordinary peasant's wife
We two's heavy head comes again
Junnu
Excuse me for abandonning you, I was powerless
at that time, can only do it in that way
Don't say again, I have already forgotten it
Junnu, please go back with me
We get back to the castle together
Get back to the castle
Lord has already forgiven your mistake
Moreover, he has also approved of your contribution
You succour because ill painful people
You contributed your own strength
in order to solve people's vexation
You are a very great person
Do you believe,
Lord wants to cooperate with you,
cures the disease
Lighten the agony
That kind of important knowledge,
only under the power of Lord
It could function and bring the people back to life
Lord can send the army to catch you,
or has killed you
But he says that does not want to do such a thing
Thing that you know you is honest to Lord
He will give us a quiet land
of happiness if he assures me
If I refuse
You and I will be killed, Junnu,
Junnu, listens to me
Junnu
Junnu,this is not a deal.
In order to look for a road making
a lot of people happy
Baiyong Song is the most sincere
present that I give to you
Please tell us the operation method
of the discredited flower
What's the matter with you? Are you still
unsatisfied with Baiyong Song?
Junnu
Then, I let you turn into rabbits in the village
I join noble you, you would not complain
Junnu, your rank among the nobles is the first
Do I make way for you, how?
No, I do not need
What do you want on earth?
All
What?
Everything in this world
Whole world
Burn her to death, burn this woman to death at once
Time slips by
On July 14, 1789, attack of Bastille prison began
The woman is a revolutionary pioneer in France
Blue transparent skin
For the love, she devoted tomorrow
The heart of the flower in spring seems very shy
Her body is dyed red
Belladonna, beautiful woman
Belladonna, the woman in the love
Sad melody
We have not heard yet
I believe the love
Even if I have already been fucked by you,
I still love you
Until you stop dallying with flowers
Changing at last turns into a good thing too
Belladonna, beautiful woman
Belladonna, the woman in the love
Sad melody
We have already heard too much