I-I am Faye the bounty hunter!
You are charged with a serious crime!
Your head belongs to me now!
Yummy...
I'll shoot you.
Since you broke your parole with the Galactic Police,
a citizen can shoot you with complete immunity!
You call that shooting?
You see, a gun works like this.
Ah, I was in over my head!
As long as ya get it now, sweetie.
Who the hell are you?
Stop it.
So you wanna get shot in the head too?
All I'm doing is telling you to stop it.
What?
BEYOND - Episode 2
The legend of Satan the Devil.
May I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Master, you said you had to rescue this girl,
and that's why you smashed that guy to pieces.
"Rescue"?
Does that perhaps fall under the concept
of "empathy" you spoke of the other day?
Rescuing someone in distress...
I felt it was the human thing to do.
You're not human, though, Master.
Good point.
I smashed that guy to pieces without
applying much strength at all.
You smashed him to atoms.
This appears to be more difficult than I expected.
She seems to be regaining consciousness.
Are you okay?
Please let me call you "Teacher"!
"Teacher"?
Yes!
That last attack move you did...
Please teach it to Faye-chan, sir!
Teach it to you, you say...
But why?
Actually, you see, I'm descended from
a long line of bounty hunters,
that started with my great-great-great-grandfather.
I'm so awkward and clumsy however
that I can't do anything right.
I wanna become stronger!
I understand how you feel, but I'm not sure if...
I'll tolerate any kind of strict regimen!
So please, pass some of your
skills to cute little Faye-chan!
This is a problem.
It's a simple thing to do, Master.
What?
You simply need to share your powers with her.
How do I do that?
Faye-san,
take off our clothes and lie down on the bed.
In order to receive Masters powers,
he must make love to you.
Wh-Wh-What?
Make love to me?
Oh my!
Teacher, please do your best!
Good. Master go ahead.
G-Go ahead? I don't think I'm
exactly ready for this, though.
If you wish to "rescue" her, though, I think
this falls under the same category.
Teacher!
Yes?
Don't hold yourself back.
Master?
So this is also a rescue?
Yes.
Oh, Teacher!
Please be gentle.
Please, don't mind me.
Right..
Um, can't you move a little further away from me?
Aw, come on, Teacher!
You gave me so much power that I'm
in a really good mood right now!
Yes, but the relationship between a teacher
and student should be much stricter.
I-I'm so sorry, Teacher!
Listen to me!
If you think that's the only way to become
stronger, you're sadly mistaken.
Yes!
True power lies in hard work!
Follow alongside me hopping like a bunny!
Yes, Teacher!
From here on, I won't go easy on you.
It's strict training!
Yes! So this is strict training, I see.
Faye-chan is doing her best!
I feel like a frog, however.
You are not a frog! You're a bunny!
Change at once!
Yes.
Not that kind of bunny, a rabbit!
Yes!
Please train me harder and
harder and harder, Teacher!
What frightening spirit she has.
Teacher! Faye-chan will work hard!
I wonder why?
When I see Faye-san and Master together,
I feel a strange sensation.
Hey, hey! Can't you keep going!?
Yes!
Where is he!? That virginity thief!
Found him!
Take this, Devil!
Cute.
Jump higher!
Yes, Teacher!
Shit!
I'm not letting this get to me!
The legend of the Black Angel?
Yes. Listening to Ren-chan's story reminded me of it.
It's a story from the Vineria Kingdom.
They have a legend about a black angel
who is very similar to you, Teacher.
Long ago,
when the kingdom was attacked by something evil,
a black angel came down to them from the sky.
The sight of the terrifying creature
deeply disturbed the citizens,
but then a beautiful girl dispelled
the peoples concerns.
After saving the people, the angel turned into
a beam of light and returned to the sky.
The end.
Faye-chan only knows about that much of the story.
Well if that angel really is me, that would be great.
He sounds like a really nice guy!
Master?
Teacher you saved Little Faye though,
so of course you're a good person.
Sorry for the wait, patron.
I wish to ask a question.
What's up with you? Your voice sounds strange.
Faye-chan and her friends wanna know more
about the legend of the Black Angel.
Where might we go to find some answers?
Ah! So that's why he's dressed like that.
If you want to know more about the
Black Angel legend, then look!
Go to that shrine over there.
O mighty Angel, please save Vineria!
Hey, young woman, why are you crying?
The Angel?
The Angel!
So you've returned to us at last!
I never lost faith in you!
"Returned"?
I've believed in you since I was a little child.
I believed that the Black Angel really existed,
and that he would protect us from harm!
Right now, our civilization faces a horrible crisis,
and in response, you've come to our aid!
Come, follow me, Black Angel!
Come with me to our palace!
Wah! But he's Faye-chan's Teacher!
My Teacher!
Here.
Your acolytes are welcome to come along as well.
Acolytes?
Faye-chan is his woman!
So this is your king?
Nice to meet you.
Umm, I mean, I'm not here to harm you.
Why are you frightened, Father?
This is the Black Angel of ancient legend!
He heard my prayer and answered
it with his holy return!
I see!
If Chime says so, there must be no mistake!
So you think I really am the actual
Black Angel of legend?
With you back on our side, we
will certainly win the war!
The war?
Father! Can we have a banquet celebration tonight?
Splendid, splendid.
Listen, subjects!
A banquet tonight! A banquet!
Oh, Teacher, you're so amazing!
Faye-chan is proud to be the woman
of such an amazing man!
Master do you suppose this too is "love"?
Were conducting a sacred banquet
today in honor of the Angel!
You must return from where you came!
Gimme a frickin' break.
Don't you have any idea who he really is?
He's the Black Angel of the Vineria Kingdom.
"Black Angel", you say?
Snap out of your fairytale!
Just look at him! He's the Dark
Devil, who destroys everything!
How dare you speak such foolishness!
Princess Chime says so, and she's never wrong!
But you can be wrong for believing her!
What's your problem?
Speaking ill of the Black Angel is the same
as speaking ill of Princess Chime!
Someone! Throw this intruder out of our kingdom!
Jeez!
Why are the people of this kingdom so clueless?
I guess my only choice is to strike
first before anyone's the wiser.
What the hell is this?
The sewer?
Dont give in, Eva!
Teacher, were in different rooms?
I've prepared a special room on
the third floor for the Angel.
His acolytes may stay in this room.
Really? You're no fun.
Very well.
So, Master, good night.
Ah, good night to you as well.
Angel, come this way.
I was hoping Teacher would make
love to me again tonight.
Faye-chan, how about I give you
a much nicer bed than that?
Aren't we there yet?
I don't want anyone to disturb us.
Disturb?
I'll explain later.
Where is he, where is he?
Looks like Princess Chime has made her decision.
Yeah.
This way, Angel.
The s-special room... Don't you
think its a little too far away.
Come, this way.
Princess Chime?
I ordered everyone to stay away from this room.
Why?
Angel, after you arrived here, I reached my decision.
Decision?
What kind of decision?
I don't want my beloved Veneria
to get entangled in this matter.
The fate of this kingdom is linked to my fate.
I still don't really get the situation here.
For now, just for tonight
please make love to me!
What did you just say?
I know it's odd for a woman to ask you this...
but for tonight please do my bidding
without asking any questions.
Angel... I've always wanted this to happen.
Come inside.
Hey!
Please wake me up more gently. Huh?
Ms. Policewoman?
Don't "Ms. Policewoman'' me!
I'm sorry I left without thanking you properly.
I don't care about that!
I think I might know the answer but I'll ask anyway.
How do I go about killing you!?
By the way, do you know where Chime is?
The princess who was here with me...
That's what I want to talk to you about.
Clean out your ears and listen up.
Yes?
Good morning, Master.
Oh Teacher you're up really early.
Get ready to depart at once.
Where to?
I'll explain later.
Hurry.
Okay.
Here!
Whoa...
This kingdom is threatened by the Assyr Kingdom.
The prince of Assyr said he would invade this
country unless Princess Chime married him.
What a horrible story!
Faye-chan is really mad about it.
The king, unable to give up his beloved
daughter, was planning to refuse,
which would mean an all-out
war between the kingdoms.
But Assyr is strong.
If war broke out this kingdom
wouldn't stand a chance.
I understand.
So when Master appeared, he helped Chime
reach a decision about the wedding.
She believes that with Master
around, this kingdom is safe.
That's exactly right.
The princess just left on a ship for the enemy kingdom.
You're a man, aren't you!?
Take some responsibility for your actions!
I can't even help Chime.
How can I be the legendary Black Angel?
Oh, Teacher?
Maybe we could catch up with her ship if we left now?
Master! I know a way.
You have yet use teleportation.
That's right!
Teleportation!
How do I do it?
Tell me, please!
Place the feelings of the person
you wish to see in your heart.
Then you will fly to her side in an instant.
Good!
Then I'll go too.
Big Sis!
Ah, how dare they leave me all by myself!
What a little whiner you are.
Come with me.
Come, young lady, why are you crying?
Angel?
I've come to rescue you, Chime.
Let's go.
Yes!
Master? The point from which you teleported just
experienced an inter-dimensional power surge.
You're trapped inhere!
You think I care about that?
It's time to punish those who tried to
use this sweet lady to start a war!
Ren, you take Chime back to Vineria.
Yes, Master. Come, this way.
Please be careful.
Now, let's test these "powers" of mine
to see how far they stretch!
He killed them.
Now it's my fault.
How can I possibly thank you?
Thanks to you, Vineria has been saved.
Though I fear I can't control my own powers...
All's well that ends well.
Father, I have a favor to ask.
What is it Chime? Ask me anything.
I want to stay with the Angel.
When I met the Angel I understood it clearly.
Even a princess, such as myself tied to a kingdom...
has the right to love someone.
"Love", you say? Umm...
Very well said! You make your father proud!
You also say some pretty bold things, don't you?
Chime-chan, it's so cool that you're
getting married on a spaceship!
My beloved Angel says he wishes to depart
on a journey to retrieve his memories.
I want to do anything I can to help.
Chime...
And helping my Angel retrieve his
happiness is also my happiness.
Aw, Teacher! Please give Faye-chan
another training exercise!
Hey...
Master, I have a strange sensation.
Are these "feelings," you think?
Looks like you learned a lot Ren.
I still couldn't find my own answer, though.
I don't get it.
Didn't I tell you?
You're the Dark Devil.
You can only destroy and kill.
You're the most evil thing in the universe.
Ms. Policewoman? What are you doing here?
Oh, shut your mouth.
I'm just keeping an eye on you to make
sure you don't remember anything.
This is part of my job.
You...
By the way...
Who in the world am I?
Who am If?
ikiru tte muzukashii
Life sure is tough.
atama o kakae taku naru ne
Makes you wanna hold your head in shame.
zenbu nagedashite dokoka tooku e
I wanna throw everything far away,
nige dashitai
and escape somewhere.
suna o kamu you na hibi ga
These gritty days,
zutto tsuzuite yuku you de
seem to go on forever.
kokoro o sokunaru jibun no mirai
My unseen future pains my heart.
nee dou naru no
Hey, what's gonna happen?
rashii to kimaran'nakute mo
Even if I can't decide what's most like me,
kakko warukute mo kamawanai
and even if I look stupid, I don't care.
yaruki ga mondai
It's a matter of spirit;
yaru koto ga daiji
doing things is important.
nee sou deshou
Hey, isn't that so?
yume no tane o makou yo
Let's spread the seeds of dreams,
suteki ni sodatta hanara
and raise them to be beautiful flowers,
kakae kirenai hodo no
in a bouquet too big to hold.
shiawase no hanagara
A bouquet of flowers of happiness.
yume no tane o makou yo
Let's spread the seeds of dreams,
suteki ni sodatta hanara
and raise them to be beautiful flowers,
kakae kirenai hodo no
in a bouquet too big to hold.
shiawase no hanagara
A bouquet of flowers of happiness.