I just... can't go on.
My name... and my memories are gone!
I get the feeling I've been
sleeping for quite some time.
Who in the world am I!?
Someone tell me!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Master.
Who are you?
I am Ren.
I am your loyal slave, Master.
"Master..."
Is that my name?
A name?
A name is merely a means to
reduce you, all-powerful Master.
If you need an example, the next
world is full of foolish humans.
"Foolish humans..."
Then what am I?
The most powerful Devil in the universe.
Ruler of chaos and fear.
And destroyer of all things.
A-All those you're calling me seem to be really nasty.
Would you like to see yourself7
BEYOND - Episode 1
Awakening Satan, the Devil
What in the world is this form?
Please calm yourself.
When you fell asleep last time,
your powers were sealed off.
You're confused because you woke up just recently.
"Sealed," you say?
If we can break the seal, we can
regain your soul Master.
What must we do?
This!
H-Hey!
Master, please do my bidding.
I'm the key to breaking your seal Master.
So this will release my power?
Ouch!
What was that sudden shock?
Captain!
A space undulation, one with
frightening gravity waves!
I think it might be an inter-dimensional tremor!
An inter-dimensional tremor, you say?
There might be a UFO near the origin of the blast.
Investigate!
Another blast is coming!
Brace for attack!
Captain, we're getting a distress signal from the base.
Relaying to the main screen!
Admiral!
It's an emergency situation, Captain Eva.
So it was that blast we just experienced.
Correct.
In that case, we'll send an away
team to investigate at once!
Wait.
Return to base immediately.
It's just been announced that the entire
universe has felt an abnormal burst of energy.
It's a huge crisis for the entire universe.
What do you mean?
The Devil has awakened.
You mean the Dark Devil?
But that's just a myth.
That's what most people believe,
but he really does exist.
He's revived after thousands of years of sleep,
to unleash his thorough and merciless
destruction on everything, and then disappear.
When he awakens from his sleep, the first
sign is an inter-dimensional reaction.
An inter-dimensional reaction...
Then we need to investigate even more!
I understand your sense of urgency,
but we mustn't underestimate the Dark Devil.
You must return to base on Ratol.
I want you to be present at the council meeting.
Very well, sir.
"When the Devil awakens,
the universe will fall into a sea of agonizing fear."
So the myth is real.
As per orders,
setting a course for Ratol!
Wait!
We mustn't disobey orders.
I haven't even suggested that yet!
But you mustn't disobey orders.
I haven't disobeyed yet though!
Ever since we were kids, I've been
able to see through you, Eva.
We will not attempt to deal with the inter-
dimensional waves without permission!
And who's in charge of this ship?
That's the captain.
And who's the captain?
Eh? You, of course.
Then, here's an order from the captain.
Tell the base that we're going to investigate the
inter-dimensional reaction waves on our own!
Eva!
This is your captain speaking!
If the myth really is true, then the
universe will be destroyed.
If there's a way we can stop it...
Full speed ahead!
Eva...
What sensations...
My powers...
My powers are flowing within me!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Another inter-dimensional reaction wave spotted!
Detecting a second-level wave directed at the fleet!
Beautiful...
Where are we?
I see that the seal has been broken, Master.
That was just a small sample of your power.
My power?
Yes. Putting it in more complicated terms,
the Giselle Sanctuary and the Etruria Galaxy
have been completely destroyed.
Very well done.
"Destroyed" you say?
This is a three-dimensional space.
And 7000 years ago, when you fell into your sleep,
you were at the bottom of this planet's dimension.
That doesn't exactly explain anything.
You were able to escape from the
seal in that dimension, however,
and erupt into the third dimension right here.
The destruction of a couple of galaxies...
is a small price to pay for the revival of your strength.
And after all, Master, your destiny
is to destroy existence.
So you mean to say that countless
lives were lost just then?
Exactly, Master.
What a horrible thing!
I'm such an evil person!
Why are you so troubled?
I'm done.
Why is that?
Because I've done something evil...
that I cant take back!
I don't really understand what you're saying.
Your name was Ren-san, right?
Don't you have any empathy for living beings?
Master, I am your slave.
Please do away with the honorifics.
Don't avoid my question.
But I don't understand the word "empathy."
Empathy is...
Right!
It's love.
And "love"... What's that?
Well this sweet-and-sour thing
boils up in your chest and...
It's a bad thing, I see.
No, it's a very precious feeling in your heart, when
someone is more important to you than anything else.
In that case, I love you.
You are more important to me than anything else.
Hmm, I don't think that's quite right!
Master, are you all right?
A-Anyway! How about I show
you over time what it means?
Okay. Very well.
Please teach me anything you wish.
Well for starters, put on some clothes!
Yes.
She's almost like a doll.
How long has our relationship been this way?
One thing is certain. I can't
tolerate not knowing who I am.
Like I said, you are the Master of Fear and Destruction.
Can't you call me something other than that?
Master, on the various planets,
you've been known by many names.
It started as legend, then became myth,
then was relayed orally from generation to generation.
I see. So perhaps that might be a
hint to discover my true identity.
Ren, lend me your power.
Okay.
There's another three-hour wait before
the next inter-galactic transport?
Teleporting would be much swifter.
Teleporting? I wish to travel the normal way, though.
Where is the liveliest place close to here?
Koike Colony.
There are many different kinds of people there.
I think you'll be able to hear the myths very quickly.
Good. By the way, it seems we
need money to ride a ship.
Can you take care of that?
Yes.
First the mirror now this.
How in the world does she do it?
Teleporting matter.
I teleported the money from
somewhere else on this planet.
Very impressive.
Thank you very much.
Receiving your praise is the source
of all happiness for me.
Oh, could this be love?
Urn, I think it's a bit different than that.
A 300-year salary hold?
You can't be serious.
The Council made this decision.
Wh-What do you mean by this, Admiral?
Your mistake was too enormous.
I understand, sir.
Losing the ship was my fault.
But-
The issue is not the ship!
There's something else?
After that blast destroyed your ship, seven
other planets were also destroyed.
Five in this sector!
The Etruria Galaxy was destroyed.
And more... and more... and more!
Admiral...
All the affected nations have
sent us bills for damages!
LOOK!
And you say that's my responsibility?
Until we find the Devils hideout
we have no choice but to help.
No way! Have mercy!
The Council has ordered your salary stopped
for eternity, until you've repaid all the losses.
You'll be demoted to the lowest position possible.
In other words, you'll be the lowest
rank for the rest of your life.
Though it's a miracle that you
haven't been fired over this.
It's a mystery!
Captain! How did your talk with the Admiral go?
Great I guess.
At least I wasn't fired.
Captain, you must fight! Fight!
I'll always be here to cheer you on!
Fight on!
The Devil... that's right.
Everything is his fault.
This vendetta of mine...
will go on!
I see what you mean.
Looks like I'll get many different perspectives here.
I'll go find a warrior befitting your quest.
In the meantime, here's your per diem.
Oh, thanks.
Well, I'll see you later!
It's a good thing she has spirit.
Well, then...
Um, excuse me.
Yes?
Umm...
Oh, no! I was just trying to talk to her!
I must clear up this misunderstanding.
Oh, no!
Now then...
Well, there were many fewer casualties
this time, so I'll consider it a blessing.
I think I'm lost.
I'm starving.
Package!
Thanks.
Roze! It's from Roze!
"Captain, how are you?"
"I wanted to help you out..."
"so I got you this present"
"made it myself I hope you like it."
"I'm taking care of things on the
space end, so don't worry."
"We'll, I'll contact you again soon."
"Roze."
Thank you, Roze!
I'll bet she sent some homemade food!
Yummy...
Roze, I don't think this will fill me up.
Umm, I wish to speak to someone.
Yeah. What is it?
I seem to have lost my way.
But there are plenty of...
Ah! Where are you going, sir?
If you wish, I'll accompany you.
What a relief. She's a nice cop.
A pretty female like you is the only
cop in this desolate place?
It must be tough.
Well, sorta.
If I were a woman, I'd never work
in a wasteland like this.
It cant be helped. I've been demoted.
Demoted?
Yes. You've heard of the Dark Devil, right?
Yeah.
Thanks to that asshole, lots of planets were destroyed.
And they made me take the blame for it.
Something the matter, sir?
Umm, well...
Don't pity me.
Even if I was demoted to the lowest
position at the lowest pay,
I'm still one hell of a cop!
And I take pride in my work.
Umm, well, actually I...
Please, be my guest and eat.
But I...
I insist!
Thank you!
Eat up, eat up. Is it good?
Yes, very.
Th-Thats great.
Um, Ms. Cop?
I don't know who you are or where you're
from, but I'm eternally grateful!
I haven't eaten anything for two days straight.
I was just trying to make up for what I did.
You don't need to thank me.
It's my duty as a cop to help you.
Sorry! It wasn't enough?
You need more to eat.
Hey! Gather all the food you can muster
and give it to this poor cop!
Thank you! Thank you!
Satisfied? Satisfied?
Right now I'm so happy!
Good morning.
Did I...
No need to worry.
You just had indigestion from
eatin too much too quickly.
I got you some medicine, so everything is all right.
How much did it cost?
Your sickness was my fault anyway. I should pay for it.
I hope you don't mind, but I decided to help
you out around the house a little bit.
You work so hard every day.
Are you hungry again?
No. I don't know who you are or where you're from,
but I'm very grateful.
I've just never been treated with such kindness before.
Well it was the human thing to do.
Uh, w-wait..
I've never met anyone as sweet as you.
Umm, but Ms. Cop, I...
Call me Eva.
I decided long ago that I would save
my first time for someone like you.
E-Eva?
Please, make love to me.
Eva!
Make love to me. For me!
Come closer.
It hurts.
Fast. Before I even came.
She must've been very lonely.
Master?
Master!
Ren, is that you?
Where are you?
Even I don't know that.
I'm currently at the farthest away point.
I received your location through telepathy,
so I'll return to you shortly.
Wait! This place is dangerous
for an unaccompanied girl.
I'll come to you, Ren.
Guide me.
Understood.
Master!
Ren.
What a relief to see that you're well.
Sorry I worried you.
I was just helping someone out.
Helping someone out?
Could that possibly be because of that
"empathy" you spoke of the other day?
W-Well, I suppose so.
Is that so?
Well, how was your progress on researching myths?
Damn! I completely forgot!
Master?
I want to see her again.
Who am I talking about?
So my knight in shining armor did this.
My prince!
Alerting all Galactic Police.
We have received intelligence that the
Dark Devil has appeared in Ratol.
He has caused numerous accidents,
and we believe he is in hiding.
Here is a montage of images gathered
from various surveillance cameras.
Please use this data to locate him.
WANTED
No way.
It's him.
It's him!
He's the Dark Devil?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Give me... Give me...
Give me back my virginity!
You're fucking dead.
Dark Demon,
I won't let you escape!
You're fucking dead.
Fucking dead, fucking dead, fucking dead!
I'll chase you as far as I have to,
even to the end of the galaxy!
I vow...
I vow to capture you!
ikiru tte muzukashii
Life sure is tough.
atama o kakae taku naru ne
Makes you wanna hold your head in shame.
zenbu nagedashite dokoka tooku e
I wanna throw everything far away,
nige dashitai
and escape somewhere.
suna o kamu you na hibi ga
These gritty days,
zutto tsuzuite yuku you de
seem to go on forever.
kokoro o sokunaru jibun no mirai
My unseen future pains my heart.
nee dou naru no
Hey, what's gonna happen?
rashii to kimaran'nakute mo
Even if I can't decide what's most like me,
kakko warukute mo kamawanai
and even if I look stupid, I don't care.
yaruki ga mondai
It's a matter of spirit;
yaru koto ga daiji
doing things is important.
nee sou deshou
Hey, isn't that so?
yume no tane o makou yo
Let's spread the seeds of dreams,
suteki ni sodatta hanara
and raise them to be beautiful flowers,
kakae kirenai hodo no
in a bouquet too big to hold.
shiawase no hanagara
A bouquet of flowers of happiness.
yume no tane o makou yo
Let's spread the seeds of dreams,
suteki ni sodatta hanara
and raise them to be beautiful flowers,
kakae kirenai hodo no
in a bouquet too big to hold.
shiawase no hanagara
A bouquet of flowers of happiness.