I am back to conquer...
From the depth of darkness.
Join me and revel
in the blood of our sacrifices.
Join me and discover unearthly pleasures.
Join me and we will conquer the world.
From the depth of hell and back.
I am back stronger than ever.
This is finally my time this time
to conquer in blood!
I am Mija, the demon!
The demon of debauchery!
I am back once again to cover the world
once again in darkness and lust!
Join me, lustful ones, and I will bring
the dark paradise to earth once more.
What is it...
I can tell something's wrong...
Darkness...
I can feel the door of hell
opening once again.
It is here to seduce souls.
Dear God, please protect us.
Protect our souls from evil.
Ease our hunger for lust.
Guide our confused mind.
Show a guiding light to the hapless souls
about to be hurled
into the pit of spiritual discord, sins
of the flesh, and confusion of the mind...
Ms. Tadeshina, The high priest is waiting.
Follow me.
I wonder how much it cost to build
something like this underground...
Aside from his wealth, he is known for
hi medical and scientific achievements, but
this is really something...
Your eminence...
Ms. Tadeshina is here.
Thank you, brother.
Excuse me.
I came as soon as I could.
What can I do to I serve
your eminence today?
Tomorrow, you will be assigned to the St.
Moses Academy as a substitute teacher.
What?
You will accept?
But, your eminence, I have my license,
but no real experience...
- Allow me...
- Yes.
I am just forwarding a message from God.
I understand.
I shall accept this duty.
- Sara, if I may...
- Yes?
You may want to show more modesty
in God's presence, my child.
Please excuse me, your eminence!
May I ask what I am supposed to do
while I am teaching at the academy?
Just observe your surroundings with the
virtue of god and the purity of your soul.
- My soul?
- Correct.
What you seek will soon be apparent.
Just proceed as directed,
and God will protect you.
Hey, did you hear?
Oh yes, but who was it?
I heard...
I heard she was a senior.
I can't believe it; how many girls so far?
More sheep are flocking to the slaughter,
and they have no idea!
We need to thank Mija, our master!
Don't you two agree?
They're not listening.
I never knew such pleasures existed
before Master Mija showed me...
Oh I agree...
After this, I don't think I can go back to
being my old self again, ever.
Don't you think?
You're right...
You could beg me to go back,
and I wouldn't, besides...
I don't think anyone here is ready
to forget these pleasures!
Please, will you fuck me now?
- I want some, too.
- I agree!
That's right!
Yeah.
What's up, girl?
What's up Yuka?
Did you hear?
'Bout what?
You know, the demon!
Whatever...
You don't believe me?
How can I?
Mayu, you know I don't lie to
anybody else but my parents, right?
Oh, Yuka, really, a horned,
transsexual demon?
Watch you back!
Make sure the horned demon
doesn't kill and eat you!
But don't worry, I'll get eaten first.
Why?
Demons kill and eat cuter girls first.
Hey, that's not fair, I'm cute, too!
You know I get hit on a lot more.
Did you know?
Yuka, Uh-huh.
Oh my god, you knew we were
getting a new health teacher?
Yuka, No way?
Miwa, where did you get that information;
are you sure of that?
Stop, don't talk at the same time!
- Sorry.
- Oops!
Okay.
You know Ms. Omoda, don't you?
Yeah, the pregnant one.
So?
Yeah?
She is taking her maternity leave early
and going to see her family for a while.
So who's taking her place?
Yes, yes, I'm curious!
I hear...
Yuka, Tell me.
No idea.
Hey, I just heard this from
someone just this morning.
I thought you might know!
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure is mine.
Is anything wrong?
Oh, yes.
- Ms. Sara Tadeshina.
- Yes.
Foreign college?
Yes.
That's great!
Please sit down, and let us get acquainted.
Good idea.
Thank you.
I am the school principal,
and please call me Shiina.
This is the vice principal.
My name is Kaori Sasamine.
It really is nice to meet you,
Ms. Sara Tadeshina.
Oh no, I'm really glad to be here,
to be teaching again.
I'm really surprised by the size
of this campus, it's huge!
Well, this school building was
also built to be used
as an emergency shelter for the residents
of the surrounding area.
We have our own
independent power generator,
water storage,
and other emergency necessities.
During the weekend,
we are host to many activities,
such as theater, sports,
and various classes.
We would love to have your participation
as an instructor then, as well.
I don't think I can!
Excuse me.
Miss Omoda, thank you for coming!
She will bring you up to date
on all the classes.
Yes, nice meeting you.
The school grounds will be closing.
All students, please exit the campus
within the next thirty minutes.
The meeting's finished for today.
- Hey Mayu!
- Yes?
How are you doing, Kotaro?
Okay, well, uh...
We should leave before
they lock the campus.
Excuse me!
I can't believe I did it again!
Every time I try to talk to her,
my mind goes completely blank.
Wait... we walk home
using the same route.
I can ask to walk her back home.
All right!
Is it the monster?
Damn Yuka's dumb stories!
Bye bye!
What do I have here?
One that's unaware of her own powerful
epicumia just wandered in!
First, let's remove
these cumbersome garments
to get a good look at her true self.
A young, innocent, sweet, virgin child!
Innocent like a baby bird
still in its eggshell...
Apparently inexperienced
at pleasing herself yet...
And yet her epicumia is overflowing...
Nooo!
She even chirps
like a innocent baby bird...
Stop!
Please!
Don't be afraid.
Of course I'm here to help you,
my virgin maiden.
Really?
Why would I lie?
Let me down, and let me go!
I can't do that.
- Why... why not?
- Because I haven't helped you yet...
We're not finished.
I need to free the epicumia inside you
that is ready to burst and is desperate
to be joined with me!
This is for your benefit.
Let me go, I have no idea
what you are talking about!
You will know soon enough, you will know
as soon as your epicumia is free.
That is when you become your true self...
That is the only way
I am going to help you.
Nooo, Stooooop, Pleeeeeease!
I cast a spell
to free yourself to act upon the desires
and the pleasures of the flesh,
to give in to your lust,
and reveal the true self inside you.
I am Mija, the master of human lust!
Epicumia!
My new convert.
The kiss of acceptance...
My master Mija...
I should practice while I'm waiting...
Hi, what a coincidence, Mayu, would you
mind if I walk you back to your house?
Oh, hi Mayu!
Oh, it's you, Mr. Gann!
Hey, Mr. Gann!
Don't lock up yet!
There's nobody on campus,
so you might as well leave.
Mayu's inside, Mr. Gann!
Oh Mayu!
Keep suckling on me
like a child to its mother...
Do you like my pleasure tool
that much, child?
Yes!
A devout convert such as you deserve
a special gift from your master.
Your mind, body and soul will be
enveloped in a thick fog.
A fog of unearthly pleasures.
There is no need to rush!
I see you are ready and waiting to
experience the various sins of the flesh.
First, drain the liquid of sin
that flows through my tool!
So maiden, you should be so sensitive
that a breath on your skin
will send incredible shivers...
You seem lost in the fog already.
Master Mija, please help me
like you said you will!
Please help stuff my pussy
with your pleasure tool!
Hurry, please!
Pray with the desires
of your heart and soul...
Give in completely to
the lust building inside you
and I might grant your deepest desire
Please master Mija, please satisfy the lust
that's consuming every fiber of my body!
Please insert your hard, pleasure tool
inside my wet, wanting pussy,
and fuck me hard!
Please, hurry!
- I will, if that is your deepest desire.
- I can't wait anymore!
Please!
Hurry!
I said, there is no need to rush.
I can feel you inside!
I love it!
Fuck me!
Let the sensations take over your being,
and let the desires of the flesh control
your every thought and action!
More, more, I'm cumming,
I'm cumming hard!
Wait, Mayu!
Mayu, you're home awfully late!
Hungry?
I'm sleepy.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
I can't stop!
This feels so good!
Master Mija, more!
Oh Mayu...
Hello Ms. Tadeshina!
Good morning!
Good morning, Ms. T!
Being a teacher's kind of fun!
Whoa!
Are you OK?
Yes...
Lack of sleep maybe?
Watch it!
I'm sorry, but I really need to follow her!
Ouch, you big klutz!
Stalking is against the law!
A very important concept in this book
deals with a man coming to realise
the duality in his personality.
Both good and evil are clearly
represented in his character.
Mayu!
This concept of both good
and evil existing within an individual
is a common subject matter
for books written around this era.
Damn it!
Looking for clues here
is going to take forever!
I don't even know what I'm looking for!
How am I supposed to see
with the purity of my spirit!
I don't get it!
Wait, what is this?
Maybe this is what I've been looking for.
Mr. Janitor!
You scared me half to death!
You are Mr. Gann?
That leads to the school safe.
You could of said something before
scaring me half to death!
Be sure to clean up after yourselves.
Mayu!
Miwa, do you know where Mayu went?
Huh, I don't know!
I'm really worried; she's been
acting really strange.
There wasn't a door there before!
Screw it!
I can tell you have been lusting for me.
You will not be disappointed.
Master Mija!
Please, feed the burning lust
that's exploding inside me!
I played with myself all day today
but nothing compares to the way
you fuck me, master Mija!
If you want me so badly, then...
Master Mija, not there, no don't!
You just don't know yet...
Your back door seems very eager to be
opened and discovered by my touch...
Master Mija, please, just take me
anywhere, in any way you want!
That is an honest, truthful answer.
Stop it!
What?
Get away from Mayu!
You sick monster!
Oh, pity...
Master Mija!
Don't Mayu!
Damn it!
Just get away from my Mayu!
Toicos!
I can't move!
That was a surprise!
Let's try this...
My!
Stop it, Stop it now!
There's something going on here...
I think I'm cumming!
I can feel a burning lust
inside your heart and soul...
Do you have lust for this young maiden?
Master Mija, please fuck me!
Fuck me right now!
Master Mija!
I can't talk sense into you like this...
I will weaken the spell
I have cast upon you
How is that?
- You are...
- Hi Mayu!
Kotaro!
Mayu!
Don't look at me!
To have your loved one resist.
No reward for such bravery!
My, what is this?
I can see your desire is increasing rapidly
at an incredible strength
before my very eyes!
I have not cast a spell on you...
I cast a spell to give in to your epicumia
swirling inside your body!
What the hell is that thing?
I think this is what his eminence
was talking about...
I need to go.
Need to get help!
Ms. Tadeshina, what are you doing here?
Come.
Mr. Gekko... why?
Ah, Lana, it's you.
Yes, this woman was spying on us.
A pretty one; who is she?
She's our new substitute health teacher.
So?
May I please have her?
It makes no difference to me,
but I wonder what Lakellter would say...
Mr. Gann, Help!
Noooooo!
What do you think, Lana.
Nooo, Stop!
Kotaro, please stop, now!
Kotaro, no!
What a pretty specimen!
What do you say, Lana?
It would entertain me greatly to watch the
both of you both fight over this maiden.
Shit!
No, Mr. Gann, get a hold of yourself!
Don't worry, Sara; you will soon be
moaning like the whore of Babylon.
Nooooooo!
No, not there!
I can't take it!
Mayu, will you let me?
Out of my way, kid!
Nooooo, Kotaro!
What are you doing here?
Because...
He was obviously getting
in my way of fucking you silly.
I'll teach you something brand new today!
Stooop!
Let's get the party started!
Noooo!
You like it, Mayu!
Stop, Noooo!
If you don't like it,
why are you getting so wet?
What is happening to my body?
This just proves that you're a lusty whore
that will spread for any cock
to fuck your brains out!
No, that's not true!
What's not true?
You'll just about fuck anyone!
You were born a lusty whore!
Lana is doing very well!
It's my turn, Ms. Tadeshina!
We really need to get started!
Your sexy body should offer me
plenty of pleasure!
I can't believe this!
Noooooo!
I'll stuff you full and make you cry
like a newborn baby!
Get away from me!
Good times ahead!
This is thoroughly entertaining!
Wind!?
From where?
Toicos!
I must leave!
A servant of God is within us!
Teullis!
I'll be back!
Wait...
The monsters...
Hey, Mayu, Kotaro!
Are you both OK, are you hurt?
I'm going to get help, OK?
Answer me, Mayu, Kotaro!
I wonder what that thing really was...
I wonder if that really happened.
But Kotaro is in the hospital, still...
The strangest thing...
No one seems to remember
what happened down there.
Oh, we first went to
the ice cream shoppe first...
Are you listening?
Of course!
That girl...
Mr. Gann retired today.
His retirement was planned long ago.
There is one more thing, though.
I have not been able to find
the entrance to that place.
Again.