Okay, you hold that
end, I'll hold this end.
Move that side.
Let go.
Physics Classroom
S-Shizuku.
Y-You...
Don't talk.
Do me, Narifumi...
But, it's so sudden.
It's not sudden.
I've always liked you, Narifumi.
Shizuku.
Sorry.
It's okay, you can do what you want.
Shizuku, I can't...
Um, I...
Not yet.
This time, I want you to come inside me.
Shizuku...
They're hard.
Don't say that.
Can you feel it?
How about this?
No.
But you're wet.
But...
If you don't want to, I'll stop.
No, come on.
Then...
Here goes.
It's in.
I'm going to move it.
Yes, do it now.
Yes.
Yes! Yes!
It's so good!
Narifumi!
Narifumi! It's so good!
Narifumi, I...
Me too.
I'm going to come.
Narifumi!
Narifumi...
Black Gate, Gate 1
Hey, Narifumi.
Huh?
If you had enough power to do
anything you wanted with this world...
...what would you do?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Hypothetically speaking.
If you had that kind of power,
what kind of world would you create?
What kind of world?
Let's see.
Why are thinking so seriously?
It would never happen anyway.
You're the one who started it.
Jeez.
Physics Classroom
Kasumi.
What are you two doing here?
How dare you both take off
at a busy time like this?
Now get back to the classroom!
Sorry, but I have things to do.
Shizuku.
What's up with you two?
Are you twins fighting?
No, that's not it.
Shizuku's been acting strange lately.
So anyway, Narifumi...
I need you to work.
The Class President was pissed.
Where have you been, Hosokawa?
Please, please, don't be
so upset, Miss President.
You're the one who said
you wanted to do a cafe...
...yet you're the one playing hookey.
It's not that I wanted to do it...
...but no one else had any
ideas so I had no choice...
Here.
What are these?
Table cloths.
Go put them on the tables we lined up.
Me?
You've been slacking off this whole
time, it's the least you can do.
Yes, ma'am.
There you are.
Koyuki.
Everyone's looking for you.
This is why you're
always the class oddball.
I don't care.
I have you, Koyuki.
I'm flattered that you feel that way...
...but I'd rather that you
got along with everyone.
What's wrong?
Maybe I'll play hookey too.
No, not here.
Don't worry, no one will come.
No!
Fuu, have your boobs
gotten bigger again?
What do you...
See?
Look at that!
They have grown bigger.
Mine won't grow at all.
I like these small breasts.
Yes! Don't stop.
Koyuki!
Yes! Yes!
It feels good!
It feels so good!
I love you, Fuu!
I love you, Koyuki.
Let's stay together forever.
I'll protect you.
Too bad!
I'm not so weak that I
need you to protect me.
You're right.
Fuu!
Koyuki!
I'm going to come!
I can't...
Fuu, I'm coming!
Me too! I can't hold on anymore!
School President's Room
Jesus!
I'm the student president, why do
I have to do this grunt work?
Dammit!
Um...
It's you, Amane.
What's wrong?
Um, are you the only one here?
Everyone's out.
What is it?
Um...
What? Speak up!
Um, it's about our black-out curtains.
The number requested doesn't match
the number that we were given.
Too many or too few?
We're short one.
If it's just one, make do!
I'm shorthanded as it is
and I have too much to do!
But we're doing a haunted house, so
we need to have the black-out curtains.
Fine! I'll take care of it!
I'll go open the storage
room for you, follow me.
There should be at least one left.
Thank you very much.
Finished...
It's already dark out.
What difference does that
make? Tomorrow's the big day.
Everyone else has gone home.
Then why don't you go home too?
I'll finish getting ready
by myself if I have to.
I can't do that.
I'm going to the teacher's
room to make copies.
Finish setting up the
classroom while I'm gone.
Yes ma'am.
I get that she's responsible,
but she no good with people.
Don't say that.
But she's just ordering us around.
That may be true, but...
This doesn't look like
our classroom at all.
You're right.
Narifumi...
Huh?
What's this about?
What do you mean?
You shouldn't say that
when a girl invites you.
Invite?
Don't you think you should
try to set the mood more?
You know what I mean...
Shut up!
How is it going? Are you
going to finish in time?
Oh, Miss Ebizuka.
I just have to put these menus
on the tables, and we're done.
I see, so you made it, somehow.
Hosokawa and Kasumi stayed so...
That's good.
Yes.
I love you, Narifumi.
Kasumi.
So please, will you...
Kasumi, I...
You don't like me?
That's...
That's not it.
What's wrong, Kasumi?
Kasumi, what's wrong?
Who is it?
Shizuku.
It took you long enough.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm going through the gate.
What are you saying?
I need power.
You don't get it, I'm sure.
Goodbye, Sister.
Shizuku!
What the...
What happened?
Shizuku...
It can't be...
We have to get in
contact with the Elders.
Wait!
Let's go after her.
What are they doing?
What is that?
I know you haven't forgotten.
It's forbidden to go to the other side.
But maybe we can still catch up to her.
And once we catch up to her, then what
are we going to do? Bring her back?
The fact that she broke
the rules won't change.
But we're the only
ones who know about it.
What are you saying, Miharu?
The true heir to the
Kanomori lineage is Kasumi.
The destiny of the branch families of the
Kanomori is to follow Kasumi's orders.
We don't have the right to complain.
That's right.
I'm not taking responsibility for this.
What are they talking about?
So, Kasumi!
Kasumi!
Narifumi?
No! Don't break your concentration!
Earthquake?
It's out of control.
No!
What is this?
Narifumi...
What is this place?
Watch out!
W-What is this?
What's that?
Who are these people?
Our welcoming committee, but I
don't think they're happy to see us.
Let's go back.
What about Shizuku?
What the hell is going on?
I'm sorry, Narifumi.
It's all my fault.
What?
There's no time to explain right
now, it should be safe here.
I have to get back to everyone.
Kasumi.
She's so fast.
Was that really Kasumi?
Who are you?
Do you want to save the others
who are fighting out there?
I have the power...
Power?
If you want the power, do as I say.
Seek...
If you do, then I will give
you the power to rule the world.
If you are worthy of it.
Yes, that's it.
Yes, harder.
Faster.
Yes! It feels good!
I'm coming!
Release your essence!
Why am I naked?
Who are you?
What is going on?
Someone tell me.