They enslave women for their "Bondage Game".
The female slaves have lost their freedom.
Now the fun begins...
I decided to trade you out...
Please forgive me...
please don't throw me away...forgive me...
I, Sakai Kanama, as your slave, promise to obey you.
Kanama wasn't sold...
I'm just sleeping over for a bit...
Ma---Mama told me...
This is horrible! Why?
WHY?
RENJI-SAMA!!!!
Bondage Game
Game 2:
Yayoi ~The Shameful Bosom of the Lady Slave Girl~
How shameful, Lady Asahi.
That embrassing look is fitting...
Do you want to be beaten...
...that badly?
Renji-kun...
That blonde is a fun play thing...
But I'm getting a bit bored...
Wasn't the one with the big breasts your father's slave?
Won't you give her to me?
She'll probably look cute, struggling...I'd like to see.
Take care of him.
Wonderful...
Very good...
I'm gonna cum...
Open your mouth and say ahhh...
What's the matter? Do you ike it too?
Good...drink that...
Show me.
I'm already full master...
Oh, please don't push on that...
It'll come out...Master!
Master...Master...please...
Who are you calling master?
Your masters are over there.
Good...good...
I'll take good care of you...
Thank you...
Master...
Master...please forgive me...
Please!
Please let me cum...let me cum!
You can't cum because of the harness...
Isn't that painful?
Noooo!!
It's moving around...
He he...
...I'm going to make you feel even better!
No...NO...NOOOO!
It hurts...It hurts!
Stop it please...ahhh...my chest!!
How is it? How do you like it?
Noo!! My breasts!!
Oh, it's getting hot!
This one too...
This isn't happening!!
Please let me cum.
Hehe! The boobies are getting bigger!
Please, stop it...my breasts...
they're getting hot!
Please, don't go on...
It's my turn.
No, it's mine...
Let's tit fuck her!
Stop! No!! St---stop!
M----my nipples!
How's my cock feel?
Nooo...Let me cum...
please let me cum!
I'm cumming.
Me too!
I'm cumming!
Ohh please let me cum!!
Get over here!
What are you going to do?
Stop!
That smell..it smells like ta-tas...
Mama's ta-tas...
Mama.
I'm not letting something like you lick that...
get away from there!
Noo!!
This one's ass is nice and tight...
...and the pussy, it's still fresh.
Let's bust it open.
And you, you can suck on this.
Master...
I can't hold it anymore,
let me go to the bathroom...master.
No, stop!
I'm not a baby! Let me go!
No!!! Don't push!
Master! Oh, it's coming out...
I--It came out...
oh it feels so dirty...
I don't want any more...
Good...come her.
Eat it.
Yes.
No! Don't take it off!
Noooo....
Don't look at it!
I'm so embarassed!
Oh, Onee-chan...
what are you doing?
You can't lick such a dirty place!
Mmm...delicious...
Don't look!
No one look!
No!
Now it's your turn
Yes...
Hey, what are you doing? No!
Oneechan...
Renji-sama! Please stop!
I beg of you!
Please!
Please, instead, I will do anything!!!
No!...Oh, it hurts!
You can do me if you want!
Why won't you just do me?
Renji-sama...what are you..?
Renji-sa----
NOOOOOOOOO!
Welcome all!
I would like to thank all you esteemed gentlemen
for joining us here this evening.
I hope you will find tonight's show...
pleasurable and memorable.
Introducing Yuu, who has lost her memory on the left,
and the gorgeous lady of Asahi.
Tonight, we shall return these two
to their purest forms.
The sword...