Renji-sama
The shipment from Auctionia
that you ordered the other day has arrived.
A bit late, isn't it...
Might not be ready for the next game...
I don't want to make excuses to Jinkuro, though...
Well then.
Yes, Renji-sama.
The odor, it has traveled a long time,
but the body on this one is especially strong...
Your name?
I...I...
Yuu...just Yuu...
I have no other name.
If I remember correctly, you have lost your memory...
Hmm..it's rather small.
Somehow, I ended up in this mansion.
Rather small, I guess you are still untouched.
Bow down...
Let me show you the greetings of a slave.
I, Yuu, swear to pleadge aliegence
to my master and will never disobey him.
I will not forget that you were once human.
I will develop your flesh and use your body.
Yes, master.
Bondage Game
Game 1:
Yuu's Sadness "The Anal Opressor's Female Slave"
Master...
Please have mercy.
Oh, master...
It's burning me...
down there it's filling me up.
Oh it's burning...it's burning.
Push it in more.
Please don't do it master!
Forgive me!
Well then...
I shall pull it out for you.
Oh...master..I'm begging you...
don't do it that way...no!
Thank you, master.
Master...
Is this something a human being does to another?
It's horrible.
The night had begun at the mansion...
The attrocities committed here
have left me speechless...
I am left wondering, why am I here?
Is there any purpose?
But...
It was also true that I am a stray...
I have no place to go out there.
Is that going to happen to me too?
Your ass...
Yes.
This is my role...
Show me your naughty parts.
Hm. I can't see it that well...
show me more.
Suck it.
Yes...
Oh...the smell.
I left it unwashed for you.
Clean it.
Why am I being forced
to suck on something this...dirty?
Take it down your throat...
Oh..it won't go any deeper.
It's hot...so disgusting.
It's hot...my ass!
It's the master's reward.
Ask for it politely.
Please cum in to my mouth.
I'm cumming.
Open up...
Why...me?
What's the matter?...
Can't take it anymore?
Then do it here.
Don't touch me with your dirty hands you bitch...
What...what do you think you're doing to me?
Do you think you'll get away with this?
Oh, it's cold...
Even though you're from the house of Asahi,
we're not going to give you special treatment.
What are you doing?
Stop this instant!
Stop it now!
Stop it...
No...
Oh...getting licked by this disgusting oaf...
Stop it...
Stop your whining! ...
You know what you have to do...
Yes.
Show off your pretty self to our customer...
You're a lady, aren't you...
You won't last very long...
why don't we give you to our customer...
To us you're just another treasure
we found at the fallen house of Asahi.
Why don't we decorate you?
No...don't do that.
This person is a lady of the Asahi house.
Then...who am I?
Take her...
if you're going to blame someone,
blame your father who allowed the Asahi House to fall.
Noooo!
So you're enjoying being touched down there.
Stop it. I'm not feeling anything!
Oh no...it's coming out!
I knew you enjoyed it...so tight...good girl.
Oh it hurts...stop!
Move your hips, bitch.
No....
I--It hurts...it hurts.
No-o-o
Whoa, you're so tight.
Please, stop, it hurts so bad.
Oh..I'm gonna cum...
Suck it...Isuzu-chan...
Oh, it's so dirty...put it away.
Moan for me..and use your tongue...
Inspite of the horrible things being done to her..
Isuzu-san's still...
So beautiful...
I--I am your slave...
use my how you wish.
Thank you...Master.
Time to go there now...
What are you doing to me now?!
Enough already! NO!
Master, please. Forgive me! No!!
Ahh!!
Oh, my nipple!
No! Forgive me! Save me!
My parts...they are deformed!
Don't lick it!
Oh, stop!
Please don't hang me up!
Don't touch me down there!
Sachie-san!
Why?
Yuu, she is showing her love for her Master.
No way!
Feed Sachie, Yuu, that's an order.
Sachie...
Why is Sachie-san eating my shit like she likes it?
Why does Renji-sama treat Sachie like this...
While letting me...Renji-sama
RENJI-SAMA!
No! I'm not Yuu! I'm...
NO!
Why?!
Stop...
Yuu...you're still beautiful
Master...
NOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!
This is horrible...
Why?
Why would you do that?
WHY?!
Renji-sama...