Welcome Mimi!
Mimi, did you come from Colombia
just to study in Japan?
Yes.
How do you like Japan
compared to Colombia?
I think it's really nice here.
Then which do you like better?
Colombian or Japanese men?
Of course she likes Colombian men.
Isn't that right, Mimi?
Mimi is amazing.
She's suddenly become so popular.
It's only for a little while.
What?
Everybody's just curious about a
new student from a foreign country.
Hey Shimada, are you
jealous of Mimi again?
Hey, I'm not like that.
I've got an idea.
I... I'll show Mimi around the campus.
S... Shimada, I'll go with you, too.
Hey, Akira!
Let's go to the Electric Brain
Study Club later...
I've got something
interesting to show you.
Something interesting?
Forgive me I keep you riding
on uneasy feelings all the time.
Cause I wanna know
everything about you
My heart starts to
drive itself uncontrollably
And I can't help
feeling great joy.
More nervous than before
because I can't tell you
I have a desire to
love you more and more
But this emptiness
is the other side of love
Only if you take us
to a more extreme level
Your hot access
Is what I am really waiting for
Most likely I will get
you in more trouble
But please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent
like I'm bare naked in front of you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
Is what I am longing for
Graceful Reset
That's the gym.
There are athletic
clubhouses behind the gym.
Mimi, you should join some clubs
if you want to enjoy college life.
What happened to you, Shimada?
You're somehow too nice to Mimi.
Completely different from before.
Well, I'm always nice to everybody.
Besides, we are very good friends.
Aren't we, Mimi?
Yes.
Oh?
What's this?
Mimi has a ring on her ring finger.
Let me see.
It's true.
Maybe Mimi has a
boyfriend in Colombia.
Oh, is it true, Mimi?
No, this is a write protect ring
that my master used...
Yeah!! That's right!!
Somebody in Colombia,
is waiting for Mimi!
Huh?
That's nice, Mimi.
It sounds very romantic.
I want to have a boyfriend
who can give me a ring, too.
Huh?
Did something get
in your eye, Shimada?
Yes, but there's no wind today.
Akira!!
W... what's wrong, Mimi?
I willjoin the same clubs that you
belong to and enjoy college life.
The same clubs as me?
You're going to join
the Electric Brain Club?
Yes... Yes.
Do you want tojoin the club?
Let's invite Mimi to our
Electric Brain Study Club meeting.
Wait for me!
Centris.
I know Quadra, my dear sister.
But I don't like that our
little Sister Performa...
is telling us what to do!
We don't have any choice.
Last time we were defeated
by an AX named Mimi.
That's because we
weren't fighting seriously!
But defeat is defeat.
We just have to do it.
Then, shall we go?
Our target is the
Japanese bio-types!
Anyway, the Electric Brain Study
Club has only three members...
Akira, Futoshi and me.
It's just a computer lover's club.
By the way Junpei, what's
on the disk you just had?
Thanks for reminding me about that.
Ta-Daa! This is a computer virus.
Oh, a computer virus.
Oh no, a virus?
Are there any germs inside?
You are really stupid when
it comes to computers.
Listen, Shimada...
this is a virus to destroy
data inside a computer.
Actually, this is a germ
for a computer, though.
It's a new virus called worm.
It's just like a worm
but it eats up data.
Worm eats up data?
Shimada, perhaps you've got it wrong.
She definitely misunderstood.
What's wrong, Mimi?
She looks pale.
I'm not feeling well.
Mimi!?
What was that sound?
Hey Mimi, what's wrong?
Hey, Mimi!
Master, let's do it.
Memory expansion, let's do it here.
What are you talking about?!
We already did it twice last night.
But, I want it.
Don't be stupid!
What?
Who's being stupid?
Mimi is acting really silly.
She must have
eaten something weird.
Are you all right Mimi?
She's all right.
I forgot I have to
go someplace today!
See you!!!
What's wrong with him?
Next is...?
N... no way!
This security protection
is completely broken.
Security protection?
Is it?
You should be more careful.
Your rear is completely
unprotected from outside input.
Hey, I'm trying to
be more serious here.
Are you two here
to bother me again...
Nac sisters?
You won't beat me
so easily this time!
Don't even bother.
You better listen to us.
You'll pay for last time!
I told you, don't even bother.
That's right.
Fight! Fight!
Thank you master.
Then I will carry
you and run this time.
Just sit here!
Mimi!
What's the matter with you?
I guess I've hung up.
Hung up? I see.
Mimi, you must have a
reset switch on you somewhere.
Yes! I have!
Where is it?
I'll have to whisper it to you.
Really?
Yes.
Tricked you! Tricked you!
Mimi!
Akira!
It's Shimada!
This is bad!
Takaoka, where are you?
It's strange, I thought
he was around here.
Shimada, you run very fast.
Of course, I am the
co-captain of the tennis club.
But why did you guys follow me?
We thought we might
have a chance to see bloodshed.
What?
Don't be stupid!
You guys give me a headache!
Hey, wait Shimada!
I can't relax yet.
Is there any place
to hide around here?
Oh, yeah!
Bootobi Electronic Store
Hello.
Hey Takaoka, how are you doing?
Where is the bathroom?
All the way down to the left.
Thank you.
Are we expanding the
memory in the toilet today?
No!!
Now tell me Mimi,
where is the reset switch?!
OK, I'll show you now.
Not again!
You don't have to
take off your clothes.
But... the reset switch is here.
Here, you mean your bellybutton?
That's right!
Alright.
Mimi?
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you...?
Hey, Mimi!
Yes, Master!
What was I doing?
I'm the one who should be
asking you that question.
When you reset my bellybutton, the
previous 24 hours of memory is erased.
What?
Then the memory
expansion last night is?
Yes... it's all gone.
So, I need to have more memory...
otherwise my performance
will be substandard.
Sorry we were using
the bathroom so long.
But it really helped.
Don't worry.
But, Takaoka, are you all right?
You look pale.
I'm fine!
Just a little tired.
Takaoka!
I was right.
I thought you might stop by here.
We were worried about you
and started looking around.
I guess Mimi got better.
Yes.
Akira reset my bellybutton.
Yes, yes!
She means I got her some medicine.
Right, Mimi?
What?
Why are you saying such weird things?
Takaoka, do you know how
much we worried about you?
You disappeared all of a sudden!
Well, because...
We're finally gonna
see some bloodshed.
What?
What's this?
Junpei!
Did you use the computer virus?
Why would I do such a thing?
I have the disk in here.
Then what's going on here?
Look out!
What the hell is going on?
What happened?
You did well, evading
my hypnotic beam.
Even though you're an older model...
I guess you must have some
skill since you beat my sisters.
Although, you seemed rather weak
when I hacked into your data.
Mimi was acting
strangely because of you?!
I am the third sister of the Nac sisters,
Performa Nackintosh.
We're not naked this time.
Last time, I was lacking in memory.
I see!
If Mimi's memory is fully expanded,
then we don't have to be naked.
Master, you're embarrassing me.
So you like doing full uploads.
Why aren't you listening to me?!!
Mimi!
Is that all you've got?
You're boring me!
Performa!
Sisters, you are so slow.
Why do you always
talk to us like that!?
We did everything
that you told us to do.
Thank you for your hard work.
Then how did everything go?
No problems, of course.
Once we do something,
we do it right, just like this.
Forte!
And, so many other
Japanese bio-types are here.
Not bad, but the two of you should've
been able to do this very easily.
She is really getting stuck up.
What are you doing collecting
so many Japanese bio-types?
Performa!
What's next?
We must copy all of
the data from them.
Can't you figure out
these things on your own?
Hey, Performa!
Why the rude attitude
towards your sisters?!
I'm the one in charge
of this operation...
so why don't you
just follow my orders.
They seem like they hate each other.
Especially Performa,
she looks really mean.
That's enough!
Centris, you better
follow Performa's orders.
Big sister Quadra, as usual,
you are very sensible.
Now, I want you to copy
all the data from them.
I can'tjust sit here and watch.
Mimi, let's beat up the Nacs
and help everybody.
You're wonderful, Akira!
I said your name right!
Please be quick, sisters.
OK, OK.
So, you're going to show me
all your data this time.
Security protection released.
OK.
Now let's take a look
at what's inside.
W... what is this?
Nippon Bank and
the Ministry of Finance.
Almost all the
government data is here.
That looks really useful.
Quadra, why don't you
hurry and copy the data?
All right.
My breasts have 1000
terabytes of memory...
and can take anything
that you might want.
Now, let's start.
That's too heavy.
Akira!
You better decide
what we should do!
Sure!
Shit!
Oh well, I can buy
another computer.
Data transfer is completed
from all the bio-types.
Now please dispose of them.
I will take care of that AX.
What do you mean by "dispose"?
Don't ask me such
an obvious question!
We've no need
of worthless junk.
You mean throw them away?
But we can still
use them for something.
That's your character flaw,
dear sisters.
Worthless things should be
thrown away immediately.
It's also important to study
your enemy thoroughly!
Rather than just kill them!
The data we extracted from them
is more than enough information!
But we're all computers!
They may be like you,
but don't associate them with me!
Don't act so rude!
You're the youngest sister!
Data load completed!
Attack and defense motion stage 5!
Mimi, beat the Nacs
and save us all!
Yes!
Run armor device!
Setup completed!
Let's go Nackintosh!
Performa!!
I'm still talking to you!
Can't multi-task.
Are you all right, Forte?
We came here to save you.
Mimi's here, too.
So you don't have
to worry anymore.
We'll help you.
Mimi will take care of the Nacs.
I said wait!
Performa!
I want to settle this right now!
Are you listening to me, Performa?!
This is the easiest way
to avoid the beam attack.
What happened to me?
Where are Akira and Mimi?
Hey, Junpei, Futoshi!
It's no use,
they're out cold.
Oh, Junpei what did you do?!
The person who owns this shop
will blame this mess on us.
I have to clean up quickly.
The game ends here, Ms. AX.
Mimi!!
You're no challenge to me!
Stop!!
Don't shoot Mimi!
Akira!?
Fool!
It's dangerous to expose
yourself like this!
Akira, run!!!
Forte?
Everyone?
You... make a good master.
True Japanese Ioyalty!
It makes me cry no matter
how many times I see it.
I have to clean up before
the staff in the shop wakes up.
OK... this must go... in here!
Hello.
What the hell is this?
It looks disgusting!
Forte...
A waste of time!
Mimi!
What should I do?!
What is this?!
How can I get rid of this!?
No way!
Now I'll finish you!!
Hello.
Th... that's!
What the hell is this?
Disgusting!
That must be Junpei's virus!
Mimi, this is our chance.
Yes!
You've stirred up an
innocent girl's anger!!
I won't give up so easily!
Remember that!
Oh shit!!!!
Well!
Who's next?
Oh well, perhaps this was
good medicine for Performa.
Actually, it was a virus.
Time to say goodbye!
They must've had so
many chances to attack us.
Oh yeah.
We have to help
Forte and the others.
Let's take them to the house.
Hello, Takaoka speaking.
Oh, Shimada.
Akira, what happened today?
What?
Mimi wasn't feeling well again.
Oh really, that's too bad.
We had quite a bit of trouble, too.
What?
When I was cleaning up
the disks on the floor...
I inserted Junpei's
virus by mistake.
What?
You mean you put it in the computer?
Yes, I'm responsible...
You're responsible for
saving us, Shimada!
So, it was you.
I owe you one.
See ya!
So, will she live?
All the data has been removed,
and her memory is gone too.
Then, the only thing we can do
is delete her like the other AE.
There is one way to save her.
How?
If you give her a memory install.
Why me?
Besides, she has a protect ring.
She won't accept another
man's data, will she?
This may be risky.
Forte could still move even
when all her memory was taken...
because she saw you were willing
to risk your life to protect me.
She felt your warmth and caring.
If you do a re-installation, maybe...
All right!
Her installer has started!
I will open the utility file.
You will have to match
the reset timing.
B... but I can't control it!
File opened.
Three... two... one... reset!
You did it!
You did it, Akira!
You succeeded!
I... actually succeeded.
Thank you very much, Master.
No... I don't deserve to be thanked.
What?
Master?
Now you are... because you
are the one who did the install.
Forte, we have the same master, now.
Yes, I appreciate it.
I... it can't be.
Akira.
You still have all the
rest to re-install.
So let's work hard
at it together, Akira.
I'll do my best.
You are the best master, Akira.
Type is small for each other
Although we hurt each other
In the name of fate we
are destined to be together
My heart still believes more than ever
Ending never
Expanding memory forever
Dreaming of that kind of love
No matter how much the
program takes over my heart
Since I feel so sure of your faith in me
Your hot access
I feel more love from you
Most likely I will get
you into more trouble
But please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent like
I'm bare naked in front of you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
Is what I am longing for