But Shimada's father
is really a big man.
He gave her a complete computer set...
just because he
doesn't use it anymore.
I'm very proud of my Father.
But I'm not really
interested in computers.
And Takaoka told me he wanted one.
Yeah, I don't how
much to thank you Shimada.
I really appreciate it.
It's nothing, because...
I want to give
anything I can to Takaoka.
Well, I don't mean that.
There are things that would keep
their value if you keep it longer.
That's true.
You've got a heavy load.
I'll open the door.
Wait!
Oh, Akira! Do you have the key!
Welcome home. Master.
Oh, God!
Who are you?!
How do you do? I'm Mimi Takaoka.
Forgive me I keep you riding
on uneasy feelings all the time
Cause I wanna know
everything about you
My heart starts to
drive itself uncontrollably
More nervous than before
because I can't tell you
I have a desire to
love you more and more
But this emptiness is
the other side of love
Only if you take us
to a more extreme level
Your hot access
Is what I am really waiting for
Most likely I will
get you in more trouble
But please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent like
I'm bare naked in front of you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
Is what I'm longing for
Gentle Hang Up
Oh, did you grow up abroad?
Since you moved to Japan,
you'll transfer into our school.
Won't you?
Yeah, I guess so.
Then, can you join our
Electric Brain Study Club?
I'll think about it.
They'll be really surprised if they
found out she's a personal computer.
I didn't know Akira
had such a cute cousin.
She is different
from everybody else.
I guess it's because
she grew up abroad.
I really envy Akira.
He could live with such
a cute girl for a while.
You guys are talking
about Mimi all this time!
Weren't we supposed to come
here to look at the computer?!
What's wrong?
Why are you being
so cranky, Shimada?
By the way, Akira, what happened to
the computer you bought recently?
It's right here...
I sent it in for repairs!
Repair?
I suggest you repair
this primitive machine.
That's very rude!
My father was using it!
It may not the newest model,
but how can you say it's primitive.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't be so hard, Shimada.
Mimi doesn't mean any harm.
I know that.
By the way Mimi, which country were
you living in before you came here?
Well, up until I was sent
as a computer product...
Com...? What did you say?
Co... Colombia, Colombia!
Colombia?
In South America?
Yes!
It was South America, South America.
It must be difficult for you,
staying in Japan.
It was difficult there,
and difficult here.
It's really difficult.
I did it!
I cleared the stage!
Well! This time I'II...
It hung up.
What are you doing Mimi?
I was about to clear the next stage.
Because, you're ignoring me.
But I wanted to play this
game for a long time.
Why can't I play it
a little bit more?
Shimada is a really nice person.
Master, you are saying
Shimada, Shimada!
Do you like her so much?
No... it's not that.
Who's prettier Shimada or me?
Well... Mimi you're... much prettier...
than Shimada is.
Thank you Master.
How do you like that, Shimada?
Don't even try to seduce my master!
Hey! Say something!
Shimada.
Shimada is this computer?
Master, Shimada
is really unfriendly.
Let's train her how to behave.
You mean train the computer?
Yes.
Now, be a good girl!
Shimada!
Oh no! Stop, Mimi!
The computer will break.
Good morning, master.
Mimi... today is Sunday.
Let me sleep.
Look Master.
Wake up Shimada.
Voice activated computer start up!
How did you do this?!
I created a start-up recognition
batch file in the memory.
I turned the small built-in
speaker into a microphone.
First, I tried to make her to say
good morning or good night.
But she only has
640 KB of main memory.
Whoa...
But she's become much cuter.
Hasn't she, Master?
It sounds like you are teaching
a child how to behave.
Silly Master,
who's child would it be?
Master!
Please use me to
your heart's content.
Master!
Forte, how is your
project developing?
Based on the schedule,
it's about 80% completed.
If you weren't here,
I couldn't have hatched this plan.
I really appreciate your help.
I am very happy to
hear you praise me.
Master's happiness is
my own happiness.
l, NBC PC 2198 AZ, Forte.
I certainly will
meet your expectations.
Shimada.
Shall we go? Master.
I really don't think
this is a good idea.
But, I have to create my records
as Mimi Takaoka, a human...
who came from Colombia.
Like a social security
number and stuff.
Correct.
So then, let's gain access.
Where the hell are we?
A data space consisting
of simulation molecules.
It means we're inside a computer.
Inside a computer?
Are we?
Why are we naked?!
Because, right now I'm functioning
with just base memory.
You have to expand my memory
if you want to wear clothes.
You mean... we have to have sex?
My bio-program system can't
save active molecules...
for more than 72 hours.
Then to make Mimi run
at full performance...
we have to have sex
once every three days.
Master doesn't seem to like
to do installation work very much.
So I didn't tell you up until now.
Well, I...
It's not that I don't like...
Then shall we do it right now?!
No! Not now!
See! I knew you didn't like it!
I'm just saying... that's...
Anyway, going inside a
government database is a crime.
Let's finish the work and go home.
Master, you'll get lost
if you go by yourself!
Hey, Mimi.
What's taking you so long?
There are too many security
programs around here.
It's the government.
It must have as many security
programs as it has signatures.
Who are you?!
What's wrong, Mimi?
I... I'm being scanned.
Opponent machine is...
Mimi!
M... my data is being read!
This is my territory around here.
You won't get in
without my permission.
W... who are you?!
NBC PC 2198 AZ...
Forte!
PC 2198?
That means she is
same product as Mimi!
Why is she doing this?
Don't make me laugh.
I am AZ. The high-end machine.
Don't compare me with
a machine like the AX.
Oh no... your memory
is completely empty.
You're such an innocent baby.
Your owner doesn't
care much about you?
Or is his owner's level so low?
Wh... what?!
Oh crap... I look stupid
being naked like this.
It seems like somebody's been
wandering around here recently.
Girl, was it you?
No!
We came here for
the first time today.
It doesn't really matter.
Erasing intruders is my function.
Mimi!
Master! Don't come here!
B... but!
M... Master, you'll be all right.
When I'm erased,
you can go back to your room.
N... no way!
Master... even forjust a
short while, I was... happy.
M... Mimi!
Oh, such a beautiful relationship.
It makes me cry!
Mimi!!!
Now!!
Mimi! Mimi! Mimi!
Thank you, Master.
W... who is it?
What's going on?
An apple logo? Are you...?
Yes I am!
Like I said, the Japanese
bio-type is really unsophisticated.
And they don't have
any sense of taste.
Sister... can't you do something
with that Japanese font?
I'm the oldest of Nac three sisters,
Quadra Nackintosh 9000.
I am Centris Nackintosh 850.
N... Nackintosh?
More weird things keep showing up.
Who the hell are they?
American bio-type computers.
They don't have masters,
and operate by OS.
The one on the left,
model 9000 has...
1000 terabytes of huge hard disk
drive space in both of her breasts.
Her performance is...
Master!
You were the ones who were
accessing my work area.
I think Japanese bio-types
are stuck up, harsh...
and really unfriendly.
They're really annoying.
I will erase you two!
Yeah... let's get rid of them!
What?
It was so fast,
I couldn't see anything.
Your naked body looks really funny.
Sister... please give me
Japanese font recognition.
I don't really care.
Why don't you kill that girl?
Of course, I would
be happy to do that.
I was at a loss because, the data
space is too large to find you.
But you saved me the trouble
by working in this area.
I will take your data!
Oh, I didn't know you still had the
power to set up data protection.
Then I will let
you in on something.
Our goal is to dominate
the Japanese market.
Put simply, we want to get
rid of Japanese bio-type computers...
make USA #1 and
then will be very happy.
That's not simply put.
Dominate the Japanese market?
Here!
Now show me all your data!
Japanese data protection
systems are really cheesy.
S... shit!
Last protection level
is about to break!
Wait!
Let that person go, right now!
H... hey Mimi!
Well, well...
I didn't know there was another
Japanese bio-type machine here.
Look, the owner is
hanging out with her.
I have lots of room to eat him.
S... shit! Let's get out of here!
It's not that easy to escape.
You two will find it very
difficult to move in here.
Hey, Mimi!
Master.
We can'tjust leave AZ Forte here.
I will fight!
Mimi.
It's really so Japanese.
How dramatic.
It makes me cry!
What's so touching about it?
I only have memory
for two shots.
So I can't miss!
Too weak!
Oops!
Hey! Be more careful!
Sorry about that.
Master, take care of Forte!
I... I got it!
Oh well, this wasn't my plan,
but I will take the boy.
Master!
Hurting humans?!
What kinds of computers are you?!
No, No, No.
I would never hurt humans? Would I?
Don't act so innocent?!
You just did...
Master, what happened
to your stomach?
Well... I'm not hurt at all.
Oh, Master, how did your
installer become so big?
N... No! Mine is not like this...
Yes, that is for
Nac machine use only.
It's an erection power saver.
S... such a dirty name
for an application.
Well, let's install some fresh
Japanese fonts from this boy.
That's a nice idea.
Hey, come on boy!
Let's install!
Master!
No!!!
How could you?!
Attacking your owner?!
What the hell are you doing?!
Sister.
What?
Well... I suggest you should
wear underwear properly.
Master! Master!
Are you all right?! Master!
I'm sorry, Master!
Master?
Mimi! Let's expand the memory!
Well then, I'll get him this time.
Master!
Centris!
Mimi!
Great!
Master, you're really strong today!
Sister!
That boy's installer has much
stronger power, because of the saver.
Why are we hiding?
I don't know.
Mimi!
Master!
I'm... so happy!
Memory expanded!
Equipped 6000 gigabytes!
OK!
Load armor device!
Set up...
completed!
Alright, you won't have
it so easy this time!
Beam attack version 4.0!
Run!
Acting perverted in front of others!
Don't you Japanese have any modesty?!
Prepare to die!
No, you prepare!
Dammit, sister!
Sorry about that!
I need more beam power!
If I had 600 kilobytes more...
I could use another version
of the beam attack!
Master, give me another
600 kilobytes of memory!
No way!
I'm spent!
Too bad!
Mimi!
Fo... Forte.
Are you a fool?
Either way, your
destiny is being erased.
This is a very beautiful friendship.
It makes me cry too.
Sister, please.
Come on, get it up!
I won't forgive you!
I won't! Nackintosh!!
Sister, it seems like she still
doesn't understand our real power.
She doesn't.
I will teach you
to fear American power!
Mimi!
Shimada! You're here!
Shimada? The personal computer?
Memory expanded!
600 kilobytes OK!
Centris!
OK!
Double Shield!
This game has been "ochazuke"! *
*(Green tea over rice)
Sister, it's pronounced "oazuke"*!
*(called off)
Sorry about that.
Well, I guess we're saved.
Yes... placing Shimada into
the virtual drive was a good idea.
Thank you Shimada.
You saved us.
Oh... are you all right?
I don't want to be friends with you.
But I owe you thanks.
AZ... Forte.
You... came here to make
your proof of existence?
I will take care of that.
So then we're even.
Yes.
You should never
come back here again.
I'm tired.
I'm sorry, I should have
gone there by myself.
W... what are you talking about!?
If you were alone,
right now you would be...
I don't even want to think about it.
Master.
But who is that girl, Forte.
I don't know anything about her.
Or about the Nacks, either.
I see.
Then it's not worth thinking about,
if you don't even know.
Hello, Takaoka residence.
Takaoka? This is Shimada.
Shimada?
Thank you! Thank you!
You really saved my life.
I... I just wanted to check
how the computer's working?
It's great!
Shimada saved my life.
I really wanted to thank you.
I'm glad you're so happy.
By the way... I...
What?
Mas... ter.
What do you want Mimi?
I used up all my memory
during that fight.
I need you to expand
my memory again.
Well... that is...
But if you're gentler this time,
I will be very happy.
Mimi!
I'm about to hang up again.
Type is small for each other
Although we hurt each other
My heart still
believes more than ever
In the name of fate
we are destined to be together
Dreaming of that kind of love
Since I feel so sure
of your faith in me
No matter how much the
program takes over my heart
Your hot access
As I feel more love from you
Most likely I will get
you into more trouble
But, please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent,
like I'm bare naked in front of you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
I am longing for
I finally finished processing the
transfer to my master's school.
I am gonna enjoy campus
life to the fullest!!
Or so I was hoping...
But those annoying Nac
sisters showed up again.
The youngest, Performa,
is quite strong though.
This could be my
biggest crisis ever!
Buttobi CPU, Episode 3,
"Graceful Reset"
I wanna memory up with you tonight.