I got it!
I finally got it!
My own computer!
I finally bought it!
What the hell is this?!
Forgive me I keep you riding
on uneasy feelings all the time
Cause I wanna know
everything about you
My heart starts to
drive itself uncontrollably
And I can't help
feeling great joy
More nervous than before
because I can't tell you
I have a desire to love
you more and more
But this emptiness is
the other side of love
Only if you take us
to a higher level
Your hot access
Is what I am really waiting for
Most likely I will get
you in more trouble
But please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent
like I'm bare naked before you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
Is what I'm longing for
Extreme Access
I... I've been tricked.
Three years of earning
money from part-time jobs...
have bought me a vinyl sex doll!
It... it moved.
Thank you very much for
purchasing this product.
I... it's talking.
I am an NBC personal
computer PC 2198 AX.
2198?
Did you just say 2198?
Th... that shouldn't be right.
But... the writing on the box said 9821.
You're mistaken, Master.
Master?
You read it this way.
See?
Oh, now I see.
This isn't funny!
I want to return it right now!!
Unfortunately, you already
filed your user registration.
What?
I will execute the owner's
utility program now.
Please begin the system format.
System format?
What are you talking about?
You're just a vinyl sex doll?
Master, you don't seem
to have a lot of knowledge...
about bio-type computers like myself.
Then I don't have much choice.
I will change the program to level 1.
L... Level 1?
That means the lowest?
I have to force you to input
your data to format the system.
W... wait!
Keep away!
Ah... wait! Hey!
S... stop!
Stop!!
H... hey!
What are you doing?
W... wait a minute.
A whole PC9821 set
isjust 98,000 yen?
I'll get it! I'll definitely get it!
It's at Animal Electric in Akihabara.
Third floor of the PC building.
Thank you Junpei! Futoshi!
Friends are always helpful.
Aren't they?
Well, if I can get it I can be.
But, Takaoka...
What?
Look at the top of the flyer.
For the first five customers only!
I'm sure there are people who've
waited in line from the night before.
The store opens at 10 AM.
What are you going
to do about school?
Well, I'll cut class and go.
Do you have enough money?
I worked hard part-time for
three years and saved 110,000 yen.
Besides, I'm the only person in the
Electric Brain Study Society...
that doesn't have his own computer.
I can't pass up this chance.
Takaoka.
What's everybody discussing?
You guys all look excited.
What's up Shimada?
Akira is finally buying a computer.
You guys are talking
about computers again?
Doesn't anybody
get bored of it?
Shut up! You don't even know
how to use a computer...
so don't tell us what to do!
Who cares!
I know you're only playing
X-Rated games on it.
Foolish girl!
We got bored of those kind of
games a long time ago!
Asshole.
Akira, are you buying a computer
to play those kind of games, too?
Don't even think that
I'm like Junpei.
Then why?
I'm going to deal with the world.
The world?
Yes!
I want to have access all
over the world via the Internet.
Akira, you are so cool!
What's so cool about it?
I must own a computer to do that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My hand slipped.
Well, we always give you
a 30 to 40% discount.
Nobody can beat our prices
here at Animal Electric.
The PC 9821 printed on the ad?
Sorry, it sold out in five minutes.
What?!
The cheapest one in all
the other places is 210,000.
I can't buy it unless I
work for another three years.
Hey... boy.
M... me?
Yes...
You came here to buy
a computer, didn't you?
Yeah.
But the one I wanted to buy
was sold out in five minutes.
I think they made that ad
just to bring in customers.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Well then, take a look at this.
9821?
How much is that
store selling this for?
N... ninety eight thousand yen.
I see... I can sell you this
one at the same price.
What?!
B... but isn't that used?
You must be kidding.
This is brand new.
This is a bankruptcy liquidated
product from a home electronics store.
W... what are the specs?
64 MB memory. A Pentacle 481 CPU.
Are you sure the price is 98,000 yen?
It comes with the
manufacturer's warranty.
I... I'll take it!
You got it!
But once you've open the package,
you can't return it.
As soon as you see what's inside,
it automatically registers the user.
And we don't deliver.
Sorry, but you'll have
to carry it with you.
Forced input completed.
It's so sad to end
my boyhood life like this.
Next, I will write the
data into a file.
Y... you, what do you...?
Oh?!
Owner format completed.
Reset and restart the computer.
Is it broken?
I... it's warm and soft.
Just like a human.
No!
This is... I...
System has restarted.
I will read your data.
Name: Akira Takaoka,
21 years old, Blood type A RH+...
Height 170 cm, Weight 56 kg.
Student of Hakusen Gakuen college.
You have 2 parents and a sister.
Your parents are living in
London for their business.
Your sister is abroad as a
member of a volunteer group.
W... wait a minute.
I never told you
any of those things.
I got it from reading your
active molecule.
My active molecule?
You mean?!
It was very good.
Oh, really?
I don't care about that!
What right do you
have to investigate me?
B... but...
I will tell you if you don't know.
It's called "invasion of privacy".
I understand.
Then let's use another parameter.
Enough!
Yes.
Master.
Please order me to do something.
Please.
Order me... to do something.
Master.
I'll wait for your command.
Forever.
It's my sister's.
Please put it on.
It's difficult for me to talk,
if you are naked.
Yes.
Master.
How do I look?
Oh... I guess it's your size.
It looks good on you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Master.
Here.
What's this?
This is my protect ring
to prevent other people...
from writing their
personal data on me.
It's proof that I serve you.
I see.
A protect ring for write protection.
How do you use this?
Put it on my...
...left ring finger.
What?
Wow!
This is somewhat like a wedding.
Now l, NBC PC2198AX,
product name Pixie...
am set to serve you.
Pixie?
I remember that means small fairy.
Use me however you'd
like on a regular basis.
I'm here to serve you.
Well, Master, you can give
me any command you want.
A... any command?
I will connect to my modem.
No, it's all right! Hello.
Hey, Akira?
What's "alright"?
Oh, nothing.
What's wrong?
Are you excited because
you bought a computer?
Y... yeah, I bought it but...
Great!
Then Futoshi and I will bring over a
bunch of software for you right now!
I'm looking forward to seeing it!
Is something wrong?
My friends are coming
to see me now.
Then let me prepare
to serve them.
What's wrong?
Warning!
A same model computer signal
is interfering in this area!
Friendly access is being rejected.
Parity check is being ignored.
I've found many bugs in
this opponent's utilities.
Warning.
Opponent model...
while ignoring my instructions,
is running an attack application
What are we going to do, Master?
But there's just a girl walking.
I don't see any dangerous...
Master!
Watch out!!
She attacked us!
W... whatjust happened?
Master, should I fire a
counter-attack against her?
Counter-attack?
How can we do that?
What's this?
These are application cards
for the 2198 series, like me.
What? This is software?
Blue card is for life.
Yellow is for emergency.
Red is for attack.
We can expand our areas of
operation by using these cards.
Opponent machine
has invaded the perimeter!!
Give me the order for counter attack!
Then, I will pick this!
Red number three!
Beam attack!
W... why are you taking
off your underwear?
Please insert the application
card into the front slot drive.
Slot?
T... there?
Master! Please hurry!
Alright, alright.
Oh yes!
Y... you don't have to moan like that.
S... she's here!
Begin loading data!
Start up beam attack!!
What's wrong?
I can't start.
What?!
Oh shit!
W... why can't you start?
I need an upgrade.
You don't have enough memory?!
Damn it.
It's because of my damn father...
This room and the toilet are
the only places I can lock.
He said something stupid, like...
"families should never
keep any secrets".
Master, please give
me 1500 gigabytes memory.
1500 gigabytes?
Do you know how much that costs?!
Hey stop.
Don't get undressed just
because we're in the bathroom.
But we can't start the application
if we don't expand the memory.
Please give me memory, Master.
There's no computer
shops open at this time.
The only way to
increase my memory...
is to install more of your active
molecules into my front slot.
What?!!
Please, Master!
M... my active molecule?
I... install into your...
f... front slot?
Master...
hurry up.
Install them into me.
B... but...
I...
I!!
Please.
Master.
I... I'll make a directory for
the newly installed memory.
Give me a name...
Mimi!!
Mimi... is it?
M... my name is Mimi.
Make a directory.
File name: Mimi.
Oh... memory is expanding.
200, 500, 700.
Memory expanded!
Current status is 1600 gigabytes.
OK!
Application: Beam attack!
She doesn't have a ring.
Is she dead?
No, just her higher
functions have stopped.
But why did she attack us?
Her protect ring was taken off...
and several people have
overwritten data on her.
That's why she locked up.
Yes.
Is he your...
Master?
He must be treating
you very nice.
I envy you.
My...
My Master is...
No.
I can't remember anything.
I'm... sorry to bother you... but...
please make me disappear.
I understand.
I will execute an extinction command.
Serial number 868091
NBC PC 2198 AE.
2198?
She's the same as Mimi.
Do you want to continue with
the extinction command?
Yes.
Executing command.
Thank you.
Mimi.
We can't choose masters.
We are computers.
We are products sent
from a factory.
She had...
bad luck.
Mimi.
Oh shit!
My friends are coming here soon!
Oh, don't worry about it.
What?
Please insert yellow R4.
What?! Install memory again?
No, I have enough memory for now.
Data load completed.
Yellow R4.
Restoration version 3.0.
Execute.
Wow, you're heavy!
Futoshi, you should lose more weight.
Junpei! Look in front of you.
What?
Oh no, the handle is bent.
Junpei.
What?
Just now, I saw Akira's
broken house fix itself.
What?
Futoshi, did you just bang your head?
No.
Just my ass.
Master, everything is back to normal.
Wow, how did you just do that?
Oh no, they're here.
Then I must welcome them.
You stay right here, OK.
Hello, Akira.
Good evening, Takaoka.
I brought lots of software,
just like I said.
Oh... but right now...
I'm kind of busy.
What?
Is something wrong
with your new computer?
Then I can...
No! Not now!
It's really bad right now.
Sorry, see you at school, goodnight!
Hey, Akira!?
He's weird.
I sent them home.
Was it all right?
I have no idea how to
introduce you to them.
From this day on, I am Mimi.
I got a great name from you.
And...
I'm all yours forever and always.
All mine?
Yes, Master.
Oh yeah, Mimi, you said you were
waiting for a command, didn't you?
Yes.
Please order me to do anything.
That's it.
I would rather be called
by my name, than master.
Yes, I understand.
Akira.
A... kira?
A... kira... A... kira, oh no.
A... kira... A... kira.
It's difficult to say your name.
Maybe Akira got an
extremely dirty game.
He might be trying to enjoy it
all by himself, so he sent us away.
Akira, Akira.
Mimi... that's enough.
Akira!
I said it!
I did it! I did it!
I said it Master!
What's the matter, Futoshi?
Oh... nothing.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Type is small for each other
Although we hurt each other
In the name of fate
we are destined to be together
My heart still believes
more than ever
Ending never
expanding memory forever
Dreaming of that kind of love
Since I feel so sure
of your faith in me
No matter how much the
program takes over my heart
Your hot access
I feel more love from you
Most likely I will get
you into more trouble
But please accept my wholeness
With my heart kept innocent
like I'm bare naked in front of you
As I stand close to you
Your hot access
I am longing for
I am a personal computer, Mimi.
I was so lucky to be picked
up by a wonderful master, Akira.
But, he lied about me.
Saying that I'm a relative
from overseas, to everyone.
So I had to hustle
to keep up with all those lies.
But you'll have to wait to enjoy
those details in the next episode.
Buttobi CPU, Episode 2.
"Hang Up Gently"
I will memory up with you tonight.