That car...
Duck down for a bit.
What, you don't want people to see me with you?
Just do it.
Hideaki?
Hey, let me have this.
You're pretty sensitive.
That's cute.
Cambrian Last Sage
Never Ending Lust
What happened between her
and Professor Yamagishi?
Keiko...
I love her... what can I do with my feelings?
A dream?
Yes, it was a dream.
Only a dream...
Are you awake?
You are just as beautiful as I remembered.
There's nothing to worry about.
My research is complete.
I want to share this joy of success with you.
Don't be afraid.
This is... love.
Wow, sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
Hirotaka...
But, how did you...
Clumsy, you left the door unlocked.
It's mysterious...
I've seen you naked many times and
yet, you look more beautiful than ever.
W, well...
Don't, I'm not in the mood today.
That's a lie.
See, you want it badly.
S, stop!
What, that's out of the question!
S, stop!!
Keiko?
Why Keiko!!?
Leave, please!
I saw you last with Hideaki last night.
With Hideaki?
Did something happen between you two!?
Leave for today, please Hirotaka!
What... happened to me?
No answers...
Sorry to tell you, but you won't find your answers.
Professor?
By the way, has signs of evolution surfaced?
If so, wasn't it while you were sexually aroused?
Make me back to normal!
The virus that contains the Cambrian DNA
is fusing with your DNA and expanding.
Once your evolution is complete
I will ask you to marry me.
I hope to see you soon.
You know you can't park here?
Hey, do you work here?
I use to work here long time ago.
Keiko.
Um... well...
I want... I want to help you!
Hideaki?
What happened between you and
Professor Yamagishi yesterday?
Haruhiko Yamagishi is the one who got banned from
society because he was trying to create clones, right?
He may be smart, but he's also dangerous.
I don't know what kind of
relationship you had with him, but...
I can't...
I can't tell anyone.
I may not be the most reliable guy...
Well, I...
I can love you more than anyone else!
Hideaki...
Thank you, Hideaki.
What do you think you're doing!?
Don't lay your hands on... my girl!
What was that for!?
You... you can not make Keiko happy!
What!?
You perverted fuck!
Stop this Hirotaka, it's all a misunderstanding.
Shut up!
Hirotaka?
Don't hit her!
Hirotaka!
What... has gotten into you?
Don't think I sleep with any random guy.
I only sleep with the good ones.
Don't be afraid.
What ever happens from here, it's all an illusion of lust.
Scared?
T, this is the best I've ever had.
It's so great!
You're an amazing girl.
You are Eve, give Adam your apple!
I'm cuming!!!!!
Cambrian DNA...
It has a particular effect during the evolution.
It has an effect of enhancing behaviors and thinking.
I recently discovered this.
For example, girls who like sex keep wanting more.
A violent man becomes more violent.
The seed I have planted is definitely developing.
And also expanding...
Keiko.
And?
I've never hit a girl before.
What amazed me was that it felt extremely satisfying.
You're evolving as well.
Let your body flow with ambition.
You'll then see a new world before you.
Look at me, aren't I beautiful?
Beautiful...
You're officially now a part of the Cambrian.
Otherwise you wouldn't see me beautiful.
I am through with Keiko...
However, I will not let it end silently, I will have my
ways.
Doing what?
I'll torment both of them into hell.
That's the spirit.
Let yourself free, don't let anything stop you.
That's the way of the Cambrian.
What does Keiko want from me... here?
What!?
Keiko!!
What's the meaning of this!?
Hideaki, you said I can't make Keiko happy.
Alright, you can have her.
However, not for free.
Show me how much you love her.
Stop, what are you thinking!?
Keiko!
Hideaki...?
Answer honestly.
How many times have you
imagined having sex with her?
How many times... have you poked this!?
Or have you had dirtier thoughts...
And fucked this relentlessly!
Don't want to answer?
Well, what is it?
Will you keep quiet after this!?
S, stop!!
Come on, say it!
Say that you though about fucking Keiko Kurakake!
P, please stop!!
Say it!
I... thought... about fucking Keiko Kurakake...
He might be bluffing.
Lets make sure.
D, don't!
Oh my.
He's fucking hard!
No...
Bodies don't lie.
No matter how much you oppose, you are enjoying
this somewhere deep inside your emotions.
Keiko, I'm going to regret this
but this is the last time we fuck.
My body is craving for lust!
Mine too.
You're actually quiet manly here.
No one can stop us now.
Hirotaka, you too!?
Hideaki, these are monsters created by Haruhiko!
Not monsters, we're evolved humans!
Heavenly lust, hellish lust.
Blood lust...
And sexual lust.
Enjoy it thoroughly!
I am... too...
Keiko!?
K, Keiko.
This is what I am.
Can you still love me?
If it's destined...
The End