N-No...
No, Naoya...
T-The class will...
...start soon...
What, Professor Serina?
Want me to stop it right now?
No, don't stop it.
Uh-uh.
I'll give you a prize if you
teach the class with this inside you.
Let's put it deeper...
See?
If you close your legs real tight,
people won't be able to hear the sound.
Squeeze your muscles.
I'll come if I squeeze...
No, not yet.
Serina!
Wake up, Serina!
It's your turn to make breakfast!
Wake up!
Five more minutes...
Serina!
Good God!
Yuimi, wait for me!
I'm Serina Kawano, I just
became a teacher this year.
You're the one who overslept!
Yuimi is my younger sister,
we go to the same school.
Of course, she's a student.
Our love stories are
about to begin, but...
So this will be the
answer to the question...
Excuse me!
Y-Yes?
You made a mistake!
What?
You miscopied the text!
Wake up, Professor.
His name is Naoya Yamazaki.
He's my boyfriend.
Professor Serina, be my girlfriend.
What?
He is selfish and pushy...
He always has his
way in this relationship.
I kind of fell for his
masculine side, but...
Recently I've been feeling a little...
Professor Kawano.
Professor Goto.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
You look pale.
I'm sure, I'm okay...
Hmm, you don't look
okay, is it this heat?
M-Maybe...
I know a good eel restaurant,
would you like to go with me sometime?
Y-Yes, that sounds good...
Really?
Great!
I didn't think you would.
I can't stand anymore...
Hey, Yamazaki!
Hey, wait!
My boyfriend is so mean...
What does Naoya
really think about me?
Maybe he doesn't like me...
Is that why he's so mean to me?
Sorry!
Yuta!
Yuimi?
Serina...
What was that about?
Was that Yuta from Class D?
Uh-huh...
Are you two going out?
He is kind of cute.
Uh-huh...
What's the matter?
You look upset.
I've been trying to seduce him, but he
doesn't want anything to do with me!
Stupid Yuta!
Jerk!
Um...
Maybe he's waiting for the right time.
But, but, but, we've been
going out for three months!
That stupid Yuta...
What's wrong?
U-Um, nothing...
What's the matter?
We should start with platonic love.
Yuta!
Even a shy girl would be
making a move by now!
R-Really?
Maybe he isn't really serious about me.
He is usually very sweet though.
I don't understand boys at all.
Yuimi...
I know!
W-What?
Tomorrow I'll ask Yuta
how he feels about me.
Directly?
Yes!
I'll never understand boys if
I just sit here and complain!
B-But...
Aren't you afraid to ask him?
Why?
What if you don't like
what he has to tell you?
What if he doesn't like me, and...
W-What?
So...
You're in love with
someone, aren't you?
What?
Good!
So, you finally...
Who is it, is it one of the teachers?
N-No, I was just talking general...
I know, I know, leave everything to me!
I have a good idea.
What?
You did it again?
Yep...
You should try to hold back a little...
She is super cute, and when
she looks at me like that...
What if she already knows?
Do you think she's disappointed?
Yuta!
Can I talk to you for a second?
I want to ask you something.
W-What?
Uh, so, what did you want to ask me?
Um...
Well...
Why do I have to act like a voyeur?
This is what you need.
You have no confidence in yourself!
Look, I'll ask Yuta tomorrow, so
you come and see how it's done.
If it works well, it
should give you courage.
But, what if it doesn't work?
If it doesn't...
...we'll have to comfort each other.
Hey, Yuimi!
I'm just kidding!
Are you blushing?
No, I'm not, Yuimi!
Good, she's here.
Well, Yuta...
What?
W-What's wrong, Yuimi?
Don't you like me anymore?
W-W-What?
That drama queen...
W-Wait a minute, Yuimi.
We've been going out
for three months, but...
...you still won't do anything with me...
You must've thought I was a slut
or something after trying to kiss you...
Are you mad at me?
I know I shouldn't have done that...
I understand if you
don't like me anymore.
Yuimi!
No, I like you.
I'm sorry, it's not like that...
Yuta...
When you tried to kiss me,
you were just so cute, and...
...before I even kissed you...
...l...
Um...
Well...
I...
I came.
What?
It's so lame, right?
I'm just a big pervert.
When you look at me like
that, I just can't hold it.
I'm really lame, I'm ashamed
of myself for being a man!
You don't like me anymore, right?
Yuta...
I'm glad.
What?
I was worried that maybe
I wasn't pretty enough...
...or I thought you just didn't like me...
But I'm glad...
B-But I'm still a pervert...
No, you're not, you're just a boy!
Yuimi!
I'm happy for you, Yuimi.
Yuta?
I'm sorry, I almost came...
What?
Well then...
W-Wait, Yuimi, hey...
Wow, Yuta is so big!
I-I'm sorry, are you okay?
Once you come, you'll be okay, right?
Yuimi...
Yuimi.
Look Yuta...
I'm very horny too.
I got turned on just looking at your penis.
Really...
...wet...
I'll do anything naughty for you.
Yuimi!
Oh, no...
You became so bold all of sudden...
Yuimi, it's overflowing...
Stop it, Yuta...
I want it.
I want to suck you...
Wow, you came so much, again...
And it's still hard.
Yuimi!
Yuimi, I want to put it in.
N-No!
Please don't rub there.
Again...
You came because I
made you feel good, right?
I'm happy...
It's a safe day of the month, so
come inside as many times as you want!
Y-Yuimi!
It feels so good...
G-Great, Yuta!
Yuimi!
You're kidding, you came just now...
I-I'm the only one coming...
So I'm going to make you come too...
Y-Yuta...
Y-Yuimi, how's this?
Yes, Yuta...
Yes!
Oh no...
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I came too...
It worked out okay for Yuimi,
but I don't know about me.
How does Naoya really feel about me?
Professor...
You know how to give head.
You're really a pervert, aren't you?
How many guys have
you slept with?
I forget.
Oh, yeah?
You've had sex with that many, huh?
No, there is no way he likes me...
Why you don't have the vibrator?
Because, that was yesterday...
I've never told you to take it out.
But...
I see, you want me to punish you, huh?
Professor...
You've never used this hole before, right?
No...
No!
This hole is already wet too.
You're really horny, Professor.
N-No...
It hurts, Naoya.
Ouch...
No, please stop it.
Then...
Say "please put your
penis inside my vagina."
Say it!
Please put your
penis inside my vagina...
Why?
Is this relationship over?
Hey, open your legs!
Open your vagina for me.
You want this, don't you, Professor?
Look, you're dripping wet...
How was the class with the vibrator?
Are you getting excited?
What a pervert!
Hey, beg me more!
Don't you want it?
You just want this, right?
No!
How can you stand it?
Do you really like this kind of play?
Are you really that perverted?
Because...
What?
I like...
I know you like it!
You like dirty sex!
T-That's not true!
How is it?
Do you feel good, Professor?
Stop!
Your boobs are so big.
No, it hurts...
It hurts, please be more gentle...
Naoya!
What?
I'm always gentle to you, aren't I?
They're really big.
They sandwich me perfectly.
No...
I know it's not fair to your other
hole, right, Professor Serina?
No, stop it...
Please...
Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
If you don't like me...
...why don't you just tell me?
Sorry, I'm just a kid.
What?
I'm not a real adult like Professor Goto!
If you like older men, it's fine, go ahead!
I'm just...
I'm just a kid!
Naoya.
Naoya...
You are childish.
Shut up.
You can come on my face, Naoya.
It's great, Professor...
Good...
Professor, I'm coming...
Y-Yes, please come...
Oh, I'm coming!
Me too!
Professor...
Professor?
Can I try the other hole next time?
You're really childish, Naoya.
Serina, you're late!
Sorry, did you wait long?
So, your boyfriend was him!
Don't...
Nice to meet you, I'm
Serina's younger sister, Yuimi!
Kawano from class
B, you're Serina's sister?
Oh, shit!
You didn't know?
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing!
Naoya, what's going on?