Hurry up!
Okay, which do you prefer?
Number one or number two?
N-number two, please!
Would you close the door, please?
S-Sure!
You've never done anal before, have you?
It's all right, calm down.
It will definitely fit!
It's in!
That's amazing!
Go on, pound me!
You can let it all out,
right up my ass, baby.
O-Okay!
Close the door, will you?
So the spoiled brat has discovered
the joys of serving others at last.
My treatments were
just what she needed...
Don't come in!
Dr. Shameless... Examination 2
It's embarrassing!
Mother-Daughter Full Course
All-You-Can-Eat
E-Emergency!
Please, help us! She fell
down the hill just outside...
I think she might have broken something.
She's in a lot of pain!
Exam Room
Does this hurt?
No.
How about this?
No, it doesn't hurt.
The hospital is in better
financial shape now...
...and the patients all seem
so much happier with us now.
Dr. Ishida is an amazing person...
Both the bone and the
ligament seem fine.
There's really no need
for an X-ray, either.
I'll write up a prescription
for compresses and painkillers.
You should avoid all forms of
exercise for the time being.
Thank you, Doctor!
Thank God you weren't
seriously hurt, Tomomi.
Actually, Mrs. Kinoshita...
Excuse me?
You look pale.
What?
Let me have a look at you.
Ms. Nagatsuka, please put a
compress on the young lady's leg.
Come this way.
D-Doctor, what kind
of examination is this?
No need to worry.
Trust me.
This smell...
It's quite suspicious...
I should take a look.
How lovely...
It's hard to believe that
you actually gave birth.
L-ls there a problem?
Well, recently there's
been an outbreak of a...
...new kind of STD among women your age...
STD?
I know it's my job, but I'm
getting fed up with young girls.
The timing couldn't be better, I've
been lusting after a mature woman...
...and here she is,
like a moth to a flame.
A pretty good catch, no less...
Is something the matter?
Um, no...
Um, Doctor?
Um...
Is this really a medical examination?
Until last year...
...I was working in L.A. As a member
of a cutting-edge medical team.
This is a gynecological
procedure developed by...
...renowned authorities, and has
been nominated for a Nobel Prize.
I'm probably the only physician
qualified to do this in Japan.
Am I hurting you in any way?
N-No, not really...
No sign of sexually
transmitted diseases.
However, I'd like to test
you further to be safe.
Please keep the blindfold on, if any light
should leak out it will skew the results.
Okay...
Please get on your hands and knees.
Yes, Doctor.
I'm going to take a tissue sample.
This may take a while,
but I have to be thorough.
Otherwise we run the risk
of compromising the test.
Just let me know if you get nauseous.
Yes, Doctor.
I'm going to insert the equipment now...
W-What's this?
I need you to relax.
I'm going to roll you into position now.
N-No!
Now I'm going to reach way
back for another sample...
Are you all right?
You look like you're in some pain.
No, I'm all right.
Please, don't stop what you're doing!
I'll be done in a minute.
It might get unpleasant
but please bear with me.
You can remove the blindfold now.
It will take about a week
for the results to come out.
As soon as I've seen
them, I'll notify you.
Yes, Doctor.
Mother, what was that all about?
N-Nothing, he was just taking down my
history and gave me a little checkup.
That's it? But your complexion's
a lot better now, for some reason.
Oh, do you think so?
Hey Mom, that doctor was kind
of good-looking, don't you think?
And he seems really
competent, too. So unlike Dad!
Huh?
Whoops.
You're taking lunch now?
Yes...
Um, Doctor?
Since you arrived, the hospital
has taken a turn for the better.
I wanted to thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
I'm just doing the job
that was given to me.
Still...
The Director is quite
the ladies' man, I see.
Huh?
Oh, her.
That's someone from the Sales
Dept. At M.M. Pharmaceuticals.
It's a business
relationship, that's all.
Daddy!
Yes!
Doctor, you're the best!
Oh, I almost forgot, Doctor...
That girl Tomomi who
was here this afternoon?
I just read all about her in a magazine!
She's actually made
herself a small fortune.
I couldn't believe it!
What are you talking about?
Well, she invented a toy called the Mole
Alien, and it's become a breakout hit.
I hear they're flying off the shelves.
She's so young, too.
I wish I could get rich!
I see...
Not again!
What a bummer.
Well, I'm about to be summoned, anyway.
You're pretty good at this, aren't you?
But you have to work a little harder!
Come on, we're rehabilitating you!
It's not easy to...
...readjust to society, is it?
Ow, hot!
What are you doing? You
have to keep licking!
Yes, you're hitting my spot!
Okay, next!
Lick the inside of my
anus with your tongue now!
You've improved immeasurably!
As a reward, I'll do
something ever so nice for you!
You're an angel...
I was right, you're a real
live angel in a nurse's uniform!
Hey, you are...
Doctor!
It looks like that leg is doing a lot better
now, but you still need to go easy on it.
My car's parked nearby.
Why don't I drive you home?
Everyday is the same...
Yes!
M-More, Doctor!
This is my house, Doctor.
It's quite an impressive house.
Mom, we have a guest!
I've asked Dr. Ishida to stop by!
Dr. Ishida?
Good afternoon.
We ran into each other at the
train station, and he drove me home.
Thank you, Doctor!
Well, it's very untidy but
please make yourself at home!
Doctor, you have to
come up to my room first.
I want to show you my Mole
Alien goods, I've got them all!
I can't wait to see them.
Shall we go, then?
Mrs. Kinoshita?
Yes, Doctor?
I'm here today to check up
on your daughter's injury.
Please, don't go to any trouble.
Um, if you say so...
What do you think about them?
Don't fight it.
It's not going to be much longer now...
Stop it!
How can you do that to my daughter?
Mom, you can't come in
here! It's embarrassing.
We're in the middle of my treatment!
T-Treatment?
Nothing facilitates recovery like the
reinvigoration of the entire system...
You've just got the wrong idea.
I would diagnose you as being
mentally drained from stress.
Um...
Like mother, like daughter.
The resemblance is extraordinary.
Now, let's see what it's like inside...
Temperature, moisture, touch...
I cannot find anything
wrong with either of you.
Let me go in deeper...
Mrs. Kinoshita, you still have
the drive of a young woman...
...but as far as wetness goes,
you're no match for your daughter.
This is an extraordinary
amount of fluid.
Oh, that's so embarrassing...
I wish I had your vibrant youth, Tomomi!
No need to sulk.
As long as a woman takes
good care of herself...
...she will only continue
to ripen with age...
In a sense, that's so much
more alluring than mere youth...
I'm tingling below my waist...
Doctor, me too...
Everything's all right.
I am your doctor and
I'll take care of you.
I'm coming...
I'm going to come!
I can't hold it in any
longer, I'm going to explode!
Physiological phenomena should
be left in Nature's hands.
Holding back would be
toxic to your system.
While I'm at it, I should take
a look at your rectal areas.
There's been a recent surge in rectal
cancer patients in this country...
Excuse me!
I guess Dr. Ishida
went out this afternoon...
Dr. Ishida...
Anybody home?
Man, I'm beat.
Had another exhausting day
tap-dancing for my boss...
Where is everyone?
Oh my God!
What the hell is going on here?
Who the hell are you?
Who's this?
He's nobody.
My loser father!
What do you mean, nobody?
Who are you calling a loser?
What kind of language is that?
I'm the head of this household!
Come on, Dad, the truth is
that you were downsized and...
...you've just been pretending
to go off to work every morning!
You didn't think we'd find out about it?
Not to mention the fact that it was
my family who paid for this house!
If you're thinking of using Tomomi's
royalties to get out of debt...
...you have another
thing coming, you loser!
I see...
If that's the case, why
don't you just get rid of him?
The two of you should spend
Tomomi's money as you please.
There are so many ways to
put it to use for society!
For instance, if you were to
make a donation to my hospital...
...you would be helping
out so many patients!
The hospital can have my money!
If it makes you happy, Doctor,
I'll donate as much as you want!
Have you lost your minds?
Hey, what are you doing?
Let me go!
Please, Doctor, examine me too!
Hurry!
Deeper, all the way!
My stomach's on fire!
It feels amazing!
I'll be winding up my examination soon...
I-I'm almost there...
Yes!
It feels too good to be
true, I'm going to die!
That word is taboo in
the presence of a doctor.
Can't help it, it's true!
Well, I suppose I can't blame
you, with a "provider" like that...
Please, take care of mine too!
I know! You should become
our provider, Doctor.
I saw what you were doing!
I knew it!
No, you've got it wrong!
Anyway, he's probably the type who
hates it when co-workers moon over him.
If he finds out about you, he'll
probably leave the hospital.
No, he wouldn't...
If you want him to stay, you're
going to have to do as I say!
Huh?
What are you doing?
No!
Now then, let me do something
ever so nice for you!
The breadwinner of
the family should be...
Big, hard and juicy...
From Shinji's Personal Chart