Please remove your top.
Y-Yes, Doctor.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Doctor...
I'd like you to examine this area, too.
I want you, Doctor...
This isn't covered by your insurance.
I-I know!
Well then, let me begin...
Doctor! Please don't look!
Dr. Shameless... Examination 1
It's embarrassing!
Show Me the Money!
Nagatsuka Hospital
Reception
We can no longer stay in
business using legitimate methods.
That's why we asked
you to come in today.
We've already heard a lot about you.
I know that most of your medical staff
left because they weren't getting paid.
Are you going to be able
to cough up my salary?
There's nothing to worry about, Doctor.
I have the money.
I've mortgaged my home...
I beg of you, Doctor!
I built this hospital from the ground
up, I've staked my entire life on it!
It's all I have.
Please, please, help me!
You're the only one I
can turn to now, Doctor...
Please!
Very well.
You've obviously hit rock-bottom.
I accept your offer.
You accept?
Thank you, Doctor!
On one condition...
Yes?
I must have absolute autonomy,
I will do things my way.
Is that clear?
Where's the Head Nurse?
The people with the highest
salaries left first, Doctor.
I see...
And you are...
Nagatsuka
I'm the Director's daughter.
My name is Honoka!
Pleased to meet you.
"Honoka?"
How do you write that?
"Moe-ru", and "Ka" for "fragrance."
The very same characters!
I remember that name from somewhere...
Doctor, please!
Don't tell me you're already
making a move on Honoka.
"I knew somebody long ago named Honoka."
You're making up
stories, aren't you?
Ms. Shirakawa, you're being
disrespectful to Dr. Ishida.
Am I, really?
Well, if you say so,
then I'm sorry, Doctor!
The Honoka I knew must be the
same age as this one by now.
Now that I think of it...
...there's something about her
that reminds me of Honoka...
No, I'm just imagining things.
This girl is the
Director's only daughter.
She can't possibly be the same person.
Doctor, what do you
think about this patient?
Higashijuujo...
That sounds familiar...
Yes, it's the Higashijuujo family
of that former conglomerate group.
Interesting...
But what is this?
It's like a who's-who
list of trivial maladies.
I don't even see anything serious
enough to warrant hospitalization.
She's a hypochondriac.
Hypochondriac?
Her parents are always
overseas on business.
I think she just wants to get their
attention, so she pretends to be sick.
Oh, I see...
You expect me to eat
this disgusting slop?
Oh, Miss Higashijuujo, how could you?
You've gone too far!
I want to eat blowfish!
And sashimi, and fried chicken!
We don't serve any of
that here and you know it!
Come on, it's not like I
have diarrhea or anything.
Why can't I eat what I want
to? I'll be happy to pay for it!
What?
But we can't...
It's against hospital policy!
What's going on?
Doctor!
Miss Higashijuujo is
being so unreasonable!
I brought her a nice, hot meal and she
wouldn't even take a bite, and then...
Are you the new doctor?
Yes, I am.
My name is Ishida.
Pleased to meet you.
A haughty little princess, eh?
I'll enjoy examining her...
Since I'm here, why don't
I take a look at you?
Nurses, leave the room.
Excuse me?
I always examine first-time
patients one-on-one...
Yes, Doctor.
All right, remove your top, please.
You're going to call my bluff now?
Wealthy patients are keepers
so I'll have to use my...
...bedside manner to
make sure she stays on.
By the time I'm through with her, she'll
know what a blessing it is to be female.
What is it?
Tell me what's wrong!
I'm afraid you might have...
I'm sorry, but you'll have to
remove the rest of your clothes.
What?
Take them off.
Why are you looking down there?
I don't have some kind
of weird disease, do I?
Shh, be quiet.
What kind of an examination is this?
I'm tired.
I'm very sorry, but you'll
have to finish up yourself.
What?
It's very important.
Unless you do as your doctor
tells you to, I can't help you.
O-Okay...
Don't stare at me like that!
I have to monitor you. I'm your doctor!
But you're embarrassing me...
That's it, you're almost there.
Very interesting...
I've studied all the latest
procedures in the U.S.
Over there, this would
be strictly routine!
But...
Now hurry up!
Come on now, hurry!
Y-Yes, doctor.
Temperature is more or less normal.
You're fine.
However, you've been holding
in your urine for some time.
In other words, you're
poisoning your system.
Now's a good time to check your
rectum as well, it's just a precaution...
This won't take long.
I'm very good at doing this.
But that's my...
Sorry...
I thought I should go ahead
and check this area too.
Are you hot?
You're perspiring profusely right here.
It's cold!
Something cold is coming inside me!
It won't be much longer now.
Doctor, please look away.
I'm so embarrassed!
Lmpossible.
I cannot diagnose you correctly unless
I have observed how you purge yourself.
But Doctor...
Don't worry about soiling the
bed, there's a sheet in place.
I can feel it coming now...
Do not restrain yourself, it's
not good for your system.
Let it all out!
Purge yourself once and for all!
Don't hold back, release it all!
You have nothing to worry about.
I am your doctor and I will
take care of you no matter what!
That was very conclusive.
I'll have the nurses take
the appropriate measures.
Really, I wonder what happened.
The exalted Miss Higashijuujo
soiling herself like that?
She was caught at a humiliating moment.
I assume she'll be more
reasonable from now on!
I suppose you're right!
By the way, I see you haven't
taken care of this patient yet.
That is quite unacceptable!
Really?
What patient was that?
Oh, I'm being summoned!
Summoned?
Well, well, look how big you are!
I'll tend to that right now...
Are you ready?
How is it?
Does that feel good?
I must say it makes me feel good to
know that you're enjoying yourself.
Wow, so much semen.
You're healthier than I thought!
Tastes weird.
I don't think I'll ever get
to like the way you taste.
But I really love this...
So hard already!
Amazing! And you haven't
been well, either!
Oh my God, that was great!
This is so amazing!
I love patients' penises,
they're so huge and hard!
They're the best!
Oh, give me a thrust
from below, will you?
Excuse me...
Oh, Doctor!
Is it time for the rounds already?
W-What the hell are you doing?
Excuse me, Doctor, I'm
occupied at the moment...
You're not an RN, are you?
RN?
What's that?
Just as I thought...
I used to be a nurse at a sex club, so
I can't answer any difficult questions!
The Director himself recruited me...
What the hell is this?
Was this woman hired for
the same purpose as myself?
Doctor, what are you mumbling about?
I'm going to beat this illness!
Because I'll never get to
feel this way again when I die!
I can see that her special nursing
skills are doing a lot more to restore...
...this patient's lust for
life than any medical treatment.
If we can help a patient
like this one to survive...
...it'll mean that much more
revenue for the hospital.
That feels so good!
You're an angel...
You're a real live angel
in a nurse's uniform!
I just came here from a sex club.
You need some fresh air,
it's for your health.
If you say so, Doctor...
You're not wearing
any underwear, are you?
No, Doctor...
We need to prevent any
excessive sweating in that area.
In addition, constrictive underwear has
been identified as a leading cause of stress.
It would be wise to avoid
wearing it as much as possible.
This is an integral part
of my medical evaluation.
Without it I cannot hope
to identify your symptoms!
Is this woman out of her mind, or what?
She's not bad-looking,
either, what a shame...
It's so plump...
Hey, look at all that
pussy-juice coming out!
What's going on over there?
How do you feel?
All that arousal must have given
you a feeling of release, no?
P-Please, hurry, put
your thing inside me!
What are you talking about?
That would not be a medical procedure.
You're so mean!
Working me up like this, you're
not going to leave me hanging!
Just stick your thing inside
me and shred me to pieces!
Miss Higashijuujo, surely you know
better than to take that tone of voice...
...when you're asking for a favor?
What's the matter?
Isn't there something you want from me?
Please, will you please stick
your big thing inside me?
Very well, then.
P-Please, I want you to insert this!
What a spoiled little girl you are.
It's inside me!
It's so hard and so big!
That feels so good, Doctor!
You seem to be a little sensitive.
Shall we try something else?
I-I can't take it
anymore, I'm going to die!
Not quite yet...
I'm tingling all over!
I'm going to melt from the inside!
Just a little bit longer.
We're almost finished...
That concludes my examination.
Miss Higashijuujo, I cannot
find anything wrong with you.
I will arrange to have
you discharged tomorrow.
No, I don't want to go home!
I'm sick, can't you see?
I won't last a day if you
don't treat me, Doctor!
I don't mean for free!
I'll just talk to my father,
he'll pay you whatever it takes!
Wait, I heard that the
hospital is about to go under.
I'll ask my father to
make a huge donation...
...just don't discharge
me, please Doctor!
All right.
If it means so much to you,
then I'll see what I can do.
Oh, I'm so happy!
Okay, open wide, now!
Miss Higashijuujo, don't
you just love the food here?
L-lt's tingling!
Isn't Dr. Ishida coming?
Dr. Ishida is very busy.
Now stop whining and eat!
Hey! No picky eaters allowed in here.
You used to be such a good
patient, Miss Higashijuujo.
Well, if you can't do as you're told...
Oh no, have you wet yourself again?
What a baby you are.
Let me make you feel better.
Feels so good...
Thanks to Higashijuujo's donation, the
hospital is out of the woods, at least.
That girl is a slave to my treatments.
But I can't go on treating just one
woman, I'll get bored sooner or later.
I'll have to find another
source of revenue soon!
People often change because
of the environment they're in.
But they also change because
they've been given an enema.
From Shinji's Personal Chart