Commence lungs, arms, and hand exercises.
Perverted Thomas
The saga of perverted thomas.
I'm getting so hot, I can't stand this.
This girl in front of me is so damn cute.
Her ass is so nice.
Just a little touch is okay.
I better not.
She might scream out that I'm a pervert, that be bad.
Alright.
Oh shit. My bag is stuck.
Just a little bit more strength here.
Oh man, she noticed something.
This is bad, I better hurry or she's going to think I'm a real pervert.
Oh shit! I really wasn't thinking about it...
This one is going to take a while.
What? That wasn't?
You'll never turn a women on that way.
Are you really serious about the way of the pervert?
The way of the pervert. I'm not into something like that!
What? Oh shit.
Old man, what are you talking about? I'm not a pervert.
Don't lie. Your quivering hand and that sweaty face of yours, are clearly those of a pervert.
Yeah, okay. I may have had some thoughts, but that was it.
Let me ask you this, when your hand was down there, did you have impure thoughts?
Yeah, a little bit, well you know I'm a man.
I rest my case.
You see, your whole body, everything about you, emanates pervert.
Really?
Yes, my years of research, tells me without a doubt, you are pervert.
What are you talking about old man. Who the hell are you?
In his forty years pursuit, I have been called The Pervert Master!
A pervert master, I've never heard of such a thing.
Watch and learn.
The first way of the pervert, the feathered touch.
Now young one, touch her breast.
No, I'm going to get caught.
Don't you worry about that. This women is in ecstasy, can't you see.
Right now her heart is immerse in this feeling.
Hurry now, touch her quickly.
Yes.
No, I'm going to cum.
She has climax.
That's amazing. How did you do that?
That was very easy.
You see, your perversion force is strong. I see you were born with a gift.
But you do not know how to use it.
You require training and discipline.
I don't think I can.
Get off at the next station with this women, everything will start from there.
All embarking passenger are required to stand behind the yellow line.
Confidence young one! Farewell!
Hmm... What a funny old guy.
Can I talk to you for a second.
You got it all wrong, it was that old man, standing right next to me.
Would you please come with me?
Idiot.
In here we can have a little bit more privacy.
I'm getting really nervous.
What should I do?
I think I'll go order something.
I'll have some orange juice.
This chick got me thinking wild things.
Why did she bring me here?
I bet she is calling the cops right now. Shit, I better not leave her alone.
Huh?
Ayami-san is not here?
Wha...What the hell is going on?!
You don't think I'm attractive?
I never said that.
It's just that this is a karaoke club.
There's all these weird people around here. They'll see what's going on.
We got to cover up and see what... oh wait...
Actually this is pretty cool.
But the Pervert Master said it will be a greater turn on.
Pervert master?
Yes, Siriama-sensei
He is called the Pervert Master.
Why don't you tell me your story, while I calm down here.
So does this calm you down?
What?!
No, I'm not calm.
How about this?
What is going on? What is happening here?
Oh, I feel it. I can't hold it.
I can feel the pervert force in you, just like the Pervert Master said.
Pervert force?
Presicely, that's what I call it after years of research.
Pervert Master said sooner or later, a man will appear, with greater pervert force.
That old man again.
You will be the one to inherit the Pervert Master position and refine the pervert force.
Inherit?
Yes, other then the Pervert Master. You are the only person
in the world with such strong pervert force.
Impossible. I don't have such talents.
Your making my body feel so hot.
What do you want me to do?
Drive me crazy with your fingers please.
Yeah.
Your that deep inside.
I'm going to cum.
You can't be the only one feeling good, I want to feel something too.
Is this good enough?
Lick the tip of my cock more.
Like this?
Yeah, now suck on it.
I'll return the favor.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum too.
Two coffee and a toasted jelly on table three.
Thank you very much.
It was just as the Pervert Master said.
The strong pervert force within you, can really melt women.
Was I really that great?
Seriously? You didn't cum though. I'm sorry.
It's okay, I was about to.
I know without a doubt, that you are the one that was chosen by god.
Chosen by god?!
Well then, lets get started with the training.
Training?
Yes.
The road to becoming a pervert master is a very difficult one.
Wait a second?!
Why do I have to lead such a difficult path?
We want you to inherit the thrown of the Pervert Master.
Huh?
I'm sorry. This just isn't something I'm interested in.
I had not known the joys of a women until I meet the Pervert Master.
One day I came across the Pervert Master's fingers.
For the first time in my life, I had an orgasm.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm sure he'll keep servicing you.
But it's no longer possible.
Why?
The Pervert Master has an incurable disease.
He only has a short while to live.
Realizeing that his future is short.
He is sacrificing his remaining time for us, in order to find a successor.
I didn't realize he was so sick.
But by us, do you mean there are others?
Yes.
There are many women who hasn't experience it.
They are all waiting for the Pervert Master fingers.
Even if you say that, I can't become like him.
I beg you! I won't give up.
You must improve your skills and grant us the joys of womanhood.
I understand.
I'll do the best I can for you.
This is the place.
This place...
I don't see anybody around.
Just be patience, a girl will be coming soon.
She will go into the bathroom, follow her inside, and then touch her.
That's crazy. She probably scream and that will be it.
You can do it, Masuo-sama.
I can't. I just can't do it.
It's all my fault.
No, its not about that.
Alright, I'll do it!
Thank you.
Here, take this.
A mirror?
I'll do this, but I feel a little odd.
If I touch her, it's more the just peeking.
If she finds me, she will scream and that will be it.
She's so cute.
To think I get to see her pee.
That pervert master guy, you know he's all right.
The first law of perversion, the prettier the girl, the more she wants it.
Now is my chance.
The second law of perversion, a pervert can operate anywhere.
Who is there?
Don't be scared.
That's wrong...
Please... Please stop.
Stay still.
S...stop.
It's so embarrassing.
Don't be embarrass, your so cute when you pee.
No, please don't look. It's embarrassing.
I saw everything, your pussy and your ass hole.
Stop. Please stop.
You shouldn't, I mean it.
Please stop.
Not there, it will turn me on.
Here's some more.
No, don't. I'm getting horny.
No, no, I'm getting horny.
Deeper. Stick it in deeper.
Yeah, don't stop.
Cumming....
Cumming, cumming.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Was it good?
Please don't embarrass me.
Thank you.
Congratulation Masuo-sama.
Who are you?
I see you on the train all the time. I'm Ayami
So you know Kasume-chan?
So your were watching me?
Watching me have an orgasm for the very first time under the Pervert Master's fingers.
But I haven't seen him for a while, so I thought I would...
That's why you went to the bathroom to play with yourself, right?
Masuo-sama, do you understand the powers of the Pervert Master now?
Well, how was it?
Tell me, how was Masuo-sama fingers?
Yes, it really turn me on, it felt like Pervert Master's fingers.
That is really great.
Please remember this, Masuo-sama is training in the ways of the pervert force, so take care of him.
Don't worry, I'll do anything for him.
Masuo-sama hasn't cum yet, so what do you say we return the favor.
Okay.
Wait, what?! You got to be kidding me.
You know this is a park, we're outside.
It might be a cold spring night, but you don't know who might show up.
Kasume-san, come join us.
Okay then. I'm not going to hold back.
Amazing!
So big, you're really big!
This is great!
Wow, this is amazing!
Amazing! This is so amazing!
Ayami-san.
Come here, lets have some fun.
Yeah! This is so wonderful!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
More, harder please.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!!
Satisfied.
It's like the whole town!
Noway!
Today's training will be difficult.
Just hang in there.
I just know your going to get past this hurdle.
Your stronger then yesterday, I'm so wet.
This escalator takes three minutes to get to the third floor.
So...
There's a girl here in the mall, awaiting your touch.
Huh.
Here she comes.
It is your task to make her cum before you reach the third floor.
She's cute.
But I really don't think I can do this in three minutes.
I know you can do it.
Or is it that you just don't believe in us?
Okay, okay.
I'll do it.
That's great. Good luck.
Okay, here goes nothing.
Oh shit!
Hang in there.
What the?
Please stop or I'm going to scream.
But your really turned on.
I'm not turned on.
This isn't working.
Remember the Pervert Master's teaching.
Check her arousal by the nape of her neck.
Okay.
I think she wants more.
Your clitoris is really hard.
Don't say those nasty things to me.
She's really wet.
This isn't working.
Oh well, all out then.
Amazing.
I'm cumming!
You can't do that here.
I feel so good.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I did it!
Congratulations!
You did it.
You past the first stage.
This means we have to celebrate.
Celebrate?
Come, lets strip!
Wait a minute!
We can't do that here!
This is a shopping mall, in the middle of the day. There are people around!