Here!
Happy Birthday!
Thanks!
How time flies!
Now, blow them out!
Here I go!
Hey, that big shot gangster is here.
It's a pretty sad state
of affairs in Hong Kong...
...when a bastard like
him becomes so important.
Oh, John Roy.
No one in Hong Kong can
stand up to his Ron Tai Group.
Say, who is he talking to?
I'm not sure, but her name
is Rei, or something like that.
I heard she's John
Roy's right-hand man.
With beauty like hers, she
must've seduced him pretty easily.
You know, she's only after his money.
I hear you.
Looks like even
cold-blooded Roy is falling for her.
Man, she's so beautiful.
Hey, don't even think
about coming on to her.
Or you'll be floating in Victoria Bay.
I know, I know.
Nobody knows anything about Rei.
Brave as an angel, sensitive as a devil.
She's that kind of woman...
Rei, why don't we split and
go somewhere, just you and me?
I'm sorry, Boss, but I can't tonight.
I see, that's too bad.
But if you have plans
already, I understand.
We'll make it some other time.
We'll make it some
other time, is that it?
That's enough!
Get lost!
Rei...
I met you for the first time in this town.
You came from
nowhere, you were just walking...
Where's the stuff?
The purest heroin, 999.
From the very moment
you appeared before me...
...I saw the perfect beauty in
you, in your eyes, in your lips.
Shit.
I can't believe this is
happening to John Roy.
No good.
W-What?
It's very well made,
what don't you like about it?
Listen, Mr. Wang, do you
know what the real one is like?
This is a joke!
I only deal with fakes that
are better than the real ones!
If you want to do business with the
Ron Tai Group, get the product right!
You hear me?
Yes, I'll get it right next time.
Hey, you!
Sung, what the fuck
were you doing to Mr. Roy?
Stop it!
But, sir...
Kid, why are you trying to kill me?
I know some people
are after me for the reward.
I don't want money, just revenge!
Revenge?
It must've been at least
two days since his death.
What's going on,
doesn't he have a family?
His father used to be a pretty
good technician, but he got into drugs.
Well, the rest is the usual story.
You guys killed my dad with drugs!
That's why my mom...
Then she got the easiest
job in Hong Kong, you know.
She must've been an addict, too.
You made her, you Ron Tai
bastards forced drugs into my mom!
That's why you're my
enemy, it's for my mom and dad!
Boss, what are you
going to do with the kid?
You may think it's
funny that I'm being so calm.
But I think he can turn out to be
useful, depending on how we train him.
Rei, he's just like I was at his
age, dirty, hungry and living for hate.
I'm the same.
No, I think you're too
young to think about a successor.
Yes, you're right.
But, I'm getting old.
It's just that there was another
boy who tried to stab me with a knife.
It was more than ten years ago.
If I didn't remember that boy,
I wouldn't have kept Sung alive.
By the way, the way you
dropped his knife was amazing.
I was just desperate to protect you.
I knew you've had some
training, but now I'm convinced...
...you're not just an able assistant...
...but a good bodyguard as well.
I want to show you something,
will you accept my invitation?
Sure, I'll accept it today.
It's a nice place.
The windows are bulletproof, to
match the lifestyle of the Ron Tai Group.
Rei, look at these.
How are they?
Beautiful!
It's just so real, maybe
better quality than the real ones.
I see, your
assessment is very accurate.
Now we can do business with them.
I started in the slums, and
finally got into the Ron Tai group.
Drugs, prostitution, counterfitting...
I did everything to gain power.
But, what is this
emptiness in my heart?
Boss, when is the next deal?
Oh, tomorrow night at
2300 Victoria Pier and...
Rei!
You're already my life, Rei, I love you!
No!
Why?
Why, Rei?
I'm sorry, Roy.
I'm still...
If you are having your period...
...I don't want to see
you until tomorrow night.
Rei!
Rei, you're either an
angel or a you're a devil!
Boss, my mouth is exhausted.
Yes, understood.
Hey, stop here.
I'm driving tonight, okay, Boss?
But...
Boss, that's not safe.
Yeah, one woman isn't enough.
Don't worry, Rei is the
strongest and closest one I have.
Rei, do we have a little time?
Thank you.
I'm sorry for bringing
you here so suddenly.
Are you a christian?
Do you believe in God?
Believe in God?
No, I just...
I just did so many things
to get into the fast lane.
That's all.
It's time.
The Japanese Mafia isn't very punctual.
You smoke, Rei?
It's not like you said...
Rei!
Rei, are you all right?
Rei, that's...
Rei.
Rei!
I did a basic dressing, but if you
move, you'll start bleeding again, Boss.
Rei?
Rei, what's going on?
Who's that?
It's me.
You?
What are you saying?
It's me dying with you.
What?
You mean you're going to kill me?
Why?
Are you helping that Sung kid?
Sung?
Yes, he pulled the trigger of my heart.
But he has nothing to do with this.
Why, then?
Do you remember
the scar on your tattoo?
What?
You are...
You killed my parents on my birthday...
...because my father, a
detective for the Hong Kong police...
...never took your bribes.
Then, it is you...
Since that day, I have been
carrying the cross of revenge.
No, it can't be true,
that was a boy, not a girl.
You are a woman, your
breasts are warm and real.
They're not fake,
I know you are a real woman!
Then, but...
It was a boy.
You are, you are...
Man and woman, and something
in-between, that is what I am.
A hermaphrodite, I understand now...
It's all about revenge.
Then why did you
protect me from Sung?
I don't know, maybe because
I've spent a long time with you...
...and wanted to kill you myself.
You'll be the first
suspect if I'm found dead.
That's why that body looks like yours.
Yes, a top ranking member of
the Ron Tai Group, John Roy...
...and his men are all
going to be killed by an enemy.
What happened, Uncle Wang?
You killed Sung, too.
Brave as an angel,
and as sensitive as a devil.
You are amazing.
Rei, are the clothes
I was wearing in this room?
Yes.
Could you get
something from my jacket pocket?
Please, take it.
I was going to leave the
organization after tonight, and be with you.
Rei, did you know that
all angels are androgynous?
You are my angel,
the fallen angel Lucifer.
Rei, as my last wish will
you take me inside of you?
It's so warm...
Thank you, Rei.
You made me feel like a human
being for the short time I've known you.
Good-bye, John Roy.
I loved you, too.
I'm happy to be
able to die with you, Rei.
I'm sorry, it's just a double.
You arranged it, just like the real thing.
I've been dealing with fakes for a
long time, I deserve to die like this.
The two bodies found at the
explosion were allegedly those of...
...John Roy of the Ron Tai
Group, and his assistant Rei Pikwa.
John Roy supposedly had
connections with organized crime.
All of his associates
were also found dead.
The police are still
investigating his background, but so far...
Hello?
Congratulations, I
suppose your game is finished now.
That's very impressive,
and it makes me proud of you.
It was perfect.
Now, will you join my game?
And if I say no?
The evidence of your double
will be reported to the police.
Well, that won't happen, will it?
That's right.
I sent you a gift, it
should be at your door by now.
Test it well and get used to it.
Your code name is Chimera.
It suits you very well, don't you think?
The chimera is a
creature from Greek mythology...
...with the head of a lion, the
body of a goat, and the tail of a snake.
It is a creature with
complex mix in one body.
However, there is
one chimera that is bigger.
Hong Kong was created
from the shadows of history.
A city of chaos with
the essence of the East...
...and the West is the
biggest chimera man ever made.
You will rule the world
of shadow in this city...
...as a reborn chimera with a lost past.
Let's start the new game!
Your first target is the
master of the Rose Garden.
Well, it's getting fun just now.
I'll wake you up.
Who are you?
A new woman?
You came back to me.
I'm so happy.
Please, wait!
Where are you?
Please, don't leave me alone again.
Please.
It's you.
Thank you, you really did come back.
This silencer sucks!
It jammed!
Did we get her?
Be careful.
You depend on guns too much.
I see that you're a real professional.
You name?
Why do you ask?
I want to take it with
me to the River Styx.
It won't help you.
I know.
I'm losing my strength.
What's that sound?
Is it raining again?
What is this serene, calm feeling?
This is a feeling I haven't had for years.
Rain?
No, this is...
This is...
Are you awake?
Don't move too quickly.
Are you surprised?
My brother found you
unconscious and half-dead.
How long have I been sleeping?
For three days.
I was so worried that
you wouldn't wake up again.
My name is Yung.
My brother is Ron.
I'm Rei.
Hi, Brother!
When did he...
Rei, let me
introduce you to my brother.
This is my brother Ron.
He told me that you took care of me.
Thank you.
You can stay with us
until your wounds have healed.
Then, Rei is going to
be with us for a while!
Brother, did you have dinner yet?
It's ready, so let's all eat together.
Sorry, Yung, I have to go out again.
I just dropped by to check on you guys.
I'll be home pretty late.
Don't forget to brush
your teeth before bed.
He's always like that,
he still treats me like a kid.
Don't be so upset, Yung,
I'll eat in place of your brother.
Really?
Thank you, it was delicious.
What's wrong, Yung?
You're very pretty,
you look like my mom.
Your mother?
Yeah, but she died when I was a baby.
I don't remember my dad,
I was raised by my brother.
Do you want to see my mom's picture?
Yes.
She's so beautiful,
she's a lot prettier than I am.
Oh, yeah?
That's the only picture of my mom.
But, you're a lot younger than my mom!
Oh, is that a compliment?
Is this your dad?
I don't know, my brother won't tell me.
Really...
You can walk already?
It wasn't a big deal.
Also, your treatment was very good.
Did you bring a doctor here?
No, the bullet went clean through,
and I know these things pretty well.
I feel sorry for Yung,
but I should be going.
If I stay here too long, it will
bring you and Yung some trouble.
You didn't say anything...
...but you saw my body, didn't you?
Yeah.
Not surprised?
I'm used to seeing strange things.
Are you a woman or a man?
That's a mystery to me, too.
I'm giving this back to you.
There's some extra
space in the recoil spring.
You should take care of it.
Who are you?
We're in the same business.
I happen to have a restaurant also.
Yung doesn't know
about my side business.
I won't ever tell him about it.
I saved you knowing what you do.
Relax and get some rest now.
Good night.
Damn good...
Your gun may be in perfect condition,
but your technique is almost olympic.
It's thanks to you
that I've almost recovered.
This is a pretty good shooting range.
I'm a freelancer, I need to have
this kind of facility to train myself.
Otherwise, I can't
survive in this business.
It's such a competitive business.
You always wear sunglasses.
I don't like to have my eyes seen.
You have...
...nice eyes.
Where are you from
and where are you going?
I don't know, but...
But?
It's my fate, I just follow it.
Oh?
It's a different chain, is this Yung's?
It must be Ron's.
Did you remember?
As you already know,
this is a soundproof room.
In here, nobody will interrupt us.
Now you know that Yung and I are
the sons of the Rose Garden's master.
My old man was sane
when this picture was taken.
He was a high ranking
member of the organization.
But he was a good family
man to me, Yung, and my mother.
I had already started my career
as a hit man for the organization.
But Yung was just a kid
and knew nothing about it.
But when my old man went nuts...
...the organization gave him
drugs and women to shut him up.
Then Rose Garden turned into a dead
mansion, filled with insanity and lust.
I knew he deserved
to be killed someday.
But, I should have
been the one to do it!
Do you know why he went crazy?
Since my mother died,
since she was gone forever...
Since then, my old man
wasn't the same person.
Please, don't leave me alone again...
I understand now.
I left the organization
and raised Yung by myself.
You understand?
How hard it is to be free from
any group and keep your business?
I have two questions.
We aren't strangers, ask anything.
Why did you cut the
family photo Yung has?
He doesn't need any
memories of his father.
I am his brother and his father.
If you wanted revenge,
why did you save me?
What's the point of taking
revenge on a half-dead body?
Why did you sleep with me?
I thought it was just two questions.
Let me introduce you to Chiney.
She is a survivor
from the Rose Garden.
Her brain is fried from drugs...
...but she can entertain
both men and women, you know.
Let her entertain you for a while.
You have a little bit, enjoy your playtime.
You will finish this whole
thing by pulling the trigger.
Say, Brother...
Did Rei really leave us?
Yes, she recovered from her wounds...
...and must have her
own problems to deal with.
Did she say she
would come here again?
What's her phone number?
She didn't say anything and I
didn't ask, I have to go to work now.
Yung, it's time for school.
I know.
How could you leave us like that?
You're awful, Rei.
Oh, did you come already?
Well, I didn't.
You can't just enjoy yourself,
you've got to make me feel good, too.
That's great!
Amazing, how did you do that?
The hunter is becoming the hunter.
How is she keeping up that energy?
I envy you.
I wish I had a body like yours.
We're going to do it again and again!
You're going to have to
take me to heaven again!
Shit, why?
You bastard, you have both
and you can enjoy it either way!
I can't stand it!
You pay for it!
You don't have to
envy anybody now.
That's it!
I wanted to keep you
alive for a little longer, but...
Don't move!
What's in your left hand?
It's hers, I was going to put it on.
I can't move smoothly if I don't wear it.
You're a guy, you
should know what I mean.
You're very cautious
despite the fact you're going to die.
You won't give up untill the last minute.
Brother!
Brother, what have you done to Rei?
Get out, Yung, it's
none of your business.
None of my business?
What's going on, Ron?
I'm not a little kid anymore!
I even know what your real job is!
So, since when have you known?
I always thought
something was going on.
And when you brought Rei
to our house, I was convinced.
A professional hit man doesn't
need a family, it just gets in the way.
Shut up!
Listen, Yung, I'll tell
you why I'm going to kill her!
She killed our father!
Please, no, Ron!
What a waste!
You knew what was going
to happen and trapped the gun?
You've only been
pretending to be fooled?
That's a Chimera.
You are a quite a
woman, no, not a woman.
But not a man, either.
You are a devil.
Now kill me.
I wasn't ordered to kill you.
I was just trying to protect myself.
You're such a professional.
Rei!
Did you really kill my dad?
If so, if so, please
don't kill anybody anymore!
Good bye...
Yes?
It's been awhile, I'll tell
you the next target.
I am Rei, she-male sniper.
My code name is Chimera.