No...
No, Kyohei.
Somebody will hear us.
It's more exciting that way, isn't it?
Well, I guess, but...
Are you feeling hot?
He'll hear you.
Beat Angel Escalayer
A tiny little thing can
make me happy everyday.
I am scared that I might
not have it tomorrow.
First love is forever.
Is it okay to dream that
my wish will come true?
When your finger touches my heart...
...my heart beats faster.
Escalation!
I can feel hot energy in my body.
To protect the green planet,
my heart beats stronger.
I awaken the power to defeat evil.
I can be stronger,
to protect someone I love.
I will hold the sword
of courage, I love you.
Episode Two: Assassin from Dielast
How did it go?
To be honest, it was not impressive.
This isn't working either?
What will make her excited, then?
So far, she's gained
enough to transform once...
...and she would probably only
last 5 minutes after that.
Will she be okay with
only that much energy?
I highly doubt it.
Shit! What're we gonna do?
We're in trouble.
It's coming straight for us!
What's going on?
Sayuka, there's enough energy
for you to transform, at least.
Sayuka...
I'll do it!
Kyohei, please get out of here.
Okay, good luck!
Fluxplosion!
Beat Change!
I'm here to protect the green
earth, and my heartbeats...
This little wind isn't going to beat me!
Did I defeat it?
Sayuka!
What is this?
My suit is melting!
What? Can't you see she's in danger?
This is dangerous situation.
Those secretions have already forced
her suit to function at 60% capacity.
I can see that!
Is there any way out?
I don't know, since there is
no more Doki-Doki energy left.
This feels sticky and gross...
But why is this making me feel hot?
Oh no, Kyohei's semen is draining.
Don't look at me, Kyohei.
No, I can't stand anymore.
The Doki-Doki Energy is being charged.
Really? Is she getting turned on?
Yes!
Charging complete.
How come she could get off
with that monster and not me?
You should be analyzing what
just happened to her right now...
...you may want to give
her orders to follow.
All right!
Sayuka! Can you hear me? Wake up!
Kyohei!!
You have enough energy.
Let's finish up!
Is that you Kyohei?
Sublimate Escalation.
You know, it's been a very long
time since I saw her bomb so hard.
It was at great cost, but we
managed to get the remaining data.
The key is that kid, isn't it?
So all I have to do
is hold him off, right?
That's right! As long as
you don't let the DDD work...
...our own Escalayer will be
superior to theirs in all aspects.
I'll be counting on you.
Why are you hesitating?
You know you're using your own
womanhood, right?
Are you mad?
Ms. Combat commander...
Okay, I'll see you then.
Sayuka's friend told me that...
..I'm not qualified
to be her boyfriend.
I see...
She said that I'm not capable
of making her feel excited.
Kyohei, calm down.
How about some tea?
She's just playing with me.
But what does that have to
do with my sexual techniques?
Ow! Hot!
Oh, silly.
I have to get this stain
out. Besides, it's hot.
Don't get so stressed out.
You are just a little tired.
You'll feel better soon.
Kyohei!
Do you want to feel good?
Miss Ryoko!
Kyohei, it's emergency.
Dielast has appeared.
He doesn't answer?
I think that perhaps he has
turned off the communicator.
It must be me.
We shouldn't be doing this, Kyohei.
I-I'm sorry!
M-Miss Ryoko!
Don't be sorry, Kyohei.
Do you know I was waiting
for this moment to come?
Don't make me say it!
Kyohei...
You've never been with
a real woman, have you?
Are you excited?
It has nothing to do with you.
That pervert is the one at fault.
But, I was the one who
embarrassed him, though.
Don't worry, I will try to turn
on the communicator manually.
Please.
Do you feel good? Kyohei.
Close your eyes...
...and feel me.
No, I don't get any response.
Can we go and fight without him?
There is enough energy for
you to transform, however...
Don't worry, I can do it!
Fluxplosion!
Beat Change!
Did you know that this is a
sensitive spot, even on a man?
I want you to cross your
hands behind your head.
If you try to get
loose, I will punish you.
O-Okay...
Good boy...
Miss Ryoko, W-What are you doing?
Sometimes you should do things
that your partner doesn't expect.
You are getting hot, aren't you?
Look at you...
Why are there so many Fu-Men?
Escalayer!
Today is your last day!
Sayuka, I'm reading a
high energy response.
Please watch out!
M-Madoka!
Miss Ryoko, I'm almost...
No.
You can't come yet...
Well, okay, I will let you come once.
Ow...
Madoka?
Madoka!
Madoka! Are you all right?
I need two hours to recover myself.
Madoka!
Is that all?
It's hard to believe
I'm made from your cells.
My cells...
You're a clone?
We have the same power?
Not quiet.
I am superior to you in all aspects.
But...
Something's missing from my heart.
The Doki-doki Dynamo...
That's the only thing I'm missing.
You can open your eyes.
I'm sorry...
No, don't apologize.
It tastes good.
Can you feel my heart beating?
Women can feel good
without sexual intercourse.
Don't rush, I will clean you up first.
The wall of Idea.
Madoka, I'm sorry.
Kyo!
Your pussy is so beautiful, Ryoko.
Please, use your finger...
Not yet.
If we take it slowly, the
pleasure will be double.
You're mean!
Please touch me deep in my pussy.
Oh, good
I want it.
I want your penis.
I want this.
Now you know.
I like the look.
It will be my sincere pleasure
to beat someone like you.
What's this?
You will open your body for me...
...I know you will.
Kyohei! Kyohei!
Miss Ryoko...
Don't come yet, Kyohei.
Please, do it harder!
Good! Good.
Miss Ryoko.
Tell me. Tell me you love me.
Well, if you beg me,
I will be nice to you.
I would never!
I wonder how long you can keep that
up.
Good! It's so good!
Kyohei, I can't hold it any longer!
Give it to me harder! Harder!
Are you getting horny yet?
No!
You're stubborn...
...but...
No!
Don't stop...
No, I mean...
You want it, don't you?
No!
For your reward...
It's deep inside me!
Please give me.
Do you want this?
Then you must beg me.
Please put it inside of me.
Call it a "shining black penis."
Please put your shining black penis...
Say "please screw me hard with it."
P-Please screw me hard with the...
...great shining black
thing, put it inside of me.
I can't wait any longer!
You're so naughty!
Now spread your legs!
Your asshole is so beautiful.
You've never let a penis in
your ass before, have you?
No, don't put it in there!
Is it that good?
No...
Why does it feel so good?
No!
Even pain can be pleasure, right?
And I can do this until you break.
Forgive me!
Great!
I can feel your pussy sucking my dick.
I'm coming!
This is my mercy!
You can die in utmost
pleasure! Escalayer!
Now, I will be...