According to legend,
once every 3000 years...
...the Overfiend is reborn
into this world to...
...unify the human, demon
and beast realms...
...and build an
eternal kingdom.
Amano Jyaku, a beast,
has come to the...
...human realm in search
of the legendary Overfiend.
His prime candidate
is Tatsuo Nagumo...
...a seemingly ordinary
college student.
Meanwhile, Suikakujyu,
of the demon realm...
...a realm opposed
to that of the beasts...
...fears the rebirth
of the Overfiend...
...and sent his minions
to attack Nagumo.
As if moved by Fate, Nagumo
approached Akemi lto...
...the idol of the school,
and fell in love with her.
Niki, a classmate of Nagumo's,
also fell in love with her...
...and sold his soul to a
demon to transform himself...
...into a powerful monster
to destroy Nagumo.
But when Nagumo was attacked.
A "power" awakened within him...
...changing him into the "Overfiend"
and causing him to murder Niki.
While observing the ugly scene,
Amano Jyaku began to wonder...
...if Nagumo was in fact
the true Overfiend...
...and what the promised
"eternal kingdom" would be like.
In response to his request,
the Elder of the beast realm...
...has sent Amano Jyaku into
the future to seek the truth.
Where am I?
What's all this? Is this the
human world of the future?
It can't be!
Where'd that senile
old bastard send me?
I see. So this is Osaka?
Now what?
The Overfiend?
Save us!
Save us, Lady lto!
Lady lto?
Help me!
Please, help me!
For pity's sake!
Take me to
Lady lto at the castle!
Are you talking
about Akemi?
What?!
Why's he doing this?
What the...?!
It's Osaka Castle.
Why isn't it damaged?
That's it! The secret of the
Overfiend legend is in there!
More time, Elder!
I'm almost through!
Come on, you old fart!
Elder!
The secret to the whole
legend is in there! Please!
Just a little more time!
There's something here!
Let me see!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Overfiend
Part 3
"Final Inferno"
I beg the Gods
not to forsake him...
Return Suikakujyu
to life and to me.
I beg you all,
now and forever.
Protect him! Revive him!
Let him live again!
O deities of all the realms...
return my love to me.
Suikakujyu, my love...
I lack the strength
to be reborn...
Fukakuki... Enkakuki...
Give me your bodies...
Suikakujyu...
My Queen...
Suikakujyu, something is
happening in the human world.
The demon realm will be
destroyed if it isn't stopped.
Hurry... You must kill
the Overfiend now!
You're my only hope...
By your command.
Nagumo!
Nagumo...
As long as I'm with you,
Akemi... I'll protect you.
I'll protect you...
You will protect me,
won't you, Nagumo?
Of course...
Nagumo...
I... I'm a monster...
Nagumo?
Nagumo, it's me.
Go away.
I'm not human
anymore. Please...
Nagumo, open up.
No.
It was a lie,
wasn't it?
That stuff about always
being there for me.
I love you, Nagumo...
I don't care what's
happened to you...
I just know I love you!
Akemi...
Nagumo...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't let me go!
Never let me go again!
Fantastic...
What'll we do now?
Let 'em have fun.
You've returned?
Elder!
I'm done for. I've used
the last of my power.
What're you saying?!
Hang on, you old fool!
Amano Jyaku!
I saw the future
through your eyes.
Then tell me: Was that really
the future of the 3 realms?
Elder!
Amano Jyaku...
The only thing I can say is
the eternal kingdom...
...the Overfiend will build
may be very different...
...from the demon, beast and
human worlds as they exist now.
What?
You're beautiful, Akemi.
Why...
Why are you crying?
I'm happy.
We'll be joined forever now,
body and soul.
And no one will ever
stand between us again.
Never...
No one will
ever separate us.
I'll never let anyone
do that... Akemi!
Nagumo...!
May I?
Nagumo!
L- l-
Oh god, I...!
I can't...!
Please...!
Not so hard...
Nagumo...
He's changing...
Nagumo!
The 3 realms
are collapsing!
ELDER!!!
Run!
It's the Overfiend!
Horrible...!
This is the Overfiend?
The god above all others?
He's an enemy!
The devil! KILL HIM!!
No! You'll die!
Megumi!
Big brother!
Boss!
Look! He's just
killing at random.
Is that all he was born
to do? Big brother?!
Nagumo...
Why...? Why?!
What the...?
That chant... No...! He's trying
the same thing he did 70 years ago!
Amano Jyaku! It's too late!
I, Suikakujyu, control
the Demon King of the Sea!
This will finally
destroy the Overfiend!
What the...?
What's he trying to do?
NO!
Amano Jyaku!
It's time you
faced the truth.
Suikakujyu...
Amano Jyaku... The 3 realms
will never be as they were.
This is what the
Overfiend really is.
A devil, bent on destroying the
human, beast, and demon worlds.
But... there's still time.
Kill him!
He's still weak
from the battle.
Use this chance
to destroy him.
Now that the Demon King
of the Sea is dead...
Our only hope is you,
Amano Jyaku...
I beg you!
He will destroy every...
Nagumo... Have I wandered
for 300 years just for this?!
Just to find a
bastard like you?
Big brother...
Boss! You gotta
kill him, quick!
Nagumo! Even me?!
Nagumo!
Change back!
Stop being the
Overfiend! Nagumo!
Boss!
Kuroko!
Why are you hesitating?
This isn't like you!
KUROKO!
MEGUMI!
Nagumo! Why are you
doing this to me?
Nagumo! Nagumo...
Stop it! Nagumo...
Nagumo! Damn you!
I'll never forgive you!
Give me back Kuroko!
Give me back my sister!
Amano Jyaku...
Akemi, why...? What are you
doing here?! Akemi!
It's no use
calling her name.
Mama no longer
has human feelings.
Mama?
Yes. I'm speaking to
you from her body.
What?
Then... you're...
Yes. I am the child of
Nagumo and Akemi.
The true Overfiend
you've been looking for.
The true Overfiend?!
Then what's Nagumo...?
What the hell is he?
Merely a male,
necessary to give me life.
And now he's become
the Demon of Destruction...
...who must destroy the 3 realms
so that I may be reborn!
Demon of Destruction?!
Papa is destroying all the
worlds for my sake.
Why?
Because it was decided
3000 years ago.
3000 years ago?
Yes. 3000 years ago,
so as to bring order to chaos...
I created the human
world you know today...
At the same time I made
two other worlds:
A world of man-beasts,
for the superhuman...
And of demons, for those
who could not become human.
Thus were born the
beast and demon realms.
And, at that time,
I made a promise...
In 3000 years,
I shall be reborn.
If I find that humans are "good,"
then all will be as planned.
But, if I find that
they have become "evil..."
...I shall reduce the worlds to
void and begin again!
That's the real legend
of the Overfiend?!
Humanity hasn't
become what I intended.
So now I have to start over.
The humans must be destroyed
so that I can replace them.
What?!
You're saying you'll
destroy the 3 realms...
...just so you
can be reborn?
DAMN YOU!!!!
Amano Jyaku...
Amano Jyaku,
don't be foolish...
There's nothing I
can do to stop this?
Nagumo, stop it!
I like the world
the way it is...
Nagumo!
I thought I'd erased all
of Mama's consciousness.
How can she be...
A-ma-no...
Amano!
Amano... It's all right.
Take it easy...
Akemi...?
Amano.
I'll help you. Come on.
Get out of here... Hurry!
Akemi...!
Megumi!
Big brother...
Megumi... you're...
Nagumo...
You still know me,
don't you?
With all your power,
you can easily kill me.
End my life now,
while I still love you.
What're they...?
I don't want the Overfiend
to control me.
I won't live as a tool.
I won't!
If you kill me,
the Overfiend will die, too.
And you, Nagumo.
Nagumo, let's choose
to die together. Together...
A... ke... mi...
Nagumo...
Nagumo!
KILL ME NOW!
Mama... Papa... You can't.
This is our destiny.
NO!!!
Amano Jyaku,
this is as it must be.
Mama cannot die before
she gives birth to me.
And Papa cannot die before
he's destroyed the 3 realms.
Stop it! Change them
back to themselves!
Stop it...
Overfiend, please...
Do not grieve,
Amano Jyaku.
When I create the new
worlds, centuries from now...
...they will be reborn,
as they appear now.
You will?
Do you mean that?!
I do. And they'll love
each other, as in this life.
All destruction leads to rebirth.
This a beginning, not an end.
Can you live to see the
new world, Amano Jyaku?
So that's it?
Sure, I'll live.
A hundred years,
a thousand...
I'll just keep on wandering
until I see the future...
Yours,
Nagumo's, Akemi's...
And until I do...
I WILL NOT DIE!!!
O arrogant humanity!
Not all that exists is
visible to your mortal eyes!
Our world consists
of the realm of humans...
...the realm of beasts,
and the realm of demons.
There is a legend shared by
the beasts and the demons.
That once, every 3000 years,
the Overfiend revives.
And upon his revival,
the three realms are...
...united to form
an eternal kingdom.
O arrogant humanity!
Humans are not the
supreme rulers of all.
You shall know the truth
when the Overfiend revives.