O arrogant humanity!
Not all that exists is
visible to your mortal eyes!
Our world consists
of the realm of humans...
...the realm of man-beasts,
and the realm of demons.
And many of the demons
live in the human world.
There is a legend
among the demons.
That once, every 3000 years,
the Overfiend revives.
And upon his revival,
the three realms are...
...united to form
an eternal kingdom.
O arrogant humanity!
Heed well the voices of those
of the demon realm.
Humans are not the
supreme rulers of all.
You shall know the truth
when the Overfiend revives.
And the promised time
is close at hand!
300 years since Amano Jyaku
went into the human world.
And not one word
of him since.
But I smell it...
Yes, I can smell it!
It can only be the stench
of the Overfiend!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Overfiend
Part One
"Birth of the Overfiend"
"Myojin University"
So he's the one...
He's got the moves, and that
smell that drives women wild.
Cut it out!
I've gotta change!
- I was only kidding.
- What are you doing?
Holy...
Hi!
- How's it going?
- Not bad.
It's Akemi!
Better give
it me all today.
Akemi...
Who's there?
Oh shit!
"Boys keep out!"
Anyone in here?!
Anybody there?
I don't see anyone.
Weird...
I'll bet someone was.
Go, Myojin!
Definitely not him.
Oh, yes...
I'm coming again!
That was great,
Ozaki!
Forget it. But men, someone's
defiling our hallowed gym!
Him!
What an idiot!
Hey man,
sorry I lost control.
I'm okay, Ozaki.
What part of Akemi
were you looking at?
All swollen,
aren't you?
Well, I, uhh...
Not just swollen...
I'll use my magic
charm to heal you.
See you later, Boner!
Thanks...
Oh god..."Boner!"
Goddam Ozaki!
How humiliating!
Miss Togami.
She doesn't look too happy.
Akemi!
Come in.
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder what she
wants Akemi for.
You wanted to
speak with me...?
It's very important.
I'm in a bit of a jam.
I'm looking for something,
and I need your strength...
No, your body.
What are you
looking for?
Well now...
It's the most wonderful
thing for us, as women.
Understand?
- No...
- You don't?
Then I'll show you.
Wha...
What are you doing?!
I haven't seen it yet,
but it's very near.
Don't you want
to see it, too?
Stop it!
Stop it, please...!
Akemi!
I think you'd better
watch a little longer.
You're that new transfer
student, Ama... Ama...
Amano.
It's a pleasure.
Look at 'em go!
You can see
behind the curtain?
I'll give you pleasures
beyond this realm!
What the...?
I can't take this!
I'm going in!
Don't!
Someone's watching?!
I wondered who...
Just some little shit!
And you're a miserable
excuse for a monster!
Little shit
with a big mouth!
You came all the way
from the demon realm...
But you just couldn't resist
a little pussy, could you?
You're no human!
At least I'm not
a fuckin' monster.
You little...!
Who are you?
You don't know me?
You really ARE a loser!
You're Amano Jyaku, the
half-breed of the beast realm!
You're after him too, right?
But you'll never get him!
Satisfied?
WELL DON'T BE!
I'll tell you, as a favor.
It's Ozaki!
Later!
What a day...
Boss!
It's been too long!
You come by
yourself, Kuroko?
Hi, big brother!
You too, Megumi?
Nagumo...
You saved me!
Oh, thank you!
Bottom of the 8th.
How will Yamaki play it?
The third pitch, and...
A hit! Going long!!
Going, going... gone!
So Megumi, do you know
who the Overfiend is?
- Sure!
- Really?
Since you bring it up,
what do YOU think?
Come on.
The Overfiend, who's been
sleeping for 3000 years?
Maybe he doesn't exist.
Cut the shit.
You've found him, right?
Hell yes! My nose's
extra-sensitive.
Better than yours.
Then let's bet on who
the real Overfiend is.
Suit yourself.
Good! If I win, we both go
back to the demon realm.
He's gotta
be the Overfiend...
That bullshit this afternoon'll
bring more demons here...
God dammit! Some guys
get all the luck!
What a horny bastard!
There you go. Enjoy.
Thanks a lot.
Here.
I'm not hungry.
Sorry.
Then I'll eat both.
It didn't happen!
Miss Togami turning
into that monster...
And what it did to me.
It didn't happen, right?
Say it wasn't real!
It wasn't!
Come on, it was your
imagination or something.
Thank you.
Let's sit down.
Look, Akemi...
I've liked you for
a long time now!
The smell... The smell!
I'm sure of it!
It's that guy, all right.
Don't be embarrassed.
I'm glad you told me.
Great.
But I'm still afraid
it'll happen again...
Even if it was
just my imagination.
As long as I'm with you,
Akemi... I'll protect you.
You will protect me,
won't you, Nagumo?
Of course.
Ozaki...
Ozaki... Please...
You're different tonight,
Ozaki. A lot stronger.
I...!! Oh god!
What's going on?
What's happening?
My body...
What's wrong with me?!
So you're
the Overfiend, eh?
He's the Overfiend,
all right.
But how do I
make him manifest?
Here he comes.
Now we'll get a good look.
Boss, he ate
him so easily!
What the...!
I don't get it!
There he goes!
I finally found you!
Those punks were nothing.
Try me on for size!
It's the Overfiend,
all right!
I've found you!
At last, I've found you!
The hell...?
What's happening?!
No... It can't be!
Shit! And I really thought
he was the one!
Boss, he must've taken the blood
or semen of the real
Overfiend.
That's why he had the
Overfiend's power.
Blood or semen...
Blood? You said BLOOD?
Holy...
That guy's the Overfiend?
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
Don't look...
Who are you?
You don't remember,
after last night?
What?!
I've never...!
You jerk!
Akemi!
You're the Overfiend,
aren't you?
Take your real form, quick!
I've been waiting a long time
to get screwed by you!
Hey... Cut it out!
What's her problem?
Maybe I should
take her up on it...
No...
He's too far gone.
The EEG's flat.
The heartbeat has stopped.
"In Surgery"
We did all we could...
I didn't think
he could die.
Guess he wasn't
the Overfiend, either.
There IS no Overfiend!
Let's go back to
the demon realm.
What the...!
I sense a demon!
What's wrong?!
It's so strong...! I've never
felt anything this strong!
Stop it...!
After 3000 years rest,
I awaken!
No! Stop it!
My first in 3000 years!
How very, very sweet...
Oh man,
I'd better tell the boss!
Boss! I saw him!
Nagumo IS the Overfiend!
What?!
- I'll check this out!
- Wait for me!
I'll stay here.
Help me...!
Megumi!
Well Megumi...
I guess you won the bet...