The readings are showing that
Bio-Body has been repaired to 100%...
...and the brain wave have
recovered up to 70%.
Begin degeneration process.
Sayuka.
What are we going to do now?
Madoka.
What is it?
Is there any chance to win at all?
There is one...
Really?
Hey, Madoka?
Just forget it. It is
beyond her capabilities.
Let's take her back to her normal life.
Dr. Arc!
FM77! What do you think you are
doing?
I've been waiting for you.
What?
Misllene, she got the Doki-Doki
Dynamo. Ah...
Stop your mumbling, old man!
Stop it!
I thought you'd be happy.
With the Doki-Doki Dynamo,
I will be absolutely perfect.
What's wrong with me
using that for my gain?
C'mon now, commander, Misllene!
Why don't you start making me feel
hot?
You!
You want to fight?
That's fine, but you'll never beat me!
Let's find out!
Beat Angel Escalayer
A tiny little thing can
make me happy everyday.
I am scared that I might
not have it tomorrow.
First love is forever.
Is it okay to dream that
my wish will come true?
When your finger touches my heart...
...my heart beats faster.
Escalation!
I can feel hot energy in my body.
To protect the green planet,
my heart beats stronger.
I awaken the power to defeat evil.
I can be stronger,
to protect someone I love.
I will hold the sword
of courage, I love you.
Episode Three: Counter-Attack
I guess it is the time for this...
There is a Beta version
of Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Beta version? So, it's a trial product?
Even though it is the Beta version,
there is not a big difference...
...when compared to the master
version of the Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Actually, the Beta version
exceeds the master one.
Then...
However, the Beta version
does has a crucial problem.
Once.
You can only charge
the Beta version once.
The advantage is that we can pull out
higher energy from the Beta version.
However, due to the higher energy...
...it is possible for the body to
melt if we do charge it twice due to the...
...current limitations
in Bio-Body technology.
And one more thing...
There's more?
The Beta version is a
very unstable product.
If the charging fails,
the Beta can go very wrong.
Conversely, it can diminish by itself...
...and take Sayuka as
well as the Bio-body.
Diminish?
We won't be able to use
it if it's that dangerous.
It's going to be fine.
Sayuka?
Sayuka!
Are you okay? You shouldn't be up.
Thank you for worrying about me.
But, I think I am okay now.
Madoka, if you have a minute, can
you put the Beta version on me?
Sayuka, were you listening to us?
But I...
It's gonna be all right, because
we are experts in Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Right? Kyo?
What's this? This doesn't
feel as good as I expected.
Your pussy's gotten a little loose.
Since your pussy is useless...
...why don't you use your mouth
and make me feel good, huh?
There...
Hurry up!
Oh yeah, I'm getting hot.
That's right. Suck it harder!
That's it! Keep doing that and make
my pussy feel good with your hand too.
That's good.
You're doing good.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
More! Harder!
Harder!
That is the Beta version.
Sayuka, are you sure you wanna do
this?
Well... how do you
want to charge it next?
How do you like to do it, Kyo?
Do you really know how serious this is?
Kyohei?
Sayuka, aren't you scared?
If this fails...
It's not like you,
getting worried like that.
I know I have nothing to
worry about with you, Kyo.
But I...
Kyo?
I'm...
I don't want to do this!
I'm scared! I can't do this!
Sayuka?
Of course...
I'm terrified too, Kyo...
...and I've never been afraid to fight.
I am going to dispose of this.
Sayuka?
You'll help me, right? Madoka?
I-I'm sorry, are you all right...?
Miss Ryoko!
Warm-up your feelings by
watching me masturbate, Sayuka.
Are you watching me?
Miss Ryoko.
Um, did something happen to you?
I'm tired that's all...
I've realized how useless I was...
I've been trying my best for him.
I've been trying so hard
to fulfill his dream...
I thought there's a person
who will finally make me happy.
I felt like I could do anything! I felt like I
could overcome anything, but...
But I don't think I can do it anymore.
I'm not sure if I can
even smile for him anymore.
Kyo, you can do it.
Let's try hard, okay?
I know I can do it with you, Kyo!
Kyo!
Sayuka.
That's not true!
You aren't useless, Ryoko!
I can't explain it, I
know that's not true!
The Ryoko that I know
is beautiful and kind...
has a wonderful smile, and is sexy...
And also you smell really nice, and...
...I don't quite know
how to say this, but...
That was for encouraging me.
Thank you, Kyohei.
Sorry to have worried
you, but I'm fine now.
I'm glad to hear that!
Well, I have to get going.
I have to go see her...
See you later.
Sayuka, are you watching me?
I feel so hot.
I shouldn't be losing
myself like this, but...
Madoka.
Sayuka!
Kyo?
Sayuka...
I'm sorry that I couldn't
understand your feelings...
...but I finally know.
And I am not running
away, I'll stay with you.
I wanted to ask you if you'd
let me fight together again!
Kyo!
Kyo, Kyo...
There is no way I'll
let you fight alone.
I might not be much help yet,
but I'm going to try really hard.
Let's fight together.
I'm really sorry.
No, don't be sorry.
Don't push yourself too hard, Madoka.
Don't worry. I should be
able to buy you some time.
Hopefully you can charge the
Dynamo while I distract it.
Don't worry, we're going to charge it!
I am counting on the two of you.
I should get going. I must
protect civilians from the attack.
Kyo, the Dynamo is stabilized.
Sayuka, I have something
I want to tell you.
Actually, I wrote you a letter
the day before you moved out.
"I wanted to be with you forever...
...and I didn't want us to be apart."
But I didn't have the
courage to give it to you.
Kyo, that's so sweet.
I regretted it all night.
I kept asking myself why
I didn't give it to you.
But this time, you gave me the courage.
I want to be with you, forever and ever.
Kyo...
Kyo!
I want to be with you too, Kyo.
I'm so happy!
Kiss me.
Yes.
Kyo...
Sayuka!
K-Kyo!
Something is burning
inside me! It's hot!
My heart is beating so fast...
I'm scared!
I'm scared, Kyo!
Kyo!
It's hot!
It's so hot!
Don't worry, I'm here.
I won't go anywhere, I'll
stay with you, forever...
There's still something
important that I want to tell you...
...so, hang in there!
Kyo!
Sayuka!
Well, well...
Is that all you got? This is so boring
I'm not too surprised, since
Escalayer was also trash.
Escalayer is not trash!
Is that right?
I know who you are...
You're Escalayer's
assistant robot, aren't you?
That's why I won't kill you just
yet, I'm going to enjoy it slowly.
Your pussy also looks like
a real one, doesn't it?
Well, what about this one?
So you can feel this one too?
How do you like it?
You seem to enjoy it.
I'll make you feel even better...
Enjoy it slowly.
Now, I'll move it...
Stop!
How do you like it? Huh?
You're going to tear my butt up!
You're nothing but a robot...
But the party has just started
What was that?
Escalayer? But how?
I took the Doki-Doki Dynamo out...
I don't care. Now I can have more fun...
You made it, I'm so glad!
Yes, so please don't worry.
Please be careful, I think she's
equipped with the Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Okay.
I'm so sorry, but I'm going to
have to get into recovery mode...
I'm counting on you, Sayuka.
The empire of evil, Dielast! I
won't let you do whatever you want!
To protect the green earth,
my heartbeats reach the sky.
Escalayer!
I am here to put an
end to your evil ways!
Let's fight, then!
I won't lose.
How do you feel about getting blown
away by your own Doki-Doki Dynamo?
It doesn't work for me.
Well, it's my turn now!
You bitch!
What is this power?
Why?
Why? I should be more powerful
with the Doki-Doki Dynamo...
This heartbeat is not
just a mere energy source.
You don't understand what the
real meaning of a heartbeat is!
What the hell are you talking about?
I'll finish you!
We'll see about that.
Escalayer, I'm going to blast this
cannon, and turn you into dust.
You're history!
Beat End!
Escalation!
Sayuka!
Kyo, I did it.
I did it!
You did, Sayuka!
Kyo!
Please do it, Kyo...
What do you want me to do, Escalayer?
Here! I want you to touch here.
You have to tell me exactly where
you want me to touch, Escalayer!
Please, don't be mean, Kyo...
I want you to touch me here...
You're like a baby, Sayuka.
Kyo! It feels good!
Give it to me harder!
Give it to me deeper!
Your nipples are already hard.
Don't say that!
Not there.
You don't like it? Then, I'll stop it.
Don't stop, I want
you to do it harder...
Harder! Harder!
Good, Sayuka.
I'm going to come!
Not too impressive.
As far as I can see, I don't see a
bright future ahead of the two of you...
...in terms of a
long-term relationship.
You're joking, right?
I'm absolutely serious.
There will be more fights
against Dielast in the future.
The Doki-Doki Dynamo will be
a waste if you don't do better.
I think it would be better if
I join and help you two for now.
I think I'm already excited...
Now Kyohei, Sayuka is ready for you
now.
Come, Kyo.
Oh, yeah!
Kyohei, not me!
You're supposed to do Sayuka!
Does it matter? We're all here naked.
But...
...it feels good...
That's not fair!
Now my turn!
Come, Kyo!
I'm coming!
Dielast is on its way!
Kyo! Hurry up!