It was our first reunion.
How are you doing?
Are you getting hot?
I think your body is
more honest than mine is.
Don't say that. You're so mean!
Sayuka Koenji
What the hell is that?
No, don't stop doing it.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my god!
What is he doing?
Beat Angel Escalayer
A tiny little thing can
make me happy everyday.
I am scared that I might
not have it tomorrow.
First love is forever.
Is it okay to dream that
my wish will come true?
When your finger touches my heart...
...my heart beats faster.
Escalation!
I can feel hot energy in my body.
To protect the green planet,
my heart beats stronger.
I awaken the power to defeat evil.
I can be stronger,
to protect someone I love.
I will hold the sword
of courage, I love you.
Episode One: Doki Doki
Dynamo, Charge Complete!
What is that?
It was 9:04 AM...
That's right!
Sayuka, you're home.
I'm home.
S-Sayuka?
Is she back in town?
Oh, this is so great!
Is that really Sayuka?
Sayuka, can I talk to you for a minute?
What is it?
We are going to charge
the Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Is that all right with you?
Oh, okay.
Please sit down and make
yourself comfortable.
Excuse me, may I?
How are you feeling?
Are you starting to feel good?
If you don't answer me, I'll do this...
No...
Not there.
You can't just get off now.
Remember, you must be very excited.
It's easy for you to say, but...
Sayuka...
Sayuka, finally you are mine alone.
Madoka.
Ah, no.
No, Madoka, I can't do this with a girl!
It didn't work, did it?
No...
Do you think we're in a slump?
It seems that I cannot
satisfy you anymore.
That's why we need your
help, Mr. Kyohei Yanase.
Would you please do it?
M-Me?
Oh, hi, Sayuka. It's been a long time!
Do I know you?
It's me, Kyohei Yanase.
You used to call me Kyo.
L-I don't know you.
I guess I have to
explain everything to you.
Okay, so Sayuka's lost her
memory and become Escalayer...
...and what about that
Doki-Doki something?
The Doki-Doki Dynamo.
And you're saying you
want me to help charge it?
Yes.
Escalayer is the only person who
can prevent the invasion of Dielast.
However, charging the Doki-Doki
Dynamo, which is our energy source...
...has been getting difficult recently.
So you're saying that the feeling
of excitement is the energy source?
Of course, you become used
to stimulation after a while.
We don't have many choices left.
However...
...when she saw me, her
excitement level went up?
That's right.
I did some research
and checked your record.
After analyzing your body
and the way you treat girls...
...there is no one as perfect as you.
Then, you want me to sleep with
Sayuka?
That's right!
Give me a break!
Kyohei Yanase...
Am I going to have sex with him?
Sayuka.
No, what am I thinking?
But, doing such a thing here...
...it might not be so bad...
Do you wanna have sex with me that
much?
What are you talking about?
Wait, was I thinking out loud?
You were speaking out
loud, we heard you.
Anyway, forget it, I'm
not going to do this.
All right then, I will have to reveal
your secrets to your closest friends.
You know. The truth.
So tell me, what exactly
do you have in your hand?
This is the love letter that
you wrote to Sayuka 10 years ago.
It's not fair!
Oh, Kyohei. I'm really sorry
that I put you in this situation.
Do you really want
to have sex like this?
I wish we could start
over from the beginning...
...go on a date at an amusement park...
...and kiss each other
during the sunset.
Sayuka...
Um, it tickles...
You know, you're going
to feel hot very soon.
Aren't you always doing
this by yourself anyway?
No, please...
You really don't want to do this?
You better say something if
you don't want to do this.
Please, don't stop...
You are wearing cute panties.
Did you change for this?
No, I didn't...
You put them on for this, didn't you?
No, I didn't, but...
But, what?
You were waiting for this, huh?
You are a naughty girl, Sayuka.
You're wet.
That's not true! I
am not a naughty girl.
Ah, no.
Come on, spread your legs.
No, it's embarrassing.
Come on!
No.
I'm putting it in, so relax.
I'm scared, but...
The Doki-Doki Dynamo
has been fully charged.
Kyohei, please stop right away.
What are you talking about?
I can't stop now!
We have enough energy for today.
Thank you very much for your help.
Wait a second!
What am I supposed
to do with my dick?
I understand. I will help
discharge your semen then.
I can't believe Getten was defeated.
Now Escalayer has been
set as our top priority.
Yes...
What about the analysis
of the Doki-Doki Dynamo?
Oh, we still lack data.
Well, how about attacking
Escalayer and collecting the data?
I need to gather our followers.
Would you please follow the
instructions on this paper?
Let's see...
We'll go to the Merry-Go-Round,
Haunted House...
...and Ferris Wheel at night?
Yes. And can you hold
onto this for me, please?
Oh, you will be watching us, right?
Of course.
Oh, here she comes.
Please remember to keep smiling at her.
Sorry, I'm late!
Kyohei, you're not having fun?
Of course I am.
Why don't we go ride on that?
All right!
Dielast Monster: Joy-Frust
Are you scared?
N-No, I'm not.
I know you're lying. You are shaking.
I'm fine. I'm really fine.
Actually I'm scared to death, but if I
let him put his arms on my shoulders...
No! Stop!
There is no way that Madoka
will interrupt us here!
No, I don't want to think about it.
Hey, what are you doing there?
Oh, wait for me!
What's the matter?
I'm so scared...
What's that?
It's here.
This is supposed to be the last
spot, but we don't have any more time.
Please charge the Doki-Doki
Diynamo right here!
Wait, what do you mean?
Hey, wait...
Gosh, I don't understand this.
I am sorry I forced you to have sex
with me and to have a date with me...
Don't worry.
By the way, Sayuka...
Yes?
Suck it.
W-What?
Weren't you paying attention
to what she was saying?
We'll be dead if you don't
become a Escalayer and fight!
B-But...
Come on! Stop whining!
Y-Yes.
Lick around it.
Use your tongue.
That's right.
Okay, good.
Now, take off your clothes.
Let me help you.
Come on, show me your breasts.
Your nipples are really
hard, aren't they?
Are you already getting hot?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Yes. I am feeling good...
No...
You're wet, Sayuka.
N-No, I'm not...
Raise your legs up.
See? It's all wet.
No, don't lick there!
It's twitching.
Don't say that.
Please stop...
You don't like this?
Do you want me to stop?
No, you're mean!
I do like it.
Okay, you're a good girl.
Let me give you a reward.
Even though this isn't the
right place to have sex...
...but we have to do
it, to save the earth.
Thank you, Kyo.
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
To protect the green earth,
my heartbeats reach the sky.
I am Escalayer, here to beat the evil!
As long as I'm here, I
won't let anyone harm...
...this precious beautiful green earth!
What are you laughing at?
Sayuka, when the two heads attack
you...
...and the main body pauses,
please attack those heads!
Subliminal Escalation!
Dr. Arc isn't capable of making
anything good, it's all junk.
We failed to get the data, huh?
Not true, we did get something.
Dr. Arc, can we use FM77?
FM77?
That is still in preparation!
He means, we're just making
some minor adjustments to it.
Well, okay. I will
get it ready right away.
How is she?
She looked extremely tired to me, I
think she already decided to go to bed.
Okay.
Hey, robot girl, can
I ask you something?
My name is Madoka.
What is it?
She doesn't remember anything, right?
No.
But, when we were having
sex, she called me "Kyo."
What do you think it means?
I can't really say anything
about that right now.
But there could be some side effects
after charging the Doki-Doki Dynamo.
Her memory will come back if I
stimulate her, don't you think?
That's what I'm afraid
of... but it's only a guess.
Okay.
Now, the relationship between
Kyohei and me has begun.
But since I didn't know anything, I was
only thinking about our relationship.
But I understand that...
...being an Escalayer is the
only way to be with Kyohei.