You did good.
Shall we get going then?
Oh, my God...
I'm going to cum!
Darling?
My reward...
I want it.
No...
Honey... No...!
I can't take it anymore!
No more, please!
Oh no!
Mother?
That's right.
Isn't she beautiful?
I will always cherish
my memories of her.
If this is what you do with your wife,
she'll leave you.
But maybe you do worse things?
You mean like whips and candles?
That sounds good.
Let's do it next time.
You devil!
How's your mom?
Fine.
I see.
And take care of your wife too.
I'm a man!
God damn!
Hikaru! There's no time left!
I know that, Panira!
First we'll have to do
something about this guy.
Hey! Hikaru!
Quit fooling around
and help me out here!
No!
Shut up, and just wait a second!
Hikaru! Now!
Hikaru!
Hikaru! Hikaru!
Are you all right?!
Hikaru!
I told you I'll protect you!
How dare you take me
for granted like that.
Don't be crazy, Hikaru!
You'll die!
Not yet!
No!
Hurry! Get me out of here!
You know what, you should
watch out for yourself a little more.
Stop picking on me...
- Welcome back, Panira!
- Glad to be back, big sister.
- Can you get me out of here?
- I sure will. Right away.
Stop right there, Panira!
I got in a lot of trouble
because of this idiot.
- Just leave her there for now.
- But...
I know!
How about some punishment?
Don't be thinking of
any nasty thoughts now.
This is nothing compared to
what you do normally.
- But you can't do this!
- Panira?!
Come on, do it now!
Wait, Panira. Wait...
Oh, Pamera. I'm sorry.
Ahh, how I'd love to
get back to earth.
I'm so sorry for
what we've put you through.
Well, at least it's not as boring
as being back on earth.
What are you talking about?
I said one day I'm going to
use my own body and soul...
and screw your brains out.
I think Hikaru likes you,
big sister.
That's nice. It'll be my turn
to tie him up this time.
Ma-kun hasn't come home yet.
Is that right?
Can I wait for him here?
Ah... sure.
- You must be his tutor.
- Yes.
I hear his grades have gotten better
because of you.
I'm sure he'll get into
a better graduate school than me.
But I'd like you to go
a little easier on him.
It just means he has
less time to play with me.
I was wondering
if I can ask you something?
Well, uh...
That's right.
He's just so cute.
But, you know that,
since you're an old friend of his.
Are you really
going out with him?
That's right.
And the two of us
have a lot of fun together.
You know, not only is he cute...
but he's absolutely
terrifiic in bed as well.
It's amazing.
I know things about him
that you can't even imagine.
No, please don't.
You only want to do it
with Ma-kun?
But I like you too.
- No.
- So, tell me. Are you a nympho?
- No, I'm not.
- Are you sure?
Now you know
what we do all the time.
So, how about it, tutor?
Wouldn't you like to
join our little group?
Ma-kun, Ma-kun...
Well, I'll see you next time,
Ma-kun.
See ya later.
Until then,
I'll make her a plaything for you.
Let's just say
it's a homework assignment from me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, are you leaving already?
Yes, I mustn't disturb
their studies any more.