Today, I will marry.
For my country's security...
CITY OF SIN
I shall marry our neighboring
country's king.
CITY OF SIN
You look lovely, Lady Beatriche.
You look magnificent!!
Faye, Adel. Thank you for
everything you have done for me.
Please look after my father,
mother and my younger sister.
I can't believe...
the princess' family isn't allowed
to attend her finest moment.
Regret, fear and anxiety
are upon me...
but my heart is beating with joy.
I shall soon learn the
joys of being a woman.
What kind of man will the
king of this country be?
Has the bride finished
her preparations?
What a beautiful woman
to look upon!
This is terribly rude!
Who are you? How dare you come into
the bride's room without knocking!
You both have served your duty well.
W-what are you...?
Please stop!
No...
Lady Beatriché.
L-Lady Bea...
No! Don't cum in me!
Please pull out!
Save us, Lady Beatriché...
Rape is legal in this country.
We are lacking warriors
from long years of war.
We are in need of strong warriors...
for me to rule over the entire land!
Then... Y-you must be...
Yes. I am Franchesco Chench,
the King of this country!
Your two servants shall remain
here with you in Balgogne...
to give birth to many strong warriors.
This is...!
The grinding of raw flesh...
The conjoining of bodily fluids...
The sound that echoes
through your body...
The overwhelming smell...
I had no idea sex between a
woman and a man was so intense.
What... what mighty soldiers!
This is to be my...
No. He is the ruler of a nation.
There must be something that...
What loud cheers!
The people must love
Lord Franchesco!
Those are the fools who preached
love and sought to keep their chastity!
It is a crime in this country for
a woman not to be pregnant.
Criminals shall be severely punished.
This is my law.
Today is a celebration.
The people are ecstatic.
We shall begin the
wedding ceremony!
W-what are you doing?
No... Noooo!
It's beautiful!
Lord Franchesco!
What are you going to do?
Here...
B-but!
It appears that you
are already wet.
Was the sight you just
saw that exciting for you?
She has sprayed her holy water
at the people! How splendid!
Take this in your mouth.
Come... You must open you mouth
more or else it will not fit.
Now... suck it!
What modestly small and
soft lips you have!
It's warm, yet hot and its
water flows like a fountain!
Princess, you must not
spill even a drop.
You mustn't! It is tradition
to swallow every last drop.
We shall continue with the
Ceremony of Seed Implantation!
Please, no more.
Let us solemnly proceed.
This is to prove your
virginity to the people...
and to implant my seed
for a future heir.
This is wrong!
This is completely different from
what mother taught me...
about the wedding night!
Princess... The people are eagerly
awaiting the coming of a new era.
It's so big! It's too big! It's larger
and more vigorous than before.
This... this is too intense!
It's so big and hard! It's so hot!
Proof she is a virgin!
She is a true virgin.
I am glad I do not have to
behead you like my fifteenth wife.
Your silky, white smooth skin...
Your nipples are as beautiful as roses.
You are of true royalty!
It's going to tear!
If you keep doing that
it's going to rip!
Please, no more!
Does it still hurt?
Yes...
It feels so good...
They are already savoring
the joys of being a woman.
It's so hard and hot!
I want more.
Give me more!
I want you to cum in me lots!!
Ignore the gazes of the
on lookers and say it.
Like them...
Princess, you shall praise me!
It's wonderful.
It's amazing! It's so big...
Lord Franchesco, your dick is so...
More... I want more! Give it to me!
My people! This is
the beginning of a new era!!
Lord Franchesco!
Cum! Cum in me!!
Beatriché, take it!
You shall take my seed!!
It's hot!
I feel like I'm going to turn into ashes...
Not only was I was not able to save
my servants who were being raped but...
I revealed my perverted
self to the people.
God is angered!
Stay as is!
You must keep praying.
What should I do?
You must pray.
Then thou shall be saved.
This is a message from God.
Get on all fours.
You mustn't turn around!
I shall now cleanse you!
What is the meaning of this!?
The scent of a virgin
still remains within you.
You shall accept the messenger of
God in your small, innocent universe!
You are?
No!
Please stop!
How magnificent!
Your Highness, I shall release...
I shall release a purifying remedy
within you as the messenger of God!
No...
Stop.
Your Highness.
No!
Don't come near me!
Forgive me!
No! Let go of me!
Your Highness...
How tragic.
Thank you, I'm calm now.
Please forgive my insolence.
Now, if I may have your pardon...
I shall not forget that there are
warriors like you in this country.
Your Highness. No matter what,
please do not despair.
I understand.
You have saved me.
Thank you very much.
Your Highness.
Yes?
We shall change this country.
Our comrades are yet too
few for a revolution, but...
Revolution?
The one who spread much, deceptive
information throughout the land...
that caused many wars was Franchesco.
If this continues, the entire continent
shall fall under Balgogne's twisted rule.
Before the night is over I shall
head to your country, Arleon.
Why is that?
The King, Franchesco is
planning to take over Arleon.
What did you say!?
It is reliable information.
The truth is, your political marriage
with him was only for his amusement.
Your Highness. Please retain yourself.
We shall stop this even
if it costs us our lives!
What is your name?
Please hurry.
You must return to the
castle before it gets light.
Please tell me your name.
Eric.
I am not worthy.
Eric. I no longer possess my
virtue, but will you accept a kiss?
I would be honored.
I shall pray for your safety.
Nooo!
Please, stop this! I beg you!
Please don't do this, Lord Franchesco!
He is a criminal who
had planned a revolt!
He shall set an example!
I beg you! Spare him. Please spare his life!
If you prefer soldiers that much, I
shall let you have as many as you want!
I can't anymore...
Forgive me...
More... Give me more. Cum on me!
My mighty...
My powerful warriors assail
me over and over.
Soon their red eyes and white juices
shall cover the entire continent.
Foolish people.
Look at me and cum
as much as you like...
Though your seeds won't
reach your queen!!
Raise the army!
My country was
mercilessly conquered.
My mother and younger
sister were taken hostage.
Sister!
I am the Queen of Balgogne,
Beatriché Chench.
This is your Welcoming Ceremony.
Mother...
You have always been
young and beautiful.
I have always envied your beauty.
What are you saying Beatriché?
Dear sister, Kathleen.
I have always hated you.
Sister?
If you were never born everyone
would have loved only me!
Am I wrong?
Please be at ease. As Queen,
I shall assure you both of your lives.
Welcome, Queen of Arleon,
Vanessa and Princess Kathleen.
Beatriché.
Sister!
What are you doing!? Stop!
Mother!
Queen Vanessa!
Franchesco! I will not
forgive such treatment!
Being in the arms of such
a strong man, you are powerless.
Princess Kathleen.
My penis is filled with my seed.
Bring your lips and
give me a blessing kiss.
Modest Kathleen,
make noise and suck my dick.
Serves you right.
This is for sacrificing me.
Fall into despair.
Fall into despair!
Bring forth the female hostages.
Mother...
Lord Franchesco!
Queen Vanessa!
Lord Franchesco. I want it!
I want your fat cock.
Hurry. Lord Franchesco.
I want it! Beatriché wants it!
Lord Franchesco?
Lord Franchesco, why?