This is a free, fan-created translation. If you have paid money for this release, you are an idiot.
This fansub is dedicated to Osamu Tezuka, Mushi Productions, and all the early pioneers of anime.
Subtitles by Animerama Archival Society
Cleopatra
-=Fansubber's Notes=-
Though this film was subtitled and released in the US in the early 70s,
No copies of that version are known to exist.
After extensive searching, the only translation to be found is a subtitle track on a Chinese bootleg DVD.
This appears to be a machine- translation from the Chinese version,
Which itself may have been a machine-translation from Japanese.
The result, as you would expect, is unintelligible gibberish.
This translation has been made with no knowledge of either the Japanese or Chinese languages.
Instead, the Engrish subtitles from the Chinese DVD have been used as a guide,
Along with multiple viewings, both with and without subtitles,
To create a plausible translation.
As such, this is not a word-accurate translation by any standard.
Though it is probably closer to the original than, for instance, the English dub of Voltron.
Every attempt has been made to convey the original story as we assume it was intended.
Though some artistic liberties have been taken to ensure the story makes some sort of fucking sense.
As much sense as is possible, considering the original content.
Frankly, this film is pretty much batshit-crazy in any language.
Enjoy the show.
Am I late?
No, you're just in time, Mary.
Lets go.
What do you plan to do?
You'll see what I intend to do.
The real Mary arrived five minutes ago.
Please sit and enjoy your meal.
We have prepared the best French food and champagne.
Caviar, Egg Crepes, Escargot
The Champagne is a 1559 from the Dulan district of Tuer.
A toast to good luck.
Please let me explain
about the «imposter» Mary.
She was a spy for the Pasateli.
I should have known.
Pasateli?
Is that the star system the Long March troops want to seize?
The Pasateli are the original residents of that star system.
They don't welcome visitors from Earth.  In fact they hate Earthlings.
We delayed our project because of this.
The mantra of the Pasateli is
«Dekesu manto»
In earth language, it translates to «Cleopatra plan»
Cleopatra plan?
Yes, it doesn't make sense to me either.
What does their scheme have to do with Cleopatra?
To solve this riddle,
we have to go to the time of Cleopatra to investigate.
We have to go back in time in that machine?
This is a very strange plan.
Is your machine reliable?
Very reliable.
It is the latest technology.
It can be used to send a person to the past or the future.
But we do not send the body.
Instead we send the spirit into someone in the past.
It is much safer this way.
We could be sent into the body of Kennedy or Napoleon?
Or Beethoven or Rasputin?
Will we be able to come back?
Yes, maybe.
The machine has only just been completed.  It is still being tested.
If it brakes, you may not be able to come back.
Whose body will I be sent into?
Gucilang
You are slave of Julius Caesar
Oh, a slave?
Hahaha! That is very suitable.
Mary will be a pharaoh.
You will go into body of a princess of Egypt.
Haluwei, you will be Luba
Luba?  Who is he?
He is, um... very close to Cleopatra.
Close to Cleopatra?
Wonderful!  Close enough to get some action I wonder?
You can bring us both drinks.
I hope you will you will enjoy being our slave.
Wait, I am not ready to go!
If this works properly, it is just your soul that will go.
If your spirit doesn't arrive there, you will certainly die.
But with good luck, you will survive the trip.
Oh, this really is like gambling.
You can be brought back if you don't die.
Well then, I will await your return.  Good Luck.
We the emissaries of Alexandria
Long live Caesar, grand general and emperor of Rome!
Wait! That is my daughter!
What good luck! I have finally found a girl who interests me.
Caesar...
Bo..Bo..Botinis
Give me some wine.
King Fudolaim, please calm down.
Caesar will pay you a visit soon.
I know.
Caesar has arrived!
I am here to inspect these lands.
He's finished.
Who are you?
I am, I am the king!
King?
King.
I am Caesar.
From now on, I will be staying here.
I'm sorry if I have frightened you.
This town now belongs to me.
This girl will be my translator to communicate with the locals.
I expect you to show her respect.
What's that noise?
Aiduo, do you hear it?
Troops have come!
Well done.
Please forgive me.
I am used to getting my way.
Do you understand?
Thank you.
Tell the leader...
Miss,
Tell your father,
It is important to follow Caesar
Those who oppose me shall die.
Send out my proclamation!
Do you hear me?
What is it?
Caesar is only a man.
And as the saying goes, «Brawn will fall to beauty.»
Now we can use beauty to kill him.
No
What?
No woman is strong enough.
Caesar is too tough to die.
Then we will use a woman who will soften him up with sex.
Caesar will never fall for it.
Then use a virgin.
I'll do it.
Libia!
You will die.
Heng, don't be silly.
Caesar won't love your daughter.
Apollo Duolia!
If I try my best...
A great mind is not enough.
Use your head!
You are no good for the task.
Why?
Caesar is a powerful man,
So it is not easy for him to love a common woman.
You should use a famous prostitute with much skill.
A flawless body and the face of an angel.
She must be someone special.
Where will we find someone like that?
I already have.
Then let's see
She is on the other side of this door.
Who is she?
Cleopatra.
Cleopatra?
Cleopatra, come in here.
I know this woman!
She is the sister of King Fudolaim.
Yes, her brother is the king.
What does he want her to do?
Sleep with us!
I have no respect for my brother.
I hate any man who yields to Caesar.
As long as Egypt is occupied by invaders,
it is every person's duty to resist.
I swear my life for this country!
Don't just talk,
do something.
Let me show you the strength of an angry cunt.
Here, I will show you.
What?
Forgive me!
Cleopatra,
do you think you can beat Caesar
ten times before the moon rises,
and ten times after?
Severe?
Don't you feel sorry for Caesar?
You're crazy.
What are you saying?
Her face...
Asshole!
Cleopatra is the best in the world!
And she will be beautiful after tonight.
Look out!
The Romans are here.
We've been found out.
Go through the cave.  Quickly.
Libia
Please convey the message,
the resistance troops have all been killed.
It is up to Cleopatra now.
Yes.
Mary Fuailuo,
You will go into a princess of Egypt.
Apollo Duolia?
What is it Cleopatra?
Can a face really be changed?
I am worried.
It can be changed if a woman truly has the will, and some magical assistance.
Your beauty will go down in history.
For Egypt, you must make up your mind Cleopatra.
Apollo Duolia will always be with you.
I will give you strength.
Stop, it tickles.
What is that?
The base of a temple.
We're headed the right way.
Look, it's Luba.
We will be arriving soon.
Luba will guide us from here.
Luba
Show us the way.
There.
There is someone here who knows the magic we need.
Who has come?
Are you prepared?
Why are you shivering?
Oh, it will not be painful.
Not Painful.
This body-changing procedure is over five thousand years old.
What shall we change your face into?
Hey you!  Scram!
The dead should not inconvenience the living.
Just lay down here please and we will get started.
Hmmm, which face should I choose?
If your nose was just a little higher, it could change history.
OK then,
Lets do it.
We need to make your skin soft and smooth.
Drink this.
It won't taste good, but beauty is never easy.
Drink it down in one gulp.
Perfect, now the real work begins.
Make the breasts large and womanly.  Just like my mother's.
A slim waist and wide hips.
The legs look pretty good already.
She's so beautiful!
Cleopatra, with that face you will conquer the world!
I am only how you have made me.
All natural flowers eventually fade away.
But your artificial beauty will endure forever.
Luba, how do I look?
You don't like it?
Please be honest with me.
Haluwei, you will be someone close to Cleopatra.
Luba.  Luba.
Bad cat!
Cleopatra, you must prepare yourself.
Maybe it is a little too narrow...
Is it uncomfortable?
A little bit.
Deal with it.
Easy for you to say!
Old woman, this is the House of Caesar.  State your
business.
I have come to bring clothes for Caesar.
OK, give them to me.
No, I must deliver them in person.
I said give them to me!
Ali, what is the problem?
Bring it here.
I feel you are not who you seem.
I despise dirty clothes.  They must be washed immediately.
Luckily I already have the cauldron boiling for washing.
Throw them in.
Put the clothes in to wash and then you may leave.
What is the matter?
They are my clothes, so I may wash them if I wish.
What's wrong,
Apollo Duolia?
You are very predictable.
Whatever your plan, it will never succeed.
Enough already.  Put it there.
I know you and Cleopatra have sworn to fight the Roman occupation.
I know everything.
Speaking of Cleopatra, how is she these days?
I came to Egypt knowing my presence would anger her.
What do you think of the situation?
The little king is weak,
And Cleopatra has openly defied her brother.
These are all interesting events.
I will deal with these clothes later.
You may leave.
Do not trouble me again.
Now I am bored.
The smell of a woman,
comes from such a small bag.
Sweet zombie jesus!
Is that Cleopatra?
You are more beautiful than I imagined.
I have been hoping we would meet.
What will you do with me?
Most people think I am simply a tool of the Roman military.
But the fact it
I am not simply a general or a conqueror.
I am only a man who needs something beautiful.
Egypt is beautiful...
You should visit Rome
You would see things far more beautiful than Egypt
But they cannot compete with you.
Any city without Cleopatra is a slum.
Then Rome is a slum.
To fight with someone so beautiful
I don't have the strength.
Cleopatra,
I don't want to fight with you.
You make me horny as hell when I see you.
I am too old for this.
Caesar is Rome's greatest general.
You can have any woman you desire.
How can I believe someone like you?
Caesar, May I ask you a question?
Are you really just a man?
Certainly I am only human, and a human who has been conquered by love.
Let me prove it to you.
You have lost your mind.
Only the brightest light from a diamond can blind you.
Nothing else can be compared to that.
One thing can.
I am searching for something better than diamonds.
What is it?
You, the jewel of Egypt.
How is the princess?
It seems she is addressing an important speech.
Did she kill Caesar?
It's Caesar
He still lives.
I believe
Egypt is the most beautiful land the gods ever created.
I have been thinking about my past failures.
This country does not belong to Rome.
Egypt should belong to the people of Egypt!
Caesar really is wonderful.
I'm his biggest fan!
That throne is Caesar's
And the one beside it is for me.
I would like to introduce the new ruler of Egypt:
Queen Cleopatra
For the people of Egypt, an Egyptian queen.
Cleopatra
Caesar
Caesar controls all of Egypt.
Cleopatra has betrayed us.
Yes.
Look, Apollo Duolia is with them.
Why does she have that mischievous look on her face?
Can we trust her?
Yes.
Think about it.
She must have a clever plan.
Pour that poison into the water.
Anyone who gets his water from the river, like Caesar,
Will be in for a nasty surprise!
Will they die?
Well, they might shit themselves to death.
Then Egypt will be liberated.
Someone is in here.
Just a minute.
Occupied.
Someone is in here.
Open up for Caesar!
Go away.
You highness,
I have a report.
Whisper it to me.
Our warships are under attack.
What?!
Mary...
Are you awake?
Please wake up.
Mary?
I am not Mary.
I am Libia.
You are a slave?
Yes.
Roman?
I escaped from one of Caesar's warships.
The battle continues.
You are lucky to have escaped.
You should lie down.
Poor thing.
Why have you come to me?
It must have been fate.
It wasn't.
I don't believe in fate.
Where do you live?
I was born and raised right here.
Perhaps you were here before you were born.
Before birth?
There is an old saying« »Before the birth of the body, there was the spirit»
Libia
Yes?
It is nice to meet you.
What do you plan to do next?
Escape.
Soldiers!
It's up to you.
Once more, in slow motion.
Are you one of Caesar's spies?
No.
Then why did you break into my camp?
I have no idea.
I'll give you one more chance!
I am just a slave.
Bullshit!
If you will not tell the truth, we will punish your girlfriend.
How do you like that?
Three minutes each,
Until she is split two!
I am strong.
It will take more than a few hundred men to break me.
Wait a minute.
Is that medicine?
What if it is?
I think I can help you out.
Let the woman go.
That's not fair!
Shut up!
Go away.
We've been waiting for this!
What am I supposed to do
with these blue balls?
Out with it.
I am a chemist for Caesar.
I can make a poison for you.
What sort of poison can you make?
Tell me what it can do.
Poison that can turn a man to dust.
Liar!
Whether you believe it or not, it is true.
OK, do it.
Give me access to those jars and I will make it right now.
If you cannot do as you claim, I will kill you.
Can you really make it?
I have no idea.
Nice plan.
I don't know why, but I have a feeling I can do this.
But something in my heart tells me I can do this.
I hope this works.
Is it done?
Just a minute.
I am almost finished.
What is that?
The torch.
OK
It is ready?
Make the woman drink it.
If she doesn't, I'll make you both drink.
No, this is not for drinking.
Then how does it work?
Like this!
Is it magic?
I will kill you!
I don't think I'll make a very good ghost.
Botinis!
You are...
You are some kind of demon!
Kill him!
King Fudolaim has drowned.
Why is that a problem?
I don't know.
We found these two in the remains of his camp.
He looks like one of our slaves.
What were you doing there?
How did Fudolaim die?
He was killed by an army.
Shut your mouth!
Lying whore!
The man is a fine physical specimen.
I think I'll let him live.
Officers, check the record of runaway slaves.
If he is a slave, I have something better in mind for him.
What should we do with the woman?
She's a sweet piece of ass.
Does this piece of ass belong to you?
It appears so.
Well, now it belongs to me.
Move out!
Yes Sir!
Now is the perfect time.
Caesar loves you.  You must get him to drink this.
Even he is made of iron, it will kill him within 3 seconds.
You are shivering, Cleopatra.
How can you be so weak?
You must be both strong and courageous for your country.
Apollo Duolia will make you strong.
Has Caesar returned?
Caesar!
I have been waiting for you to come back.
I worry every time you leave that I will never see you again.
My travels leave me tired and sore.
I want to have a bath.
How about a steam bath?
A steam bath, Roman style.
Oh Caesar!
Oh Caesar!  No!  Don't do that!
No Caesar
We can't do that here.
Someone might see us.
I'm begging you to stop.
Caesar!
Water!  Give me water!
Quickly, water water.
I'm saved.
His condition is the result of an illness he has had since he was very young.
It comes and goes from time to time.
The symptoms are varied and sometimes bizarre.
If a nerve is pinched the wrong way, he can have a severe reaction.
That is to say,
it could come on at any time without warning.
Caesar will likely spend his whole life with these problems.
Is there any cure?
The cure is to drink poison.
A strong poison for a strong disease.
For a man with this condition, poison is medicine.
Get away from me!
Oh, you were trying to help me.
You want me to escape?
Thank you.  I will give you a reward.
Bye bye, lovely little leopard.
I need some lemon.
Bring me a lemon, quickly!
Lemons for her highness.
Put it there.
Leave the room!  All of you!
Am I knocked up with Caesar's Child?
What should I do?
Give birth to Caesar's heir?
Or end it?
OK, stop now.
I find your skill very interesting.
Yaonius,
Be my warrior and fight for me.
And win.
What?
That gladiator made this.
How does it work?
Well, Yaonius?
I've never seen this before.
I don't know how to use it.
There is something suspicious about that man.
Don't be a dick.
Give it a try.
That's an order.
Try it.
What is the problem?
Hurry up.
My apologies,
it's Cleopatra.
What is wrong with Cleopatra?
She has given birth to a son.
Apollo Duolia.
Caesar is coming.
Yes.
Use this.
Must I kill him now?
This is the best time to kill Caesar.
No, I can't do it.
This is for your country!
Have you forgotten your mission?
If you do not succeed, we will all fail.
OK, keep that in mind.
Wait here.
You look thinner than the last time I saw you.
And you seem to be in a good mood.
Dad, meet your son.
He looks like you.
Pick him up.
I shouldn't.
Of course you should!
You are his father.
Well if I must, then I must.
Good boy!  Good boy!
Cleopatra, my child is looking at me!
You never know how beautiful a child is until you are a father.
This child is perfect.
Son, you will go on a tour soon.
You will go with your mother to Rome.
To Rome?
Yes, to Rome.
Oh, I've just thought of the perfect name.
How about Leo Caesar
Our little Leo Caesar.
Leo Caesar.
Oh, what is that?
They say motherhood changes a woman, but that is too much.
You do not need to worry about such things.
I love you more than anything in the world.
I would never let anybody hurt you.
Good night.
How is he?
How is the child?
Where is Cleopatra?
Can you imagine a woman
Who gave birth to both a baby and a dagger?
Be more careful.
A failure.
That was a perfect opportunity.
He said he would bring us to Rome.
Yes, he will go back after he finalizes the defeat of Egypt.
But he loves me.
You are shameless.
How can you love an invader?
That man has seized your heart and made you lose your will.
But you will kill Caesar in Rome.
I have prepared this celebration and a glorious feast to welcome you.
You are my niece.
If you need anything at all, you just ask me.
Later there will be a gladiatorial competition.
Where men will fight to the death.
Your man Yaonius is scheduled to fight.
If your man defeats the challenger then you will be the champion.
The champion will be richly rewarded.
Very richly rewarded.
Can Yaonius win?
He should.  The odds are in his favor.
Mark Antony, you are my best friend.
Welcome to the Coliseum for the greatest battle in history!
The battle for the championship of Rome.
In this corner, fighting for Caesar, weighing in at 288lbs: Yaonius!
Who is he?
He looks very strong.
Caesar looks too calm.  He must be up to something.
Huh?
And over in this corner,
Twelve-time coliseum champion, weighing in at 581lbs:
The big blue bastard!
Kill him quickly.
There are three rounds for this competition.
Competitors my use any weapon at any time.
Lets get ready to rumble!
That's the end of the first round.
His hand!
Attack his right hand!
Heads or tails?
That's the end of the second round.
Enough playing around.
Use this sword.
Somebody help that man!
Yaonius!
Caesar! Caesar!
Well done, Yaonius.
Caesar, give it to me.
Oh, I'll give it to you all right.
Long live Caesar!
Long live Caesar, champion of Rome, Destined to go down in history!
His illness is back.
Be quiet!  Be quiet!
He has been asleep since the incident.
He's tired.
He'll be good as new after a good rest
This is all that Egyptian woman's fault.
Father has nothing in common with Cleopatra.
That woman is a savage.
Just let him rest for now, Octavius.
Mommy, I won...
Go ahead and sleep.
I can do all the work myself.
Cleopatra.
Yes.
What do you think you are doing here?
Give me back my husband.
Your husband?
You are mistaken.
The father of my child.
I think not.
Leave Caesar or I will kill you.
Get out.
This man belongs to me.
Then Caesar will be mine after I kill you.
Do you know Apollo Duolia?
She planned for me to kill Caesar,
but I changed my mind.
I will let you live if you leave now and never return.
No!
I will kill you.
Caesar doesn't love you any more.
Lying whore!
Wake him and we'll see who he really loves.
That's impossible.
Why don't you get naked and give it a try?
Caesar
Eh?
It is your wife.
Mommy?
Are you my mommy?
I am Cleopatra.
Oh, it's you.
Where is my mommy?
Wouldn't you like to come with me?
Mommy!
Yes, my son?
I had a nightmare.
I dreamt I died.
Silly boy.
Mother will protect you.
Sleep now my beautiful child.
I'm afraid to sleep alone!
OK, OK, you can sleep with mother.
Do you understand?  This is Caesar.
The man regresses to a child-like state whenever he comes to Rome.
You are just a conquered whore who wants to trade sex for power.
No man could ever love a greedy whore like you.  Not as a man loves a wife.
Go back to Egypt, Cleopatra.
That man does not love me.
That man has never loved me!
Caesar is everywhere.
The people of Rome are inundated by his image.
He claims to be a god.
It is an eye-sore.
Or more like a public health hazard.
This trend must be stopped.
Brutus
The senate chairman has been bought out by Caesar.
Now he can pass any law.
That is not all.
Antonius, Octavius, Lumanicus, Levicus.
How can Caesar pay off so many senators?
Julius Caesar
I propose we build a temple devoted to Caesar.
The people need a place to worship me.
All those in favor of the proposal to build a temple of Caesar, please stand up.
All those opposed, state your opposition.
I have something to say.
Cicero.
This senate is a farce.
Half of the senators do not bother to show up.
The other half are corrupt.
Chairman,
I have a response.
Caesar.
Cicero is not in possession of all of the pertinent details.
The senate is functioning perfectly.
That sounds reasonable.
Cicero's comments are stricken
from the record.
Caesar's proposal passes.
The temple will be built immediately.
This session is closed.
Oh shit!
Caesar or one of his cronies steals every vote.
Something must be done.
Don't worry about Caesar.
I will pay him a visit.
Right now.
Brutus
Oh, it's Cleopatra's creepy old lady friend.
Cleopatra would like to speak to you.
Please kill him.
Isn't that a bit harsh?
I can't do something like that.
He wants absolute power over Rome.
Rome is a democracy.  Caesar must not be allowed to seize power.
That isn't possible.
You can't just go around killing people.
He must die.
Just because he dumped you does not mean he deserves to die.
What's that?
Think of this as a political donation from Cleopatra to Brutus.
A bribe?  Don't be ridiculous.
I will keep piling on bags of gold until you say stop.
You're being serious?
It is for the common good.
Don't joke like that.
This is no joke.
How will I spend all that?
That's up to you.
Et tu, Bruté?
Caesar!
Caesar is dead!
Caesar died!  Caesar was killed!
Bring Yaonius here.
We must leave Rome quickly.
Rome without him is pointless.
Yaonius?
Yes?
Are you happy to be going back to Egypt?
Libia is waiting for you.
But who is waiting for me?
Yaonius!
Libia!
Mark Antony is coming from Rome to see you.
Has it been a whole year already?
It is said he is already entranced by your beauty.
Just like Caesar.
Exactly.
Mark Antony is just like Caesar.
He will be easy to control.
This meeting with Cleopatra must go well.
Are you feeling OK Mark Antony?
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
Then why are you so nervous?
You would not understand, Kaba.
It's Kabanius.
Yes, yes, I always forget the «nius».
You used to just be «Kaba»
The saying goes «To get a Tiger, grab its ass»
Or «To get a tiger cub, fuck a tigress».
Either one works.
I'm sure Cleopatra will enjoy your crude jokes.
She will, Kaba.
Kabanius.
I know, I know.
What does any of this have to do with war?
I don't know.
What about Egypt?
What if Cleopatra asks for advice about running the country?
You will have to help me.
I understand.
I will speak to her myself.
What am I going to do?
I'm scared.
Man up and do what you must.
You're not helping.
It..it..it is I, Mark Antony, come to speak with Cleopatra.
Welcome.
I have missed you, Mark Antony.
I haven't seen you since I left Rome.
I am so happy.
Oh, you've gone all stiff and hard.
I believe a man should be stiff and hard.
I'm glad you think so.  It takes a stiff man to satisfy me.
Here, let's drink a toast to our happy reunion.
When I see a beautiful woman, um, not that I look at a lot of them...
No, what I meant to say is...
Hold on.
What was I trying to say?
A beautiful woman.
Yes, when I see a beautiful woman,
I get confused.
Nonsense.  You speak like a poet.
Ah, good wine.
This wine is called «A delightful kiss»
Delightful kiss?
Yes, just like this.
Was that delightful?
Yes.
Would you like more?
You stopped.
Why?
This ring,
This is Caesar's ring.
Yes, he left it to me.
When I wear this ring, I am Caesar's official deputy.
I carry on his legacy.
Did you love Caesar?
I respect his memory.
And now I will pass it on to you.
Hey, what the fuck?
Forget the dead.
The past is the past.
All that matters now is the two of us.
What's wrong?
I can't do this.
Why not?
I cannot satisfy you like he did.
I have a small dick.
It's pathetic compared to Caesar's.
Oh don't be ridiculous.
That doesn't matter.
Let me show you.
Say «Ahhh»
What do you taste?
I don't know.  I swallowed it.
Now, try this one.
Say «Ahhh»
Did you taste that one?
You see Mark Antony, size is not important.
Cleopatra
Get ready for a hard dicking.
Bombs away!
How did you like that?
Oh, you're the best I've ever had.
You are being manipulated by Cleopatra.
She will ruin you.
No, Kaba.
Kabanius
That's what I said.
Cleopatra is good.
No, she's great.
I would gladly lay down my life for that woman.
You're a mess.
You have 200 thousand troops under your command.
If you conquer Egypt,
you can conquer the world.
The world.
There may be some truth to that.
Yes.  You must leave Cleopatra.
Go east.
I will.
To conquer the world for Cleopatra!
Prepare Mark Antony's bed.
Yes sir.
You look like hell.
You would have conquered the world by now if that woman hadn't turned you into such a pansy.
Why are you babbling like a retard?
Get rid of Cleopatra.
Thank you for your hospitality.
I think the king has something to say.
What's on your mind, Siluodiao?
Leave us.
Kill Cleopatra.
Listen to me.
Cleopatra killed Caesar.
She will kill you next unless you kill her first.
That's crazy.
Stop joking around.
Listen to me.
Cleopatra brought nothing but bad luck to Rome.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is ridiculous.
Kill Cleopatra.
Either she dies,
or you will die.
I don't believe it.
I can't believe it.
Kill Cleopatra!
Kill her!
What happened Mark Antony?
No..nothing.
I'm just a bit tired.
Report!
Octavius has taken control of Rome with 130 thousand soldiers.
They are fighting your supporters.
Transfer all my troops from Alexandria back to Rome
All my warships too.
Understand?
Mark Antony will be victorious!
One more bottle.
The perfect poison.
It should take effect in the midst of battle.
We must take the fight out of the soldiers.
OK ladies, you know what to do.
Fuck them till they
can't even stand up.
Sweet.
What are you doing, Kaba?
Where the hell is everybody?
Yaonius should be here.
He's a special case.
I can count on him.
Definitely.
I had no idea your girls would be so effective,
Libia.
Sex is a weapon.
It sure is.
Mark Antony was totally fooled.
We'll kill the general first, then the soldiers.
This will be the end of Mark Antony.
Say it again.
Call me an idiot.
Come on, say it to my face!
Bastard.
Who put you up to this?
Was it Cleopatra?
I see the answer in your face.
I should have known that bitch was up to something.
OK, now I am pissed.
I am going to kill Cleopatra.
And I will kill every last traitor involved in this plan.
Starting with you.
It can't end like this.
I have failed.
I really mean it this time.
It is quite hard to pick a winner this time.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I win!
Load up the crossbows!
Hoist the sails!
Listen to me.
Full speed ahead, We can take them.
Their boat looks much bigger up close.
Oh god, is this really the end?
Congratulations.
I heard that Mark Antony has been totally defeated.
He will be killed and his corpse thrown into the sea.
Haha
No.
I know all about Mark Antony.
Why?  What business is it of yours?
He hates me.
Because he trusted me.
My queen,
What is wrong with you?
Mark Antony has returned!
Cleopatra!
He has a sword.
Your highness, you are in danger!
My queen.
I am here, Mark Antony.
Cleopatra, where are you?
Mark Antony
I recognize your scent.
I wanted to come back, now I am back.
It was worth it.
I am so tired.
Please ki..ki..
Kiss you?
Yes, I need you to kiss me.
Thank you, for a sweet last kiss.
Mark Antony, don't die!
Mark Antony!
No. No.
First Caesar was killed, then Mark Antony was killed too.
Now it is Octavius.
When will it all end?
It will never end, Cleopatra.
As long as Egypt is under attack, it can never end.
It's too much, too much.
Apollo Duolia, change me back to the way I was!
Do you even remember your life before?
I was plain and normal, with a simple life.
I want that life again.
What do you want?
My original face.
What else?
Love.
Meaningless.
I want to be an ordinary woman again.
So I can have the the things that ordinary women get to have.
Will you reconsider?
No, I have made up my mind.
Do you not care for the fate of Egypt?
How can you be so weak, Queen Cleopatra?
Don't ignore me!
Where do you want to go?
Anywhere I can be free and lead a normal life.
There is no more freedom in Egypt.
Cleopatra has disappeared.
Yes, I'm sorry.
You will find her or you will die.
Don't worry, I will find her.
I can't hear you over the wind.
We'll have to talk in
speech bubbles.
We need to get out of this sand storm.
I think I see something ahead.
Is is a giant rock?
What is that?
It has the body of a lion and the head of a man.
This is the tomb of a king.
It's automated.
The entrance to a temple.
Anybody home?
Wait, there are instructions.
«Welcome to OOKAI tomb»
Whoever wishes to enter,
Must first relinquish their mortal coil, or in other words, die.
There are many varied and interesting ways to die here.
For details, see the instruction manual.
In the 1st room, you will be crushed by falling stones.
In the 2nd room, you will be buried alive.
Room three contains poisonous snakes.
Room four...
Enough, Yaonius.
We are not safe here.
This is some sort of temple of death.
Let's go.
It won't budge.
I think it opens from the outside only.
Oh.
We can't open it from here.
You cannot enter here.
Cleopatra must be inside.
You are protecting her.
This is the tomb of a king.
You can't go in.
Move.
Please.  Wait out here.
I will go inside and look.
I will bring Cleopatra out.
Please just wait out here.
Cleopatra
You have come at last.
Yes
What is it you want from Egypt?
I want you, to begin with.
I am a Queen with no power, but you are a hero.
I think it will be different this time around.
You look so beautiful.
Only for you.
Octavius,
Ever since we met back in Rome,
You have left an impression on my heart.
So you've missed me?
Yes
I will bring you back to Rome.
Really?
I will take you back as a captive.
You can watch me rebuild Rome
from inside a cage.
I am nothing like Caesar or Mark Antony.  You are useless to me.
But I will take you back with me anyway, as a trophy.
You shouldn't joke like that.
I am still young.  I can love you like no other. I can make you the greatest king in the world.
Compare the world to Rome.
Think about it, Octavius.
My Queen, I've come for you.
Your warrior.
Yaonius.
Oh!  I have heard about you!  Nice to meet you!
Just look at this body.
I heard all about you back in Rome.
Imagine meeting you way out here.
I lose sleep thinking of you.
It's true.  Sometimes I can't fall asleep.
I am so happy, and you are so gorgeous.
You must come live with me, OK, my darling?
Octavius?
I will go back with you if you will wait for five minutes.
OK, five minutes.
My Queen.
Libia?
Yes?
Bring me to the third room.
But your highness,
that room...
You mustn't go there!
Why not?
I do this as my final act as queen of Egypt.
Thank you for all you have done for me.
Cleopatra
My Queen.
Libia?
Yes?
You said there was no freedom left in Egypt.
But there is.
I have found it in your loving heart.
Mark Antony, come take me away.
I will be with Mark Antony in the afterlife.
So don't cry for me, Libia.
Mark Antony, I am ready.
Mark Antony...
You highness!
Your highness!
Look Libia, an air shaft.  Maybe we can escape through there.
Luck is with us.
Libia, it is time to go.
Roman troops, get out!
Thank you.  Is there anything else you would like to add?
No.
Haluwei, how is Luba?
OK then, the Cleopatra Plan...
Cleopatra Plan No.1548 Report
The marriage task force is in place and operatives are attached to nearly all the planet's leaders.
Everything is going to plan, and the operatives are prepared.
It seems to be 90% effective.
We await the final kill order.
Lead Invasion Officer, Pasateli Army.
Animerama Archival Society would like to thank the
developers of the following
free, open source applications.
Without their software, this fansub would not have been possible.
Handbrake http://handbrake.fr
SubRip http://zuggy.wz.cz
Jubler http://www.jubler.org
VirtualDub http://www.virtualdub.org
MKVMerge GUI http://www.bunkus.org
OpenOffice http://www.openoffice.org
For more Animerama Archival Society fansubs, keep an eye on Youtube and alt.binaries.anime.
We will be releasing «One Thousand and One Arabian Nights» and «Kanashimi no Belladonna» soon.