I, Tomoya Asahina,
...became the acting manager of a
coffee shop named Noel.
The previous manager risked his
life to save me from a car accident.
Since he's still in the hospital, I'm
taking over...
...his duties as manager for now.
Welcome.
What would you like?
Well, I...
Excuse me.
Here's your order, an Einspanner.
But I ordered a wiener coffee.
Yes, well Einspanner is
German for wiener coffee.
Huh?
Oh, I'm so vulgar.
It reminded me of a gentleman's
wiener.
Of course, the customers aren't
satisfied with my hastily prepared tea.
We lost a lot of customers.
Tomoya, I need 3 coffees.
Yes Ryoka.
Currently, with the ideas of
the manager's daughter Noel...
...along with the
regular customer Akiho...
...we decided to start a cosplay
cafe.
Good morning.
You have a lot of customers today.
Thank you for coming so early, I know
you had the afternoon shift but...
It's okay.
It's good to see that you're busy.
I'll go and change.
Akiho.
Thank you very much.
Cosplay Cafe Vol. 1
230,000... 240,000...
250,000...
260,000... 270,000...
Noel sure loves money.
Way to go, acting manager.
You sure know how to run a
business.
You should go change Akiho.
But...
I'll be fine on my own.
Thank you.
Why are you looking at
her with eyes like that?
What?
You never say things like that to me.
Kanae?
I feel sad.
When did you all get here?
Plus you're getting so big down
here.
It's so improper.
I had nothing to do with this!
Well, we're all married.
Except for Akiho who lost her
husband and is now a widow.
But it's just a shame.
You have such a beautiful
woman in front of you.
I made a peep hole right here.
I can see Akiho changing.
Wait a minute, Seia.
She has small boobs, but
they're perfectly shaped.
Her lingerie is pure white.
It's her kind of color.
Why would there be a hole?
Ouch!
What the hell?
Well, we have to go pick up
our kids from kindergarten.
So we'll be on our way.
Thank you for your service.
I'm coming too! Wait for me!
I won't allow any romantic
relationships within this shop.
I know.
Besides, Akiho doesn't want me.
But it's dangerous to have
her walk home alone at night.
So I'll let you walk her home.
It was really busy today.
I think I'll collapse if this keeps up.
But I'm really happy.
After Taichi, I mean
after my husband died...
I didn't feel like doing
anything for others.
I'm sorry if I bored you.
Not at all, but I'd rather be
one of the customers at Noel.
I just might go to the shop everyday
just to see you...
...in that waitress costume.
I was just kidding.
Forget about what I just said.
Akiho?
Umm, should I be more confident?
What?
I don't have a good body
like the other three girls.
That's not true, I
think you're wonderful.
Thank you so much.
At first, I was really afraid
to be seen in public like that.
But these days, it's a little different.
I feel like I'm having more fun.
Is that right?
Yes, but please don't tell
this to the other girls.
If they find out about it, then
they might make me wear a costume...
...that's really extreme.
Well, this is it for me.
Thank you for walking me home.
Oh, it was nothing.
Good night.
Taichi...
I'm lonely...
I want to lick it...
Your cock Taichi...
Hot, Taichi...
Rub it with your hand...
No...
I know that...
...this is vulgar...
But touch my private area...
More...
Masturbating...
My fingers...
Yes, stick it in...
Stick it inside me...
My hand won't stop...
No...
I shouldn't be doing this...
It feels good...
I'm coming...
Tomoya...
Sorry for making you come along.
It's okay, I have nothing to do
anyway.
What should I make for dinner?
I'm really indecisive about things.
Really?
Are you having trouble
deciding on the dinner for tonight?
We have a special today on beef.
How about some sukiyaki?
Good idea.
I have some Chinese
cabbage for sukiyaki.
I'll add in some shiitake mushrooms
and yellow button mushrooms...
...for 500 yen.
Right...
Sukiyaki eh?
Then I have this really nice pot.
Made of Teflon, it's a fine pot.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
I think I know what
I'm making for dinner.
But you shouldn't buy
things you don't need.
You don't need a whole Chinese
cabbage.
I'm really bad at this.
But that's also the good
thing about you, Akiho.
Delicious.
Just as I expected, you're
really good at cooking, Kanae.
In order to cook simmered
meat and potatoes...
...you have to take
extra care of the soup stock.
Thank you for the lesson.
And who are you cooking this for?
For Tomoya.
He lives alone, so it's kind of hard to
get a taste of home cooking, right?
I see...
He said he wanted to eat some
simmered meat and potatoes.
You two talk about things like that?
It doesn't taste good
when you eat alone, right?
I ask him to come eat
dinner once in a while.
And then...
Oh I see...
Then you have sex with him after
dinner?
What?
I'm back from shopping.
Thank you so much.
Looks like it might get
busy from the late afternoon.
Let's try to get things stocked up.
Hakugenya
By the way, how do you feel about
Akiho?
How? Nothing really.
No feelings whatsoever?
Right...
I see.
Then you don't mind us eating Akiho's
simmered meat and potatoes, right?
That's...
If you don't feel anything for
her, then you wouldn't mind, right?
But...
Simmered meat and potatoes
from this place or Akiho's...
Which one do you want?
I want to eat Akiho's...
He wants to eat Akiho!
That's disgusting!
Are you people feeling frustrated?
Look who's talking.
I mean my husband is really busy
with his work,
...so I haven't had sex in a while.
I haven't had some in a while, too!
Seia!
Let me taste your wiener.
It's huge!
What are you doing? Please stop.
Your wiener is dead.
I'll revive it for you once again...
Seia, stop...
Now just imagine Akiho is
sucking on your cock right now.
What...
I can't fit anymore inside my
mouth...
Kanae.
My boobs are very sensitive.
I can't take it anymore!
I feel stupid for being
the only one who's calm.
I'll let you use my boobs as a pillow.
It's so hard...
It's twitching!
Looks like you need to unload,
Tomoya.
Let's stop now...
Just leave it to us.
No...
Oh my, you have a
really cute voice Tomoya.
No...
Don't move your head Tomoya...
More, more!
Feels good!
It's your loss if you don't enjoy it.
I want you to give me
your thick semen, Tomoya.
This is Kanae...
Kanae's scent...
Kanae's taste...
Tomoya's balls taste good.
Seia...
You're putting me in agony...
Ryoka, you're too tight...
Amazing technique...
I can't believe I feel it
all the way to the root...
But if you suck on it that hard...
You really don't remember
anything from last night?
No, not really.
Please wear this, Akiho.
No. It's too embarrassing.
But I do remember one thing.
What is it?
If you like someone, then
you just go and say it.
Come on, it's okay.
But...
But she's still thinking about Taichi.
But Taichi won't do
anything for her, right?
He won't ask her out on a
date or have sex with her.
Ryoka...
Get him out of her way.
If Akiho can be happy
with that then it's okay.
I bought too much.
That's because you're
too good of a person.
You scolded me once before for
that.
I didn't scold you...
Taichi also scolded
me for the same reason.
You're coming over to eat dinner,
right?
Since I bought so much.
Yes...
Plus there's something
I want to ask you.
What is it?
We can't talk here...
We'll talk at my place...
It was Akiho's room, I've been
here several times for dinner.
Akiho is changing next door.
Akiho?
Seia told me to wear this, but I
don't think it looks good on me...
But I wanted to get your opinion...
I made my decision.
It's bad, right?
I'll go back and change.
Akiho's costume made me feel bold.
I'm sorry Tomoya.
It's my fault. Because
I dressed this way...
No...
The scent of Akiho's shampooed
hair, softness of her boobs...
They're making me feel much
bolder.
Tomoya...
No...
Akiho's nipples were getting hard.
No, not my nipples...
Akiho.
No...
It's embarrassing...
No!
I'm sorry.
But I like you Akiho.
Tomoya...
Akiho...
In the next room...
Maybe it was Akiho's way of
being respectful to Taichi...
Kiss me more...
You're amazing Akiho...
So wet...
I'm a girl, too, you know...
Your cock is so big...
Akiho.
Amazing...
It's so hard...
Akiho.
I want your cock inside my...
Inside your...
In there!
What do you mean ''there?''
You're mean...
Then I have to make it more wet.
Tomoya, slowly...
It's going to...
...pour out...
Please...
Stick it inside me...
Akiho...
You wanted it so bad?
I held it back all this time...
Akiho...
No...
It's embarrassing...
It's very beautiful.
Don't say that...
Just do it.
Okay Akiho, here I come.
It's coming inside...
It's really going inside me!
Are you okay Akiho?
I'm okay.
It's been a while so...
It's amazing inside you....
Feels good inside you...
Your cock is big and...
I'll start moving.
Okay.
It feels big inside me...
More...
So tight.
So tight...
I think I'll...
Try to hang in there...
I'm coming!
No...
Inside...
Release it inside me!
I haven't done this in a while...
I've always been alone...
Akiho.
Cosplay Cafe Vol. 2
Time passed by, and the very popular
''Noel'' went through remodeling.
Noel sure has the
talent to run a business.
But Akiho and I maintained
the same relationship...
Tomoya, can you get me 3 coffees?
Okay.
What's this?
How come you two are
turning red all of a sudden?
That's right.
I've been watching them
without doing my work...
...but they're acting rather strange.
Please get back to work, Seia!
Get back to work, Kanae!
Akiho, there's a hickey on your
neck.
What?
You can't fool us.
We're much smarter than you think.
I feel sad.
I'm telling you.
Please get back to work!
Tomoya, Akiho.
We're going to drink tonight.
What?
We're going find out how this
romance between you two started.
What?
But...
Hakugenya
I told you, we never had sex.
Then did you two at least kiss?
Well...
The fried sand borer is really good.
Then you licked Tomoya's thing?
Kanae, that's too much!
Kanae, you're totally in madam
mode.
Really?
This ice cream tastes so good!
Seia, where did you get that from?
Akiho...
I'm going to the ladies' room.
We have ice cream
I'm wet...
It's because Kanae mentioned
licking...
Okay, here's the sausage
meal you've been waiting for.
Man!
Stop teasing me like this!
Sake tastes great when we
talk about things like this.
I have to do some laundry,
so I'll be leaving now.
What?
You can stay a little longer, Akiho.
I should go too.
You can stay and drink some more
Tomoya.
Bye.
See what you did? You made her
angry.
She has no feelings for me, but you
people kept on saying weird things.
What? Then you two
didn't have sex at all?
We did it...
But it was a spur of the moment.
I'm sure Akiho regrets about it.
Sex without love...
So cute!
Ryoka, do we need to have
feelings in order to have sex?
I don't know.
Only thing important is if
it feels good or not, right?
I can't believe he would say
such a thing in this day and age.
He's certainly a modern day
coelacanth.
A relic of the 20th century perhaps?
Cocks? 20? Genitals?
I'm going home now.
Bye.
I want to teach him
how to do everything.
I have this desire to take my friends'
boyfriends...
...or other people's belongings.
I haven't had sex with
my husband in a while.
Maybe I'll play with some fire.
I want Tomoya's cock too.
Cosplay team of married women!
Their job is to correct the ways
innocent young boys think about sex.
It's a squadron of married women.
Married woman blue!
Married woman yellow!
Married woman red!
Thus, the battle for the
prize of Tomoya has begun.
I'm almost finished, so be patient
okay?
Okay.
You can't really eat home-cooked
meals when you're living alone, right?
Thank you so much.
It's okay.
My husband is away on a business
trip, so he won't be back tonight.
I was thinking of eating
dinner with Moe anyway.
Well, let's drink some wine shall
we?
Are you good at popping the cork?
I'm sorry, Tomoya.
It's okay...
You can think of me as your
mother and behave like a baby.
Huh?
You haven't been breastfed
in a long time, right?
You're right.
If I'm still being breastfed,
then I'm a mama's boy.
Mama, I wet my bed!
What?
You're going to be in first
grade starting next year.
What are you going to do then?
Move aside.
Everyone, we must capture him!
Using my power, I'll
correct your misconceptions.
Maid squad!
Yes!
Butler squad!
We're approaching a curve that's
ahead of us, please be careful.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, you didn't do it on
purpose.
I'm sorry.
You can touch me more if you like.
What?
Tomoya's hands are on my
left breast and shoulder...
You pervert!
Where do you think you're
touching!
Ryoka!
They must be planning something.
What are we planning?
Ryoka.
The pervert's injury will
take 3 months to recover.
Oh my, did I go too far?
You know...
Well, you mentioned that
we're planning something but...
We're actually all worried about
you.
Worried?
Well, we do feel like
having sex with you, too.
Have sex?
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Do you want to keep me company
tonight?
I want to talk to you about Akiho.
Thank you for waiting.
Sure.
You hear it often, right?
Don't think that she
becomes your woman...
...after you slept with her just once.
Tomoya, you don't have any
confidence?
What?
Akiho's not comfortable being with
a guy who's not confident, right?
Well, I'm still a student and I don't
really know about my future, so...
I'm not talking about that.
I mean your feelings toward Akiho.
If you're confident enough
tell her how you truly feel...
...then you can go right at her,
right?
But Taichi...
I told you to make her forget
about her dead husband, right?
Try to love her to a point
where she'll forget about Taichi.
You're not confident?
You want to know?
How to make love so that she'll
forget about her dead husband...
Ryoka...
You're not going...
...to tell me that women don't have
desire for sex, right?
I'll show you what's
really inside Akiho...
Could it be that...
...he has fallen?
Bon appetit.
You just let a woman do it up to
here...
...but you can't go further
since you're a coward?
Are you sure?
Are you really sure?
I'm wet for you.
Please, come...
Amazing, it's coiling around...
It's expanding...
The whole thing...
Is it inside?
Yes.
How does it feel?
It feels amazing inside you...
But we're just getting started...
Ryoka.
You sound weak...
Come on Tomoya...
I want you to keep moving more.
Yes...
No...
What is this?
It can't be...
I'm being dominated...
It's tight, Ryoka.
But your cock is so
big and feels so good...
I feel like I might become addicted...
I'm already...
Yes! You're stirring me up...
Tomoya...
You have good techniques...
That's not true. I have to change
positions, so I won't come early.
You have pretty long eyelashes.
What?
You have time to fool around?
That's not it.
I have to think about other things.
This is good.
Ryoka, I...
You're pathetic...
But it's okay...
I'm going to climax too...
Ryoka...
Keep doing it...
Feels good...
Why didn't you release it inside me?
Well...
You thought you might get me
pregnant?
You think I'll let that happen?
Don't worry, I'm taking good care of
it.
Ryoka...
You think this is over?
I said I'll teach you everything
about the female body, right?
2nd time will be from behind.
3rd time will be anal.
4th time around might
be the Ryoka special.
Today is Cosplay day!
All right! I'm going to ask Akiho
today.
Welcome!
Today is Cosplay day!
Hey Akiho.
Did you notice?
Tomoya keeps staring at you.
What? Why would he...
I want to be in love too.
If you don't approach
him, you'll never be happy.
Are you enjoying this, everyone?
But Tomoya despises me.
I made such loud noises...
You two are so cute.
I admit, Tomoya has a bazooka.
Special service!
Are you done?
Yes.
But Kanae and the others are mean.
They just leave after they're done.
Don't you agree?
What can you say? Housewives are
busy.
I...
What?
Please Akiho.
No, you first.
No, I insist.
Really?
Then, I want you to
accompany me to my dream.
What?
It's embarrassing...
Please forget what I said.
Akiho's dream was to
become a stewardess.
Umm, I brought some coffee.
T-Thank you.
I'm really sorry.
I'll bring you a new one right away.
I'm really sorry about that sir.
You can't be this
sloppy as a stewardess.
I'm sorry.
Get ready for takeoff.
Fasten your seatbelt.
What are you doing?
What? Your seatbelt.
That's not a seatbelt.
T-Tomoya...
I'm not Tomoya.
I'm a passenger.
I don't know if this is the
result of Ryoka's training.
My body was moving on its own.
It's not...
It's not wet yet...
You're a bad stewardess.
Here, make an announcement.
There may be some turbulence...
...so don't get up from your seats...
You have to say it clearly.
It feels so good...
I can't...
...make an announcement like this.
It's just...
All right, I'll say it...
Any passengers feeling ill
should contact a crew member...
You don't feel well?
That's not true...
It feels good!
Akiho, if you move that much...
I climaxed...
This is a first for me.
Akiho...
Tomoya, you're getting big again...
Akiho?
I want more of your stuff.
I can't give it to you right away.
Akiho...
See? Your cock is hard now.