- Mr. Motoura.
- Ms. Oyama.
Call me Mayumi.
What's the difference?
That's good.
So good.
You're so tight. What's with you?
Mr. Motoura, incredible!
Hot, like an iron rod!
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Thick is the chest
of an ex-All Japan Team spiker.
I never thought we'd be like this.
When you came to our school
six months ago...
...you were rough and hard
to get close to.
I'd had it.
I couldn't trust people
and I hated the world.
Those girls saved you.
What a bad man.
You did nasty
with all the volleyball players, and now me.
Nothing happened with them.
Liar. Some of them used be virgins.
No, really, nothing.
Who was the best?
See, I knew it.
I'm kidding.
Let go, let go!
Got it!
Sho Marui - Left Front - Scorpio
5'9" - 35-23-36 - Blood Type: A
Nao Inabe - Right Front - Leo
5'10" - 35-24-35 - Blood Type: B
There.
Kumi Marui - Setter - Aries
5'6" - 31-22-31 - Blood Type: AB
Got it.
Mayumi Kitajima - Center - Capricorn
5'8" - 33-22-33 Blood Type: A
Kuzuha Shionogi - Left Back - Taurus
5'9" - 32-22-33 - Blood Type: A
There.
Mio Matsuda - Center - Virgo
5'10" - 35-27-35 Blood Type: AB
Take that!
Kozue Nekoda - Substitute - Libra
5'7" - 33-22-33 Blood Type: B
Angels in the Court
City Championship
Aota Academy
Here you go.
Sho!
Oh Motoura - 27y.o. - Leo
6'3" - Blood Type: B
Your back was open.
You moved in too far.
You lose speed that way.
Yes, sir.
Kumi, you set it
one inch too close to the net.
Okay.
Next.
Oops. Out.
Nao. Put your heart into it.
Okay.
Next. Next.
Shionogi.
Why can't you dive in farther?
I'm sorry.
- Kitajima. Drop your hip!
- Yes.
Matsuda, don't look tired.
If you look tired in a game,
they'll bombard you.
I'm sorry.
- Nekoda.
Aota Academy is nothing to us.
They're no match for us.
The ticket to
the National Championship Game...
...is in the hands of yours truly,
Kabanishi and O-Ring Academy...
- Listen to us.
- Hey, you, bitches.
Who's that, the Drama Club?
No way, you don't know us?
- Not a clue. Selling something?
- Shut up, you student call girl.
- What did you say?
- Come on!
Wait.
Oh, more!
Motoura!
Long time no see.
Who are you?
It's me. Your arch enemy.
Haruo Kabanishi.
- Huh?
- What do you mean, huh?
Kabanishi Haruo,
O-Ring Academy coach and...
...Aiko Yada, their ace spiker.
Kabanishi and our Coach Motoura
were rivals on the All Japan Team.
That's me.
Haruo Kabanishi - 27y.o. - Virgo
6'2" - Blood Type: A
Aiko Yada is rumored to be
a shoe-in for the All Japan Team.
Well informed.
Aiko Yada - O-Ring Academy - Scorpio
5'10" - 34-23-33 - Blood Type: AB
Not bad to play for laughs.
- You bitch, shut your trap...
- Don't.
Motoura, I'll see you at
the City Championship Game.
Wait a minute. Who are you?
He doesn't remember.
Sho Marui.
I will never lose to you.
Let's go, Aiko.
We'll practice
our Rolling Killer Special.
Yes, Coach.
Good-bye. Good-bye.
- Killer...
- Rolling Special...
- Major Roll...
- Uhhh...
- Finish.
- Right.
A new strategy, perhaps.
Okay. We'll send out spies.
Mission lmpossible in Disguise.
Regular clothing would be less conspicuous.
Got it.
Nanase Morimura - Gemini
5'9" - 33-22-33 - Blood Type: AB
Who is she?
Coach Motoura?
Yeah.
Nanase Morimura, 8th grade,
a new transfer student.
I heard this team was contending
for the championship, like O-Ring.
I see.
You move in too close
when you spike.
You set one inch too close to the net.
That makes it harder for her.
You have supreme talent,
but your heart's not in it.
You don't dive close enough
when you receive.
Defenseless against a good fake.
You lack concentration.
What's with you?
Coming out of nowhere.
Show us how you play.
- All talk and no walk. Get up.
- Nao, that's enough.
Give me a few minutes.
Suck it.
No.
That's good.
Ready. Now I'll show them.
Wait! What is this?
There.
Got it!
Incredible.
There.
She's good.
Nanase Morimura, she's joining us.
The mysterious new student.
You can't stir ice cream soda.
- Why not?
- It gets muddy.
- Tastes better that way.
- Ice cream soda doesn't suit you.
But she wants to be a manager.
- Who?
- Nanase, I mean.
She doesn't want to play.
Same thing at her previous school.
What's her deal?
A player like that is hard to find anywhere.
I hate muddy ice cream soda.
You're not drinking it!
Oops.
I'm outta here.
Where to, Nao?
Work.
Massage Parlor
Coach.
Hey, Sho, isn't it?
What is this store?
Massage Parlor
Coach, don't you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
And you?
What about...
What about me?
No.
You play, I coach.
I've noticed you look really sad
from time to time.
Anything I could do...
Give me some release!
Lick my balls, one at a time.
If you play well,
that's all I can ask for.
- Coach.
- Sho.
I'm really doing this.
My heart is ready to burst.
I don't want to let you go.
But then I won't be able to hold you.
Coach. Mr. Motoura.
Excuse me.
I brought you something to drink.
I didn't order anything.
It's on the house.
Nao, Aota Students
are not allowed to work.
What about doing the nasty
with a student in a Karaoke box?
There's nothing about it
in the School rules, but...
...why are you taking your clothes off?
Captain, you can't monopolize him.
I'm joining you.
Put it in.
Nao.
What a horrible man.
Couldn't you find a more romantic spot?
- The place doesn't matter.
- What dedication.
Men love first-time girls like this,
don't they?
Shut up.
No.
Coach, give it to me, too.
Time to hear you sing here.
It's going in.
No, no!
It's so good.
Karaoke
More time, please.
If we win the semi-finals tomorrow,
we'll play O-Ring in the finals.
Yeah.
Her turn, maybe.
- Nanase, get changed and warm up.
- Okay.
Time out!
What's wrong?
- You're not playing serious!
- Nao.
- Captain, say something.
- Coach, it's not working out.
I guess.
Let's all stay focused.
- Hey, let him go!
- Coach!
Go, go, Aota!
- Don't.
- Are you toying with me?
- My cherry is for someone I love.
- You gotta be kidding.
What about this?
Finish what you started.
Let's go.
Let me finish it.
Take that!
Coach, do it to me, too.
Now I get it.
Nanase needs to be loved.
Only then she can relax.
Only then can she let herself go
and play to her full potential.
And she's still a virgin.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I am.
If we beat O-Ring,
we'll be in the National Championship.
With your ability...
I need that at every game.
No, I need that at every practice.
I can't bother you like that, can I?
It's no bother.
I love volleyball.
I really love it, so I quit.
Can you forget volleyball,
just like that?
But if you've made up your mind.
You can come back anytime.
I'll be waiting.
Tomorrow is the final.
Practice spikes and serves, and that's it.
No, no.
You were looking at me
with dirty thoughts, weren't you?
Go practice. Start practicing!
Yes.
It's the finals tomorrow.
I have to focus on the ball.
Exploding Pain!
Ball Pain!
Broken Dick - Nervous Explosion
Supreme Zen-like Pain
Don't act all jealous,
just because you got laid once.
- Men don't like jealousy.
- It's not like that.
There's a game tomorrow.
Go home.
As soon as you have your release,
you get cold.
Yo, give us some release, too.
- No!
- Don't be so mean.
We can force you, you know.
- Coach.
- You have a game tomorrow. Run.
But...
Buzz off, if you don't want to get hurt.
Your dick's out. Shut up.
- Kozue, run.
- Okay!
Asshole.
Stupid.
Take this.
Sis. It's the Coach!
What?
Today's the finals.
Our match against O-Ring Academy.
But Nao got hurt, Coach is missing,
and my sister got sick!
We're in trouble!
So, is that all you got?
What a disappointment!
I am the only one who can save them!
Coach, please give me energy!
- Nanase!
- Coach!
Angeles in the Court.
Second set.
We've also prepared
many nasty scenes for you!
We'll see you soon!