We the Volleyball Team at Aota Academy...
... aim to be victorious
at the City Championship.
We've got a new player.
Nanase Morimura.
Sometimes she makes easy mistakes.
Other times she shows incredible talent.
She's rather mysterious.
We won the semi-final.
In the final, we face our rival, O-Ring.
We should focus on the game, but...
... we are too distracted
by our coach and Nanase.
Trouble! It's the Coach!
It's my fault.
He got attacked by a gang.
O- Ring is so strong.
How can we beat them without our coach?
Angels in the Court
Coach.
Hi, it's Motoura.
Yo, how you've been?
What? I can't hear you.
Oops, sorry, I'm out.
He's not back yet.
What can I do?
He was protecting me.
Kozue.
His cock was out.
He was at a disadvantage.
Maybe the gang beat up
our coach.
- And drowned him?
- No.
It hurts.
Natalie
Heaven. I'm in heaven.
Mister, are you rich?
For now.
Sorry, I'm out.
- Not home yet.
- Where's he gone?
He'll be all right.
Right, Captain?
There is no point in hanging around.
Coach is fine. Tomorrow is the final.
Let's go home and sleep.
Coach.
The Championship Final
at O-Ring Academy
They're in no hurry.
Where is he?
What's going on?
Kumi Marui
- Kumi?
- Nanase? Where are you?
- Well, I'm at home.
- Come over to O-Ring right away.
- We lost the Coach and my sister.
- What?
We need you. We'll be waiting.
Hey, what're you doing?
If she's not serious,
she'll only be trouble.
Hey, Nao, give it to me.
- Nanase. You're here.
- Why are you here?
Nao.
- Nanase.
Morning.
- What time is it?
- Well. Dawn, maybe.
- You have such stamina.
- Do I?
- Yes.
- What time is it?
Morning.
Hey, where is Motoura?
You don't mean to play
without a coach?
Where is Sho Marui?
You don't need your ace spiker
against us?
- No, what happened was...
- Exactly.
- I see. You got tits.
- You mean, I got guts.
Soon you won't be able to turn up
your nostrils at us.
- You mean, turn up my nose at you.
- Gosh, you bitch.
Don't.
Ready for the Lust Judgment.
Last, right?
Motoura
Hey. What time is it?
Hey.
I'm scared.
O-Ring - Aota
No more.
Welcome to Hello, Housewife,
It's 12:15 pm. I'm your host...
12:15? You gotta be kidding.
What's wrong?
The game has started.
This is bad. This is bad.
- What am I going to do?
- You don't have to come to the game?
I have to come, of course.
Back attack.
Give me all you've got.
So long as I'm in the front.
You've stopped only one.
Nothing to be proud about.
I am proud.
- Nao.
She landed on the ball.
Nao.
Here we are.
You got a fever or something?
Don't overreact.
I just twisted it a little.
Why don't you forfeit?
This stupid slut won't play for a while.
You have no other player.
- This is no way to win, but...
- Not yet.
- Sis!
- Captain!
Sis.
So you're here. Sho Marui.
What're you doing?
Fuck, that full monty bastard.
I underestimated him,
because he was full monty.
Next time, we'll beat him up.
No, kill him.
I'm flying.
No way.
- Sis.
- Captain.
I knew it.
Captain.
This is it.
You only have five left.
What to do?
We'll end up forfeiting.
I'm in.
Who is she?
Aota's secret weapon?
I can't do it.
I told you.
If you're not serious,
you're only trouble.
- I'm sorry.
- No more, Nao.
Why, Nanase, why? You're so good.
Nanase, go away.
- Nao.
- Nao, no.
You can't. You're injured.
I'm not the type to get excited.
But I don't want to lose today.
Nao.
Let's win for our stupid missing coach!
- Sis.
- Captain.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry about the trouble.
As the captain,
I shouldn't have stayed out all night...
...Iooking for the coach.
I can do it.
Let's go.
- Coach.
- Nanase, you?
How's the game going?
We can still make it.
Nanase needs to be loved.
Only then can she relax.
Only then can she let herself go
and play to her full potential.
Coach.
This is too much.
Okay, let's go.
Nanase, it's about time. Hey.
Coach, do it to me.
They're very good. I need more power.
But...
I want you, Coach. Only you.
It has to be.
Nanase.
O-Ring - Aota
- Coach, I'm scared.
- It's all right.
My first time, and in this position.
I'm embarrassed.
Does it hurt?
Just a little. But...
...it's good.
We'll do it.
Multiple-strike attack.
- Sis.
- I'm sorry, Kumi.
This is not a victory.
We've only just begun.
Sho Marui. What a disappointment.
- Sis.
- Captain.
O-One more point.
One more point.
Is this it?
Time out. Time out!
Coach!
Motoura.
Coach.
- What have you been doing?
- Where have you been?
- We were so scared.
- Whose bra is this?
Die, die, die.
Hey, hey, hey. You're so late, stupid.
Who the hell are you?
- Captain.
- Nanase. Good luck.
Substitution!
Let's go.
There.
- Give it to me.
- O-Here.
Kumi.
She read my ball.
- Nanase.
- Yes.
I never knew about her.
Motoura, is she your secret weapon?
Yeah!
No.
We did it!
Infirmary
I'm sorry I made you worry.
You're awake.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Next is the National Championship, Sho.
I don't have a single drop left.
It's the National Championship next,
Coach!
Yeah.