What the hell is this?
What the fuck?
Please give me some fresh semen.
Huh ?
What the...?
Oh !
Hey!
He, hey!
What's happening here?
Eek!
Ugh...
May l bite down?
What?
Aaah...!
DAIAKUJI 6
Huh? You are...
Aah , ah...
Aah, ah... look.
lhabella did this much to me...
Look, the petals became this big .
lt's hot inside, and l feel it deep inside me.
What should we do?
Her eyes ...
lf we leave her like this, she'll lose her mind!
We have to bring her back to consciousness.
Ugh...
Argh!
lhabella's human cyborgs...
Boss!
We have captured them.
Well done... Bring them to lhabella.
Yes.
You!
You were a spy?
Yup.
Spy?
l have been a faithful servant of lhabella's, ever since birth .
l just got my memory back.
Oh, oh my...
Number B5, l'll leave the rest to you.
Roger!
So much power...
We received this power from lhabella.
A power much greater than humans.
Ou, ouch... Stop...
Before l destroy you , l'll use your body to dispose...
...my amplifying sexual desire.
No, no!
Fresh, fresh, freshy fresh semen, semen!
Fresh, freshy fresh, semen...
Something's not right. Like the mood...
Even if you squeeze, it won't come out!
Not coming out?
No!
Then l'll bite...
Don't bite down !
l feel it, l feel it!
Yes, feel it even more.
Wow...
Why don't you beg. What do you want?
Please lick me. Please lick me down there!
Wow. Your nipples are rock hard.
This is at its limit.
l'll make you feel better.
l feel something.
Like l became a guy.
lt's rubbing, rubbing and...
l'll make you feel good.
Aah, right there...
What is right there?
lf you say so, l'll stick it in.
My ass... my asshole.
lt's my nasty asshole.
A little bit more. Ready?
Aah, it's opening!
lt's going in my stomach!
Aah, the tongue action...
Who taught you this tongue action...
lhabell... Aah !
Who taught you this satisfaction?
A... Aku...
Say it!
Ah, ah, ah , ah, ah ...
lt's Master Akuji.
Master Akuji!
Good, keep that in mind when your cummming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming...
Cumming!
Damn, can't you like moan or something?
Moan?
Like ''ooh ,'' or like ''aah'' or something.
ooh, ooh, aah...
l guess that's a little better.
ooh , ooh, aah....ooh, ooh, aah...
Shut up!
Ooh?
Enough! Tighten up a little bit.
Like this...
Oh , yeah...
Oh, l think l can cum.
l'm cumming!
Wha...
What the hell?
He, hey...
Ha, ha, ha, ha, Osaka is over!
Who are you?
Fu, fu, fu, fu...
What you've revived is an ancient weapon with tremendous destructive power!
What?
You've sparked the wick of destruction.
You fucking dirty bitch...
Welcome to Eden.
lt's useless if you're keeping me as hostage.
Your fresh and young body.
Calm with intellectual composure.
Beautiful eyes.
l shall take over your body.
What?
This body was slowly reaching its limit.
You...
Before, l used to be an ugly, foolish, and disgusting man.
Everyone ignored, looked down upon, oppressed, and stepped on me.
But one day...
l was successful with my long years of experimentation.
Finally, l was able to have this body, which is close to my ideal.
Fool...
What? You call me a fool?
l deserve to be praised!
Ugh...
How is it?
lt's a feeling you've never felt before right?
Now, break time's over.
No, no...
No more...
Not in my ass!
Oh my...
My ass feels hot...
l'm taking the front end.
No, no!
lt's fat... l'll break!
l have to stop that weirdo.
That voice...
Wha...
Akuji...
Mi... Minka...
You were alive...
l was trying to die...
But l was saved ...
A Ouime guy recovered me.
Of course, l knew what he was up to.
But, l didn't care.
No! lt hurts, ouch!
No!
What was waiting for me was one of the most miserable experiences l've ever had.
Why... why do l...
Oh please...
l began escaping reality when l started to feel the sensation in my body.
l forget about everything when l'm feeling good...
Everything to white...
They wouldn't miss that space in my feelings.
When l noticed, my body was hooked on that sensation.
lt's going in...
Please look at my embarrassing spot.
lt's cumming...
Every hole l have was fucked and spread open...
l was fucked and raped, until l felt no shame.
l couldn't get away from the sensation that my body feels.
Finally, l was sold here.
l am no longer the Haku Minka you used to know.
l'm a nasty sex doll, only hungering for more sensation.
This is me now.
Hold me, Akuji...
What is that?
An enormous woman?
A monster!
Look at that!
Fu fu fu... checkmate.
Fu, fu... nice face.
lhabella!
Our sub terranean force was broken through!
What?
Yume!
Let go!
Please, come back!
Reinforcement of the erogenous zone.
Seems to be an interesting research...
But, not enough ascetism.
Come on, cum!
One down!
Yup!
We're going to help our boss!
Yeah!
l-lhabella!!
Shit!
Minka...
Akuji, fuck me!
Fuck me harder, please!
Starting to feel better?
Use me to feel good...
Akuji... l'm with Akuji...
For a long time, l've been dreaming.
Just like this...
Minka...
l'll follow you right after...
You are...?
Akuji...
Akuji will never be yours!
l'll protect you...
Hey, Toko.
Wake up , Toko!
l lost...
Go...
Minka...
Make her happy.
Sorry.
lt's pitch dark.
l can't see anything.
ls it really here?
Where is this place?
Ah, it's brother!
Master!
Oh, all you guys are in one piece.
You too!
Yup!
Huh? Where is Sat-chan?
Well...
Fu , ha, ha, ha...
You were a little too late, Akuji.
Sat-chan!
Boss!
This girl's body is mine.
Besides...
What the hell is this!
lt's fucking huge!
The city of Osaka will be...
ls this the ancient weapon?
Osaka is over.
This is the beginning of the end of the world of male dominance.
What?
Fu fu fu fu...
We don't need men anymore to breed.
Fu fu fu...
Eek! She became a mummy...
Fu fu fu fu...
Body transfer is finished!
All is going according to my plans...
Fu, fu , fu... Ha, ha, ha, ha...
Akuji...
What the hell?
Akuji, destroy the machines on the wall behind me!
Fool, if you do that, your life support will...
Do it, Akuji.
Hell yeah!
Grind your teeth , Sat-chan!
Daiakuji!
Stop! Stop it! Aah...
Oh my...
That can't be... a very strong mind...
What the hell was that?
Putting that aside, we have to do something about that.
lt's no good!
We're in a pinch!
Shit, this is trouble.
What should we do?
We have to stop it...
Osaka is mine. l won't make it your way!
Earth Dragon!
Daiakuji!
Shit, he's so hard.
No use...
We need to brace ourselves to do this.
Don't give up!
Akuji!
Aa-kun!
Yeah!
Daiakuji!
How is it being under the sunlight?
People are coming.
lf they come, show them off.
Stupid...
What, so you've been waiting to fuck.
Because... after marriage... l didn't really...
So cute...
lt's going in... lnside...
Raise your voice.
lt feels good.
Akuji!
Fuck, more, more, more!
l'm going all the way up in you.
Hey.
Yeah?
This isn't a dream right?
What's up all of a sudden?
Like l still can't believe it...
Fighting against Ouime... Unifying Osaka...
Don't be foolish , who do you think l am?
Or, that's what l would like to say...
l wonder who on earth...
Emergency!
What? You guys followed me on my honeymoon ?
Everyone else is here too!
Look at me!
Reserved for ladies. No men allowed !
Now is not the time to be saying that.
Ah, you're right...
Yoko is being kidnapped!
What?
And this was...
Huh ?
Compensation accepted.
ls that...?
l see...
Fu, fu, fu , Ha, ha, ha...
Freshy fresh
Good job guys!
Preview?
lt said ''The end'' at the very end!
Did you really want this to finish?
Huh? No, it's not that...
All right, then l shall...
Take over the earth , conquer the galaxy, and go up to episode 100!
l hope it lasts.
Daiakuji, the special episode
Sat-chan's Story
Sat-chan's story?
That's what it is.