Your pretty tough.
I'll show you true strength!
He's strong.
I know
Sorry so sudden.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
DAIAKUJI 3
This the Nako god's... blood
The baby couldn't be helped, but look at how healthy it looks now.
Miracle! It's a miracle!
I will leave your clothes here.
Thank you, Haruka-san.
Nako god, please don't call me in such way. It's my due respect.
Please excuse me.
I am finished, Nako god.
Yoko-san, there is nobody else here, so please don't call me god.
Yea, I'm sorry Yume.
What is the situation in Osaka?
Akuji absorbed Wakame-gumi.
Defeated General Nogi of the Ashiya region, and is still growing.
If this continues, eventually...
I am going to request a cease fire to Akuji.
That can't happen. You are the god of the Neko religion.
Incorrect! You should know, Yoko-san.
I am no god. I am a monster, not a man or a woman.
I have no memory of my past, and you just found me on the shore.
Your blood has a special power to cure people...
Besides, there are many people who believes in you and was saved.
But, it feels like I'm tricking everyone.
Yoko-san
I understand. I'll take care of it.
Thank you
Now, a word from our leader.
Sat-chan is so cute.
She doesn't look like our leader.
I am Takeda Satsu. In advance, this goes to all members.
All of you are disposable bodies, be prepared to throw your life away.
If not, we will never accomplish domination of Osaka.
You're scaring me!
Then throw your life away right now.
I take my words back...
She's definitely Akuji's aunt.
I'll be out for a while.
Where to?
For a little walk, with her.
Tamanegi was impressed.
No girl was able to handle his moves in 10 years, until you came, Kikko.
Don't call me in such a manner.
I am Nogi Kikuko, General Nogi's great grand daughter.
With a guy like you...
No matter what happens, I can't back down.
Even if Ashiya gets taken over.
What is that? I wonder what's happening?
Why a leash? Shh, don't look. Looks nasty.
Hey hey! If you don't get a move on, You'll make a puddle on the road.
Just chill. Have you ever waited to take a leak?
The feeling of pissing after you surpass your limit is exceptional.
I get goosebumps all over.
It's been a week since you came here, You've gone under me and Tamanegi,
and it must feel good to release everything that was building up in you.
Who would do...
We'll fuck in there.
In there? You're kidding...
No surprise, it's just a house. But I don't know whose house it is.
Akuji's life...
The Nako clan should be controlling the holy ground of Osaka.
We cannot allow Akuji, who is the devil's servant, to be alive.
This is what the Nako god has told me.
The Nako god has said so...
Nene-sama, Nene-sama!
I'll be counting on you.
Yes Ma'am
Nene-sama, Nene-sama
Nene-sama, you were over there.
Good timing Yoko. May I have a word with you?
Actually, I was thinking of sending an envoy to Akuji to request a cease fire.
Really?
Indeed
No one's home. Something's going right.
You can take off the things on your tits and in your pussy.
Only if you take off your clothes.
Who, who would...
I can make it vibrate stronger. What are you gonna do?
You jerk!
Is this ok?
Yeah, you can take it off.
How does it feel? Spilling out everything you saved up.
Stop being so stubborn and just relax. I'll make you feel good.
No, I don't want to.
However your pussy says differently.
I am not a dirty slut.
Of course you're not. Look at me.
You're not a dirty slut.
You're my bitch.
You have nice curves.
Don't look at me.
Hey, my bad! Sorry to bother you, this won't take...
Shit
Who the hell are you?
I am Nako god's royal servant, Toki Haruka.
I am here to take your life!
Now's my chance.
Damn! You're pretty good for a cutie.
Please grant me with power, Nako god!
What?
Now we're even.
Did I ever said you owed me one?
You shouldn't underestimate the Nako clan.
I don't give a fuck. Whoever my foe is, I am taking over Osaka.
How's your wound?
I don't recall you ever worrying.
You're so stubborn.
You're conscious.
Nako god...
Forget about Nako god, because from today, I'm your god.
What am I thinking of? I came all this way to escape.
Are you awake now?
Don't give me that scary look.
You have no guy experience, do you?
It's probably the first time for a guy to see you naked, isn't it?
You have a nice body.
Today is your opportunity to show your naked body to everyone!
Don't get that excited.
Oh, you're back.
Yes
It's beautiful...
Yume!
What happened?
Yoko-san...
Why am I doing such thing...?
Komiya-sama! Komiya-sama!
Haruka was captured by Akuji?
Yes, Tsukigase-sama went to go negotiate with Akuji.
That can't be.
And Yoko-sama is to stay here and protect the Nako god.
Yume...
Huh?
Yoko-san
Akuji has denied our cease fire, and kidnapped our member.
This is not to be forgiven!
Hell Yeah! Can't be forgiven!
Destroy Akuji-gumi! Kill Akuji!
Our soul is one. We have to save our member, and defeat the evil!
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Now, take your weapons!
How do you feel?
Please let go of me! I can see in you, the Nako god...
Good, Good! You're exciting me.
Observe
Isn't it beautiful? A week ago, she was stubborn like you.
No!
I love watching stubborn girls like you falling for your temptation.
Just watching makes my pussy so wet.
I will never fall for...
You're still a virgin?
Then you probably never used something like this before.
No, You have to look up.
Koharu-san, I'll leave her up to you.
Ok, please say it once more from the beginning.
Yes. I will never run away again.
Master Akuji... Master Akuji...
Little bit more.
Yes
I swear loyalty to Master Akuji.
Please use my holes at any time you please. So please...
Very good. You hung in there.
I accept your loyalty.
Come over here.
Yes
Smell my dick.
Does it smell?
Yes, a little.
Do you not like it?
No
This is my smell. Savor the pleasure.
Yes
How is it? It's gorgeous isn't it?
Women are actually built to be dirty.
Deep down inside, we always think of dirty things.
We always want to have sex.
That is the woman, not the female conscious. Do you understand?
Right? You're thinking of getting down and dirty.
No, no you're wrong!
Don't worry. I just need to open the lid and let your feelings take over.
After that, see for yourself.
I'm fucking you deep!
Melting! I'm melting!
That's good. Melt like you never did before!
Yes!
There! Right there! Wonderful!
Deeper! Deeper!
Say it clearly. What do you want me to do?
Yes, Master Akuji. Please watch me. Please watch me cum.
Well said. Take this!
Master Akuji!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Well, well, looks like you cummed along.
But you can't be satisfied with that toy.
Look forward
I'm gonna fuck you up.
No...
Don't lose yourself.
No, stop it!
It hurts... it hurts...
It hurts
Deep... oh my...
It hurts!
I can't take it... It's hot, so hot...
Deep, deep... It's so hot...
Deep down feels weird...
Cumming, cumming... Something's cumming!
She spouted on her second time. She'll sell at a good price.
It's a beautiful pink!
Such color cannot be seen in our country.
So embarrassing... I don't want to do this.
Awww...
Nozomi
Yes, Master.
Please proceed.
Wonderful!
Delicious!
Look at this ass!
It's slippery like a boiled egg!
Hey, having fun?
Who are you?
Please don't worry.
He is the one who brought the presents.
Akuji, are you ready?
Yeah. Come in.
Oh! Japanese beauty!
Beautiful
What...?
Smells good...
Please...
I am a dirty bitch.
Please fuck us with the nice cock of yours.
Is this Lady Kikuko of the Ashiya?
Oh, you know her.
Hey, don't worry. No one knows that she's here.
Kikuko, Kikuko can't wait any longer.
Please... hurry.
There!
This is great! Wonderful, Akuji-kun!
If you like it, I'll leave one here.
Please, please Akuji! I'll pay plenty of cash.
Haruka will be ok?
Yeah, I can't leave a Nogi member in this house.
Besides, she has the ideal...
Now then...
Big Brother! It's horrible!
Right now at the office...
Come out Akuji!
Haruka-san!
Come out scum! Give back Haruka-san!
What shall we do, Sat-chan?
Murder!
Hmmm...
That's good too!
No it isn't!
Hey, sorry for the wait.
That's Akuji.
Give back Haruka-san!
So, you are Akuji...
Give back Toki Haruka!
Haruka...?
Oh, that bitch.
She's not here anymore.
She's probably getting fucked by cocks in Ouime.
What have you...
As you can see, Akuji is evil.
Negotiation is useless. Everyone!
Huh, interesting...
Bring it on!