Hey...
West point 2B-34, check complete.
Attention section 3 Maintenance crew, go to south block 54!
East point 3D-4. There is miscalculation if 0.5 in data.
Any problems in the final check for all sectors?
No, so far all sectors are clear.
We better do good! Beause I'm the one who gets in trouble.
Yes.
Weren't you going back home after this mission, Pricilla?
Uh, no...I...
Now that "Eden" is complete, we should just burn everything in Japan.
This country's moist air isn't good for my skin.
Hello.
How have you been?
Ihabella
Right now we're in the final check. When that's complete...
Well done.
Since I don't have time, I'll just get to the bottom line. I will take control of Eden.
DAIAKUJI 5
Open today, the house of fun, "Nako-god is Watching!"
Once you step in, it is absolutely paradise!
But before going in, watch this presentation!
Like this.
First is the Giant bathing cavern!
He-hey! You weren't told to do that much!
The body washing and massaging service is excellent!
No!
Next is the banquet hall, where you get to drink sake with beautiful girls!
If you get them drunk...
You can enjoy this kind of sake!
Look at me!
24 hours open...
The fascinating show!
And at the end take it slow...
Soak it in.
Please let us be of service.
Oh my, it's amazing!
Then please stop by.
I will treat you good with a Sakura storm!
One customer coming right up!
It seems to be going pretty good.
Yes, because of the anti Ouime spirit, people have been rooting for Akuji-gumi.
Yea, leave it to me!
Hey, it's Big brother!
Hey, how you've been?
Then the leader of the Nako clan has something to do with Ouime.
Yes, not really sure but they're planning to use Yume for something...
Please! Help Yume!
I know I can't ask this favor, but I have a bad feeling about this.
But with your information, we can't do anything...
If we know their plans...
That outfit. You're an Ouime member.
Ihabella's been doing experiments on women to have reproductive fuctions.
When the experiments succeeds, she is getting rid of all men from the world.
Why does an Ouime member bother to bring this information?
Ouime isn't one big ironclad organization.
Besides, I have a promise with Akuji...
Are you okay?
No!
No, not right here...
You guys just don't stand there...
It's useless.
I tricked them so that they'll only listen to me.
That can't be...
I will let you taste it too, the taste of my invention.
You bitch...
Relax, it'll hit you quick...
Not like despicable men, this secretes the liquid of the licentious substance.
Observe.
It's hot, it's hot!
No, no!
No, stop, stop! It's gonna rip!
I'm losing, losing!
Suck on it.
Yes.
Shenel, you can't...
Be happy because I'm going to use you to perform my final experiment.
Experiment?
No, no...
If the sperm this shoots out will survive in your body!
No!
Aah! Ouch! No, no!
Relax, the sensation will soon run all over your body.
No!
Wonderful!
I'm cumming!
Good. Cum with me...
Do you want it?
Please, hurry, hurry...
Deep, deep in me!
It's tighter...
I'm cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming!
She's saying she can't stand it anymore.
You have a nice tightness. Here we go!
Accept my sperm!
Did you capture Pricilla?
I am terribly sorry. She received major damage, but to my regret...
Shit...this wont effect us!
Yes!
Lets go on to our next phase.
Both of us got separated. Let's just think about survival.
More, stick it in more Akuji!
Being raised in a maternal country, you sure do listen to me...
Because I...I want to be treated this way...
By a man, a strong man like you pleasuring me and I feel so good...
Yup, that is more lady like. Just feel everything.
Akuji, I...I...
Let's go!
Akuji...
Akuji!
Akuji?
You...
Why do you know my name?
Oh yea, I completely forgot!
I think it was Luson island where we were together.
You're such a terrible person! We promised that we'll meet agian...
Did I?
Can't fight the blood of his faher.
I thought I knew you but I'm surprised that you're this bad...
Wait! Do you have a place to go?
Leave me alone!
You escaped from Ouime to come to my place right?
If you leave, that's it, I'll never hold you agian...
Good girl. Hey Toko, make something to...
Ouch ouch ouch...
What the hell?
Nothing...
What was that?
Another characteristic of your father...
Huh?
Excuse me...
You two are...?
We always wanted to be taught dirty things by you.
Oh, very well.
Beautiful...
Now, slowly move your mouth.
Yes, roll it gently with you tongue.
Lick how you wanted to be licked.
You two are pretty good.
Wa...wait a second...
You two are...
No!
He's been getting dirty with girls of Ouime...
All right, I'm gonna be out for a while.
Why are you laughing...
Because it fit me better!
Huh?
That's my Toko...
Akuji...
So all that was just...
Hey Toko, are you here.
What? No more pain for me.
I'm not interested in that way.
Akuji...
Huh?
What are you planning after taking over Osaka?
I don't know.
Do you want to become rich? Or be the biggest player in Osaka?
I have no interest...
I thought I knew you back then, but I don't know you...
You're still too stubborn.
You want to ask, right? How I feel about you.
Don't fool around! Who would...
Relax. I'm serious about you.
Akuji...
No, let go...
Don't worry. I know everything about you.
Everything...
Akuji...
It's beautiful.
No, please...
Don't spread it!
You have a cute voice.
Stupid...
You've been saving up for a while.
Here, don't be selfish and just relax yourself.
Oh no, because...
No, I'm cumming, cumming!
Relax, I'll be here watching.
No!
I'm really cumming! Cumming, cumming!
Cumming!
The fun starts from here.
No, it's...
No!
Wow, wow...
My ass, my ass...
Please...
In my ass too...
It's comming!
I'm full, I'm getting full... stuff my ass...
Akuji, Akuji...
Toko...
I always had... I always thought of...
I'm going...
Come, Satisfy me! Please! I want you...cum!
Toko...
Akuji... Akuji!
Master!
Master, oops, sorry...
Don't mind. What is it?
Emergency! Kikuko Nogi got kidnapped!
Kikuko? Which bastards?
That is, Ouime...
What?
Oh, please...
How is it? Doesn't it feel good?
I am Master Akuji's...
Filthy...
I will teach you a lesson for being a man's slave!
No!
Don't worry. We're just messing with your senses.
Right now your brain feels everything as a sensation...
That's not...
Like I place this finger...
...right on this spot.
How is it? Didn't your whole body orgasm?
What do you think will happen if I kept on doing this?
No, I'll lose... I'll lose myself!
I'll help you lose yourself completely.
No, no!
Hurry and come Akuji. That will be your...
...no, that will be the end of all the men!
What?
You're really going to attack?
It's obviously a trap!
Stupid! If you don't take care of business, you're the fool of Osaka.
We can't hurt our reputation.
But the foe is Ouime...
Yes, Ihabella won't just start this for no reason...
I don't care!
We can't leave alone a fool whose trying to destroy all men!
Master!
All right! We're breaking in from the front!
It's a mass attack!
Yeah!
Akuji and others are moving.
Block A, party 3 located enemy form the main hall.
Engaging in battle.
Everything's prepared?
Yes!
Transfer complete. The completion was delayed a little, but we have all systems go.
Let's hurry.
Yes!
Number 4 defense line defeated!
10% reduction of our forces.
Sending reinforcements to Sector 6.
Current status of the Dogu weapon?
Setting complete. Ready to go!
Good. Isolate Akuji.
Yes!
Hurry Akuji...
Shit, they're annoying.
Leave her up to me!
Toko!
Shit Toko!
I'm okay. Go on ahead.
I'm with her. Please!
I got it.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You are...?
What is this?
Wha...a human?
A talisman?
2nd infantry, Number 4 defense line defeated!
14th unit, engaging battle with unidentified species!
A fish is flying. What an idiot?
Akuji-gumi even has a pet.
Huh?
High physical level...
Plus young and beautiful.
This is a gift from Akuji to me.
Finally Akuji-gumi enters Eden.
What is the truth behind Ouime?
And who is the figure who stands in the way of Akuji?
Wait Akuji! That way is...
Daiakuji sixth episode! Control the war and dominate Osaka!
I finished it nicely this time.
Really?