And what?
What my friends said is that it's the blood from god.
This is it. This is the blood of the missing experimental project "N".
Where is this god you're talking about?
I don't know the details.
Listen, I will give you a better lesson when you find the owner of the blood.
Yes, Professor Ihabella.
Weak shit!
Look here! Look here!
Everyone look at me!
You'll get hurt if you stare at her too long.
DAIAKUJI 4
Shit, they're pretty good.
Take this!
Right here! Huh?
Die Akuji.
Die for the Nako clan.
Now!
Tsukigase-sama is defeated?
Oh my god...
Run! Retreat! We're retreating!
You owe me for this one.
Just like always Toko, nice assist!
How is it?
You want to get down and dirty, don't you?
This must be the greatest experience for you right now!
Yes...
He really loves to stare at pussies, and he'll look at it for months.
Oh no...
Oh, it moved just now.
Look at here, she's becoming wet.
But look at this dirty sight!
Grotesque, dirty, and it smells bad!
Want to cum?
Yes
Cum by thinking dirty!
Yes, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
No, it hurts!
Good, you're exciting me!
Please stop!
No you can't!
Pain lovers deserve more punishment.
She's a strong women.
Has she spilled anything?
No
My examination shows that they have their own way of making revenue.
If we don't cut that first...
We don't have such...
Looks like you don't know how to ask.
Did you know fluids extracted from the stomach is ejected from the bladder?
How is my eternal orgasm?
It's been a while since I fucked you, Yuko.
So I'm going to have plenty of fun with you.
You haven't changed.
The fun's just starting.
Master Akuji...
Kikuko
I brought her since she wanted to fuck too.
Come over.
Yes
You take care of over there.
Master Akuji, it my pleasure.
You got better Kikuko.
Thank you very much.
Is it good?
Yes, very...
Akuji, don't move. Today the two of us will serve you.
Oh yeah?
Today Akuji is my toy...
It's been a while since last time.
Your tightness hasn't changed.
Thanks. Here we go!
How is it?
It feels great.
Kikuko, watch carefully. This is you Master's sweet spot.
It's good!
Your cock grew agian, Akuji.
Yuko-san...
Inside, inside, good.
Good Kikuko-chan, come here.
Yes
Excuse me, Master.
You're soaking wet.
Me, me too...
Master's tongue is going inside, inside...
You look so cute all mellowed out.
Here, watch the penetrating cock.
Everything goes in and it's wrapped around. Wonderfull!
You have to work harder Kikuko.
Yes
Your cock's hitting me deep.
Yes, rock harder! Deep, deep...
I feel the power overflowing!
After all, you're the best Yuko. I appreciate it.
Kikuko, I'm gonna fuck you up. Spread open.
Yes
A little bit more.
Huh?
My whip is gone.
Akuji took the whip with him.
In the next room.
Wha...?
Ooh, it's Motoko! Do you want to have fun too?
Fools
Boss, Master.
They're getting busy.
The bitch from the Nako clan finally spilled.
They were opening shops to build their funds.
Shops?
A shop?
Nene-sama wouldn't do such thing?!
Yes, it was orders from the Nako-god.
That can't be...
It's a lie. Anyways, we have to go save Nene-sama...
It's too much. We contributed our money, and we eat poorly.
The women get fucked at the shop and the earnings get contributed.
All this for the blood of the Nako-god.
Please! A little is enough for my child...
No, I get it first!
I've been told six months!
Nako-god! Nako-god!
Everyone...
Hold on! We can't give the blood all at once...
The blood! Blood! Give me the blood!
In short, they say it's the blood of the Nako-god?
Yes
The blood has the power to heal any illness.
The god is probably at the Nako headquarters in the Shikina region.
Professor Ihabella
Please give me more treatment.
No, you hand...
Show everything you have in front of me.
Yes
Please...
Blood, give me the blood!
If I only have the blood...
Yoko-san
Don't worry. I am by your side.
Please escape, Yoko-san.
Yume...
This is entirely my blood's fault. If I wasn't here, none would have suffered.
No, that's wrong.
Yume. You've saw all the people that was saved, didn't you.
You saved the baby from dying.
You also saved the elder who couldn't walk.
But there are people who suffered because of this.
It doesn't make sense.
I don't deserve to live. Good bye, Yoko-san.
Yume, wait!
Oh no...
What's going on?
Please run away Yoko-san!
Yume...
Right now, no one should be here, hurry!
Yoko-san...
Yume, I always loved you...
We will die together.
So this is the truth about the shops of the Nako clan.
I'm disgusted.
Master, what shall we do?
Let's go to Shikina. Gather everyone!!
Are you serious?
Yeah, we'll have to eliminate our competition.
You're beautiful, Yume.
That's not so. I don't have big tits like you, and besides...
That's not true. You are better looking than anyone, Yume.
No, don't...!
Yume...
No!
It's all right. You must have been suffering untill now.
No, don't do...
Relax, and let me make you feel good.
Don't do such... No... it's dirty...
Yume
Yoko-san
Having fun?
Who are you?
It's the experiment. I have finally found you.
What is the meaning of this?
What? What the...
Come!
Ouch!
What are you doing to Yume?
Yume? She's given a nice name.
Even though it's a lab rat.
A lab rat?
Yes, you are my creation.
You're coming with me.
No! I will not go.
You can't disobey to the words I'm saying.
No!
Don't move your hands.
I've had you under a strong mind control since your birth.
That can't be...
Then try to disobey to what I'm about to say.
You can't bear to stick the thing on your crotch into her pussy.
No way...
You want to fuck her and feel the sensation.
Yume, don't listen!
How is it? Doesn't the thing on your crotch feel so hot?
No... I... don't think...
Look at it, such a wonderful body.
The beautiful pick pussy.
What happened?
Yume!
It's ok! I'll just cum like the last time...
You can't do such a thing. I won't permit it.
No, please! Get out! If not, I'll go crazy!
What the hell is this?
Hey, where is this Nako god of yours?
In the shrine...
Not even a god could save us today...
Shit, they just make the people suffer and vanish when trouble comes.
Don't worry. You won't cum even if I touch you.
Only until you stick it in.
You'll feel relief after you cum everything.
Relief...
Cum, don't you want to cum?
Yume...
Do you want to cum?
Yes
Say it out loud this time. What do you want to do with this cock?
I am going to stick it in Yoko-san...
What do you want to stick in?
Stick my fat thing in...
You're going to stir as fast as you can, stroke and cum everything you have?
Yes. I'm going to stir as fast as I can, stroke and cum everything I have.
Huh, filthy! Go!
Yume, stop it! Wake up!
Useless. It's only thinking about cumming.
I want to cum... now...
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Cum everything you've got.
Yes
No, please stop this!
Yume, please stop!
Wow, it's tighter, tighter...
Yume, please stop.
Stop, please!
Please, if you keep this...
Yume!
Yume, Yume, your thing...
is in my pussy...
Yume, your...!
Yume! Yume!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
Akuji
It's my turn to pay you back.
What?
Hey, wake up!
You are...
Please help... Yume.
Yume! Please help...
Hey!