You shouldn't pick a fight indiscriminately
If the opponent is strong, you have to prepare.
Punching a strong guy without preparation is stupid.
It seemed that my country was stupid.
They should've thought a little more before picking a fight.
It's too late now.
DAIAKUJI
(WHY? WHY? DAIAKUJI)
What the hell?
Why am I so tiny?
The backgrounds funny too.
Hey!
Sat-chan, you aren't so different.
What is it?
"It's troublesome to explain the relationships of the characters."
That's right
"And the dirty scenes will be shorter because of that."
That's not good.
"So I decided to explain it now."
Who does?
It's the producer's consideration.
I see.
(OUIME)
First, Ouime.
I explain this?
The country, Ouime put our country under occupation.
Right. We lost the war.
It's been like that for a while.
Ouime is a country dominated by women.
Women are superior to men.
That's why this country's army, companies...
and even souvenir stores are run by women under law.
If you disobey the rules, you will be sent to jail like the gangs.
(WAKAME GUMI)
Wakame-gumi too, which Akuji is an heir to.
Wakame-gumi is my grandfather's Ippatsu Yamamoto.
He inherited it properly by sleeping with the daughter there.
I don't get what is proper about it.
But it sounds like something my father would do.
That's right. My grandpa made some women pregnant, then you were born.
"Some woman?" Isn't that a terrible way to say it?
Sorry. It doesn't mean anything.
Do you remember that I, Satsu Takega am your aunt.
That's why I said I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Watch your mouth.
I know I have lots of aunts and uncles, whom I don't even know.
The number is increasing, too.
Anyway, my grandpa left the family, and has gone somewhere.
And my father was killed in the war.
The family is falling apart.
After I came back from jail, my grandpa's lover was the boss.
The representative has to be a woman, according to the Ouime.
I came all the way back home.
She used all of her men to beat me up and kicked me out of there.
You are weak.
You should train yourself more.
I was just out of jail. I didn't have any strength.
What are you doing now?
I was saved by Yoko Aoba, the leader of the volunteer group.
To repay this kindness, I joined the  group.
The volunteer group?
Yeah.
It was organized by the idealistic youth.
It is a pure volunteer group. I can say that.
Is it from some textbook?
What do they do?
We collect money from the shops and...
run lots of adult entertainment stores.
Is that called "volunteer" work?
Because I'm here now.
It is poor and small now.
But someday it'll conquer the whole Osaka area.
(OSAKA'S SITUATION)
Stop it.
But what is the situation in Osaka now?
First there is Wakame-gumi.
The boss is Ichihashi Ran.
She is a bitch, who took the family by taking advantage of my grandpa.
Haruko Tsujiya works for her.
She is the wife of one of my boys, but she has a grudge against me.
Motoko Kaga. I called her Toko.
Her father was an executive at Wakame-gumi.
I wonder where he is now.
Anyway, we've been good friends since we were kids.
There is Ai Morita, who likes chivalrous movies. And there are more.
And the volunteer group that I'm in.
The leader is, as I said before. Yoko Aoba.
There're also Mirai Kako and Tomoko Kinugasa.
It's a small organization, but with my power it'll be...
I heard that already.
Oh, she is Minka Haku.
She has a restaurant in Kobe.
Since I fell in love with her six years ago, I've been asking her out.
She's been rejecting me because she hates gangs.
I want her to be mine. But I can't take a strong attitude somehow.
To return to the topic...
Nako-kyo is extending it power steadily now.
Formally, it's called Kanze-nago-shintou-kyo.
The founder of Nako-kyo is Yume.
She is called "a living god."
But it sounds very suspicious.
Her women are Yoko Komiya and Nene Tsukise.
They are called holy women. There aren't such things.
(OTHERS)
Wakame-gumi and Nako-kyo have the power in Osaka now.
Other than that there are Ouime, and many weird bastards in Osaka.
Whoever they are, I beat up men and I fuck women. That's it.
Well, there are some unidentifiable objects.
Do I have to deal with them?
Well, I do whatever.
AND...
And this is the end of the explanation.
All I'll do is be violent.
Can I be violent too?
Yeah. I'm looking forward to it soon.
Did you say "soon"?
I look forward to a bright future.
Good luck.
I'm gonna check up on Tamanegi.
Oh. Hello sir.
Is she the next?
I'm counting on you.
Leave her to me.
Where am I?
Where is this place?
What's going on?!
Who are you?
My name is Tamanegi.
I serve my boss, Akuji. I'm his private trainer.
No
Stop it, it tickles.
Stop it! Don't touch there!
It seems that you don't know anything as a woman.
First you have to open up the door to ecstasy.
No, What are you doing?
I feel weird.
It tickles.
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop it. Help me!
It hurts.
Please stop it now.
Strain, then relax.
That combination will paralyze her brain, and overflow here with ecstasy.
You are very wet now.
You are hopeful.
Go ahead. Release yourself.
Somehow...
I'm getting a funny feeling.
This is the first time.
What is that?
No. Don't.
No, What are you doing?
Stop! Stop it!
No. Something...
Something, something is cumming.
I'm scared, I'm scared! Help me!
You can burst.
The training is going well.
I left you the job of penetration.
Let's see.
You did great, Tamanegi.
You trained the girl, who didn't have any experience.
This is only the beginning.
She has a masochist talent.
Don't forget the serving spirit.
Give my boss the pleasure of yours.
No!
She is a virgin for sure.
It hurts...
It hurts. Hey don't run away.
You already feel good, huh!
That's good.
It feels good.
Oh, no!
That's good.
You can make lots of money for us.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
One customer is coming!
Welcome!