Excuse me?
What?
This is your parent's home isnt it, Akuji-san?
That's right.
You are going home, but why?
I'm the third Wakame-gumi boss,
Yamamoto Akuji.
I came to repay you.
DAIAKUJI
Akuji, He finally came here.
He is coming back.
So?
Are you trying to stop him from coming back here?
The ruler has changed.
This country must change too.
You are just a lover...
You don't understand your situation, do you?
Motoko!
She is good for your daughter.
So I assigned her to be an executive here.
Motoko, you...!
Get out of here.
I don't care if you were an executive here before.
There is no place here for you.
Go home.
Motoko
Show this old man the way back home.
What are you doing?
Hands off of me! Hands off!
Please do whatever she says.
That's the best for you, father.
Motoko, you...
You'll be sorry later, Ran!
Motoko
Yes?
Do you know the reason I made you, Kaga's daughter, an executive?
I have high expectations for you.
Don't disappoint me.
Look here.
Yeah!
This is the home of the gang.
What should I do?
I'm so nervous and want to pee.
Sir
We can't hold back.
You are the one who picked this fight.
Okay!
Let's show the volunteer group's spirit!
Yeah!
Let's do it.
Let's do this.
Where is the bathroom...
Say...
Are we storming in for a fight?
Why are you standing?
You don't want to die, do you?
You are the boss.
What? What is that?!
I'll kill you!
I'm sorry!
Ah, no.
Where is it?
I see this is the house of the gang.
Let me introduce myself.
Huh?
My name is Shogoku Hashima.
What?
Done!
Out of arrows.
Does anyone have extras?
No! Stop it!
If you move around, you'll cut yourself.
Let's do it.
Here!
It hurts!
It feels good doing it during battle.
I'm cumming!
No! Don't cum inside!
It felt so good.
I told you not to cum inside.
I thought there would be a bathroom outside.
I hope nobody comes here.
What is that?
No, don't come here.
I can't stop peeing
Smell of...
women!
Hey, Tsujiya.
How's your husband?
We're separated because of you.
My fault?
Please don't.
Don't play with me.
A newlywed wife is very tempting.
No!
Stop!
My husband is coming home.
No.
If I cum... If I cum...
My husband...
I'm cumming!
Darling...
You raped somebody's wife.
You are so low!
Your husband came home late.
So I ate you before he did.
Don't treat me as food.
Die, asshole!
You are too young to point the gun at me.
Let me go.
You are as wet as before.
This horrible gang.
You are as tight as before too.
Of couse
I haven't done it since you raped me.
Why?
It's your fault!
No, I hate that...
You are making me cum agian.
Don't touch, my asshole... you sick fuck.
Stop it!
What are you talking about?
It feels good.
It went in easily.
I'm cumming!
Hey! Toko.
How are you?
I heard you are the executive instead of Kaga.
First of all, why don't you put that away?
When did you come back?
I got out of jail a month ago.
Help me!
Somebody...?!
There is no one to help others here.
Give up.
Please don't. I'm married.
I don't care.
No. Don't!
Please stop it!
Who the hell are you?
Don't interrupt me.
Help me!
Shut up!
I have one months worth of sperm.
No!
Don't! Don't cum inside!
Stop it!
You are disgusting!
Stop it! No!
We only permit labor from men.
Other than that, men are worthless.
Here you go.
Minka-chan, you are always cheerfull.
I can work at this restaurant agian.
I can't get depressed.
Minka-chan, could you take my order?
Okay
Liver, leek pan fry, and ramen, right?
Welcome...
Hey
Huh, Akuji...
Akuji!
I'm glad you are okay.
The war was over but you didn't contact me.
I was in jail.
I came here right after getting out of there.
Forgive me.
Then, you haven't gone back to your home?
Is something wrong with the family?
I see.
Akuji
Please stop being in a gang.
Even if that is your wish, I can't grant it, Minka.
My father was killed in the war and my grandpa is missing.
There is no one else.
Akuji
Why can't I go inside?
This is my house
Well, but its's the order from the boss.
Boss?
Boss
Don't make a fuss. Get out of here.
There is no place for you here.
Weren't you the twenty-sixth lover of my grandpa.
No, you were twenty-seventh?
I'm Ran Ichihashi, the fourth of Wankame-gumi.
I wondered who the boss is.
It's just the lover of my grandpa.
I'm sure I'm better than your father.
I don't care, but this is my house.
I guess you prefer fighting to discussing
Kill him!
Don't hesitate because of me.
Come on fight with your full might!
You will die there.
Why don't you count on your bad luck?
It shouldn't have been this way.
You woke up.
Where am I?
This is the headquaters of the volunteer group.
Even the ambulance won't come, if the patient is a man.
The volunteer group?
We help the people who are unhappy because of the war.
Who are you?
I'm the leader here.
My name is Yoka Aoba.
I see.
When you were raped, was that a part of the volunteer?
No it was not!
I was on the way back from visiting an old woman who lost her son.
To kill the group, I'd better make a new group.
My body is weak after being in jail.
I need to train.
Please stop.
No. Please stop.
You are very wet.
It seems that you've been waiting.
You are so wet.
You've waited for so long, haven't you?
I'm embarrassed.
Don't talk about it.
Then, put it in your mouth.
What? What is it?
What is it?
This.
Wow!
You are good at it.
I'm sorry, my dear husband....
I can't take any more.
I'm cumming!
What is this all about?
I redecorated your office.
Isn't it neat?
I haven't had a Shinto altar for a long time.
Where should I put this?
Mirai-san, Tomoko-san you are helping out. Did you...
Of course, I did.
Don't look. I'm embarrrassed.
Is it your first time?
Yes
I don't think its a good idea.
Yoko will scold me.
She won't get mad at you.
She did the same.
I feel funny.
My body is out of control..
Relax. Mine's the best in the world.
How can i relax?
I'm cumming. Somehow I'm cumming.
Eating is my happiest thing.
I'll teach you another happy thing.
How is it?
I'm happy!
That's the story.
Well, I had a hard time.
I got surrounded by other people while i was talking.
I'm not like before.
I'm in good shape now.
I can play with anyone of you, but prepare yourself.
I'll take your life.
Don't, Toko.
It won't do any good to serve that bitch.
What are you doing?
You haven't gotten rid of him yet?
You are useless.
You finally came out.  I thought you'd run away.
I thought you'd ran away.
What is that?
I called him form Shikoku.
Suteki Ishi, stop laughing. Do your job!
It's show time!
A Monster...
Fuck. I should've been more careful.
Knock him out! I'll finish him off!
Shit.
Motoko, what are you doing?
Toko, you..
Run away now.
I'll be back.
He is running away. Follow him, Dekao!
Not this way, not this way!
Let's go, Akuji-san.
Let's go home.
Let me go! Shut up!
I'll pardon you for today.
You disappoint me, Motoko.
If you want to kill me, do it right now.
You are an idiot. I won't let you go that easily.
Boss are you sure about this?
Yeah. Do it from the back or the front as you like.
You are so lucky.
They are both virgins.  Really?
Really?!
I have a hard on already.
Don't think of killing yourself.
If you do something stupid, I'll kill you father.
No!