Here before god and all these witnesses, even in times of sickness and health...
The two shall swear to love each other affectionately until death you do part.
My name is Takega Satsu.
l'm 18 years old.
Upon Akuji's grandfather's request, l am having a wedding ceremony today
This man will be my husband, Yamamoto Akuji.
From this day on, l will be Yamamoto Satsu.
DAIAKUJI 7
Now, you may kiss your bride.
Akuji! Your life is mine!
Forgive us!
Master! Master!
Did l get him?
During my wedding ceremony! Morons!
Akuji!! lan, Kilika, go!
Your life...
ls mine!
Ha, ha, ha...
Retreat!
Yes...
Whew...you're pretty good for a kid.
l'm an adult now
Really?
Here.
Your driver's license...
Where...
Damn, a class C and A license?
Do you want to see my licenses for the plane and the boat?
Nope...
l also have a license for explosives.
Now have l proven to you that l'm old enough?
Yeah, l got it.
You're grown up, an adult.
But why are you suddenly my wife?
lt's your grandfather's wish.
Are you okay with that?
What? What?
l don't mind you calling me "Sat-chan."
Umm...
Oh yeah, you want some tea?
Yes, please.
Hey, aren't you making some tea?
Yes...
l thought a newlywed should wear this to make tea.
Umm...
Shouldn't l?
Well, that's if it's the husband's request or not.
That's not your request?
Quite frankly, l'm not interested in that.
Sorry, l never knew that you weren't interested in women.
No! That's not the point!
You are still like...
Like what?
Like a little... not matured.
Are you saying l have not developed? You want big breast or something?
You have a problem with the way l look?
Well, l'm not trying to get into a fight.
Hey.
Don't worry. l won't make life hard on us.
Let me see under your skirt.
Why?
Aren't you my wife, Sat-chan?
Cute panties.
This was the only one that would fit.
You look cute when you blush.
How long are you going to...
We didn't have our kiss of oath yet.
But, why here?
ln this situation, the wife shouldn't complain.
Very cute breasts.
You want to say that they're small?
Still angry? My bad.
But size and sensitivity are different.
First time being touched by a man?
Looks like it.
What are you doing?
Just be quiet.
Wait. l don't mind doing it, but l'm still a virgin.
l know.
l think l know how to treat a girl.
l see.
You have beautiful skin.
Spread open a little bit.
Like this?
Let's see.
Leave you knees there.
You're more sensitive than l expected.
No wonder you're a virgin.
Stay still. l'll make you feel good.
Relax your whole body
Right. Enjoy this pleasure.
Wha...what.
Wait, my strength...
Good. You'll land right here.
What do you want to do? l feel weird.
lt's not weird, it's being feminine.
This is being feminine?
Right. Feel your body getting pleasure...
The lustfull and sexy part of a woman.
Right.
lf you learn this, you'll be a very charming woman.
There, try to feel it.
How's that? Feel good?
Come on, say it.
l make you feel good.
Feels... good... but...
Something... something's coming!
No, Focus until the last moment.
Bu...But...
No, no.
No...
l can't hold it...
Good. Release everything.
No...
Something's coming... coming...
l'm cumming... cumming... cumming...
Akuji...
Now it's your turn to put in some work.
My turn...
l'm sure you studied what to do, right?
Ye, yeah...
Very nicely done.
When you're licking, look at your partner's face.
Like this?
Then with your open hand, massage the balls.
Good. You're very good.
Oh yeah, since your mouth is so small, it's hard for you to swallow the whole thing.
l'm all right.
Don't force yourself.
Don't worry about me.
This girl...
Nice...
l'm cumming!
Ready?
Please.
Don't force yourself.
Just let me handle you.
Got it.
They say smaller nipples are more sensitive.
l'm putting it in...
Your so tight. Relax, Sat-chan.
l'm trying to relax myself.
Really?
Ouch, ouch...
Are you okay?
Yeah, just make love to me.
ls that what you want...
Please!
Oh man...
Ouch...
Fucking shit...
Ouch!
A little more... a little...
Sorry.
You...
l'm alright. Let's get...
Let's stop.
What?
Well leave it here for today
Huh?
lf you're in that much pain, it's harder for me.
l'm sorry.
Well, let's just take our time, all right?
Oh no...
No!
l see, so that's why you came to talk with
me.
Yes, is my pussy too small?
No that's not true. Perfect timing...
Behold...the purity of a woman.
With training, you too can handle something as big as this.
No, no. Not that big.
lt's going in.
Behold.
Does this look like a face full of pain to you?
How is it? Does it hurt?
No.
Tell me how it feels.
lt feels good.
No, that's not right.
lt feel's good, master.
Great. Nicely done.
Now, the next step.
Let's see...
Ohh, good timing. Look at this.
There. The pussy is spread wide open.
No, don't spread it.
lt's so soft. Try touching it.
A delicate touch...
Feels great...
Now do you understand? With proper training it can stretch even more.
Yeah.
What's waiting is a splendid world!
Hey, don't stop now. Give me more...
Akuji, let's go to the hot springs.
Huh?
We're leaving tomorrow morning, okay?
Hey, what do you mean, "okay"?
There will be no excuse for oversleeping.
Hey wait! Why to the hot springs?
Our honeymoon.
Huh?
Honeymoon!
We're here.
Welcome!
He, hey...
We made a reservation under Yamamoto.
Oh, yes, yes, we were expecting you.
Huh?
May l help you?
Yeah, l just have a feeling that we've met before.
Come on! Stop trying to flirt with me in front of your sister!
l'm not his sister. l'm his wife!
Huh?
What?
What!
This is like paradise.
You sound like an old man.
Well, l came here just for the heck of it, but the hot springs feel good.
What's that you're wearing?
Would you like a swig?
Oh yeah.
This is it!
Beautiful scenery with a good hot spring.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
This hot spring has the effect of making your pussy softer.
l see. That's why you suddenly wanted to come here.
Leave it to me.
lt's a lot softer than before.
Really? l can't really tell.
You're so cute.
l'm starting to get horny,
Let me handle it.
How is it?
You got better, didn't you?
Why do you do so much?
l want to make you feel good.
lf you're worried about me cheating, then don't.
One day...
No, l just wanted you to feel good, Akuji.
That's all it is.
Sat-chan.
l want you to fuck me first.
Hey...
Ready?
Wow...
You have a gorgeous body
That's very good.
That feels great.
l'm getting ready to cum pretty soon.
l'm going to fuck you here. Understand?
Here...
Yeah, l'm putting my dick in.
That's going in?
Don't you want it?
Stick it in!
l want to feel all of you, Akuji.
l'm going in.
Ouch!
A little more...
Little more...
Ouch...
Relax.
More...
l'm going in!
l'm going to start moving.
Wait. lf you do that now...
Don't worry. Once it's in, it's all ok.
Ouch...
Starting to feel better...
My pussy feels hot...
Akuji...Akuji...
Akuji...
Don't worry.
You're my wife.
Akuji...
Akuji!
l'm cumming soon.
lt's coming, coming. l feel it...
Cumming...
Me too...
l'm cumming, cumming!
The wind feels good.
Yup...
How does it feel being a woman?
l don't really get it. But l feel like l'm yours.
Looks like you haven't got enough.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Not acceptable? l heard guys like this stuff.
No.
l'm all right. Come over here.
Akuji...
lt's in...
lt's tight!
Sorry, but...
Good, just feel it!
How is it? Doesn't hurt anymore, right?
l'll fuck you inside out.
lt's opening... Everything...
No, lt's going to rip!
lt's in all the way
No, not this... not this...
Just cum. Forget everything, and become a full-grown woman.
Give me everything you've got.
Deep...it's so deep...
Wha, what?
People will see...
Something's coming.
lt's only a dream.
Mommy! Daddy says he wants your help!
He said he's going to beat up the fools in Shigi-kai!
What are you doing?
You too!
l see.
l'm going now
Oh, mistress, they've been waiting.
Hey, Sat-chan. Sorry about that.
Yup...
Take care!
Have fun storming the castle!
Leave it to me! Let's go, guys!
YEAH!!