Break time's over.
No, please
Hey, don't let go of your mouth!
Suck this one too.
Great sound
Isn't it a honor as a father to be able to watch your daughter in her precious moments?
Motoko!
A virgin two days ago and now she's like a professional.
Probably sucked a hundred cocks in three days.
No!
It's show time!
No, stop
No!
No, no!
She's saying she can't wait!
It hurts!
No! It's gonna rip, it's ripping!
Stop!
No, no! I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
Not too bad.
Boss.
Akuji?
This sound interesting.
Prepare to head out!
Yes Ma'am.
You should relax and watch because the show will continue longer.
DAIAKUJI 2
It is over from today.
Is this the job of the youth service group?
Yes, our job is to be of service for the community.
You are to do plenty of service for the gentlemen in this community.
With your dirty body.
What do you mean dirty?
Isn't this dirty?
I touch you gently and it's rock hard.
What's the matter?
Because, you...
This has been giving your pussy a pleasure since the day you came here.
You love this don't you?
No I don't.
Lying isn't good.
You want this right now to fuck with your pussy, don't you?
No I don't.
I see.
Then let's call it quits.
This finger has rubbed your clit and gave you the melting satisfaction.
The hot breath, and this tongue has licked you all over.
This fat one will never satisfy you ever agian.
You can't satisfy yourself.
If you want it, I told you what to do, didn't I?
Can you not speak?
Please...
When you ask for something, you ask for it clearly.
Please do more dirty stuff to me!
Very well.
So you like to be dirty?
Yes
Today is your graduation exam.
Proceed
Are you a dirty bitch?
I will ask agian, are you a dirty bitch?
Yes! I'm dirty, I'm a dirty and a nasty bitch.
Well done.
Just like I expected.
Shimamoto and the others are working at the site.
Keep up the good work.
Where to, Master?
Going out to eat.
What are you up to?
Rumors say that the youth service group are making money by prostitution.
Maybe.
Maybe? Are you for real?
I can't let Wakame-gumi have stuff their own way.
To do that, we need money.
Here, thanks for waiting.
It's hot!
You deserve that for mistreating women.
Minka-san
You came back alive, but you repeating the same thing over.
Have it you way!
Minka-san
Shit, man.
I'll leave the money here.
Stupid Akuji.
Who are these people?
Don't you know?
They are new recruits of the youth group.
New recruits?
The one in the glasses is Shimamoto Jun.
He was an ex-staff member of the Wakame-gumi.
The guy with the round eyes is Oasugi Tsuyoshi.
He was Akuji's training coach in Wakame-gumi.
He is very strong.
He was training with Akuji yesterday.
And the beauty over there is Kanbara Yuko.
She was the sex trainer for Akuji, and she too is very strong.
She also was Akuji's first experience.
First experience...
Hey, I'm back.
Welcome home, Aa-kun.
What happened after?
We finished purchasing Ikoma and Heguri.
Master, what shall we do with the hostages?
Oh yea, we have to do something soon.
All right, I have an idea.
Bring the hostage over here.
Just what I expected from Aa-kun.
What do you mean just what you expected?
Doing this kind of thing...
Didn't you get some too?
But he must be crazy saying that after five minutes, she could stab him.
Don't worry. Just observe.
Would you like to work for my place?
No, I don't...
It's so soft...
It's like flooding down here.
I feel it. It feels like it's not my body.
How does it feel?
I guess it feels good.
If you open any wider...
Oops, that's five minutes.
It's a promise.
Stab me with that knife if you want to.
Or do you want me to continue?
I can't do it.
Good girl.
Good, Aa-kun wins.
For your reward, I'll take you to the world of the unknown.
That big thing won't fit in...
I never had this before.
Don't cum yet.
It feels great.
No, I can't take it any longer.
I can't handle any more.
I can handle more.
That can't be, please cum, or else I'll go crazy.
That's all good.
Just go crazy as you like.
No, please...
Please forgive me...
Emergency!
We got a call from Wakame-gumi. They have Minka.
They want Akuji to go by himself.
What the fuck?!
Master, this is an obvious trap.
You should let our younger guys
It can't be like that.
Especially this situation.
Master...
I didn't cum yet.
This is straight being half dead!
What a nice body.
What are you...
Something very good.
What is that?
This is a Ouime brand love potion.
Maybe a little strong.
No, no, no, no!
My good luck charm.
This has a good reputation of working.
Sorry, but I can't take it.
Akuji
We live in a completely different world.
I'm not the guy who you should worry about.
Bye.
Please, please come back alive.
This is it.
Minka-san!
Don't come here!
What the...
You really came.
You must really have a crush on her.
You bitch!
What the hell did you do to her?
What you wanted to do.
We'll let you have plenty of fun.
Bitch
Lets get started.
But...
Didn't I tell you before?
If you don't do it, Akuji will go straight to hell.
Minka-san, don't listen to that bitch...
Akuji
Saying that you didn't want to do this, down here is like a fountain.
Because you...
Next, be of sevice with your pussy!
Noway...
No, don't...
Akuji
Akuji, I...
Minka-san
I feel strange.
It's so strange, but I can't stop.
Akuji, please move, or else I...
Minka-san
Akuji, Akuji...
I'm cumming, so please cum with me.
No, I'm cumming, cumming!
Huh? What the...?
We won't let you have all the fun.
Akuji, watch closely...
at how she'll get screwed by other dicks!
You fucking bitch
No, no...
What do you mean no? You're so wet.
No, this is because...
You have a sexy voice.
No. Don't do it so much...
Their tension was up there, so falling is fast.
No, I'm gonna lose it, please stop!
I'm gonna lose it. I'm losing it!
Your such a cutie.
No
It feels...
Good, It feels so good.
Minka-san!
Tell me what to do with this.
I want it.
Where do you want it?
In my mouth, I want it in my mouth.
You dirty slut.
It tastes good.
All right, next I'll fuck you from behind.
I'm taking this virginity.
No, stop, it hurts!
It only hurts in the beginning.
After it goes in...
It's coming in, coming in...
Where is it going in?
In my ass.
Deep, deep in my ass.
Come on, cum in front of Akuji.
I can't, Akuji.
I'm sorry, I can't handle any longer.
There, does it feel good?
Yes, good, it feels good.
Sorry, I'm cumming.
No, it feels good, I'm going to...
That'll teach you a lesson not to have beef with me.
Dekao!
Die.
What the...?
What's going on?
Just get the hell out of here!
You are...?
Don't mind me, what about the girl?
Yeah.
Stay away.
Minka-san
Sorry, I no longer can stay with you.
You saw me in there. I can't...
Minka-san!
Good bye.
Minka!
Master's aunt?
Yes, to be exact, I was born under Akuji's grandpa, Ippatsu, and one of his lover.
My name is Takeda Satsu.
You're an auntie at your age?
If it's hard to say, you can call me Sat-chan.
This is?
I found it on the floor.
Isn't this important?
She still had this...
It's Kaga's pops.
What is a Wakame-gumi member doing here?
I have a special favor for you.
A favor?
I want you to take care of Ran, no the Wakame-gumi.
I already have plans.
Shit...
Why does trouble come at such a bad timing?
Your everyday actions speaks for itself.
How dare you!
We're getting raided!
What the...
It's terrible!
Looks like Kaga's pops was behind this...
so we've allowed entry in this place.
There are traitors on the other side.
Plus, there's this really strong kid.
Don't be in such panic!
First, we need to take care of Dekao, or we have no chance.
For this occasion, I mixed a sleeping potion in his food.
Finish him while he's asleep.
He's not here.
That can't be.
Impossible!
Motoko!
Akuji
Your plans are too obvious.
I won't let you run away this time Akuji.
Dekao, kill him!
Too slow!
Dekao, attack!
This is for the finish!
Oasugi!
Master, use balance, not force. Strike the critical point!
Dekao!
All right
Eat this!
Now Master! Use what we did in training!
Okay
I can't believe I ended up like this.
Now I can have Akuji finish me off.
That won't happen.
Since I did most of the job, I get to fuck with Akuji.
Hell no, it's gonna be me.
Dream on! It's gonna be me!
It's gonna be me!
Me!
No! It's me!
Huh?
Fools
How you doing?
Don't talk to me.
I guess you're ok since you're talking back.
When will this stop?
Who knows?
While they were out, I've fed them with Viagra that will knock out an average man.
They'll probably fuck you until they die.
That can't be...
I'm cumming
No, stop. Don't fuck me any longer.
I couldn't find her after all.
Sorry, but now it's over with.
I still got shit to take care of.
So, have you decided to join the Wakame-gumi, no I mean the Akuji-gumi?
What are your plans after?
I'll take over Osaka.
Sorry for the interruption.
The Shikina region has a religious group on the rise.
A religious group?
They're called "Nako-kyo"