Stop! Stop or I'll scream!
Exams start tomorrow, so
nobody's really left at school.
No matter how loud you scream, I
don't think it'll reach the faculty room.
C'mon, teach! It may not look like
it, but we're pretty stressed out.
We just wanna blow off steam!
St... Stop joking around!
This is no joke!
No!
The only reason we're doing this
is because you're so attractive.
We can't help ourselves!
Shinji, give me a shot at her!
What?
You tape it. I'll do her.
But you said you just wanted to tape it.
I changed my mind.
Alright already.
This is gonna hurt a
little bit, but bear with it!
There's something I
really want to do with you.
Wow! What a great shot!
Shinji, make sure you get this!
OK... I got it!
Shinji! Are you getting this?
Ye... Yeah.
So what would you do if
someone sees this tape, teach?
Like your boyfriend or a
co-worker or a family member...
You don't want that to happen, do you?
So let me do whatever I want to you.
It'll only take about two hours.
I'm so happy you're listening to me.
Satoshi's a little extreme today.
No. What we're doing
here is just fucked up.
So it's not just him!
She's really good. This is
how an adult gives head.
Ah... That's awesome!
I've done this a lot though
so I don't come easily.
Let me help you out a little.
Satoshi, can I join in?
I'm gonna come just watching you.
Fine. Suit yourself. Set
the camera on the tripod.
Alright.
Let's get this over with!
Shut up, Shinji!
It's no fun if you don't
take the time to play.
Don't just tape her ass.
Get her face! Her face!
That's more important!
I'm not really into this...
Wow! You can really hold it, teach!
Let's try one more.
C'mon! Let it all come gushing out!
You only teach freshmen so you don't
have to worry about us after this year.
Ah... I can't...
Shinji, be sure to get this!
We got some great footage today.
I've had my eye on her for a while.
And older women are
better than I expected.
I guess.
Looks like we'll get A's on
the Japanese Classics test.
No need to study for that.
I'm looking forward to
seeing her face on exam day.
One good thing after another.
Shinji?
What?
Let's do your teacher someday too.
I know you're into her.
That woman has a great body!
Y... yeah.
This is gonna be fun!
Are there any questions?
Teacher! Over here.
Y... Yes.
About this one here...
Which one?
Nobody else notices that
she has a vibrator in her.
Excuse me?
It... It can't be... Yagami?
Sh... Shinji...
Shinji!
Oh, Miku. It's you. What's up?
Ah... Well...
What is it? Say it!
Yeah... You see...
Shinji!
Hey, you're late so
I came to see what's up.
Sorry. Something came up.
This is Miku lino from
my class. You know her.
You guys've been friends
since you were kids, right?
Hi!
Hello.
We'll talk later.
I have to go now. See you.
Something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Chika!
Hey! You're not coming to
club today? Exams are over.
No, I got my period.
Oh, OK.
Chika, can you sneak out for a little
bit? I wanna show you something cool.
Something cool?
Yep. You'll love it!
Music Room
No!
Please don't! Leave me alone.
This music room has soundproof walls.
Nobody in the hallway can
hear anything from in here.
Cute breasts!
No!
Stop, Shinji!
Let Nana do it.
Me!?
Yeah. Strip.
Good. This is gonna be amazing!
Right, Shinji?
Y... yeah.
Here, Shinji, you take this.
Huh? OK.
Time for a little experimentation.
Both of you, spread your legs
and show me your pussies!
We have to do this at the same time
or we won't know the difference.
I see. They are different...
Their body temperatures
and tightness are different.
Shinji, did you see that? They even
react different to the same thing.
Y... Yeah.
Good. Let's try two.
Three!
It hurts!
You won't die. This is nothing
compared to giving birth, right?
Next! Four!
Shinji! These girls are awesome!
Satoshi's totally fucked up!
What's wrong with him?
But if I blame Satoshi I
also have to blame myself.
I'm just as much
a criminal as he is.
I know. I know that.
But it's so exciting knowing
how wrong this is.
Once you know what it
feels like, you can't stop.
Don't bite! Don't use your teeth!
I'm coming!
This is so fucked up.
Yeah?
Miku! What's up? It's late.
I know. Can I?
Yeah. Come on in.
Thanks.
So...
...what do you want?
Yeah... Well... I'm sorry
if I'm wrong about this.
Shinji, you've changed
since meeting Kojima.
There's something weird about him.
I don't know what it is
but he creeps me out.
And with all these crazy
things happening at school...
Like with Kamimura, and Miss
Himenogi right before exams.
Are you saying you think that I've
got something to do with that?
I don't know. But...
...you were laughing when the
teacher was acting all strange.
I was shocked because
you're not that kind of a guy.
You're the kind of person who
helps people if they're in trouble.
Isn't that right?
You understand people's pain.
If the Shinji I know is doing
something wrong, please stop!
Stop what?!
Do you have any evidence?
Not really, but...
Hello?
It's me. Your teacher
is all alone, working late.
What do you say?
Tonight?
Are you coming?
Yeah. Yeah. OK. I'm on my way.
Well, I have to go.
OK. Bye.
Shinji...
...What's going on with you?
He was in a hurry.
What was that phone call? Tonight?
See you next time!
See you!
So how was my
English test score?
I think I did pretty good this time.
Well... I haven't checked them yet.
I'm just so busy with this club.
I see...
I'm gonna stay late and grade
five sets of papers tonight.
I'll be correcting until I die.
Good luck!
Shinji!
What are you guys doing?
He told me he really wants to fuck you.
Hey, I didn't say that!
You don't want to?! Suit yourself then.
I'll have her all to myself.
That's...
You coward! So for now, you just tape.
Shinji! Are you taping this?
Hey, Shinji. Look what a slut she is.
She may try and deny it
but her body is loving this!
You wanna do her?
Put the camera on the tripod!
What? I can't hear you.
What are you saying?
More! Don't stop! Give me more!
What?!
I worked at an S&M club in college.
It's been a while since I had sex
like this. I'm so fucking horny!
Do me harder! Do you
have a whip or candles?
How awesome is this?!
You're quite a teacher!
Come on! Fuck me raw!
It's no fun if you're into it.
We only tape girls who
don't want us to fuck them.
What do you wanna do, Shinji?
I don't wanna.
Really? Maybe I'll stop
too then. I'm pretty tired.
No! Once you start,
you can't stop like this!
Miku!
Shit! She saw us.
I know.
Wait!
She definitely ran in here.
Hey!
Miku, we know you're in here.
Come out.
Hey, Miku! We won't
hurt you. Come on out!
Miku, you didn't
see anything, right?
Was it you guys
who raped Kamimura?
Yeah. Her and more. We had
our way with every one of them.
Disgusting! How could you?!
Did he force you into this?
Hey, hey! I don't like to be
made the bad guy here!
We're just good friends with the
same interests. Right, Shinji?
Shinji!
You know how we shut
noisy women up, right?
I know...
But...
What? It would be too weird
fucking your childhood friend?
Is that it?!
I thought shit like that
only happened in novels.
Sex is all that exists
between men and women.
Love... Trust...
There's no such thing!
It's all bullshit!
I remember now. You two played
doctor when you were kids, right?
Don't you wanna see how
this little girl's grown up?
If you're really a man,
you'll want to see it.
Looks strange.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't! If you close your legs,
I can't give you a check up.
I'm your doctor!
Have a look!
Let me see.
You've changed, Miku.
I see your pussy's enjoying this.
Your clit is getting swollen.
I envy you, Shinji.
Enjoying this kind of play.
Miku, take a look at this.
Look how big mine's gotten.
I didn't expect to
get so excited with you.
Shinji, I can't help myself.
Let me do her too.
This is amazing!
She's so fucking tight!
It's great! You're doing great!
Shinji, it's my turn.
Let her taste me too.
OK!
Wow! She's really good.
This is awesome!
Miku... I'm coming.
Miku, I'm so happy.
You've become such
a beautiful woman.
The real deal starts now.
No! It hurts. I'm gonna die.
What are you talking about?
What a little whore!
Hey!
Satoshi, that's enough! Stop it!
Satoshi!
Shut up! The fun is just beginning!
What?!
I'll tell them everything!
I'll tell the school, the police, our parents...
No one talks like that to us!
Satoshi, stop it!
This bitch just said she'd tell
them everything. You want that?
That's...
This is no good. So...
She has to die!
No... No!
Satoshi!
Nooo!
Stop!
Soon after, Satoshi dropped out of school
and was placed in a mental institution.
Now that he's gone, Miku has
been keeping an eye on me.
No more raping or rough sex for me.
I'm not into watching stuff
like that anymore either.
Not so much out of regret but out of fear
that I'd end up like Satoshi if it went on.
Shinji, you've been
very quiet these days.
But you're already well on
your way to being like Satoshi.
But maybe if I push you little, you'll
get right back on track again.
All men are nothing
but beasts anyway.
Who do you want to rape next?