There's been a popular rumor about some
porno website floating around school recently.
They say that at the site...
... you can see pictures of girls
from our school being raped.
And that the pictures were
all taken in our classrooms.
It was nothing but a rumor...
Until that day...
When it happened...
Go to the nurse's
office second period.
The nurse's office?
Why?
You'll see.
Just be there.
Wh... What are you doing? Stop!
I'll scream for help.
It's her.
This is it!
This is what I've been waiting for!
How's this? Smells good, no?
I'll make you come too!
Yeah! I'm gonna come! Inside you...
Hey, Yagami!
Oh, you're from the
class next to mine.
I'm Satoshi Kojima. I heard you're
pretty good with computers.
I'm no expert but I
know my way around them.
And you?
A little.
Here. This is a secret gaming site.
Check it out sometime.
That was a crime.
What's going to happen to me now?
Would you like to live openly,
indulging in all your secret fantasies?
I'm hard!
It's no big deal. It happens
sometimes when you can't relax.
Or you don't think I'm attractive?
I was worried at first when
I didn't enjoy normal sex.
But ever since I found this
site, I'm really enjoying sex.
It's encouraging to know there
are others like me out there.
Was that really the
girl from the pictures?
Yeah. What did you think?
She was great.
But how did you know she'd
be in the nurse's office?
Does it really matter?
How was it?
Did she satisfy you?
Yeah. I was so turned on.
That was your first time, right?
Yeah.
Congratulations!
Goodbye, cherry!
Lino! What are you doing?
I... I'm sorry.
We've got only three days
left to train. Concentrate!
Yes!
But that was rape, wasn't it?
I violated her.
What if she tells the
school or the police?
Don't worry.
But...
Shinji!
Sex means you can do whatever
you want to the other person.
If you worry about your partner's needs and
wants you'll only end up stressed yourself.
I guess so.
Who do you want to rape next?
Next?
You were watching me swim
yesterday, weren't you?
Not really. I wasn't watching you.
Really? I'm disappointed.
I'm joking. You take
everything so seriously.
Don't screw with me like that!
But I'm not lying either.
You broke up with
me six months ago.
I haven't had a boyfriend since.
See you.
Did you get back
together with her?
Oh, it's only you, Miku.
Only me? Thanks.
Sorry.
So how are things with Nana?
There's really nothing going on.
Why did you break
up with her anyway?
She's really cute. It's a shame...
Hey! Are you even listening?
What'd you do that for?
You were spacing out.
Aren't you getting off? It's your stop.
Shit! Gotta go.
He hasn't changed a bit.
Student Council
Sex means you can do whatever
you want to the other person.
Well, that's about it. We just
need to throw away the garbage.
Y... Yagami?
What's up?
Nana... let me fuck you.
What?! Just because you say so?
Stop it! Don't be so rough!
Yes! It has to be like
this or it's pointless.
Nana... I know you
still like me. Right?
If you do, do as I say! Suck it!
But...
Listen to what I tell you. Do it!
Is that the best you can do? You
can do better. Use your tongue!
Good! I knew you could do it.
You should have done
this right from the start.
Too good to use your hands?
But this is just not fun. It's too normal.
Good. I'm about to come.
Don't spit it out.
Swallow it!
Nana! Look at the monitor!
Your pussy is enjoying this.
No...
Look!
Check it out. You're
getting wet. Look at this!
This is next.
Wh... What are you going to do?
That hurts!
Be quiet! What happens if
someone sees you like this?
Yeah! This is amazing!
This is the best sex ever!
Remember! These images will last forever.
I have to shoot it carefully as
someone might see this tape.
Please... Don't show anybody!!
If you don't want me to show
this to anyone, listen to me!
I'm gonna come!
Nana, be sure to
throw away the garbage.
It's just like you said.
If you do whatever you
want when having sex...
...you feel almost more
alive when doing it.
It's like "I fucking did it!"
That's good to hear.
I taped it. Wanna see it?
A porno starring Shinji Yagami?!
That I'd like to see.
Let me check it out.
So who are you going to rape next?
Next?
Yeah. Your next target.
Who do you want to rape next?
Are you the one who made that site?
That really doesn't matter.
What's important is your next target.
Is there anyone you have in mind?
Well... No. Not really.
Then how about you do
the next one with me?
With you? You mean like
we double-team some girl?
Exactly.
Who?
Someone everybody in school knows.
To prevent theft, we will
keep all the clubroom keys...
...in the principal's office
and the faculty room.
Please make sure you
return them when finished.
You are not allowed
to make spare keys.
Next week we will meet to go over
last semester's club activities.
Captain's meetings...
Megumi Kamimura?
...will be held as usual after midterms.
Isn't she president of the student council?
Yeah. She took the job
because nobody else wanted it.
She's a straight arrow
and an easy target.
I'm sure she's still a virgin too.
She's definitely worth raping.
I've got a student council meeting.
Make something up and blow it off.
Well... But...
His parties are always a blast!
You can't miss it!
You'll regret it!
Come on! Let's go!
Hello.
Hey, Yamamoto.
What are you doing? You're late!
Huh? Your mom's in the hospital?
Really? Yeah, I understand.
OK, I can handle it by myself.
Take care of your mom.
I always end up alone.
Yagami and Kojima?
What's up? Can I help
you with something?
Help us?
Yeah. You can help us
with something important.
So you're all alone here today?
Don't worry! We'll help you out...
and you'll have a good time!
No!
OK! Everything's ready.
So this is the smell of a virgin?
Hey, Miss President, you
are a virgin, aren't you?
You have to be, right?
Answer me!
See. I told you.
Good guess!
Shinji, you're a real pervert.
I'm proud of you.
The taste of a virgin...
Poor girl. You're still a virgin, right?
Take it easy on her if she's too tight.
Do you know what this is?
You use it down here.
How's that?
This feels a little bit better
than my finger, right?
Miss President, you look so innocent.
I'm surprised you've got such huge tits.
Shinji, with breasts that big
I bet you can tittie fuck her!
Yeah? Let me try it.
Ah... Nice! This feels great!
Time for me to join the fun!
C'mon, Miss President, use
your tongue a little more.
Your future husband will cheat on
you if you can't give good head.
Suck me next!
Good. Keep going while you
put your ass up in the air.
Let's try this hole now.
That hurts!
Watch out! She almost
bit my dick off!
Sorry. Sorry.
How's that? Your asshole
isn't just for shitting.
I'm sorry.
I won't tell anybody.
Just please stop this.
You don't have to apologize.
It's entirely our fault.
Right, Shinji?
That's right.
Well, time for me
to get in there too.
It hurts!
You're pretty noisy.
This should shut you up.
Excuse me?
Kamimura! What happened?!
Who did this to you?
It can't be...
Yagami?!