Ayane, I'll definitely...
R
Ri
Rip
Ripp
Rippe
Ripped
Ripped B
Ripped By
Ripped By H
Ripped By Ha
Ripped By Han
Ripped By Hana
Ripped By Hanak
Ripped By Hanako
All right, be a good girl.
Little Mie...
Don't move.
I'll take you back to your owner.
Don't make your
owner worry too much.
No, stay away!
Be quiet.
We'll take you to your brother.
What are you big guys doing?
Why are they surprised?
Unbelievable, he's still alive.
In that case, we'll take care of you.
What?
Hey you!
Come with me.
Hurry up!
Shingo, just as I
hoped, you are all right.
What?
Ayane Akimoto?
Yes.
But I'm not your missing brother.
I'm just a detective.
Here.
Thank you very much.
Takayasu, you used that trick of
yours on an automatic pistol, didn't you?
Yes.
What type of gun?
Let me see...
Maybe, Browning?
I don't remember,
because I acted instinctively.
Be careful.
You can only use that trick
on a gun with a recoil slide.
What?
Otherwise, it could still fire.
You should be careful about that.
Excuse me...
Please help me, Mr. Higashino.
I'll give you any reward.
Takayasu, would you turn
your back on a crying girl?
All right, please tell me the details.
Yes.
Shingo...
You got back safely, did you?
It was a miracle.
Are you really Shingo?
Gosuke, because of
the accident, his memory is...
He lost his memory, did he?
Yes.
How did he ever survive that accident?
Shingo, you need rest, don't you?
Yes...
I see.
Go back to your room and recuperate.
All right.
Taizo!
It's OK.
We'll get the story later.
Sounds good.
Well, what happened here, I wonder.
Ayane's parents died...
...the family fortune was inherited by
Shingo and his adopted sister, Ayane.
Ayane's aunt, Kiyoe,
the sister of Shingo's father...
Her husband, Gosuke...
Kiyoe's brother, Taizo,
the brother of Shingo's father...
None of them got any inheritance.
Then, it was two months ago...
Shingo, Ayane's step-brother,
had an accident and died...
After that, Ayane was attacked.
I think it is trouble over the inheritance.
The question is, who is...
Yes, come in.
Ayane...
What's going on so late?
Shingo...
I missed you so much.
No, I'm not your brother...
Excuse me...
It's all right.
Please make me forget, Mr. Higashino.
Ayane...
Shingo, you are...
...fantastic.
Ayane.
I realized that...
I realized after Shingo had died...
I still love Shingo.
No...
I'm sorry.
Shingo, you are still hard.
You really are sensitive, aren't you?
You're getting wet.
Shingo, please love me...
It's all right, even if it's forbidden love...
Please...
Ayane.
I want you.
Please, Shingo.
You are good...
Shingo, it's so good...
Please, together...
Shingo...
Oh God, I finally made love with you.
Mr. Higashino, thank you very much.
Ayane, you are...
Mr. Higashino, you really
look like my step-brother.
Ayane...
Ayane!
I screwed up.
I didn't imagine they
would take action so soon.
Oh!
Kiyoe...
What's happening?
Was that Ayane's scream?
Have some...
It will relax you.
Thanks.
Where's uncle and the others?
They went out to find Ayane.
We should go to.
But, somebody has to stay here.
By the way, who are you really?
You're not Shingo, are you?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to lie.
How did you approach Ayane?
Why don't you become my partner?
I'll make you feel better
than such a young girl can.
What do you mean, auntie?
You are so rude to call me that.
Call me Kiyoe.
How's that?
You feel like your body is
melting completely, don't you?
What a waste of drugs.
You're gonna kill her, right?
We're gonna enjoy her body until then.
You can't stand any more, can you?
I mixed some drug into the drink.
The drug will make you very horny.
First of all, why don't
you tell me who you are?
I'll make you feel much, much better.
You want to feel better, right?
Come on, you won't be able to
control yourself if you don't tell.
I don't think so.
You can't fool me.
You're becoming horny to the core.
Looks like you're the
one who's getting hot.
What?
I noticed something wrong, so I
substituted your glass for mine secretly.
You're so bad.
How can you say that
after you set a trap for me?
Do you want it?
I want...
I want yours.
Can I come into your mouth?
Please come inside me.
Give it to me.
Make me feel good, please.
That's the way.
I'm going crazy.
I'm coming.
Don't stop!
Please tell me where Ayane is.
I don't know.
Don't play dumb, please.
If you don't tell, I'll stop.
All right, I'll tell you.
So please, give it to me now.
She is really enjoying it.
The drug is too effective, isn't it?
Never mind that, our boss is so strong.
How many times has he done it so far?
Please...
Give me more...
Who are you?
You are...
That's it...
I never knew there
was a basement here.
Good things are
sometimes right under your nose.
You're not Shingo, as I thought.
Come on, release Ayane.
Don't move if you
consider her important.
It's too late.
It's too late for you.
You as well?
Sounds like you are not Shingo.
But who cares?
You're going to die with Ayane.
It is a good story for us,
you'll kill Ayane and then yourself.
How do you feel?
Take a look before you die.
Ayane can't think of
anything but sex with the drugs.
Here, she looks happy.
Ayane is your adopted niece...
How can you do this,
even for inheritance?
Ayane and Shingo's father,
my and Kiyoe's brother...
...left a legacy for Shingo and
his adopted daughter, Ayane.
I will not forgive them.
There is another story...
I knew of the relationship
between Ayane and Shingo.
Although she grew
up to be so beautiful...
...she was innocent...
...and even though I
thought she led a happy life...
...she had a relationship
with her step-brother, Shingo.
I felt jealousy.
I think I wanted to rape her
because she was no longer innocent.
The whole idea originally came
from Kiyoe, who has a big debt.
We kill Shingo, and pretend
that he died in a traffic accident...
Then we get the inheritance.
We will kill Ayane
after we enjoy her body.
You aren't human.
Are you finished talking?
I really have a grudge against you.
Say good-bye.
You're kidding me, can it be...
...you are still alive.
No, you cannot be alive.
You changed my
looks a bit, but I am Shingo.
Shingo, you are...
Shingo!
Kiyoe is already waiting
for you in the pits of hell.
Wait, Shingo.
I came here only to pay you back.
Ayane...
Brother...
What's that?
I set fire to the mansion.
I guess something exploded.
What?
Come on, let's get out of here.
We are fine.
What are you talking about?
Hurry up!
Leave us alone and run away.
I can't.
There is no other way but
for us to finish ourselves.
Thank you for saving Ayane.
I appreciate it.
Good-bye, Mr. Higashino.
Ayane.
Shingo, Ayane...
After everything I did not save Ayane...
I'm disappointed about that.
That's life.
They'd already decided
that from the beginning...
...in order for her to be
with her step-brother forever.
I know, but...
Hello?
Come in.
Hey, your client is here.
Yes.
Did you find my cat, Mie?
Shit!