I like it!
Don't!
Let's see...
Stop, please don't look at me like that!
Shiori, your pussy's so wet now!
No, no, don't talk dirty like that!
It's embarrassing!
You're so sensitive, Shiori.
Look at this!
No, stop showing me stuff like that!
I'll make you feel good
with my monster cock!
Please, don't make me wait!
Here we go!
Oh, your cock is really big!
Yes!
You feel so good!
- I think I'm cumming!
- Me too!
Where do you want it?
My face!
You like that!
Hello, hello!
This is Shiori!
Can you hear me, Kathleen?
Yes, I can hear you clearly.
Did you obtain any information?
Yes, everything we need!
But that guy, Matoba,
was just really terrible in bed!
I didn't like it!
You can tell me all about that later.
So, what's going on with our target?
Let me see...
He's coming back to Japan in 3 days.
He will be at the usual restaurant
that night.
Well done! We'll see you soon
at the planned pickup point.
Roger!
Are you going to be ready?
Yes.
One week earlier...
Good morning, everyone!
About our latest mission:
This will be our target...
... Mr. Kusuhara, 66 years old.
I think everyone has heard of him before.
The president of Kusuhara Conglomerate.
He looks like a greedy bastard!
This is a mission
requested by Kusuhara's wife.
So you're trying to say
that the wife wants a child...
...but is asking for us to help?
Isn't that rather strange?
Yes, you're right.
But Kusuhara only married his current wife
to advance his career and also for money.
So, there is no real relationship
between the two.
No children.
So, Kusuhara no longer
has any need for his wife.
Yes, that's the situation.
A child will be her security
no matter what happens.
That's all for now.
Soda will give you the details.
I expect excellence out of
all of my DNA Hunters.
The agent selected for
this mission will be...
...Mai.
Y... Yes!
We found out that your appearance
comes closest to matching Kusuhara's type.
We've also found out,
after doing more research...
...that he's surrounded by bad, scary rumors.
Mr. Soda and I decided that
this would be a dangerous mission.
That's right.
It's usually one agent
assigned per mission.
This time, everyone will be involved.
Shiori, Masumi and I
will be backing you up this time.
Yes.
Yes, we'll all be helping you out!
Yeah, so you have nothing to worry about.
This is not going to be
like our standard mission.
Proceed cautiously.
Especially Mai.
Your position will be the most dangerous.
Please proceed with extreme caution.
Yes...
Kusuhara's entering the restaurant.
Mai, can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Kusuhara's just entered the building.
All you have to do is just follow the plan.
I got it.
Good luck!
Thanks.
I haven't seen you before.
My name is Mai, and I just
started working here a few days ago.
I see. Well, would you pour me some sake?
Of course.
So, do you know who I am?
Yes, Mr. Kusuhara.
I've been informed
that you are our VIP client.
I like you. You'll be mine!
You'll never have to worry
about money ever again.
No, please stop it!
- Stop resisting!
- No, no!
No, don't!
Just shut up!
Ouch!
I beg you...
...just be gentle with me.
If you don't like it,
why are your nipples hard?
That hurts!
No!
At least your body tells no lies.
Please, don't look at me like that!
Yes, that feels good.
I like that very much!
I think it's about time you suck my cock.
Good, now lick my balls.
You're good!
Mai, you like sucking my cock, eh?
Yes I do.
My cock hasn't been this hard in a while!
Boss?
Huh?
I was just starting to enjoy myself.
What is it, Matoba!
Boss, one of the pets
has escaped the residence.
What?
Why can't any of you bastards do your job?
I'm leaving now!
Damn!
- Mai!
- Yes?
Come to my mansion tomorrow at 3 P.M.
I'll be waiting for you.
Tomorrow at 3 P.M...
Everything is so easy when they're horny!
I don't know about this.
Huh?
Hearing all those rumors...
We all still need to be very careful.
This way; the boss has been waiting.
It's Mai.
Yes, please come in.
Thank you.
I've been waiting for you, Mai.
Hurry and come over here.
No!
Please, don't be rough like the last time.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
So, you'll be more obedient this time.
Okay, take off all your clothes.
What?
What is it? Were you just lying to me?
I... I wasn't lying to you.
Then, hurry up and get on with it!
Do you think the transmitter's broken?
It's the walls of his mansion.
Probably shielded to prevent
eavesdropping and such.
I hope Mai's doing okay!
We'll sit tight for a little longer.
You are definitely my type.
Let me look at you.
Come over here.
Let's see...
You're already getting wet!
Now you can make me hard by sucking on me.
Unless you get into it,
this will take a while.
Since you're not really getting into it...
...you need to be punished.
When did I tell you to stop sucking?
It's getting hard.
Keep sucking!
Go on, keep on sucking!
You can stop now.
On top of the bed,
on your hands and knees.
Y... Yes!
Now, lift your hips.
Your pussy tightens
every time I spank you!
Like it?
Yes, I love it, it feels good!
Like that!
Just like that!
I can't take any more!
Cumming!
Yes, yes, cum with me!
Yes, yes!
We still haven't heard anything from Mai!
I'm going out and get some fresh air!
Don't be long.
Got it!
All this waiting around business
is just not my style!
Huh?
What is that?
It's probably just roadkill.
Huh!
Oh, my God!
You're awake now!
Where am I?
You're in the van. Don't worry.
Thank God.
If you don't mind me asking,
what happened to you?
Yes, I'll tell you.
I got the goods,
and I think I'm done with the mission!
I need to get out while I can!
Mr. Kusuhara!
You left, so I was going to leave!
You're not in a hurry, are you?
I have a present especially for you!
Oh, no, that's not necessary!
Just turn around and
close your eyes for me.
Like this?
I think this will look nice.
You shouldn't have.
Th... This is...
Now you're going to be my pet forever!
Wait. Wait a minute!
No, get this thing off of me!
No, no!
Please stop joking around and let me go!
Now don't be scared!
I'm just going to
make you feel even better!
This is a potent aphrodisiac.
It's supposedly been used
since Emperor Nero's time.
When I apply this to your pussy...
...you won't be able to think about
anything but my cock!
Please, let me go!
- Just like this.
- No, no, no!
You'll like it!
It seems like the drug's already working!
I was working
as a maid at the Kusuhara residence.
Kusuhara forces himself
on pretty women...
...then drugs them
and keeps them as sex slaves.
I was unfortunately
one of them.
Yesterday,
I saw a chance to escape, so I did!
We need to get Mai out of there!
We need to get inside
Kusuhara's mansion.
I won't need this anymore.
Now, get on your hands
and knees like a good pet!
Yes!
I'm going to introduce you
to my other pets now.
My master!
Please make us feel good!
My pretty little pets!
Make your new friend feel welcome!
Then I will please you all!
Yes!
Please help. Somebody. Oh, Youji!
Over here!
I was surprised
to get a call from you, Shiori!
Because you're so good,
so I thought, you know.
Who is she?
I told her about you
and she wanted to meet you.
I see!
We should go inside instead of
standing out here.
Stop!
I'm sensitive there.
It feels so good!
Your nipples are getting hard!
You'll really like this!
I don't know if I can take
any more of this!
I love it!
I'm begging you, no more!
You're really a naughty little girl.
I'm going to blow your mind!
She's dripping wet!
Stop that, I can't take any more!
Yes!
I'm going to cum!
Oh, my God!
So, you'll be my little pet, right?
Oh, Youji!
Help me!
I can't. I'm really sorry!
Youji's your lover?
But nobody's going to come
and help you, darling!
Just forget him,
and be my pretty little pet!
- You'd like that, right?
- Yes!
You'll be in heaven every day
if you become my pet!
There!
If you want to be my pet,
you have to say it.
Say, "I want to be Mr. Kusuhara's pet!"
I want...
Huh, I can't hear you!
I want to be your...
Mai!
Who the hell are you
and where are my goddamn guards?
We were playing with this
when they all accidentally fell asleep!
All your guards are unconscious, too.
Shit, those stupid good for nothings!
I'm going to call the police right now!
Oh, you really think
what you're doing here is legal?
Shit!
You have something
coming from me, asshole!
You fucking bastard!
Oh, Mai!
Mai!
Mai, are you OK?
Hi, Kathleen. Hi, Shiori!
You're OK now!
Let's get out of here!
Masumi's waiting in the car!
Yes!
Kusuhara speaking.
Mr. Kusuhara?
Stay away from Mai and the others.
If you don't...
I understand!
I'll do as you say!
He cooperated as soon as
he heard the owner's name.
The mission was a success.
I'm glad!
- Where is Mai?
- She's at the cemetery.
I see.
Youji, I'm going to keep
doing this for a while.
I want your baby!
But why did you have to die Youji... my love.