Oh, Youji.
Oh, Mai.
Yes, sir.
Please accept my condolences.
Thank you for your understanding.
You two were going to be married!
This is so unfortunate.
Please don't worry about work
until you feel you're ready.
If there's anything I can do...
You are like a daughter to me.
My fiancée, Youji, died in
a mountain climbing expedition.
Leaving me all alone.
My last memory of him
is the night before he left.
Yes...
Your pussy tastes good, Mai.
I love you, Mai.
Ready?
Yes.
I can feel it!
Why are you stopping?
I think I want to change positions.
Here we go!
Yes... I would like that.
I'm going to cum!
Me, too.
I'm cumming!
- Youji?
- Yeah?
So this will be your last
mountain climbing trip, right?
Yeah, this will be the last.
I wouldn't want my new bride
to worry about me.
My research is at a critical phase.
Your research?
Normally, how are babies made?
By having sex.
Babies are made when
the sperm and egg come together.
The research I'm doing
makes it possible...
...to create babies from a piece of hair,
or from saliva on this cigarette.
So, Youji.
When we get married,
we'll have kids the normal way...
...instead of something like that, right?
Mai...
Come back home safely!
Don't leave me all alone.
After the trip, we'll be together forever.
Promise me.
Youji, you lied to me!
You said you wouldn't leave me all alone!
I wanted to be your wife!
I wanted to have your baby!
You can make babies
from saliva on a cigarette.
My condolences.
You were Youji's fiancée.
I'm really sorry.
About what I just said...
Yes, we have had successful animal trials.
It is theoretically possible
to create offspring...
...using genetic material from body parts
by extracting genetic information.
While we are confident that
we can duplicate the result with humans...
...it is no easy feat.
But you said that you were confident!
Yes, it's not a matter of
technological hurdles here.
It's all financial.
We still need millions to continue research.
It's not affordable for most.
But I just can't give up hope!
I want to have his baby,
a living proof of our love for each other.
I would be willing to do anything,
even sell my soul to the devil!
If you are that desperate...
I understand.
Please go to our branch office;
I will give you their address.
The director's name is Mr. Soda,
and I've known him since college.
They front as a research facility
but they might be able to assist you more.
He might be able to help.
3RD RESEARCH SECTION
Mr. Nozaki told me about your situation.
You must be Mai Sakakibara.
Yes.
Call me Mr. Soda.
Can you promise that you will keep
our conversation strictly confidential?
Yes.
All right.
This way, please.
Let me introduce myself.
I am the owner of GSC and all its branches.
It's nice to meet you.
We did a background check
on you prior to your arrival.
Mai Sakakibara, 22 years old.
Born in Saitama, living in Tokyo.
You are employed.
You work at Okazaki Inc.
As a trusted personal assistant...
... to the president of the company.
You lost your fiancée, the late Youji Ina,
our researcher, very recently.
I will briefly explain our business here.
There are many kinds
of women in the world.
Instead of having children
with their husbands or lovers...
... our clients want to have
exceptional children...
... with professional athletes, renowned
scientists, authors, painters, celebrities.
These are our most frequent requests
and our main targets.
We essentially arrange
to combine the client's egg...
... with the desired man's DNA material.
This is illegal, of course.
This is where you come in.
Your job is to get DNA material,
meaning ejaculate material...
... by having intercourse with the man
targeted by our female clients.
Mr. Soda will tell you more.
That is all I have to say.
It's your choice.
Do you think you can do this job?
Well, I'm going to have to think about it.
When you make your decision...
...please call or e-mail me ASAP.
Ms. Mai.
Ms. Mai!
Yes.
Sir?
Are you feeling all right?
I'm feeling fine, sir. I was just thinking.
Okay.
If you say so, but you know
I'm very worried about you.
I appreciate your concern, sir,
but I'm really all right.
Youji, do you think I should do this?
Otherwise, I can't have your baby!
Please understand.
I'm glad you've accepted.
I'll introduce you to the others.
I've been informed about you already.
So you must be our newest DNA hunter.
You will be working with everyone here.
Kathleen Bartlett.
Hello.
Masumi Saeki.
Hiya!
Shiori Fukatsu.
Nice to meet you!
This is Mai Sakakibara.
It's nice to meet everyone.
Please sit.
Yes.
Please bring the case.
The case? Right away!
Let's see, it's in here somewhere
Here, Mai!
Open it, Mai.
You just slide this switch over like this.
This is our specially designed,
female condom.
This is used to obtain
ejaculate from your target.
It's made not to leak
so you don't have to worry.
Afterwards, make sure
to close off the condom opening...
...and put it back in the case.
The case is also a GSC patent.
A specialized cooling device
is built into the case to ensure viability.
The device runs for 48 hours.
This is for you.
Please learn to insert the condom
correctly by tonight.
Yes.
It's a good idea to use a mirror at first.
And let me give you some advice:
Don't try to move your fingers
too much when doing this.
You'll like it too much.
You're so weird, Masumi!
Okay Mai. I want you
to be back here at 6 p.m.
This will be a test
to see if you can really do this job.
I want you to go out tonight
and obtain some ejaculate from a stranger.
It's not something that
can be taught with words.
This is just a test.
We'll make our final decision afterwards.
I know you're nervous
since this is your very first time.
If you just relax,
you can even have some fun.
Yes.
Let's see...
They look like an easy target.
Hey, you two.
Let's hang out together.
Yes, I love it!
Damn, this is my lucky day today!
I like that!
Oh, yeah!
Yes!
Yes, baby!
What's wrong?
Damn it.
Are you frigid or something?
At least your friend looks like
she's enjoying herself.
The best!
Baby!
I think I'm going to join those two
before I go limp.
No, wait!
Blow me.
She's fucking great!
Oh, yeah!
I'm gonna cum!
I heard about last night from Kathleen.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you another chance.
Please hand her the file.
Yes.
This will be your target.
But, I can't.
He's my target?
Yes, Mr. Okazaki, your current boss.
How can you do this to me?
You guys are sick!
How dare you say that!
We work based on orders from our clients!
We can't choose our targets.
You understand?
But, but...
I don't know.
Everyone that works here
does this because they have their reasons.
I know you have a reason
to be here as well.
Don't forget about that.
Tell me, Mai?
It's your decision.
I promise to complete my mission.
Mai, try to love your target
during your mission.
If you can't do that, this job isn't for you.
Got it?
Kathleen?
Yes.
Thank you.
No.
I'm happy to be of service.
But how strange!
You don't usually thank people.
Hey...
So Masumi...
Yeah?
Do you think Mai will be able
to pass her test this time?
Who knows?
You weren't mean to her
last night, were you?
Damn it, why would I do
something like that?
I hope she can pass
her test today and join us.
Yeah, me too.
Mai, try to love your target
during your mission.
If you can't do that, this job isn't for you.
Oh, Youji.
Please, give me the strength.
It's really too bad.
You've been through so much lately.
I didn't mean to resign
with such short notice, but...
No, no.
It's important to get
your life back together.
It's important to make life decisions
based on your happiness.
Yes.
I couldn't have asked for a better assistant.
But that's life, you know.
Well.
Wishes for happiness and joy in your life.
Wishes for your health and happiness, too.
Cheers.
Oh no.
Hey, are you feeling OK?
I hope I didn't keep you up too late.
No, I'm sorry I got so tipsy tonight.
I think I'll be all right.
I'll hail a cab to take you home.
Uh, sir...
Yes?
If you don't mind...
...will you grant me a final wish tonight?
Sleep with me?
But Mai!
Just for tonight.
I just want you to help me forget
all the sad, horrible feelings tonight.
- Oh sir!
- Call me Ryosuke tonight.
I think I've been trying
to deny my feeling for you...
...by telling myself you were
like a daughter.
Try to love your target
during your mission.
Tonight, sir...
Tonight, Ryosuke, I am your woman.
Thank you, Mai...
Oh, yes!
Oh, this feels so good!
I want you to feel good.
I like that you get so wet like this!
Don't stare too much down there.
It's embarrassing.
It's my turn.
Mai, I love it!
Swallow it!
Inside here!
So big!
I can't control myself anymore!
You're the best!
I think...
...I'm cumming!
Please cum inside me!
I'm cumming right now!
So Mai...
Yes?
After talking with the owner...
...you're in.
Congratulations.
You did well.
Congratulations, Mai.
I'm happy for you.
Mai, I'm so thrilled
you're going to be part of our team!
I'm glad we'll be working together!
I expect excellence out of
all of my DNA Hunters.
Yes!
Please watch over me, Youji!