First Annual Vanilla People's
Choice Award, story by Tarorin
Like Mother Like Daughter 1
Koichi...
Huh?
His cell phone...
He forgot to bring it.
Maybe I'll take a peek inside...
Why?
Tell me why Koichi...
He never lays a finger on me...
Well, you see Koichi...
We sleep in the same bedroom but
in different beds, right?
Why don't we just make it a double
bed?
Then you know...
We can spend our nights
together, as husband and wife.
Umm...
Not only do I have to play family
man...
...but I have to satisfy
your sexual desires as well?
I want it real bad...
I'm getting really wet from
excitement...
I want it inside me!
Come on! We're not related by
blood...
We don't have to do it now.
I'll be leaving this house soon, why
can't we wait until then?
I want to do it with you right now!
But I don't want our
parents to find out.
Don't worry about it.
Yukiko and the rest
are already sleeping.
Fine.
But be gentle with me, okay?
It can't be.
It can't be!
We're a family...
My clit is getting excited...
It went inside smoothly.
Maybe I can fit one more...
This is great!
If I don't do this, I'll go insane!
Come to think of it, your father is
visiting us today, right?
Should I order out for some sushi?
I don't care.
Do whatever you feel like.
Even if I see him, it's not like we're
going to have any fun.
Yuuki, Rio, what about you two?
What are we supposed to say?
Right?
Yeah.
I'll leave it to you, mother.
I'm sure that's the right thing to do.
Right Yuuki?
Huh?
Yuuki!
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
Okay, I'm heading out.
Me too.
Wait for me Yuuki!
See you later mother.
I have to make it really wet.
Will this fit?
It's going in...
It's going inside!
My pussy...
It sucked it inside...
Koichi...
Please, I really want to do it with
you...
Please...
I want the real thing!
I want a huge cock inside me!
This won't satisfy me!
It has to be much, much bigger...
Something that can tear me apart...
I want it inside me!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm shoving this in and out...
I'm coming!
I played with myself again...
I hate myself...
Oh, there you are, Yukiko...
Stepfather?
I rang the doorbell but nobody
answered.
Then I saw the door was open...
But I can understand if
you were taking a nap.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
I guess I fell asleep.
I'll get you some coffee.
Yukiko.
Yes?
I don't like coffee.
Can you get me some tea instead?
Yes.
She really wet herself...
Why did I wet myself?
Was I excited after someone saw
me?
I wonder where Koichi is.
He should've left the office by now.
I think I'll give him a call.
Yes?
Koichi?
This is Yukiko.
When are you coming home?
Everyone is here but you.
Your father is also here...
I can't go home tonight.
Looks like I can't go
home until tomorrow night.
What?
I just got a load of work.
Just do whatever you want.
But you never mentioned
overtime this morning...
What can I say? It's work.
Koichi, who are you talking to?
Is it your wife?
No, it's nothing.
Hey, you listening to me?
Don't worry about me.
Just do whatever you like.
Hey Kochi, let's do it already.
Well, seeya.
Hey, wait a minute...
Looks like Koichi has to do
overtime.
Well, bon appetit.
Wait a minute, Yuuki.
It's too bad for Koichi.
I dished out a lot of money
for this special dinner.
He was very disappointed
that he couldn't make it.
Delicious...
All right, I think I'll eat
Koichi's portion as well.
Mother...
Delicious, this is really good stuff.
Why?
Why do I feel so horny today...
I really want to feel myself down
there...
My hand just moves on its own...
I can't control myself!
I don't care who it is, just
stick your cock inside me!
I'll wet myself!
I played with myself too much...
I'm urinating!
If I keep masterbating and thinking
about sex, I'll end up brain dead.
That's right.
Yuki, I mean "lady"...
You were really pleasuring yourself.
You didn't even realize I came in.
Is your pussy feeling real hot?
Who are you?
I'll call for help.
If you do that, Yukiko...
...I mean lady.
You're the one who'll regret it.
Don't take an
embarrassing picture of me.
Don't worry, I'm not going
to blackmail you or anything.
Well, we can forget about that
since we'll have so much fun.
Oh, could this be...
I can't believe you're this wet.
I guess there's no need for foreplay.
Please stop, I'm begging you.
I'll do anything you want.
Do you really want me to stop?
You'll do anything, right?
If you suck on my cock, then
I'll leave here in peace.
What's wrong?
Hurry up and suck on it.
If you want, I can go
and wake up the kids.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and suck on it.
Yes, that feels good Yukiko.
You seem to be hating this, but
you're using your tongue really well.
If you hate it that much,
then you can just bite.
But since you're not biting...
...you really wanted
some cock, didn't you?
I'm coming!
It's coming out strong!
You really wet yourself...
Koichi didn't pay much
attention to you, huh?
But if you're this wet...
You're feeling ecstatic already.
Looks like we can go all the way.
No, no, no!
I'm being raped...
I'm being raped but I feel excited!
No, don't grab my boobs too hard.
If you squeeze that hard, I'm going
to be all numb deep inside...
My hips are going to move on their
own!
The real thing feels good!
You can keep sticking it deep inside
me!
I'm coming...
I'll climax!
I got raped and climaxed...
I got raped and...
I still didn't come yet.
Isn't it a bit too early to stop?
Stop.
Don't lick that area...
We have to smear this liquid real
good.
What are you...
Instead of worrying about
what's about to happen...
...you should just prepare
for this new sensation.
Just try to relax.
No!
That's my butt hole...
No, no, no!
Don't stick it in there.
You're complaining, but
this hole seems to like it.
Look.
Even though it's your 1st time
taking it in this hole...
...your ass is really feeling it.
That's not true! I'm not feeling it!
Boobs feel good...
My boobs feel good...
Your front looks unbelievable.
No, no!
I feel excited after wanting your
cock...
I don't want to be like a bitch!
Looks like I'm about to come.
I'm about to come, too.
My boobs feel so hard
and they feel very sticky...
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
My asshole is expanding.
I'm going to climax!
I got raped and climaxed...
I got raped and climaxed!
I don't want to be a slave to this
cock!
I have to kill myself!
No! Let me go!
Yukiko, you don't have to be the
only one with a sense of guilt.
What are you doing?
You probably know it by now, right?
You're the only one in the
family who feels lonely.
You should just admit it.
Rio, Rio.
I love you, I love you.
It feels so warm inside you and...
...my hips just move on their own!
Why?
We're supposed to be a family.
Because we're a family, I tried
so hard not to destroy this family...
Do you really have to cry?
What?
What's wrong with trying
to protect my family?
Koichi won't have sex with me,
so I looked at dating sites...
...but I thought about my
family and gave up on that idea.
But later, I decided to register again
for the site, but I just couldn't do it.
Because of that...
Because of that I...
I get excited by being raped!
Yukiko, you must've been very
lonely.
I'm sorry...
By the way, why aren't you fleeing?
Plus how do you know my name?
You were calling my name, right?
You didn't recognize me?
Stepfather?
But why?
You just want to do it until
you're really satisfied right?
Let's just forget about
Koichi or the family for now.
Hey, I'm home!
Where is that woman?
She wants me to be a perfect
husband in front of others...
...but she doesn't even
greet me when I come home.
Hey Yukiko!
I told you I'd be home
in the evening, right?
Why can't you greet me?
If you want me to play the
perfect husband, you have to...
Yukiko...
...and Gonzo...
What are you two doing?
Can't you tell by looking?
I'm giving Yukiko lots
of pleasure with my cock.
You don't pay any attention to her,
but...
...she feels pretty damn good!
Right, Yukiko?
I'm sorry, honey...
I really wanted some cock...
I don't like the idea that
you two are a sexless couple.
Koichi, I'll take your place by
keeping her busy and satisfied...
...so why don't you just watch
this and whack yourself off?
She was constantly
masturbating in her free time.
Try to feel what she had to go
through.
Right, Yukiko?
I haven't been masturbating.
I never thought about
Koichi's huge cock...
...or stuck a big vibrator inside me.
I feel embarrassed and excited
and...
...my hips just keep on moving!
Look at me Koichi!
You have to watch me do
this embarrassing act!
Yukiko...
This guy just takes pictures of girls
on his camera and thinks it's worth it.
Just forget about this
impotent loser for good.
What the hell did you say, you old
fart?
My cock is about a million
times better than your puny cock!
Koichi!
Yukiko!
Here I come!
Try to relax.
Koichi's cock is going
to tear apart my rectum!
Then let's see who can make
Yukiko climax the fastest!
You're on, you old fart!
Father is already home.
I have to tell my father.
It's just not fair for mother.
Even if he doesn't mean it,
he should at least act nicer.
Koichi's cock going into my ass...
...and my stepfather's cock
going in from the front...
They're going back and forth inside
me...
...and it feels so good!
I never felt this way with my cock...
This feeling...
Is that it?
Both cocks...
I'm getting really excited and...
It's moving really wild!
Both cocks are entering
my rectum and my uterus...
I feel like they'll
come out of my mouth!
I'm going to come!
Yukiko,
I'll give you lots of loving for
making you feel lonely for this long.
I feel so happy, Koichi.
You're going to release your stuff
inside me...
...'til I can't take any more, right?
What are you talking about, Koichi?
You can just keep having fun
with that other girl of yours.
I'll keep on loving
Yukiko in your place.
Right, Yukiko?
I'm really happy that my
family loves me this much.
No way...
What is this?