No...
Don't touch there...
I feel so good...
My love juice is overflowing.
Please, please don't tease me...
I can't wait any longer...
I can feel you inside me...
Slave Nurse, Chapter Two
How did I get to this room?
Good morning!
Good morning, Mikuru.
You just woke up? You
are such a sleepy-head!
Um, can I help you?
Well, I started working here today.
So I stop by here to say hi.
Working here?
Yosuke.
Hey, Haruka.
Mikuru, you shouldn't bother Yosuke.
Come out here right now!
I'm sorry about her.
Oh, it's okay.
Mikuru is...
Yes?
She is so friendly with the old men...
I think she enjoys coming here too.
Good morning, Haruka.
Good morning.
Good morning, Mr. Kawahara.
What happened?
You look pale. You didn't
sleep well last night?
I need to talk to you.
Oh, me? What's it about?
I can't talk here.
Okay, let's go to my room.
Yes.
Sorry, Haruka.
I'll be right back.
So what is this about?
Do you like this room?
I'm sure, last night...
In this room...
Mr. Aida's room is incredible, isn't it?
Everything in this room from
sofa to carpet is first class.
There is no wonder that he is
surprised...
That's not the reason!
Last night, I saw you
torturing Eri in this room...
I knew that you were peeping us...
Voyeurism... you have nice tastes.
That's not true!
You guys are...
I think you misunderstood the
situation...
Kiba!
Yes, sir.
E-Eri!
You bastards!
Let Eri go!
Please stop it, Yosuke!
Eri...
I just told you that you
misunderstood the situation.
Her parents owed me a lot of
money, and to settle the matter...
...they sold her to me.
Well, of course, Eri
herself knows the deal.
You got it now?
I can't believe such a crazy story!
Let her go!
You still don't get it, do you?
No...
No!
That's my spot...
See what I mean?
Eri is excited as I
torture her in front of you.
She is that kind of girl, right? Eri?
No, Master, I beg for mercy...
Please, I...
Eri...
Because you're here...
...Eri is more excited than usual.
Oh please...
Please give it to me!
This is her real self.
Stick it in by yourself!
Show it to Mr. Kawahara!
No, I can't do that...
Then you're not getting this.
But...
It feels so good, Yosuke!
Can you see?
My pussy wraps around...
I want you to see this, Yosuke.
You took the whole thing?
Yes, Master, it's deep inside of me.
I'm nothing but a slut.
Oh no...
This is insane...
You guys are crazy!
Mr. Kawahara.
It may sound surprising, but she
lost her virginity just recently...
And the person who
took her virginity was...
Who took her virginity?
What was he trying to tell me?
Yosuke.
Oh, hey, What's up?
Did you see Natsuki today?
Natsuki?
Nobody has seen her since this
morning.
Natsuki...
I haven't seen her today, either.
I see.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing...
I'll ask the director. I
wanted to talk to her anyway.
Thank you.
What happened to me?
Yosuke?
Okay, talk to you later.
Yosuke...
You can't keep your
eyes off him, huh?
Mikuru!
Haruka, you like him, don't you?
What are you talking about?
You don't need to hide it.
He looks like a nice
guy, I like him too!
What?
Oh no, don't worry, I
won't steal him from you!
I didn't say anything!
Natsuki?
She came to the office this
morning and took a day off.
Why all of a sudden?
I don't know, I didn't ask further...
By the way...
Since you're here...
How about this?
Stop it!
Oh?
Ooh, how manly.
You know about Aida, don't you?
What about him?
Don't pretend like you
don't know anything!
He calls Eri his personal helper,
but he is treating her like...
His sex toy?
If you know this, why
don't you try to stop him?
What do you want to do?
What?
They both know what
they're doing, right?
You are crazy, all of you!
Do you want to say that you're
the only sane person here?
What?
You toyed with my body, remember?
You started that!
You could've said no if you wanted to.
I know that you are craving a women's
body deep inside of your heart...
You are nothing but an animal!
Excuse me.
Yeah, you are nothing but an animal...
That's the reason I
asked you to come here...
Yes, I think Aida handled
the situation very well...
I guess it's just a matter of
time before he loses control...
In the case of Natsuki Kamimura,
he didn't demonstrate any rejection...
Well, no, not really...
I've been working overtime recently,
so...
I don't need to bother you.
I'll talk to you soon.
When I can put an end to this?
Animal, huh?
There's been something wrong with
me since I started working here...
Here...
What is this?
I'll give this to you...
To me?
It's for you...
Big brother!
Hello there.
Hey...
Wait, Mr. Tomii...
Anyway...
Oh, Haruka, I asked the
director about Natsuki...
I see...
She should've told me so...
Well, maybe she was in a hurry...
But Natsuki told me that she
was excited to work with me!
She'll be back here tomorrow.
By the way, are you
staying here tonight?
I'm going to sleep in
the same room with Yosuke!
Cut it out, Mikuru,
Sorry, she's joking.
She's going to stay in my room tonight.
O-Okay...
Disappointed?
Yeah, a little...
Natsuki?
Wait!
Where did she go?
Do you have enough space, Mikuru?
I can sleep on the floor.
No, I want to sleep with you.
You are such a spoiled child!
Oh stop it!
What are you doing?
I envy you because you
have such big boobs.
Stop playing, you have to sleep!
Okay!
A videotape?
What is that man thinking?
Oh no, that hurt!
This voice...
N-Natsuki?
Hey, Haruka.
Hmm?
Have you ever had sex before?
What are you talking about?
I've never done it
before, but is it good?
I don't know!
Stop talking, just go to sleep.
M-Mikuru!
I feel something strange down here...
Between my legs...
What's happening to me?
Mikuru, stop playing...
Haruka...
She lost her virginity just recently...
...the person who took it is...
It wasn't a dream...
Was he talking about me?
Eri...
No...
Please stop...
You are cute.
Please tell me how you feel...
Why? My body feels so strange...
You feel strange between your legs,
too?
No, we can't...
Aida! I need to talk to you!
Who's there?
Natsuki...
I've been waiting for you.
Look, Natsuki, here is Yosuke.
Eri, what's this about?
She's getting excited. I
haven't even touched her yet.
It was just last night
you took her virginity.
Why are you doing this?
Did Aida force you to do this?
Do what?
You're the one who took our
virginities, in just one night.
What do you think, Natsuki?
But I...
It's not healthy to
deceive yourself, Yosuke.
It's overflowing...
It's twitching, it's so lovely.
Her pussy looks like a young
bird, who is longing for a worm.
Don't you feel sorry for Natsuki?
I know you do, Yosuke...
Just be myself...
She's right, I'm...
You want to come inside
of her so bad, don't you?
Please, I can't wait anymore.
Please give it to me!
I...
I want to fuck her...
You don't need to hesitate,
she is waiting for you.
Yeah, I don't need to lie to myself...
This is what I am...
Natsuki's pussy is
totally stretched out now...
Yosuke, you feel good?
Yeah, it's okay...
Should I make it tighter then?
No, not there!
I know you want it.
You're squeezing my finger.
Oh no!
You don't need lotion
since you're wet enough.
It won't fit...
It's much tighter...
The party has just begun...
My stomach will burst...
Come!
Come inside of me, Yosuke!
I'm coming too!
I'm fucking a girl and having an orgasm!
Mikuru, please stop...
I feel so hot between my legs...
And it feels so good...
Oh no, I wet myself!
What's happening to me?
Let's stop this.
You wet yourself, too...
That's not...
Oh, do you feel good too?
It's so wet down there.
It feels strange...
Please do it to me too.
Haruka, it feels good...
Mikuru, I'm coming!
Wow, it's still hard.
Yeah...
You screwed us so many times,
but you haven't had enough yet.
Not enough?
No, not enough.
I haven't done what I
really wanted to do yet...
You want to fuck Haruka, don't you?
You want to rape her and shoot
your come in her, don't you?
Haruka...
I bet she's waiting for you now...
She is waiting for me?
Yes, she's waiting for
you, wetting her underwear.
She wants you to screw her so hard.
Haruka...
I can't believe I did it to Mikuru...
What's wrong with me?
Haruka...
Yosuke?
What are you doing here? It's late.
Please don't come in!
You've been waiting for me, right?
Stop it, Yosuke!
You are kidding, right? Yosuke?
No!
What's wrong with you, Yosuke?
Please, stop...
I know you want me to fuck you.
Oh no...
This can't be happening!
No!
Please don't do it...
It hurts!
Please don't move...
Ow, you're hurting me!
You're going to break me...
Please stop it...
Please pull it out.
If you keep doing it...
It feels hot inside of me.
This is me!
I've been pretending to be
a nice guy, it was all a lie!
Mikuru...
Please don't wake up...
No...
I feel strange. Why does it feel so
good...
No!
I'm so embarrassed...
Yosuke...
It's so deep inside me!
I can feel it!
I feel his penis deep inside of me.
Haruka...
You're so rough...
No, I can't take it anymore...
I want more...
It's so good.
I don't care anymore... Yosuke!
I can't hold it...
I'm coming!
Haruka!
I can feel it...
Yosuke's come is filling inside me...
Why...
Now you know what kind of man I am.
It looks like everything is
going well as planned.
Yes, I hope it all
goes fine this time...
He's already lost control,
it's sooner than I thought.
Y-Yes, you have keen eyes
for the right person...
I-I can't take this anymore. Please...
No, not yet...
Please, I can't take it anymore.
You're like a horny kitten.
Please have mercy...
I'm coming!