No...
Please, stop...
Please stop it...
I-I can't...
I can't take it anymore...
Please...
Gosh, I've been having the same kind
of dream all the time...
Tanagokoro Village
Man, I still have to go up this hill?
It's middle of nowhere...
I'm sorry!
Are you all right?
Yes, I am...
Thank you very much,
Mr. Yosuke Kawahara.
H-How did you...
I see, so you work at
the nursing facility too.
Call me Haruka.
We have only female
staff at the facility now...
...but then I heard that a male staffer
was going to join us as a part-timer...
Did you expect anything?
Anything is better
than the old folks!
Hey!
Wow!
This is such a great facility...
...considering that it's
located deep in the mountains.
Deep in the mountains?
That's an exaggeration!
This is a great environment for
old people, surrounded by nature.
What? Again?
Are you all right?
I think I'm just a little tired.
Well, anyway, I would like to
see the director of the facility.
All right, I will show you around.
Then, make a turn here, and...
I couldn't tell from outside but the
building is quite complicated.
Well, actually I just came
here just a week ago,
so even I'm not familiar
with this building yet.
Are you okay?
Let me think...
I think it's this way...
Is that man one of the staffers, too?
Haruka?
I think director's room is
located at the end of this hallway...
Yosuke?
Where did he go?
Hello, Haruka!
Hello, Mikuru, what are you up to?
I'm working here as a part-timer
during summer vacation.
Oh yeah? That's great!
Yup. I just started this week.
Well, we got a new
part-timer today...
Oh that reminds me,
I have to find Yosuke!
You guys are already calling
each other by your first names?
I can't believe it. Haruka can't
even navigate the facility!
Okay, the director's room is that one.
Thank you Natsuki, I
really appreciate your help.
No problem, I'll catch you later.
Yes, the system is ready for that.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Come in.
Hello...
You must be Yosuke Kawahara.
We've been waiting for you.
I'm Saeko Nakajo, the director
of this nursing home.
Really?
So you brought him to
the director's room?
I can't believe a staffer
got lost inside of this building.
It's just impossible.
But a male staffer, huh?
Huh?
Nothing. By the way, Haruka...
Uh, Haruka, do you
sleep well at night?
Why do you ask me that all of a
sudden?
I'm just asking...
...because you're taking naps
all over when you're on your break.
Oh, that's one of my bad habits...
Hey Natsuki!
You make it sound like I'm always tired!
Let's get back to work!
How dare you!
Oh, I'll be here for a month...
That's a long time...
Since he introduced you to this
facility, you must be a reliable person...
Well...
This is a nursing home for men...
...it'd be very helpful if
we could have a male staffer.
Do you have any problem
with the patients?
Not really...
...but old people
behave like kids sometimes.
It's too much for a
woman to handle them.
I'll introduce you to everyone later,
so please rest for today.
I'm the only man...
I'm a little nervous.
I feel strange...
Maybe I'm a little sexually frustrated.
Hey, young man...
A-Are you a new employee?
Yes, I am...
I want to show you something.
Why do you...
Mr. Yosuke Kawahara joins us
today to take care of you this month.
You can tell him anything
you don't want to tell the female staff.
Miss Saeko...
What do you mean by "Anything we
don't want to tell the female staff"?
Well, it's a...
Good question, Mr. Aida!
What?
Oh no...
Nothing...
Yosuke...
He seems to be a good guy...
What's happening to me?
I feel strange...
Damn it, I can't sleep!
This is because I saw that...
Oh, Yosuke.
What are you doing this late?
Saeko...
I just can't sleep, so...
No wonder, because you're not
used to this environment yet...
Would you like to join me?
Huh?
I usually do this by myself...
Please keep this as our little secret.
Oh, sure...
But it's going to be real fun tonight!
I haven't had a chance to chat
with a young man in a long time...
All men at this facility are old, and...
Saeko, are you drunk already?
S-Saeko!
Don't pretend you
aren't feeling anything.
I know you've been so excited...
Am I right?
But...
To tell the truth, my underwear
is already wet, it's all sticky...
See?
Take them off for me.
I feel a little strange today...
Why...
Oh no...
Why am I doing this?
I shouldn't...
I feel strange...
I'm scared, I'm scared...
I can't stop it...
Yosuke...
No...
It's so hard, that's
why I like young boys.
Does it feel good?
Answer my question...
Yes, it does...
But don't come yet.
Good, you made it...
You want to come
inside of me, don't you?
It's your turn...
A little lower...
Not there!
Oh yeah, that's the spot...
Right there, I want you to lick there...
Oh, I can't wait anymore...
Yeah, right there...
Please go slowly, slowly...
You are coming inside of me...
I can feel it...
Yeah, harder, harder...
That's good...
Do it harder.
Harder!
I-I'm coming...
You can come inside of me...
What are you doing?
I said I want you to give me a
massage, put your back into it.
Yes, sir.
There...
How do you like it now, Mr. Aida?
Okay, that's better.
Is it better?
Yes, keep doing it...
W-Was it good?
I bet you slept well last night.
W-What are you talking about?
Please don't mind him.
Mr. Tomii is a little senile,
so don't listen to what he says.
Why don't you have
a massage, Mr. Kiba?
Ask Natsuki for a massage.
I'll go clean around the entrance.
She won't get a joke like that.
Oh, that feels really good, Haruka!
So, I'm talking about Mr. Aida.
Oh... He is like a mischievous child.
That's not mischief!
Why are you so mad?
I don't know why he behaves like that.
He used to be a member of congress,
so he is like a celebrity here.
Eri.
Is she a helper too?
What? Again?
Eri is a personal helper for Mr. Aida.
A personal helper?
Well, I have to go.
Oh, me too.
Yosuke, please take care of the rest.
All right.
Ex-congress member? He must have
donated ridiculous amounts of money...
Mr. Tomii! What are you doing here?
C-Come on, look at this...
Huh?
What is this?
This is hers...
What happened to me...
Oh no, again?
Y-Yes!
It's me.
Come in.
Did I wake you up?
Natsuki?
What? You're quitting?
I think you should do the same too.
Why do you think so?
I know it's a tough job
because all the patients are men...
B-Besides...
This place is...
Huh?
N-Natsuki?
Don't you feel anything?
What are you talking about?
My body is craving something...
My body is...
Natsuki...
N-No!
So, sorry, I didn't mean to...
What's gotten into you, Natsuki?
I'm so sorry...
Please forget this!
Natsuki...
There is something
wrong with this place.
What are you doing?
No!
Please stop it.
Please.
No, that hurt!
Please forgive me...
No please, don't do it...
Now I know. I've been
waiting for this...
I've been wanting
this for a long time...
A big dick of a man... 
It's filling inside of me.
It's hot...
It's so hot...
A dream...
Why did I have a dream like that?
3 AM?
Damn, I'm so thirsty.
Why?
Why am I so horny?
What happened to me?
God, where is the bathroom?
What's that?
No...
I can't do this anymore...
Eri...
Do it, now!
Yes, Mr. Aida.
Aida!
That cannot make me hard.
Kiba.
Yes, sir.
Ow!
Please stop it!
Kiba is the master of whipping.
You make girls scream with joy.
Thank you for your compliment, sir.
It's cold!
Please forgive me.
I swear I'll do my best!
It's driving me crazy!
Open up!
No, I beg you...
You're feeling it now, aren't
you? You filthy bitch!
I-lt's too big for me...
She is such a sensual girl...
Oh, it's burning.
I'll go crazy...
Her teeth are giving my
dick incredible stimulation...
Look at this nasty look on her face!
I'm coming too...
I'm coming!
It didn't take too long
to dominate this girl...
I think that's in her nature.
I picked up the right one!
Who told you to take a break?
Clean up this mess first!
Yes, Mr. Aida.
This place is insane...