Israndia will be punished by banishment!
That's right! That's right!
As the guild's god, his mistake is inexcusable!
It is indeed inexcusable!
Execute the banishment.
Banish him!
It must not be delayed.
That was a small, insignificant experimental mistake, but
the alchemists of the guild banished me.
With an exceptional ability, I climbed to the top of the of the Alchemist guild, but
My name is Israndia.
it appears I've received resentment and jealousy from my peers.
Those men should cry.
However,
as long as they are alchemists
I cannot let them be.
After 15 years passed
I have returned to this capital.
That's right.
My purpose is revenge.
Aria will be sent in as Emperor Clarence's consort clerk.
If Aria is able to seduce the emperor,
in other words, as the governor of this country
I will be able to single-handedly obtain power.
At that time
I'll be able to exercise divine retribution
to those foolish people that banished me.
Banish him!
There are still 35 days until the qualifying competition
for the choosing of the new clerk candidate.
I waited for that day,
hiding in this town's slum.
The greatest humiliation received as an alchemist.
I waited for 15 years to get rid of this grudge.
15 years of channeling my rage into energy to continue my research.
So much energy and time
and finally the day has arrived.
Prima materia, deliverance from the original sin,
philosophical marriage of the King and Queen of Love,
and then the creation of the Philosopher's stone.
The thing that was born from that was the Doura.
I gave Doura a magical power to seduce the Emperor
and placed it into an artificial human, Aria who is much older than she appears.
Wake up, Aria.
Aria, your creator is calling you.
Your name is Aria.
I understood. My name is Aria.
DOURA
I brought books and experiment tools into some place in the slum of the city,
and made preparations with her.
I called this place a pharmacy just for appearance, as I never thought to sell drugs.
Look there.
You're right.
Suspicious.
Look over here!
Get away, brats!
Master...
It's okay for cleaning. Get inside.
Yes.
If I didn't do this way, my precious time would disappear.
My only purpose is revenge.
I have no time to spend on trivial things.
To prepare my revenge, I have sent a mail to an alchemist Yanburikos.
When the entire guild decided to banish me,
he covered me for an obvious reason.
Hello.
My name is Yanburikos.
Can I see Israndia?
Yes, please come in.
Yanburikos is famous in the Emperor's palace.
He also is a member of the selection committee for the new clerk.
I made him introduce at least one more member
to dispatch Aria in the royal palace.
Mr. Yanburikos came to visit you.
Let him in.
Yes.
Thank you, miss.
Yanburikos is a doctor's disciple,
but he has a bad habit of giving female patients the wrong prescriptions
and by that I mean his cock.
Looks like it's ready, huh?
I believe we had a deal that I provide the medicine to your place in time.
Doesn't it matter, my friend?
Let me check it here.
Let's finish today's job before that.
Oh, don't worry about that.
I will introduce you to Pennel and Jack.
Both of them are members of the selection committee.
They will recommend your very capable Aria for sure.
And I will order a lot luxury items from you.
So let me check it right now.
All right, watch from there.
I thought I will be testing it.
Owing to Yanburikos's mediation, I received luxury grocery orders
from Pennel, the lesbian, and the older brother of the emperor,
named Jack; Duke Sharol's butler.
Both of them are essential for my revenge toward the guild
being completed.
It's indecent work as far as I'm concerned,
but I'm ready to do whatever it takes to accomplish my mission.
Hey, Aria, where are you?
Yes, my master?
We're going out, with you.
Eh?
I must show Aria the capital city.
I took Aria shopping.
The next one is a snake shop.
An exotic shop where we can get
cheap yet quality materials.
Sure!
Yet I'm angry at them.
Pennel's order is a rotor and some lubricants.
Jack's one is ropes and a cylindrical enema syringe.
And this is what they are ordering from the
unique alchemist, me?
Oh, that's bad.
I was immersed in shopping too much.
Where are you, Aria?
Aria!
Hey, little lady,
looks like you're lost, let us walk you home.
Hey, not necessary.
Isn't she the stepsister of that chemist?
Oh, shut up.
They say he is brewing some strange magic!
So what?
What's the issue?
Why do I have to listen to that?
Let me walk you home.
If you really want to.
No need to worry.
Let's have a talk at my home?
I'm a sorcerer, and Aria is pretending to be my stepsister.
That's convenient that the folks think this way.
It's a proof that my disguise is just fine.
Hey, Aria, what are you doing?
Do you have something for my stepsister?
N-no...
We thought she's lost and were to bring her to your home.
That's so kind of you.
But please don't worry.
I'm here, after all.
T-thank you very much.
I believe you have understood now.
The place we're living in is not safe.
Be careful.
Yes.
The deadline for provision of the lubricants that Pennel ordered is close.
I'm sure it's good, but I must test it.
Master, I removed my clothes.
Put your hands behind.
Yes.
Sit on the floor.
Is it cold?
Yes.
I see.
Try to hold.
Also, avoid bumping your head against the stone floor.
I feel bad.
I see. Hold on.
Yet, I can see everything from here.
I feel a bit shy.
Your work involves this.
Oops. If you get wet I can't do the test properly.
What is it?
An essential element for the revenge.
It's wet.
The matter in the bottle is similar to Aria's nectar.
The same lubricant.
I made it with the same viscosity, smell, taste.
Using this, they will be able to penetrate from both sides.
Even for the first time.
This is a good usage, too.
Eh, master...
How do you feel? You feel amazing right?
What is it? Looks like you're enjoying something.
It's nice.
Answer honestly.
Please don't be stressed.
Of course. It's for testing purposes.
Please, give me...
the master's one.
I understand your feelings, but...
If you continue like this, I'll come!
The master's...
Master...
I don't need to use anything.
Don't worry, Aria.
Oh, don't stop!
Walking along the windows, I'm hearing Aria's voice more often.
Oh, keep doing that.
I guess she's having fun with somebody.
Hey!
Don't you dare disobey!
She's acting like me.
"You're just a doll, don't you dare speak like me."
A doll?
Oh, I forgot!
Aria is a doll, not a human.
Right there!
Master, do you need something?
Oh, no.
I heard strange voices.
I thought somebody snuck into the house before we came.
Did you worry about me?
Aria, who were you speaking with?
Are you hiding somebody from me?
If you won't get mad...
Is it something that will upset me?
I am sorry, but I have a pet.
Aria, where did you get it?
I saw it chased by cats in the backyard.
I feel it would be teased if I let it go again, so.
Please, let me have it.
I will take care of him.
I was so impressed with how Aria was.
I never thought she could be so serious.
It must be some important.
Do as you like.
Thank you very much!
Are you happy?
His name is Albert, it's the first artificial existence I made.
Eh?
In other words, he is your stepbrother.
He had ran away before I made you.
I never expected to meet him now.
My stepbrother?
Take care of him.
Sure!
For some reason, I felt reassured when I got to know that
Aria was speaking with Albert.
When I am immersed in research, I can't do anything else,
and have problems dealing with every day life.
Letting Albert go was one of those issues.
However, since I received requests from Yanburikos, Jack, and Pennel,
and get to research, my stress increased severely.
Recently, I noticed that my stress is reduced
thanks to Albert.
Wait, Albert!
His quick movements make a human's heart lighter.
The same was true for Aria, as well.
I'll give you this.
Earlier, when I saw somebody talking with a pet,
I thought it's a stupid thing that can't understand words,
but now I get why they did it.
Experience is the mother of knowledge,
and books are no more than its older cousin.
Now I understand this ancient saying.
There is no sense in crying. You still have your ginseng.
You'll get meat after this.
Hmm, Aria, your meat cooking skills have improved.
Why don't you eat it, Aria?
Hey, are you angry about something?
Oh, you finished eating. I'll give you some meat, then.
Say it aloud, if you're unhappy with something.
Aria, stop it already.
You're not a child, you can eat it by yourself.
Aria is a child.
When a child gets a new younger sibling,
it acts the same as an infant to get the parent's attention.
I guess Aria feels jealousy towards Albert.
What is it? Are you starting this time?
I can't eat now.
Master, I'll feed you.
I am not a child.
Here! Is it tasty?
What would happen with my dignity?
However, watching Aria's face change
made me think it's okay sometimes.
Elections will start in no more than 24 days.
The items that Yanburikos ordered will be ready in time.
In tandem, I have to teach Aria the art of seduction
to get the emperor Clarence.
Okay, go do it.
I am not happy using myself for the experiment,
but I had to test the sex object I will give up.
What is it? Go ahead.
Yes.
Aria's assiduity doing carnal things
made my potency even stronger.
Yes, that's right.
Follow from the most outside part.
Right.
She must seduce the emperor.
It's for our mission.
Aria was enjoying pleasing me.
Are you feeling good?
It's good but could be even better.
I'll do my best, so please teach me.
I will do my best to focus my juices.
I'll cum in your mouth, so please swallow it all.
Look here.
In order to maintain this power,
even emperors will prostrate.
Aria's lower lips beckoned with such delight.
I'm so happy.
Master.
Aria is happy.
I did it many times that night.
I guess this night helped Aria to strengthen her will to be Clarence's clerk.
For my sake, of course.
Yes, I must complete my mission for sure.