Naked Eyes 2
What a nice breeze, what a nice view.
This is the famous La Cress.
And that's Pennel's house.
I wish I could live in such a place.
Let's go, then.
Pennel who was introduced by Yanburikos, set the delivery place as her home.
Pennel is a woman, but I received her order,
and drove a carriage to La Cress.
Because Pennel, a direct subordinate of Kremense, directed everyone in the country.
Her influence is the strongest in the country.
Also, she is a new selection committee member.
I had to entertain her and make her vote for Aria.
I don't know if Pennel is sane.
All her maids are trained by her.
I came to deliver the goods.
My name is Israndia.
It's a pleasure to hand it over directly to you.
Her name is Aria.
You have a good woman.
That's fine for greetings. Show it to me.
Okay.
Aria was uneasy until recently.
Aria knows,
how important this demonstration is for me.
Aria got rid of all her shame, and, even being oppressed from pleasure,
she must hold it back.
This is the item.
It's using a special spring so it can move inside as well.
Wait!
Such a good woman. Let me try it on her!
No, we have to test it first.
I can't let this woman touch Aria.
Let's begin.
Hey.
Not yet. Hold on.
Oh.
That's what is happening.
Please, enjoy it.
Please, this one is completely new.
No need for it.
I want to try it tonight.
Please.
Is there a time limit for a spring?
I understood what she's trying to say.
Even if it's moving long enough for Aria,
it's not long enough for overnight play.
That's fine.
I liked the introduction from that liar Yanburikos.
Do you want something else, apart from money?
I was holding on to my hot desire.
She liked my toy, but she's not pleased yet.
If not, please have this.
The unnecessary fan.
However, it seems she liked Aria, at least.
By the way.
I can give this to you. It might help you in some way.
Are you okay with it? I'm happy, my master!
I was unexpectedly shocked.
Is it because Aria received Pennel's fan?
No. The problem is, why I created Aria?
What made me create her?
Once, when I was wandering in an Eastern country,
a god's shrine maiden fell in love with me.
She abandoned her god and came to me.
I loved her too, but I was a mere traveler.
The farewell day came, and our love ended.
She abandoned her god, and I abandoned her, but...
But I guess she left a scar in my heart as revenge.
I guess her hatred made me fall in love.
Aria, wear this.
But then, what would happen with the ten years I spent on my revenge?
What would happen with my position as Aria's creator?
It's all the revenge of the Eastern woman.
Instigation of the abandoned god?
I tried to dress Aria in the Eastern clothes the woman gave me.
If Aria can dress alone...
Come in, master.
Aria? You managed to dress alone?
I was right. I created Aria, but in fact I was forced to.
I decided.
I had no right to use Aria as a tool for my revenge.
Aria, if you like it, you can wear it anytime.
I'm glad for your kindness.
But...I want...
Really?
I like how you want to be going far when I wear it.
Am I going far with you?
And you like it?
As if I'm not me anymore...
Aria...My Aria...
I'm very happy.
I see. That's good.
But...
I understand. I'll do anything for my master.
Aria.
Alchemical instruments are like springs.
You have to make it bigger to work longer.
But...
Impossible?
Yes, you'd break.
Me?
Yes, exactly.
Morning, Albert. Here.
What? Won't you eat?
Is it sick after yesterday's carriage travel?
It slept until the morning.
Hey, Albert!
Albedo, it's an important thing.
Wow, Albert is a genius!
Even I didn't know despite creating Albert.
From the evening till morning, Aria was happy.
I can't help but like Aria so much.
But... can I call this love?
Also, I have no time.
The selections are soon.
Yanburikos is mine, but Pennel is not certain.
Jack...I haven't started yet.
Is there time limit for a spring?
Yes. Even I will die someday.
Even I, as a creature living inside an hourglass.
Pennel's words have a hint.
Not everything is worth the struggle.
Yes, I better remove the hourglass.
Is Albert here?
Albert? What do you want at this time?
I'm sorry for the disturbance. Albert was supposed to sleep, but...
You can't find it.
Albert!
Albert? Are you the Albert?
Albert?
What happened? You should not sleep in such places.
He's dead.
Eh?
Albert, wake up! Albert!
Aria, it's over.
But...
Aria said she wants to bury Albert in the backyard where they first met.
Goodbye, Albert.
But, why? Why? Why?
Aria, the sand ended.
Sand from Albert's hourglass.
Albert is an artificial creature I made before Aria.
I knew it had defects, so I could say it's normal it died before Aria.
Pennel sent a new order, as I thought.
Only 15 days left before the selections.
I have to persuade Pennel this time.
Okay.
We have chances. I'll need you to work, too.
If Pennel asked about the fan, tell her it's stored with care.
It's underground, though.
Okay.
Why are you so sad?
I can help you with that.
It's Albert?!
Albert? Are you Albert?
What does it mean?
It's early for surprises.
Named Nigred; it is Albert's brother.
Nigred?
Oh, stop it, it tickles.
I said a wrong thing, despite trying to be careful.
This time it should be all right.
They won't die suddenly.
They are created and I can make as much as you want.
For you, Aria.
As much as you want.
Aria, wait!
Irreparable damage.
I understood how much I had hurt Aria.
I cannot fight without Aria.
Aria, please, understand,
you're my irreplaceable comrade.
Okay.
Aria, I'm entering.
Yes, Master...
Where are Albert and Nigred?
They're still sleeping.
What about making a pillow for them?
Yes, if it's your preference.
Don't stop that yet.
I know I'm an experimental doll created for your plan.
Yes, I created you for the battle.
I have to send you to Clemens on a mission.
And you must seduce the king.
This is our fate. Yours and mine.
Aria, I need you. Understand it.
Aria's eyes were saying,
he would create another me when I die.
Understand.
"Understand"?
I will obey your order.
Stop this nonsense!
Did I let Yanburikos touch you?
Did I allow that woman Pennel to have you?
You don't understand my feelings.
I'll show them your body.
Please get undressed.
Yes.
Lower your arms.
Raise your legs. Both of them.
Open them and show me inside.
Move them apart.
Your hands are not needed.
Open.
You can do this with your mind.
It should follow your thoughts. Try to close.
I...can't...
Think about something good.
Now open.
Invite a man by opening it wide.
Master...
What?
Please, insert yours, master...
Master, master!
After that, Aria befriended the new Albert and Nigred.
Yet, Aria still needs consoling.
Aria cannot get a grip on her feelings toward me,
but it must irritate her that I know her better than herself.
Aria doesn't know her power, Dora.
That she can seduce the king Cremens.
Her heart is sometimes open to me, sometimes not.
Is the lighting good?
Yes.
Please, start.
What is it?
A small electrical current.
What? That's electricity?
When it works, metal becomes a magnet.
The new item uses this power instead of springs.
It's not magic?
Yes, it's an alchemical invention. Let's begin, then.
Pennel likes immorality and cruelty.
One of her words gave me god's revelation.
A pure item made from indecent things.
Let's think somebody would use this current.
Small pieces in their bodies react to electricity,
and send various impulses in them.
Are you feeling good?
Yes, Pennel-sama!
Very much so.
They are enjoying, you saw?!
More power.
It's a nice start, so...
Oh, just add power.
Oh, that's nice, that's nice.
Do you like it?
Crap.
What does it mean? It's useless.
No, they just haven't used it before. They need training.
Training? Are you sure?
Please, wait. Aria.
She is holding it in for now.
What? In the front?!
More power, more!
Crap, it can break Aria.
Aria...Is it ok?
Aria, you can do it. Imagine this pleasure.
Yes, it's going inside.
Good job, good job.
I understand, it's okay, it's nice.
Pennel agreed at the last.
Pennel promised me she will vote for Aria.
Aria did a great job.
After all, Aria is the only partner for me.
THE END