Mrs. Pennel, where is my master?
I've ordered them to stop searching for Israndia.
As for the moment, he'll be fine.
For the moment?!
It depends on what Prince Charlie would do.
I bet he doesn't like the Israndia's idea of
sending a half-elf to the Royal Castle
to seduce the prince.
Uh...
Normally, the Prince should succeed to the throne,
but now he must concede it to his younger brother,
because of the last will.
Then, what about the Prince?
He won't give up on the throne.
This is what people say.
Then, what about my Master?
He will be a hindrance for the Prince. And your seduction won't help either.
Please, stop!
What will happen then?
I have to warn my Master!
How?
This is...
Israndia will come for you, don't worry.
Let's think of it. How can Israndia's desire come true without you?
Master...
Pennel. I can't call her a perverted duke anymore.
Stay at my place for a while.
Why are you so kind to me?
Am I kind? I wonder.
Prince.
Did you call me?
Jack? Get in.
Hello.
So that alchemist who sent a half-elf has run away?
Yes, he has escaped from jail.
What?
Right after a member of the next selection committee,
Pennel, ordered to release him.
That's outrageous.
It's out of my control.
Where is the key, the half-elf?
Pennel took her.
That woman...
So she helps the half-elf to seduce my brother for the throne?
I have no words to say.
So bloodshed cannot be avoided, huh?
What are you going to do to Pennel?
Send soldiers to capture Pennel and the half-elf.
But what about the king's approval?
I'll take care of my brother.
Prince...
I'm going out to the Castle.
Wait for me, brother.
To kill him?
You'll be the chancellor if I get the throne.
Today is election day.
I won't allow Pennel to do what she wants.
Your desire is my command.
What a nice quality.
I can't believe you're a half-elf considering this moisture and grip inside.
Mrs. Pennel, what about...
Tomorrow is decision day.
I have enough influence, however,
the agreement between Yanburikos and Jack is necessary.
That's why I trained you so much; to melt both
their hearts and souls.
Pennel is making Aria her own thing.
Aria, you don't have to be emotional.
Your Master is me.
You shouldn't be trained by Pennel.
Now, train your skin before your appearance before the committee.
Whoa, what a smell!
What a beautiful smell after the training!
Jack won't be able to resist it.
Hold up, Aria, listen to my orders.
Israndia's life is in my hands.
That's difficult. Even if he'd kill the King, is it possible to retain the kingdom?
No, there is no way.
There is no Minister or General that would submit to him.
Aria, Aria.
Master...
Your eyes are strange! What did she do to you?
After the bath, something still penetrates through my skin.
Something is giving me unbelievable pleasure.
Is it an aphrodisiac?
Oh, during an earlier appearance.
I must praise you to be able to notice my precious aphrodisiac herb.
What about a trade?
What?
It's our mutual aim to influence the King's will.
What do you want?
In order to continue ruling the castle and manage the garden of pleasure,
we must not let Charlie see our breach.
Prince Charlie is the older brother of King Clemense.
I see. Jack captured me by the Prince's order,
to prevent Aria from reaching the Castle.
It seems you've got the situation under control.
So, what is the trade?
A good trade to reach our goal.
Can you tell me straight?
Your true aim is
not to gain power by seducing the King.
You want revenge, right? And you'll get it.
I can promise that.
If I'm able to get revenge for my guild, what do you want?
The complete falling of Prince Charlie, so he won't be able to rise again!
In other words, to get him under your control?
Something like that.
So your only wish is to maintain the garden?
Yeah.
I was reassured for a bit. Our objectives are quite different.
Desire and struggle.
In exchange for your revenge,
Aria will be my lover.
Forever.
Forever?!
Sure.
Do you need Aria for any other purpose?
She'll be just a burden for you.
I was stunned by Pennel. She knew my initial motive.
Do you mind if we conclude the deal?
It's your product so you put energy in.
What about tasting it at the end?
As my farewell gift.
You rascal! You want me to taste Aria?
The secret recipe is what I got from an alchemist when I was young.
Aren't you interested?
Let me be alone with Aria.
You don't want to show me your coupling?
In term of sexual desire,
even Israndia is a mere novice.
Call it whatever you want.
Fine. This is the last time you'll be with Aria.
Take care of her.
Aria.
Aria's whole body is sensitive like her special area.
The last decisive meeting is in the morning.
If Aria isn't selected, your revenge will cease.
Remember that.
Get out from this bath.
It's a mere physical herb with no alchemistic merit.
Aria.
Please, insert it.
I can't wait any longer!
Aria, do you recognize me?
You're...
Aria doesn't seem all that sharp right now.
Her whole body became a sexual organ, and she is distracted.
I can't hold it! Insert it deeper!
In the deepest!!
Aria!
If this continues, Aria's mind will collapse.
I've had sex with Aria, with no emotions.
I had to work hard for it.
It's good.
It's not because Pennel has told me so.
I had to save Aria.
I've concentrated all my mind and body.
I've never done it so seriously.
Aria, do you recognize me?
Master, my Master.
Aria.
I've returned Aria from the critical point.
Tears were falling for some reason.
What?
Brother...
Clemense!
How unfortunate.
You son of...
Master.
Aria, are you feeling good?
Yes.
I do, my Master!
Aria's body returned back to its initial state.
Her consciousness has returned, too.
Aria, do you understand your situation?
Yes, Master.
What is your duty?
Obtain a right to serve the King,
and help my Master get even.
I have to face Yanburikos and Jack in order to do that.
No! I don't remember that!
But they won't choose me otherwise.
Why would you do that? I've made goods for them already.
It should be enough.
But that would be the determinative step!
What?
I was stunned because Aria had such a strong will.
As Pennel said, in order to please my master, I...I...
I will devote my body.
I've done my best creating Aria similar to a human,
but I didn't give her self-consciousness.
I can't allow it.
King Clemense must be remain beside me!
But then revenge will fail!
I was confused.
Aria is thinking about what she has to do.
We must complete our mission.
Yes, but...
What is bothering me?
I didn't make Aria for Jack or Yanburikos.
Envy? No, that's ridiculous.
The selection committee is present, Aria.
Yes, I'm ready.
Aria, don't go.
Aria.
This smell...
Aria's training is advancing.
Do you agree to have sex with Aria and to choose her?
If I could have Aria at least once...
This smell. If I could enjoy it.
Aria, do you agree?
Yes, if I will be chosen.
What a beauty.
Oh, my!
What a smell! It's a perfect smell!
Go ahead! Go ahead!
To choose her is your only way to avoid problems.
I will allow you to do whatever you want.
This was unexpected.
Israndia.
Why are you here?
What are you saying after all?
Yanburikos had Aria once in the past.
It's a lie!
You can ask them.
Yanburikos, Aria!
I'm sorry, my Master, but this is for your sake.
It's all for your sake, Israndia.
I felt the worst loss and humiliation.
What should I do now?
I should take a part of the cake, then.
What a good grasp.
Wait.
Oh you...
What are you doing?
Master.
Aria.
Aria!
Mother?
What's happened, mother?
Your Majesty!
What?
Your Majesty.
Mother, my brother was executed for high treason.
Who is she?
Aria, the next King's aid.
And him?
Aria's guardian, Israndia.
A Master of a former guild; a talented alchemist.
Can you resurrect her, then?
I hope so.
Do whatever it takes and take her to the Castle.
Don't you mind, mother?
Did you like her?
I like her, but I'm unable to leave an heir.
What? He is impotent?
But she'll be a beauty of the Castle, though.
So why did Pennel?
Israndia, you said?
Yes.
It's destiny whether you resurrect her or not.
Do everything you can.
As you wish.
Mother, my generation will end.
Due to my disease, I have not much time left.
Can I ask you to be a Queen if I won't find a good successor?
Clemense.
I thought Pennel was a pervert who is interested in women only,
but she is a mother of the King...
It's fine to laugh, Israndia .
I had an affair when I was young.
It went on for a long time.
So I gave birth to Clemense, and Charlie was born from another woman.
The day that Clemense was born,
the previous King bequeathed the throne to Clemense and died.
I was a servant,
so I earned my living in the castle managing other servants for Clemense.
Then...
Yes, I'm not able to receive a man anymore.
I immersed myself in a paradise of women to forget that.
It was my life. But everything has its end.
Yes, everything is over.
It's meaningless to seek revenge now.
I didn't resurrect Aria.
I had a chance to do it with my skills.
But what would Aria feel then?
I understand it's cruel for her.
Even if Aria will fulfill our plan,
the King has already died, and my life has not ended yet.
Aria will have to suffer alone.
Doura. Eternal Aria's heart.
I've left Albert and Nigred as Aria's grave keepers
and left the royal capital.
Many years later,
during my trip, I spent the last days in the small town of Bossa.
This stone's name is Doura.
Under certain conditions, you can plant it,
and charm a person you desire.
Master, master!