Aria's heart kept opening and closing for me.
She couldn't understand her own feelings.
However, like the sand falling, our time approached its end.
Then...
Yanburikos visited me with no prior contact.
Sorry for the suddenness, but I've brought Jack to you.
Naked Eyes - 3
I'm going home then!
What happened Jack?
Give me a ride! I'm going back home.
Don't worry, I'll take care of him somehow.
I'm counting on you, Yanburikos.
I'm counting on you!
Jack, why are you so angry?
It was way too rude!
Why would I recommend that girl?!
Israndia was asked that, too.
I believe it's natural to have me do something to her at least once.
And yet he didn't allow me to even touch her.
Who's asking in such a rude way?
And what that the only issue?
Yanburikos! I've paid a visit to the poor district because you begged me.
Why did he just give me this?
He just wanted to show her to you.
And you liked that, I guess.
Am I right?
Of course, it's impossible to get her right away.
I've not touched her yet either.
I want to spread it to confirm how it works.
It works already. Right, Aria?
Yes.
Please, go ahead.
Aria...
Yanburikos.
What?
We can't touch her not because it's the first time.
The reason is because we're the selection committee.
I see. I think I understand now.
Nah, you understand nothing.
If a doctor would brag about his position in the alchemist guild,
it'd be unworthy of the selection committee member.
What should I do now?
I didn't expect them.
Why did they come together?
Master.
What?
Go say it.
In order to calm that person down,
let me stay at his house.
You mean, it was a mistake to refuse that Jack do it to you?
Yes. I understand your concern about me,
but what if everything would end like this?
At that moment, I...
I've been beckoning him mentally,
as you taught me, master.
So this is why he's angry.
You did it well. It's not your fault.
But I couldn't see what you did.
Let's go to his house then.
Mr. Jack? Are you going to Duke Charlie?
It's urgent!
What happened?
I need permission to use the soldiers.
Okay, if it's for a butler's service.
But what happened?
Somebody tried to win over the emperor using a dark elf.
Using Clementz to gain info about the experiment?
That's correct.
Perform a bloodless coup dՎtat, huh?
For our plan to be revealed. What a brazen man.
Okay, crush him!
Okay.
Oh, Aria? Where are you going alone?
This voice...Yanburikos-sama?
Get in, I'll get you there.
I want to visit Jack.
Strangers told me to go this way.
What a coincidence. I'm returning from his house.
But he left his home.
Where?
To the house of Duke Charlie, older brother of the emperor.
Brother of the emperor?
Israndia, you're arrested!
Why?
What is the reason for my arrest?
I don't know. Ask Jack.
Jack's order?
Aria, run!
Shut up!
She has run away already!
Aria? Aria!
Aria noticed the contradiction in her deeds.
She compromised her relationship with Yanburikos to be friends with Jack.
Besides, Yanburikos introduced Jack and Pennel.
What should I do now, master?
It was luck that Aria wasn't arrested.
Where is she?
She shouldn't leave the house without my permission.
I was worrying, so she left.
Could it be she ran away from me?
Master!
Yanburikos arrives!
I've brought Yanburikos.
Let him in.
I was surprised by the urgent matter. I've lost one carriage.
Did something happen with the Duke?
It's about Israndia.
I've arrested him.
Israndia? What for?
I believe he wanted a bloodless coup dՎtat.
Half-elf? Did you mean that Manmade race?
Yes.
But isn't that impossible?
It's a pretext that nobles use to exploit peasants, like the witch hunt.
Watch your mouth!
It's a mansion of Duke Charles, not mine!
Sure. But...
Listen to me, Yanburikos.
There are a lot of people like Israndia who don't fear the God.
Therefore the half-elf race exists for sure.
The problem is we've let the half-elf slip.
Who are you talking about?
Aria.
You say Aria is a half-elf?
I'm asking, Yanburikos, where did you hide Aria?
Me and Aria? Nonsense.
You've recommended her, too. What is that wound on your forehead?
This is...
That's fine. Wait for the interrogation in the prison.
Are you going to put me and the rest of the selection committee in jail?
I wonder where Aria is now.
And why did Jack arrest me?
Jack, who was supposed to be my ally.
I probably irritated him with my attitude.
The contempt deep in my heart.
He must be more powerful than Yamburikos and Pennel.
Or...
What if he wanted to have Aria for himself?
So he imprisoned me.
If so, Jack is a mere butler who needed a good reason
for Duke Charles to enforce the army.
What kind of a reason could it be?
Yanburikos is under arrest too? Why?
Pennel from the selection committee has arrived.
What? Pennel?
Let her into the reception room.
I'm fine here.
Oh, well.
You're so great to call me without honorifics.
This is, uh...
Don't worry, we're equal committee members.
I'm returning from La Gunse's villa,
but I wanted to discuss something here.
I see, I see. Please, take a seat.
So what exactly did you want to discuss?
An important person for us,  on the selection committee,
disappeared last night.
Also, I want to make an unofficial conference so please summon Yanburikos.
Yanburikos?
His house should be close to this mansion.
He's been imprisoned...
in this castle.
That's great! Let's start the conference, then.
I don't mind doing it here.
What kind of a conference?
Also, who is that person?
Y-you!
Yanburikos! You're going to go to the conference! You're free for a while.
A conference? What kind?
I thought it's an interrogation.
Well, doesn't matter if I can get out of here.
Okay, now Yanburikos knows I'm here.
Albert?
Albert, is it you?
Is Nigredo with you?
I see.
Help me.
So, Israndia is in the underground prison.
Yanburikos was in jail until now, too. Is that correct?
Yes, correct. Right, Jack?
Jack, give us an explanation.
This woman is a half-elf.
So I have to arrest him as her creator.
Half-elf? Wait, how can you conclude Aria is a half-elf?
Here is a love perfume that Israndia made.
I got the perfume I liked.
I understood it once I smelled it.
The symptoms of its effect were on Aria's body.
Her skin flushed and got goosebumps.
However, I noticed something.
Her clitoris enlarged and she was very excited.
I see. The smell was the same?
The smell?!
A woman's smell changes when she is aroused.
Aria shed drops of her love juices, but the smell was nice!
Israndia knew this and hid from me!
That's why he stopped me.
Oh, I didn't notice this.
Now I get it.
Israndia couldn't let us touch Aria.
Probably because I was the only one who noticed it.
Are those all your reasons?
One more reason.
There was a cat-like animal in his room.
But not real cats. Surprisingly it was the two of them!
They were alike as if God created them! He must have made them.
This proves that Israndia possesses skills; the magic to produce half-elves!
I'm sure of it.
That's true, two identical animals is a strange fact.
So that's why she is so strong!
Oh, shut up.
Aria told me what you planned to do last night.
What did you do, Yanburikos? Could it be you with Aria?
No, that's...
Hey, Jack! Listen to me.
Release Israndia immediately.
I'll take care of him along with Aria.
As if I can do it!
I'll arrest Aria after the conference!
Also, what is Aria doing here? She isn't allowed!
Are you saying you're allowed to capture Israndia and Aria?
It's natural to arrest a half-elf and its creator.
Shut up! I'm not your blind slave! It must be your will,
or Duke Charles's will!
You won't go unpunished even if it's an emperor's brother's desire!
Why?
That would mean mutiny against the emperor.
Mutiny?
But why?
Your face says I'm right.
No, that's my sole will,
and the Duke is unrelated.
Uh, your will?
So why did you want to arrest both of them?
I want Aria.
Did you want to fuck Aria?
Yes.
Can you make a statement that you won't cover for Duke Charlie?
Of course!
Then, do Aria.
Are you letting him have Aria?
Only once, and here.
Don't you mind, Aria?
Sure.
Also, you'll recommend Aria as a committee member and give me Israndia and Aria.
No, that's...
Why are you so hesitant? Could it be that
you're covering for Duke Charlie?
Not at all!
Jack wanted to do it to Aria. Right?
Go ahead, Jack.
Forgive me, master!
Everything is for your benefit.
This is the first time with another man.
What's happened? Go on.
No end to this in sight?
I've seen something I shouldn't!
So you're unable to!
This makes no explanation of your motive.
So it was an order from Duke Charlie after all.
No, I have a male's sexual desire.
I see. But you can't do anything with your thing?
I can.
How?
I smell the scent of an aroused woman.
So that's why your nose so sensitive.
But Aria...
Yes, her scent doesn't change even if she's aroused.
Even if Aria lures you...
I can do nothing.
Such a pity. I'd do everything imaginable with Aria.
We have a problem.
You're saying you see Aria as being nothing but a doll.
I feel much more than strongly than that.
If I can't see your ejaculation, I can't decide whether you are aroused or not.
I can say that your body didn't ever have true desire.
Are you saying I've tricked you?
Your words that you want fuck Aria can't be explained otherwise.
I don't know what to say.
I have an idea if the problem is the smell alone.
What is it?
At that time, I had escaped from the prison and was wandering in the labyrinth.
The underground duct.
What a smell.
Yanburikos's idea was to get Aria aroused without this perfume.
But you just wanted to entertain yourself
by watching how he was going to try to do that?
What is it, Yanburikos?
This is the first time I'm doing it, and your gaze is...
Aria!
Aria, Aria!
A seductress...She is a seductress!
Yanburikos.
What?
Make Aria come now.
Okay!
This smell is the problem.
What a scary woman.
I lose no matter if I cum or not.
Yanburikos, you're free to do whatever you want.
Are you sure? Then...
Smell it while watching those two.
I'm entering.
What a pitiful look.
Jack, if you don't cum, you'll lose.
Not to mention you demonstrated that shame to us.
Jack...It seems you've ejaculated.
If I didn't come, it would have proved that it wasn't my intent,
and if I did, it proved Aria is not a half-elf.
Pennel has won completely.
But Aria should be a half-elf.
It must be Pennel's filthy smell that made me come.
It's as if I've been seduced by the tricky Pennel.
Israndia has escaped.
Master.
What is it, Jack? Are you saying you let him escape?
Give Israndia to me!
The End