Ole! Ole!
Wow, oh man!
Oh, please look this way!
Would you like some alcohol, Natasha?
\NI'll have a little wine, then.
Hey, back off, dude.
Like I said, nothing beats a\Ndagger in close range combat.
Nereid, you'll get drunk at that rate.
Don't worry about it, all right?
Man, you're just way too wimpy, Seil.
I don't know about this...
Now here they are. I even got you\Nthe artillery you've been dying for.
Of course you'll want\Nthem to join, right?
From the left, it's Garvin,\NNecromancer, Santos, and
Sarah from a ninja unit.
She's proud of her legs\Nbeing so nimble and quick.
That's not all. Don't forget these\Nlegs are sleek, shapely, and elegant.
Thanks for having me.
There are some problems\Nwith her personality.
As long as she is capable,\Nit's not a problem.
Is the leader of your force here? I'd\Nlike to see him. Where is he?
My name is Bianca.
I am a knight of Ronboni.
I am not really the leader, as we all\Nconsider ourselves equal comrades.
She's the princess\Nwho was in the castle.
I have heard you are the\Nonly force that's defeated
Lucifon's armies while\Nadvancing eastward.
I ask that I may be\Nallowed to join you.
Of course, we welcome you eagerly.
We'll fight together. Feel free to\Ndemonstrate your skills in our struggle.
Do you not have a test or some trial?
I pride myself in matching anyone\Nin handling a lance or a sword.
Forgive me if I have\Nwounded your pride.
But the fact is, in our situation\Nwe can use any help we can get.
I see. It does seem you\Nare short on manpower.
Yes, but please don't dwell on that.
Everyone here is allied together to\Ndefeat Lucifon.
Kick Lucifon's ass!
We'll take off tomorrow at dawn.
But for tonight, please,\Nhave a glass, Bianca.
Hey, is it like, did you come after me?
Oh, of course not! I... I...
I wanted to become a\Nsorceress like my mom.
So I wanted to... To do training.
That's right. Why would\NI come after you?
It's nothing like that!
So like Mom, huh?
But even Mom, and everyone else...
Don't worry! Once we defeat Lucifon,\Neverything will be back to normal.
You're right.
Once we defeat Lucifon...
Hey, about the talisman I gave you!
Do you still have it?
Yeah, I got it.
Let me see.
Okay! What?
What's wrong?
Weird...
I bet you lost it long\Nago! That's it, isn't it?
Why would you care about\Nanything I gave you?!
Hey! There it is!
See, I had it around my\Nneck, but before I knew it,
it slipped down into my underpants.
No way.
There.
Oh, all right. I've seen\Nit, now just put it away.
Oh, okay. What? Did it smell?
I'm joking, it's a joke. I had it around\Nmy neck the whole time.
Kakeru, you never change, do you?
What's that?
You've just liked to make fun of\Nme, ever since we were small.
You think so?
You always do.
Even when I try to talk\Nabout something serious,
you poke fun or do\Nsomething I can't stand.
Well...
Why can't you act more grown up?
I don't care how good you are with a\Nsword as long as you act like a child!
Like how Eto is all grown up?
What does Eto have to do with this?!
You like Eto, don't you, Natasha?
What? Why?
Somehow, I can tell...
Oh, forget it. Why don't you\Njust go away and leave me alone?
Who is it?!
Hey, hi...
Eto! Oh, so you were watching?!
Well, I guess...
So, you had a fight with Kakeru?
Yes, I guess I did.
Oh, why does Kakeru act\Nlike that all the time?
Well... Look, he may act like that,
but I imagine that's because\Nhe wants your attention.
But Kakeru... He's always\Nacting as if he's a child.
Just look at how he\Ntreated my talisman.
Well, he said it was\Njust part of a joke.
He couldn't stand admitting out loud\Nhow he cherished that talisman.
Natasha, he was embarrassed\Nover letting you know that.
That's why he said that.
Really? But...
Hey! You were listening in on\Nus all that time, weren't you?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, it doesn't bother me.
Whenever I talk to Kakeru, it\Nseems like we end up fighting.
Right now, I'm sure Kakeru is feeling\Nguilty too, over how he acted.
He's wishing he hadn't done that.
Well, I don't feel guilty at all!
Oh, really?
It seemed like you were depressed.
I'm not depressed, I'm just frustrated!
Both of you aren't acting\Nforthright enough.
Natasha, might you be wondering\Nwhy you become so flustered
when you're dealing with Kakeru?
I'm not acting flustered!
You keep getting into fights because\Nyou disguise your feelings too much.
As if you knew anything about this!
I'm really sorry, Eto.
For a moment, it seemed like\NI was talking to Kakeru.
No, it's all right.
I'll go to sleep now. Goodnight.
All right.
Well, let's see if you can catch\Nup with my beautiful, fast legs.
All yours now!
Magic users, ready!
Easy now, easy!
Not yet, wait...
Magic users, commence fire!
No, wait, Bianca!\NDon't jump the gun!
Hey, that's not fair!
No, not yet!
Kakeru, go back to Natasha\Nand stop them.
Yeah, sure!
That damn spitfire!
Swordsmen! Calvary! Charge!
Natasha! Stop! Stop now!
Nereid! Call off the magic!
Necromancer! Stop now!\NBianca is in there!
Bianca, heads up!
Pull! Now! One! Two!
Three!
Hey, wait a sec!
Kakeru! Just hold on!
Thanks, Neptune!
Neptune!
It would seem we need\Na dragon unit as well.
We just need to hang\Nin there a while more.
You must persuade me.
Lucifon's powers can be\Ncountered if I am with you.
Tonight we'll rest at\Nthis village of hobbits.
Make sure you get\Nwell rested, everyone.
Are you the commander?
Are you the sappers we heard about?
We'd like to come along,\Nif we may, dear sir.
We'll help you out real good!
Nice to be workin' with ya!
Oh, Seil...
I don't know...
Come here.
Eto...
Who is it?
I've been waiting for you.
I'm not in the mood, if that\Nwas what you were thinking.
While you may not be\Ninterested in finding out,
I am interested in seeing\Nhow skilled you are.
Wasn't the fighting on\Nthe battlefield enough?
No, I must fight you directly.
Unless we do, you will not be able\Nto learn of my true strengths.
I am well aware of\Nyour strengths, so...
I wish to assess your\Nstrengths. Please.
There's no need for this.
Are you mocking me?
No, but I am thoroughly appalled.
What do you think you are doing?
I will have you unsheathe\Nyour sword, no matter what.
I can only respect valiant,\Npowerful men.
I've had enough of the feeble, gossipy\Nmen so prevalent at my castle.
You claim I am like them?
I am about to find out.
Bianca, do you judge men\Nsimply by their swordsmanship?
What else is there?
You are still a child then.
What?!
The strength of men lies elsewhere.
Then what is it?
Impossible...
How could I be so easily...
That should be enough.
Once more!
It won't make any difference.
Are you afraid of losing to me?
Losing? Winning? Who\Nare our true enemies?
Even now, the forces of Lucifon\Nare increasing their numbers.
We need to rest ourselves, so that\Nwe can proceed as soon as possible.
Isn't that right?
I must be convinced before\Nany of this matters!
I'll have to teach this selfish\Nprincess a little lesson,
so she'll never exhibit\Nsuch bad behavior.
What are you doing?!
Have you no shame?!
Let go!
Stop!
Stop this at once! Do you have any\Nidea what it means to soil my skin?
Those who dared to touch\Nme in the palace...
Princess Bianca, listen to me!
Princess, you will not\Nbe able to defeat me.
Are you a woman who will do\Nanything to elevate her honor?
No!
Stop!
My journey with the others has nothing\Nto do with inflating your pride.
Stuck-ups and those brandishing\Negotist pride are
nothing more than a burden on us\Nright now.
We don't have room for that!
We have no need for some\Nswell-headed woman in our ranks.
What I... what we need is to
share pain and joy amongst ourselves
as we march toward defeating Lucifon!
Comrades in arms!
Eto...
Your eyes... They're filled\Nwith such sadness.
You must have lost someone very dear.
We cannot allow ourselves\Nto be defeated by Lucifon.
To win, we need your help, Bianca.
Hurry it up!
What's holding us up?!
We have room for another ten.
Get the women and children on first!
All ahead full!
Wow!
You're still awake?
Yes...
It seems everyone is asleep already.
You must persuade me.
I'd like to secure more\Nbows and arrows.
Yes, we'll see what we\Ncan do in the next town.
Marlene...
What do you plan to do\Nwhen you meet Lucifon?
Of course, take revenge\Nfor the death of my...
Are you sure?
I have the feeling that you will try\Nto prevent us from defeating him.
Why? How could you say...
You mustn't. You will regret doing so\Nmuch later.
How would you know of such things?
Because you yourself told me.
I don't recall mentioning\Nany such thing to you.
No, you wouldn't. Your\Nfuture self told me so.
Eto, I don't fathom what you're saying.
You wouldn't know right now.
What I am talking about is from\Nanother continuum of history,
a future event that takes place there.
Me in the future?
You told me you're from Trianon.
But that's a lie, isn't it?
Truth is, you are from... from\Nsomeplace far, far away, I believe.
Just like me. I have also\Ntraveled from a far off place.
Or I should say, came\Nback from a far off place.
I came from the future.
I came from the future using the\Nblack stone that you gave me there.
The black stone!
You know about the black stone,\Ndon't you? And what it can do.
Marlene, I am Kakeru.
That... That can't be!
I used to be Kakeru.
Now I am following through\Nthe flow of time yet again.
You can't believe me?
I'll let you know something.\NThis ship is about to sink.
Sink?
It's dragons!
They're...
Fold the...
Let's run...
Eto! Marlene! Big trouble!
Douse the flames!
Fire!
Captain! Will the ship make it?
No! It's going down! Now!
Those damn bastards! My ship!
Eto, the bow is taking in water fast!
What are we going\Nto do? I can't swim.
If you don't want to\Ndie, you'll have to jump!
Marlene, are you all right?
Yes...
Come on, everyone! Abandon ship!
Natasha!
Okay...
She's going down.
Yes, just like it did before.
What's going to happen to us now?
Just make sure not to drown.
We'll take this up later.
I'll go ahead then.
Yume wo akiramenai hito wa
Itumo hitomini tuyoi\Nhikari wo yadoshite iru
Kimi to issho ni watashi mo ituka
Yume ni mukai habatakeru\Nyou ni nagatteru
Donna ni kurushii toki\Nmo soba ni irukara
Hitori de mayowazu\Narinomama wo tsutaete
Futari nara wakeaeru itami
Kimi no tsubasa ga\Nazayaka ni hikaru
Chikara zuyoku habataiteiku\Noozora wo jiyuu ni
Dare mo zibun no\Ntaisetsu na mono wo
Mune ni idaite iru kagiri
Itsu no hi mo kagayakeru
Next Episode
How can I get Marlene\Nto open her heart to me?
While I grow ever more anxious, the\Nfighting grows ever more intense.
My friends fall, one by one.
As we get closer to Reimling Castle,
more powerful forces of Lucifon block\Nour path.
But the time has come when a friend\Nwill awaken to his true powers.
Next Dragon Knight: Destiny!