Eto, please have some. If\Nyou would like, of course.
It's just like when I was Kakeru.
Thank you, Marlene.
Why did you save me?
When that mast fell on\Nthe ship and you saved me,
that mast almost\Nfell on top of you.
I don't know why.
Before I knew it, I had\Nshoved you aside.
Eto...
Were you marooned on\Nthis island before?
Yes, it's the same\Nisland as before.
So, unless you do something\Nintentionally to change its course,
history repeats itself?
Well, it seems like it.
Of course, if everything\Nrepeats itself to the very end,
then there would be no point\Nfor me to have come back.
Do you believe me when I claim\NI'm Kakeru from the future?
It seems I have no choice\Nbut to believe you.
What is that black stone?
Well, before I can explain that,
I'll have to explain\Nabout where I came from.
Then I need to ask you. Where are\Nyou from, Marlene? Who are you?
Before I answer that, there\Nis something I'd like to ask.
Eto...
While we were on the\Nship, you said to me...
That I would live to regret\Nhelping Lucifon.
Yes, I said that.
Why would I regret?
Every one of us will fall\Nprey to Lucifon's powers.
And only I will remain alive.
I will be left to live a\Ncaptive for years on end,
until one day you\Nwill come before me.
When you handed me the black\Nstone, you said to me,
"Go back to the past\Nand persuade me."
You told me you could\Ncounter Lucifon's magic.
Persuade me?
You also said something\Nabout being wrong,
though I don't know what you\Nfelt you were wrong about.
I was wrong? That's what I said?
That's right. Your tone, your\Nvoice, it was exactly the same.
That I was wrong.
Yes, that's why I am here now.
Marlene, can't you\Ntell me anything?
Have you seen anything?
Nothing. Just clouds, ocean,\Nseagulls, sun, and the Black Mist.
It seems like the Black Mist\Nhas stopped moving these days.
That's right.
It will begin coming after us\Nonce we get off this island.
Why?
Because Lucifon is getting\Nkicks from watching you suffer.
Me?
That's right.
I wonder if a rescue\Nship will really come?
Don't worry. It will.
Eto, you sound like you\Nknow a ship will come.
Well, no, not exactly.
I'll leave you in charge, all right?
Oh, Seil...
Well, look...
Oh my, c'mon Seil!
Don't grab onto me like that!
You must persuade me.
Tomorrow, the ship will appear.
The journey's already half complete.
Marlene, what am I to do?!
Natasha?
What's the matter, Natasha?
Did you have a fight\Nwith Kakeru again?
Ever since we've come to this island,
I've hardly had a chance\Nto talk with Kakeru.
You may not have had a\Nchance to talk to him,
but that hasn't changed your\Nfeelings toward him, right?
Eto, you're so kind, thinking\Nof me. Not like Kakeru.
Maybe I should just dump\NKakeru and go out with you.
Get rid of silly thoughts\Nlike that, and get some rest.
But once I awake, my head will\Nbe filled with anxiety again.
I've had enough of this.
Natasha...
I'm just tired of all of this.
Natasha, are you crying?
Natasha...
No, I'm not crying. I am not!
What?
What is it?
What is that you have on?
Oh, it's nothing.
Why do you have this talisman, Eto?
Well, actually, yesterday, Kakeru\Ngave it to me to hold on to.
That's a lie! I saw it on Kakeru's neck\Nwhen he slept on the watchtower!
Well...
Yes, this is the one I gave to Kakeru.
Eto, what's this about?!
Who are you? Take off your helmet!
If you won't say anything, then\NI'll tell everybody about this.
Oh, no, please don't!
If Kakeru were to learn who I\Nreally am, then I would disappear.
What's that?
No, nothing.
I'm serious! Why do you have the\Ntalisman that I gave to Kakeru?!
Why? Why would there be\Ntwo of the same thing?
I'll ask Kakeru about this tomorrow\Nmorning in front of everybody!
Wait, wait a minute!
All right, I'll tell you the truth.
I am Kakeru.
Don't be silly.
No, that's the truth.
Kakeru? Really?
No, wait! Don't put it on!
Let me see once more!
No, I can't. If someone else were\Nto see, it would all fall apart.
Just once more!
No!
Just show me!
Natasha!
Natasha, are you all right?\NSnap out of it!
You're Eto, right?
That's right, Eto.
Eto, but you are Kakeru as well.
I can't believe it.
I beg you, Natasha. Don't\Nlet anyone learn of this.
But why?
A strange feeling would come over\Nme when I was talking to you.
I didn't know why I\Nfelt the way I did.
Kakeru...
Call me Eto. Right\Nnow, I'm not Kakeru.
How come there are now\Ntwo of you, Kakeru?
Because we were defeated by Lucifon.
I came back from the future,
so that the errors made in the\Npast would not be repeated.
But how? How did you\Ndo a thing like that?
I can't reveal that\Nright now. I'm sorry.
But please, keep this a secret\Nbetween just you and me.
I will, Kakeru.
It's Eto.
All right, Eto.
But just answer me one thing.
Does Kakeru love me?
Yes, he loves you very dearly.
For a long time.
Thank you, Kakeru.
I love you, Kakeru. I love\Nyou very dearly as well.
Yes, sure.
I love you, Kakeru!
Natasha, I am not Kakeru right now.
Two individuals cannot occupy the\Nsame time as the same person.
Oh, Kakeru...
It's Eto, Natasha. Please, you\Nneed to regain your composure.
Kakeru, I love you.\NI love you so much.
Natasha...
Sure is hot.
No ship in sight yet?
Nope.
What is it, Kakeru?
Nothing.
Wait, Kakeru!
It's a ship!
Everyone! It's a ship! A ship's here!
It's begun moving\Nagain, coming after us.
Eto, I don't intend to help Lucifon.
In fact, I'm intending on doing\Nsomething contrary to his wishes.
Contrary to Lucifon's?
That black stone comes only from a\Nwomb of a woman of the Underworld.
Both Lucifon and I used the black\Nstone to enter into this world.
From the Underworld?
Yes, I am a woman of the Underworld.
You and Kakeru both trace back your\Norigins to the bloodline of the gods.
It would seem we should\Nnot fight together anymore.
Unload our luggage!
There don't seem to\Nbe many people here.
We might have problems\Ngetting warriors here.
Where are the inns?
We'll go look together.
Who is it?!
You are?
Rhea... My sister Helen and I made\Nour escape from the Lucifon forces.
I talked to Torheths at the docks,\Nand he told me you were the leader.
Can we join your forces?
Yes, you can.
My sister Helen can administer\Nhealing magic treatments.
I employ a bow.
I see.
I am not a spy!
I don't find you suspicious.
I welcome you.
Show us your best in our fight.
What is it?
Are you adverse to women?
No, and this has nothing to\Ndo with that.
I'm glad. You simply must be tired.
Yes.
I understand. Why don't\Nyou take it easy then?
Why?
My mother taught me that I\Nshould service men devoutly.
It's wonderful.
Weren't there men among\NLucifon's forces?
No one normal.
Either they are complete\Npigs, or just simply filthy.
That's fine. You can just\Nlet it loose like this.
This guy looks like\Nhe's ready for more.
You're tired, aren't you?
You don't have to do a thing.
Help me take this off.
You're amazing.
Oh, no...
I can't hold back.
I'm coming!
And I'm good with a bow.
Yes, I'm well aware of that.
That's...
Ouch, meow! How dare you say\Nthat? Hitting me like that, meow!
Tanyan...
Kakeru...
What's up?
Oh, about...
That cat girl from before!
Aren't you missing something, Kakeru?
You're the one, aren't you?!
Meow?
Knock off the meowing.
You picked my talisman from me!
Give it back, now!
Meow? I have meow clue!
I don't know anymeowing about it!
What are talking about, meow?!
Why, you little runt!\NHold it right there!
Meow, meow! What are you doing, meow?!
Where did you hide it!
How would I mya-know?!\NStop it, meow!
That's a special talisman Natasha\Ngave me! It's precious to me!
Damn it, give it back!
Enough already, meow! Meow,\Ndon't take off my clothes.
What if I don't have it, meow?
What's going to be your\Npenalty, meow?!
Well...
If you really don't have it, then\Nwe'll let you have the talisman.
Whatcha sayin' meow?! I don't want\Nanything I already have, meow!
I want somethin' else, meow!
Something else?
Hey?!
Meow?
You just said you had it!
You said it! You did take it from me.
Meow!
Kakeru!
What are you doing?
Oh, Natasha.
Who is that child?
Meow!
Hey! Come back!
Something dingy like this is\Nyour precious treasure, meow?
I got no time for poor\Npeople like you, meow!
Kakeru...
So this is...
The Dragons' Bastion...
We were driven back\Nhere the last time.
Easy there, easy!
Wait! Don't do anything!
Hear me, humans. You do\Nnot belong here.
Leave this place immediately!
All we ask is to rest for one night.
This is the sacred Dragons' Bastion!
Humans go home!
Well, you're a human\Ntoo, aren't you?!
What's a human child doing\Nin the Dragons' Bastion?
Screw Lucifon's armies!
Go home! Get out!
We are not part of Lucifon's armies!
We fight them!
Heed, humans. If you leave right\Nnow, no harm will come to you.
Nor do we wish to have\Nharm come to you.
All we ask is to rest briefly.
We are all tired from battling\Nthe forces of Lucifon.
You may not!
Wait! Among us is...
Natasha?
Seil...
Wow, you're pretty!
Lord Dragon Knight?!
Dear Elder! Your health will suffer\Nneedlessly venturing out like this.
Is your father Lord Burn?
As prescribed by the ancient alliance,\Nmy tribe shall
henceforth fight along side our\NDragon Knight!
So Seil really was the Dragon Knight.
\NEto...
Yes?
Are you sure Seil's okay? I\Nwonder what he's doing right now?
Don't worry. He'll join us as soon as\Nhe gets the hang of riding on dragons.
But we're talking about Seil. I'm\Nguessing he's wailing right about now.
We'll take a break once\Nwe get past this pass.
The mountain-side must've collapsed.
Making it over this isn't\Ngoing to be easy.
Artillery, have the cavalry help you.
Time for action, sappers!
This is a trap! Keep your guard up!
Nereid!
Bastards don't fight fair!
This isn't good!
They've cut off our rear!
We're surrounded!
Did this happen before as well?
People who won't give\Nup on their dreams
They all have a bright\Nglitter in their eyes
Together with you, someday I wish
We'll take off flying\Ntoward realizing our dreams
No matter how tough it\Nis, I'll be with you
So don't let things bother\Nyou, let me know everything
Between the two of us, we\Ncan share any suffering
Your wings shine\Nwith vivid radiance
As they beat through the air,\Naiming into the sky, flying free
Anybody, as long as\Nthere's something precious
They hold dear to their heart
Then they'll always shine\Nthrough any day or time
Next Episode
I wonder how many times\NEto has confronted Lucifon?
Each and every one of them must\Nhave passed on to the next Kakeru,
the next Eto, great\Nanger and deep anguish,
before they then disappeared.
To break from this endless closed\Ncycle of history, Marlene,
it will take you to do it.
Next and final Dragon Knight: Eternal!