Long... Oh, so long ago.
So long ago that I can't\Nremember anymore...
I was in a war.
It seemed I had been in\Na war for a long time.
But against who? And why?
The war... I wonder what\Nhappened to it?
And why am I...
Why am I still alive?
There's no time to explain.
Marlene?
Come, put this on.
This was your most\Ncoveted possession.
If only... If only I had\Nlistened to you before.
To me?
Kakeru, I beg you. Please do as I say.
Take this.
What is this?
Now, hold this stone\Nagainst your chest.
Please believe in me, and pray hard\Nso that your wish will be granted.
Wish what?
Kakeru, do you wish to remain here\Nand rot until the end of time?!
You must go back to the\Npast and persuade me.
Lucifon's powers can be\Ncountered if I am with you.
Go back to the past\Nand persuade you?
That's right.
I can go back?
Yes, you can.
But there is something\Nyou must never forget.
You must never allow your past\Nself to know who you really are.
Is that clear?
I don't quite get what you're saying.
Do not worry. As long as you\Nremember what I have said,
it will be fine.
But what about you, Marlene?
I can't leave you here alone.
As long as you have such\Nkindness in your heart,
you will overcome\NLucifon the next time.
Marlene, we'll run away\Ntogether! Okay!
Don't be alarmed. Once you change\Nthe past, I will no longer be here.
You must hurry.
Lucifon will be here in no time.
He will kill you.
If you should die,\Nit will mean the end.
Please pray.
Nothing's happening.
Kakeru, can you recall Natasha's end?
Kakeru!
Natasha! Grab my arm!
Do it, now!
I can't! My grip is so weak!
No! You have to force\Nyourself to grab on to me!
I can't! Kakeru, I just can't!
Kakeru, please let go. I don't\Nwant you to fall with me.
I don't care if I do fall down\Nwith you! So please, hold on to me!
Kakeru... You've done all you can.
I'm sorry...
Natasha!
Natasha's life is gone forever\Nunless you change the past.
I want to go back!
I want to go back to the past and\Nsave Natasha, keep her from harm.
I've got to save Natasha!
Yes, pray even harder.
To save her, you must\Ngo back in time.
You must go back! To the past!
I want to go to the past!
Yes, to the past.
To the past. To the past! I\Nhave to get back!
Now, I will return back to the past!
Forgive the sad state of my castle.
Alas, most have run off.
We are the few that\Nhave remained behind.
And so, you are the heir\Nto Sir Takeru the Brave?
Heir?
He is asking if you are Takeru's son.
Oh, yeah, sure. My name's Kakeru.
And he's Burn's son, Seil.
I ask you, then. Where are\NSir Takeru and Sir Burn?!
Well, they're at home!
That's why Seil and I came.
What shall we do?
Are you aware of the Black Mist\Nencroaching from the western skies?
The Black Mist?
Yes, anyone engulfed in the\Nmist is said to turn to stone.
What?! Then does that\Nmean... My dad is...
If Sir Burn is still in the town\Nof Sogya, then I'm afraid he too...
Oh, no!
The Black Mist was dispatched\Nby Lucifon, a man who appeared
in the far eastern\Nkingdom of Reimling.
Lucifon has employed\Nsorcery to deceive people,
compelling them to send\Ntheir armies against us.
There is word that even dragons\Nhave been dispatched against us.
Dragons! Ain't that cool, Seil?!
Yeah, sure...
Wow, that's so awesome.\NWish I could see them!
Such idle talk!
When even Sir Takeru has\Nbeen turned to stone!
It was absolutely imperative\NSir Takeru the Brave
and Sir Burn rallied to our cause.
My daughter was being married\Ninto the Reimling royalty.
No matter now. The Black\NMist is almost upon us.
There is nothing we can do anymore.
Let them retire.
Yes, Sire.
Kakeru, what should we do?
So that's the Black Mist.
Its color really is black!
Well, isn't that rather obvious?
I'm not sure I can make it\Nif I'm with you, Kakeru.
Kakeru! Kakeru!
What are you doing here?!\NWe need to run! Come!
Hurry, there's no time to waste!
Who are you, old man?
I am not an old man! You can\Ncall me older brother!
But there's no time for that! Just run!
Who does this geezer think he is?
There's no time! Just\Nhurry and run! Now!
Yeah, sure. Let's get\Nout of here while we can!
Just run! Everyone!\NRun toward the east!
Run! Run!
I can't go any further.
We'll be safe here for the moment.
So who are you, old man?
I am not an old man!
Enough of that, already.\NI'm asking your name.
Oh, I see. Yes, well, uh...
That's it! Eto! My name is Eto.
Our town...
Mommy!
Who would do such a...
Everyone listen to me!
Everybody, please hear\Nwhat I have to say!
We need to defeat that mist, and\Nrestore those turned to stone!
To do that, we need to defeat the\Nperson who unleashed that mist!
So you're talking about Lucifon?
That's right!
Lucifon is in the Reimling kingdom\Nlocated far to the east!
Just now, the forward forces of his\Narmies are just about to reach us.
So, we're between a rock and a\Nhard place if we do nothing.
We will embark upon a\Njourney to the east.
This will be a long journey where\Nwe aim to defeat Lucifon's armies
and take down Lucifon!
And here with us is Takeru\Nthe Brave's son, Kakeru,
and Burn the Dragon\NKnight's son, Seil!
They will come with us!
Come, those who boast\Ngreat skills in combat!
Champions of courage\Nand noble at heart!
Rally to our cause and\Njoin us in our odyssey!
Days of fighting begin yet again.
Though my view has changed,\Nthe fighting is familiar.
The same encounters repeated again.
The same unfortunate souls\Ndoomed to die once again.
But I have to change the course\Nof events, no matter what!
What? The Lucifon forces\Nare petty wimpy.
My, my heart, still going\Na mile a minute.
I'm so scared.
Don't let your guard down.\NWe've only just begun to fight.
Let's go! Let's make it\Nto the town before dusk.
Once we make it to the town,\Nrelax and get rested, everyone.
Make sure to grab something\Nto eat and tend your weapons.
I used to be held captive by the\NLucifon forces. Please let me join you!
Sure, no problem. Right, Eto?
Of course.
I'm still a beginner sorceress,\Nbut I'll work hard!
I won't forgive the Lucifon forces!
Forward march!
Heed my call, travelers!
I am the Knight Charon!
I found this woman collapsed\Non the road to Lavinnia,
but I am traveling to Lavinnia to\Nconfront the Lucifon forces there.
I ask that you take her\Nand tend to her care.
Natasha!
Seil, help Nereid!
Yeah, sure.
Easy now, easy...
But what is Natasha doing here?
My type...
Natasha! Natasha!
Ka... Kakeru...
Kakeru!
Natasha...
Natasha!
Horrible...
This is so awful...
She's alive! This lady's still alive!
Wow, she sure is a beautiful lady.
They were all murdered.
As a proud elfin tribe, we told\Nthem we would never join them.
You should save your strength.
Eto, let's get her\Nunder a roof somewhere.
Eto! What's the matter?
Oh, what did you say, Kakeru?
I said we should get her\Nto a safe place and rest.
Oh, yes...
Certainly, sounds good.
Eto, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing. I'll carry her.
Just as you pleaded with me to,
I've come back, Marlene.
I beg you. Please do not\Nleave me behind.
Please take me with you!
But...
I know a thing or two about archery.
I will not let myself\Nbecome a burden to you.
Sure, okay.
Right, Eto?
In any case, with this rain, we\Nmight as well stay here to rest.
Natasha...
Huh? It's Natasha. You\Nsure are awake early.
Humph.
Wow, is it like, you're seeing me off?
Oh, don't flatter yourself!
I was taking a stroll thinking\Nover things, and by coincidence...
This early in the morning?
Oh, be quiet!
I bet you're gonna feel\Nlonely when I'm gone.
That's not likely. Why should I?!
Yeah, I suppose so. You wouldn't\Nmiss me a bit, I guess.
Oh, I just wish you would go\Nfar way and never come back.
I'll finally be able to walk safely\Nwithout you messing with me.
You're right. I'm sorry, Natasha.
Well then, bye-bye, Natasha.
Bye-bye? Wait, Kakeru,\Nare you leaving already?
Yup!
Kakeru! Kakeru!
I said wait!
Here, take this with you.
What's this?
I made this... cursed talisman!
A cursed talisman?
Yes, that's right.\NA cursed talisman!
What?
Thank you, I'll take it since you\Nwent through all the trouble.
Take care, Natasha!
Kakeru, you big jerk!
Kakeru... You've done all you can.
I'm sorry.
Natasha!
Yes, pray even harder.
To save her, you must\Ngo back in time.
Eto!
Hey!
There you are. Let's go!
Oh, yes, I'm sorry.
Right, let's go!
Aeolus Blade!
Get set to take the fort!
Help me!
Help! Help me!
Who the hell are you?
No! Stop this!
I'm in the middle of something.
Why don't you take a hint?
Marlene!
Yes, Sir.
Listen while you\Nstill have your ears.
We've defeated everyone\Nin your little group here.
What?!
Beat it! I don't have the time to\Nmess with small fish like you!
No, wait!
Who is it?
Well...
I was in such danger. I must\Nthank you for saving me.
No, I did nothing special.
Is there something else?
I, well...
It's all right. It'll be all right.
Claris...
The Lucifon forces... My\Ntwin sister, Claris, was...
Did they murder her?
No, they took her away.
Then don't lose hope, Mayfair.
Everyone with us has lost a father, a\Nmother or siblings in this war.
We aim to defeat Lucifon so there\Nwon't be any more needless victims,
to put an end to the\Npeople's suffering.
Those separated from loved ones\Nmight still be rejoined with them.
So don't give up hope, and\Ncome along with us, Mayfair.
At the end of this journey,\Nwe will defeat him!
Eto...
So, Eto was comforting Mayfair.
Now I know what he\Nwas doing back then.
Perhaps this was also Eto's mission.
Not only to fight, but also to...
Eto, let me be on top...
Eto...
Your face... Please let me\Nsee your face.
I can't.
I have a horrible scar upon it.
That wouldn't bother...
Eto! Eto!
Kakeru...
This time, you must defeat Lucifon.
You must persuade me.
Eto?
Mayfair...
Yes?
I have something I have to ask you.
You're from the village\Nof Trianon, right?
Yes, that's right.
Is Marlene from Trianon?
Marlene? No, the first I saw her\Nwas when you came to save me.
I see.
Forget I asked that\Nquestion. All right?
Yes, Sir. I understand.
When will you be leaving today?
Well, right after the sun rises.
Then Eto, could we...
Once more?
To be continued
People who won't give\Nup on their dreams
They all have a bright\Nglitter in their eyes
Together with you, someday I wish
We'll take off flying toward\Nrealizing our dreams
No matter how tough it\Nis, I'll be with you
So don't let things bother\Nyou, let me know everything
Between the two of us, we\Ncan share any suffering
Your wings shine\Nwith vivid radiance
As they beat through the air,\Naiming into the sky, flying free
Anybody, as long as\Nthere's something precious
They hold dear to their heart
Then they'll always shine\Nthrough any day and time
Next Episode
As Kakeru, my odyssey was so simple.
I slew my enemies before me. That\Nwas all.
But now, I cannot allow\Nmyself to be defeated.
I don't want any of my friends to die.
Nor can I lose Marlene again.
However, this newcomer female knight\Nkeeps trying to provoke me.
Damn spitfire.
Next Dragon Knight: Princess!