Once upon a time, when
swords and sorcery ruled all things...
The Dragon Devil clan
emerged from beyond time and space.
They laid waste to the earth, and
pandemonium filled the human world.
ln order to save humanity, the Dragon
Knights bravely fought against them...
...astride their own dragons.
The battle with the Dragon God clan
was the second war between God and Devil.
After the struggle, a
controller of magic named Reyna...
...confined the three kings of the
Dragon Devil clan, Uruto, Golgo, and lrya.
Musa, a knight of the Dragon God clan...
...entered the Devil world in order to
annihilate the rest of the Dragon Devil clan.
Musa, don't think
you have already won.
l will definitely resurrect the
three gods and destroy you!
Oruga!
Where are you hiding?
Hey Oruga, you're thinking of slipping
away through time and space, aren't you?
The castle of the Dragon Devil clan was
destroyed and peace returned to the world.
And then, ten years passed...
Thief!
What will you do?
What?
Mom!
ls that so?
You want to return to the
castle and become a Dragon Knight?
Yes, my name is Rike, Rike Arrow.
Sorry, she thought you were a thief.
Karisu is so careless, l
wonder if she'll ever get married...
Oh, yes, Rike, would
you like to marry her?
Wait, Mom!
No thanks, not my type.
What did you mean by saying that?
Well, let me see...
Thank you for dinner.
Time to go.
To be a Dragon Knight, l have to
find my own dragon, so l have to go.
Dragon!
ls that so?
l hope you can find one.
What is that?
lt's the Dragon Devil clan!
Karisu, Aunt, run away, now!
How about you?
l will fight with them!
l am a knight.
How can l run away?
Before the three Devil gods are
reborn, l must kill everyone in this town.
l got it.
Mom, hurry up!
Oh!
Mom!
Karisu, l'm okay, so go ahead!
l can't do that.
Wait a little, l will save you...
Forget about it.
lf you do...
But...
Aunt, Karisu!
Asshole!
Aunt, shit!
Karisu...
Flying Dragon Transformation!
Karisu!
Flying Dragon Strike!
Karisu?
What are those wings?
This is my other form.
Rike, please take care of my Mom.
Wait, Karisu.
God damn, Dragon
Devil, killing innocent people...
That girl is...
Vacuum Flight!
Shit, who is that?
Rising Dragon Stomp!
Dancing Razor Gale!
You killed my group of
Dragon Devils in a moment.
But, you can't kill me like that.
Your attack failed!
Shit!
Cut it out, now!
Mom...
l will tear you to shreds.
White Dragon Light Ray!
Oruga!
Musa, you came all the way here!
Who are you...
Karisu, can you fly?
What?
Yeah...
She knows my name.
Who is she?
Karisu...
Karisu, l have to report the
Dragon Devil clan to my king right away!
l have to go.
We will go together...
Rike, please take me with you.
l want to know...
Who l really am...
What happened in my past...
Otherwise, l won't be able to
live in peace in the human world.
All right, let's go to
the capitol together.
Rike...
Yes.
Sorry, Mom.
l'm leaving you all alone.
She was a very kind
mother, wasn't she?
Mom saved me when l was abandoned
by the forest lake sixteen years ago.
Hiding the fact that l was
the descendent of a dragon...
...she brought me up as her daughter.
However...
Rike...
No, Mom!
Don't die!
Don't leave me here alone.
No, Mom!
Hey, Rike?
Why do you really
want to be a Dragon Knight?
lt's always been every
young man's dream to be one.
lt's not easy to find one's own dragon.
However, l will
definitely be a Dragon Knight.
For myself and my dad!
Your father?
Yes, l was found by
my foster father, like you.
He had a hard time
bringing me up by himself.
l want to let make him proud
by becoming a Dragon Knight.
You are so kind, Rike.
Not really, l'm just...
Rike's dragon...
l have no choice!
l'll be your dragon.
What?
What do you mean?
Red Dragon Transformation!
Karisu...
Dragon!
This is my true form.
Karisu!
Did l scare you?
l am talking into your heart.
ls it true that you are Karisu?
Here, get on right away!
Sure!
lt's wonderful and amazing, Karisu!
Thanks.
You know what, Karisu?
Can my thoughts reach you, too?
lt's impossible now,
you need a little practice.
Wish strongly with
my image in your heart.
lf you do, your thoughts will
definitely reach me someday soon.
Wish strongly, huh?
l didn't know that Karisu had been
reincarnated in the human world...
Destiny is strange.
Karisu, l wonder if l
should wake you up.
Karisu, look.
That is Dragon's Eye, the
king's castle of Dragoon kingdom.
Who is flying up there?
Hold on, where is Ramie?
Ramie, come out, now!
That you, Ramie?
You shouldn't come such a place.
Horrific Demon gods
have been confined here.
Okay, nobody is here.
l will transform into a human.
Here l am.
What is this dragon?
lt's an illusion.
l used a magic called lllusion.
This is embarrassing, so
please put me down now.
Rike, are you okay?
Rike!
Rike...
l love you...
l love you very much.
Rike, please come back soon...
Rike.
Rike, do you have to go?
Yes, l will definitely find
my dragon and come back.
Lydia, if l become a Dragon
Knight, l will always stay with you.
l'm so happy.
Oh, there, yes.
Rike...
lf Rike doesn't stay with me, l will be...
l love you, Rike...
Princess!
Hey, what are you doing?
Ramie...
Princess, Rike came back!
ls it true?
lt's true, isn't it?
Thanks, Ramie!
Dad!
Oh, Rike, you came back!
You look fine, yes.
Absolutely.
Daddy, look.
Wow...
That's a wonderful dragon.
Rike, who is the girl?
Daddy, let me introduce her.
She is Karisu from Tarutarp village.
Karisu, this is my father.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, my son, how did you find her?
lt is hard to find such a beautiful girl.
Hey, tell me.
Ouch!
Rike!
Lydia!
Welcome back!
l've been worried about you!
l am sorry, Lydia.
But you have become
so beautiful in a short time.
Well, thanks.
Rike!
Oh, Lydia, let me introduce her.
She is...
Nice to meet you.
My name is Karisu and l have
traveled with Rike all this time.
All this time?
ls that true, Rike?
Oh, yeah, l have to go to the castle.
All right, l will go back and wait for you.
Okay, l got it.
Please explain what's going on later.
See you, Karisu, talk to you soon.
Yes, we will be good friends.
ls that so?
Tarutarp village was
attacked by the Dragon Devil clan?
Send two Dragon Knights to Tarutarp.
Yes, Sir.
Rike, welcome back from
your long training journey.
Let me see your
own dragon, right now.
Sure.
Wow, it's a wonderful dragon.
l think you are
qualified to be a Dragon Knight.
You are too lenient!
We are called the strongest
Dragon Knights in the world.
lf you accept such a young boy as a
Dragon Knight, we will be dishonored.
Oh god, l can't believe that they
are fighting over Lydia's love here.
That's right, it's hard
to control a jealous guy.
Rike, l don't approve of a
Dragon Knight being so young.
Say that again!
Stop, stupid boys!
Fighting in front of me is
the last thing you want to do.
l reject your initiation
into the Dragon Knights!
l would say that, but
it would be no fun at all...
Right, Leon?
Yes, Sir.
l will give you a chance to
fight each other as Dragon Knights.
You will have a contest of
flying speed as Dragon Knights.
lf Rike wins, l will approve of his
membership in the Dragon Knights.
l'll show you!
What?
That's my line!
Don't cry later.
l can't believe that Rike left
right after he met with my father.
Why didn't he come to see me?
Karisu somehow bothers me...
Ramie!
Princess, did you call me?
Ramie, do me a favor.
Please go to see what
Rike is doing, right now.
What?
lt's so late.
Please, only you can help me.
l really want to know what's going on.
Jesus...
lf you use magic for trivial
things, your late mother would cry.
My mom is my mom!
l am me!
Love is a scary thing.
Who are you?
Ms. Avisu...
Please stop.
Ms. Reyna's tomb is
located in this room!
We can't let you in,
even if you are Lydia's nurse.
l see, you'll fight with Voon.
Good, good...
When l was young, l often
fought with the king, Kaizerd.
But today, l was impressed.
Because you came back
with such a beautiful wife.
You're joking!
Such a kidder...
No, no, we aren't...
l mean, she isn't my wife...
What?
lf you are a man, you
have to make it clear.
Yeah, about that...
Karisu, please explain exactly.
Rike, l want to have your baby soon.
K-Karisu!
lf you say no, l'll take her!
He doesn't know who he's dealing with!
You fool, Rike!
Relax, you'll break your best crystal!
Avisu?
l'm your nurse...
lf you're hiding something, l'll find out.
You love Rike, don't you?
Avisu, l'm so sad.
Oh dear!
You are the descendent of...
...a controller of magic, you can easily
dispose of a young woman like Karisu.
Don't worry.
l prepared everything for you.
lt's up to you now...
Avisu!
l...
l'll try.
These women were highly skilled.
ln addition, they've
taken away the Rod.
Who could have done it?
lndeed...
Anyway, report it to the king.
Yes.
During the second war between
God and Devil, one of the three devils...
...Golgo, was confined.
When he rapes a woman...
...he traps her and sucks up all her
spirit, turning her into a vegetable.
Let's use Golgo to keep
Karisu's heart away from Rike.
Come to me, Devil Golgo!
Finally, l broke the seal over the devil.
Golgo, l command you!
You've been trapped, Lydia.
l'm not Avisu.
l am Oruga from the Dragon Devil clan.
You're kidding...
Great three Devils, listen.
lt is time for the
Dragon Devil clan to be reborn.
lt's been a while,
Sir Uruto, Sir Golgo, and Lady lrya.
Oruga, you did a good job.
Listen, Kaizerd the Third, we finally
have a chance to take revenge on you.
And on the magic
controller who confined us...
The magic controller has already died.
But her daughter is there, look...
You arranged things very well.
ln that case, l will enjoy her slowly.
No...
Don't come near me!
No, stop!
No, stop, please.
Oh yeah, you're well equipped.
Please, help!
Cry more, scream more.
Golgo, you haven't changed.
Stop...
l'm losing my mind...
Rike...
l will do her.
As you like.
lrya, you always keep a straight face.
No!
Stop, l'm embarrassed!
lt's been a while
since l fucked a human.
l can't stand it...
Please forgive me.
Look, her love juice is dripping all over.
Please don't do it!
No, no, no!
l'll be torn apart!
Rike, help me...
Rike...
You tighten around me well.
l am going crazy.
Not there...
There...
She is the daughter of Reyna, a
controller of magic. How shameful!
We don't have to fear her now.
Such a...
l've never had it like this...
N-No...
No, l'm coming...
What can l...
l'm...
...coming, Rike, l'm coming...
Anything wrong?
No, nothing.
Rike?
l can hear Lydia's voice...
Now that l've raped Kaizerd's daughter,
l'm looking forward to seeing him cry!
Daddy...
Give us your body and accept us.
Accept us, accept us...
lf so, you will have endless ecstasy.
Accept ecstasy, accept it!
`Accept ecstasy, accept it!