Oh my god!
Now what do l do?
My princess has been
possessed by three demons!
Now she scares me more than usual.
l'm afraid that Rike alone
will not be strong enough...
Then there's Karisu, but what is she really?
Next episode, we will
find out in the climax!
Look forward to it.
What?
Someone's going to try and rape me?
Oh no!
At a time when swords
and sorcery ruled all things...
Rike Arrow, a candidate
for the Dragon Knights...
...met Karisu, who was
the decedent of a dragon.
Her mother was killed
by the Dragon Devil Clan...
...and she vowed to
fight as Rike's dragon.
They traveled to Dragon Kingdom,
the stronghold of the Dragon Knights.
However, they are opposed by
three devils, revived by the evil Oruga...
...and Rike's fiancee, Princess Lydia,
who was possessed by the demons.
Now, another battle will rage...
Oruga is so obnoxious.
Karisu, if you wake up, the
three demons wouldn't be so scary.
We should just trust our destiny, now.
Ramie.
Yes!
Oh, no.
You realized it was me?
You know where l was, don't you?
You saw Rike and Karisu, didn't you?
Tell me more about
this Rike and Karisu.
P-Princess...
Avisu, what are you...
Who are you?
l'm lrya.
Dragon Devil Clan?
How did you know, kitty cat?
No, no, no.
Help me princess, l'll be eaten!
l don't wanna die, l don't wanna die.
Be quiet, l won't eat you.
You're lying.
l'll be killed and become bones!
Princess, princess!
You're such a cute kitty.
May l help you, Rike?
lt's okay.
l'm sorry, Karisu.
My dad was too excited.
No problem.
He was happy because he
hasn't seen you in a while.
And, about what my dad said...
What?
Well, he wants you to be my wife.
l know, you have Lydia.
And, if he saw my real form...
Don't think like that!
Rike!
No!
What's this?
Karisu, don't struggle!
No, no, l can't believe it.
Karisu, calm down, Karisu.
Rike, leave me alone.
B-But, l have to make the bed.
l'm sorry.
Good night.
Rike...
l know it was my fault, but...
Karisu was suddenly
ashamed, what's with her?
l don't know why but,
l'm thinking about Karisu.
l have Lydia, though...
Rike, are you still awake?
Y-Yes.
Don't worry about earlier.
O-Okay.
l was thinking about tomorrow's game.
l hope you can win.
Yes, thank you.
Then, you can see Lydia everyday.
Well...
No... Y-Yes...
Why are you stuttering?
N-Not really.
Look, what do you think l am?
l look human as well as Dragon.
Karisu...
Well, it's okay.
lf you become a Dragon
Knight, l'll leave here, anyway.
N-No.
Please stay here, Karisu.
Karisu, if you leave, l'm...
R-Rike...
K-Karisu, l...
Karisu...
Finally, you'll have a
game with Rike tomorrow.
Yes, l will certainly win tomorrow.
And, l'll show him the real
power of a Dragon Knight.
l'm sure you can do it.
Go for it, tomorrow.
Y-Yes.
M-Miss Lydia...
The King and the Dragon Knights
will pray for the Dragon Devil Clan.
We will have your body, too.
Y-You guys are?
Warrior Karisu, who was once
called the best of the Dragon God Clan...
l can't believe that she lost to someone
like Oruga of the Dragon Devil Clan.
Orufe, it's good.
Orufe, l love you, Orufe.
l don't care about the
Dragon God Clan any more.
lf you are with me...
l want to go somewhere
nobody knows about, with you...
Why can't we love each other?
Come on, Orufe!
Come on!
l want to have your baby!
Orufe...
Karisu loved a young man
from the Dragon Devil Clan.
l didn't expect her to intercept Oruga
when he showed up among the humans.
However, she was sealed and
reborn as a human in modern times.
Hey...
What?
l'm sorry, last night, l slapped you.
lt's my fault.
l was stupid.
Besides, it was just
payment for a good feel.
S-Stupid lecher!
Rike...
Karisu, we have to win!
Yes.
For Rike's grand dream.
Lydia!
Hey, Lydia, it's me.
Lydia, l promise, we will win today.
What happened?
Excuse me, Karisu.
Wait a minute.
O-Okay.
Hey, Lydia, wait for me!
Lydia, Lydia!
Karisu, Karisu, Karisu, my Karisu.
l'm your mother from now on.
Don't fool with me.
Oh no, you're a problem child.
You have to learn cooking
soon and become a good wife.
You grew so much.
You'll be taller than me soon.
Karisu, my precious Karisu.
l want to go back my mom's village...
But, l decided to do
my best as Rike's Dragon.
Karisu, l'm sorry about...
lt's okay!
We should
concentrate on the game, now.
We will begin the race
between Rike and Voon!
Get the flag on the peak of
Erukesu Mountain, 30 km from here...
...and the one who
comes back first is the winner.
Are you guys ready?
Yes!
Ready, go!
Does Voon think l have a handicap?
Voon, he's giving up the lead...
ldiot, don't dig your own grave.
A final bit of entertainment...
Have a fun, Kaizerd.
Karisu, we should
finish this game in one rush!
Okay, hold on!
Did Voon give up?
Rike!
Voon!
Rike, are you all right?
What is Voon doing?
Where did he go?
Karisu, left!
lllusion!
Where's the real one?
What is that?
Good timing.
She is the garnish on
today's entertainment.
Twin Darkness Ring!
You are...
l'm Musa of the Dragon
God Clan, Karisu's side.
Where is Karisu?
Hey!
She is all right.
And, you will know
about her past soon.
Karisu's past?
These wings...
Dragon Devil Clan?
Voon, what is this?
She is a demon, pretending to
be Rike's dragon to deceive us.
We should finish her off.
Who is this girl?
This is the girl who killed
our fellows in Tarutarp village.
Then we should kill her, immediately.
Wait, Voon.
Go to hell, monster!
White Dragon Light Ray!
White Dragon Light Ray?
Rike and you are Musa's...
Shit, Musa already detected us.
Karisu!
Karisu, wake up, Karisu.
l see, you followed Oruga to get here.
That voice is, as l expected...
Lydia?
Karisu!
Lydia, what are you doing?
Karisu, Karisu, wake up!
Karisu!
lrya, Golgo, appear!
Now we'll get revenge!
Long time no see, King Kaizerd.
However, l guess you
don't recognize me in this shape.
Demon Dragon Transformation!
Shit!
That...
The three headed dragon...
Oh, no, did Lydia make them appear?
Everybody, get together!
Come on, Kaizerd.
l'll fight you myself!
Karisu, wake up.
Don't die!
Dragon Devil Clan, l'll obliterate you!
After we beat you...
...we will exterminate
all humans in this world!
Originally, this wouldn't kill a
member of the Dragon God Clan...
...but her power is sealed now...
Tell me, what happened in her past.
Majesty, are these not Dragon Devils?
Kaizerd, you should watch as your
proud Dragon Knights are destroyed!
Deadly Darkness Extinction Blast!
Kain, Roisu, Randy!
Shit, son of a...
Really, Karisu did all that...
Rike, put your hand on her chest.
To break her seal, she doesn't need
only my power, but also someone's love.
Rike, do you love this girl?
lf she has your love, her seal
will be broken and she will revive.
Wish strongly with
my image in your heart.
lf you do, your thoughts will
definitely reach me someday soon.
The three headed dragon
is whirling about in the sky.
Like the battle back then...
My love, Orufe...
You deceived me and
killed many from my clan.
l believed you, though...
Orufe, Orufe, did you really love me?
But, you are already mine.
l won't give you to anybody...
All mine...
Karisu, wake up, Karisu.
Who is calling my name?
l see, this young person
is the other man l loved.
But l wasn't really myself...
No, Karisu.
Although you were reborn in the
human world, your love for him was real.
Karisu!
Respond to Rike's heart!
Karisu.
Are you Karisu?
Finally, you woke up.
Musa?
Karisu...
Orufe...
l'm glad!
Rike...
Majesty, it's hopeless.
They are too strong for us.
Shit!
Oh no, my Dragon's Eye!
We must beat them,
even at the cost of our lives!
Please, pull back your soldiers!
Musa?
No, it's not!
That's the girl, Karisu!
Rike's Fighting Dragon!
Back off, Kid!
l will get Lydia back.
Cheeky brat.
We'll show you our true power.
What?
Yes!
Good job, but if you
use your breath any more...
This girl, who is
fused with us, will die too!
Lydia!
Rike, Dad...
Rike, l'm sorry.
Many people died because of me.
lf l didn't do such a stupid thing...
Don't worry about me.
Please, destroy them!
lt's unavoidable, Rike.
No, Majesty, we shouldn't...
l drove Lydia to this...
That's true.
Just stay quiet until we
complete our regeneration.
That is a horrible power, which
steals souls and converts it into energy.
lf Lydia doesn't try to
save herself, she'll never escape.
Rike, only you can make her try.
l understand, l'll try.
Help me, Karisu.
Sure.
What are you doing?
Will you leave our princess stranded?
lt can't be!
Where did you hide?
What are you trying to do?
Rike, it's okay.
Everyone has a grudge
against me, and even you hate me.
l have no place to go back to.
Don't be stupid!
Lydia, no one has a grudge you.
You were just deceived.
Everybody is waiting for you.
Don't die, let's go back, Lydia.
Don't make everyone sad.
But...
You have Karisu...
l'm sorry about Karisu,
but Lydia, l want you...
l want you to live!
Rike, l...
l actually don't want to die...
l want to live more and more!
Rike!
Karisu!
Lydia, Rike!
Karisu, Rike!
ls Lydia okay?
Don't worry, Majesty.
Karisu!
Was l dreaming?
No, it was an obvious fact...
There is a man who needs me.
l also need him.
To respond to that, one more time...
...one more time...
Rike...
Karisu...
l was...
You passed out after
beating the three headed dragon.
Karisu, l'm sorry.
l've been...
Don't say anything,
l know what happened...
l've heard everything from
Musa, but l love you as you are now.
You fool...
No, if you do it...
lt's too...
Too good...
Please...
Don't...
K-Karisu...
This is for earlier,
l won't forgive you easily.
l'll stroke you slowly.
l'm already...
Hold back!
Don't come by yourself, it's not fair.
You naughty girl, l'll punish you all night.
No!
Please, be nice to me...
B-Beautiful...
That tickles!
No...
Rike...
Rike, please don't be mean to me.
What do you want me to do?
My body feels so strange.
Please...
Lick me, lick me there!
Karisu, you are so cute.
Good, good...
Rike, lick more...
Karisu, touch it.
See?
l drank from your
vessel, and l got so hard!
l know, dummy!
Please, enter me!
l feel it!
lt's so hot and thick inside me!
Good, good!
Rike, push it in deeper!
Great!
l can feel it all the way inside me.
Move around more!
Move...
So good!
Karisu, l'm coming.
Wait, Rike!
l want to come with you!
Karisu, you're getting tighter!
l know, you're getting bigger inside me!
Rike!
l feel so good.
l feel you filling me up more and more!
l see, he's gone.
Yes, with Karisu.
He promised that he would become
a true Dragon Knight, and come back.
Sounds like him.
He is the man who l trust.
Don't forget, he is my son.
Rike has left...
With Karisu...
Please come back
safely, then l will be your lover.
Don't you envy young people?
Yes.
Rike, have experiences as broad
as this sky, and then come back.
Rike, where are we going?
First, we will visit your mother's grave.
After that?
After that...
Let's explore the wide, free world!
Rike, l'm with you.
Feeling good, Karisu?
у