There's no point in you dying with us.
What is that supposed to mean?!
If you die, you won't meet Lucifon.
My...
We can't keep up.
We're suffering heavy casualties.\NWhat should we do?
Eto, let's make a break for it!
At this rate, we'll be cut\Ndown like animals in a cage.
Finish off everyone but Kakeru!
You may do with the\Nwomen as you wish!
Oh, yeah! Let's finish 'em off!
It's Seil!
Now! Hit them while\Nthey are scattering!
Damn it! Pull back! Pull back!
They took Marlene!
Marlene!
It seems we're quite a\Nbit ahead of the others.
It will probably take them three\Ndays to get here from the valley.
Marlene?
Eto, I beg you. Stop\Nthis war with Lucifon.
Why are you saying\Nsomething like that?
If we stop, then what?
But at this rate, everyone,\Nyou, Kakeru, Natasha, will die.
You know well that we have\Nfew other choices remaining.
I have a sister that I left\Nbehind in the Underworld.
My older sister Mano; she\Nsacrificed her own body so that
her father would accept\Nher marriage to Lucifon.
She had the black stone removed\Nfrom her womb well aware of
the curse that would\Naccompany such an act.
So you're telling me your sister\Nwas in love with Lucifon?
In the end, my father came\Nto accept the marriage.
As the king of the Underworld, no one\Nwould oppose my father's decision.
So that's why you came to this\Nworld chasing after Lucifon.
Do you really love Lucifon?
Yes, I do. I love Lucifon.
Then why do you ask me to\Nstop our battle against him?
Why did you save me when the
dragons attacked Captain Zum's ship?
If you love Lucifon that much,\Nwould you not want to see me die?
Marlene, you are not in\Nlove with Lucifon.
How can you say that?!
The feelings you have are because you\Nfeel you are competing with your sister
or because you might have\Nrevered Lucifon in some way.
And you believe you\Ncannot go back anymore.
Oh, please stop!
I beg you. Please, please stop.
You are free. Why don't\Nyou go to Lucifon?
It would probably be better\Nthat we separated here and now.
Wait!
Please wait. Eto, please stay with me.
I can't!
But I'm in love with you!
I recognized this\Nfeeling inside me,
but I am the daughter of King\NMinakkus of the Underworld,
and you are the one from\Nthe bloodlines of the gods.
I knew professing such\Na thing wouldn't...
That's why I...
I didn't want to admit\Nto what I felt inside.
So warm.
I... I don't want to\Nmake you suffer any more.
Eto, no matter what\Nhappens from now on,
that won't change\Nhow happy I am now.
If this is a dream, I\Ndon't want to wake from it.
Marlene...
Eto...
I can't hold back anymore.\NPlease, come into...
Wait, please don't move yet.
Please stay still\Ninside me for a moment.
I want to feel you inside me.
Please... Lie if you must, but\Nplease tell me you love me.
I love you, Marlene.
Oh, why can't the flow\Nof time stop right now?
Eto, please don't forget me.
I won't. Ever...
Eto...
Eto, please go ahead.
Marlene...
Not yet.
Let me be like this\Nfor a moment more.
Marlene...
Eto!
Are you all right, Eto?
Eto?
This is all that's left?
Yeah...
I see. But we must move\Non, to defeat Lucifon!
What about Marlene, Eto?
Oh, she will come later.
Yes, she will!
This is Reimling Castle?!
Lucifon's in there?
That's right.
In honor of those turned to stone\Nand those that fell coming here.
All right, everyone. Let's go.
Seil, aren't you afraid?
Thinking about defeating Lucifon\Nso I can have my daddy back...
Thinking about that helps\Nkeep my legs steady.
You were so nice to come,\Ndear Kakeru.
Where?!
So that's what Lucifon sounds like.
You cheatin' bastard! Show yourself!
Enough with the theatrics.
Come out, Lucifon!
It certainly has been\Nan entertaining time.
I'm a little saddened to\Nthink it will all end now.
Show yourself, Lucifon!
So those insignificant germs\Nare your friends, Kakeru?
You'll find out just how insignificant\Nthey are when we fight.
Is that so? Well...
Why don't you ask your friends just\Nhow insignificant they are yourself?
What?!
My body... It's frozen.
Kakeru, it's as if our\Nbodies have turned to stone.
Seil, help me!
It won't budge!
I can't hold a pen!
Kakeru...
My body won't move either.
What?! What's going on, everyone?!
Mayfair! Charon!\NNatasha! Bianca?! Eto?!
Damn it! What the hell\Ndid you do to my friends?!
Is this the end?
Oh, dear Kakeru, this is\Nwhere it gets interesting.
He... Help!
Ka... Kakeru... Get Marlene...
Eto!
Ka... Kakeru... My mouth... I can't...
Natasha!
I'm sorry, Helen.
Well, what do you think, Kakeru?
It seems your friends were\Ninsignificant germs after all.
Damn you!
What?!
We can move again.
Ino!
Marlene!
Ino, what are you doing here?
Lucifon...
Please don't kill these people!
Ino? It's Marlene, right?
Please, Lucifon...
Marlene, how do you know Lucifon?!
How did you enter into this world, Ino?
Using the black stone that\Nmy father had...
Is that so?
You chased after me, didn't you?
Lucifon...
It's all right, Ino. I should\Nhave given you more attention.
I understand, so why don't you\Ncease countering my magic now.
Ino!
Marlene...
Dear Kakeru, this woman's\Nname is not Marlene.
She is Ino, daughter of the ruler\Nof the Underworld, King Minakkus.
Tell me. It's a lie, right?
Lucifon, I beg you. Go back.
Back to the Underworld\Nwhere Mano awaits you!
Ino, are you siding with the humans?\NYou couldn't possibly do that.
I... I...
Why, that would be preposterous,\Nwouldn't it?
Lucifon, I...
My adorable Ino. Come\Nto my side, child.
You can't do that, Marlene!
What is it, Ino? Did you not enter\Nthis world hoping to be loved by me?
You... You could not bring\Nyourself to love me.
Nor can I love you.
I am in love with Eto.
Marlene!
I am Eto!
Why, he's nothing but a human!
Ino, how could a woman of the\NUnderworld love a human male?
Lucifon, you'll most likely\Nnever learn that answer
no matter how many times\Nyou are reincarnated.
Rubbish. Come, Ino. Come to my side.
I will not! I now know how wrong I\Nwas before.
Ino! Oh, to think how saddened\NKing Minakkus will be to hear this!
The curse that has enveloped your\Nsister will never be lifted!
And you tell me to use the stone\Nto go back to the Underworld?!
Lucifon...
It would take little to\Nhave you all killed.
I would die for the\Nsake of Eto. Willingly!
Enough!
Souls of my servants without bodies,
exact your wrath, and feast upon\Nthe bodies of the bugs before me!
Listen up! This is the last battle!
Once we defeat him, peace\Nwill come back to the world!
Ready, Natasha?! Lucifon!
Aeolus Blade!
Lucifon!
Do you wish that I unleash\Nmy true powers?!
Oh, no!
I had so many ideas in mind of how\Nto entertain you, dear Kakeru.
But I'll have to make you pay\Nfor scarring me like this.
You will pay slowly.
Kakeru!
And oh so painfully.
You cheatin' bastard, Lucifon!
Come out, I know\Nyou're hiding here!
Eto!
You...
Let Marlene go, Lucifon.
Ino, seems you've beguiled\Nthese two quite thoroughly.
I have not beguiled them.
Only those of the Underworld and\Nthose from the bloodline of the gods
can enter this space.
Then... Who are you?
Lucifon, it seems there are\Nthings even you do not know.
Who are you? Who?!
Damn you...
You runt!
Eto, watch out!
Now, Kakeru!
It all ends now, Lucifon.
You?!
Impossible! How could I... I...
My God!
\NEto...
Eto!
Sir Kakeru, Sir Eto!\NWe have persevered!
How is your injury?
Now I can go back to the\Nbastion, where my grandpa is!
Eto...
Wait, Eto! Take me.\NPlease take me with you.
Eto? Are you going away now?
Eto...
You've grown big\Nand strong, Kakeru.
I'm proud of how you\Ndefeated Lucifon.
It's all thanks to you, Eto. I was only\Nable to fight this long thanks to you.
So, Eto, where are you\Ngoing? I'll go with you.
Kakeru!
Kakeru, it's time we part ways.
Daddy?
Do I look like Dad?
You look like Dad when\Nhe was young. But why?
I am...
No! You mustn't! Please don't say it!
I am Kakeru.
But you're Eto, right?
Kakeru, I don't have\Nmuch more time left.
Kakeru, your body...
You protect the peace of\Nthis world from now on.
You must not let it slip into\Nthe hands of the Underworld.
Wait! Where are you\Ngoing? Take me with you!
I... I am returning\Nto where I belong.
Make sure to be more\Nkind to Natasha.
Hey, wait a minute. What's\Nthat supposed to mean?
Seil, please help out Kakeru\Nfrom now on as well.
To think, Sir Eto was Sir Kakeru...
Natasha knows all about\Nthis. Good day, Charon.
Wait, Eto... Will you... Will you\Nbe my husband? Please?
Bianca, make me proud by becoming\Nan exalted princess of Ronboni.
Eto...
Mayfair, I am certain Claris is fine.
Combine your strengths and\Nrebuild the village of Trianon.
But I was hoping to invite\Nyou to our village, Eto.
Natasha, take care of Kakeru.
I'll never forget you.
And I will never\Nforget you as well.
Take care, everybody. I'm so\Nglad I was able to meet you all.
Eto...
Marlene...
No, please, don't go. Please.\NDon't leave me behind.
Goodbye, Marlene...
Eto...
Yume wo akiramenai hito wa
Itumo hitomini tuyoi\Nhikari wo yadoshite iru
Kimi to issho ni watashi mo ituka
Yume ni mukai habatakeru\Nyou ni nagatteru
Donna ni kurushii toki\Nmo soba ni irukara
Hitori de mayowazu\Narinomama wo tsutaete
Futari nara wakeaeru itami
Kimi no tsubasa ga\Nazayaka ni hikaru
Chikara zuyoku habataiteiku\Noozora wo jiyuu ni
Dare mo zibun no\Ntaisetsu na mono wo
Mune ni idaite iru kagiri
Itsu no hi mo kagayakeru