Starvation will kill me before
these stupid monsters will!
Maybe the time's come to give
civilization another try.
What's going on?
Hey! Anybody home?
Talk about screwy setups.
Not a soul around.
I can't believe that even
the bars are closed.
This is ridiculous.
Can't a guy even buy a meal
in this burg?
What a pathetic excuse for a city!
Maybe I should check out that castle.
DRAGON KNIGHT
Ouch!
Hey, take it easy! Didn't anyone ever
tell you girls are the weaker sex?
Will someone explain this
ruffian's presence?
Yes, Your Highness.
After breaking into the palace kitchen,
this knave proceeded to
ravish the royal pantry.
Stealing food? How vulgar!
Now, wait just a second!
I was out there yelling, "Yoo hoo!"
until I turned blue,
and nobody saw fit to answer me!
What can I say? My stomach
was empty,
and my eyes saw food on the table,
so my arm decided it was time
to take matters in hand!
"Breakfasting and Entering"
is the charge.
Is eating on the sly a habit of yours?
Not on your life!
Takeru Yamato's the name,
freelance adventurer, philosopher,
and party animal.
I also swing a pretty mean sword,
if you know what I mean.
We have no need for sword swingers
here, freelance or otherwise.
We're just a bunch of
simple women here.
Take him out and banish him!
Right!
Please, don't!
Please don't, Your Majesty!
Luna?
Your Highness, have you forgotten
the words of the prophet?
What of the promised hero, the
one who will deliver Strawberry
Fields from this curse?
Can we take the chance
of ousting him?
He's the hero?
The hero?
Yes! Now I remember the prophecy:
"When darkened fields
are stripped of flowers
and leaves, out of season,
begin to change,
the moon shall light our waking hours,
and the hero shall come from
the southern range."
I know he looks pretty bad, but first
impressions can be deceiving.
Excuse me for not measuring up!
There is no doubt in my mind;
he is the promised hero.
I see.
Takeru Yamato, seeing
as you are the hero,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Once this was the most
beautiful of countries.
The blessings of the
goddess were many
and the waters of the Fountain of
Happiness flowed throughout the land.
Then, one day, a dark cloud appeared
and enveloped the Goddess' tower.
Suddenly, the water from the magic
fountain ceased to flow,
taking with it our happiness.
The following day, our Goddess
was returned.
This is how we found her.
Encased in stone...
This was the work of the
Dragon Knight clan.
Dragon Knight?
Indeed.
The Dragon Knight overlord
made a proclamation...
Dark clouds are trendy!
The days of Good are gone!
The power of Evil shall triumph,
so let's party till we drop!
It was a really stupid speech!
A showdown between the forces
of Good and Evil...
What's the story on these holes?
They're the key to the
Goddess' powers.
Six jewels fit the six holes.
To restore the Goddess we must
retrieve these jewels.
The jewels being in the hands of
the Dragon Knights, I suppose?
That's right.
Either the Overlord's, or one
of his five Dragon Knights.
To make matters worse,
they've also captured
all the warriors we sent after them.
Even as we speak, they're somewhere
in that dark tower, being tortured.
A tear!
Even sealed in stone, she weeps
for us. It breaks my heart.
Brave Takeru, this is the path
destiny has chosen for you!
Rescue our fallen warriors! Restore
peace and tranquility to our land.
Do these things, and not only shall I
drop the criminal charges against you,
I will grant you any wish you desire.
Now, wait just a second.
Didn't you say something about there
being some monsters involved?
Are you frightened?
Aren't you a MAN?
No, that's not it exactly...
But how can you abandon
all those lovely warriors?
Lovely?
Indeed! Some even prettier than me!
Really?
So, that's how it is.
You know, this "Goddess in a Rock"
business has really touched my heart,
and I could certainly
use the exercise.
You'll do it? Oh, brave Takeru!
But I wouldn't put any money on it!
There's something I've been
wanting to ask you.
33, 22, 32!
No, not THAT! What's the deal
with all those swords?
Those mark the graves of the men
who've gone into the tower before you.
That's one thing about those Dragon
Knights; they really follow through.
They even dig the holes themselves!
That's just swell. I have a bad feeling
about this whole concept.
What are you saying? We have
no choice but to continue!
I guess not.
Oh well, since it's babes
in bondage we're after,
it's a good thing I brought
my trusty instant camera!
I don't understand him at all.
This way.
Hey!
If you knew the way all along,
why didn't you say something?
Don't be dense! Why did you
think I came along?
Because you were swayed by my
awesome good looks, of course.
Jeez, what a wimpy monster!
He really is the hero!
He's incredibly good!
What's that?
Stop it!
Golly! He's whipping her!
So, where do you want it next,
sweet thing?
Please don't do this.
If you want me to stop,
you have only to give me the secret of
the jewels the Dragon Knights want.
That...
Since you weren't listening, I guess
I'm going to have to do it again!
Hold it!
Who the hell are you?
I don't give my name out to
dungeon fodder like you.
You son of a bitch!
Are you all right?
Thank you so much!
I'm Sheela, a warrior from
Strawberry Fields. And you?
He's Takeru Yamato, the
hero of the prophecy!
The queen sent him here to
defeat the Dragon Knights!
Well, that's very nice, but...
Could you please untie these ropes?
Oh, sure thing!
But first, let's preserve this priceless
moment on celluloid!
What are you doing?
Untie her this instant!
Sure, sure! Boy, do you get scary!
Excuse me, you don't have to do that.
Don't worry. It's not a problem!
Not there!
Hurry up!
The Dragon Knights and their Overlord
have one jewel each.
Each Dragon Knight can be found on
his own personal level of this tower.
The queen needs a full report,
so I'll head back to the castle.
Good luck!
Hey, wait! I need your three sizes
and your telephone number!
Please stop it. Please.
Of course we'll stop,
once you tell us the secret
of the jewels.
I don't know anything, nothing at all.
What a stubborn little bitch.
All right, let's take it from
the bottom again.
No problem!
You'd better be ready,
'cause here I come!
Stop...
Not there...
That looks enjoyable!
No, don't!
I can't believe I'm jealous of
a bunch of lounge lizards!
It's a filthy human!
Are you going to fuck with us?
Wouldn't dream of it. I'm just
going to kill you!
That's that, you perverted
handbag wanna-bes.
Perfect! What a picture!
Hey, wake up!
Oh yeah, this is the way
to wake a girl up!
You're here to rescue them,
nothing else.
But of course! It was just a thought.
Who are you?
Takeru's the name. The queen
sent me to rescue you!
I'm Jane, but...
Why is your hand where it is?
For goodness sake! I guess
it just got there by itself!
Hey, come on, lighten up!
I'm not mad at you.
You say you're not, but you are.
It's not as if I have to get permission
from you or anything, right?
Isn't that right?
I don't...
Luna!
LUNA!
I'm sure Takeru is doing his best.
After all, he is the hero
of the prophecy.
Well, my prophecies have
never been wrong before.
Only three jewels left to go.
Godspeed, Takeru. We await
your safe return.
Who's there?
As beautiful as we were told!
We are vassals of the Lord
of the Dragon Knights.
I am Green Dragon, one of
the Dragon Knight clan.
We have been sent to put some
questions before you, Your Majesty.
Give us the answers quickly and
nothing too repulsive shall befall you.
Takeru...
This is getting rather repetitive.
You Lose
Now, Lady Queen, you will
tell me everything.
What is the secret of the jewels,
and who is this hero Takeru?
I have nothing to say to
lowly filth such as you!
I can respect that, Your Majesty.
But I cannot help but wonder how long
you'll hold that regal pose.
Do it!
What do you think you're doing?
The royal orbs are truly magnificent!
I would like to touch them.
Go to hell, you stupid jerk!
My, my, such offensive language!
Let's see what you say to this!
Now that's what I call royal splendor!
Shall we get on with this?
That hurt!
What the hell is going on here?
Takeru! Save me!
So, you are the hero, Takeru!
Your escapades have really put
a hair up the Overlord's ass!
I take it you're here on business?
You don't look too enthused.
Will you stop talking
and do something?
I'm blushing to the tip of my toes!
So I see.
Get on with it! I could use a
little exercise before lunch!
Now you shall experience the true
power of the Dragon Knights!
Green Dragon!
The notion of a pathetic human
fighting one of my kind is laughable!
Attack, Green Dragon!
Your futile evasions only
serve to piss me off!
He's slow, but that fire
could be a pain.
Okay...
Your Majesty! I'm going
to rescue you now!
How is hiding behind that column
going to rescue her?
Dragon, to the right!
Now I've got him!
Dragon, to the LEFT!
I can't believe you did that!
I'll take out the big one first!
You're next, asshole!
One more left?
Strike!
Takeru!
How dare you play with
that priceless jewel!
Chill out! You're not exactly dressed
in your most authoritarian
attitude at the moment!
Still, no matter how one looks at it,
Your Majesty's bearing is impressive.
I should thank the Dragon Knights for
showing me such unexpected aspects!
Get back to the tower and rescue
the remaining warriors!
Man, talk about a harsh mistress!
Boy, am I hungry.
Her royal highness sure doesn't know
how to show her appreciation.
I never even got a chance
to ask about Luna.
Now what?
He may be ugly, but why pick
on one of his own team?
Hold it!
What the? Human scum!
Yet another pathetic excuse
for a monster.
Are you all right?
Little monsters are safe from me.
Get along now.
Go on, get out of here!
I'm here to defeat your associates!
That makes me your enemy, got it?
Suit yourself.
What? That way?
You'll show me where to go? I want
to go to the upper levels!
Dang, the monsters on the
fifth level were tough!
I'll just give myself a
small power boost
with a little bit of the old cheesecake!
This is Ann. What an incredible bust!
And this is Annie. Intelligent, beautiful,
and with legs that won't quit!
Tina! Boy, was I surprised when I lit
that match! Not a stitch in sight!
Maria! How sad to think of her, forced
into such a compromising position!
What do you think?
See anything you like?
Hey, what's the matter?
Why are you so angry?
You're not jealous, are you?
Hey, hey, hey!
Say, I bet you're female!
Hey, it's all right! I'm right here!
I can't believe we're actually
inside the column!
I found this hidden in here too!
What? Is it really that important?
Takeru, the so-called hero
who snuck into our tower,
has proven to be an unexpectedly
strong adversary.
In only a short time, he has already
defeated four of our Dragon Knights!
You worry too much!
He is only human, after all!
Never could he hope to match one
of such magnificent vileness as I!
But My Liege, he has already
acquired four of the jewels!
Worry not!
The only chance he might have
would be to find the White Sword!
But a human, who trusts only what
he can see with his eyes,
will never find that!
Rest assured, Black!
Now where do you suppose the
stairs to the sixth level are?
The other staircase ended
here at the fifth.
Do you know?
I see.
Hey! Something smells good.
I was hungry anyway.
Let's stuff our faces!
What a spread!
This looks particularly appetizing!
Who's copping that feel?
Don't you have any manners?
Yeah, ain't you got no fuckin' couth?
What?
Oh my goodness! It's a human!
You don't suppose he's the human
who's been carving up
the Dragon Knights?
That's right!
Now it's your turn to be
served on a platter!
So, he's going to cook
our goose, is he?
I say we reverse that and serve
HIM as the main course!
Damn, I can't keep an eye
on all of them!
I think I'm getting motion sickness.
Thank you so much!
Well, that literally sucked! Every inch
of my body is soaked with drool!
Thanks for saving us, by the way!
I'm Laura and this is Leira.
You're Takeru, right?
How did you know?
The demons were talking about you.
And you've found the
White Sword, as well!
You're talking about this?
That's right! You'll need it to defeat
the Dragon Knight Overlord!
Still, the White Sword alone
will not be enough.
Only the daughter of
Strawberry Field's priest
can unleash the power of the sword.
That daughter is Luna!
But I've been looking for Luna!
No one has seen her since
she was taken prisoner.
In any case, Black Dragon and his
Overlord still lie in wait above.
Well, you see, I can't find the stairs...
That's the way up, through
the old aqueduct.
But there's no water in the channel!
Once the water poured forth
in endless bounty.
It fed the Fountain of the Goddess
at the top of this tower.
It rushed through here
in rippling torrents,
cascading past that window in a
glittering spray of liquid radiance!
But now, because of the Overlord...
All right! I'll take care of it!
I'll put that water back
where it belongs!
So, after I do the hero thing,
how about going out with me?
All right!
That so-called hero's
not going to show.
You think he's turned tail
and gone home?
Humans haven't got the guts to
follow a course to its conclusion.
That's certainly the truth!
Hey!
This human's come to finish
the job he's started!
Prepare yourself!
He's right here!
You escaped us once, but never again!
Dang, I knew I should have
finished them off!
Overlord, please let us kill him!
Idiots!
I can't believe you let him
get so close!
Please, forgive us!
You little...
Looks like the old black magic
is having an off day!
He's got the White Sword!
But without the priest's daughter,
it will avail him naught!
You must die!
You call yourself a hero?
Still, I must compliment your
achievement in getting this far.
When I send your queen
to meet her goddess,
you'll be waiting to greet her!
You can't be alive!
My Lord, you must escape! The
child of the priest is...
What was that all about?
Takeru!
Luna!
Don't look, you dork!
Sorry...
It's just that you're the prettiest
girl I've ever rescued.
Honest?
It's the truth.
Now let's be reasonable, hero.
Your soul is no purer than
any other human's.
Why not join up with me?
Think of it, all the booze and
broads you can handle!
Unlimited wine and women?
Takeru already has all the woman
he can handle with me!
Powers above, time to fight!
Heaven's spirit is my might!
Fill my body with power bright!
White Sword channel this holy light!
Foolish hero! Someday
you'll suffer for this!
That's not too likely, right?
Takeru!
We love you, Takeru!
We're all yours, Takeru!
I never thought I'd start
suffering so soon!
I feel my heart
Commanding me
It stipulates
I do this immediately
From the time
Of our merger
Since we first met
We've been bound together
I'm sending you this gift from me
A piece of my heart by telepathy
There's someone else
Who's after you
You're in their sights
And they've got laser guidance too
Please don't bare
Your true feelings
Please don't share
With anyone but me
A feeling like ice runs down my spine
Don't change yourself for
these feelings of mine
Shooting Lover
Love in shining armor
You won't know what hit you
It's just my amour
Shooting Storm
Wish me the best of luck
You know this battle's for
Your heart
Even though it really hurts
Doing nothing would be
much, much worse
So is this my chance
To win romance
Look at my hands shake
How much can I take
Look straight in my eye
I won't be too shy
Take me on this dare
True love will be there