Sempai??
If only I could tell him how I feel.
If only I could...
...but I can't.
Even if it were only
in my dreams...
...that I could be close to him.
Secret Dreams...
We will make your dreams
come true.
Sempai?
Welcome to Secret Dreams!
Uh...I...
We've been waiting for you.
Please enter.
Hello.
Uh... This is my first time, but...
The initiation and fantasy
chamber fees...
...come to 3,000 yen.
Any other options are extra.
List your specific desires...
...right here on this paper.
I just want to be his lover.
Come this way.
Wow...
And...
How far do you want to go?
Uh, just a regular date will be fine.
Regular?
Maybe a little kissing
would be good.
What type of location
do you want?
I'll leave that up to you.
I see.
I can run the standard program
for you.
Please change into the sensory suit.
Sure.
Please take everything off first.
Or the sensations won't be right.
Sorry.
This feels really strange.
Please.
If there is a problem with the
sensory machine...
...a message will be displayed
in front of you.
You will hear a message as well.
You can respond with your voice.
All right.
Well then, enjoy your date.
Hi, Kaori.
He said my name.
Finally dumped my friends.
It's just the two of us now.
Just the two of us?
That's right. From now on,
I am all yours.
I'm so happy.
I'm really with Sempai.
Just like my fantasy.
I'm so glad I came.
Where shall we go?
I'll go anywhere as long as
I'm with you.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
It's really like a dream.
I'm sorry.
To make you take me out like this.
What are you talking about?
Come here.
What's wrong?
What was that?
Help me!
An error has been detected
in the program.
Would you like to force
a shut down?
So, you saw that movie too.
I was so touched by it.
Especially the reunion scene.
That's right. The scene goes
to sepia tones, and...
...then they go to an amusement
park and...
Kaori!
That's beautiful!
I found the most beautiful
one just for you.
Sempai, I'm so happy!
Right now, I'm so ecstatic.
I'm just happy seeing
that you're happy.
No, Sempai.
If you love me, you should
release your inhibitions.
Sempai...
No! I can't. No! No!
Where am I?! Where's Sempai?
Sempai?!
Sempai!
Kaori.
Do it.
It's a dissection. Don't you like it?
No!
Stop this!
Nice tits!
Help! Sempai!
Stop it!
It's dripping wet.
And it's moving, too.
Don't look. I'm so embarrassed.
Stop it!
Don't hold back.
Stop program! Stop program!
A type 1 1 error has occurred.
Program termination
was not successful.
Someone...!
Well, well, what's
happened to you?
Oh, Sempai! Everything's
back to normal.
Wasn't it good enough for you?
That looks really good on you.
Don't look!
I didn't know you were into this.
That's not true! I'm not like that...!
No. Sempai. Please don't look.
I'm embarrassed. Don't look.
You sure are a dirty little slut.
That's not true.
I can't control my body.
I like the way you are.
Please stop the program!
No! Please... No!
Stop! Stop!
Yeah. That's it. Yeah...
There is an error in the program.
Please reset the system after
choosing the correct program.
Sempai, please forgive me.
Please forgive me.
Well, well, isn't this enough for you?
It's not true. Not true.
Look, she's dripping
from her pussy!
Check it out!
No! This is embarrassing! Sempai!
This is what you want.
But, I can't... I can't...
This isn't right. No.
My reputation is slipping.
Who told you to stop?
That's it. That's it.
She's pissing on the floor!
No... No...
Kaori, make sure everyone can see.
Wow, this is great!
No... I don't want to be doing this.
Stop it. Stop the program.
Forgive me!
I'm going to cum.
I've been waiting for this.
Sempai.
Why? Sempai, let me down.
Oh, did you say you wanted
to be pierced?
I never said such a thing.
Well, where should we start?
With my nipple.
Sounds good.
That's not right. Not right.
Please initiate a forced shutdown...
...and reset the system after
choosing the correct program.
Help me!
So embarrassing.
Kaori, you've sure got guts.
I'll give you another. Where next?
Oh, dear.
In my pussy. My pussy.
I never said anything like that.
Here?
Yes, that's it. Right there.
No, the program is wrong.
Looks good on you.
Please. No more.
Please let me down.
I can't take it anymore.
I see. You want to show off
a little more.
Please stop.
There is an error in the program.
Please reset the system after
choosing the correct program.
No...!
It hurts!
Forgive me, Sempai.
Stop it!
How do you feel?
Everyone's happy for you.
It feels so good!
I'm going to cum!
Exposing myself like this...
...in front of strangers.
How terrible.
Sempai.
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to treat you
like a woman?
Tea ceremony?!
Feels good, huh?
Sempai, please forgive me.
The tea ceremony is
a woman's pastime.
Please stop. Forgive me.
That was pretty good.
Everyone, take your turns.
Right on!
No, please stop. Forgive me, Sempai.
I see. You want to
drink it yourself.
I'll do as you say.
Drink it.
If you want me to play with you.
I can't take it.
No!
Spread your ass for me
with your hands.
Sempai, I'm scared! Please stop!
They say in stressful
situations like these...
...the pussy gets nice and tight.
What?
You're the one who's
really going to feel it.
Forgive me.
Raise your ass higher for me.
Tighter, tighter. Kaori!
Sempai! Sempai!
That's right, Kaori.
No.
Stop!
No more!
It's sure hard to satisfy you.
Your last desire is my fist.
No, please! Please, no!
Face it, Kaori, you just
can't get your mind off...
...of doing it with a man for real.
Right, Kaori? Isn't that true?
Say it's true.
That's not true. I just wanted to...
...be with you, Sempai.
Please, Sempai. Forgive me.
Are you still going to
keep saying that?
Then how about this?
Feels good, doesn't it?
No! I don't want this!
Stop it!
The program is complete.
Would you like to restart
the program?
Please make your selection.
Hey, there.
Wanna buy some discount tickets?
I...
...want them?