Hyde, I want you.
But what about your injury?
I'm fine.
I want you to make me forget everything.
Hyde, that feels good.
Yes!
Wait!
No, wait.
Hyde!
No!
Yes, Hyde, Hyde!
Wait, wait Hyde!
I'm going to...
Hyde!
Hyde, Hyde!
I'm coming.
Hyde, I'm going...
Yeah, me too!
Hyde I'm coming!
Teres.
Hyde, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
It's not your fault.
I'm sorry.
This earthquake might have
something to do with Youra.
Youra, where did you go!
Shit, I think here is something
going on with the legacy.
Slain! It has to be him!
He's probably up to no good.
Youra, where in the world are you?
Youra, Youra!
What the...
Dearest Hyde, you came here after all.
Youra!
Youra, where, where are you?
Listen to me.
I'm going to stop Castor's ability
to move for a short while.
Please kill him while I do this!
Are you talking about this monster?
But what will happen to you?
Hyde, we don't have a lot of time.
This is what you, Slain, and countless
others have been looking for.
It is the "legacy of the old world."
This is it?
This thing?
He's one of Youra's kind.
Youra?
And this monster?
That's right.
It's not like I know that much.
The royal library has a lot of information.
So, you're from the capital?
The power of the spirit is distributed
between this thing, Youra, and the amulet.
There may be more of these giants.
This may be the only one,
or there could be many others.
All we know is these giants
destroyed the old world.
And now, I'm sure it could destroy
our country, no, our world again.
Wait, what about Youra?
If we have Youra and the amulet,
we can at least...
keep him contained
even if we can't destroy him.
So, I see Slain was the one that helped
awaken this beast.
That's only part of it.
Youra awakened first, thanks to you.
So this is my fault?
We have to act now,
he's starting to open his eyes!
What can I do?
I can't tell you.
All I know is you need that amulet.
If you can't figure it out, I will.
Give me the amulet.
Youra.
Please Hyde!
Hyde, I'm going to stop Castor's ability
to move for a short while, so...
Youra!
There is no escape from this?
I have to kill him.
Damn!
We need to get out of here.
Youra!
Where are you, Youra?
Hyde.
I thought I heard someone was calling me.
I was trying to figure out who,
when I saw this light...
Damn, it's not working.
Youra, what's wrong?
The power of the spirit.
Power of the spirit?
Yes, it's becoming unstable.
At this rate...
Youra?
Hyde.
I'm sorry, but I can't come with you.
What are you talking about?
The spirit is becoming unstable
because it used to be...
contained within Castor's body,
but now it's free.
Without a body to contain it,
the spirit is running wild!
It becomes pure energy
when it is not contained.
Soon, here...
actually, not just here,
everything will be destroyed.
That's why we need to get out of here fast!
That's not it, even if we escape this cave...
the city of Arville...
She means the whole world
is going bye-bye.
This can't be true!
What are we going to do?
I am the only one to stop it.
But why you, Youra?
Castor and I are the only ones
that can stop this.
Wait Youra, this is going to kill you!
If I don't stop the spirit,
everything will be destroyed.
Everyone I cared about.
I'm sorry about how I behaved a while back.
Well, I'm sure being told you're not human
was a shock to you.
Yes, but I'm okay now.
I'm feeling much better.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Answer me if you can.
Yes?
Are your memories coming back?
Yes, they are.
I'm really grateful to you, Hyde.
Grateful, to me?
Yes.
I really wanted to thank you.
It's no big deal.
It was you, Hyde,
that awakened me...
and also the one that saved me
from that man.
It's no big deal, really.
You always saved me when I thought
I was done for.
And I'm truly grateful.
Youra...
I'm sitting here with you because
you saved my life.
It's a wonderful feeling.
About my fate...
I met you, Hyde, and also Sakura,
Ms. Shizuki, Maria.
Everyone helped me so much.
Everyone was so kind,
although I was a complete stranger.
You should just relax and enjoy yourself.
Everyone wants to help you,
because they really like you.
Myself included.
I like everyone, too.
Well, that's the most important thing, right?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much, Hyde.
You've done just so much for me.
I don't know what I would have done.
I want this moment to last.
Yeah.
Hyde, I'm really nervous.
But it feels really good.
I've never felt like this before.
I see.
This will feel even better.
Yes.
Your body is so beautiful.
Hyde, I want you!
I like it!
Now, touch me down there.
Like this?
Yes.
Hyde, it's so hard and warm.
You're probably all warm here, too.
Just insert it very slowly.
Yes.
It's warm.
Does it hurt?
No.
See, now we are joined together.
Yes, I'm joined together with you.
Hyde, I can feel you pulsing
gently inside me.
It's because I really like you.
I'm so happy.
Me too.
I love you a lot, Hyde.
I love you a lot too, Youra.
What's funny?
Nothing.
I'm just getting embarrassed, that's all.
I want more of you Hyde.
Do what you like.
Yes!
I'm sorry, are you okay?
No, I'm fine.
I'm just not used to this.
I felt tingles all over my body
when you moved like that.
Did you like it?
Yes.
All right!
Yes!
I think I'm going to come!
I think I'm coming, too.
Yes!
Youra!
Hyde, I feel so warm.
Especially my stomach.
Yeah.
I'm very happy.
No, I can't let you do that!
You're not going to be the martyr!
I was here in this cave so I could meet you.
Goodbye, Hyde.
Later!
See you, bye!
Hyde!
Did you call me?
Shit, you know, it's not what you think
and it's a really long story.
It's a really complicated story.
I swear nothing went on in there,
so why are you looking all pissed off?
I mean I'm really innocent
of all wrongdoing.
Why does this happen to me?
Hyde, you're always just playing around
all the damned time!
Well, it' not...
Hyde, where do you think you're going,
come back, you bastard!
Hi Manaty, what's up?
See you later!
Slow down Hyde!
Wait, damn it!
No way!
Hyde!
Hi there! You two are looking awfully good
on this fine day!
See you later!
Wait up, you lazy bum, Hyde!
I think I'm going to stay and enjoy
Arville for a little longer...
before I go hunting for the next treasure...
probably with Sakura.
Hyde!