This?
What, again?
Hey.
Hey. What's going on?
That was close.
Hey. Wait a second.
A thank you wouldn't hurt.
l say this for your sake.
Don't get involved in these problems
of the Ancient World.
What?
lf you value your life.
What's that?
Are you threatening me?
l never asked you to help me.
Anyway, l gave you the advice.
Hey.
Wait a second!
Damn!
My name is Hyde.
l travel around the world
with a childhood friend, Sakra....
searching for Treasure
of the Ancient World.
We're staying in Arville,
a town on the edge of the frontier.
And there is this cave.
The cave is inhabited by monsters,
which is upsetting.
But, there are many pretty girls in the town.
I was hoping I could have
a reasonably good time.
Well, I was hoping, anyway.
Your ladyship! That man is cursed.
You must stay away from him.
You're okay now.
How did l get here?
The Suhyle Family carriage carried you here.
Hyde, this time it was really close.
Thank God Miss Priol found you.
l see. The Suhyle Family. Priol.
Anyway, Manaty, thank you.
You saved my life again.
l've told you many times already.
Please be careful with suspicious weapons.
Okay, okay.
l have to make a big contribution this time.
-Hyde.
-Yeah?
l'd gladly accept contributions, but....
there's something else
l could use your help with.
l have to exorcise a curse
placed on a gem stone.
But this may be a little too much
for me alone.
l can't do any of this magic stuff.
That's fine.
lt's just that, once in a long while...
the evil things that are sealed
away get resurrected.
Just in case.
Evil one, l order you under the name
of God and Spirit.
Leave!
Evil one! Disappear!
Manaty!
Manaty! Hey, Manaty!
Something is weird. lnside me.
No way. You failed?
Hey, Manaty!
Hey, hey.
Ouch!
Manaty, should l call for help?
Get a hold of yourself!
Damn, what should l do?
Manaty, are you all right?
You were, like....
The curse is gone. Thanks to you, Hyde.
Really? But, Manaty,
you 're acting a little strange.
Hyde, our task is complete.
Let's take a little break.
What?
With me.
Hey, Manaty!
What're you doing?
What's gotten into you?
Your thing is twitching. Cute.
lt's getting big.
My lovely Manaty.
Your tongue is so warm.
But why?
l'm so glad. l sucked it,
and now it's this big.
No, Manaty. lf you do that....
lt's all right, come.
Come a lot, in my mouth.
No, Manaty, really.
Your semen is so thick and delicious.
But l can't be satisfied only
with sucking alone.
Not with just my mouth.
Now l want you to lick mine.
Hyde, there. lt feels so good!
Wow, Manaty,
you're already drenched here.
l've been like this for a while.
Manaty, you're a bad priest.
Would your God forgive
a horny priest like yourself?
l don't know.
No, don't lick inside!
No, not there, no!
No, l can't anymore, no.
No more.
l can't wait anymore. l'm going crazy.
Okay. Then lie down over there.
Okay, relax. l'm coming in.
lt hurts!
What?
Manaty, this can't be your first.
Hey, hey.
No.
Don't stop. Give me more.
Push inside me. With your cock.
But, Manaty....
Manaty.
Okay, Manaty.
A priest preaches about love.
A priest has to know about love.
Don't worry.
l'll teach you all about love.
Look, relax.
No, no!
ls this too painful?
No, don't stop. lt feels good. Good!
Manaty.
l'm going crazy.
l see. Manaty is a horny priest after all.
She looks like she's enjoying it so much.
Okay, l'll make it better for you.
No, no, if you do it like that.
Come on, Manaty, you can come
anytime you want to.
No!
l'm so hot.
Oops!
You!
Ouch!
No, Sakra, why?
That girl you brought to Dr. Shizki,
who is she?
Who? l've never even heard of her.
Listen, Sakra, l meant to tell you.
You suddenly brought a naked girl
to the doctor and said....
''Please examine her!''
What's wrong with you?
l didn't know what to do,
so l figured l'd better bring her here.
l'm sorry, l'm sorry.
She's coming to.
You have no need to be afraid.
l am Shizki. l am a doctor in this town.
A doctor?
Yes. What is thy name?
Eura.
Now, Eura, what was thy doing in the cave?
The cave?
Yes.
What happened in the cave?
What cave?
Thou was in the cave, or not?
l don't know. l just don't....
Could it be you don't remember?
No.
Wait a moment.
You don't remember me, rescuing you?
Then, you....
However you slice it, it doesn't make sense.
A girl, alone, passed out in a cave?
And she was naked?
l'm telling you the truth!
Enough is enough!
This is getting us nowhere.
l'm not lying. l'm telling you the truth.
l'm so unlucky today. No treasure.
All the monsters.
Hey, Dr. Shizki.
You're out late, Hyde.
What's up?
Well, l wanted a word or two with thee.
l'd be delighted!
Sorry to bother thou this late.
Make yourself at home.
l have nothing to offer you, though.
Don't bother. This is good enough.
ls Sakra out?
She's in the next room.
Aren't thou staying in the same room?
Why would you think that?
Why? Thou are either married or lovers.
lt doesn't make sense.
What makes you say that?
Thou two are not, then? l figured....
Hey, you didn't come all the way here
at this hour to talk about that.
That is true.
l wanted to talk to thee about Eura.
What about Eura?
Who the hell is she?
What do you mean?
l, too, thought it was strange.
Thou said she was all alone in that cave.
Thou know about the rumor everybody's
talking about in the town?
They say that cave is the largest
ancient world ruin ever discovered.
lt sounds like an old wife's tale, yet...
here comes a girl with no memory,
discovered in the same cave.
What are you saying?
Thou are hiding something, aren't thou?
Okay, l'll tell you.
But l don't know that much, either.
Tell me.
Two weeks ago,
l entered that cave for the first time.
There, l ran into a man.
He was dying when l got there.
When l held him in my arms....
He pushes this into my hand.
Then that was the end of him.
Then, about a week later....
Not here. Not yet.
Let's move ahead.
What is this? lt's shining.
What the hell?
No way. She can't be alive.
A doll, maybe?
Not here.
Not here, not here, not here.
Nothing's here.
There's no treasure here.
The quick way would be to ask her.
Not again.
What is it this time?
So that's what happened, in a nutshell.
Then Eura is....
l'm not quire sure yet.
But l'm sure she has something
to do with the Ancient World.
l see. And what is thy intention?
What?
Could thee be after the treasure?
Hyde?
l'd be lying if l said
that l didn't have that angle.
Hyde, thou not--
But?
You've seen Eura, haven't you?
She's just an ordinary girl,
however you look at her.
l'm not conceited enough
to think l could somehow help her.
But l would love to be of some help to her.
That's what l want.
Of course, l haven't given up
on the treasure.
l see. Then l had nothing
to worry about, after all.
What?
l don't care who that girl is.
Makes no difference to me,
what l have to do.
l just want to make a difference
for the injured and the sick.
But l wanted to find out
what thy intentions were.
Just in case thy sole motivation
was to somehow exploit Eura.
l am relieved.
Now l know thou cares about that girl,
like any normal person would.
lt is getting late. l shall leave.
What? Leaving already?
Of course. My business is taken care of.
What's wrong?
Why don't you spend the night?
You came all the way over!
Thou art speaking ridiculous!
Why should l?
Why did you get up?
Dr. Shizki.
What?
You came to visit a man's room,
late at night.
You were ready to face the consequences,
weren't you?
What the hell art thou thinking?
Sakra is asleep next door,
for heaven's sake!
Don't worry about her.
Once she falls asleep,
nothing can wake her up.
That is not the issue!
l just came over to talk.
Thou would approach any woman.
ls that it?
Thou hast no real sense of fidelity!
That's not true.
l do this only for you, Dr. Shizki.
l won't be tricked like that.
Dr. Shizki, you're not resisting any more.
Even if l resisted, there's no way l could
physically overpower thee.
So you say, but this is
what you want, isn't it?
Don't be ridiculous--
No, don't.
See how much your body is begging for it?
That is just a physiological reaction.
This too, down here?
ls this one of those
physiological reactions?
What about....
This is just hard, isn't it?
We have to relieve this
physiological reaction.
Not like....
Do you like it that much?
No, no, l didn't mean....
No, no....
lt's not good for you to fight, Doctor.
No!
No, not like that.
Not there.
Good.
You're pumping nectar down here,
begging me to lick more and more.
No, that's a lie.
That's not a lie.
No. l'm so embarrassed.
Not there, not there.
You're very sensitive here.
Yes, l am. So, please don't be so mean.
No.
Time to come inside the doctor.
No, wait.
No.
lt feels good.
Finally, you're being honest.
But it's been such a long time.
l see.
How does a cock feel,
after such a long time?
l can't say. l'm embarrassed.
No, don't.
No, no, Dr. Shizki.
You have to be more honest with yourself.
lt's so good. l want you to do more.
Well said.
Now that you've said that, Dr. Shizki,
l have to satisfy you.
No.
Come all the way inside me!
lt feels so good!
No, it feels too good, no!
Dr. Shizki, no, if you do it like that, l can't....
Hyde, l can't any more.