Please, no more.
Help!
No more.
No!
Miss Mia!
Miss Mia.
Help me.
You're right. Even Dr. Shizki
cannot cure some diseases.
You're talking about the Suhyle lady.
I've heard she's suffering
from a serious disease.
They decided to use a very
dangerous medicine.
And then what happened?
The medicine worked all right,
so she is cured of the disease.
She is cured, but it had
a strange side effect.
Sakra side effect?
Yes.
What kind?
Well, that is...
She's become a slut.
Sakra, a what?
Is there a medicine like that?
I've heard about it!
Elixir, the legendary secret medicine.
I really don't know the details.
A few days ago, Priol, who works
at the Suhyle Mansion came by...
and I just overheard when she
was consulting Dr. Shizki.
Hyde.
Dr. Shizki.
Are you making progress in searching
through the Cave?
Well, I've been quite busy
with this and that recently.
Who knows what keeps you busy.
I see. So she took the Elixir.
Yes.
She's suffering every night ever since.
No wonder.
What can we do?
- Give her a man.
- What? A man?
Once she experiences a man,
the side effect will cease.
That's what I hear.
No way.
If the old man Folkiss finds me
here at this hour...
- I won't be able to get away alive.
- Don't worry.
The master has business
in the town of DayVeen.
He won't be coming back tonight.
Right here, in this mansion,
there are only you, me and Miss Mia.
And, what's up?
Is it about that medicine?
Yes.
Just the other day, Miss Mia's condition
got worse all of sudden.
She took that medicine.
So she finally took it.
It worked very well.
It was you who saved Miss Mia's life.
We all thank you very much for that.
Miss Mia, the Master,
and even I thank you for that.
I couldn't do anything to help her.
That's not true.
It was only because of your last...
act of dedication that I got it.
Silly.
To be honest with you...
I wouldn't ask you to do
something like this.
Something like what?
Hey.
Mr. Hyde, I didn't know you were here.
How are you feeling?
Well.
I seem to have been cured
of the disease itself.
Thank you very much for the medicine.
I'm so glad that medicine worked so well.
I would like to say so.
Priol called for me today.
She told me about the side effect.
I asked her to ask you to come over.
I know I'm causing trouble
asking you something...
like this all of the sudden.
Mia. Let me.
Yes. I like you, Mr. Hyde.
I like you, too, Mia.
Should anything happen to Miss Mia...
I won't let him get away.
I'm the same age as Priol...
but my breasts are not as big as hers.
I like you just the way you are.
You're very pretty.
You mean it?
Come on, don't try to slip away.
But...
No!
Come on, let go.
Okay.
No!
I have to get you really ready.
But maybe this is the side
effect of that medicine.
You're so very wet.
That bastard.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I feel...
I'm putting it in.
Yes.
Hot! Your cock is hot!
Doesn't it hurt?
No.
Mia. We're one now.
Look.
Now, I'm moving a little.
Yes.
Mr. Hyde.
Mia, you're petite, so...
let's do it like this.
I don't have strength.
It's getting good for me, too.
Mr. Hyde.
I can't, anymore.
No more!
Mr. Hyde.
Mr. Hyde...
Hyde, wake up already!
Hyde, what were you
doing last night again?
My dear, Sakra...
It's all a misunderstanding, Sakra.
Let's put aside the question
of what I'm misunderstanding.
Eura is gone.
What?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It is not for you to apologize.
Teres is gone, too, which means...
They are both in the Cave.
I'm sorry.
Then I'd better get going.
Hyde.
What?
Tell me all about last night
when you get back.
See you later!
Somehow, all the monsters
are very rambunctious today.
Finally you are here.
Eura! Teres!
I'm tired of waiting for you.
Is it you? Do you have it?
What are you talking about?
The amulet. Give me the amulet.
I shall exchange it for the two girls.
I cannot do that.
The Stormbringer isn't it?
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah.
You want this?
I can smash this into pieces right now,
right here.
All right. I don't need this girl.
But I won't give you this doll
until I'm done with it.
Doll?
You're here and you don't even know that?
This is the very key to open the gate.
Once the gate is open...
I won't need it anymore.
So, give me the amulet!
Just watch.
Kill them.
Eura!
What?
What the heck?
Hyde, destroy that sphere!
Hey, are you alive?
What the hell was that?
It must have been a type of magic
organism created by the spirits.
Eura...
I am not human.
No, don't touch me!
Hyde, not you!
- Where's Teres?
- She's gone after Slain.
What?
Why don't you go after Teres?
Why me? She's one of your men, isn't she?
We had a little fall out. Besides,
I really don't know what to do with her.
What?
Don't worry. I'll take Eura
to that lady doctor.
You why do you know everything?
Who the hell are you?
If you don't hurry, Teres might die.
Nice place, isn't it?
This is my hideaway,
rather, my supply base.
Why did you help me?
I came in here, ready to die.
But I even failed at that.
What are you talking about,
why do you have to die?
I took Eura with me, because...
I meant to use her as bait.
But that didn't work with Slain.
I can't even avenge my friends.
How could I?
If I live any longer,
I'd be just shaming myself.
That's not cute.
I can't depend on others.
If I depend on others,
I'll only get them involved.
I'll only get them killed.
I get everybody killed.
No more. I don't want it anymore.
I don't want to lose people
important to me anymore!
I don't want to suffer like that. I can't.
I don't need friends.
That's enough.
You're not alone. Not now.
Not anymore.
That bastard's thing,
that was following him...
around like a fish crap?
That magical organism?
I killed it.
Don't worry.
I can't get killed that easily.
Don't be nice to me.
Don't worry. I won't die.
Hyde.