Is that why you are almost always
confined in the mansion?
Yes. I easily take ill,
ever since when I was born.
My father created this garden for me...
so that I can see it from my room.
This branch?
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Hyde.
You're welcome.
Miss Mia.
Hi, Priol.
It's about time for you
to get back to your room.
See you later, Mr. Hyde.
Yeah.
Mr. Hyde, you will come visit me again,
won't you?
Of course.
Good. See you then.
She's a good girl.
It was Miss Mia who helped you
when you fell into our carriage.
If it hadn't been for Miss Mia,
I wouldn't have...
Helped a stranger from nowhere,
is that it?
If you really wish to show gratitude...
please save Miss Mia's life.
What do I need to do?
They say it's a miracle medicine
that cures any disease.
Elixir?
The only person who might know
about Elixir would be Serafias.
She's something of a witch.
She lives in the forest, south of town.
Thanks.
Mr. Hyde.
Hey, you don't have to be on guard like that.
I'm Ghuran. Why don't you
have a drink with me?
I've seen you before. Many times.
Where?
In the cave, of course.
You are in the same trade, aren't you?
Yeah, sort of.
I rarely see guys entering
those caves alone.
I was wondering if you're sane.
Which means, you are...
I belong to a small band of thieves,
though I'm by myself tonight.
You're after the Treasure
of the Ancient World too?
Sort of. What about you?
Well, nothing so far.
I see. Tough luck for both of us.
Yeah.
Or maybe you're trying to fool me.
Well, fine by me.
I have one more question.
You know there's a huge door
on the Second Level.
That door was opened yesterday.
It never opened before,
no matter what we tried.
What could have been inside?
Why do you ask me that?
Well, why not?
I have no idea.
I see. Too bad.
Next time, I'll pay.
Maybe he was talking about Eura's.
Shush, Sakra! Don't mention Eura in public.
Okay, I got it.
What do you think, Hyde?
You cut her hair?
But what's that weird dress?
I'm sorry it's weird.
I used to wear that years ago.
Wow, Dr. Shizki once wore
such a flowery dress...
I want you to go find the cane
I dropped in the cave.
Then you'll mix the Elixir for me?
That would be the 28th.
Here it is.
Where is your leader?
What do you want?
I need the amulet he has.
I don't know about it.
What about a woman covered with tattoos?
I don't know.
I don't know anything about
an amulet or a woman like that.
I see. Then I don't need you.
Wait, Slain.
You know my name?
Of course! How could I forget?
Three years ago, in the Kattoosh ruins!
You killed all my friends.
Then why don't you die, too?
Net yet.
You.
Slowly, Hyde.
Well, at the very least, her ribs are broken.
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to slap me tonight?
Hyde, is it dangerous in the cave?
That's an unexpected question.
That girl, she was the sole survivor,
wasn't she?
Yeah. So far.
I've been to many ruins and caves, but...
It's here, the Ancient World
ruin is waiting for me here!
Of course, many guys have
their sights set on them!
So, there will be some danger!
But I'm going to do it!
That man in the tavern,
and Slain the wizard.
I found the cane you were talking about.
This is it, right?
Yes, this is it.
Okay, now the Elixir...
One more.
That's not what we agreed.
What?
I'm not saying I won't give it to you.
I ran out of something I need.
I want you to go get it.
Okay, okay. What is it, then?
A virgin's lust juice.
Can I ask you?
How would I go get such a thing?
It's up to you.
Lust juice. Lust juice. Lust juice.
Lust juice?
Finally, here she comes.
You took your sweet time.
Well, you know...
You have it in, do you?
May I?
I can't anymore.
I'm so hot and jumpy inside.
No.
Looks like you're ready.
Okay, spread your legs.
No. I'm so embarrassed.
Come on, Priol.
Come on, spread them right.
Please, get it over with quickly.
Could you give me some more?
It's easy for you to say.
This is a problem. Let me help you.
No, no!
No more. No.
Here it is.
This will be more than enough.
Aren't we done yet?
Quick, pull this out of me.
Are you sure?
You're sucking it in down here,
like you're enjoying it.
No! That sends vibration deep inside.
But your lips down here say they like it.
No, that's not true.
Or maybe you're a slut who gets drenched,
even when she doesn't want it.
You must be.
I know you're doing this
for the medicine, but...
it's your first time and you're
sucking this in like this.
But that's because you told me to put it in.
But you are so wet.
You have the vibrator as a plug,
yet you're flowing and flooding.
That's a lie.
Please, don't be mean.
Please pull it out quickly.
All right.
See, it tastes like Priol.
No, don't do that.
You didn't want me to pull it out?
I did want you to.
Be honest.
Then, I'll make you feel even better.
I can't. I feel like crying. What should I do?
What do you want me to do?
I don't know. I don't.
I'm just so hot down there. Please!
I got it.
Come on, over there.
Like this?
You're so wet, you've got nothing
to worry about.
Okay, relax.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Does it feel better now?
I don't know, but...
it feels weird down there.
Hey, if you make so much noise,
Mia might hear you.
No! I don't want her to!
It would be a problem if Mia saw you now.
While Mia is sick in bed...
you're doing this slutty thing.
No. Please don't say that.
That's not true.
But you're squeezing me
down here so tightly.
You're wrong.
I can't anymore.
I can't, either.
It's so good.
It's so good. I'm coming.
Hey.
What?
Weren't you going to use
that to mix the Elixir?
What? Who said that?
But, you said you needed
a virgin's lust juice.
I just wanted to drink it.
Then what about the Elixir?
As I promised, here's the Elixir.
Could it be that you've always had it there?
Where is Sakra?
What, Sakra's already back?
Yes, quite a while ago.
Sakra.
Sakra. May I come in?
Sakra, what's wrong?
Hyde, if you just tell me it's all right...
then I'll be all right. Because I trust you.
I'm just being selfish.
I don't want you to do anything dangerous,
because I'm selfish.
I'm sorry. I promised myself I'd never,
ever say it.
But you never said that before...
Is it because you saw Teres?
Because, if I said it, you'd worry,
wouldn't you?
Then, you'd worry about me, and
you won't be able to do what you want.
Sakra, you mean...
I didn't want that.
I didn't want to be your burden.
So, I decided to just watch you.
I decided I'd never be weak.
But, why haven't you told me?
Can't you trust me?
No! It's not that!
I've been selfish enough
to follow you around.
I didn't want to act more selfish
and trouble you.
I can't be a burden to your dreams anymore.
But I had to say it.
I was kind of scared today.
When I started thinking,
what if you didn't come back?
Silly.
I'm sorry.
Silly. You have to say these things.
I'm, you know, insensitive.
I know. That's why I never told you.
You.
You've always been telling me never
to hide anything from you...
but you never told me anything, either.
Because I was shy.
What's there to be shy about?
I do, how can I put it, worry.
Well, I had you worry about me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Hyde, you're kind of kind today.
Silly. I'm always kind.
Hey.
Could we stay like this a little longer?
Yeah.
- I'm glad.
- Why?
I think you do care about me.
Of course.
Yeah.
Hey, Hyde.
What is it?
I've always loved you, Hyde.
I know that.
What about you, Hyde?
Me?
You're more precious
to me than anyone else.
Hyde!
I love you, I love you!
Sakra.
It's okay, Hyde.
It's okay, because it's you.
It's not okay if it's not you.
I want to feel you forever and ever, so I...
I want to be one with you, too, Sakra.
Hyde...
I've always wanted to feel closer to you.
Really?
Yeah. Because I love you.
Because I love you more than anyone else.
Hyde.
I'm happy, but I'm crying. This is so funny.
Sakra.
I'm so shy. So shy.
There's nothing to be shy about.
You have such cute breasts.
Really?
Yes, so soft here.
You're so cute, Sakra,
when you're being shy.
I'm so happy.
You're telling me I'm cute.
If you touch me like that, I'll go crazy.
It's okay.
No, Hyde.
Not so hard!
No.
Sakra, your boobs are sweet and delicious.
Don't talk like that.
Sakra.
Hyde, don't touch my breasts like that.
No, no. Hyde, no.
Sakra, you have a very beautiful body.
I'm so shy, Hyde.
Sakra.
Right there.
No. I'm so shy.
Sakra, show me more.
Yeah.
No. Not there. I'm shy.
Sakra, I can smell you down here. So cute.
No, Hyde. It feels so good.
Sakra, I want to come inside you. Can I?
Yes, please. Come, Hyde, please.
Come inside me.
Hyde...
Sakra, does it hurt?
I'm okay. Because it's you, Hyde.
It's all right. Come inside me.
Sakra, I'm all the way inside you.
Sakra, bear with me a little.
I want to feel you.
I can't hold back anymore. So...
It's all right. Hyde, do whatever you want.
I'm all yours.
I want to feel you, too. It's all right,
even if it hurts.
Sakra.
It's okay, come on, Hyde.
I want to feel you more.
Sakra.
Hyde, it's weird. I'm so hot.
I can't control myself.
Sakra.
I'm so hot down there.
I'm so hot where I'm connected to you.
Hyde.
Sakra, Sakra.
Hyde, you cock is so deep,
it's hitting me deep inside!
Love you, I love you, Hyde.
I love you!
No. Something's happening.
Sakra, I can't hold back anymore.
Sakra, Sakra.
Hyde, come for me, Hyde!
Sakra!
I'm so happy now.
Finally I've become one with you, Hyde.
And you love me, too, Hyde.