Wind of Ebenbourg
Chapter 1: Land of Passion
Come in.
About your dinner.
Could you bring it here?
Very well.
I believe that it will ready in a short while.
Monsieur McDonald, you ordered
the beef dinner, correct?
Yes.
You are in for a treat, Monsieur McDonald.
Tonight's beef dinner is wiener schnitzel.
We're proud to say
that it is our train's specialty.
It's delicious.
I'm looking forward to it.
Coming right up.
This luxurious trip
is all thanks to Sophie.
The Grand Duchy of Ebenbourg?
My name is Sophie Delmotte.
Were you writing a letter?
It's a side job.
I write letters for others.
I really enjoy it.
You are studying commerce right now?
Yes. My dream is to travel
the world as a great merchant.
It may be a bit exaggerated.
Bernard...
Come to Ebenbourg, where your late
father used to live.
Why are you doing this?
Don't ask a thing.
I'm sorry. It's my first time.
It's my first time too.
Be gentle.
Does it hurt? Are you okay?
I'm fine. I want to know.
Does it feel good?
Yes. It's wonderful, Miss Delmotte.
Call me Sophie.
I will. Is it okay for me to move, Sophie?
Ever since my mother died,
I've worked at many stores.
It was more useful than class.
So it served you multiple purposes?
Yes.
So, why are you asking me
to ride such a splendid train?
I will be frank and straight to the point.
You're real name is Claude Flavini.
I'm to meet you as the Lord of Ronsard,
a town in the Grand Duchy of Ebenbourg.
What did you want?
Put this in his food?
Allow me to carry them.
My, sorry to interrupt your conversation.
No, I've already finished.
Remember my words.
Where is my seat?
I'll show you right away.
Are you fine with sharing a room?
I can find you another private room.
It's okay. My granddaughter took extra care
in reserving a shared room...
because she thought it was dangerous
for me to travel alone.
I understand.
In that case, please follow me.
Come in.
Excuse me. She's sharing the room.
Nice to meet you.
My, you are quite young.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Your main dish, Madame Delmotte,
is flounder from the Straits of Dover.
My, it looks delicious!
Monsieur McDonald ordered
the wiener schnitzel.
There you go, enjoy.
I'm sorry, but could you
pass me the water?
Yes.
My! How clumsy of me.
It's okay, I'll clean it up.
You don't have to worry.
I'm sorry. Please, have my dinner.
Won't you?
Your dinner?
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
I put the sleeping drug in.
That Madame accidentally...
Just as Sophie said,
he looks like his father, Bernard Flavini.
He's a very handsome young man.
Maybe he will be able to revive Ronsard
and bring new wind to Ebenbourg.
Ronsard. Was it this desolate before?
Someone! Stop me now!
I order everyone to save me!
Mistress Rosalie!
Mistress Rosalie, please be careful!
What happened? Did someone get hurt?
What's with all this ruckus?
An accident?
Look at all the smoke.
It's still in the morning.
What's going on? I'm trying to...
Grab hold.
I don't know what you were
doing in this cold weather.
Here.
Just a whore.
Back you go.
What is your name? Tell me.
Claude McDonald.
How courageous.
I appreciate it that you didn't
hold me too tightly.
All right, I've made up my mind.
Claude, you are to marry right away.
Mistress Rosalie!
Worry not, I am unharmed!
This man here...
Mistress Rosalie,
please don't be so naïve.
Let us handle the driving.
Now, come with us.
Claude McDonald, I shall wait
for our fateful reunion!
It's already past the scheduled time.
Did I get lost?
That's odd, I don't see the convent
I'm supposed to pass.
Excuse me, sir!
I wonder if he didn't notice me.
There it is. The convent
I'm supposed to pass!
Please, become the new
wind of Ebenbourg.
There it is!
I have been waiting for you,
Claude McDonald.
Allow me.
No, I'll carry it.
It is my duty.
Please watch your step.
The floor is slippery right now.
What's your name?
Pardon me.
I am Mylene Trantoul,
I am the maid of this mansion.
Well, nice to meet you.
What a wonderful bath.
I'm relaxed.
Lord Eric!
Mylene.
This beautiful scenery, hot springs,
it has appeal as a tourist attraction.
Road maintenance
and establishing enough lodgings...
are the first things I need to do.
It's not like it's been decided...
that I'm going to be the lord
of this desolate region.
But I want to live
up to Sophie's expectations.
It's my first time too.
Blood's starting to rush
to my head I'd better get out.
Mylene!
You mustn't, Lord Eric.
You mustn't, Lord Eric!
Why did you come back?
I want one more chance.
You don't mean become
the Lord of Ronsard again?
That's right. And then...
Ebenbourg will be mine!
At this rate, Ebenbourg will be seized
by a more powerful country.
Before that happens!
You mustn't, someone's here.
Plus Mistress Delmotte will soon arrive.
Sophie Delmotte!
The wretch who sold me out?
Miss Trantoul!
Mylene?
This isn't it. Where was the room
I'm supposed to be staying in?
Mylene, do you know where my clothes are?
They were wet,
so I moved them by the fireplace.
You were changing? I apologize!
- Master!
- I heard a sound.
It's a rat or a fox, maybe a wolf.
Is that why you wanted me?
No, that's not it. It's a mistake.
Do your bidding, Master.
Master, lower.
Okay.
It hurts, Master, please be more gentle.
Sorry.
Lord Eric!
Yes!
It seems that you've failed.
He got lucky.
I've been ordered to help you
from now on, but not directly anymore.
It's up to you whether or not you make
a comeback as the lord.
Eric Flavini.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
To be continued