Promise?
I promise.
Really?
I'll promise I will!
Wind of Ebenbourg
Chapter 2:
The Sea of Treason & Jealousy
I know I was dreaming.
But I can't remember it.
Mylene, Mylene!
Why didn't you wake me up?
I'm finally here.
Found it!
It looks like he is doing well
as the new Lord of Ronsard.
Lord Claude Flavini.
Yes, Grandmother.
He is trying to revive the land
that was dilapidated...
by the previous lord, Lord Eric.
His efforts to strengthen military forces
through heavy taxing and forced labor.
Eric was not a bad lord at all.
He worried about this country's future
in his own way...
and strengthened the military
and weapons industry.
You can say that he tried too hard.
But with that military power...
he attempted to take over Ebenbourg
with a coup d'etat.
Since you caught wind of his plans
beforehand and reported it to the Duke...
Ebenbourg is peaceful today.
So thank you, my dear.
How long will that last, Grandmother?
You're right.
Ebenbourg's state of affairs
with the other kingdoms...
isn't anything to laugh about.
Tourism and trade, the establishment
of this country...
as a center of commerce
is the key to protecting...
the development and independence
of this country.
That is his intentions, Grandmother.
Standing around like that,
he looks exactly like his late father, Bernard.
Lord Eric, Lord Eric.
Mylene, over here.
Did you bring it?
You did well in finding this.
So you slept with him for it?
There is no need to do that with him.
It seems that he doesn't like
to suspect people.
He shows me all the documents
and budget for restoration plan...
without regard and even asks
for my opinion.
He's a failure.
As a lord.
Since Lord Claude has come,
whenever I go out to buy food...
there are so many people out,
you'd think that the population has risen.
Construction and cultivation.
The work load has increased...
and the people must be tired,
yet their expressions are so alive.
Forget it. He's a swindler.
They're all being fooled by his façade.
It's just a game. That's not real politics.
Know what this is?
It's a memorandum I sent
to the Empire of Germany.
When I conquer Ebenbourg,
the Empire will sign...
this non-aggression treaty
and become an ally.
I will have secured the future and safety
of the people of Ebenbourg.
That is politics!
The Lord is a solitary position, my dear.
Lord Eric!
No, don't.
Please stop it.
No, Lord Eric!
Keep going, keep going.
I can't!
Call me Master! Women like situations
like this, you know?
Please stop it, Lord Eric, no!
It hurts.
It hurts!
Lord Eric.
Call me Master! Master, I say!
Master!
No, please!
No, I can't. Please don't, no!
Doesn't this bring back memories?
Back then, when you were full
of desire and passion!
It was incredible.
You like it.
This is really steep.
Better watch my step.
Lord Claude Flavini? Is it you?
Yes. Nice to meet you.
We've met before.
You probably already forgot.
Are you...
Yes?
Are you going home already?
Yes. I was thinking it's about time
to go to the sewer maintenance assembly...
that's being held tonight by the people.
Tonight?
No, wait!
It's lunch time.
And here I worked so hard to make you
such a splendid lunch, Lord Claude.
Isn't it?
You made this all by yourself?
Just for me?
By the way, who are you?
Charlotte Verlaine.
Under the orders of Mistress Sophie,
I have become a maid for Ronsard Manor.
I remember Sophie saying something
about hiring another maid...
because Mylene can't handle
the entire mansion by herself.
Starting to feel good, aren't you?
Your body can't live without me any more.
Stop, it hurts!
No, not yet.
No, it hurts!
You sure? You really want me to stop?
Don't stop.
You telling me what to do?
Then, clean my dick,
covered with your blood.
Stick it in your mouth. Come on.
All right then, get up.
Turn around and stick your ass out.
No more. Please stop it.
No, please stop it.
I can't take it anymore.
It hurts!
It's a good hurt.
I can't take it!
We're just getting going.
No more, please!
Mylene, it's not quite over, yet.
Good.
You like it? It's freshly boiled chicken.
The boiled chicken, I thought I put it
somewhere around here.
Lately foods have been
disappearing. So strange.
What's wrong, Charlotte?
Lord Claude!
I'll prepare your meal right away!
It's okay, I have to go
oversee the bridge.
The Duke of Ebenbourg is coming
to inspect, so I need to prepare.
By the way, have you seen Mylene?
I don't know where she is.
Now that you mention it...
she was setting the silverware over there.
I wonder where she went.
It's okay, I'll look for her.
Yesterday's lunch was delicious.
I'm looking forward to today's meal.
Yes!
You can use the carriage today.
Okay.
I guess there's no way
he remembers anything...
about this town,
or those promises he made back then.
Plus, our social status is so different.
I'm sorry. This mansion
doesn't allow for me to have pets.
Come in.
Excuse me.
You were looking for me?
I thought I put the design for the bridge...
around here, but I can't find it.
Have you seen it?
No sir, I haven't.
Lord Claude,
I will look for it and bring it to you.
You must leave soon.
That's right.
Then, could you?
Charlotte is going to bring my lunch,
so you can hand it to her?
As you wish.
Come to think of it, Mylene,
your birthday is coming up, isn't it?
My birthday is next month.
It may be a bit early...
but you've been working so hard
since I came.
So I prepared a present
for you over there.
I'm just a maid, I cannot take it!
I need you to take it.
They're perishable.
I'll see you later!
Lord Claude.
Lord Eric, what should I do?
That's enough for today,
you can go home now.
Promise?
I promise.
I promise I will.
Lord Claude.
Charlotte?
It looks like I fell asleep.
Do you still have time
before the Duke arrives?
Yes, I do.
Thank goodness.
Were you having
a pleasant dream, if I may ask?
Why's that?
You looked so peaceful
in your sleep.
A dream?
I finally remembered my past.
A promise I made here long ago
with someone I loved.
To get married the next time we meet.
You remembered it. I'm so happy.
Charlotte, I didn't recognize you.
You've become so lovely.
You too, have become so magnificent.
You there! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
This is Ronsard. My land.
We are the Guards of the Duke Ebenbourg.
We have come to check the route
the Duke will take ahead of time.
And we have found and removed
an explosive from the girder of the bridge!
You can't be too careful,
the Duke has had many death threats.
An explosive was planted?
What are you...
It's almost time.
Now all I have to do is wait
for the Duke's arrival.
We will be entering the territory
of Ronsard shortly.
I hear the new Lord
is a noble young man.
Yes.
Unhand him, he is not a villain!
Mistress Rosalie!
It still is dangerous.
Lieutenant, this man is Claude McDonald.
He has saved my life once before.
And will become my groom!
It has already been decided.
Well, that's not...
Lord Claude!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Charlotte, what's going on?
The bomb under the girder is a dummy!
The real one is somewhere else!
What did you say?
Lmpossible!
Something's going on.
Please, stop this nonsense, Lord Eric!
Mylene!
The Duke is here!
He's here!
Let's run away together!
Lord Eric, I love you.
Mylene.
I'll go warn them!
Charlotte!
Charlotte, keep them going!
Yes!
Claude!
It's too late!
Keep going straight ahead!
Lord Claude.
So you are the new Lord of Ronsard.
Pleased to meet you.
Please save the introductions.
Milord! Is everyone all right!
We made it!
All right!
This is the memorandum from Germany!
Tell that swindler to use this and develop
good international relations.
He can make it fall into place.
I'm going to America.
I'm going to start again in a new land.
Lord Eric.
Lord Eric, I'm coming with you!
Call me Master.
It's my first time, I'm scared.
There's no need be.
Charlotte, Here I go.
Are you ready?
I'm ready, Lord Claude!
Are you okay?
Death will come to traitors.