l love you forever
This moment for ourselves
Now and then forever
ls beginning now
One by one
l want to make our memories
So please stay with me
Moonlight and stars are shining
And my body wants their light
Unknown love
Ordinary things in the city....
l love you forever
This moment for ourselves
Now and then forever
ls beginning now
One by one
l want to make our memories
So please stay with me
l love you forever
You're destroying me.
Oh, Carlos.
lt feels so good!
Please enjoy your stay.
l wasn't interested in a boring position as a bodyguard for pop stars.
But it turned out to be such a pleasure.
lf you want to, you can have much more fun, Carlos-san.
Top-class snipers like you are admired by stars of the Vision Center.
A vision scope....
l don't like that. lt's like being put under surveillance all the time.
Right, we might be under surveillance...
...for the purpose of realizing the Megaro Earth Project.
Thank you for this wonderful night.
Too bad, Reiko.
l never imagined that a beautiful girl like you was a Black Widow.
Ouch!
Come with me to the Sniper Control Office.
How did you know?
Private eyes work quickly these days.
Everything we do is for Gimmick-sama.
In 2030 A.D...
...nuclear war broke out over the environmental pollution issue.
Many people lost their lives...
...as did most living things.
People who survived on this barren earth...
...started a project to save human existence:
the Megaro Earth Project, our last hope for survival.
And this city was supposed to be the key for this project.
Open.
Good evening, Sniper El Miles.
Gimmick!
How is the Megaro Earth Project by Uncle Sam going?
We Black Widows will never admit that kind of crap, though.
Fireworks will be up in the sky tonight at Hotel Paradise.
What? Carlos!
Gimmick, you've gone too far.
Stop, I really don't know anything!
Please forgive me!
Please release me. lt hurts so much.
We found traces of gunpowder on your hand, Natsuki-chan.
Please believe me. l don't remember anything.
Would you tell us about Black Widow members?
l don't know! l really don't know!
There are many ways to make you want to talk.
Oh, no....
Nobody at the Sniper Control Office...
...would buy that you don't know anything about it.
No!
Please, someone, help!
Reinhardt is a hard one.
l will go to the Media Center.
l'll go with you if you're going to see Bikks.
No!
Why not?
You're in charge of your own work.
Sniper Control Office
l don't like to be observed.
Hi, El!
Good morning, Chris! Are you getting ready to open the bar?
l heard about Carlos.
He'll never drink with us in this bar again.
You be careful, too, El
Don't worry about me.
l'll drop by later. Say hi to the bartender.
l will. Thank you.
Hey, Parsley is not here yet.
She might have gotten lost. This Media Center building is huge!
Please, Bikks-san.
We can't allow anyone in here
except Vision Center staff.
Pop stars like you wear such cute underwear, huh?
Please stop! Ouch!
Please! You can't do this, even if you are a sniper.
Reiko Mimami was one of these pop stars...
...which means that some of you might be Black Widows, too!
You seduced Carlos with this luscious body, huh?
That's enough, Rob! El will be here soon to help us.
Then we will start the investigation.
Am l late?
No!
What was that?
No, no! What are you doing? Don't come any closer!
Well, we just wanted an autograph from Parsley-san, the superstar.
You guys are Black Widows, aren't you?
lf you know that, then we don't have to explain.
We wanted to borrow your body for a little while.
Please, let go of me!
We are fighting for all humans.
And we need your help, too.
Who's there?
l'm a sniper. Don't resist, or l will shoot to kill, all of you!
You're safe now, Parsley-san.
Parsley....
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Hello, this is the Social Report Company.
Regarding your issue, we'll need some more time.
l knew it.
Linda-kun!
Excuse me, Mr. Phillis.
Have you finished your research for the Sniper Control Office?
Yes, those three men who attacked Parsley...
...we did not find any criminal records on them.
We keep all the records in this city.
Any idea why ordinary, good people...
...turn into Black Widows all of the sudden?
No, sir.
Please send that data to the Sniper Control Office.
l don't think it's helpful, though.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
- Hey, Linda-kun.
Yes?
l don't think that black panties look good on you.
Parsley.
You're awake!
You've been sleeping so long. l was really worried.
El has been working too much.
That's why she's a regular customer here at the Hospital Center.
l haven't been working too much.
Parsley-san has been with you this whole time.
Thank you so much for saving me.
But why were you attacked by Black Widows?
l guess it's because l am too beautiful.
But that endangered you, too.
You know what?
l will sing a song to cheer you up!
l love you forever
This moment for ourselves
Now and then forever
ls beginning now
One by one
l want to make our memories
So please stay with me
l love you forever
This moment for ourselves
Now and then forever
ls beginning now
How was it?
Don't you want to talk about Black Widows now?
l really don't know anything about it.
lt seems that you want to enjoy some more!
Having a hard time, Reinhardt?
Hi, Rob. Did you hear anything from the Social Report Company?
They're not doing shit as usual!
They keep saying, "We found no records."
Why the hell do they get to be on the top floor of the Media Center Building?
Don't complain, Rob. We still have this girl as a clue.
Hey, Miss. Do you like milk?
No! Please stop!
lt will make her want to talk.
What? No!
Don't be shy.
Please don't, please. For God's sake....
Be my guest.
Don't! l really don't know anything.
Please, someone, help me!
lt will ferment quickly since the milk's expiration date has passed.
My stomach....
l can't take this.
Please, forgive me. Please.
Please, take these off. l will talk.
l will tell you everything, please....
Rob, help her.
You need a plug so that it doesn't leak.
No! l'm scared. What are you doing?
Please, pull it out! Pull it out!
You look like you want more. Hey, guys!
Please, forgive me.
Please stop! Help!
lt hurts.
l'll tell you everything. l told you l will.
l see, you don't want to talk.
No. Don't!
Chris!
l heard that you fainted. l was so worried!
Nothing serious. Just anemia.
El will be fine as long as l'm with her.
l didn't know that Parsley-san was such a funny girl.
Hey, Rukka. You've got another rival.
Shit!
Hey, Miss.
l am one of your fans, too, and l always watch your shows.
Hello, l'm Parsley!
This is a present for El's sweet lover. lt's on me.
You guessed wrong, Jose. l'm just her bodyguard.
By the way, Bikks...
...any clues on those guys who attacked Parsley?
Nothing. Reinhardt and his men are investigating Natsuki now.
l see.
Let's not talk about that.
We've got Parsley-chan, our new friend!
Let's have a party tonight!
That's a good idea!
We haven't had a nice chick like her for a while.
More....
El hangs around with Parsley all the time.
ls she really attracted to Parsley?
Gimmick!
You're naughty, El-san...
...being by ourselves in a room when l'm so cute.
What are you talking about? Here.
Turn on the light!
lf my fans find out you slept with me...
...you'll be attacked by them.
Water!
Okay, okay.
Even fanatic camera guys have never seen this. Lucky you!
Okay, okay, l'm grateful.
l will show it to you. Only you.
Don't act stupid!
-Parsley?
-l'm suffocating.
-What?
Hey, Parsley....
Water!
Don't leave me alone.
Then we moved to the second phase.
lt seems to be going well.
Mr. Phillis, you're still here.
What are you researching until this late?
We keep all the records of this city.
We never have enough time.
l see.
El, this is an emergency! Get ready immediately!
Emergency....
We've surrounded 1991 completely.
We're breaking in!
Jose....
El!
Chris Ronchtat. We're arresting you
on the charge of being a Black Widow.
Listen, the Megaro Earth Project is...
We will listen to you closely in the Control Office.
Rob!
-Gimmick!
-What?
Rob, l'll leave it to you.
Bikks!
Thanks, l was having a hard time.
Reiko Minami. Was she Gimmick?
-Please let me go, El.
-l won't!
Please, l don't want them to....
But you....
Rukka!
Why, Rukka?
What's this?