No need to worry.
No abnormalities anywhere.
She is our precious original.
It would be a problem
if anything happened.
It is about time to introduce Joe.
Otherwise it would be disastrous
to the Megaro Earth Project.
Too many accidents this time.
There are elements beyond our control.
Impossible.
Everything is moving on as programmed.
Could there be something
to do with the small fuzzy elements?
They have only one way
to interrupt into this side.
That room in the Social Report Company.
It may become necessary to
terminate the scenario.
In 2030 A.D...
...nuclear war broke out
over the environmental pollution issue.
Many people lost their lives...
...as did most living things.
People who survived on this barren earth...
...started a project
to save human existence:
the Megaro Earth Project,
our last hope for survival.
And this city was supposed to be
the key for this project.
Sniper Control Office
What are you doing? l'll sue you!
Stop acting spoiled!
Black Widows don't have human rights.
You want friends?
- Show her.
-Yes, sir.
l don't know anything.
Really.
Believe me, l'm not lying.
Please.
That girl was quite strong willed.
But now she talks to the walls.
Now...
...tell us everything.
Hey, Parsley.
Maybe l wasn't born to be a Sniper.
That's not true.
El-san, you rescued me.
You were so cool.
l always lose consciousness
at the crucial moment.
l feel like l'll end up doing something irrevocable soon.
Besides....
Chris, Jose, and even Rukka.
They were all Black Widows.
l don't know whom l can trust anymore.
El-san.
You're tired.
l believe in you, no matter what.
Parsley....
l shall share with you the energy source.
Hey, hey, Parsley....
El-san, l love you.
Forgive me. l'm not a Black Widow.
What an unrepentant bitch.
What do you want me to do?
l don't know anything.
Still lying, aren't you?
Believe me. l'm not one of them.
No, no!
They look good on you.
They are gifts from us. Do you like them?
Are you excited by the needles?
What a slut.
Believe me. l'm not lying.
You look far from telling the truth.
ln which case....
We shall let you have more fun.
Until you wish to talk.
What....
Now, Natsuki was fairly tough....
l wonder how long you will last.
Yes, l have fooled Linda well.
Yes. l have already made
arrangements for Rukka.
Yes. Be assured.
Gimmick-sama.
Oh, no, Mr. Phillis is a Black Widow.
l love you forever
This moment for ourselves
Now and then forever
ls beginning now
One by one l want to make our memories
So please stay with me
Moonlight and stars are shining
And my body wants their light
No, no, Parsley.
You're liar, El-san. You aren't hating it.
Parsley....
El-san, l found your weak spot.
l'm telling you, don't....
Parsley. Not there.
There....
El-san, you're so cute.
Like you've never been touched before.
No, it's not like that....
You can't lie to me.
Parsley!
El-san, l love you.
Not there.
Don't do that, El-san.
Stop! Stop!
Lick me, too.
El-san, you're so good.
Something's weird, Parsley!
El-san, l'm coming with you!
El-san....
That's right. l did see Mr. Phillis...
...talking with Gimmick.
Yes.
l understand. Then l'll be waiting.
Chris.
Are you on the job, El?
We received an internal report
from the Social Report Company.
l'm going to check it out.
Geez, what a busy bitch.
Yes, by the time
l came around on my rounds....
Rukka. He must have suffered.
l'm sorry.
lf only l had made my rounds earlier....
No, it's not your fault...
You!
Everything is for Gimmick-sama.
What's going on?
Please don't look at me.
-Black Widow!
-Don't reach for your gun.
You don't care what happens to her?
No, don't kill me.
Now take off your clothes.
l shall rape both of you together.
Do it now!
How embarrassing, you are leaking.
No more! Help, please.
What are you doing, Sniper?
Right, that's good.
No!
-No, no, what're you doing?
-Parsley, how did you get here?
El-san, El-san.
Don't cry, it's all right now. Okay, Parsley?
What do you say?
It's about time we interrupted.
Wait a little longer.
I'm analyzing El's behavioral pattern
up to this point.
l'm sorry, l failed.
You tried to get your hands
on El on your own.
Gimmick-sama is angry.
Damn Kana....
Phillis. Who has done such a thing?
Wait a second, it's me.
Loris? Why are you here?
-Parsley.
-Parsley?
She cried and begged me to come
take a look to see how you are doing.
Did you report
to the Sniper Control Office?
Of course l did. But the problem is....
The Sniper Control Office has been...
Hey, Rob. How is
the 1991 investigation coming along?
-We don't have to do it anymore.
-What? Rob, you!
What happened to
the Sniper Control Office?
-lt doesn't exist anymore.
-Who's there?
-Gimmick-sama.
-Loris, you, too....
Gimmick, you're under arrest.
What? Not again!
Ready for termination.
Let's give it a little more time.
If things go well,
we may be able to introduce Joe.
But what if we miscalculate?
We might end up damaging the original.
We don't have much time.
If it goes well this time,
that would be for the best.
No!
-Hey, are you awake, El?
-Kana.
-What's wrong? Bad dream?
-Yes, a nightmare.
What's going on, Kana? What is this?
Your nightmare has just begun, El.
Or, shall we call it sweet dreams?
Loris. Then, Kana, you too!
We do everything
as Gimmick-sama commands.
Now, l shall start your examination.
No, don't!
Please, no, Kana!
Are you embarrassed, El?
Chris and my other friends
suffered much more.
You've been using this a lot recently?
lt's very fleshy here.
You should suffer just as much as they did!
But Chris committed a crime.
She tried to subvert
the Megaro Earth Project.
Right.
Now.
What is your favorite treatment?
You seem to be able to withstand
ordinary torture.
How boring.
lf you know that,
why don't you just kill me quickly?
l'd love to.
But Gimmick-sama has decided
to finish you off himself.
l wonder why Gimmick-sama
cares about you so much.
Kana, are you jealous?
That's embarrassing.
-Parsley?
-El-san. El-san.
While Parsley watches...
...you will be raped.
Finally, it's my turn.
No, don't, please, no.
Take Parsley away.
El....
No, no.
Don't look, Parsley.
Parsley.
l'm sorry, Parsley, l....
l can't anymore....
No more!
You came, didn't you?
l'm coming inside you shortly!
Bikks.
-Bikks.
-Let El go!
Damn.
l'm so glad you're safe, El.
l'm sorry l'm late.
Bikks?
No. lt's too soon.
l still have things to do.
No. No!
-Parsley?
-Die!
Gimmick-sama, why?
What does she mean, Parsley?
She called you Gimmick.
-No! You, too!
-Don't look at me like that, El!
l peeked into the central
computer at the Social Report Company.
-What're you talking about, Parsley?
-Don't move!
l meant to get you laid
with someone other than Joe.
But we're the only two people
left in this city.
Joe? Who is Joe?
Do you know why Bikks and others
have vanished?
What was l born for?
Tell me, El.
-Parsley.
-Stay away!
lt's all right.
l'll always be beside you.
El....
l love you, too, but...
l don't want them to reset me!
Parsley, what's wrong?
Get a hold of yourself, Parsley...
Parsley!
Parsley Program, Forced Reset Complete.
Parsley, Parsley.
What's wrong? Talk to me.
Please, say something, Parsley.
This Scenario has concluded.
That was close.
We came close to losing the original.
I hope this will have no ill effect
on the emotional side of El.
I do not think we have to worry.
But we never expected the
Replicants to develop self-awareness and...
...revolt against us.
Well, it is important for them
to have many experiences.
Next time we have to
let her consummate with Joe.
After all, they are the
only two human beings left in this world.
Next time we will create
a more romantic scenario.
Until then, sleep tight, El.