The Elven Bride 2
Honey!
Ho... ne... y!
It's morning, wake up, Honey!
You'll be late for work,
if you don't hurry up.
What?
You'll wake up if I kiss you?
Alright, alright!
Boy are you spoiled!
Hey, Kenji, no fooling around!
Milfa...
He's totally gone.
Honey!
Major morning breath!
I guess you're up now.
Come on, time to get going.
Wash your face, and then you can
have your breakfast.
Okay!
Milfa!
I did tell you that I was going to
take you to the clinic, right?
I should be home by noon.
That's fine, I guess,
but is it alright for a National Guard
Captain to take the afternoon off?
It'll be fine.
I know I can count on my staff.
Here's your lunch. Be careful!
Love you!
Bye-bye!
Open up! Open up! Open up!
I'm home, Milfa!
What's this disturbance?
Grandma!
Why are you...
Kenji...
I've told you not to call me Grandma
when I'm in this form!
How many times do I
have to tell you?!
Okay! Okay! Mitsuko! Mitsuko!
Good!
Well, I was in the neighborhood,
so I thought I'd swing by.
I just wanted to see how
you two were doing.
This sucks...
By the way, Kenji, what about your
job with the National Guard?
Even though you're very much
in love with your young wife,
you can't just blow off your job
playing around here.
You'd be neglecting your d uty
as man of the house.
I got off early to take
Milfa to the clinic.
She's going in for a check-up.
Didn't you hear from Milfa?
Yes, I did,
but I sent someone to tell you
that since I'm here,
you didn't need to come home early.
Didn't you get my message?
From who?
That's weird.
The guy said he was a new member
in your squad.
Captain...
You...
You're Gaku, the replacement!
Your grandmother is...
Oh, you're still here?
GAKU!
Hey, this isn't the time for stupid puns!
Pull yourself together, Gaku!
Did you eat him, Grandma?
What did you say, idiot?!
Oh! Mitsuko! Mitsuko!
It's not right to say I ate him.
I just took some of his spirit.
In order to stay in this form,
I need a lot of spirit.
You ghost! Bitch!
You know, he didn't want me
at first, but...
You can't run away from me.
You don't need to be afraid.
I just want a little bit of your spirit.
I'm gonna be raped!
Are you surprised?
This is what we call the secret magic,
the Rejuvenation.
So beautiful!
Excuse me, but...
It's Mitsuko, Mi... tsu... ko.
What's wrong? Is that it?
Mitsuko!
Don't lose your head!
You do have one really good thing...
...a very good sex organ.
Mitsuko! May I do it one more time?!
Mitsuko! Mitsuko!
You're so good...
Mitsuko, let me do it one more time!
Mitsuko! One more time, please!
Why don't we take a break now?
Mitsuko! One more time! Please!
I asked you to wait!
Mitsuko...
...one more time...
...please...
I'm the one who was held,
and not let go.
We did it one hundred eight times.
Naturally, I got tired. So I was resting
when you came in.
Well, then, where's Milfa?
Milfa?
Well...
I forgot why I'm here.
Don't get senile, Grandma!
Oh! That shock helped me remember!
I'm the one who got shocked.
I came back because we forgot
the insurance card.
Milfa's already on her way
to the clinic.
Which one?
She went to the new clinic.
It's on this flyer.
Here!
What the?!
Grandmother is late.
I wonder what happened?
Ma'am?
It seems like I'm the only elf here.
Ma'am?!
Yes?
You look so young. How old are you?
I'm eighteen.
Eighteen?!
Well, she is an elf, you know.
Oh, yeah!
I see...
So she's eighteen in elf years?
In human terms, she could be
hundreds of years old.
No, I mean it's only been eighteen
years since I was born.
Who are these people?
But if that's true, you're not officially
an adult, are you?
I wonder how you managed
to get married?
Well, we've been through a lot,
but we managed it somehow.
I see, it seems very complicated.
Oh, my name is Ion, I'm a mix
between human and jinro.
My husband is a quarter jinro, but
he has a lot of human relatives.
It's very difficult, you know.
But you know, Ion, at least in your
case it's the same two races.
Look at my situation...
My situation!
Since my boyfriend is part beast,
his thing is huge!
I'm gonna break apart!
I'm only a half-hobbit!
I can sympathize with her.
Noitie, you're always like this.
Is that all you have to worry about?
What do you mean, is that all?
This is a very serious problem!
I'm in deep trouble here!
What if our sex life doesn't
improve at all?
I...
...should've known someone who's
already past her prime
wouldn't understand my problem!
Well, let me tell you something!
My husband's only a quarter jinro, but
his thing is like a thoroughbred's!
When he puts his thing inside me,
it's so tight all the air rushes out,
"suka, suka."
Oh, "suka, suka!"
You're so naughty!
My, they're very open!
Faster, Silver!
So Kenji, you know the chief doctor?
You bet I know him!
His name is Perio.
We partied together once.
He used to be a mercenary soldier
who could also do medical magic.
His hobby was housewife hunting,
and he's the best there is.
Now he calls himself a gynecologist
and runs his own clinic,
but his true form is a perverted freak!
Milfa's in danger!
Ma'am, are you okay?
We must finish the examination, so you
can go back home to your husband.
No, please don't talk about
my husband.
Well now, this is really difficult. You...
...have already come so many times,
and you're still getting wetter.
I couldn't let you go now,
even if I wanted to.
Doctor, I...
What if rumors start about adultery
between myself
and a housewife with a good honest
reputation like yours?
No, please don't...
I, too, have to keep up my reputation
as an honest doctor.
So this will be my last time with you.
Please go home after this.
Yes, but...
Please, hurry!
Hisenkyo?
I just heard about this.
There's a fountain whose waters
accelerate body growth.
I did some research about it.
You see, I have certain problems
with my body size.
What is it called?
I can't seem to remember.
Estrogen?
Oh, yeah! That's it!
Ion, you know about this?
Some...
Do you know where it is?
Well, I...
Mrs. Milfa Links, the doctor
will see you now!
Yes!
Just a sec!
Yes?
I'm warning you because
you're so cute.
Be careful with that doctor.
Look at that lady who j ust
finished her consultation.
Thank you so very much.
You see how red her face is?
They say when he looks at you and
touches you that it feels really good.
He seems to be using some
sort of magic charm.
He's a very good doctor though.
But is he a molester?
Go ahead and yell if
something happens.
Okay!
I'm much more relaxed now.
Thank you very much!
She's so innocent.
Really!
And only a year ago, we were
newlywed wives just like her.
Whatever...
Hello, I'm Mrs. Links.
Nice to meet you.
How do you do, Mrs. Links?
I'm Dr. Perio.
Hurry up, Silver! Speed up!
Kenji, this is a dead end!
Jump, Silver!
Right at this moment, Milfa could be...
He looks so much like
his late grandfather.
So, you're having problems
with your husband
because of the size differential?
Yes...
I understand.
First, I'm going to give y ou
a simple check-up,
so please remove your clothes.
Oh, no!
Excuse me, but I don't have
any problem with my breasts.
Well, I'm sorry,
but I need to check your
general physical condition.
Oh, so that's it.
Kenji, I'm sorry.
Well then, please...
Beautiful...
Nice smooth skin and big breasts,
which is unusual for elves,
and a well proportioned body.
I like it!
I think I'll have her too.
If she falls for my charm eyes
she'll become my sex slave
even if she's the most dedicated
wife in the world.
Now then...
Don't! Please don't. Not like this.
Stop...
No!
Open your legs wider
and show it to me.
No! Not...
Here...
It hurts!
No!
Come on, open up.
No, don't look!
It's beautiful, Ma'am.
This is great, Ma'am.
No!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm sorry for taking so long.
Were you cold? Please forgive me.
We'll continue our examination
over here.
Okay...
I'm so glad he's such a nice doctor.
Almost there! Hang in there, Silver!
What's wrong? Run! Please, run!
Grandma!
I will shoot some of my spirit
into the hydra's body.
Hang on!
Go, Silver!
Oh, no! My legs will be
spread wide open!
Don't worry about a thing, a first time
patient is always nervous.
Just try to relax, I'm a
professional doctor.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
That's right, he IS a doctor!
He sees these poses all the time.
Like this, and this, and...
Oh, my God!
But... but I need to have this
examination done,
so he has to look at it.
Therefore... But I just can't bear to
have any one but Kenji see it!
No, be brave, Milfa!
Or else I shouldn't even be here!
Okay!
So, have you decided?
Lovely, fresh bride,
let me help you.
What is this eerie feeling?
Milfa!
I've changed my mind.
Now, don't be afraid.
I 've decided not to.
What's this?
My body is numb from the waist down,
and I can't get up!
Ma'am, you're just an undeveloped elf.
In human terms, you're only
about five years old.
Having sex right away with a body
like yours is an impossible task.
No!
Your body must first be developed by
stimulating all your sexual points.
Fortunately, your body has developed
faster than normal.
With my help, all your problems
will be solved.
Charm Eye!
Milfa!
What?! The power of my charm eyes
is being reflected back out!
What?
No way!
Kenji!
Honey!
Perio! You bastard!
Oh, damn! I can't believe Kenji
is her husband!
PERIO!
Kenji!
I'm fine now.
Is that so?
Milfa...
Newlyweds are so cozy, aren't they?
Ma'am? Are you okay?!
You pervert doctor!
I won't forgive you!
Stop!
Wait!
Damn you!
You're finally here, Doctor!
Doctor, you told me
I was the only one!
You told me that too!
Me too!
Please ladies, let's discuss
this peacefully.
He's trying to escape!
Let's get him!
Stop!
Stop! Let's get him!
You must be Dr. Perio.
Don't be scared, I'll make you
feel really good.
My transformation is
about to melt away.
I must've used up way too much
spirit back there.
Your spirit looks very delicious.
What the fuck...
He called me a kid!
He said I'm only five years old.
Perio has a good eye anyway.
We should be more naughty.
Okay, let's do our best!
Yahoo!
Silly boy!
Just by being there you make
my life wonderful
I'm so excited, please accept me
Let's be such a happy couple
That all the people in the world
get jealous of us
Please love me forever
I trust you forever
I want to embrace you
like the rustling wind
I'll never leave you
We'll never change
mWe'll never change