I can't believe it!
Really, how could he choose
an elven girl?!
I bet she bewitched him
with her magic.
I think so too.
The Gods won't allow
a thing like this.
Yes?
Milfa, are you ready yet?
Kenji!
You're beautiful, Milfa.
Have my parents come yet?
No...
I'm sorry...
Elves are prejudiced against humans,
but I wished they'd celebrate
our wedding.
It's the same for humans.
Never mind, I think they'll
understand us someday.
Oh no, my make up will come off.
I'll protect you from now on!
The Elven Bride
How does it go?
Please treat me kindly
for the rest of my life.
You don't have to be so humble.
Oh, was I wrong?
Your grandmother taught me
the human traditions.
Yeah, she's old fashioned.
Just relax, Milfa.
But...
Right?
We have to follow tradition.
Maybe it's old fashioned,
but for two different races...
Don't talk...
Can I put it in now, Milfa?
Please...
It hurts!
I'm sorry. Are you alright?
This is strange.
There's enough lubrication,
so why is it so painful?
What are you doing, Kenji?
It's so tiny.
It's about half the size
of a human one.
Are all elves like this?
I think I'm normal.
Is there something wrong
with my body?
Is it because I'm an elf?
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
No, of course it's not.
If I had been born an elf,
we'd be together already.
Kenji...
It will be okay.
I'll do something.
There has to be something
in this world
that will successfully unite
a human and an elf.
Wait for me, Milfa.
I'll find it and bring it back,
no matter what.
Wait for me, Milfa!
It's a beautiful day.
Kenji... I wonder what he's doing?
Does he have food every day?
Is he in danger?
I hope he's alright.
I miss you, Kenji!
It's from Kenji!
To my lovely Milfa...
How are you doing?
I've finally found the harpy's nest.
I'll bring home the ultimate
lubrication, harpy ooze.
Wait for me...
I love you, Kenji.
Be careful, Honey.
I've finally found it,
the harpy's nest.
I heard they secrete harpy ooze,
but how will I get it?
Anyway, I have to catch it first,
and I don't want to be too rough.
No!
Another harpy? No, it's not!
Don't hurt the harpy!
Momma...
What the hell are you?!
I am a harpian.
Harpian?
I've never heard of those.
We live in secrecy.
Even if humans see us,
they think we're harpies.
Wait a sec, harpy ooze could be...
There it is.
That is our country.
Jugtrasi Castle!
Princess!
Hi, there.
Princess, is he for...
Yes, I am going to.
Wow! Let's celebrate!
Our princess will finally!
Excuse me.
We've got to tell every one!
Yeah, we'll be busy!
What the hell was that?
Never mind!
Why are there so many human males?
That's...
What is this? Why am I so horny?
Is it because of this smoke?
Wh... what's going on?
Hey, Princess, what is this?
Princess?!
Pyully...
My name is Pyully.
Please use it.
We harpians can't produce
offspring with each other.
Well we can, but they're
always harpies.
Harpies?
That's right.
Now I know why she told me
not to hurt the harpy.
We can only have more
harpians with humans.
The genetic system is
an ancient mystery.
So you kidnap human
males for mating?
Right!
But you're only...
Oh, her tongue's crawling around my...
She's good!
Hang on! Hang on, Kenji!
Don't disgrace your wife!
What a deadly attack.
Hold it, Pyully!
Yours is too tiny for...
Unbelievable! It went in easily,
with no friction!
Into such a small one...
Is this harpy ooze?
It's so smooth yet tight.  Ah fuck!
Please! Shoot inside me!
NO I CAN'T!
This way I'll never come!
Now I'll get the harpy ooze!
I won!
With this harpy ooze,
I can finally do it with Milfa.
Now I have to get back home!
I'll be back soon, Milfa!
A few months later, Pyully had triplets,
two girls and one boy.
You can make a girl pregnant with
just a drop of semen, you know!
Elven Bride
Elven Bride!
You damn elf!
My mom said an elf isn't human!
You monster elf! Let's get out of here!
Hey, the elf girl is mad!
My Gods, why can't I be
friends with them?
Look, a female elf.
Whatta babe!
Well, may I have a squash
and a pumpkin?
No you can't!
I'll sell to you if you really insist,
but the price will be this much!
Three times more?!
Why is it so expensive?
You don't have to buy it
if don't want to.
Our disgusting food won't
please an elf, right?
No, I'll buy it!
Otherwise, I guess I'll
have to gather nuts.
I wish I had a chance to be
friends with a human.
Get out of my way!
Get out of my way, elf!
Or I'll crush you!
Hey Gordon! Stop, stop now!
The children!
Spirits of the Earth, I summon you!
Please come to me!
Hurry, run away!
Milfa, I'm home!
Honey!
I've finally acquired the
mysterious harpy ooze.
Oh, my!
Let's go home and try it.
Wow!
Hi-ho, Silver!
My hydra...
What about your hydra?!
Shut the fuck up!
Yam, Seaweed, and Green Onion
dressed with Soup Stock
Super Power Drink
Whole Grain Rice
Stir fry of Garlic and Bacon
Turtle Soup Fresh Egg
Blast off!
What a lot of nutrition!
Oh, can you tell?
Well, I thought you'd
need more energy.
Oh...
I'm embarrassed!
I've been thinking since then.
Although it's too big to
fit there, it might...
Well, we tried only one.
One? One what?
Well, you know, something
about the position...
Oh, you mean the different
positions for sex?!
Geez! He's just trying to
embarrass me.
Yeah, I think we should try
various positions.
Don't!
I'll finish this first!
There should be a position
that makes it easier.
Do you have any ideas?
No! I have no idea.
Crazy!
What? Didn't you think of anything?
Anyway, I was going to ask you...
Ask me what?
From the backside...
Alright, the back?
Let me try it!
Wait, Kenji, let me take a bath first.
No! I can't wait!
No problem, just leave it to me.
Can I try now?
Here I come...
Brace yourself...
Now...
The harpy ooze...
I'm ready!
It's getting in a bit.
It's no use, no further than that.
But a bit got in.
Honey...
Try some other ways too.
I got it!
I'll try until it's all the way in.
Milfa...
What?
It shrunk. Sorry.
Let's try again, next time
with a better aide.
Kenji...
It was so painful!
There, there...
If I force it, I could hurt her.
She looks better now.
But even harpy ooze didn't work.
I wish there was a way.
Kenji?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
These are big.
Honey?
They grew so big.
Yeah, this is rare for an elf.
They're so soft.
What?
Kenji is always so sweet to me.
I'll make an effort too.
Kenji, are my boobs that good?
Oh yeah!
Do you want to...
What did you say?
With my boobs?
Do you mean...
I want to make you happy.
You're always good to me.
I want to do something for you.
Thank you, Gods!
Okay, sit on the edge.
Yeah!
He looks so happy.
This makes me so horny.
Is it that good, Honey?
Okay, let me use more friction.
Sooo goooood!
Oh, Kenji?!
Milfa!
Hurry up!
Okay!
Keep watching.
Is this really enough?
I'm sure.
She's poor and sometimes
she only has nuts to eat.
How do you know such a thing?
The elf girl...
She's so beautiful.
He seems so satisfied.
It was embarrassing,
but I'm happy anyway!
Say, Milfa...
What?
Now you've created your
ultimate technique,
should I call it
"The Golden Boob Finish?"
Hey, knock it off!
If you say that, I won't do it again!
Just a second, Milfa!
What?!
Sorry...
What's up?
Hey, what's this?
Thank you, we're sorry.
Thank you too!
That's good.
I can make friends with
them gradually, can't I?
I think so.
So, we shouldn't fight.
Oh, I don't know!
Just by being there you make
my life wonderful
I'm so excited, please accept me
Let's be such a happy couple
That all the people in the world
will get jealous of us
Please love me forever
I trust you forever
I want to embrace you
like the rustling wind
I'll never leave you
We'll never change
The shining sky is all ours