Licensed by Airu
Original Story Direction: Aki Rivahara
Please don't touch my sister.
Osamu Momoi
No!
The king of Valdland is coming.
The king is more
merciless than Prince Vice.
It hurts! It hurts!
Ninia!
This is the end of Fiel.
If you don't serve well, you'll
be immediately sent to the gallows.
Now suck my dick.
Character Design: Toshihide Masudate
Come on now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Director: Hiromi Yokoyama
Production: Pink Pineapple
My future-seeing eye...
What a sinister future it was...
Servant Princess - Chapter 3,
White Princess and Black Princess
Marna.
What is it, Your Highness?
I'll become king in the future.
When I become king, will you, Marna...
Will you stay by my side?
Your Highness!
Miss, I have an important
thing to tell you.
Your Majesty wants
you to be his new wife.
Prince Vice?
Queen Marna wants to see you.
My Mother?
It's been a while since the
last time I met you, Vice.
You came here with such a few escorts?
What brought you here?
I thought if I were here...
...I could protect you a little.
The king has decided
to kill you for treason.
What did I do wrong?
You've pushed things
too far in this country.
However, it was his Majesty who said
Prince Vice could do anything he wished.
I see.
The whole thing was originally
planned to set me up...
Wasn't it, Mother?
No, stop it.
Please, stop, Your Majesty.
No.
It hurts!
I can't do this, it's too
embarrassing, Your Majesty.
It was a long time ago,
but I still remember...
Is it you, Ann?
Yes.
Well, may I ask you a favor?
Even if my body is disgraced, my
heart is dedicated to Prince Kwan only.
I'm so glad that I
could make you feel good.
Stop it, Elfeana.
I don't want to stop it, Prince Kwan.
I want to be one with you, Prince Kwan.
Elfeana...
Elfeana, why have you changed so much?
Please stop them.
It's only hurting the Princess.
Why should I stop them?
I allow them to do it.
Is it because they make your pussy wet?
No, I can't say such a thing.
Say it, or...
No, not there!
So say what you want to say.
Yes, it makes me so horny.
Just looking at Your Highness
doing it makes me horny.
It also makes me sad.
It makes me crazy.
After I separate them, what
are you going to do with Kwan?
If you want, shall I give him to you?
What?
Isn't that your true wish?
No, I'm not...
When King Bandious comes
here, Kwan must be killed.
Princess...
Soon I have to decide what I should do.
Vice...
It hurts.
What's the matter?
We shouldn't do this.
I'm your stepmother.
What are you trying to start?
I don't think of you that way.
Let me go.
It's too late, we can't
go back to the past.
If the king finds out, you'll
get terrible punishment.
You knew that, yet you still came here.
You and I have to go
forward. There's no other way.
Good boy.
So sorry Princess...
Prince Kwan...
No, it's so embarrassing!
No, stop it. You're making me crazy!
Tonight, I make you mine.
Marna!
Vice!
P-Prince Kwan is missing...
Prince Kwan, we can be
out of this country soon.
You want to know where Kwan is?
I released him.
Ann is with him.
No.
Get off!
No!
Prince Kwan!
If you want, why don't you go after him?
This country will die soon.
No!
What?
You didn't expect that I'd
tell you to escape from here?
I haven't gotten over what
the King did to me before.
Are you crying for me, Elfeana?
I made you feel the same way.
No, it's okay now.
I'll die with the King when we
fall upon each other's swords.
You should do whatever you want now.
Prince Vice...
I'm coming.
Vice.
Come back from this battle.
Elfeana is pregnant.
It's probably your child.
What timing!
I won't die!
To make love with you
both, I'll come back here.
Several months later.
You can't escape any more.
You stay here as men's toys forever.
Please, stop it!
Both of you got pregnant
with Vice's children.
You are both horny bitches.
Elfeana, wait for me.
Let's go!