Wataru
You've watched me all along?
There's only you in my heart
I love you, hug me now!
Mai!
It hurts! Back at home indeed
Almost can be with Mai in the dream...
Who is it?! So noisy!
"Doukyuusei ~ Chapter 1"
"When summer ends"
Wataru has gone out
Please call again after 10 years
Wataru!? It's me. Katsuya
That guy. Katsuya, idiot!
Calling me so early in the summer morning
There's one thing which is very important to me
There's a big matter of life
I have to talk with you
I know nothing!
I just know I have to see Mai now
Wait, you heartless!
We still have chances later on, let's meet with me first
Understand, no matter how
I have to hang up the phone
Promised?
See you at the station at 11 o'clock!
Today is the birthday of Kurumi,
no wonder... Katsuya..
Work hard! Work hard!
Wataru!
It hurts!
Wataru, you come to peep on girls again?
Misa!
Only obscene people peep
You say so because of having a guilty conscience
What?
Misa, even if you're naked,
no one would come to peep.
Is it from the Banbi of track club?
It's too impolite to me
Banbi said...
You think whatever you like
Wataru, could you write back a letter?
What letter?
Oh, Miho, she is very annoyed!
That kid is so simple!
This will hurt her heart
Understand, I'm a gentleman you know
Wataru...
Bye
Idiot!
Misa, that girl never changes at all
just like a boy. Compare with her.
Mai is the best beauty.
she has woman style, no matter what I have to do.
I must date her in this summer.
Mai! Try hard!
Everybody stand by!
Moroko Wataru!
Don't watch Mai in nasty eyesight
Ready!
She is the golden sportswoman who
bears the reputation of the school
Do you knew what your status?
The flower on high mountain, can you pick it in your hand?
Before you fail painfully, let's give up!
Keinze, how you can you talk to me in this way?
Mai is for me.
I'm a different man
You'll know it someday
What? This guy...
Not good!
Miho
Yes, welcome
Wataru!
Good afternoon.
What can I do for you? Really...
Make a bunch of flowers of 3000 dollars for me.
Let's make a luxurious one with 10 thousand dollars.
Understood!
You!
This is the punishment of you being late
Do you know I've worked part time job
almost the whole summer holiday?
This money...
Only with Mai I can...
have a wonderful memory of summer holiday
Serious? Let's stop.
Mai is a 100% real rich daughter.
Doesn't suit you, you will only cry at the end
Understand? Face the reality
Aren't you the same?
Kurumi also haven't showed anything to you, right?
So, today is Kurumi's birthday...
I've already decided to give what present.
You've waited so long
Is this?
Big Gift
Then... thank you, bye, thanks
Lend me your motor bike.
Wait... Katsuya!
I...
What?
You already read the letter?
I've seen it, this is...
No, so shameful
I'm so shy, use letter to reply me.
Please!
Mi... Miho...?
Katsuya! You're late!
Sorry... look at this!
Happy birthday!
Katsuya, you really... Thanks!
So beautiful
But, are the flowers expensive?
Nothing
But I don't have anything in return
Then... Give me a kiss is alright...
If you hug me, that's even better...
No, Katsuya always joke with me.
It's not a joke!
Welcome!
What happened, Wataru?
In short, can't say in few words
Such a hot weather
Treat people as puppet...
Katsuya!
Hello!
Wataru, good afternoon.
Kurumi
Katsuya is good at playing ropes and candles the most
Be careful!
Yes, but I also like switching off the light.
the thing that lighting lots of candles.
Seems like their lines are perfect.
I also can't consider so much anymore
I have to date with Mai as soon as possible.
Mai!
Thanks
You like reading this kind of novel?
You always come here?
Not always
When I have an exam...
Want to take a walk with me?
Sometimes you have to relax
This... I have to join the alumni club...
and I have to learn piano and tea ceremony
Many things have to do...
So...
Sorry!
Mai...
What kind answer is that?
So tired! Can't concentrate...
Katsuya!
Listen to me... Kurumi...
Kurumi she...
Very tired...
Katsuya just said such words...
He must have taken her to the hotel then be refused
"Yes, that's it..."
Just come back after saying that?
Work hard! Work hard!
Everybody is sweating the sweat of youth
Misa
Just as what Banbi said
If you work a little bit harder,
you'll be able to stand out in this field
Not good
Wataru, don't you sleep more in summer?
You even come to school everyday
Is it because you always shirk as usual?
This is because...
I disgust the school which we have to study a lot
But the school we don't have to study, I like it.
Satisfied?
Even with such an excuse, you have other purpose, right?
Wataru, no matter what, you're free, right?
Then... something...
Tanaka
Yes
Tanaka, please come with me
Wataru, bye!
What did this guys say?
Forget it!
Undrestand? Tanaka
Yes
Keinze and Mai...
Mai! Don't show your smile in front of that guy
Should find out some solutions...
Who is it?
Wataru, come with me. OK?
Your parents want you to quit the track sport?!
Quit the sport club, and concentrate in preparing for the exam
Already in form 3 of high school
Your parents are right.
After you quit track club,
maybe you can be more girly.
Wataru, I'm serious to discuss this with you!
You even...
It's good to be as you
Just feel happy being with girls usually
How come...?
Wataru, if quitting from track club,
can you imagine what would it be?
From form I to now at high school
Till the start of final racing
The final racing,
I have to complete it.
Let's complete it!
Then continue the track!
Don't care about what your parents said
Wataru...
Do it with confidence, Misa
Isn't it the best?
Yes... yes
Thanks, Wataru
Yes...? She even says thanks from her mouth
She must be sick
Wataru...
No!
Don't shout like that, OK?
Wataru
Although it's a very shameful thing.
But you also have to courage to speak it out
I Miho...
I Miho... want to date you to watch movie.
It's best to watch love story
Waiting for your response
From Susuki Miho
No!
Miho, can you be quied?
Sorry...
No!
Behave yourself!
Let's go out!
Wataru, what have you done to Miho?
Nothing... that?
Yesterday when she called me, she was crying all along
What's happened?
This is... That event...
The one who wanna cry is me.
This date would result this way
You're thinking of any trick again?
Do you know? Wataru
Miho is different from the girls you used to date with
This time you make her cry, then there'll not be next time
Who you like then?
Don't ask... This...
Say it clearly!
This... It's you, Misa
Misa, you're the one I like most.
Really, idiot
What's the matter?
Bye-bye
Bye
See you tomorrow
Mai, bye-bye
Bye-bye
Can't refuse a date this time,
right?
Sorry, goodbye
Is it true that you date with Keinze?
Really true
Don't say these, it's a lie... those words
Really?
Right
Men should have strength
If you have strength, that's the best
Family background and property
are just the next important things
Don't gift me, MY SON
Wataru have no strength!
That's something in novel...
That fire shoot out
If that fire shoot out
Next chapter is...
A body appears in front of a girl
his chest is shaking on the girl's breast.
This...
That's this elastic force!
I've imagine that under this school uniform before...
The teenager is touched
In a scene just as he said
Expecting all along...
Let's go to southern island together, OK?
The playground of YaBuCyo city
Just heard that at southern island a
"WATER PARK" opened
Let's go to play!
I...
This Friday, 01:00 pm
I wait for you at playground
Piano lesson is arranged that day...
Can't you skip once?
Yes... yes...
Good, we've decided it
See you at playground this Friday!
Success
Really a pestering boy again
Misa?
What you doing here?
Bleeding?!
Nothing! Just a little wounds means nothing to me
Don't touch me!
Misa
What... are you doing? Stop!
C'mon! We return to take back the bike later
So shameful! Put me down!
You...
I've told you to put me down!
So hurt!
Idiot! Wataru, put me down!
If you still move so violently, the wound will be more serious
You'll be a cripple
The racing is near, right?
You should protect your legs well
Misa...
Your breasts are so big
Blockhead!
Can't say in anyway?
Your knee bone being so because you've over practiced
Now stop the running practice
If you don't do surgery...
No
Don't be so self witted!
Teachers are worried about you so
Misa, you've already try your best, let's just give up
When you've cure your legs, then enter a common U...
Enough! Don't worry!
Wataru...
Hello, I'm Moroko Wataru... Makon Sensei!
If you wanna date me, it's more suitable to be at night
Misa? Yes... I come at once
Even such thing! Is it really?
But, why call me?
I don't know also
Tanaka has something to talk to you privately
I've heard from her, maybe it'll have a big effect
Maybe just you can do it only
Depend on you
Yes
I'll be at the teacher's office...
No, nothing
Stay by her side...
She's in the most painful period
Yes
Misa
Fell down during the morning practice...
Even changed into this, really unbelievable
Makon sensei has already told me
Right?
I'm really a fool
Because of practicing with all my force
Changed into can't run again
But... only Wataru you...
Told me that do with my confidence
Then that's OK...
Thank you, Wataru
Misa...
Finally, you can achieve what parents hope this way
No! Don't say such thing!
Everybody is worrying about your health...
I understand!
But...
Wataru
Misa
Although I don't know it clearly, if you recovered
Doesn't it mean that you can continue running?
Everybody say so!
This is my last chance
Therefore I endure the pain all along till now
No one understand my feeling originally
Sorry, Misa... But...
Everybody say so just because they worry about you
Especially me, I can't quarrel with a healthy you
I'm so lonely
Wataru
Let's brace up
Even you can't run again
It doesn't mean that you're over as so
I...
Is my muscle solid?
Very soft... So great
Very nice
Wataru... So shameful
No
Wataru
Here I go
So painful
Don't move
Wataru
Wataru, Wataru
2 days later
Misa handed the resign letter to the track club
In autumn, I met Misa on the street.
Misa
Good afternoon, Wataru!
Long time no see
Accompany me for a while. OK?
I've heard that you've performed the surgery already
I'm fine now, I think
I can return to school soon
Really? That's great
Thank you
I...
I also feel that I persist unbelievably
How could it be that? Wataru
Don't know...
All along
I think that the track club is my whole life
But I found an other things which even excited me
What things?
I won't tell you now
Forget it! What kind of things will excite you?
A person who have so strong fighting feeling like Misa
Thank you, Wataru
Bye
Next time...
Next time, I'll to go your home to play
You can't run!
Forget it!
But... Misa, this tomboy
Finally speaks as a woman...
Why is it like that?