Really! What's this ghost place?
It's even hard to find a convenience shop so early
Wataru...
I'm totally hopeless this time
What has Katsuya done?
Kurumi don't want to date with me
Seem she has someone she love already...
Maybe it's someone we know...
Kurumi, you're so lovely
Wataru...
Wataru... I wanna die...
Why Natsuko and Kurumi is just the same?
Seems like between people,
the same things happened repeatedly
Especially the relationship between man and woman
Really an unbelievable thing
At first Katsuya wooed Kurumi
Then Kurumi being nice to Katsuya, but he haven't cherish it
And is that I have to think of her all along
Till the summer ends?
"Doukyuusei ~ The final chapter"
"When summer ends"
Welcome!
Boss, a cup of cold coffee
Today's weather is really so hot
What's wrong? Wataru
Seem you are not very energetic
Are you suffered heatstroke?
No such thing!
You see how strong I am
Really not having a fever?
It's better for you to take rest when you have time
You don't be too involved.
Welcome
No need for change
Thanks
So great
He is that kind of man
When women saw him they will think he is very handsome.
And his action is so gentle.
Is that really?
Never thought I'd meet her in this place
I think I won't see her again this summer
From Mai, it's for you
Mai!
Wataru
When I saw you at the coffee shop
I still think that I'm dreaming
Sorry
I wanted to talk with you clearly last time
But I didn't have a chance.
This time, I can meet with you
I really thanks for the arrangement of Got
Thank you, sis.
My dad is very strict looking after me
So he doesn't allow me to get along with friends of other sex.
Then Keinze?
He will go abroad with family soon.
We are just as friends.
Nothing happened at that time
I haven't cheated you
Really!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I thought even I've said that.
You wouldn't believe me.
Sorry.
Mai
Don't mention the past anymore.
Let's go to playground together, OK?
But...
Alright?
So great!
The dating time has passed.
What happened with Mai?
Maybe she doesn't want to come?
Wataru
You've waited so long, sorry.
You are Mai?
Since there's a reason,
I have to wear like this
No! I don't mean that.
It's just a little out of expectation.
Then let's go quickly!
Mai?
Don't speak!
They are the staff of my dad.
They come to get you, Mai?
So great, haven't been discovered by them.
But it should be OK being here.
Don't let them destroy our date.
Let us play heartily!
Long time ago,
When I was small...
My dad brought me here to play.
At that time, there were many people waiting down there.
My dad is the boss of here.
What? Your dad is the boss of this playground?
At that time, the ticket staff saw that I was waiting,
so he let me in first.
One time, the one before me was my classmate.
Seeing that I had priory,
his attitude to me changed in to a great degree
My dad also fired the ticket staff.
From then on,
I won't come to playground anymore.
That's not your fault, Mai.
Thank you
Wataru, you're really nice to me.
Mai...
Miss, we come to take you back home.
No!
We come by the order of the director.
No! I won't go back!
Get me go!
Wataru!
Mai!
Wataru...
Wataru!
Mai... Mai!
Disgusting, what nonsense are you talking about?
What's the matter? Wataru
Teacher Senri!
Are you being dumped by a girlfriend?
No... not that...
Seems like you're finding trouble to yourself.
The next semester is coming soon.
Are you energetic to go to school?
Are you OK?
No...
Wataru
You just lack of courage and force in your age.
So have to...
Courage and force...
Thank you! Teacher!
I will work hard!
I gotta go now!
Remember this summer holiday is just 3 days left.
Yes! I know!
Does he really understand?
Only 3 days left, then the summer holiday will end.
Courage and force?
Seems like no one home.
Mai!
What are you here for?
I come to find Mai!
Mai is now forbidden to go out.
You better leave her farther, in order to not getting in trouble.
What?!
Get away!
I'm the bodyguard Mai's parents sent formally.
What are you saying?!
See! This is the evidence!
See it clearly yourself!
Authorization letter?
I hereby authorized Mr. Aihara
Keinze formally.
to take care of Sakuraki Mai's life?!
Then you should understand, right?
You won't be able to be with Mai.
What are you saying?
Mai's everything belongs to me!
Idiot
Little kid! I warn you!
Don't think a plan of Mai!
No such petty gains!
Get away with your tail quickly!
You're really disgusting!
Do you want money?
I ask you if you want money?
Mai is the daughter of a rich family...
Damn it!
No such thing! I treat Mai with my heart!
It hurts! Very painful!
No!
Wataru...
You know my strength now?
Hari! Sair!
Wataru...
Mai... I must find a way to see you!
Mai
Sorry, there's a little trouble outside.
You've been scared.
So shameless.
He wants to be a hero this way.
Wataru...
Poor people always like doing this.
Man I had to work hard all along without afraid of failure.
Then at last, success will belong to you.
I must not afraid of failure, work hard till the end.
I left my family just because of this!
Mai!
Wataru!
Mai...
I want to open the knot in my heart.
I can't stand my dad and the people surround me already.
I... I...
I have to surpass the present me.
Please take me!
Mai...
Mai
Wataru...
Can the light be dimmer?
If I switched of the light, then
I can't see your tempting look.
No
No...
Can't...
Wataru...
Mai, I love you.
I love you too.
Mai...
Wataru, be gentle to me...
No!
What's wrong?
Nothing, but...
Are you shy?
Anything else?
Just shy only...
No!
No... no...
No... no... Wataru...
No!
What's the matter?
It's my first time, sorry...
You said so. Will make me even more excited?
Really?
I am a person who always give others trouble...
Really... silly...
When it's comfortable.
Open yourself just following your feeling, OK?
Let me... let me feel more, alright?
Wataru, I feel it, very shame...
Wataru!
No... no... Wataru...
So shameful...
No!
No... please don't watch there, very shameful
Your place is very cute, Mai
Don't say it! I'm so shy!
Really
No...
Very shy...
I feel it.
So sore... Wataru...
Enough...
Mai...
Wataru...
Come to me...
Mai...
Wataru...
Are you OK?
I'm very happy
I feel that I'm become one with you.
Mai...
Wataru...
So painful...
Be stronger...
Mai...
I love you... Wataru...
Can I stay here tonight?
I'm so happy
I'm going back home first.
Please don't worry about whether my dad will be angry.
I can't meet you before the summer holiday ends.
But, that doesn't matter.
When school starts, we can meet everyday.
I'm late!
As if forgetting the time, spreading out.
Wataru, Misa ask me to say hello to you.
Good morning, Wataru
Good morning...
Seems like I'm going have troubles this semester.
Wataru! Wataru!