Mai, you're here?
Wataru
Mai!
Do you love me?
Of course!
This...
Mai!
If you catch me...
You can do whatever you like
Good!
Here
Still... you have no chance
What's the matter?
Only I can suit for...
Keinze... Keinze
You're lying, that's just a lie
Stop! Stop...
"Doukyuusei ~ Chapter 2"
"When summer ends"
That's a joke
Why would I see that kind of scene in a dream?
Did I eat something rotten?
Seems like she still wants to say something
If you can't get along with Mai
Maybe it's the reason that idiot Katsuya said
Kurumi being with Katsuya, really is a waste...
Anyway
This Friday I can date with Mai finally
I shouldn't care of that little thing
Work hard! Work hard!
If we have the foundation, before the summer ends,
Maybe I can be with Mai...
Keinze this blockhead, always hinder me
Satomi...
Satomi, why are you here?
What's the matter?
I must go back to the swimming pool in school to see Mai now
Mai
Good morning!
Good... good morning! Mr. Moroko
Mai, I beg of you
Don't call me Mr. Moroko anymore, OK?
How can I say... seems like there's a little distance
Calling Wataru or Mr. Wataru should be...
Doesn't it feel much friendlier?
The rumor is true really
Mai, this saying...?
Can't come near to Moroko Wataru within I'm...
This... how could be such a rumor?
Mr. Wataru
Yes
In fact, I want to talk to you long time ago
Really?
So, Friday, we must play very happily
Success!
Welcome
What, it's Wataru
Anything unhappy?
No need to worry, what do you want?
That's it, coffee
Coffee, got it
Please wait for a while
...something bothering you, right?
No such thing, but for Wataru
No matter what you said it can also be accepted, that's true
Come again, haven't ever thought that
I'm a man also?
I don't mean it
But... since secondary school
I've known you for 6 years already...
If we meet in common situation, it should be that
We would have at least 1 to 2 sex relationships
Not exactly! You're so young that
you already indulged yourself
Isn't it too foolish?
Discussion finished
Keep on saying
Satomi, would you give me one more cup of coffee?
Yes
Wataru, you really like Mai?
Even be infatuated
Right
That's trouble
Is the relationship of that girl with Keinze good?
That guy has no relation with her
Yes
But... why would you talk about this?
No...
If saying so
When I saw you at the river side this morning
Seems like you're laden with anxiety...
Nothing
Understand! You're jealous about Mai and me
Idiot
Really!
No solution to Kurumi's childish
Right?
Damn it!
Is it because he did something disgusting to her?
Forcing her too much?
Forget it, what should I do?
The most important thing is are you treating her heartily?
Pretending to be silly again?
You can't do what Kurumi want
Then you'll never understand her at all in your life
Also one time...
Even her father appeared saying to me
"What you wanna do with my daughter"
Even said so to me!
Really?
OK... decided! Then I give up on Kurumi
Find a more mature woman!
What should you do about Kurumi?
Not my business!
Then even no problem to give her to me?
Up to you!
Bye
Forget it, he...
A while later he will...
Satomi and Keinze...
Then... I can't see Mai
Is there something wrong with Mai today?
Should it be it, she's sick...
You won't see Mai anymore
What are you saying?
Tomorrow I'll go with Mai to...
What's your relationship with Mai?
Not your business!
Anyway, you can't get close to Mai anymore
MASTER, is Satomi here?
She called back and said...
Today I'm sick, I need rest
Such a rare thing happens?
Have you felt that Satomi is a little bit strange recently?
Don't know why
Bleeding a little after broken something
Then she keep silence...
Also one time
She poured coffee on customer's suit
Really trouble
Is it him...?
That's it, you know why?
No...
Wait, Wataru!
You must know something?
I don't know, how could I not know the business of that guy?
Yes... But I'm really worry about her
Welcome
Kurimi! What's happened?
Wataru!
I...
Kurumi... Kurumi
Katsuya is very cool recently?
What...
You shouldn't cry so loud just for such thing?
But! Even he doesn't talk with me when I'm dating with him
When I call him, he always says he has something to do
Just as he doesn't want to see me
This idiot! Seems serious
I...
Not long ago, he took me to a hotel
Is that why he's unhappy being refused by me?
This...
No! No! No!
How could it because this, Kurumi?
Since Katsuya didn't comforted by you, Kurumi
If so Kurumi, you should show your smile
Katsuya will be very gentle at once!
Really?
I believe in Katsuya totally!
That's it
The affair between man and woman is always tangled up!
I can't distinguish it also
How come?
I...
Wait! Please listen to me!
Satomi
Wataru
What's the matter? It's rare to see you look sad
Satomi...
What's the matter?
Last night, at the coffee shop, in front of game center
I saw you talked with Keinze
What did you say?
No... we just met coincidentally on street
Bye
So soon...
Anyway, I'm free...
Wataru
MASTER, what's the matter?
Big event!
Have you seen Satomi?
Satomi? You haven't seen her?
That kid disappeared!
Since she hasn't come to the shop this morning.
So I'm worry about her
I called her home
Her mother even said she went out to work
If anything happened, it would be trouble
Will you help find Satomi?
Now I've something to do
Please! Mr. Wataru!
I understand...
Don't know what I'm doing...
Wait...
Satomi? Have you seen her today?
Really, didn't see her?
Have you seen her?
What happened? That kid...
No! Nothing!
Bye
Satomi... MASTER is worried about you very much
Let's contact with him...
Satomi... maybe I'm too involved...
You and Keinze...
Don't care of me!
Sorry... please... let me be alone
Satomi...
Finally caught up
Girls always have to spend more time to dress up
It must be I've said the wrong time...
Yes, Sakuraki's home
Excuse me... I'm Maroko, is Mai home?
She said before starting school,
she won't meet with you definitely
She won't do that kind of low grade dating
Sorry!
May I ask...
Why is that?
Mai...
What's the matter?
So noisy!
Wataru is out now
After the "Beep" sound, please...
Wataru...
Satomi?!
Sorry for calling you so late
No, it doesn't matter
Thank you for this afternoon.
I'm very happy...
Wataru, I...
Satomi, where are you now?
That?
Satomi
Thanks... Wataru, you worry a lot about me
I really haven't think of it...
No...
Have you contacted MASTER?
You gave everybody so much troubles...
Really sorry.
Satomi
Wataru... I've been dumped by Keinze...
I really like him so much
But as a result...
He loves another girl again
Other... girl...
Hug me! Wataru!
Satomi...
Please! Help me forget him
Doing so... is it really OK?
Only you can do that
You're so beautiful... Satomi
So happy
Make me forget all the things...
Satomi...
So great
I'm very happy
Let's make me forget all the things...
Wataru...
Satomi... I almost
I also coming
Bye, take rest soon
Wataru! I...
Next time, when I come to the coffee shop
You have to make coffee for me!
Thank you, Wataru