Sachi. Your breast turns big recently
Let me see
Don't!
No, I can't
Mai isn't here, really
How's that?
Satomi
How long do you need to peep?
This behavior is so bad!
Satomi You are just the same
You can't forget him. So you come to school?
Him?
You mean Keinze?
Wrong
I forgot him, so I come here
Satomi
Satomi Seems to have forgotten him
Look at yourself again
Can't forget Mai
"Doukyuusei - Chapter 3"
"At the end of summer time"
Welcome!
Very hot!
Boss, I'll have a cup of cold coffee
Okay
Welcome!
Wataru, too much coffee isn't good to the stomach
Don't worry
My mind is bad but my stomach is good
Okay! Yes!
You have usual meals three times a day?
Summer posses soon, it's good to eat more
Weclome!
What! Satomi suppose to know much
She is so mature, cheerful as well
Really can't imagine before
I am worried of a thing for a certain time
Do you know that?
I beg you
Help me forget him
I can?
Only can help me
Wataru
Are you thinking of something?
No!
Something did happen
No, no big deal!
But Satomi has grown up and mature
Yes
Hey! Wataru
Satomi needs to keep operating
the coffee shop after graduation
I heard that, so touching
Boss, no need to exaggerate
How's that?
Nothing
Satomi, you are so cheerful,
I am so glad
Boss, coffee, hot tea, one for each
Also two yogurt cakes
Yes, starts working now
Satomi, have you got a boyfriend?
I won't abandon Wataru who is too slow
Hey! Satomi, you mean who?
Stupid
Satomi, that girl,
I ain't so slow
Thanks!
Please come again!
Bad, it's Miho
It's bad!
Wataru?
It's really you!
This is. Please take this letter
Miho
Sorry
Don't look over here, I feel sorry
I know that
I'll return here again, I gotta go
Wataru
Wataru, what's the thing between
you and Misa?
Please reply
Sure something happens
Miho, I have something to do
I gotta go.
It's really troublesome!
Shit! So careless
Really sorry!
Here is?
What's this?
Sorry
Mai!
Mai, I haven't forgotten
the engagement that we are go to the playground
Sorry
Mai!
It's Keinze!
Youthful!
Katsuya
Ten days later summer is over
I need to keep my body fit
So that won't lose to anyone
You seem energetic
I can observe
You and Kurumi, still in good condition?
Kurumi? I won't keep in touch with that child
I go out with women who are mature
I can't understand that kind of child
I now go with a beauty who is recognized
A recognized beauty?
Natsuko! Katsuya comes back!
Thanks! Makes you tired!
What to do next?
Who is this?
He is Wataru
Wataru?
Wataru, what's up?
What's up? Got sun-stroke?
No, nothing
Natsuko
At this time, Natsuko's pretty shadow
It's so shiny!
See? I didn't lie.
Natsuko has a mature charm
What happened, Wataru?
No, nothing
Isn't it? That's good
You envy me?
I can see Natsuko everyday.
Once is good
I want to make love with Natsuki
Wataru
I'll tell you next time, the process between Natsuko and me
I gotta go now!
He really knows how to enjoy
Kurumi
What's up, Kurumi?
Katsuya... Katsuya...
A woman who is older than Katsuya?
Yes, he hung up suddenly...
I dialed three times, and still can't connect
Can't connect?
Really no method
Kurumi, he goes with the girl in the boutique
No, he won't!
What do I have to do?
Don't worry, Katsuya is busy at the shop only
No!
He invited me several times to the motel, but I refused
So...
What should we do?
You really Katsuya?
Really! Really!
Follow his request, go there once!
Men! Loving one woman requires you to think!
Wataru, you better not teach Kurumi something bad
I haven't said anything
Kurumi, women's precious thing.
don't pay any costs casually
I know, Kurumi won't pay any costs casually.
I grant my heart to Katsuya
Don't be so loud
Sorry
I decided it! But a bit afraid
Wataru, can you help me now?
Me?
Really
Why I must do something for them?
Come on, Kurumi, show your courage
Kurumi?
Yes, she is so serious
Give women's precious thing to me?
It is quite right
Really?
If really so
So I suggest you dating with her
Excellent!
Enter, Kurumi, hurry
We already been to here
Work harder!
Hurry, enter there!
Kurumi!
Wataru!
What happened, Kurumi?
Katsuya went too far
He said he doesn't like me
He doesn't want to see me anymore.
You went out with him recently, right?
Still it isn't okay
I've been to entrance of the motel,
but I was afraid
You ran out, right?
Yes!
What should I do?
Katsuya really hates me a lot!
Don't worry
Men's likeness or not is not superficial
Katsuya that quy!
Saying too excessively!
C'mon! Do whatever you like!
Let me be an adult
How... how could it be?
Please!
Do you want to go to that hotel?
Just joking
Kurumi won't do such thing.
Let's go together
Please!
Hey! Kurumi, please wait
Let's forget it
Dad said
This kind of place is where adults come
From now on,
I have to be an adult
Let's go!
I get it! I understand!
It's really a little different
What's the different?
He is not as gentle as Wataru
Take a rest or stay for the night?
Decide quickly!
Taking rest is fine.
Resting is 1 hour
It looks nice inside
Kurumi
Wataru
Kurumi, you're so cute
What?
Sor... sorry, I don't mean it
Really no solution
Sor... sorry
Kurumi, let's go back!
No! Wataru have to help me to become an adult
But, if we do so...
Otherwise, tie me up will be OK
Although you say so, but there's no rope
Do you need rope?
Even have such thing?
You want rope?
There're golden, silver and common, three kinds
Three kinds?
Which kind would you like?
You can pay the bill when you're back
Since we've be here, let's go wildly, use the golden
I want the golden one
I want the silver
You just left with the common rope
Wataru, tie me with the rope quickly
No! Still not good
You said no now?
Wataru! Be quick!
No!
Then it's OK now!
Kurumi
No!
No! Still not! Stop quickly!
No! I'm afraid!
No! No! Wataru!
If you move carelessly this way, the dress will be wrecked
Kurumi hates Wataru who does such thing
If you detest, you won't come here
But I still can't
Even you say can't, you can't help it now.
So then! I can only...
Don't act so
just as I like, it's what you said
Don't be like that! Release me quickly,
Wataru
No!
It's you who wants me to do so
Don't be self-witted
I'm very self-witted?
Yes! Katsuya also said that
Kurumi, sorry, I don't mean other things
Let's go back, I release the rope for you now
Don't release it!
Don't release it, Wataru
just leave it like that
Please
Wataru
Kurumi
Teach me about the things which is forbidden
Please
No!
Wataru!
You have the feelings?
No!
I? No!
So cute!
Kurumi, you're so sensitive!
Don't say it, OK?
I fell so embarrassing
Even more like a child
Kurumi
Wataru, I like you.
I like you so much
Me too
No! I'm so shy! Stop!
Kurumi, what's the matter?
I don't know, I don't knew even myself!
I just want to be an adult quickly, please.
My body can feel it
I still can't touch the most sensitive place of Kurumi
Wataru, don't just keep saying, touch quickly!
Can't be that
Kurumi, so great!
No, don't come in, but it feels so good
Wataru
I have a strange feeling again, so...
Is it OK, now?
Stop!
Are you OK?
Don't stop! I want to be an adult quickly
Kurumi, I like you
No!
What's wrong? Feel pain?
A little bit, but don't know what will be?
What should I do?
What will I turn to be?
Kurumi's future will be very wonderful
No!
Still like before?
But, it's much greater than before
Kurumi is very afraid
No! No! But it's very comfortable
Help me! Just as I'm torn
Wataru! Wataru!
I don't want it now, don't know which kind of feeling it is.
Doesn't matter
Don't stop! Wataru! Please!
Wataru, here is OK
Kurumi, from now I am an adult
But still a bit as a child
Next time, surely I can do it without tying up
Thank you very much
Kurumi!
Wataru, you listen to me?
I'm totally hopeless.
Natsuko, Natsuko said we just be friends.
Really, the best person is the first consideration
Wataru
What's the matter?
Katsuya, he...
Has called many times
Now it's my turn to joke with him
Kurumi!
Really, I am going.
Wait for me! Kurumi!
Wait for me first!
I don't want to
For me? I feel like cheating someone
Also as being confused.