Endless Serenade
Satsuki!
Can you take over the register, please?
Oh. Is it that time already Yuji?
Uh... uhh...
It's all right, Yuji. Don't be so shy.
Uh... Satsuki!
What is it?
I... I...
Ever since that day my brother
introduced you to me, I...
I've been in love with you!!
Huh?
Miki... Where did Satsuki go?
I don't know.
Hey, Miki! What are you doing!?
Open the door!
If I don't hurry, Satsuki is...
Satsuki, I love you.
I love you more than anything.
Me... Me too...
Huh? You're so wet already.
You were always such a pervert.
But... But... I was so lonely.
Ryoichi, you just left me so suddenly.
That's right! That's what happened...
It's been almost a year. I'm sorry.
Oh yes!! It feels so good, Ryoichi!
Yes, Satsuki! It feels really good!
It's wonderful. All the way... all the
way... I can feel it all the way in me!!
Satsuki, you're amazing! It feels great!
Umm...
What?
If you have something to say, just say it!
Don't I always tell you that at the store?
Yuji? Are you really in love with Satsuki?
Of course I am!! I'm absolutely
in love with Satsuki!!
My name is Yuji Mikage.
I'm a full-time college student, but right now
my job is the most important thing to me.
Oh! Good morning boss!
Don't call me boss in the store.
S-sorry.
Let me introduce him. He's Makoto Amano.
He's an underclassman from the same college.
He's the new guy that's
only been here for a month.
For some odd reason he looks up to me
and calls me boss. He's kind of a goofy kid.
Good morning!!
Hey?
Were you working today?
I'm on my way to school but I was
thinking about getting a bite to eat.
She's Kurumi Kagura.
She started to work here around the same
time as Makoto, so she's a newcomer too.
She's a hard worker but she does things that are
completely unexpected, so it really worries me.
You're late, Yuji!! Late! Late!!
S-sorry!
She's the woman who was in my dream, and
is also the owner of this store. Satsuki Miné.
A year ago my brother died in an auto
accident and she was his fiancée.
Actually, my brother and Satsuki were
supposed to start this store together.
She could have voided the
contract, but she wanted...
... to carry out my brother's
wish, and opened the store.
As I watched Satsuki come to terms with my
brother's death, I became atracted to her.
And as we worked together,
my simple admiration for her...
... slowly but surely, had turned into love.
Thank you very much! Please come again!
Although Satsuki is cheerful
and is the ideal storefront girl...
... her business skills as an
owner were questionable.
So by me taking charge of the entire
background managerial workload...
... the store is somewhat able to stay afloat.
Oh. Morning!
Good morning.
She's Miki Asou, who was also in my dreams.
She is one of the part-timers but...
By the way Miki...
Did you make a checklist for the new products?
The file is in the computer.
Out of all the part-timers,
she's been here the longest...
... so she knows the ropes of the job really well.
As for me, I'd like to get along with her but...
... as a convenience store worker
she has a crucial problem.
What the hell is that attitude!? You
call that customer service!? Eh?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Wha?!? Are you fucking with me!?
Hey, get me the manager!
I want to speak to a manager!
I'm wasting my time with you!
Excuse me. What's the matter?
Is there something wrong?
You have got to be kidding me!
Who does she think she is!?
You call this attitude friendly customer service?
I'm very sorry. Come on!
Apologize to the customer!
I'm really very sorry.
W-we're really sorry!
Yes... She's flawless with the office work but...
... as for customer service, she
was absolutely terrible at it!
She's been working for almost a year but...
... every now and then, she ends
up angering a customer like today.
Cheerfully!
With a happy face!!
Smile! Smile!!
This is not good.
You've been working here for almost a year.
Why can't you do something that's so simple?
I'm sorry.
It's going to affect the store's image.
You can't keep this up.
Anyway be careful, will you?
The biggest mistake you can make is to upset
a customer. You understand that, right?
Yes...
Well, go back to the register for now.
She's a problem...
Yes...
It feels kind of good. I wonder why...
Miki! What are you doing? Why are you?!?
I know it's a dream, but what am I thinking?
Geez! This is what a middle school kid does...
Am I really that horny?
I can't believe I'm having
wet dreams about Miki too...
But why is she in so many of my dreams?
I wish Satsuki would be my girlfriend.
We'd be having sex every day, I
wouldn't have time to have wet dreams.
Hello!
Huh? I thought today was your day off?
Yeah, but I wanted to talk to
Kurumi about something so?
She's taking a break in the back room.
Please excuse me then.
Do you think Makoto and Kurumi are dating?
Huh? Oh, no way.
I don't think Kurumi would
think twice about Makoto.
You really think so? I think he's pretty cute.
No way! He never gets girls!
Wow, Kurumi.
Stop it! The managers are here!
We can't be doing this here.
Don't worry.
It's busy right now so no one will come in.
O-ok.
It smells a little sweaty
because you've been working.
Don't say that!! That's so embarrassing!
But it kind of turns me on too.
Yes. My body... It's getting
hot in there! It feels so good!!
A change of scenery makes
it even more exciting!
It's in me! I can feel your
cock all the way inside!!
Kurumi, you're such a pervert, it's great.
Harder! Harder!
Ok then! How about this!?
Thank you so much!!
I wonder what Kurumi is doing?
There's going to be a wave of customers soon.
You're right. I'll go get her.
Kurumi. We need you to
come to the register soon...
Ah Yuhi! I'ff we vright dhere!
(Ah, Yuji! I'll be right there!)
Thank you very much!
Umm... Please keep it a secret from Satsuki.
How could I tell her something like that!?
Promise you won't do it again!
Ok!
When did you guys start dating?
A-about two weeks ago.
Oh no! Boss, did you have your eye on Kurumi?
No, I didn't. Trust me.
Thank God!
As your devotee, it would've
been horrible of me...
...to steal the boss' girl!
No. I really could have
cared less about Kurumi.
But while I'm dealing with
these miserable emotions...
Thinking that this dumb-looking
kid is living a lovey-dovey life...
... is pissing me off, but it also
makes me feel even more lonely.
Oh Yuji, your cock is hard already.
Satsuki...
Well? Does it feel good?
Yes. It feels really good Satsuki.
It feels really fantastic...
Yes, Yuji. You're doing great.
Satsuki... I...
Go ahead Yuji. I want you in me...
It's in me! You're in me, Yuji!
Oh my God! Oh yes! It's so numbing!
It feels great. You're amazing Satsuki!
More! I want it harder!
Satsuki! Satsuki! I love
you! I'm in love with you!
Me... me too. Yuji, will you
always... always stay by my side?
Of course! Whatever happens, I'll
never let you feel lonely ever again!
Really? You promise?
Satsuki. I can't hold it anymore!
Go ahead. Come in me! Give it to me.
Hello?
Hello. This is Miki.
Oh, it's you.
I was just getting into it too...
What?
Oh nothing.
What's wrong? Did something
happen at the store?
The main office contacted us about
the list of the items on order...
Isn't Satsuki there?
Oh right... She won't be able to do it.
Ok. Can you read it to me?
Uh-huh.
I got it. Anything else?
N-no, that's it.
Umm... Sorry to call when
you're not working. Good bye.
I don't feel like doing it anymore.
It was work related so it can't be helped but...
All we have to do now is send out the letters
to our relatives and figure out who's coming.
Great job, Yuji.
Our parents are gone, so it's my duty to
hold a memorial service for my brother.
I'm here too you know!
Oh... I'm sorry. You're right.
It's great to have Satsuki
around me, but Ryoichi is gone.
I can't make her stay forever.
Satsuki!
Huh?
After this memorial service, please move on.
Satsuki, you're still young, so it's okay if
you want to go do something you enjoy.
I'll figure something out about the store.
Yuji?
Yes?
Are you sure I can do whatever I want?
Yes... It's not my place to stop you so...
Then if it's all right with you, I'd
like to keep working at the store.
Huh?
I really enjoy the job.
Or would you rather I didn't?
Of course not! I wasn't thinking
that! Of course you can!
Really? Yuji, thank you!
Oh yes! Satsuki's going to stay!
As time passes, she'll forget
Ryoichi and fall in love with me!
I...
Y-yes?
I wasn't able to get married to Ryoichi, but
I think of you as my real younger brother.
I was an only child so I was always really lonely.
I was always envious of people who had siblings.
Younger brother?
What's up with Miki? She's going
to karaoke by herself this early?
Ever since I was little I've been shy, and
I've had trouble interacting with people.
But I thought it couldn't stay like
this, and I've tried to overcome it.
I deliberately chose jobs
involving customer service but...
Everywhere I went it didn't go
well and I kept getting fired.
I'm at the end of my rope!
If I get fired from this job...
As is, I'm dealing with self-confidence issues.
I feel like someone who's
completely incompetent socially.
So that's what it was...
Please! I'll work hard so I can
provide better customer service...
Please, don't fire me!
Please!!
Ok.
I don't know how Satsuki
feels, but I'll back you up.
Don't give up and let's work through it together!
Most of your hours overlap with mine,
so if we work together it'll be all right.
Come on, stop crying. It'll be all right!
Y-yes.
I feel so much better after
talking to you about my shyness.
I feel like everything will work
out. Thank you so much.
I didn't know how cute Miki
looked when she smiled.
Satsuki only sees me as her younger brother.
She'll never accept my feelings.
N-no!
Looking back, Miki and I have been
working together for almost a year.
But there weren't any special
emotions between us.
And I've wondered why she
decided to have sex with me...
Miki who has trouble interacting with people.
Maybe she was lonely from
being by herself all the time?
I'm a terrible guy.
I'm taking advantage of her emotional
insecurity to fill my own lonely void.
Yuji... I... I...
But I wonder what this peaceful feeling is?
What is this emotion that
makes her feel so dear to me?
Sympathy perhaps?
A litle sympathy for Miki's sense of courage
to keep trying to reach out to others.
But?
But right now we are...
We are here, spending time together.
And this time is somehow...
Somehow...
S-sorry.
It's all right. I'm not expecting
you to start dating me.
You're in love with Satsuki, right?
I've known that you've been
watching Satsuki the entire time.
The two of you, you share the
memory of your late brother.
There's no one who can come between you two.
So Yuji...
You go win Satsuki's heart and...
...make sure you become a couple!
Miki knew...
... that it was only an act of two lonely
people mending each other's lonely hearts.
And still, Miki forgave me.
By accepting it herself, she forgave me.
So I thought it was absolutely
necessary to tell Satsuki how I felt.
And to repay her efforts for
smiling and wishing me luck.
Miné
Satsuki?
S- Satsuki... wow. She's really into it.
I... I can't anymore!
Ryoichi...
I didn't know! I had no idea!
A year... It's been a year and Satsuki's
feelings for Ryoichi are still that strong!?
That night really hit me hard.
And because of it, I've developed a fever.
I was bedridden, which hasn't
happened in years, and I had to
take off from school and work.
Uh-huh. Yeah...
So that's the deal. Sorry, but if you
can take care of it, I'd appreciate it.
S-sure...
Um... Get well soon.
Uh-huh. Thanks.
Talk to you later.
This past year, Satsuki convenience store
was the most important thing to me.
For my brother's wishes and for
the prosperity of the store...
... everyday I cracked the
whip to my fatigued body.
Perhaps no one else but Miki really
cared for me this entire time?
Although her customer
service was questionable...
... she was the only one
who paid extra atention...
... to the merchandise and
cleanliness of the store.
It's true that I've worked hard up until now...
... because of my feelings for
Satsuki and to be helpful but...
... but without Miki's help, today's
success couldn't have been possible.
Miki... The most important
thing to me could be...
Oh, Yuji!
Good morning.
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
You don't have to push yourself.
Miki will take your night shifts.
Yes... but I can't just lie in bed forever so...
Really? Well, it would be
great to have you here but...
Miki!
You get off at five, right?
I'll be waiting for you at the park.
I wonder what's up with Yuji?
I was such an idiot.
I finally just realized today
who is really important to me.
Yuji...
I love you, Miki.
I want you to always be near me.
Miki...
I... me too...
I've loved you... for so long Yuji.
Yuji.
Miki, I love you.
I love...
...you too.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes...
Miki...
I love you...
Miki... I... I can't...
Oh yes! Yuji, come with me...
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
Nothing at all...