D, damn!
Fucking perv!!!
So you're the one!
You're the rapist on the loose!
What, is he not... human!?
My tongue ish also a vibrator.
S, sto...
Me ish Lividolls best giver.
Does ish feel good?
Stronger...
Weaker...
See, look how turned on you ish are.
Can't be...
I'm being violated, yet I'm turned on.
How embarrassing!
What, already?
I ish just getting started.
Hold it!
Who ish it!?
Spinning and twirling!
I'm here to take your order!
Sex Warrior Pudding
- The Best Order-
Sex Warrior Pudding is a fighting waitress.
Pudding fights to put a smile on your face.
Sex Warrior...
Pudding!
What?
Waitress Excellent...
Flash!!
So, Lividolls are really a doll...
Sex Warriors, eh.
I'll remember that.
Wow, that sounds very dangerous.
But luckily you're safe, Misuzu.
Yeah, but I have a feeling I've seen
those girls somewhere before.
You're thinking too much.
But yeah, I would've never imagine that
you work as a manager at ALamode.
I didn't expect it either...
It never crossed my mind once...
Where am I?
Welcome, to ALamode, Shuta Todoroki.
I mean, Manager!
Huh, manager?
W, what the!!!!!!!!!!?
P, please tell me what this is about!
This is for your welcome and my obedience.
I'm sorry, I am the assistant
manager, Chiyoko Fujiwara.
Here, your dad left you this.
My father?
Wazzup, how you doing Shuta?
Let me make this short.
Your father opened up this restaurant
while doing some research.
So when I'm gone, you're taking care of this place.
Thank you
T, thank you...?
Get the details from Chiyoko, see you later!
Father, Father!
Manager.
This restaurant, ALamode...
Is also the Global Defense Organization!
Global Defense...
The Earth is currently being attacked by the
unknown attackers only known as the Lividolls.
The rapes that's been happening are their doings.
This feels too good...
ALamode was created to counter their attacks.
In orderto get the power to fight against
them, we needed people's smiles.
That's why your father came up with
the idea of running a restaurant.
This story sounds very far-fetched...
Dang, she's speeding the pace up.
I, I'm going to...
C, cum!
Welcome, Manager!
W, what the?
I, I'm really the...
Crap, it's in full view!
I'm Pudding Nishimura, nice to meet you.
Manager.
I'm the Manager?
I never though a guy who likes hentai
games like you would fall for a real girl.
Misuzu, don't call them hentai games, they are...
Bishojyo games!!!
So, what do you like about her?
Her big boobs!?
It's her smile actually.
Not to mention her cuteness.
Manager looks so happy...
He must be very close to her...
Excuse me!
Yes!
What's up?
I'll show you that real girls don't smile
all the time like in-game girls.
How may I help you?
A, are you ok?
Y, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm really sorry, Manager.
No, it's my fault.
Thank you...
This is the smile I'm talking about.
Pudding's Emogauge is up 30%.
Roger.
Have the manager come to the manager's office.
Chiyoko...
Are you sure?
Yes, as a manager, you have the responsibility
to unite the employees by heart and body.
I don't really understand, but...
Why think about it!
T, this feels great.
Hmm, what was that one position that game had...
Let me try!
Good... does it feel good?
Yes, it's good, Manager!
You're so tight, I'm going to... cum...
It's ok... inside... please cum inside!
W, what is that?
Lividolls sighted at the park!
They are attacking the girls!
Everyone, get ready to deploy!
Sex Warriors, ready for service!
Shiet, I forgot!!
Manager, please give the orders.
Confirmed!
Hold it right there!
Who is it!?
Sex Warrior
Pudding!
Jelly!
Panna cotta!
Such a nice view.
What the!?
I want this girl.
Girl, you got nice tits.
Waitress Stick!
Girl, hold it right there!
Girl, if you want to save her
life, put down that weapon.
I'm Lividoll's best massager.
Girl, this is good!
Girl, you put down your weapon.
Now, I'll give you the massage too!
Now it's time to transfer this
pleasure to King Lividoll!
King Lividoll?
Is that the mastermind behind this?
It's not fair!
This pleasure is now being directed to King Lividoll.
Great job, Momi-bot!
Keep up the good work.
I can tell you like it by your nipples.
It feels good...
Oh, Pudding!
Chiyoko, I'm going... I can't stand this!
Yes, please!
Shuta?
Cuming, are you cuming?
Are you alright, Pudding?
No, not again!
Manager!
I won't forgive you now!
Pudding's Emogauge is maxed out!
Manager, Pudding has special
powers that no one else has.
Only you can activate those powers.
Activation code is "Maid Up!"
Maid... Up?
Maid Uuuuhh...
What's wrong, Pudding!?
I don't need your help to beat this guy!
Frame Up!
Heart Mode 1, Power Frame Mode!
Pudding, you're disobeying orders!
Damn, so annoying!!
Pudding, we have to work
together and use Maid Up!
I can do this... myself!
Pudding Dynamic!
Shit, not again!
Pudding!
Why... why didn't you Maid Up?
What was that?
What's going on?
Pudding is the one who saved me?
Stop!
You've passed, Ms. Terai.
I mean, Tiramisu.
Tiramisu?
Why is Misuzu here?
She accidentally saw the fight two days ago.
So I told her our secret and decided to test her.
Misuzu a Sex Warrior?
Pudding!
Manager, looks like things are
working out between you two.
Um... well, I don't know how to put this
but I think she hates me now...
There is a way.
What, what!?
Forced sex!
This isn't going well...
I better talk to Pudding.
Hey, Manager!!!
Serica, aren't you working?
I'm on break now!
Thank you for... saving me... yesterday.
Nako...
Serica, what are you...
What if someone sees?
It's my way of saying thanks.
You don't like it?
I, it's not that...
Great.
Do you not like small ones?
No, no, of course not!
Is this heaven!?
Yes, I know he saved me
But he didn't do anything with me...
I'm so stupid!
I'm always... Smiling!
I better thank him for saving me.
Pudding, um...
What is it.
Well, this is...
Serica is pacing up...
Feels too good...
I'm still working, so!
W, wait up!
I can't hold it anymore!
He won't come after me even when I'm angry...
My latest masterpiece is finally completed...
I will make the Sex Warriors weep!
The combination of Momi-bot and Name-bot
You are MomiName-bot!
I think I saw Pudding heading towards the lockers.
Pudding.
Pudding, it's me.
Misuzu...
Shuta, I mean, Manager.
I look ugly...
No, that's not...
I joined this team not for world peace
but because someone I like is in it.
See... it's beating fast.
I'm not really feminine, right?
No, you are...
W, what am I doing to Misuzu... but I can't stop!
Manager even lays his hands on the new one...
But, what's this I feel...
I feel so down.
I'm wet!?
Why, why am I so excited?
N... no Pudding.
Y, you can't...
But I can't stop!!
Girl, lma squeeze and ish lick.
Girls are being attacked at the park!
Tiramisu, Jelly, Panna cota, save them!
Understood!
Huh, what about me?
You ignored orders last time
so you are on probation.
OK, Manager?
Yeah...
Understood!
Pudding!
Hold it!
Sex Warrior!
Tiramisu, Jelly, Panna cota!
Sex Warriors, all in danger!
Already!?
Pudding...
Everyone is in danger and we need your help.
But! You told me I'm on probation.
It's not a time to say that.
If we don't work together, we won't beat the enemy.
I want you to open up and go help them.
I can't...
I can't... trust you anymore.
If I was a game hero, I would...
Alright, I will.
No, I can't do it...
That hand... it must be from...!?
Pudding... let me be honest.
I... love you!
I would rather have your heart
than saving this planet!
Please open up your heart for me.
Well...
I'm a bad girl, I'm sorry...
No, you're not.
So please... punish... me.
This is punishment!?
Please...
W, well...
You won't punish me still?
Here's your punishment!!!!
Here I go, Pudding.
O, ouch...!
Y, you OK?
Yes, I'm... OK.
So great!
So big...
Feels good...
No, I... l'm going to... cum!
Pudding's Emogauge is to the max!
What!?
I don't know what's going on, but fire away!
Girls, this ish the end of the Sex Warriors ish.
What, what?
What the!?
Wha, what is this?
I'm flying?
This is so embarrassing!
This is the legendary warrior when
two becomes one, super Pudding!
Legendary?
I can't stay like this forever!
Here I go, Lightning Pudding Kick!!
Good job, Pudding!
S, so strong!
This is... the power of love!
Love?
Manager, thank you.
Really...
Pudding...
Stop talking!
Alright, Pudding is...
That's right, Misuzu likes...
Is mine!
D, don't tell me the one you...
It's Pudding.
Wait a...
Damn Sex Warriors!
Not fair, me too!
No, stop it!
The fight for peace and love is not finished!
Fight hard, Pudding! Don't loose, Pudding!
Oh, and you too, Shuta.
Here we go!
The Super Sexy Waitress Bikini Contest!
And here are the competitors!
First up, energetic Cerica Gotou!
Cute smile, Harue Kagami!
Petite and young Nako Kitamori!
And smiling Pudding Nishimura!
Wow, Pudding!
Looks like Pudding is all pumped up.
Lets get ready for the opening ceremony.
Damn her!
Nothing but Pudding, Pudding.
Fools!
Hold it right there!
Hows this beautiful body?
And this sexy bikini.
Now everyone is looking at...
Not me!!!
Pudding Nishimura!
Challenge, I challenge you!
Alright!
Looks like you are up forthe
challenge, so you're welcome in.
We will start off with 100 meter race.
Get ready.
My goal isn't to win against Pudding.
I'll pretend like I'm swimming and take off her top...
Yikes, it's embarrassing!
She doesn't know what's coming up.
Now! H, huh?
The winner is Pudding!
Yikes, this is embarrassing!
Damn, I'll get her next...
Hey... l'm trying to embarrass you
but you keep doing it yourself!!
Why are you such an airhead!
I'm so sorry!
That's it, I need to take this to the next level.
I'll take off her bottoms too.
We are at our last game, Chariot!
Manager, lets do our best!
Will the winners be Pudding's team?
Orthe challenger, Ai Sudo's team!?
Or the others!?
Now!
Pudding!
I'm sorry, my hands slipped.
Heh, you must be too embarrassed to continue now.
Just run away and...!?
I'm not going to loose!
Pudding's cat is rubbing against my head...
Take this!
You wish!
I'm sorry!
Pudding, watch it!
This must be... l'm in heaven...
Oh no, Pudding's team is out of the competition.
The winner is challenger, Ai Sudo!
Wait, Pudding, I'll get you next time!
But you won, silly?
Me name is Fan-bot
Just show me those panties.
Everyone, lets use our Waitress Kick!
OK!
Waitress Kick!!!
I can see your panties!
[Fan-bot powers up]
Counter Waitress Kick Attack!
Waitress Kick doesn't work!?
You can still stand after my counter attack?
Looks like this girl can't.
Here I go!
Nako!
Shit!
Chiyoko, Nako's in...!
Yes, please deploy Manager!
If you come any closer, she will die.
Dirty!
You got cute tits.
Just the way I like it.
Stop...
Me pinching and pinching.
This is... whew, it's wet, really wet.
Me stroking and stroking.
The slut is liking it.
D, damn it!
What to...!?
Why stop me, you can see she's really liking it.
Me opened and opened!
So embarrassing... I never showed it to anyone...
Alright, time to make you cry!
Huh, it's so tight I can't stick it in!
Hmm, this guy...
Powers up the Sex Warrior...
[Power Up!] [Might loose] [Not that!]
See you!
Wait up!
That's a smart Lividoll.
Manager...
N, Nako?
W, what, um... well...
Nako...
I better go home...
I, I'm sorry, I didn't mean to come in while changing.
I was just worried because you
were in here for a long time.
It's been a while since the store close...
has he stayed here this last for me?
Sorry, I'll head back.
Don't go...
Na, Nako?
The Kimono... looks great on you.
I'm from an lkebana family.
My parents always has been strict with manners.
So I always held in my feelings.
But after I started working here... after
I met you, I became more open.
Then, don't think too hard about today.
Smile big and forget about it, OK?
Oh, I thought of something funny.
Um, would you please hold this?
OK, here I go.
O, OK...
Is it... not funny?
No, it's funny, but I meant for you to smile.
I'm not good at smiling, so
I want you to smile for me.
That's why I want you to be my first...
N, no panties!?
Um, well, but...
I know that you like Pudding...
But just for now, please!
Na, Na, Na, Nako?
N, no, it feels to good...
No, I can't hold it...!
I, I, I, I... I can'...
Hold it much longer!
Na, Na, Na, Nako, here I go...
Yes...
Nako, you still here?
If you don't leave soon, you'll miss the train.
Huh, I though I felt a presence in here.
Maybe I'm thinking too much.
Hurts... it hurts, but I'm hot.
My body is on fire...
Inside, it's inside Nako.
What have I done?
Damn, this isn't good at all.
I better get back to work.
Phew, I'm safe.
Just kidding!
This is, well, how should I explain this...
You are such a pervert, Manager.
Sorry to bother you.
Pudding!
Sorry Nako.
Wait, Pudding!
Not going to!
Sorry, it's my fault.
You don't need to apologize...
I'm not angry... I mean we're not a couple...
Not a couple? But I...
...elieve you...
I don't believe that you love me...
And also... it's peeping out!
Pudding...
Manager... what are you...?
I'll prove it.
No, we need to... stop now...
Stop, please stop, Manager...
You really want me to stop?
It's really wet down here.
This is how I feel about you!
I love you so much that I want
to do this with you all the time!
So warm... Pudding is so warm inside.
M, Manager, not so rough...
No, I love you Pudding!
I'm going to show you how much I love you!
N, no, Manager, not so rough...
what... what's this new feeling?
Na, Nako, you...
I'm sorry Pudding... I seduced Manager.
Manager cheered me up while I was feeling down.
But I felt really safe in his arms...
Manager... please have it your way.
Alright, you first Pudding!
My head is so blank...
Next, Nako!
I never seen Nako so happy...
Pu, Pudding, if, if you...
Nako, you're going to make me...
Inside... give it to me inside... inside!!!
So you're here, Sex Warriors!
Show me your panties again!
Assistant Manager, Nako's Emogauge is to the max!
Manager, have Ms. Kitamori Maid Up!
Maid!!
The Maid Up can only be done
when two becomes ones and Nako is...!?
Up!!!!!
Weakness Scan!
Found it! Fan-bot, your weakness is...
This!
Damn...
And peace was protected once again.
Thanks Sex Warriors, Fight Sex Warriors!
Damn, my poor little Lividoll.
I'll get you next time!
Hello, come on in.
So what do you think of my store?
Who are you?
Ai, Ai Sudo! Remember it, damn it!
A, anyway, we are each other's competitors now.
Although, at this rate, I think
your place will go bankrupt.
Bankrupt?
ALamode?
That's ridiculous!
We're going bankrupt...
On top of that, if we don't get any customers...
No customer means, no Emoenergy, which
also means Sex Warriors would be powerless.
We need to find a way to solve resolve this.
Think we're OK?
I think we should cuddle more to look like a couple.
Manager, I'm only doing this
because it's undercover, OK?
T, this was a surprise, Manager.
Yeah...
Sorry for the wait, I am Betty... here.
N, no, l"m quite fine right now...
Give me a chance.
Pu, Pudding?
How do you like our service, Shuta?
Ai!?
How did you know!?
How could I not know it wasn't you.
Here, special ice cream on the house.
Looks delicious.
Manager, don't... I need to stop him, but...
I can't move!
Well, here I go.
Manager is such a pervert!
She's jealous, very jealous.
Feels great... now to finish it off.
Here's your main dish.
Pudding's here, I can' do this...
And something is very strange
of this 'customer service.'
Manager, don't!
When did you... why?
See, look at Pudding enjoying herself.
B, but!
It feels good...
Come...
Here I go!!
Manager, no...!
Warm, so warm...!
So deep!
I... I... I
No, cuming... cuming!!!
Dear King, hurry...
Tell me where you want it?
Say it.
Dear King, please stick your big thing in here...
You're such a slut.
So big...
F, feels so good...
So, how are the plans?
Did you find out their weakness?
N, no, not yet, but...
Shuta Todoroki is under my control.
What!? I had sex with Ai!?
Is this true, Pudding!?
Yes, but I don't remember much about it...
I think I was part of it too...
You!!!!
What were you doing!?
[Summersault]
You piece of shit!
[Fatality]
Stop it, Misuzu!
Don't blame Manager so much.
I mean, I was part of it too...
That's how powerful Trifle was.
So, please... don't blame him... please...
H, huh, what's wrong...?
Pudding's feeling down...
It's my fault... because of me, Pudding is...
Chiyoko, what are you?
There's something I need to check.
Chiyoko, what's this about!?
I thought I smelled something strange from
you when you came back from Trifle.
I'm sure I'll find something with your sperm.
So please, release every single drop.
I... I can't...!
T, this is!?
Huh, w, what!?
I don't know.
Well, I'll have the research
department check on this sample.
Thank you very much.
Yes?
Hello, Shuta.
Aren't you coming today?
I'm so lonely.
Ai?
I'm very wet right now.
See, can you hear that?
You said you'll come.
Lets have fun together.
I want your big thing, Shuta!
Ai... Ai!!!!!
Putting Shuta aside, we have to think of something.
Pudding, did you notice anything at Trifle?
Hmmm, we had sex?
Hey, where is Shuta?
Huh, I haven't seen him.
So good, but if this continues...
Crap, I'm at her pace again...
B, but otherwise, I won't be able
to find out Trifle's secret...
Don't cum yet.
You have to unload inside...
Hey Shuta... does it feel good to you too?
Y, yeah...
Feels damn good.
So happy... more, give me more, Shuta.
L, like this?
C, crap, I'm falling into the trap.
Hey, Shuta...
You lead the Sex Warriors, correct? Shuta.
W, what are you saying?
Don't play dumb, we all know.
We even know Pudding is a Sex Warrior.
C"mon Shuta, tell me their secret.
I... I can't.
I don't know!
Even if I did, I won't tell you!
Strange, my mind control isn't working?
Really?
Hey Shuta, don't you love me?
Y, yeah...
Ai, I just discovered your secret!
You're controlling people with that brooch!
I won't fall for it anymore!
I have Pudding with me!
What, the perfume isn't working!?
And it's getting bigger!
The reason is this!
Pudding's panties!
Now I'm fine!
I won't fall for it anymore!
No, not so...!
You're making me... cum... cum...
Cuming!
I lost again!
Damn, so close!
What's wrong, Pudding?
So embarrassing!
And peace was saved again.
Thank you, Sex Warriors.
Fight, Sex Warriors!
This is...?
You're finally awake, Shuta Todoroki.
My name is King Lividoll, the
leader of Lividoll Kingdom.
King Lividoll, why are you doing this!?
That's a silly questions.
I do as what the libido says.
A lust that is kept inside every living thing.
That is the Libido.
And...?
Yes, it is within you too... no, you hold
one greater than an average person.
You are the same as me.
Nonsense, I'm nothing like you!
Oh really?
This is my favorite game, "Dokidoki Memory Club."
Shi... Shiorin?
I wanted to see you.
W, what, the tongue!?
Has to be a trap... but so soft...
Shiorin, the game character, now real...
Feels good... but this is King Lividoll's trap!
Um, it's embarrassing... but I'll lick you, Shu-chan.
Shu, Shu, Shu, Shu-chan!?
Let me explain.
Level 1, Mr. Todoroki.
Level 2, Shuta.
Level 3, Shu-chan.
Higher the level, the more
closer you get with the girl!
Shu-chan... it's big.
Crap... cuming, I'm going to... cum...
Feels so good!
Maaaaanaaaaageeeeer!
Whaat aare yoou dooing...
That's... the legendary Black Pudding!
Legendary?
Although smiling, Black Pudding is the very opposite
of Pudding, her powers are from the dark side!
This Shiorin has an self-destruc mechanism...
Aslight movement and
Shuta's manhood will be gone.
Pudding, I don't care what happens to me!
Destroy the Livedoll!
Manager, I know...
I already know!
Welcome!
OK, so your order is...
What was that dream about...
Pudding... can't be.
Harue?
Sorry, I'm so sorry, I...
So, sorry, I didn't mean to surprise you...
Harue, I though it was your day off?
Yes, but I wanted to create a new
menu to keep the customers happy.
I want it ready before the festival.
New menu?
She's thinking about the store more than me,
Manager...!
It's a shape of a breast...
I thought of something great!
Tell me and I'll make it!
After all, I'm clumsy... and not cute...
I want to be good with at least one thing!
Don't say that, you're very cute Harue.
Manager, you're so kind...
My dream is to be a bride one day.
I have a feeling your future bride is a happy one.
Harue being my wife...
Welcome home, Honey.
Manager, I'll do anything so please tell me!
Let me make your new menu!
Are you really sure?
Yes...
It's embarrassing, but I'll do my best.
i did as you said, Manager.
Alright, keep still until the silicon dries.
OK, but... can you please come here and check?
What's wrong, Harue?
It feels weird, can you rub my back?
A, alright...
I will.
Like this?
Um, little bit lower...
Lower?
No... lower...
Here?
Yes, right there... thank you.
Please don't stop.
OK...
Feels good...
I heard you're different than
other men, I can see why.
Your hand is very warm and it's comfortable.
Really? Thanks...
Can you rub me more... a bit lower?
Harue... here?
S, she's wet...
Damn!
Manger... l... more...
More... does she mean...!?
I think the it's dried now.
U, um, I can't do this alone.
Can you help?
O, OK...
H, here I go.
OK...
H, huh, it's stuck...
Watch out, Manager!
I'm glad you're safe, Manager...
Harue!
Manager!?
Manager... we're...
I, It feels...!
It's... my first time... but, but...
Amazing, so amazing, but...
It's also embarrassing!!
More, more, give me more!
I am really... truly a slut!
This feels so great... great!!
Cuming... cuming... cuming!!!!!
It's finally done.
Tad-ah, breast-shaped pudding!
Manager and Harue looks happy together...
Pudding?
Pudding, I'm here.
It's me... where are you?
Oh, Pudding.
What's wrong, why you bring me here?
Manager! Well, um, err...
Stupid me, I can't ask about Harue...
Danger, Pudding's Emogauge
is hitting the negatives!
What!!?
That means!
I wonder what?
Um, my Mom...
My mom knows you live alone... so she
wants you to invite you for a dinner...
W, what, your house!?
Yeah, I'll go, I will! I won't miss it!
I'm home.
Manager, please come in.
Finally here... but nervous...
Huh, where is Mom?
She should be home...
Welcome!!
O, oh my?
Hey, what are you doing!?
Sorry, I was trying to surprise him.
My bad, my bad.
W, who is this person...
Sorry, I was just trying to be cute.
Thank you for taking care of Pudding.
N, nice to meet you.
Sheesh, Mom... that was embarrassing.
I'm really sorry
Same hairstyle, same face...
Y, you girls look alike.
Pudding you look like your mom...
Oh, I'm not that young!
Mom, no one said anything about being young!
Oh my, clumsy me.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
I made a lot so eat up!
Mom, shesh.
Let me feed it to you, Shuta.
Say Ahhh
H, hey hey, Mom.
Woops, forgot he's yours, not mine.
Uh... well, it's not like... that...
I didn't think I would spend the
night here... now I'm really nervous.
I'm coming in, Manager!
W, wait up... l'm not ready for this...
I thought it was the mom, but since she
said Manager, must be Pudding?
Stop it, Manager!
It's embarrassing so stop staring!
Let me help you wash your body.
O, OK... thanks.
He's so cute when he's nervous.
How is it, Manager?
O, OK...
Pudding, how can you not
lay your hands on him yet.
Alright, Mama's going to help you out.
Great, it's relaxing.
Woops, I'm really sorry!
Pu, Pudding!?
Wow, he's really hard... and really big!
Does it feel good?
W, was Pudding always this bold?
Oh, let me make you feel better!
It's Pudding's... Pudding's...!!
Manager, yours is... so big.
D, damn! Pudding has my thing in her... in her...!
S, such great tongue technique!
Pudding is... Pudding is so...!
I, I can't hold it... l'm going too...
Cum!
Not yet, lets take it slow!
Manager, lets continue in my room.
Pudding told me to come, but...
Now that I'm here, I'm really nervous...
But she did invite me...
I have to do this!
Pudding, it's me.
Pudding, are you here...!?
Erotic lightning... see-thru nighties...
An exotic bed...
She's...
Expecting me in bed!!
Mission is a success!
You are the same as me.
I'm stupid... I know Pudding invite me...
But if I continue, I'll be the same as a Lividoll.
I'm sorry, Pudding...
huh, what!?
My plan to get them closer isn't working!?
Manager...
Eh, Pudding?
Why are you leaving?
I'm so lonely...
But... but...
Manager, I want your hard thing...
But I though you were sleeping so...
No, I was embarrassed, that's all.
Come...
Are you sure?
Yes...
Huh?
Your nighties look different.
Uh, well, I changed into this one because
I thought you would like it better.
You don't like?
N, no, it's not that.
Fine, I'll take it off
Pu, Pu, Pu... Pudding!!!
Don't be so hastey, Manager.
Pudding, I'll get him ready and swap when he is.
So needy!
Ma, Manager, lets take it slowly...
S, she's using her breasts!?
Was Pudding always this bold?
G, great!
E, even her mouth!
C, cum... cuming!!
Wait, not yet.
Explore inside me...
A, alright, here I go!
It's deep, deep inside me!!!!
Manager, you're so big!!
More, more, more!
Fill up inside me!
Cuming, cuming...
Huh, Manager, why you here?
Two Pudding!? What the?
Oh, we must be having sex.
I see.
Good night.
I'm the mother!
So that means it was you in the bath too...?
Yes, I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help Pudding.
I was going to swap, but it felt good.
So I kinda forgot.
What to do, Pudding saw me...
You say that, but looks like you're hard again.
But still...
Don't worry, Pudding won't remember a thing.
So why don't we... have some fun!
Great, it's big!
Good morning, last night I...
Had a really kinky dream!
Everyone should be here soon.
And it looks like people are ready for festivity.
Yeah, want to take a break?
Yes!
Would sure like to enjoy the fun.
No, everyone can see...
I don't mind, besides it's more of a turn on.
No there!
Eh, um, well...
Pudding...
I was really lonely...
I was worried you did something to Harue.
Or maybe even with my Mom...
It all happened... but I can't say that.
Tell me one thing!
Do you really care and have love for me?
Of course, you're the only one!
Really?
Of course, I'm speaking the truth.
Then have me anyway you want...
I, I must've fallen asleep!
Looks like you guys had fun.
Manager, wake up, please wake up!
Harue, you're breasts feel good...
Mom, Mom, don't lick there...
Manager... Manager... I hate you!!
Manager doesn't really love me!
Huh, what's going on?
Misuzu?
White panties...
Shuta, I have always...
Hated you!!!
How dare you make Pudding cry!
Alright, lets get ready!
Lets forget about this idiot and lets get ready!
Manager.
Are you hurt?
Nako, Harue...
but sorry.
I'm sorry, Pudding... very sorry!
I need Pudding...
I can't do without!
Pudding!
Pudding, lets go home... everyone's waiting.
Pudding is Black Pudding!
Let me explain again.
When Pudding's negative emotions reaches
to the max, she becomes Black Pudding.
What do you want?
You are the same as me...
I'm sorry, Pudding!
But I'm not lying about my feelings for you!
I know it'll be hard to forgive me, but!
You said I am the most important person.
Yes, I did!
I'm not lying, you are the most important.
Even if I do this?
Yes, of course.
I see...
Still?
Yeah...
Not yeah, it's yes!
Y, yes...
Fine, prove it to me then.
If you make me orgasm, I'll forgive you.
Make Pudding orga...
That's such great... I mean... Y, yeah, err... Yes!
Alright.
Takashi, it's great...
Me too, Chiko.
Monster!!
Damn it, it felt so good my disguise came off!
Oh well, hold still!
Hold it!
Sexy Warrior Jelly!
Parfait, Panna cota, Tiramisu!
Don't bother me!
Dang, he's strong!
We need help...
Good, good... tighten them up more...
Alright, looks like Pudding is starting to feel good.
Manager, Lividolls are on the attack!
Where are you, please come, can you hear me!?
Manager!
I'm sorry, but right now is not the time!
What!? Manager, Manag...
I know Lividolls need to be destroyed
but I must show Pudding my love!
I'm sorry, everyone...
What's wrong...
You think you can make me orgasm this way...?
D, damn... but she is getting very wet.
Hmm, Pudding's blackness
seems to be fading away?
W, what, Pudding forcing herself on me!?
Ohh... D, damn it!
I'm going to cum before she does...
Feels too good!
C'mon, what's wrong, start pumping!
Y, yeah, I mean yes!
It's deep inside!
This is so great!
Make me go wild, stir it inside me!
I can't... take this!
Great, great, great!
I'm cuming. cuming...
Me too, I can't take this... going to cum!
This is the Pudding Cutter!
So justice does win.
Justice?
Shit, not again!
Pudding, I'm sorry...
And this is how the Sex Warriors won.
However, the real battle is just beginning.
Along with the battle of love.
Don't loose Pudding, do you best, Pudding!
And you too, Shuta.