Haitoku no Shoujo 2
We're home!
Welcome back.
Would you like dinner first?
Or take a shower?
Or start, start your studies?
Ms. Hiroko, you're terribly sensitive today.
Oh Shizuka, I can't wait!
P...  Please!
Oh, let's see...
give me!
I want Yuki...
I can't wait anymore!
Oh Shizuka!
I want Hiroko, too..
Oh, I was thinking of doing
something different today.
What should I do...
Shizuka what are you...
I'll change my plans, I'll have you
and Ms. Hiroko connected together...
I like this Shizuka.
Oh my god, yes!
Yes. Yes More!
Harder, Yuki. Faster!
Watching you and Ms. Hiroko is starting
to make me really wet down here.
Yeah!
W..Wait!
Yes!
Yes, yes, Ms. Hiroko, more!
Coming!
Oh Ms. Hiroko,
I'm about to come hard, too!
I'm coming now!
When did this strange relationship begin...?
Yes, it all started
when I met these sisters...
Please!
Pretty please!
I don't know if I can do it, Rika.
This is really short notice!
I'm desperate now, please!
Pretty, pretty please with sugar on top!
So what will I be doing?
Private tutoring.
Private tutoring?
For a daughter of a really wealthy family.
And, you're always complaining
about lack of money!
This pays really well, too...
I can't believe I agreed to do this...
It really sucks being broke!
I suppose complaining now is pointless...
Hello, are you the tutor?
I'm here to interview for the position.
Wow... what a mansion!
Hello, my name is Shizuka.
I'm yuki.
Ms. Hiroko, we would love to
have you tutor Yuki.
Oh no, thank you,
the pleasure is all mine, really!
I never would have imagined
at this point that...
...these two would be
hiding such a big secret...
Is this correct?
Well, let's see.
You see, if you just concentrate,
you can do it!
It's because you're such a good tutor!
Really, you think so? Thank you!
Now, to the next problem...
All right...
Oh, are you OK, Yuki?
uh, may I go to the bathroom?
Oh, I'm sorry!
Of course.
Ms. Hiroko. would you like some tea?
Great, we were just about to take a break!
Here, Ms. Hiroko.
Thank you.
It must be lonely being by yourselves at
home during your father's business trips.
Don't you get lonely?
Oh no, since I have Yuki here.
We also have you here as well, now.
Oh Hiroko...
Ms. Hiroko!
I want you so bad. Ms. Hiroko.
So how is Yuki doing so far?
She's doing great,
she's catching on really fast!
I'm sure Yuki will be pleased to hear that.
But I'm kind of worried about her,
you know...
I wonder if I need to slow down some,
she seems really nervous.
Oh no, I think that's
because Yuki really likes you.
I'm glad she likes me as her tutor...
You are an very attractive woman.
I think Yuki likes you a lot.
What do you...
I find you very attractive as well...
Stop Shizuka.
This isn't funny...
I'm very serious, Ms. Hiroko.
I think Yuki can't wait any more, either...
What the...!
What is going on!
We've been waiting for you
to wake up, Ms. Hiroko!
Shizuka, untie my hands right now!
Please stop fooling around, and untie me!
This is no joke, right, Yuki?
Ms. Hiroko, Yuki would like to
ask you something.
Go Yuki, ask her!
I'll do what you want Yuki,
just untie me right now!
Really?
You'll do what I ask?
I promise, okay, so Yuki, please!
Ms. Hiroko.
I really, really like you a lot...
Will you please...
let me...
You're a boy?!
Yes, that's correct, Ms. Hiroko.
I want you to take your time...
...to teach my lovely brother something
with your lovely, luscious body...
This is crazy!
How is it, Yuki?
Yes, Ms. Hiroko's breasts
are so soft and bouncy!
We need to have Ms. Hiroko
enjoy herself as well!
No! No!
Stop it!
Please stop!
Oh no!
Your pussy doesn't seem to mind!
No, not there, stop!
Ms. Hiroko, I'm...
I'm comming!
Honestly, Ms. Hiroko. you really
enjoyed this, I know you did.
Wait, I...
I didn't...
Enjoy...
You don't have to deny it.
Your body doesn't lie, you know.
You're wrong...
Ms. Hiroko see...
Apparently Yuki isn't quite satisfied yet...
See, he's already getting hard as a rock!
You'll learn to like this, I promise.
...promis...
...Ms...
...Hiroko.
Yuki, now is your chance
to really enjoy her!
Don't! No!
Ms. Hiroko!
God!
Your pussy...
You're soaking wet here all over again!
Wait... not yet...
Don't stop!
See, I told you.
I knew you would like this.
More, More!
Your pussy feels great!
Oh yeah...
Right there, don't stop please!
I'm going to...
...Join you two.
Oh my god!
This is the best!
I'm coming!
Jesus!
Ms. Hiroko!
No.
I'm coming!
Oh god, right there!
I'm coming...
I'm going to come!
Oh god,I'm coming!
Yes, Yes, Oh god, god!
What did you think?
Did you like it, Yuki?
Yes!
I'm not satisfied yet.
Yuki.
Shizuka!
I'm glad you enjoyed it as much as we did!
So good!
This is how I came to be their sex toy.
And now, this...
I'm back!
I'm home!
Welcome back, my master.
The kids are at it again...
Welcome back, dad!
Were you good, Yuki?
Yes!
You're back earlier than expected!
I finished my business early,
but who is she?
This is out brand new toy.
Do you like her, father?
Her name is Ms. Hiroko,
and she's my very favourite!
Well, I'm happy for you.
Just don't break her
like you did the last one.
Sure!
Yuki, do you promise not to break her
like the last one you had?
Promise!
I was planning to play with her soon.
You'll join us. won't you, please, father?
Yuki don't be selfish,
he's probably very tired from his trip.
Actually...
I think I will join you.
Really? Hurray!
In that case, I'd like to join in, as well.
All right, we'll all play with her together.
Great!
Wow!