Did you hear that the man here
got a new wife again?
I heard it's his fourth already.
My, he goes through them quickly.
But I heard that he had to go
on an extended business trip.
She must be pretty lonely.
I wouldn't be able to stand such lonliess.
Neither would I.
IMMORAL GIRLS
RAISING A PET STEPMATHER
Hello. This is the Saegusa residence. Who is it?
It's me.
Oh, hello Father. How are you doing?
Well, It looks like it will be a year
before I can come home.
I see. That's a shame.
I don't mind much, but Yuuki was really
looking forward to seeing you.
I'm sorry.
By the way, how are you girls doing with Yoshie?
There's nothing to worry about, Father.
Our new stepmother has been
extremely kind to us.
That sounds good. I'm relieved.
Giddyup, giddyup!
Yuuki really seems to like her.
She plays with her everyday.
There, come on! Come on!
Can I talk to Yoshie now?
OK, please hold on for a moment.
Mother, it seems Father wants to hear your cries.
Hey, Shizuka, what's going on?
Yoshie? Yoshie?
Sister, Mother looks a bit uncomfortable.
Oh my, I'm sorry. You can't talk
with that thing on, can you?
Dear.
Father, sorry. Mother seems to be out right now.
Yes. Yes, I understand.
Well, good luck with your work.
Such a shame. It was a great
chance for you to get help.
Please forgive me! I promise I won't
do anything like that again. Please!
But these... You set me up!
But you betrayed father and us
by sleeping with a young man.
That is unforgivable. Right, Yuuki?
Yup. When you do something naughty,
you should be punished, Mother.
You promised to be our toy, our
pet, if we don't tell Father.
Isn't that right?
M O T H E R?
It's dinner time. Go ahead, eat.
No way. I don't want to eat that.
Since you haven't eaten for three days,
your body is saying otherwise.
And, I think you're making a mistake.
You're our dog now, So you should
reply with  "Woof Voof".
Do you understand?
Please... Please stop!
So, what is your reply, Mother? Or
should we tell Father about you?
I can't hear at all.
Come on. Clearer... and louder.
That's a good girl.
Now you may eat.
Hey wait, sister.
What is it?
Don't dogs have to do something before they eat?
You know, a trick, like standing up.
I suppose so... Perhaps we should
make her do something.
Mother, how about standing
up like a dog and barking?
Your reply?
Wow. She really did it.
Good. Now you may eat.
After eating, I guess it's time for a walk.
Giddiyup! Giddiyup!
Huh? She isn't moving anymore.
What are you doing?
Come on, we're going.
It seems like the drug I mixed
into the food is working.
What happened, sis?
Mother seems to want to go to the bathroom.
You don't have to hold it in here.
You're a dog, so go ahead.
I don't want to...
Come on. Bess and Ricky want
you to hurry up as well.
I understand. If you can't do it yourself we'll help.
Of course. After all, we are family.
My, my. You're trying so hard to hold it in.
No, please no!
Perhaps we should loosen it up for you.
Yup.
No, please, no.
No! No!
Wow. She's completely flooded.
It's a sign that Mother is getting excited.
See? Take a look.
No! Please! Not there!
No! No!
No...
Only â little more.
No! Please stop!
Mother's breasts are so soft. It feels good.
No, please, Yuuki-san.
No!
NO! Please! It's coming out!
No! It's coming back into me!
It seems she is about done.
My, my. It must have felt so good.
Mother, are you OK?
Let's see how tilings are down here.
No! Stop! Don't pull it out! I beg you!
I can't... hold it... in... It's coming out!
Holding it in isn't good for your body... Mother.
No!
Would you please clean it, with your tongue?
Yes, like that. You are becoming obedient at last.
Here you go, sister.
Now, as a reward for your obedience, we
shall make you feel even better, Mother.
No... Please stop.
Now, we ñàï let the dogs have
fun among themselves.
Bess! Ricky!
Here, this part tastes the best. Eat plenty.
No! Not there!
OK, go ahead.
No, no! Not there!
Huh? Sister, there seems to be
something wrong with Bess.
My, these boys want more.
But holding back is bad for your health, right?
You're right. Well, then.
No! Please! Anything but that!
So, Bess, you're older so you can start. Go ahead.
Well done. You're a good dog, Bess.
Well then. I guess it's Ricky's turn now.
My, Ricky must really like Mother.
Bess is saying he wants to do it again.
Yuuki. what is this? Your cute
little dick became this large?
Oh, this? I'm pretty excited.
Huh? Sister? What happenned to Mother?
Mother, what is wrong?
My, my. It appears that she finally broke down.
What shall we do, sister?
Seems like we have no choice.
I guess we'll have them take care of her.
Hello, we would like you to take our toy.
Yes. Yes.
This new toy was plenty of fun.
Well, thank you.
Seems like they will ñome pick her up soon.
That's good.
That's good, isn't it, Mother?
This.. This is it! A human's... a man's cock!!
This is what I wanted!
Wow, this is great.
Lîîê at her hip movement.
Great fuck!
Use your tongue.
Not... done... yet... More...
This, this.. I'm coming!!!!
More... Give me more...
Mother seems to be doing fine.
Former. Former mother, Yuuki.
Oh yeah, you're right.
Anyway, isn't the new toy coming yet?
She should arrive very soon.
It seems she has arrived.
Now let's go pick up our new toy, Yuuki.
Yes, sister.