l love it,,,,l can feel your cock
pulsing hard inside me!
l'm burning up!
Mr, Daina!
Stop! Get away!
You bitch!
l'll never, l'll absolutely never
become your slave!
Good-- you're getting pissed again!
All right, l'll give you a special treat,
Mayu,
No, no,,,get away from me!
No, get away,,,Daina, Help!
Five Card 4
Nobody's going to hear you,
Stoooop!
Can't you be still!
Mr, Daina,,,l'm cumming,
l'm cumming again!
Naoki!
Coming,,,coming!
l'm going to cum, too Naoki!
Mr, Daina!
Daina!
l ,,,,l can't even see straight anymore!
I am so happy!
Onikuma!
Gotta get out of here!
Can't reach it,,,where are you Daina!
Giving love can be a lot of work!
That damned Onikuma!
He's been using energy drinks
to fuel his endurance!
Mr, Daina!
Where were you, Lisa?
Mr, Nariyuki!
-Oh, l,,,l,,,
-You don't have to tell me,,,
l back to have a taste!
-But today l didn't make you lunch,,,,
-No, not lunch!
Huh?
We need to finish what we started!
Finish what we started?
l've come to taste your secret ingredient!
Mr, Daina,,,
You know, l am no longer a virgin
like l was before,,,,
So, well, uh,,,
There's nothing to worry about!
As long as you are a virgin at heart, right?
Don't worry, you're still very beautiful,
Lisa, you taste so good!
Now l know why your lunch
always taste so good!
Mr, Daina, will you please let me,,,
taste you?
Where did you learn this!
l practised at home,
With your sausages and
eggplants and carrots?
Yes,,, I even practised with corn!
Why use corn???
Oh my god!
Mr, Daina, you're completely
filling me up inside!
l'm basting your jumbo sausage
so it tastes like my secret ingredient!
So Good!
l should pay special attention
to these cute testicles as well!
Oh Mr, Daina, your testicles
seem to be getting firmer!
They're happy because
you're paying attention to them!
l'll keep paying attention to them!
These energy drinks work well!
I'd bet Onikuma's using something much,
much stronger for his targets!
You're supposed to make women happy,
not drug them!
Lisa, I'm going to try to help you
make you forget those awful memories,,,
with my,,,my piston of love!
Mr, Daina! Daina! Daina!
Daina!
Lisa!
Mr, Daina, you've made me so happy!
Oh god,,,what's happening to you!
This drug wasn't meant for me!
That's none of my problem, bastard!
No, No!
Now it's time,
Noooo!
You'll pay, you'll pay for this!
You're going to take some, too!
lt should work extraordinarily well!
As a teacher you should be
setting examples,,,
not hanging there with your stiff nipples
when l haven't even touched them!
Your pussy is getting so wet and juicy that
you're making the a puddle on the floor!
Well well,,,now, what happened
to your hateful attitude!
So l was right, you whore!
l'll make sure l'll break you well enough for
you to become my perfect personal slave!
Guess who!
Hey Fumiko!
What the hell do you think,,,!
Fucker, take this!
Cry,
Mr, Daina!
Just as l thought!
You stalk around campus pretending
to be so strong and tough, but in reality,,,
you are a sensitive sweetheart,,,
with large, sensitive breasts,
Whatever,,,what the hell do you want!
l don't want anything at all!
l just want to give,
What's wrong?
You usually get pissed when l joke around!
Mr, Daina, l,,,,
l know,
Cumming!
What's next, what do you want me to do
with this now, Mayu??
l'm not going to guess here,
You'll need to speak up!
Do me from the back,,,,
l said you need to speak up!
Do me from the back!
You've got it wrong, Mayu,
Hurry, please, l want it, want it!
You want me to stuff
your cute asshole, right?
lf you don't say it
you're not going to get it,
Please,
Go on!
Stuff me, please!
Please put it inside my asshole!
One more ''please'',
Please, please!
So you want it in the ass that bad,,,
What do you want stuffed
in your asshole, Ms, Misomi?
-That!!
-That?
What is ''that''?
Please don't stop!
Then say it out loud,,,
tell me what does my slave want
stuffed in her cute little asshole!
C,,,C,,,Cock!
No, l can't take it!
You're something!
This is a good position,,,,
Beautiful women have the right
to be completely happy,
More, more!
Hurting my queens like he did!
Onikuma, bastard, I will never forgive you!
Like that, Like that!
Fumiko, all you need to do
is receive my love!
Good,,,good!
Mr, Daina, you've made me happy,
Tight, you asshole is so tight, Mayu!
Coming, coming, coming!
All right, slave, where next?
Where do you want stuffed now?
Hurry and say it!
You know,,,
No, l don't,
Where is it?
Come on, please!
You're not getting it until you tell me!
Tell me where you want me
to fuck you with my hard, thick, cock!
You're going to look at my face and
tell me exactly where you want my cock!
P,,,p,,,, pussy,
Onikuma,,, you have something else
coming, you bastard!
Even l don't do too well after having sex
for two days nonstop with very little sleep!
But l need to keep moving forward,
have to revenge for my beautiful queens!
Stop!
Noooo!
Once more, please,
Stop!
Noooo!
l've didn't notice until now,
but l haven't seen Mayu today at all,,,
l really don't like Mr, Onikuma,
The way he undresses me with his eyes,,,
it totally creeps me out!
Oh shit!
-Here Mayu, you like it like that, huh?
-Yes, Yeeeees!
How come your pussy is tighter
than your asshole, huh?
You've got something here!
Oh no! That! That means,,,,
l can't hold it anymore!
l'm going to dump a load all over you!
Mayu Misomi,
your hole is the best l've ever stuffed!
Oh yeah!!
Daina!
l'm sorry! l was taking care of
a lot business, but l'm glad you're okay!
Des this look like l'm OK to you?
Vaginismus strikes again!
After that, Onikuma was transferred
from the hospital to a jail,
In the real world,
the good side doesn't always win,,,
but I'm glad that was not
the case this time!
I think I can rest for now,
Mr, Daina!
Hey Mimika!
Ms, Misomi is checking out
from the hospital today!
Oh, l know,
l'm about to go pick her up!
l'm coming with you!
Wait,
Wait,,,this is a hotel!
This is the right place!
Everyone,,,,,,
Daina, we need to discuss
something important today!
Something important?
Yes, you need to pick one of us!
Pick?!
Yeah, pick one person,
From us,
And make a commitment,
That's right!
Hey now, everyone here should know
that l don't commit to anyone!
Yes, but we really think you need to pick,
We all know that you love all of us equally,
None of us think
you've been cheating on us,
We can tell
that you love every one of us equally,
Then why?
But we want to be that special one,
because we're women!
You know every girl dreams
of getting married!
B,,,But!
Daina!
Go ahead, pick the hole
that you want to stay with!
-Mr, Daina!
l just can't pick!
I want to,,,
but once I bury my cock in
one of the holes,,,
I'm stuck with that person for a long time,
And that goes against my life philosophy!
How am I going to get out of this?
l have no alternative,,,
l'm just going to have to,,,
Hey, no masturbating!
All right Daina,
you don't have to pick today!
But, instead,,,,
Absolutely, totally, completely!
You're going to have to love us all!
You get no sleep tonight!
l won't last that long!
That's all right, we have this special drug!
HELP!!!
The End