My name is Daina Nariyuki,
l am a high school English teacher
at the Kokuyotei Academy,
l am known for my light,
humorous personality,,,
although some would say l'm too flaky,
My goal is to love as many beautiful
women as possible,
Right now, my targets are:
Mayu Misomi, my new assistant
and student teacher,
The vice president of the student
government, Lisa Koenji,
The tough girl, Fumiko Hojiyo,
The basketball player, Naoki Amagake,
And the bookworm, Mimika Aobajyo,
I have already sampled
my delicious assistant, Mayu Misomi,
Apparently, Fumiko Hojiyo
and Naoki Amagake,,,
are caught in a sinister plan operated
by the school dean, Mr, Onikuma,
Stop!
l need to rescue all of my beautiful queens
from Onikuma!
Watch me everyone!
l will save all of them through the amazing
strength and power of my love!
Well, coming from me,
it might sound more like a joke,
Five Card 2
Darn it, Naoki, where did you go?
l can't believe she's missing
her favorite basketball practice!
l heard Naoki's been absent
from practice for three whole days!
Huh, three days already?
So that was Naoki we saw that night!
So, what did Mr, Onikuma,
the dean and basketball coach, say?
Nothing!
He said she's most likely
at home with the cramps!
l really don't like Mr, Onikuma,
The way he undresses me with his eyes,,,
it totally creeps me out!
Creeps you out?
What do you think you're doing?
l was just curious to see what you look like
when you get totally creeped out!
Really?
l'd be happy to show you more if it's just,,,
the two of us!
Right now, we need to concentrate on
finding Naoki!
Oh, women!
I really wonder,,,
where she could have gone!
That was very good,
How,,,, how did l get into this mess?
See, you're not in a stable position!
You need activate the muscles here,
And tuck your arms in a bit,
And thrust your chest out more
like you're showing off your breasts!
Stop lt, pervert!
l'm going to scream!
Don't you want to be a good athlete?
Not there!
Come on, you need to trust me,
This is a very, very important massage!
B,,,But!
Your body is relaxing, already!
l'm,,,l'm not sure,
Not sure?
lsn't this starting to feel good?
Yes,
Feels very good!
Yes, you have a lot of potential,
l 'm willing to give you a private lesson
to improve your game,
A private lesson??
Right, Meet me
in the old school building later,
l'll make you a star player!
Star player?
Me?
Yes, l think you can be
a great basketball player,
You definitely would make a superb,
slutty little whore!
Mr, Onikuma? Where are you?
Mr, Onikuma?
l've been waiting!
Sit right there,
What? Where is your team uniform?
That got dirty this afternoon,,,
Got dirty?
Doesn't matter;
you look good either way to me,
Huh?
lt's hot today,
Go ahead and drink that juice-- it's for you,
But, l'm not really that thirsty!
Go ahead and drink it,
l customized it just for you,
lt will improve your performance,
strength, and endurance for the game,
You can be a star player!
Star player!
You mean performance drugs?
Kind of,
lt's very effective!
Excuse me,,,
What is it?
What about the private lesson?
We've already started!
What?
lt looks like it's working!
Mr, Onikuma,,,,
What did you give me?
l didn't give you any performance drugs,
Your juice contained some black market
aphrodisiac from lndia!
Aphrodi,,,?
My body,,,my body!
Works well, doesn't it,
Now all you can think about it
having a hard cock inside of you,
l, l can't take it!
God,,,oh my god!!!!
You'll probably want this right about now,,,
Oh yes!!!
What do you want to do with it?
l want it,,,l want it inside!!
Exactly where in your body
do you want this?
Here!
Right in here!
l don't know where ''here'' is,,,
you'll have to tell me,
Well,,,
All right, well then,,,
l'll say it, l'll say it!
lnside my,,,
please put it in inside my pussy!
That's a good girl,
Here's your treat,
First you get to suck on the cock,
Huh?
This cock will be pumping in and out
of your little pussy!
This,,,lnside me!
You want it now?
Well then, you can suck me some more,
then l'll put it inside,
The wait's over,
l'll let you have it now,
Thank you!
What do you mean you want to quit!
l just can't do this anymore!
l'm going to the police now!
l'm probably going to have to
leave the school,,,
but l'd rather tell than continue this!
You don't understand anything!
Who do you think all your clients are?
They are the head of the PTA,
local politicians,,,
members of the school board,
all very powerful people,
Go tell the police all you want--
you'll easily get squashed like a bug!
But!
l'll show you what will happen to you
if you bring this up to me again,
Follow me!
-Naoki!
-Oh Fumiko!
Student Government Office
You've completely finished
your lunch today, too!
Of course!
You are an excellent cook, Lisa!
l do my research,
That's why you are a good student!
Besides, l have a secret, special ingredient,
Hmmmm,,, will you tell me?
No, it's a closely guarded secret!
Well, thank you, as always,
No, no,
l have always dreamed about
being your,,,
Whoa,,,Stop right there,
Huh?
Lisa, you know
that l don't ever commit to anybody,
Marriage limits me to a single partner,
Committing myself would
cause sadness to too many women!
You mean Naoki, Fumiko,
Mimika and your assistant, Ms, Misomi,
Wh,,,what,,,how did you know?
Yes, l did my research,
Yes, including you, l love all of you equally!
Mr, Daina, didn't you go to a hotel
with Ms, Misomi the other day?
You also know about this?
l'm guessing you and Ms, Misomi
had sex at that time?
Sure,
lf that's the case,,,
you need to,,,
We absolutely must have sex together!
This is unexpected,,,!
Fumiko? Why?
She also wanted to quit, just like you,
so l was teaching her a little lesson,
Naoki, don't let this dirty bastard win!
Don't let him take your free will!
Let's see how long it takes
before you change your tune,
This capsule is filled
with the usual aphrodisiac,
Apparently, it works very well
as a suppository,
lnside,,,l'm burning!
l'm coming, coming, coming,,,
Fumiko, do you have anything to say now?
l want it!
Huh? Say what?
l want,,,l want it, l want it, please!
Where did your attitude go?
l really want it,
l want your cock, your huge cock,
l want that thick, hard,
meaty shaft inside me!
No! This is supposed to be a lesson!
lnstead, you can have this thing,
You can't use your hands,
You'll remain tied up,
What? Don't you want it?
l want it,
l want it inside, inside me!
Oh, yeah!
lnside, it's deep, deep inside!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Coming!
So do you still want to quit your job, huh?
Please, l really want some cock, please!
Thank you!
Why, Mr, Daina, you said just now
that you love all of us equally!
lf you had sex with Ms, Misomi,
you really have to have sex with me!
lf you say so, l'll take your offer!
Mr, Daina,,, l'm,,, l'm,,,
l've always dreamed about sleeping
with you since the first time l met you!
What's wrong?
Lisa, l thought you were virgin?
Well, um, today would be the first time
to have sex with a real person,
You mean?
Since l've met you, l've researched,,,
and been trying different ways
to please myself,
You've been masturbating,
Yes,
Never would have guessed,
Well you sure master everything
from school to sex,
At first l was only using my fingers,,,
but l started using larger
and larger things,,,
until l was using dildos
from adult toy stores,
But it's not like l've ever been
with a real, live, person,,,
so technically, l'm still a virgin,
Oh well,
l guess brainy, studious types can also be
a slutty and horny girls as well,
Mr, Daina, do you remember the lunch
l made for you today?
Of course,
there was grilled sausage and corn,,,
stuffed eggplant,
and carrot and giant radish salad,
Wait a minute,,,the secret ingredient,,,,
Yes,,,the secret ingredient is my love juice!
Sausage!
Corn!
Eggplant!
Carrots!
You couldn't fit a giant radish!
Of course not!
Giant radish!
I hope there are
no more secret ingredients,
Mr, Daina, please, now you can taste me!
All right, time for dessert!
Daina!
Mayu! Miss Misomi!
Please knock before entering!
lt's an emergency,
Some students just told me
they saw Naoki around school!
Well,,,
Let's split up!
l'll take the gymnasium,
you check the grounds,
Yes,
Naoki, where did you go?
Ms, Misomi, what are you looking for;
maybe l can help you?
Mr, Onikuma!
l am looking for Naoki,
Have you seen her?
Naoki? No, l have not,
By the way, would you like to have tea
in my office; get to know each other?
l'm in a hurry, Please excuse me,
Stuck up little bitch!
I'll soon turn you into my personal slave!
You need some serious training,
But before I get to you,,,
How long should I wait like this?
l've been waiting here,
patiently waiting here!
Lisa,,,?
Naoki,,,what?
Unfortunately, I was not able to find Naoki,
I guess the only thing I can do
for now is to get back,,,
and attend to Lisa
and maybe that will make me feel better,
Ouch,,,
Hey, are you OK?
Mimika?
Mr, Daina! Oh Sorry,,,sorry!
l just can't believe
l didn't see you coming at all!
Uh-huh,
Mr, Daina, will you go out on a date
with me?
The End