Kokuyoutei Academy,
My wonderful place of employment,
I like it here, it's a lot of fun,
I don't know why the campus is so large,
but it is,
In fact, it's so large the dean, Onikuma,,,
was operating his sinister plan on campus
without fear of being seen!
My name is Nariyuki Daina,
I'm known for my light
and humorous personality,
The subject I teach here is English,,,
but the girls here seem to
be more interested in my body,,,
rather then my English lectures,
Let me introduce my queens,
My former college classmate,
Mayu ''vaginismus'' Misomi,
The vp of student Government,
Lisa ''love juice lunch'' Koenji,
Fumiko Hojiyo, the tough girl, apparently
has very large and sensitive breasts,
The school basketball player,
Naoki ''I love basketball'' Amagake,
Finally, the school bookworm,
Mimika ''endurance'' Aobajyo,
But while I going about
minding my own business,,,
Fumiko, Naoki,,,
and even Lisa ''love juice lunch''
disappeared without a trace,
During this crisis, I somehow
ended up on a date with Mimika,
My goal in life is to sleep with
as many beautiful women as possible,
An act stemming from love
can conquer all!
Everybody, l promise this is no joke,
Five Card 3
l'm cumming!
You are on birth control, right?
No, no, please!
Oh well, too late now,,,going to cum!
Please don't cum inside of me,
stop, please!
Please, l'm begging you, please don't!
You know, l don't really
approve of prostitution,
l have to see a patient this afternoon,
lf you get pregnant,
come see me at the hospital,
l'll take care of it,
Fumiko, Naoki, what are you doing to me?
Why am l,,,
,,,chained up?
We can't be doing this!
We're supposed to be classmates,
please stop!
Talking to them won't do any good,
Who?
Right now, they're drugged zombies,
Mr, Onikuma?
What is going on here?
What do you think is going on?
l thought you were supposed to
be the smartest girl in school!
You can't do this;
especially on school grounds!
l'll have you know that there are absolutely
no campus rules against chaining students,
When did l tell you to stop!
Here, give this to Lisa; make her feel good,
Naoki, no!
What is this?
Oh, more, give me more, please,
More, more!
Oh yes, yes!
Lisa, l'll have you working hard
just like these two right here,
Please, give me, that,
give me, please, please,
No rush, Lisa, you'll soon have more dick
than you know what to do with,
Please, please,,,
will you give me that thick, meaty cock?
All right all right, if you want it that much,
You're pretty,,,
good at this!
l want it deeper; give it to me harder!
l'm,,,l'm cumming!
That was pretty darned good!
Fumiko, Naoki,
make sure to lick her clean,
Remember, if you tell anyone,,,
l'll post these hardcore pictures of you
everywhere on campus,
lf you don't want me to ruin your life,
work hard!
Mr, Daina!
Did someone call me just now?
Giant sundae!
Mr, Daina, open up real wide!
Mimika, you know that's way too much!
Really cold!
I really should be looking for the others,,,,
I know Mimika is one of
my many targets, but,,,,
Right now I'm worried about
the three missing girls,
Fumiko, Naoki, Lisa,
Where did you guys go?
Mr, Dinosaur! How are you?
You're so fluffy,,,
can you tell me your name?
Hey Mimika,,,
May l ask where you were born?
Oh gosh, really!
Mr, Daina! Thank you very, very much!
lt's my pleasure to be able to
bring you happiness!
Stuffed animals are so expensive!
Oh that's Daina,
And that's, Mimiko Aobajyo,
the school bookworm!
lnstead of dating, he really should
be looking for the missing girls!
All right, l'm going to go tease him!
Daina!
Did someone call me?
I wonder if,,,,
Something's wrong,,,
I really shouldn't be on a date,
I should be looking for everyone,
The sunset is really pretty, isn't it?
You know l've always wanted to
sit with you and watch the sun set,,,
behind the city like this,
I must admit that going on dates
can be fun,,,
l really enjoyed our date today!
Mimika!
What is it?
Can l ask you something?
Sure, ask me anything!
How did bumping into each other
in the hallway turn into a date?
lt was fate!
l think you and l are fated to be together,
Mr, Daina, let's go!
What, go where?
You know we haven't finished
the most important part of the date!
What do you mean?
Mr, Daina!
It's looking good
when a date ends up here!
Kissing feels really good!
lf it's with someone you like,
So it feels good because l love you,
lt feels good for me, too,
lt really hurts!
We can stop, you know,
No, l made up my mind
to lose my virginity!
l'll be as gentle as possible!
Thank you,
Ouch, Mr, Daina!
Oh, l'm really sorry! l haven't done it
a while, so l'm just excited,
That's OK,
Have you noticed?
Can you believe l'm the main character
and this is only my second real sex scene!
There are pretty girls everywhere!
l'm about as backed up
in sperm as l can get!
Who are you talking to, Mr, Daina?
Oh no, it's nothing,
lt's painful!
Now it's starting to feel sooo good!
l thought the first time
wasn't supposed to feel so good!
Are you sure it's really your first time?
l know!
lt's because l'm having sex with you!
Onikuma, you bastard!
Show yourself, Onikuma!
l know that you are behind all of this!
You're full of energy
and attitude, aren't you?
Do you think you are going to
get away with this?
l think you should be more worried
about yourself at this point,
Well, bark while you still can!
You'll soon be a willing slave!
You'll be begging me to thoroughly
fill your every hole with my big, hard cock!
You obviously think you're funny!
You don't know how much pleasure l get
from dragging women like you!
Wha,,,what is that?
No, damn it, stop, no, stop, stoooop!
Mr, Daina!
Naoki!
Mr, Daina! l,,,,
l already know, lt's Onikuma,
Onikuma!
Mr, Daina!
What is it?
Sleep with me!
l always said my first love was basketball,,,
but ,,,l really love you,
Mr, Daina, please!
Uh Naoki, this might not be,,,
lt's ok,,,l'm on birth control pills,
All right,,,
You sure, Naoki-l'm cumming in!
Yes,
What is it, Naoki?
l can't believe it!
You came already?
As soon as you put it in; l couldn't help it,
l'm glad,
l can feel it!
Oh my god!
You're really big!
l can't believe l've cum twice already!
That's because
you're with someone you love!
Someone l love,,,
Why don't we shoot for three?
Naoki, you fell good!
Deeper, much deeper!
Mr, Daina, l'm cumming again!
l can't think straight anymore!
Good punishment!
l'm going to take my time with you
and give you special treatment!
Unlike the little girls,
l'll give you something you'll never forget!
VlP treatment!
Onikuma,,,l'll never forgive you!
There's the face!
There's nothing better than
watching you get really pissed off!
Mayu Misomi, l'm going to turn you
into my personal slave!
What the hell is that!
This is a black market drug from lndia,
You're my guinea pig,
so l couldn't tell you exactly what it is,
l know it's supposed to be
a potent aphrodisiac, for sure,
lf this becomes a one-way ticket to heaven,
you'll just have to forgive me!
Daina, where are you?
Mr, Daina, why are you looking outside?
Did you hear anything?
l didn't hear anything!
Oh, l love it!
l can feel your cock pulsing hard inside me!
l'm burning up inside!
Stop! Get away!
You bitch!
l told you, l have no plans to whore you
out like the other girls,,,
if you know what l mean!
lt's not a good idea to
damage my merchandise,,,
but treatment of a slave
is different story altogether,
l'll never, l'll absolutely never
become your slave!
Good, you're getting pissed again!
All right, l'll give you a special treat, Mayu,
No, no, no,,,get away from me!
No, get away,,,Daina, Help!
The End