Mayu Misomi, 22 years old,
she is a new, transferred teacher,
She is currently working as my assistant,
We went to the same college,
She can be a bit careless,
which delayed her transfer here,,,
but more on that later,
Lisa Koenji, sophomore,
She is the vice president of
the student government here at school,
A very pretty, very good student,
It's cute how she gets nervous around me,
Fumiko Hojiyo, sophomore as well,
She's kind of the tough, rough type,
Almost everyone is intimidated by her,,,
but there are those
that try to take advantage of her,
You'll often find her on the roof
of the school, alone, enjoying the sunshine,
Naoki Amagake, sophomore,
One of the basketball players at school,
She is usually perky,
but watch out when she's depressed,
She is almost manic in her high and lows,
She always refers to herself in the
male dialect, for some odd reason,
Mimika Aobajyo, sophomore,
She might as well be the school librarian,,,
as she spends
every spare moment reading,
She's the dreamy type,
floating about in her own dream world,
And the object of affection
of all these cards, I mean cuties,,,
is none other than myself!
I am their English teacher,
and my name is Daina Nariyuki,
I am 25 years old,
My light, humorous personality
seems to make me popular,
Obviously, my good looks
don't hurt, either,
Ah! To hell with professional ethics!
My goal is to make all five cuties,,,mine!
Five Card
Thank god the inspection
by the principal is over!
My lovely school-- known for
its beautiful campus and liberal rules,,,,
Bye bye Mr, Principal!
Until we meet again!
Wish you a long, happy, healthy life!!
God,,, can't you ever be serious?
You haven't changed a bit!
Huh? You make it sound like a bad thing,
Call it humorous, easygoing,
l'm just a fun guy!
You know, it makes life much easier,
l am still single, you know,
Did one of your adoring students
bring you lunch?
What? How did you know?
lt's kind of obvious,
l figured it was something like that,
l've always been popular with the girls,
Any one in particular right now?
Actually, four, Haven't pursued any, yet,
Of course, They're students,
You'll get in trouble,
Oooh! You're worried about me?
Thanks! Changing the subject,,,
What? Leaving early?
Not early, Classes are already over,,,
and l thought my assistant might help me
with some things,
With what? Me?
Of course, you,
By the way, don't get any ideas,,,,
l know, You're not interested in
anyone with boyfriends,
Absolutely,
By the way, how is your boyfriend?
Don't know,
Since you have the same name
l figured you guys weren't married yet,
l haven't seen him for a while,
Which means,,,
Yes, We broke up,
Almost immediately after you graduated,
Wow!
Come in!
Hi there!
Hi Lisa! Working hard! Just wanted
to thank you for the great lunch!
l'm glad!
Where's Naoki?
l think she's at the gymnasium,
Basketball practice, Mimika?
Library, l'm sure,
Obviously, Fumiko?
l haven't,,,
Seen her?
Not since this afternoon,
Well, thanks again! Bye!
Are you leaving?
Got work to do, work!
l was almost done,,,,
I hope Mr, Nariyuki drops by,,,
Maybe since the principal was here
for inspection, he's busy,
Of course, Naoki has no idea
that I am leaving early,,,
or that I am with my new assistant,
former college mate, Mayu,
Same goes for Mimika,
Here, Mimika!
This is Fumiko's favorite spot,
But today, like Lisa said, she isn't here,
That old building is the original school,
It's no longer used,,,
but the principal keeps it around because
it is considered to be a historical building,
No one goes near it anymore,
Unknown to anyone,
Fumiko found herself in trouble, here,
Why am I here?
It's so warm in here,,,
Why am I so horny right now?
Drugs,,, that's right,,, I was drugged,,,
ooh,,, I think I'm coming,,,
Coming ,,,,Coming ,,,,Coming!
I've never come that hard like that before!
That was something else!
l know you want this bad, now, right?
What the hell?
Come on,,, lf you want me to fuck you,
you should at least suck on it first,
Go fuck yourself!
Go ahead, Try to move,
Where's your clothe, your underwear?
Smells good!
Sick, old bastard!
You drugged me, you shit!
Scream, lt's not like
anyone would hear you,
You need to learn some respect,
and know when to give up,
You should know that much,
You fucking shit! Damn you!
l will get you back for this,
What! Watch your mouth!
You're already dry,,,
The drugs must be wearing off,
lf you would have sucked on it,
it would have been easier for you,
You're getting wet again, You like it,
You can say what you want
but your body doesn't lie,
You're getting wet,
your nipple's getting hard,
You're just soaking wet,
You like it, you dirty girl!
Shit! I can't come
while this bastard's doing this!
The drug's messing with me!
Gotta try not to come,
See,,, you're resisting,
l know you want to scream,
Go ahead-scream as much as you want,
Nobody's going to hear you,
Come on,,, scream! No point resisting,
l know you like getting your tits fondled,,,
just like this,
Jesus! l'm coming!
That was very good,
You're good for something,
Here, You know why you're here,
See-- that is the whole campus,
lf you look at it from here, you can tell that
the forest is actually school property!
lt looks very different from the ground,
That's why the principal inspects
the school using his helicopter,
He must like the view,
Unless you inspect from the ground,
you can't tell what's really going on,
Like this?
You haven't changed at all,
Hey Mayu,
Something serious?
Wanna get a bite to eat?
Celebrate your new job?
Really? What if l say no?
According to school rules, assistants need
to take direction from their superiors,,,
You're always joking around!
lt will be my treat!
You sure? Thank you!
l wasn't planning anything fancy, but
are you sure cheap Chinese food was ok?
Oh no! l've been craving fried rice!
lt was good! By the way,,,
Something about work?
Let's talk about it over a drink,
No, Listen, do you have any complaints
about the school??
What do you mean?
There is something fishy,
You mean about Onikuma?
Something smells
about the dean, Onikuma,
I'm not playing well recently,,,
and practicing isn't helping, either,
You need to tighten up your abs and back,,,
Shit,,, it's him!
See,,, you're not in a stable position!
Ugh! Pervert!
You need activate the muscles here
and tuck your arms in a bit,
What the hell? Stop It! Sick Asshole!
If he touches me again,
I'm going to scream!
And thrust your chest out more,,,
like you're showing off your breasts!
Let's review, Tighten your abs,
tuck in your arms, thrust your chest,,,
This isn't right,,,
why isn't she saying anything?
Excuse me! ls everything Ok in here?
ls there anything l can do?
No, l think l'm just about done
helping her out,
ls everything OK?
Thank you very much!
Okay?
The basketball team
is practicing in the next gym,
l was called out for private practice here,
By Who? On purpose?
By Onikuma, the dean?
Probably,,,
Why didn't you say something???
That sporty girl, What was her name?
Naoki, Naoki Amagake,
The fact that
she was quiet the whole time,,,
She's hiding something,
She was obviously uncomfortable,
What do you think she's hiding?
Now you're showing interest,
Wait a minute,,,
You're drunk, You've drank too much,
Are you OK?
ls Naoki one of the four girls that like you?
Yes,
Well, doesn't this bother you?
Of course it does,
lt's not just her, The tough girl,,,
Fumiko Hojiyo,
The bookworm,,,
Mimika Aobajyo,
The Student VP,,,
Lisa Koenji,
lt seems like Onikuma
has something to do with all of them,
Really?
He really had no idea!
Those are my cuties,,,
l know! Those are the four girls
you're after,
So?
Daina! You haven't touched them, right?
A man's gotta take his time,
You don't care about the consequences?
Not really, no,
l think Onikuma is beating you
to the prize by using some kind of force,
What if that's the case?
That damned Onikuma!
lt's cloudy, Looks like rain,
Make 10 color copies of these!
Sure, ln color, right?
What if Onikuma already
beat you to all of them?
She's trying to get a reaction out of me,
Why is she doing this?
She should know me better,,,,
You okay?
l'm just fine,
''Raindrops keep falling on my head,,,''
Whatever,
Are you sure you're OK?
Not really, since you left me!
l never left you,
You had a boyfriend when l met you,
You ran away instead of pursuing,
Hey!
By the way, l spent a lot of time
at the hospital,
-You were ill?
-Not really, Vaginismus,
Huh? Excuse me?
Vaginismus,
That's when you get stuck,,,,
When was your first time?
Personal questions tonight!
l was in sixth grade,
A bit young,
Hurt like hell!
You're in sixth grade,
l was really traumatized,
As a result, during sex,
it sometimes happens,
Vaginismus,,,
that really hurts for both parties?
Hurts like a bitch!
That's why l wasn't late on my first day,
Jesus, That's was
what you meant my ''accident,''
No wonder they broke up,,, would be
hard to keep them around after that!
Wanna know how it feels? Let's try it,
See how painful it is for yourself,
Wait a minute!
lt's embarrassing being carted away
into an ambulance like that,
You're kidding,
You're being a chicken!
''Rain, rain go away,,,''
I gotta get myself out of this,,,
but she'll get pissed if I just take off,,,
Daina! Come here!
Shit!
You're not yourself today?
l'm fine!
Ah! you're regretting
not pursuing me earlier!
Of course not!
What does that mean?
Well,,,uh,,,,
l know! Scared cat!
What!
See,,, you're not hard at all
because you're scared!
l didn't know you were circumcised!
l'll wash it!
That feels good,
No need to lie,,, you're scared
so you're not getting hard,
It would be a very bad idea to get hard,
Must divert my mind,,,
think of counting sheep!
No! Think of something gross,
Trauma,
Think of old women in bathing suits,
Think of my parents having sex,
Fat, hairy, women,
The principal getting upset,
My favorite baseball team losing,
Ah,,, this is not working,
See! l've never seen your happy weenie!
Got an idea! I can make her cum
without having intercourse!
''Rain, rain go away,,,''
lt tickles!
You're really sensitive,
You're nipples are already hard!
Are you sensitive all over?
Even your ears are sensitive!
l can feel sparks when you do that!
This feels so good! Daina!
What about here?
See,,, your clit is getting nice and erect,,,
You're embarrassing me!
You're getting wet! lt's almost like
your pussy's sucking my fingers inside,
Now you're acting more like yourself!
How does this feel? You like it?
Wait,,, No,,, Stop,,, l'm coming!!!
You came!
Yeah,,,,
See, you didn't have your vaginismus!
Well, that felt really good!
See?
l really wanted you, though,
Me? You want me?
Yes, but,,,,
Daina?
Really? Are you sure it's OK?
What do you think?
l can risk getting carried out
to the ambulance buck naked,,,
screaming in pain, on a stretcher, for this!
How sweet! l'm touched, really!
l'm coming in!
l'm not hurting you?
No, this is great!
You scared me!
Did you come more than once?
Several times, already,
Wait,,,oh,,,l'm going to come,,,again!
l want you to know, l really liked you,,,
and wanted this, for a long time,
lt stopped raining!
You didn't have your vaginismus!
You were so nice and gentle!
Wait,,, wait a minute,
That's for not pursuing me back then!
Tricked ya! But that was really great sex!
That's not fair, By the way,,,
l know, You're not
the committing type, Right?
See that?
lsn't that?
Naoki Amagake!
Something's wrong!
Leaving a hotel alone at this time of night?
BCD Hotel, Will have to remember,,,,
The End