Feels good...
See, you like it, don't you?
Oh, there's the beach everyone!
Wow, it's so pretty!
-This time, we're near the beach!
-We're almost there.
Too bad it's too cold now.
Well, at least it won't be crowded.
Maybe we can play beach volleyball!
Flashback Game 2
This is really nice!
I really like it!
Your treatments start at 5 pm.
We'll see you back around then.
Okay!
-Let's go to the beach!
-Yeah, the beach!
Ms. Mizuho?
Are you all right?
I'm doing fine.
Let's go!
Jumping attack!
Yuri, are you ok?
I don't think so!
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to hit the ball that hard!
You'll be ok, Yuri!
Oh, damn it, you're a jerk!
You're going to freakin' kill me
with a damned ball someday!
You're just not suited for sports, Yuri.
Well, Yuri's not an athlete like you.
Shut up, both of you!
I can hit the ball hard, too!
Go right ahead!
You just watch me!
Where's the ball? Where did it go?
Hey Yuri! Are you ok?
What is it?
Did you see someone you knew?
I'm just spacing out.
Everyone!
It's time for your treatments!
Yuri, Sure.
Come on, Mizuho?
I'll pass.
-What?
-You're not coming with us?
Go without me.
I want to hang out at the beach instead.
Why, Mizuho?
I'm just not in the mood! I said no already.
Mizuho?
-Thanks for waiting!
-Yes, thanks for waiting!
Wait a minute. Where's Mizuho?
She wasn't in the mood today.
She wanted to stay at the beach.
Is she OK? Someone should check on her.
Yes. I understand.
We'll go ahead without her.
They use the same treatment pods.
We'll start now.
I'm closing the pod door.
Have fun, you two!
Now.
Watch the pods for me.
Checking on Mizuho?
Yes, I'm going to go
check on her right now.
-Was I dreaming?
-That was no dream.
It's something that you tried
really hard to forget for a long time.
What?
It's an experience that molded you.
Am I right?
Go away!
You should be more honest with yourself.
You were really
in love with Reiko, weren't you?
Not true!
I did admire Reiko for a long time.
I wanted to be perfect just like her.
No, you really were in love with her.
You just didn't want to admit it to yourself.
You didn't have the guts.
No!
You want to be in love.
You're afraid.
You build a wall to protect your feelings.
But you have no need for that now.
There's nothing wrong
with loving another woman.
Love isn't just
between a man and a woman.
Same with sex.
Just be honest with yourself.
I was only a young girl back then.
My favourite friend.
What?
I'll buy you ice cream, just follow me.
Yeah, okay!
It will be over very soon.
Is this a game?
I'm going to teach you something.
Here.
Do you like it?
It tickles a little bit.
But....
It feels kind of strange....
You're getting wet.
I didn't pee in my pants!
This feels even better.
Your pussy tastes delicious!
This feels really good!
Wait...pee.
Stop it!
I'm going to...
...pee now, right now.
Ok Yuri...
What's wrong with your dick?
Now it's your turn to make me feel good.
Oh wow, that's really gross.
What did you say?
You had better do what I say.
Suck on it.
Come on, you can suck on it!
Yucky....
You can't go home unless you do it.
Not fair, I want to go back home!
Then wrap your hands around it first.
And move your hands back and forth.
Very good.... Suck on it like a popsicle.
Gross!
-Shut up and just do it!
-Ouch, That hurts!
Just like that.
You're not bad....
Put it deep inside your mouth.
Yuri, you're really good...!
Gonna come!
No, I don't want to remember....
There is nothing wrong
with making love with a woman.
Oh, Ayame!
I'll teach you something new.
Something only
another woman can make you feel....
Not there!
Well, how about here, then?
Right there!
There's nothing to be afraid of!
I'm going to come!
Yes, I'll come with you.
A dream?!
That's no dream.
That couldn't have been a dream.
I don't like sleeping alone...
Is Noriko and Mizuho asleep already?
What is that?
I'm going to come.
Sex is not just for a man and a woman.
Oh Reiko.
Noriko....
What is this?
Welcome, Ms. Yuri!
Who are you?
Where am I?
This isn't about me.
This is about helping you out.
I'm here to help you heal
your wounds from your childhood.
No, no let me go! I don't need your help!
No, Stop!
Both of you,
you may start Yuri's treatments now.
-Yes.
-I don't need any of your treatments!
Let me go!
Someone help! No, get away from me!
Just relax. Learn to enjoy the sensations.
Stop!
Don't be scared, okay?
It's okay to enjoy it.
Don't you like it, Yuri?
I don't like it at all!
Oh, stop denying yourself the pleasures.
Stop denying your body of what it needs.
I'll take care of her.
You're scaring me!
There's absolutely nothing
to be scared of here, Yuri.
You know you like it.
You're nipples are hard....
I know this excites you a lot.
You like being touched like this.
No, don't!
Deep inside you really like it.
I know you want more.
Just admit that you like being fucked!
Stop it!
How about some nipple clamps?
You like the pain, right?
This makes it even better.
Can't take it....
I know your pussy is
begging for my attention.
No, no!
You're soaking wet!
Stop!
How about this...
Your pussy will really like this!
You dirty, slutty girl!
I like girls like you.
I'm going to give you something extra.
Just for you.....inside your pussy!
Oh, I love it!!
Wait, no!
Oh Yes!
Mizuho?!
-No, Mizuho!
-Will you let me, please...
Yes...
I've always wanted to.
Noriko.
We should stop.
We shouldn't.
Right there....
There...
Yes!
Oh Mizuho.
Noriko.
Mizuho, I...
We'll always be together.
I like this...
Wait...
Yeah...
We really shouldn't.
I don't know Mizuho....
Are you going to come?
I want to come with you.
-I think I'm coming...
-Me, too....
Oh Yes!
I'm glad you're awake now, Yuri.
See, that wasn't so bad, right?
Yeah.....
We need to finish your treatment.
No!
Don't!
Stop!
-Please, let me go!
-Don't be scared, Yuri.
-No, no!
-Yuri, it's going to be okay.
-Yuri, can you suck on this?
-Nooooooo!
You're still not afraid, are you?
We're not going to hurt you!
-Promise?
-I Promise.
-Can you suck on it?
-Okay.
It's not scary, right?
Now put it inside your mouth.
See, you can do it.
You can stop now.
That wasn't bad, right?
Now I'll make you feel so good.
I don't know...
Here I go...
Okay.
I can feel you!
-Your pussy feels so good!
-I like your cock, too!
More, please!
Let me join in, too.
So tight!
Oh my god!
Yes, I love it! You feel good!
I think I'm going to come!
-I can't hold on anymore!
-We'll come with you!
I'm coming inside you!
Was I dreaming?