Thank you for participating
in the total beauty and health spa tour.
Ms. Yuri Honjyo?
Here!
Ms. Noriko Yoshii
and Ms. Mizuho Sakakibara.
My name is Ryouichi Egawa,
and I will be your guide for this tour.
And he will be our driver
throughout the tour.
My name is Takuya Saiki.
This tour is to offer the latest
in relaxational and aesthetic technology
in the gorgeous countryside to replenish,
rejuvenate and beautify the body and soul,
but everyone looks great already!
The flattery is unnecessary!
Don't get me wrong!
I was just stating my observations.
Can't you stop being
so grouchy and just relax!
Oh Yuri, I'm not an airhead like you.
I'm not an airhead,
and you're just being really grouchy!
I'm not a grouch, I'm just careful.
Sorry to interrupt your lively discussion,
but I just want to point out
that the hotel is now visible to your right.
Oooh, that looks really nice!
Yeah!
-I just can't wait!
-Me too!
Flashback Game
The first treatment start at 3 pm today.
Please enjoy the spa's other amenities
until then.
Hey Ryouichi, doesn't
this hotel have a hot spring?
Actually, there is a very nice, large
hot spring, as well as indoor Jacuzzis.
I love hot springs, they feel so good!
Sounds like fun!
Noriko, a good soak is just what I need.
All right! Let's go!
I'll see you at 3.
Please don't forget to
bring your bathing suits.
We got it!
By the way, my new swimsuit
is sooo cute!
Wow!
I'm impressed!
This is great!
Just like Ryouichi said!
Yeah, really!
It's much nicer than I imagined!
I'm going in first!
Me too!
This is paradise!
Hey, don't get my duck wet!
Yuri, that's the purpose of bath toys.
Well, ducky is my favourite!
Are you two arguing again?
Oh a good, hot soak
is exactly what I needed!
During the vacation, maybe
you can stop picking on Yuri!
I'm just kidding.
This place is really nice, though.
See, and I won it
so it doesn't cost anyone a dime!
I've always loved hot springs.
They offer all kinds of treatments here.
I don't think it's possible for me
to get prettier, though!
Oh stop it, Yuri!
If the aesthetician is a man,
I think I'll pass.
It wouldn't bother me if he's really cute!
Noriko, didn't you think both Ryouichi
and Takuya were both so cute?
Huh? Well, I don't...
Come on...
Noriko isn't a little slut like you are!
I am totally not a little slut at all!
Well anyway, Noriko is going to be mine!
Hey, that's not fair, let me join!
Did everyone enjoy the hot springs?
Did everyone like it?
It was awesome!
It was really lovely.
I'm glad you liked it!
I hope you'll enjoy
your spa treatments as well.
Ms. Mizuho?
Oh...y...yes!
We've arrived at the treatment rooms.
I am done for today,
but please change into your swimwear
in the rooms to your right,
and proceed to the treatment room.
What Ryouichi, you're not coming with us?
From here, the head aesthetician,
Ms. Ayame, will guide you!
Unfortunately, I am done for the day.
Oh I'm totally bummed out now!
-Come on, hurry up!
-Hey, wait!
Your clients will be heading
to the treatment room soon.
I'm starting to get a bit nervous!
It's just a spa treatment!
You worry too much, Noriko!
I think this is fun!
Hi, we're here from the tour,
and we're here for the treatments.
I've been waiting! Please come in!
Welcome to the total spa tour!
Ms. Yuri, Ms. Noriko, and Ms. Mizuho!
Looks a lot like Reiko...
Hey, Mizuho!
Are you ok?
What are you worried about?
You must be Ms. Ayame?
It's a pleasure to meet you!
I am Ayame Shitano, the head
aesthetician here, and it's my pleasure.
It's nice to meet you, as well!
Our facility uses
the latest, advanced whole body treatment
pod here for its spa treatments.
The only thing you have to do is to just slip
inside the pod and relax your stress away!
Does anyone have any questions?
Well,...uh...!
About this?
I know it looks strange,
but these fluids are special extracts
that course through the pod to treat you.
Do you have any more questions?
Oh guys, there's absolutely nothing
to get worried about!
Mizuho, let's get you started
first in this pod.
We will begin the treatment now.
Please, just try to relax.
I hear the sound of waves.
and...I'm suddenly feeling so comfortable.
Where am I?
I'm supposed to be inside the pod...
What's happening?
Come on.
Come on Mizuho slow down!
Why are you running?
Running isn't going to get
anyone to help you!
Come on, huh!
Slow down, huh Mizuho!
Slow down!
Here!
What do you want with me?
Aren't we your classmates?
We just want to get to know you better.
Well I have to go now....
You don't want to hang out?
-But...
-You don't want to miss out!
We'll all have a lot of fun, right?
A baby probably feels like
this inside its mother.
I feel so snug!
Huh...?
What is going on?
My little Yuri!
Thank you for the ice cream.
Special treat for my prettiest friend.
Did you know that it feels good
to be touched here?
But that's where
your pee pee comes from!
Here...right here...here?
Do you like it?
It feels funny, kind of tickles.
Really, it kind of tickles, huh?
Oh, but It's starting to feel kind of weird.
This is so relaxing...
I feel like I'm floating in the ocean.
Where am I?
Hey!
Stop running.
Nobody is going to help you!
-Got Her!
-Noooo!
You got her?
Somebody help!
You cunt!
Hurry up! Come on!
Yeah, hurry up!
You don't want to run away from us!
You don't want to make things
more difficult for yourself.
If you don't co-operate,
we might have to hurt you really bad.
-Can't you people be more civilised?
-Please, please help!
You guys, ganging up on a girl like that.
Don't you think you should all be ashamed!
Well, uh....um...
We're just trying...
No need for lame excuses.
But you know, Mizuho, you're at fault, too.
You would have avoided a lot of pain.
Reiko, why....?!
Unfortunately, we don't want to
upset you Reiko, so we'll go.
This is a precious party
I planned just for Mizuho,
so, please proceed and enjoy yourselves.
What are you talking about, Reiko?
The weak should only serve
and obey the strong!
To think that I admired you, Reiko...
You are so popular,
and I thought you were so perfect...
Let's first take a good look at the tits.
She's got a pretty nice pair, here!
They're looking nice, firm and soft!
-Stop!
-These are fucking awesome!
Instead of playing with her tits,
hurry and strip her.
Yeah, he's right!
Let's have her do something for us.
Instead of spacing out,
why don't you try sucking on this, huh?
Check this out!
You need to look this way to suck.
Hey, open your mouth!
Next turn is mine!
Don't be hogging all the fun, now.
I want a turn, too.
Aren't you fucking done yet?
Your hands are free,
might as well jack me off!
Yeah, a hand job sounds real good.
You need to grip tighter.
You're learning this real quick.
This is working out well!
After all the fussing,
she's doing pretty good.
I saw a gang bang in a video once.
Really didn't think she would do it!
It seems like you guys
are just pleasing yourselves...
Why don't you do
something for poor Mizuho?
All right.
In that case,
I will do something for her, then.
You lucky bastard!
Good things come to those who wait...
What...no...not there, please!
Not to worry, you can relax.
I'll make sure you'll still be a virgin.
Ouch...that hurts...please stop, ouch!
She's tight...
I'm not going to last too long!
Not too quick.
We don't want to hear you complain
so why don't you just keep on sucking!
Keep doing that.
-I'm about ready to cum!
-Let's all cum on her face!
I'll be cumming in her ass.
Thank you for your time today!
We are all done with the treatment today.
Please rinse off any remaining extracts
in the shower room!
What did you think; I think
everyone looks much better already!
This is only our first treatment!
Absolutely. Everyone's looking
very relaxed and very pretty.
-You really think?
-Yes, you don't you believe me?
-I see a difference already.
-Goody!
You'll be a completely new person inside
and out by the time we're done!
I'm absolutely sure.
Now, please head to the shower room
down the hallway.
Say...
did everyone feel kind of strange
inside the treatment pod?
I felt like I was floating.
For me, it felt like I was a baby floating
inside its mother!
Yeah, it was like floating...
and I really liked it!
I think I was dreaming
while inside the pod.
Yeah, I think I saw one too;
I think I was dreaming.
Dream?
Dream, no.
That was no dream!
I know for sure that it wasn't a dream.
That was a memory
I forced myself to forget forever.
Why now?
But, why is this coming back to me now?
I thought I put that behind me.
Was it the aesthetician?
But...but why?
The weak should only serve
and obey the strong!
I am not
a weak, spineless person!
Are you all right, Mizuho?
Are you feeling all right?
What... I'm okay, I was just spacing out.
Ok, you scared me for a minute.
It seemed like
you haven't been yourself today.
I was just thinking about a lot of things.
305...hey, this is my room here.
Were you planning something for tonight?
Yuri and I were thinking
about possibly hitting the Jacuzzi now.
You're coming with us, right?
Jacuzzi? Not right now.
We've been in water almost all day today.
Oh well, Noriko,
it looks like just the two of us!
Okay? You don't mind?
Mizuho, we'll be heading off now, then.
All right, have a good time!
What is this light?
Wait....
What is going on?
I thought I just walked inside to my room...
Yes.
You're inside your room, but you aren't.
Confused, just like you are.
What on earth are you talking about?
I see...,I'll make you understand.
Open yourself up to me.
Open.
The person that you buried
deep inside yourself, I'll help her.
You think you might have put
the past behind,
but you haven't really, have you?
You've tried really hard to forget
and just pretend like nothing happened.
Open.
You need to open you soul up to me.
Please, don't stop!
See, you're doing much better already.
You probably would like this?
If you want this,
you'll have to suck on it first.
You are quite skilled.
Just like I promised.
I'll give it to you.
I'll cum!
Come on...you can open up even more.
See, I'll let you cum real soon.
Wake up, Mizuho! Mizuho!
Let's go eat dinner!
Was I dreaming?
Really just a dream?
Hey Mizuho,
don't you want to eat dinner tonight?
You think she might have stepped out?
You think so?
I'm sorry,
I'll be ready in a minute, so wait up!
-Huh?
Did she say sorry?
I'm not allowed to say sorry?
Oh Mizuho-- major bedhead!
-What? Oh No!
-You look funny!
Welcome, we are heading
to the second destination of our tour.
Tell us Ryouichi,
about where we're going today.
Where we're going today?
What about "It's going to be a surprise."
Surprise?
Yuri, I hope you will enjoy it.
Oh, I love surprises!