Dream?
Oh Mizuho...
Oh Mizuho!
After all,
I am my mother's daughter.
Flashback Game 3
So, where are Mizuho and Yuri?
Mizuho and Yuri have advanced
to the next level of their treatment.
You'll be the only one here today.
Oh, I see.
Please enter the machine.
- Ryouichi.
- Yes.
Please have Takuya check on Mizuho and
Yuri to make sure they are doing all right.
Yes.
I love this!
You're so easy to please.
You're nipples are so hard...
Stop it!
You're soaking wet down here, too.
I love what you're doing!
I love the way you taste.
I'm going to lick all your juices.
This feels so good I can't take it!
You're unbelievably wet!
Oh Yes!
Yuri, you can be such a little slut!
No, no!
Mizuho, please don't stop!
Okay, I'll continue.
You ready?
I'm ready, Mizuho.
I can feel it!
You like it.
Yes, Yesssss!
Do you love the way this feels?
Oh Mizuho!
- It feels so good!
- Yuri!
Mizuho, I love you!
I think I'm going to come!
Let's come together, ok?
Oh Mizuho!
Yuri, I'm coming too!
- Coming!
- Yuri!
This is...
This is my old house.
Yes baby!
This is great!
Mother!
My old memories...
This bitch is a great fuck!
What a goddamned slut!
- More!
- What a goddamned whore!
After my father died, my mother was
always sleeping with young men.
I like easy sluts like this!
Give it to me harder!
Mother...
You fucking love it right...
Let's trade places.
If you want to.
I love easy women!
Oh yes!
Now it's my turn to make you scream!
Put it inside... yes!
Fuck me harder, deeper!
She's so tight, I can't believe it!
Now it's your turn to suck me.
She's good!
She's better than professional whores!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah!
I shouldn't be doing this.
She's a fucking machine!
Oh yeah baby!
Hurry up.
Oh Yes!
I'm just about to come!
Me too!
I'm coming!
Coming!
Oh Yes!
I'm...
Doesn't she have a daughter?
Maybe we can sample her, too.
Her mom's practically
the whore of Babylon.
If she's like her mother,
she'll spread her legs willingly!
Maybe, huh?
The memories I have
suppressed for so long...
No!
How was it!
We're all done for today!
You should relax now!
Yes.
I thought I forced myself to forget...
Yes!!!
My mother died a year ago.
My mother that fucked young men.
More, more!
I was very afraid of becoming
a woman just like my mother.
Yes.
The memories I have suppressed
deep inside my soul.
Where did Mizuho and Yuri go?
I'll drop by later.
For now...
What the...
Welcome, Ms. Noriko!
Who are you, and where am I?
This is a place where your
deepest desires become reality.
You're crazy!
I'm going to free your troubled soul today.
No!!!
Stop it!
You need to be more honest with yourself.
What makes you think I'm lying?
You have so much fear in your mind
about becoming
a carnal creature like your mother.
You deny yourself the pleasure of sex.
But sexual desires are natural.
There is nothing wrong
with enjoying it at all.
There is no reason
to be afraid of your desires.
This will make you feel better!
Isn't this fantastic?
You have such a beautiful pussy, Noriko.
It's tight around my fingers.
Even your pretty nipples
are so hard and erect!
Yes!
I can't take it!
You're dripping wet!
Look at this, Noriko.
No, I can't take it!
I think you're about ready for me.
No, don't!
Oh, but your body wants me badly.
I'm coming in!
I feel it!
No, No!
I like your pussy!
Noriko, your pussy is so tight!
I can feel him fucking me hard!
Yes!
See, isn't it good?
Yes, I like it!
Just like I said, now you can
be more honest with yourself.
Just give into the pleasure.
Noriko, you're a little slut!
Am I a slut.
Goddamn, you are so tight!
I'm about to...
It's okay to enjoy this.
Coming, I'm going to come!
- Coming!
- Yes!
I'm coming!
What just happened?
This is my hotel room!
Was I dreaming?
Okay, we're taking off!
We'll be heading to our final destination!
We'll soon be at a beautiful resort hotel!
Oh great!
We have to check out the pool.
What's going on?
Welcome, Ms. Noriko!
Noriko, hey Noriko!
You've been so quiet; are you feeling okay?
I'm worried about you!
Oh no, I was just thinking.
Really, are you sure?
Yeah, I'm ok.
We can see the hotel from here.
Let me see!
Looks so nice!
It's really big!
Our final treatment will be at the hotel.
You girls will feel great afterwards!
Your final treatment will start at 3pm.
Have fun until then.
The heated pool here is enclosed,
so it's used year-round.
I highly recommend it.
I'll see everyone later.
Let's go to the pool!
Yeah, let's go!
Noriko, are you sure you're ok?
I was just spacing out. Let's go!
If you're sure.
- Hurry, let's go!
- Ok Yuri!
The pool is not going anywhere, Yuri.
Already the final treatment...
That's right.
This is so big!
Feels nice!
I'm glad we came!
Did you bring that stupid duck again?
I want him with me at all times!
Hey Noriko.
No more treatments...
But it feels so good!
Yeah, I love it!
I've really started to enjoy it a lot!
Yeah, I've grown to like it.
Oh Yuri, Mizuho...
Oh no, I'm late!
I don't feel like it, but...
I'm sorry to be...
What is this?
No Mizuho!
No Yuri!
I can't believe...!
This is where I will teach you
to finally learn to open up to yourself.
There's no reason to be scared, Noriko.
Miss Ayame?!
You're just so afraid that you're going to
turn out just like your mother.
Even if you did, there's absolutely
nothing wrong with that at all.
Men are crazy for girls that like sex.
So Noriko...
Be more honest with yourself.
Come on, see, look at everyone here.
Mizuho was just like you before the tour.
The treatments made her understand
her desires, and look at her now!
Yuri discovered the pleasures of the flesh,
and now she enjoys having sex...
Look at the expression of bliss
on their faces!
Don't you want to experience that?
Discover your sensual side...
You don't need to be quiet.
I know you like this.
I can't resist anymore!
I love being stuffed like this!
Noriko, your ass is super tight!
Your pussy feel so good!
I'm going to go crazy!
Noriko, let's go crazy together!
Oh Yuri!
We'll be together forever!
Be honest with your carnal desires!
It will make you that much more beautiful!
Oh, I love this!
See Noriko, it's okay to be a slut!
For being honest with yourself,
I'll give you a special treat!
Oh Yes!
Yuri, I love it!
I have something special here for Yuri!
It's big, but I like it!
Noriko!
I can't hold on!
This feels too good!
I'm coming!
So Yuri, do you like this?
Yes, I love it, I can't handle much more!
I think I'm...
I'm going, I'm going to come!
Yes, Yes!
Final treatment was successful.
A few weeks later
How are you doing lately?
Well, the Chicago branch
is shutting down...
Well, we'll forget about
all the bad things tonight!
Ladies and Gentlemen!
I would like to thank everyone for waiting!
We will be commencing our auction now!
Today's precious merchandise
will be our highest quality sex slaves!
Wonderful!
This is Mizuho, item 1701:A.
She especially enjoys sharing
her sexual bliss with a woman.
A prefect present for
a special woman tonight.
I like her...
This is Yuri, item 1701:B.
She looks much younger than her age.
She will be delightful for
your naughty Lolita-type fantasies.
She looks quite nice.
Yes, I would really enjoy having her!
Final item, 1701:C, is Noriko.
She will be the prefect slave
for those S and M aficionados.
I'd like to have her as my pet.
Yes, you should bid for her.
Let's start with item 1701:A.
Starting with a 1000...
- 1200!
- 1300!
- 1400!
- 2000!
How is the auction going?
Yes, they are going at a high price.
Good, and I do have your next assignment
from the owner.
We need the next round of goods
by the tenth of next month.
I think I can manage that.
We have our next targets lined up already.
Good, we're counting on you.
I hope your masters will love you all...
Mizuho, Yuri and Noriko...
THE END