Time flies. Has it been a year already?
Sorry for being late.
This doll will make you feel less lonely.
I can't believe you put his doll on the grave. It's in bad taste.
You came here as well.
I-I was just passing by.
N-Nothing more.
Wh-Why are you smiling!?
Got something to say!?
No, not really.
Even if you're just passing by, would you like to pray?
Okay.
I don't want to admit that this was fate.
Still, I wonder if you were happy.
Did you ever feel happiness?
Flutter of Birds
Wings of Angels
Part 1: Reminiscence
One Year Ago
Excuse me. This is the last stop.
The last stop.
I see. You're from Mitsuru-san's household.
My name is Shinya Sinclair.
I know. You're the son of her sister, aren't you?
My name is Yukiyanagi Yuzu.
Yuzu is written in hiragana.
So, how much farther to the church?
There's still a long way to go.
I see.
Do you find the scenery strange?
No, not really, but...
This country is where my mother was born,
and where she met my father and fell in love with him.
I used to wonder a lot about what it might be like,
and what the people here were like.
Wondering if I could sense my mother here.
Wh-What's wrong?
Shinya, you're wonderful.
What?
You're wonderful.
Thank you.
No way, a bear? In the middle of winter?
Run!
Ouch!
Shinya!
Shinya.
Don't worry about me. Hurry up and run!
But...
Oh, there you are!
You were taking so long I was becoming worried.
You're Shinya-kun, right?
I'm Mizueda Mitsuru. Nice to meet you.
Oh, yeah, nice to meet you.
My foot...
Ouch!
It hurts!
You've sprained it.
It will take about two weeks to heal,
so you'll be staying in the hospital for now.
What? I just got here!
Now, now, look on the bright side.
At least you didn't break anything.
Hey...
Shinya, I'm sorry!
Huh? Why are you apologizing?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It's fine.
Right?
Yes.
Well, I'll go fetch your luggage.
Take care, Sinclayer-kun.
Um, would you mind using the standard pronunciation?
I thought I did.
I'd say it was quite original.
I see. I'll work on it, Sinclayer-kun.
Yeah...
I'll see you two later. Have fun!
M-Mitsuru!
Umm...
Yes?
Huh? Wh-What is that!?
I'm Doll-Yuzu! I'll speak on Yuzu's behalf!
Wh-Why are you laughing?
I-I'm sorry. So, what do you want to talk about?
Well, you see, this hospital has a nice cafeteria.
Would you like to go there with me?
Sure, let's go.
Great!
Umm...
You looked, didn't you?
Well, they showed, so...
You saw it!
I can't believe you did that!
I'm sorry. I didn't bump into you on purpose!
Shut your mouth!
From now on, you're my slave. Got it?
Slave?
Do something like that again, and you'll be sorry.
Got it, slave?
Her name is Kayaba Kazura-chan.
It seems she's from a really wealthy family.
I see. That explains it.
Her lungs are weak, so she came to Kuramachi to convalesce.
Hard to tell from the way she acts.
We can't judge her illness just by appearances.
We're not doctors, you know?
You're right.
Um, Shinya?
I'm back!
Welcome back. Did they have coffee beans in stock?
Yes, I bought everything you asked for,
but it started snowing on the way back.
We might get a blizzard tonight.
I-I'm sorry!
Sh-Shinya!
Oh, I can't believe this!
Sheesh, Akane-san.
I'm very sorry. Are you okay?
Y-Yes, I'm okay... or not!
Shinya, hang in there. Shinya!
This feels great.
Yuzu, let's wash each other!
I couldn't tell him.
Have you fallen for him?
If you have, then make sure you're prepared.
Eh? Prepared for what?
You know, man and woman: in it goes!
Don't blush.
Now then, I wonder how much you've grown.
Stop it.
Oh, now you've done it! Take this!
No!
Yuzu hasn't come by yet today.
Slave! What are you doing here?
It'll take much more than that for me to forgive you, understood?
Yes, I understand.
Very well then.
You've done it not just once, but twice!
This time I will not forgive you!
Hey, slaves are not supposed to run away!
Wait up! Wait up!
— Where are you?
— I'm saved.
She's a nightmare.
Penguins are birds.
What? Hey, you...
Oh no, an eel got up my nose.
Good morning.
I wish we could have met under better circumstances.
Narahara Narumi... The same name as this clinic?
Narahara Nao is my father.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Only Kazura-chan comes to visit me, so I'm happy you stopped in.
K-Kazura-chan comes here often?
Yes, she comes here to talk...
but she hasn't been by today.
I-I see.
If Kazura-chan didn't come, I'd always be alone.
I read books and rest in the sunlight, but I'm still lonely.
You... You really do have a lot of books here.
Have you read them all?
Yes, I love books!
Even though I'm stuck inside,
reading takes me on many adventures.
The only thing I can do is spend time.
Huh? Don't you ever go outside?
I was born with a weak body,
so this room and the books my mother left me are all I have.
I'm like... a bird in a cage.
It's not uncomfortable, though.
I've gone on many adventures through these books.
I've visited distant countries or gone to old Japan.
I've played with fairies and strange creatures.
I do this every day, so I'm not bored.
I think that's strange.
It's difficult to say this, but the worlds inside books are fiction.
They're not real adventures, are they?
But I don't know what else to do.
That's easy.
You just have to look at a bigger world. Like this!
There are people and animals out there, too.
Adventures just waiting to happen!
It would be a waste to just stay inside.
Shinya-san...
You have to look forward.
If you do, your dreams are sure to come true, right?
Narumi, look at the beautiful flowers I brought you.
Slave! What are you doing here!?
Well, this is...
Oh, so Shinya-san's last name is "Slave"?
N-No! Kazura-chan decided that on her own!
You bastard!
When you refer to me, address me properly!
Besides, you were about to make a pass at my best friend, weren't you?
Jeez, I won't forgive you!
H-Hold on! I wasn't getting close to anyone!
Shut up! I don't believe you!
Don't run away, slave!
Hey! Not again!
Stop it, would you?
— Wait up, you monster!
— I'm a patient in recovery!
The outside world.
...and then it started snowing heavily,
and I ended up looking like a snowman.
Are you listening?
I-I'm sorry!
You were talking about the fish, right?
No, I wasn't! What's wrong with you today?
You're spacing out.
Hey, Kazura-chan...
What?
Should we go outside?
Here.
What have you done to Narumi?
I haven't done anything.
Don't act innocent!
Narumi has never wanted to go outside before,
but now all of a sudden she wants to!
Narumi-chan?
Shinya-san!
I decided to go on a little adventure!
Narumi-chan!
What have you done to her?
I haven't done anything, just...
Just what?
I just opened her window.
Her window?
Hello!
Tomorrow I'll go on another adventure.
Not yet...
I don't want this to end.
My dream is just about to start.
Hey!
I haven't done anything today!
What are you talking about?
I just wanted to say thanks, for Narumi.
What?
D-Don't misunderstand.
I still consider you my slave.
Don't get any strange ideas.
Narumi-chan?
It's Shinya.
I'm coming in.
Narumi-chan?
I wonder where she went.
S-Sinclayer-kun!
Please pronounce it correctly.
Have you seen Narumi?
No, she wasn't in her room.
Has something happened to her?
I can't find her anywhere.
What?
I've been looking for her, but she isn't in the hospital.
She knows her limits and shouldn't be walking around.
Maybe... I think she's outside!
What!?
— Narumi! Answer me, please!
— Narumi!
Kazura-chan, you'd better go back.
No, I'll help look. Narumi is my best friend.
Narumi!
Narumi-chan!
She's not here.
Let's look somewhere else.
Narumi-chan!
Where could she be?
Dammit, this is all my fault.
These footprints...
No way. A real bear?
Oh, no!
Wait! It's me.
That voice is...
N-Narumi-chan?
Yes, I'm Narumi the bear.
Thank God.
With this leg, I wouldn't be able to run from a real bear.
Why are you out here?
After listening to you, I wanted to see more of the world outside.
This bear costume keeps me from getting cold.
B-But that's...
Just like you said, going outside is really fun!
This is what a real adventure is like!
Adventure?
Yes! An adventure, an adventure!
That's right.
For her this is a huge adventure.
Let's have a snowball fight.
Okay.
Take that!
That was fun. I've never enjoyed myself so much.
I see.
But from now on, you shouldn't go outside on your own.
Okay.
Um...
Um, I want to tell you something.
What is it, Narumi-chan?
Well, you see... I... I...
Are you okay, Narumi-chan?
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry. I... I...
Don't say anything else. Let's hurry back!
Everything is your fault! She is... Narumi is...
How is she doing now?
The doctor said the next few days will be critical.
What?
I'm sorry. I went out without telling you.
Don't worry. Did you have fun?
Yeah.
I see.
[No Visitors]
I can leave?
Your foot has healed.
You should be able to leave.
I see.
Don't worry about Narumi.
I'm grateful for what you've done.
This hospital had always been like a cage to my daughter,
but you took her outside of it.
As her father, nothing could make happier.
Thank you very much, Sinclair-kun.
You're welcome.
This is it.
Shinya-san...
It's been a while.
Are you feeling better?
Yes! I'm feeling a lot better.
Good. I feel relieved.
Um, I couldn't tell you this before. Will you listen?
Sure.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
I played with you, even though I knew you were sick.
This isn't your fault!
I did it of my own free will!
So, you're no to blame, Shinya-san!
Besides, I had a really wonderful time.
I became a bear and had an adventure in the forest.
For anyone else, it would just be a walk,
but for me it was very special,
because it was the first adventure in my life.
Narumi-chan...
Please, listen to me and promise not to laugh.
In this room, I've dreamed of the future and many other things.
Dreamed about the kind of person I want to be,
what kind of job I'd like to have,
and even what kind of person I'd want to marry.
Strange, isn't it? I may not even have a future...
Don't say that! Everyone is entitled to dream!
"Future" is the word all my dreams lead to.
That one day, I'll run outside,
and live happily with the person I love!
That's my dream!
That's the future i want myself to have!
Shinya-san, I want to make this dream come true with you.
I want a future where you and I are together!
Narumi-chan...
Shinya-san!
You're beautiful, Narumi-chan.
Don't. I'm embarrassed.
Don't say that. Let me see you.
Oh, Shinya-san, you're a bad boy.
If you call me a bad boy, then that's what I'll have to be.
Do you like it?
I'm not sure how to explain it to you, but my body is...
Don't... Don't do that, Shinya-san! If you do that...
Are you okay?
Yes, I felt something through my body just now.
It's because you're feeling good. You're so cute.
This is...
This... This feeling is wonderful.
Wow, you're very wet.
Shinya-san, I... I...
I'll make you feel much better now.
No, don't look at me.
Nope. I want to see all of your body.
No. You can't lick a place like that.
No!
Narumi-chan, I'm going in.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine. Please keep going.
Okay.
You shouldn't push yourself.
I'm fine! I want to feel you inside me.
I want you to fill me up!
I feel strange. What is... What is this?
Are you feeling it?
I'm not sure, but...
the depths of my body are getting hot!
I love this! It's all the way in!
Narumi-chan.
If you do that, I'm going to feel weird!
Narumi-chan, I'm going to...
Shinya-san, me too! Me too!
Aren't you cold?
No, I'm quite warm.
Narumi-chan...
I've finally become a normal girl.
Hello?
No one's here.
Hello, Suzuka-chan and Akane-san.
Kazura-chan!
What's the point of you coming now!?
No. That can't be...
It's not true! It can't be real, right?
Say something, Narumi-chan! Narumi-chan!
Narumi-chan!!
kinou made no koto zenbu watashi no takaramono
[Everything up until yesterday is my treasure.]
kono mama zutto issho ni iraretara yokatta ne
[If only we could be together forever.]
yakei no kirei na oka de mata te wo tsunagitai yo
[I want to hold your hand again,]
[on top of a hill on a beautiful night.]
demo korekara hoshi ni naru no takaramono
[But all those treasures will fade away.]
aenai no aitai yo samishii toki wa itsumo
[I want to meet you but I can't, so whenever I am sad,]
sora ni ukabu hoshitachi ga kirari hikaru kagiri de
[as long as the stars up in the sky are shining,]
anata dake ni okuru yo hoshi no messeiji
[I'll keep sending their message to you.]
The lost memories.
The feelings they don't want to lose.
Will their wandering hearts find each other?
Next episode: Fate.
Shinya...
You are my precious future.