I remember Shinya-kun's face.
I couldn't bear to look at it.
He blamed himself for Narumi-chan's death.
He deserves to!
If only he hadn't played around with Narumi and her feelings...
I know you're not really thinking that.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
I-I mean every word of it!
However, you can't blame a person for someone else's death.
Mao-chan!
Death is a destiny you can't escape.
Thanks for coming.
The important thing is to live a happy life.
Narumi lived her life the way she wanted to.
She came to know happiness.
You're just trying to excuse your helplessness!
You know it was going to happen. You can tell the future!
You knew that she was sick...
and you knew she was going to die!
I won't deny it!
That's my power.
The bow's fortune telling shows a destiny none can avoid.
Mao-chan was always there for Narumi-chan,
even though she knew that
Narumi-chan's life would be short.
I know, but that's what makes me mad.
She was about to find happiness.
Why was fate so cruel to her?
Yes, fate is cruel.
Both for those who die, and those who are left behind.
Shinya also cursed her fate.
That was when I met him.
It was destiny that led me to him.
Did you also foresee that?
I simply allowed my fortune telling and destiny to guide me.
The destiny I was entrusted with.
Flutter of Birds
Wings of Angel
Part 2: Fate
One Year Ago
Narumi-chan...
Shinya, you're going to catch a cold.
Let's go inside.
Leave me alone!
I knew nothing about her --
neither the kind of illness she had,
nor her feelings when she gave her body to me.
I didn't know anything.
I had no right to be loved by her.
Shinya...
I'm making stew for dinner tonight.
So please, do come back.
I'll be waiting.
I'm so bored.
Neither Kazura-chan nor Shinya have come here in a while.
Can you blame them after what happened?
This must be hard for them.
I still wish Kazura-chan would come.
Although whenever she's here,
she complains that the tea is too hot,
or that the cake is too sweet.
Nothing but complaints.
Still, the place feels empty without her.
Sorry for being such a bother to you.
H-How long have you been there?
Well, now I know what you think of me.
I was only joking.
I'll have some tea, preferably not too hot.
R-Right away.
I see you're doing better.
Well, I can't be sad forever.
Narumi would laugh at me.
I guess so.
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
I only wanted to...
Get out of here!
You just played with her feelings!
You have no right to be here!
You're right.
You're right. I have no right to be here.
H-Hey...
Wait!
Shinya-kun is taking a bit too long.
Shinya...
What's wrong?
I'm going to go find him.
You can't! It's late, and the snow's started.
I heard it! I heard Shinya's voice calling for help.
Yuzu...
It's really cold.
If I fall asleep here, I'll surely die.
That's not so bad, though.
If I die, I could see Narumi-chan again.
Oh, yeah. Yuzu is making stew for dinner.
Forgive me, Yuzu. I...
Naru--
Ah...
Awake now, are you?
I-I'm sorry. Um, did you save me out there?
Would it be better if I hadn't?
N-No, that's not what I meant.
I had no intention of saving you.
I'm not the kind of person who would stop someone from trying to die.
If your fate had been to die, I wouldn't have saved you.
My fate?
Death is a destiny no one can escape.
Just like Narumi.
You knew Narumi-chan!?
My bow foresaw what was going to happen,
but Narumi already knew her fate.
She didn't try to escape and accepted her lot.
She followed her own fate.
Are you telling me death was her fate?
I've told you already. No one can escape death.
That doesn't justify the death of a good girl like Narumi-chan!
Good or bad has nothing to do with it.
It was simply her fate.
You don't know what you're talking about!
What is fate? Who decides that fate?
Narumi-chan was finally able to leave her cage of a room!
She was about to live a life of happiness!
But despite that...
She was denied even the slightest joy!
I won't accept a fate like that!
I never will!
However, Narumi's death is real.
Humans can't change fate.
That can't be! We can change our fate!
There has to be more than one!
It's too late now, but Narumi must have had another one as well!
I-I'm sorry.
Don't worry,
I don't mind being with you, Shinya.
So please, look at me.
I have another reason for bringing you here.
I have a destiny to fulfill as well.
Your body doesn't lie.
Well, that's...
It's all right.
This may be my fate, but it's also my desire.
I carried you here to free you of your past with Narumi.
There's no need to hesitate. Please, sleep with me.
B-But that would just be cruel to you.
I'm Mao, Makimura Mao. That's my name.
Mao-chan?
Yes, Mao.
B-But I don't know anything about you.
If I sleep with you, I'll be going back on my word.
You're more stubborn than I thought, Shinya.
I'm not stubborn.
Relax. Like I said, this is what I want.
If this helps you move on from your past with Narumi and into the future...
I want you to show me.
Show me that fate can be changed.
Does that mean you know what will happen to me in the future?
I'm also looking for another destiny.
Do you think I can do that?
I do, and that's why I want you to prove it.
You can take responsibility for your own words, right?
You have me there.
Are you sure about this?
Are you cold?
A bit.
Shinya, come with me.
Here?
Don't embarrass me too much, okay?
Of course not.
You're so eager.
If you do that, I'll... I'll...
Do you like it?
Don't ask me that.
Looks like you like it, too.
A-Ah...
M-Mao...
Enjoy it. Enjoy it enough to forget about anything else.
Wait. If you keep going, I'll...
Come to me.
The two of us will become one, just like our destinies.
Mao...
Hurry, come inside.
Wonderful.
Amazing. You're all the way in!
Yes, so strong! More!
It's all the way in, Shinya...
Shinya! You're so good! It's all the way in!
So good! You're too good!
Mao! Mao!
Shinya...
Mao... Mao... I... I can't hold back anymore.
Yes, Shinya, cum. Give me your fate.
I'm almost... I'm almost there!
Mao!
Shinya! Shinya!
So much cum...
Feeling better?
I've done what I can.
Wh-What do you mean?
I can only show you the way.
Someone else must open the door and share your future.
What's that supposed to mean?
You haven't noticed, but that someone is already close to you.
Always looking after you...
Looking after me?
Shinya!
What's wrong?
I heard something. I heard a voice.
In this blizzard?
That voice... It's...
Mao!
Over there!
Where? I can't see anything.
Yuzu!
Yuzu, wake up! What are you doing here!?
Sh-Shinya...
I'm so glad. I finally found you.
Yuzu, hang on.
Yuzu! Don't go to sleep!
Open your eyes!
Yuzu! wake up!
Yuzu!
Yuzu...
Doctor, what's wrong with her?
She'll recover once her body warms up,
but there's a problem.
It can't be...
Wh-What is it?
You see, Yuzu has a form of amnesia.
Amnesia!?
Yuzu can't remember anything about her childhood.
But that's not all.
There's another aspect to her amnesia as well.
If something happens to her, it could trigger another lapse in memory.
Y-You mean her memory might disappear?
This time she might forget everything.
I can't believe this! Can't you do something?
I'm sorry, Sinclair-kun.
There's nothing I can do to help her.
Yuzu, open your eyes.
You promised to make stew for dinner, didn't you?
Don't sleep, okay? Wake up!
Please, wake up! Yuzu!
This is her fate.
Is this really the way it's supposed to be?
It's way too harsh on Shinya.
Excuse me. This is the last stop.
The last stop.
[Shinya Sinclair | Pick up Shinya at Kuramachi Station]
[Go with him to the church | Shinya          Wonderful]
Shinya, you're wonderful.
What?
You're wonderful.
Thank you.
I'm Doll-Yuzu! I'll take over speaking for Yuzu!
Why are you laughing?
[Shinya is sad... | I'm also sad.]
[I want to help him. What can I do? | Make him happy.]
[Dinner tonight. | Make stew for Shinya.]
[I hope it will cheer him up.]
Is this what Mao-chan was talking about?
Why didn't I realize it?
Yuzu, I'm here with you.
I'm by your side.
So, please come back.
Shinya-kun, did you stay up all night?
It's my fault this happened to her.
You're wrong. It's not your fault.
Her amnesia started long before she met you!
That doesn't matter.
Ever since I first came to this town, she's been looking after me.
Even so, I failed to realize it.
Shinya-kun...
Yuzu is still alive.
I don't want to lose anyone else... not again...
When Yuzu wakes up, there's a chance she won't remember you.
Can you handle that?
Even if she loses her memory and forgets about me,
she'll still be the same.
I see.
Shinya-kun, now that I know how you feel,
I'll leave her in your hands,
but no matter what happens, don't run away again.
Face whatever happens and accept it.
I wonder if there's something we can do to help them.
I've got it! Hey, Suzuha-chan, give me a hand!
Okay.
Come here!
Yes, come in.
Hello, we're from the cafeteria!
Room service at your disposal...
I haven't asked for anything, though.
Ta-da!
It's a gift from us.
We hope you'll like it.
You're very kind. I'm grateful.
It's been three months.
She still hasn't woken up.
This is a bad sign.
Is this her fate?
Of course, fate can change.
Shinya, show me.
Show me that the two of you can change fate.
Yuzu...
There's nothing. I can't see anything. I feel nothing.
I see, I'm locked in my own mind.
The forgotten past, the vanished memories...
I'll lose everything.
Stil, if that's my fate... I...
I won't be sad.
I have nothing left to be sad about.
No past left to lose.
No precious memories.
Yuzu...
Who are you?
Shinya!
These are my memories of Shinya!
Shinya is inside me!
No, Shinya is disappearing!
My memories of Shinya!
My memories...
Yuzu!
I have wonderful memories.
Memories I don't want to lose or forget.
Yuzu, let's go home.
Shinya! You're my future.
Shinya!
No reaction. Maybe she's tired.
Yuzu!
Shin... ya...
I'm not dreaming, right?
You've woken up.
Yes, I heard your voice.
Thank goodness. You haven't forgotten me.
I haven't.
Shinya, I have wonderful memories of you,
and you are my future as well.
Shinya, when I had nothing, you gave me memories.
I want to do more memorable things with you.
I want to be by your side forever.
Yuzu...
Shinya, I love you.
I love you too, Yuzu.
I don't want to be alone anymore, Shinya.
Yuzu.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm just nervous.
Don't worry. Leave everything to me.
Okay.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
My breasts... are small.
Don't worry.
I want to see them because they're yours.
You're beautiful, Yuzu.
You really mean that?
I got hard just from looking at you.
A-Amazing. I didn't know it could get this big.
It only gets like that when someone I love touches me.
Yuzu!
No... No, stop!
Don't worry, Yuzu.
Shinya...
My body... My body feels strange!
Do you like it?
I don't know. I can't control my body!
I-Incredible!
It's so big.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Don't worry. I'm a grown woman now.
Shinya, how is it? Does it feel good?
Yes, I love it!
Not it's my turn.
No. Stop.
Relax. I want to see it.
Show me everything.
No, stop it. Don't look at me up close.
You're beautiful, Yuzu. I want to lick you.
No, don't.
Shinya, not there! No... Shinya! I... I...
Shinya!
Yuzu, here I go.
Okay.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Now we are one.
That's right. Can you feel me inside of you?
Yes. I can feel you inside me.
Sh-Shinya. Shinya!
Yuzu!
This is so embarrassing. My body... I'm losing my mind.
Does it feel good?
I don't know.
I can feel you inside me, all the way inside me.
— You're opening me up all the way.
— Yuzu...
Yuzu, I love you! I love you, Yuzu!
I love you too, more than anyone else.
I love you, Shinya!
I can't hold back anymore. Yuzu, I'm cumming!
Yes, cum inside me.
Shinya...
Shinya!
Yuzu!
I can feel Shinya. I can feel him inside me.
Shinya...
Yuzu.
Now I have another memory with you.
Thank you, Shinya.
Yuzu...
So what's the story with her illness?
Well, since then, it hasn't happened again.
The doctor is amazed.
Because her illness has no cure, he said it was like a miracle.
Like a miracle...
Where is he anyway? It's getting late.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Sorry, sorry.
There was so much snow to shovel that we were delayed.
You're too late, moron!
Hurry up and go to Narumi!
Are you okay, Shinya?
Shinya!
They haven't changed at all.
Maybe...
No, it's nothing.
anata no shiroi shatsu ookisugite choppiri hazukashii
[Your white shirt is big and embarrassing to wear.]
anata ni tsutsumareteiru mitai de nandaka ureshikunaru
[It feels like you're embracing me, and it makes me happy.]
fuan wo kazoete naitebakari ita kinou made no watashi
[Up until yesterday all I did was worry and cry.]
umarekawareru to oshietekureta
[But you told me it was possible to change.]
anata ga iru kara nanimo kowakunai
[As long as you are here I have nothing to fear,]
unmei mo toki mo koeteku
[neither destiny nor time.]
tsunaida kono te mo hanasanaide
[I will never let go of your hand,]
anata no mirai wa kitto watashi no mirai
[because I'm sure your future and mine are the same.]
That bird... It looks like an angel!