To Narita From Shinobu
Dear Narita...
The Sorceress
Hoshino
Narita...
Mika! Where are you going
at this time of night?
To college for a bit.
You've got to be kidding!
A proper woman doesn't
go carousing at night.
What are you talking about?
I won't be long.
Mika!
What'll I do with her?
Who talks about being
a "proper woman" these days?
Mika!
Hurry and come to breakfast
or you'll be late for college.
Goodness!
Mika. What on earth...?
What happened last night?
I don't want any breakfast.
Mika. What on earth's gotten into you?
Are you hanging around
with a bad crowd?
Good morning...
Enoshima College
That's Hoshino, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey, you!
You're Hoshino, a freshman, right?
What's with all the makeup?
And that lipstick!
How dare you look at me
with such defiance!
It's none of your business.
Now move.
Pardon?!
I said move.
I'll devour you.
Stand! Bow! Be seated!
Lunch time!
Let's hurry and go
to the cafeteria, Mika!
What's wrong? We should hurry.
Not hungry.
What?
I'll wait for you in the cafeteria.
Nobody else is here yet.
This is great! Glad I came early!
What's that?
Here goes!
Mika.
What's the matter, Shinobu?
I saw something weird in the pool.
Really? Shinobu.
I'll show you something
really interesting.
What?
Now, come closer.
What is it, Mika?
I'm scared!
What's going on, Mika?
I won't forgive you!
No! No!
Hey, what is that?
Think it's another replinoid, Iijima?
Yeah, definitely.
She was such a cute woman. The beast!
Whose body is it going to devour next?
There is a witness.
Where?!
A student was drawing by
the pool at about the same time.
She saw somebody running by.
Is that right?
Let's go talk to her.
Quit staring, idiot!
Fine Arts Club
Yeah, I saw her. Just before
class this morning.
Did you see her face?
It was very brief.
I just glimpsed her profile.
Anyway, what's it to you?
I've already told the police everything.
I don't have anything
more to tell you two.
What a terrible morning this has been.
Take a look at this woman.
Yeah, what about her?
Her hair was wet.
She was going the same way
as the woman you saw.
Did she look like this woman?
I was sketching when
I heard a woman's scream.
I turned to look in that direction.
That's not her.
A student would wear a white blouse.
The woman I saw was wearing bright red.
She was wearing red?
Come on, a criminal wouldn't
dress so conspicuously.
Whatever. But I study art,
and I never mistake a color!
You've asked enough questions,
now how about leaving me alone?
Why red clothes?
She's not a firewoman.
Red... red... red...
A red shirt.
On Sale Now!
That's enough for today. I'm going home.
That's strange. I'm sure it was closed.
This red bathing suit
sure is something else!
Bet she's going to take it off soon!
Narita! What are you looking at?
Iijima! What are you wearing that for?!
What do you mean?
What's wrong with my outfit?
Oh, it's a white tank top.
Too bad. Just an afterimage.
Iijima! It was an afterimage!
Hoshino was the killer after all!
Let's get back to college!
Wait!
What was that?
Oh no!
How did you figure it out?
I was too late, Iijima.
If only I'd figured it out
a little sooner.
Narita.
How'd you know that
Hoshino was the killer?
It was an afterimage.
What do you mean, "afterimage"?
Like when you stare at
something yellow...
...then look away at something white.
For an instant, it appears blue.
The other day...
Saiki was drawing trees,
and constantly looking at green.
Suddenly she looked up
to see something white.
She only saw for an instant,
so she mistook white for red.
We learned about color
illusion in art class, right?
The killer was wearing a white blouse.
You're brilliant, Narita!
That means the killer
must be Mika Hoshino!
Maybe.
We've got to do something
before she kills someone else.
But...
But?
Hoshino's not to blame.
It's the replinoids.
Look, I brought the Hero's
Sword you gave me. And this!
I'll destroy the replinoids
and save Saotome!
Lucky Saotome.
Huh?
See you tomorrow.
Mika, what about dinner?
Don't want any. I'm not hungry.
What's gotten into her?
All of a sudden she's wearing makeup,
and she won't eat.
I wonder if she's started going
with a bad crowd.
Maybe she found a boyfriend.
A boyfriend? That's a good one!
It's nothing to laugh about!
Women's Changing Room
If we're going to solve this thing...
Turn around! I'm trying to get changed!
She sure has a great bod.
Let's go find Mika Hoshino.
She hasn't been around since this
afternoon.
Then we have to act quickly.
Narita!
My panties.
You're depraved!
Fine Arts Club
Mika Hoshino.
I've been waiting for you.
You have?
I need to talk to you.
I've had my eye on you.
Hoshino.
I get so flustered and confused
when I think of you.
That's strange. Not a tentacle in sight.
My heart aches for you.
Okay, I get it. But I don't
think this is the time to...
I like you so much.
I do!
Hang on, I don't think this is right...
When another woman gets close
to you, I get so jealous.
Hoshino!
I won't let anyone else have you!
Damn, I can't move! It was you, Hoshino!
Narita!
Narita! Narita!
It might not be too late!
I'll give him this ball,
left from the last replinoid.
What is it, Flash Rabbit?
I see. It was a parasite in Hoshino.
Then it metamorphosed into a replinoid.
That's right! I have to hurry
and give him this ball!
Flash Rabbit, hurry and
give him the ball!
Quit playing with it, stupid!
Put it in his mouth!
Narita!
Oh no!
Drop the gun, Megumi Iijima!
Take off your suit, if you
want to save Narita.
Now!
Okay, I will.
I'm not going to kill you quickly,
Megumi Iijima.
I'll suck your blood very, very slowly.
No! Stop!
How does it feel to have
the life sucked out of you?
Hurry, Narita!
Nice tits.
I'm finished, Narita!
No!
What?!
I'll save you, Saotome.
Narita, you came back to life!
You bastard!
I've had enough of you!
Say your prayers!
Narita!
What? Hoshino?
They've completely merged!
Help me!
Narita.
Hoshino!
Narita!
Take this!
Thank you, Narita.
You bastard!
Are you okay?
Not exactly.
Yeah, I think I got it in the eye, too.
What happened to me?
When you killed that first replinoid...
...there was a glowing ball left behind.
It has the power to bring
you back to life.
What are you talking about?
That thing.
That ball is Hoshino's life.
Narita!
Wait! Let's walk home together!
Sure. Want to go for a tea or something?
By the way...
Sure it's all right? You're positive?
Yeah! I think.
You think?! Oh, I don't feel very good!
Are you okay? Here, I have another one.
Are you sure it's okay
to take these things?
There might be some side effects.
Hey! What do you mean "side effects"?!
You might turn into a replinoid!
A replinoid?!
Just kidding!
Iijima!
Wait!
To Narita From Maiko Saotome