Enoshima College
Women's Locker Room
The Chosen One
What I'd give to nibble on
those big mounds of flesh!
Too much...!
Hey, who turned the lights out?!
Where am I? Who am I?
My goodness!
Mutsumi Narita!
What are you doing?
Iijima.
If it's women's panties you
want to see, here's mine.
No, stop!
What are you doing, Iijima?
Fooled you.
Got my gym shorts on.
Come on, let's get back to rehearsal.
You sure are a pervert, Narita.
She's Megumi Iijima.
We're old friends, and we're
both in the Drama Club.
I think she's got a crush on me.
But I've got my eye on somebody else.
Maiko Saotome.
She's the reason I joined
the Drama Club.
Narita! What are you doing? Hurry up!
Really, Sato?
Yeah. If you can do this, you'll make
the lead for sure.
I'm leaving!
Hey, wait!
Romeo and Juliet, coming November 3rd.
Where's Saotome?
She's not here today.
What's going on between
you two, anyway?!
Don't be stupid, Iijima.
I just meant we can't rehearse
without the lead actress.
Narita, you like Saotome, don't you?
That's ridiculous.
Hara! This is your scene.
Huh?
What's going on? Saotome and Suzuki
aren't here either.
I saw Hara with Sato just now.
She said she wanted to rehearse alone.
That's her.
I'll go get her.
I don't remember a screaming scene.
I wonder if that scream's good enough.
Who's there? Sato?
Sato, I don't know if I can...
What's going on?!
Wow! Brilliant acting, huh?
Yeah, she could go places with that
talent.
Oh my God!
It's Hara! She...!
Sato! What happened to Hara?
I've had a crush on you
for a long time, Narita.
Saotome...
Wait! Maybe we're rushing into this.
Saotome!
Save me, Narita!
I'll save you!
Hang on! I'll come rescue you!
- Narita!
- Romeo!
Saotome!
Juliet!
- Narita!
- Romeo!
- Saotome!
- Juliet!
Oh, Romeo!
How long have you
been sitting here, Iijima?
A while. I've been rehearsing.
But forget that.
You had another dirty dream, didn't you?
It was about our play
for the cultural fair.
I've been having the same
dream ever since that day.
It's Hara! She...!
Sato! What is it? What happened to Hara?
Sato!
Huh? It's locked.
Hara! Hara!
What's wrong! Answer me!
What the...?!
What is it?
Hey, Narita!
What'd you see?
Got to open it! Damn! It's locked from
inside!
Somebody get the key! Hurry!
What's the matter?
Replinoids.
The following is an important
announcement from the dean.
I would like to ask for
your full attention.
About one hour ago...
...there was a terrible
accident at this college.
One of our female students has been
killed.
Let us pray for her soul.
Also, there is another concern about...
...two female students that have been
missing since yesterday.
Keiko Suzuki and Maiko Saotome.
Saotome.
I have to catch whoever's done
this and save Saotome!
Right. I think your dream was a bit
more on the wet side.
What?! I'm really serious about saving
her!
It's only because I was
worried about her.
I knew it! Another
perverted dream of yours.
What's that?!
So I get a hard-on when
I get worried. Big deal!
Hey!
Narita. Iijima.
What's up, Sato?
It's the Drama Club.
The police say...
...we're not allowed in the Drama Room.
They're canceling classes
until the case is solved.
Okay. Thanks.
Sato!
Nothing. Forget it.
Listen, Iijima.
What?
Don't you think he's acting strange?
What do you mean?
I don't know...
...but I have a feeling
he's involved in this mess.
How could he be?
Hara died in a locked room.
Just before she died,
Sato was with Hara.
I heard him talking to
Hara from the hallway.
He said...
"If you can do this,
you'll make the lead for sure."
What? But Saotome's
playing the lead, right?
And nobody knew then
that Saotome was missing!
Yeah. And another thing.
Sato was the first to discover the body.
Wonder what he meant
by "If you can do this..."?
I bet if we figure it out,
we can solve this thing.
Just don't get too involved.
For Saotome's sake
I've got to solve this, or...
...l've got to solve this...
...or...!
And do something about
that filthy mind of yours.
I tell you, I'm seriously
worried about Saotome!
The problem gets bigger and bigger.
The replinoids are finally here.
Unless the replinoids are stopped...
...this College will be drowned in a
sea of blood and despair.
To this sword hilt...
...the power of justice will
form a phantom sword.
But where is the legendary hero?
Iijima! We've caught him!
Hey! This is the Women's Locker Room!
What did I come here for, again?
You said you caught him.
Oh yeah! Sato was the killer after all!
I'll be in the Drama room!
Hurry and come!
Wait a second!
Do not enter
Narita! What'd you do that for?
Some Drama students filled me in, Sato.
You told Hara she'd be the
lead if she could scream well.
So that's what you meant...
But why?
I'll tell you what happened.
He tricked her.
That day...
...remember the first scream we heard?
Hara was practicing, like he told her.
He ran out to get her
and went to where she was.
That's when he killed her.
Then...
He came back, pretending
to have discovered her...
...and acting as if there
was a killer on the loose.
Not a very good act, though.
The last scream we heard
that day was for real.
So that's what happened.
Wait a second. The door was
locked, and from the inside.
That's the only part I can't figure out.
He must have stuck something
through the broken glass...
...and locked it from the outside.
Confess!
Ooh, that feels good!
One of these days,
you're going to be the lead!
Yeah, right!
Hey, what's that?
Who threw that rag onto the wall?
It's moving!
What the...
It's not a bug.
Doesn't look like a slug, either.
No, you're wrong.
Wrong? Which part's wrong?
You're wrong. It wasn't me!
I didn't do anything! Honestly!
Then who did it, Sato? Who's the killer?
Narita... help me. Help me!
Help you?
All right, I'll help.
And you tell me everything.
Who's the killer?
This is the truth...
the God honest truth.
Actually, the killer is...
...the one who killed her is...
I'll dispose of you...
...just like I did those women.
What the hell are you?
And what do you want?
This college is nothing more
than fodder to our kind.
You will not interfere.
I knew it! A replinoid!
Run for it, Narita!
Iijima.
What are you thinking?!
At a time like this!
I get it! It used a tentacle to
lock the door from outside.
Narita! It's dangerous!
I can't breathe!
I never expected to
see you in this era.
I'll suck every last drop
of blood out of you.
No!
No! Stop!
Iijima!
What the hell's going on?
Stop it!
No!
Hurry and grab the hilt, Narita...
Grab it and pray to rescue Saotome.
Pray to rescue Saotome?
Hurry, Narita.
Go to hell, you slimy beast!
This is Keiko Suzuki's pendant.
Suzuki.
Saotome.
What have you done
with Suzuki and Saotome?!
Narita!
Saotome.
Narita! Look out!
My picture.
My precious picture!
You bastard!
Narita! Take the hilt and pray again!
You can do it!
My precious picture!
Saotome! I'll save you!
He is the legendary hero.
You bastard!
Not the tentacles! Aim for his body!
Return Saotome, you beast!
Narita!
You'll be fine.
Narita, you destroyed the replinoid.
Good job.
It's you, Flash Rabbit!
Come here.
Nothing to be afraid of.
You had to follow me, huh?
So even a harmless thing
like you came back in time.
That means all those replinoids
could be here too!
This is terrible! I have
to do something fast!
Or else they'll devour
the entire college!
You're awake, finally.
Ow!
How'd I get in here?
Don't you remember?
No, I feel kind of dazed.
Oh. Well let's just go home.
It's dark out now.
Yeah, okay.
I remember!
Megumi Iijima.
Figured you'd be here.
I remembered what happened yesterday.
I guess it's time I told you the truth.
The truth?
I'm not really Megumi Iijima.
Come to my place after college.
Iijima...
See you tonight!
You're such a bloody pervert!
Get back here!
Getting back to what
you said this morning...
...what do you mean
you're not Megumi Iijima?
This'll be hard to believe,
but I'm here on a special mission.
I came through a time
warp from the year 2112.
Don't be stupid.
We've been friends since grade school.
A month ago I reprogrammed
all the students' memories.
The daughter in this family
was my age, but she died.
So what's this mission of yours?
To follow the replinoid
invasion of this world...
...from the future, and
come up with a solution.
So you came from the future?
This is my true appearance.
What's that animal?
It's a kind of replinoid too.
But it's harmless, don't worry.
I want to show you something.
Come with me.
Never knew a place like this
was so close to the college.
But it's pitch black in there.
No problem. He'll show us the way.
Let's go.
It's a dead-end.
This is my Time Capsule.
Unreal!
Tell me the rest of your story.
Our world isn't peaceful and
happy like this world.
In our era, there lives an
evil beast called Black Murder...
...which gives birth to
thousands of creatures.
We call them replinoids.
The replinoids feed on
the bodies and blood of humans.
And they have a particular
fondness for young women.
The replinoids have almost
wiped out our generation.
With those tentacles?
Right.
They entered a time warp
to come to Enoshima College.
They possessed Sato as a cover...
...and they're waiting to seize the
chance to leech us alive.
If we don't do something,
they'll devour us all!
It's too unreal.
Narita. Take this.
I used that last night!
That's right. Take it once more,
and think of Saotome.
This sword has long been kept
in one of our museums.
Only one man has ever
been able to bring it to life.
It's the sword of a hero.
The sword of a hero?
Yes. And you are that hero.
You destroyed the replinoid
that invaded the college.
You are the chosen one
who can rescue Saotome.
Saotome.