You're so damn pert!
Ouch!
You actually like being bullied,
don't you?
- Well?
- Oh, no!
God damn you! I'm bleeding!
You'll pay
a high price for this!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Be still, will ya?
Okay. Spread her legs.
What?
Oh, no-- Stop!
What a scorcher!
I can't take it!
What the hell?
What was that about?
Professor!
What is it, Yukika?
Ms. Nogami, sir.
Be that as it may, I request
we evacuate at once!
- Yeah, let's go!
- We'd better run quick!
You have nothing to worry about.
As long as I don't press
this button right here.
Professor, what have you done?
You're onto me, huh?
I like that--
You're Yuo Yamao, right?
I don't mind a woman like you.
I made it myself.
It's pretty powerful.
That one just now was
a timer-operated model.
This and all the other bombs
are remote-controlled.
I can detonate them at will
with this controller.
Of course, I've got some set up
here in this room.
No way. Why?
Please stop, Professor!
It's too late, Yuo.
It's already begun.
There's no turning back.
Nobody can stop it now.
You know...
I've always had my doubts about
the current educational system.
Knowledge by itself
is absolutely useless.
One must know
how to use it and why.
But this system is not meant
to teach you any of that.
It's wrong to just shove it
all down your throat.
So, I thought I would give you
my own special lesson.
The kind of lesson that
nobody else can teach...
"To know and understand one's path
is to die without regret."
- Know what I mean?
- You must be joking!
Why should I go along
with this nonsense?
I don't care what you do,
but I ain't getting mixed up!
If you wanna die, do it alone!
What's with the lamp?
It's warning that
the safety's disarmed.
With one touch of the button...
the whole university will
vanish without a trace.
Do you want me to end it
once and for all?
No! Please stop!
He's bluffiing!
"Bloody feisty in the morning,
dead as a doornail by the evening."
Get it?
What the hell!?
Can't you see he's serious?
Good for you,
Mr. Chemistry Club Member.
You realize it's neither
a bluff nor a mere threat.
I'm so tickled.
Know what?
We've got a long road ahead.
Why don't you be my assistant,
Mr. Mitsuya Kamishiro?
If you insist.
It's settled then!
Wait, wasn't there another
club member in this room--
There you are...
Mr. Naoto Murano, yes?
You'll be my assistant too.
Okay?
Oh, this is just great!
I'm so excited about this!
If only you were usually
this obedient...
my job would be so much easier.
Kanon.
You don't think you can get off
with a slap, do you?
What?
I'll appoint you as the first
subject of my special lesson.
- Ms. Motoi?
- Yes?
You can slap her.
What?
Haven't you had enough
of her bullying?
Go ahead and slap her.
But I--
Need I remind you of
what I saw earlier?
Oh, no! Please stop!
It ain't bad losing
your virginity to a mop.
If Mr. Murano hadn't
happened to come by...
it would have been
a real mess, no?
Don't you want to take revenge?
A cold-blooded bitch like her
should feel pain for herself.
Don't you agree?
What's the matter?
Do you mean to disobey me?
If so, I'll just have to
make you a subject too.
What?
That's outrageous, Professor!
Oh, you're against me too?
Mr. Kamishiro,
take care of her.
Don't!
Naoto.
"Depart ye; it is unclean--"
Don't touch me!
Don't you touch her!
Oh, my! My assistants are
having disagreements already?
That's a sad, sad thing.
By the way, I see you're
very learned, Mitsuya.
You've just quoted the Bible.
That's so stupid!
Why hurry off to death when
my lesson has yet to begin?
Anyhow, you're up fiirst,
Ms. Motoi.
Tawa!
Naoto.
No way.
One moment, Mitsuya.
Yes...
Murano, first...
we experiment with the physiological
structure of the human body.
I need your help with
our test subject, Ms. Motoi.
For the best possible view,
have her kindly strip for us, please.
Oh, no.
Ms. Motoi, be still.
Or else he might cut
more than what's necessary.
You have not only a baby face
but also an undeveloped body.
You should have reached
full growth by now.
Mitsuya, would you mind
lifting her pants up a little?
Women lack such male features
as the scrotum and the penis.
- See that?
- It hurts!
There's nothing down there,
you see?
Ms. Motoi, stick out your butt,
so everyone gets a good look.
That's right.
Mitsuya, will you
pull down her undies...
and show us
what she's all about?
No, don't look! Please!
Now I'd like you to observe
the female urinary system.
Instead of the penis...
women have a tiny hole called
the urethral opening.
That's where their pee comes out.
This drug will help
demonstrate my point.
It's so powerful
it'll work in no time.
It's started to work.
Please let me use the toilet.
No can do.
But you can use this instead.
Ms. Motoi must be dying
to pee just about now.
Oh, why not? Go already.
We're waiting, Ms. Motoi.
It's not healthy to hold it in.
No.
That's one way you get a bladder
infection. My father told me.
So let it go.
No! Don't look! Please!
You pissed a lot!
Tawa, thank you for
the great demonstration.
You're next, Kanon.
No!
You wouldn't do such a horrible
thing to me, would you?
Next we use Ms. Enami here for
an experiment on pain receptors.
No! Stop!
No!
How does it feel, Mitsuya?
Nice?
You earned that reward.
Tawa my dear,
you're remarkably obedient.
I suppose
it's a form of virtue.
Goes to show you...
the humans are an odd
species of animal, indeed.
I'm gonna cum!
Let's start our experiment
on Kanon, shall we?
Mitsuya, would you fondle
her breasts for us?
Well, aren't they soft?
With her formidable size,
she'll make a fine subject, I think.
I know about you.
Your bullying habit goes
way beyond Tawa, am I right?
All living things have
"nociceptors."
They're the receptors of pain
in the skin and flesh.
For instance.
It hurts, doesn't it?
But the breast is mostly
made up of fat.
While she feels the pain,
she's in no mortal danger.
So why, you might ask,
does it hurt so much?
The female breast is a crucial
organ for rearing children.
Therefore it's armed with
extra sensitivity as a protection.
So you see--
"Protect me. Let's get out of
this trouble immediately."
It sends a signal of pain
to the brain.
Painful?
I see, but I'm afraid
I can't stop yet.
Above all...
the nipple is the most crucial,
as it dispenses milk to babies.
Naturally it's one of
the most sensitive parts.
It might be the most
developed body part of all...
when it comes to nociceptors.
Oh, my. It's not over yet.
Mitsuya, wake her up, please.
There's an important
experiment to finish.
Yes, Professor.
Good. Stick your finger in there
and rub her real good.
When a pain persists beyond
the point one can tolerate...
the brain excretes an endorphin
similar to morphine.
This blissful substance functions
as a pain suppressor.
Then the pain slowly
turns into pleasure.
What a well-designed organism
the human body is.
The blissful substance stirs up
the core of pleasure.
It gives us the will to live.
It revives our so-called
survival instinct.
Invigorates us, you know?
Now that she's invigorated...
let us induce pain in another
part that's even more sensitive.
How's that, Kanon? Good?
Or is it merely painful?
Too bad, she's fainted.
I guess we'll never
know the answer.
- Hey, that's a TV chopper.
- We're rescued now!
Just as I planned.
It was I who informed them.
I told them all about the bombs
and about myself.
Yoshihiko Ohse!
Are you there?
Answer if you can hear us!
I know you can hear us, Ohse!
Will someone please draw
the curtains over the windows?
You don't want to get
sniped, do you?
Here! We're right here!
Professor, please stop this now.
There's no way in hell you could
win against that many people!
Keep it down, will you?
Well, let's see.
Oh, right, the people outside?
Actually the bombs are not
only inside the building.
They're also buried
in the ground.
If I were to blow the remaining
bombs all at once...
everyone on the premises would be
blown away without a trace.
These bombs are that powerful!
It can't be--
But this must be kept secret
from the people outside.
Or else someone might get
a naughty idea...
Oh, I know!
Yukika, will you tell them
not to get any foolish ideas?
Tell them there are
a lot of hostages at stake?
Yes.
Not like that though.
I mean, you have media out there.
Gotta give them more impact.
First off, I think
you can lose the clothes.
Mr. Kamishiro, Mr. Murano.
Yes.
No!
Please go away.
Why don't you all give a hand?
You guys are all joking, right?
Please stay away!
No! No!
Stop! No!
Yours are a different size
and shape from Ms. Enami's.
No, stop.
They feel a little harder
to the touch.
But this might make them as big
as Ms. Enami's, if not bigger...
the professor has
kindly suggested--
Well, look at that.
Looks much bigger.
- Stop! It hurts!
- I'll squeeze this one too.
No! Please stop! It hurts!
It hurts! Stop it!
Ready to say hello
to the people down there?
It hurts. Please, stop.
Hey, look at that!
Please don't! Stop!
What are they doing?
It's dangerous!
Wow! You can really
hang someone by the tits.
Pull her up, guys!
Well? Did you say hello
to everyone down there?
I'm asking you a question!
Don't!
Please don't look! Help me!
Don't look! Please don't!
All right, that's enough.
This time, a hello from below.
Guys, please?
What are you doing? Stop!
No! Don't!
No!
I see you.
It's tight. You nervous?
Know what might work?
My father made this muscle
relaxer for my shoulder aches.
I've got to give them
a good look inside too.
No. Stop. Please.
No. Stop it.
It's gotten much softer.
But my fingers are numb too.
How about this instead?
No! Don't! Please.
Wow! It goes in smooth.
It's still pretty tight deep inside.
I'll move it, okay?
I guess this is
what they were waiting for.
Go on, say hello.
Oh, no! Stop!
Mitsuya's become quite
a performer, indeed.
I don't see the need for
any more directions.
Here I come.
No!
A great shot,
don't you think, Yukika?
Frankly, the Japanese media is
so shameless if you ask me.
Just look at it.
- Holy shit! You can see it all!
- No touch-ups, man.
The truth is,
I sent an E-mail earlier saying...
"If you dare try any video FX,
I'll pull the trigger at once."
No!
Calm down, Yukika.
It's all right now.
Please calm down.
No. No.
It's all right now. Don't worry.
Professor,
the secretary's fallen apart.
I'm amazed at how fragile
the human spirit is.
I won't forgive you.
Your behavior is inhuman!
Really? So what are you going
to do about it, huh?
There's nothing I can do now.
But you haven't seen
the last of me yet!
Oh, I love it!
You're something else, Yuo.
I don't mind
your type of women at all.
In a field with
an oppressive fragrance
A proud and pristine flower blooms
The wind scatters its petals
They fly high up in the air
dancing haphazardly
At the bottom of the valley
a murky backwater gleams
I'll sail a boat named Lust
And drift aimlessly
through unknown places
Only to arrive
at a defiinite destination
So here I go
The flower, the moon, the world
Mark my name, my existence
Mark them firm and deep
Mark them till it hurts,
so it can't be erased
Recognize the sacred love
in my name, in my existence
I'll take this ache and
turn it into pleasure
Such is the power of temptation
I am about to
open its door for you