Professor Ohse!
Are you there?
Oh, it's you, Professor Kumehara.
You were out with a cold.
So why do you have to stick
your butt in my business now?
Professor Ohse, listen to me.
You've already killed or injured...
over a hundred college students
and faculty members.
You must release the hostages
at once and come out of there!
I don't know
what your demands are.
But if you must
take a hostage--
If you must...
I, as a professor, will let you take
me hostage if you let them go.
What a cheap, trite line!
Don't make me laugh!
Mitsuya, you carry a cellular,
don't you?
Yes.
Professor Kumehara.
Mr. Kamishiro, Mr. Murano.
Are you all right? Are you
the only ones released?
Hi, Professor Kumehara.
Professor Ohse!
I admired your
courageous remark earlier.
Nevertheless, I'm not
as stupid as you may think.
Did you really think I was going
to fall for that trap?
Trap? But it wasn't!
Whatever you say, Professor,
but I need some sort of proof.
Proof?
What do you mean?
Right. We can start by checking
for hidden wiretaps and such.
Please take off everything
you're wearing.
But why is that necessary?
Are you telling me that you can't?
Does that mean
your earlier remark was a lie...
just a load of crap
designed to hide the truth?
I'm relieved actually.
It's nice to know that
you are only human after all.
The self-love obviously comes
first and foremost.
Fine! I'll get undressed.
I'll do anything you say.
But you must absolutely
guarantee the hostages' safety.
We'd better throw some light
on you while we're at it.
Enjoy the show, Inspector.
I don't see anything
suspicious so far.
Let's check your underwear next.
Mitsuya, that should satisfy your
concern; nothing more please.
I think Professor said,
"Everything you're wearing."
I let you off the hook for now.
I'll be waiting for you,
Professor Kumehara.
What do you mean? Where?
In the chemistry lab, of course,
where everyone else is.
What in the world?
What has happened here?
Thanks for coming,
Professor Kumehara.
Professor Ohse, whatever have
you done to these poor women?
Why the hell
don't you say something?
Mitsuya, you haven't finished
checking her thoroughly for the wire...
am I correct?
Not yet.
What do you guys want?
They all want to help with the search.
But can you blame them?
Finish what we started--
Shall we get on with it then?
No!
Stop! No!
Damn, these huge tits are
gonna be a handful to search.
Mitsuya, you won't fiind
anything that way.
Yes.
Is that breast milk?
Oh, my!
Is that a physiological
abnormality, or is it the pills?
The pills cause a pregnancy-like
condition to suppress ovulation.
In some rare cases,
this has been known to happen.
You'd better watch those pills.
I wanna squeeze them.
Don't be ridiculous!
It's alright; go ahead
and squeeze, Mitsuya.
I understand that breasts get
painfully bloated from milk.
I'm not bloated!
I know about this.
When women get sexually aroused,
their breasts swell up.
I've heard my father say that.
Please stop.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's see how much milk
you can make for me to squeeze.
Are you ready?
I see your breasts are swollen.
Right, Professor?
Hey, it's not coming out.
Kinda tricky.
Is it like this, or--
Help me out, will ya?
C'mon!
I got it!
So this is how it tastes.
How sweet.
Your breast milk is absolutely
delicious, Professor!
Well, well.
Whatever happened to
the body search?
Here you go.
That's the last one.
It's all right.
Not much damage.
Look, no bleeding.
Pull yourself together.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I've been such a bully.
Let's just forget it, okay?
We bring you a special report on
the ongoing hostage situation...
at Aoi University.
The bombing suspect barricaded
there has been identifiied...
as Yoshihiko Ohse, a chemistry
professor at the university.
In this program, we'll unmask
the man behind the mystery.
I see the media's already
having a field day with this.
Suckers!
Our researchers have dug
deep into Ohse's past.
And in doing so, they have
come across an intriguing fact.
This discovery led us to
a certain woman...
who may very well
hold the key to this incident.
We've obtained her photo.
Take a look.
She is none other than
Ohse's older sister.
She was also a professor.
But after engaging in improper
relations with a male co-ed--
Now I remember!
She's that slut who seduced him
with her filthy mouth.
She preyed on not only one
but a few others at the time.
What a scandal!
No! Let go of me!
No! Please stop!
No!
The incident came to light
resulting in her dismissal.
Her teaching license was
also revoked.
Naturally.
However, later investigation
raised the possibility that...
it might have been a rape.
Where are you going, Sis?
Since her suicide,
the matter has become hazy.
Sister!
- Stop it.
- Our theory is that...
her suicide was in defense of
the co-ed she was trying to protect.
- Stop it!
- What? That's impossible.
Stop it!
She must have reacted to
the negative publicity.
That's a bunch of bullshit!
It was you!
You people ganged up against her
and drove her to it!
Because of you, my dear sister
ended up-- she ended up--
Professor--
The fucking media, the police,
the ignorant public--
The whole world conspired
to murder her!
This sugar-coated idea of
"holy profession" is for the birds.
When something happens...
we're always the first ones
on your suspect list.
The police, the media, and
you with the victim complex!
You don't give a damn
about the truth!
I can't--
I will not forgive you!
Yoshihiko!
Yuo?
Sister dear?
Can't be--
But you had me fooled
for a second there.
There is something about you
that reminds me somewhat...
of my dear sister.
l--
Yoshihiko Ohse!
Can you hear me?
What the heck is going on?
What happened to Kumehara?
Is anybody hurt?
Answer me, Yoshihiko Ohse!
Oh, I get it.
That's how you knew my name.
Alright. It's so nice of you to offer
to be my next subject, my dear.
Enough, Ohse!
What are you saying Murano?
What's gotten you so agitated
all of a sudden?
Oh, I see.
Mr. Murano, let's see
how determined you are.
Why don't you go make love
with Yuo on the roof...
in front of the media?
Oh, no?
You don't want to?
I thought you'd rather
do it with him.
- Too bad. Mitsuya!
- Yes.
Will you do it for Mr. Murano?
- Wait.
- Yuo.
I'd rather...
do it with you, Naoto.
Yuo?
Yuo, are you sure about this?
I mean, with me?
Yuo--
Naoto--
Naoto, I--
Yuo, you're so beautiful.
Yuo.
You're lovely, Yuo.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
This is just incredible.
Yuo...
Beautiful.
No... I'm embarrassed.
You're beautiful, Yuo.
Oh, gosh.
Here I come.
Naoto... I--
Yuo!
Naoto!
You guys make me wanna puke.
Humping like animals
in front of a TV audience...
so that all the world can watch
with depraved indifference.
Hey, I know!
You like to be watched, right?
You don't get turned on
unless someone's watching you do it.
That's why you guys were
showing off, right?
- Mitsuya--
- If you like it so much...
why don't you and I put on
a show for them this time?
- No! Naoto!
- Yuo!
Mitsuya, don't do it!
C'mon, let's show it off.
Stop it!
Don't you touch her!
I'll show you
I'm much better than Naoto.
No!
I beg you. Please stop!
I don't care what happens to me.
Stop torturing Yuo!
Why should you have all the fun?
Is that fair, Yuo?
You feel so good inside.
It's so warm and nice.
Here I come!
No! No! No!
Okay, your turn.
What?
I can't possibly satisfy her
exhibitionist urge all alone.
They can help her too.
Oh, no. Don't--
No!
That's right. Let them watch.
I'm live at the scene--
What on earth is happening?
A group of male hostages are
assaulting a female hostage.
I have no idea what is going on
around here anymore.
No. Please stop.
Stop it!
Stop torturing my sister!
Mitsuya.
Serves them right!
All blown away like garbage.
I did it, Sis.
I really gave it to them!
Now as for the survivors...
I'm going to sell you
as slaves on the internet!
Come see the grand opening
of the cyber slave market!
Mitsuya...
Where have you been?
Oh, it really doesn't matter.
Here, shoot them with this camera.
I'm going to play it live
on the Internet.
I'm doing a popularity contest.
The poll will determine
who's the sexiest here.
I understand...
Professor...
Shit! What the hell is
going on in there?
Inspector, it's horrible!
Look at this!
What the heck are they doing?
I hate you. I hate you.
I hate all of you.
Mitsuya, come here.
Mitsuya.
Tawa... I--
For the longest time,
I've been in love with you, Mitsuya.
Oh, dear.
You're acting like a baby.
I just wanted somebody
to tell me that they love me.
Since my mom died,
nobody has ever-
It's all right now.
You got me.
But Tawa, I did such a horrible,
horrible thing to you.
Still I can't help
loving you regardless.
I'm sorry, Tawa.
Well, what do you know.
A million hits just like that!
People, that's enough for now.
The hits are through the roof.
What the hell is all this about?
Mitsuya, tell everyone to
quit this orgy shit right now!
Mitsuya.
Tawa. My Tawa.
What the hell is going on?
What is this?
What the hell is this?
How could you? You shouldn't
have gotten so carried away.
Stop it,
you subhuman animals!
Don't you have any pride
as a human being?
That's it! I'll end it all!
Stop it, Yoshihiko.
Let's not do this anymore.
No way, it just can't be.
Yoshihiko, let's leave it at this.
Sister, is that really you?
I--
Sister, I missed you so much!
Yoshihiko.
Why? Why did you die?
How could you die and leave me
behind all alone in this crummy world?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for leaving you and
making you feel so lonesome.
Sister! Sister!
I've been watching you.
I always will.
So you're not all alone.
Sister, I did as you said and
made those bombs you mentioned.
Just like you said
in your E-mail...
the reason you came back is...
because I took revenge on
those who did you wrong.
Isn't that right?
It was me.
I sent you the mail.
Mitsuya.
I was also unhappy all alone.
I study like hell to become
a doctor like my father says.
But that kind of life seems
so pointless and vain.
I felt I'd be better off dead.
So I figured to get revenge...
I'd provoke Professor
to make bombs and--
But you're not alone anymore.
I won't leave you alone
Mitsuya, my darling.
Yoshihiko, you must make amends
for the wrong you've done.
It's for your own sake too.
Every person has two lives.
One for living and one to
leave behind in people's memory.
The latter is eternal.
It lives on forever as long as
they remember you...
for all the good and bad.
Do you understand?
I understand, Sister.
Oh, no!
Over the forest that shines
in the afterglow
A bird dances about
drawing circles in the sky
Then it prepares to bury
its claw on a prey
As if carrying out
heaven's will
The pale moon lies
on the bottom of the water
It flutters a shell of gaiety
I'll drift aimlessly
at the edge of mystery
Only to arrive
at a defiinite destination
So here I go
The flower, the moon, the world
Mark my name, my existence
Mark them firm and deep
Mark them till it hurts,
so it can't be erased
Recognize the sacred love
in my name, in my existence
I'll take this ache and
turn it into pleasure
Such is the power of temptation
I am about to
open its doors for you
The flower, the moon, the world
Mark my name, my existence
Mark them firm and deep
Mark them till it hurts,
so it can't be erased
For you, I'll burn out
all the life that's left in me