WICKED LESSONS
Part One
My parents are gone...
They died together...
It was a car accident...
My stepbrother and I are from
our parents' previous marriages.
I haven't seen him in six years.
He came back after he
heard about the accident.
For some reason he hated dad,
so he also hated his new family.
He left the house right after
he graduated high school...
...and never came to visit.
I looked up to my new father
and brother when I was young...
...and I loved them greatly.
Although my brother would distance
himself from our parents...
...I remember him being kind
to me because I was younger.
Brother...
We only have each other now...
Let's get along.
Just the two of us.
That's right.
That means I'm your guardian now.
You have to listen to what I tell you.
That hurts! Stop brother!
No! Stop, brother! Please!
No! Stop! Brother!
Stop!
N... No, don't!
Shut up!!
Brother... You're terrible...
I've always loved my brother.
I've never been able to
get serious with a guy...
...because I loved my brother so much.
But this...
You're getting raped, but you're feeling it.
Th... That's not true...
Don't lie! Your pussy is dripping wet!
Now you're a real woman...
But maybe I was waiting for this day...
The day when we would make love...
Brother... I... I... It feels so good!
Your dick is filling me up...
It's all the way inside...
It feels so good.
I'm gonna cum.
Yes! I feel like I'm going to go crazy!
I'm so happy.
We're going to be together now...
Let's make love like this every day.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just needed a fuck
because it's been awhile.
You're going to transfer to
Takamine College tomorrow.
It's a boarding college...
...so I'm going to sell this
house sometime soon.
But...! I thought we were going to be
able to live together from now on...
I'll be working there as a professor,
so you'll see me everyday.
You're going to report everything
about the students to me.
Every prestigious college
has their problems.
Brother, what are you...
You just listen to what I say!
Don't do such terrible things! Why
can't we live happily together?
You're the only one I have now!
Brother!
Just do what I say! I won't
allow you to talk back!
Takamine College
Director's Office
My apologies. I should really be the
one talking to you about it, but...
Director's Office
It's okay. I hear you're really
busy with the election.
Yes, I think it's going to be okay, but
this is the first time I'm running, so...
...reading the polls doesn't
make much sense to me.
It's going to be like this until election day.
Elena is late...
No! Stop! Please!
Father, it's Elena.
Come in.
You're late. That's not the way
you should treat a new professor.
I'm sorry.
This is my daughter Elena.
She's only a third year student...
...but she'll be running the college
during the election period.
Nice to meet you. I'm Elena Takamine.
I'm Shuichi Kano. Nice to meet you too.
I have to go, but the new
dean will tell you everything.
Dad, do you have everything?
I do, but I almost forgot my goodbye kiss.
How embarrassing.
Please excuse us. We forgot
we have company. Goodbye.
Sorry about that.
My father can't get it through
his head that I'm an adult now.
I'm sure every father is like that.
Yes, this is the Director's
office. My father's not in.
What? Oh, that's not good.
Okay, I'll be right there.
I'm sorry. Something
important just came up.
I'll have someone else
come in and talk to you.
No problem.
Hi, it's Elena. Is there a
professor that can come in?
That's amazing. You graduated
from an American university?
I wouldn't be able to do that.
A Japanese classics professor
wouldn't need to go abroad.
That's true. But I'm still impressed.
What's wrong?
It's nothing. Shall we?
Huh? Professor Kano. You
know where the gymnasium is?
Yes. I got here early, so I took a walk.
Phys-Ed sucks!
I told the teacher I have my period!
I did too!
Hey, you three!
Oh...
It's Haruko.
You scared us!
They're triplets.
Haruko's with a guy!
Is he your boyfriend?
I knew you had it in you!
You're wrong! He's...
It's all right!
I thought you were married to your job!
Hey, did you fuck him already?
Of course she did. Who can resist these!
Oh, Haruko! You're so cute!
I'm Kano, the new professor.
I'll be introduced at the
morning meeting tomorrow.
A professor!?
Unfortunately for you three, I just
met Professor Misaka today...
There are no juicy stories
like you three are hoping for.
But Haruko is a catch you know!
I don't need to see the inside of the gym.
Can you take me somewhere else?
Y... yes.
All dorm rooms are doubles, except
for the director's daughter's room.
She's my sister.
Nice to meet you. I'm Noelle Kano.
She's Professor Misaka. She's
showing me around the school.
Hello.
She's my roommate. Shirone Takamine.
Takamine?
She's the director's niece.
Her parents passed away
when she was young...
...and the director took her in.
She grew up with Elena, but their
personalities are very different.
The cafeteria is down the hall.
Find out about the
Takamine family from her.
That's it for today. Next class is a
lab, so make sure you go there.
Hey!
Sorry!
Thank you very much.
It's not the first time, is it?
Please don't tell anyone at the college!
I'm getting bullied by my
students... It's embarrassing.
I understand. It's a prestigious college,
but it seems to have its troubles.
If it's all right with you,
could you tell me more?
You've been here longer, so...
Sure, if it'll help you.
No... Stop... Please...
Stop? Did you really think I
asked you to come this late...
...so we could talk about the college?
You didn't get a chance to
take a shower, did you?
I can taste the day's filth. Perverted
old men would die to taste this.
There's no use in crying.
Acting tough doesn't suit you.
Are you feeling it?
Don't lie.
You're not a virgin, but
you're still inexperienced.
You're wet... You're ready then...
Relax... Let me in... Enjoy it.
This is amazing. I can fit more!
I bet I could fist fuck you.
Use your lips and tongue.
Yeah... Just like that...
I'm not interested in what
you were going to tell me.
I'm interested in what you
have to say from this point on.
As a female professor, you're going to
find out the truth about this college.
You're going to find out the most
scandalous information for me.
Do it faster!
Faster. Faster!
Yes, it feels so good! It's never felt like this!
I feel like I'm burning inside... I
feel like I'm going to go crazy...
Yes!
I'm going to die!
Want to do this again?
Yes! Again!
Then listen to me! You're
going to work for me!
Yes! I'll do anything! I'll be your slave!
Yes! That's a good girl! I'm gonna cum!
Nothing?
I can't get anything out of
Shirone. She barely says hi to me.
Fine. I'll do something about it.
Brother, what are you up to?
Please tell me. I'm sure I
could help, if I knew more.
Don't make me repeat
myself. Just do as I say.
What are you doing?
I know I can't get away.
Have your way with me.
I didn't come here for this.
I want to find out secrets of
the Takamine family from you.
There's nothing to tell.
Is that it? If that's it, I
have things to do, so...
Wait. I can't just let you go...
I'll ask your body...
You didn't think your first time
was going to be like this, did you?
Is this what you do with Noelle?
You...
It'll be easier to fuck me like this.
And here I thought you were a
virgin... You're full of surprises.
Well? Are you going to fuck me or not?
Who trained you so well?
The director took her in.
It can't be!
Who cares about that. I made
you cum... Now it's your turn.
This is amazing...
It feels incredible. He's been
fucking you all this time...
Shit!
Yes... It feels so good.
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Yes! It feels so good!
It's bigger and harder than
uncle's... it's amazing!
I'm gonna cum!
Do you hate him?
You hate him, don't you?
I may be able to help you get revenge.
In return, can you help me?
Takamine College Faculty Housing
Finally, the time to execute
my plan has come.
It feels so good! Yes...
Brother... What are you thinking?
You're scaring me...