I was five years old when my father died in a traffic accident
It was a horrible affair
I cried a lot when he died
I kept trying to get him to wake up
Mother held me gently
She told me my father had traveled ot a different world
I could not understand her at such a young age
My mother always holds me with a smile when I cry
I was unable to stop crying
Mom gently stroked my head
Like my father's big hands my mom held me with her slender warm fingers
From that day warm fingers have become a part of me
Since very early I have learned to depend on my mother
But mother married before splitting the family assests
So mother did not get any of the assests
Mother alone raised me
As mother and daughter we didn't spend a lot of time together
Becuase my mother was busy working, she di not have any leisure time
So we treausre our time together
Although sometimes I feel lonely
However my mother's care has made my life happy
One day my mother met the former principal of my school
The company she was working for was operating with the school
Then she became the principal of the school
At that time I decided my dream
In order to help my mother I wanted to be a teacher
The first step to this dream was to enter my mother's school
My mother was pleased
I have never seen my mother that happy since my father died
Seeing her similing happily made me happy
Knowing I could do something for my mother
Mother was busy like before
I can only see her during breakfast
We lived two different lives
However our bond between mother and daughter is unchanged
My mother thinks this too I believe
Until yesterday
This is a school matter
This morning hidden cameras were installed on campus
What would happen if they saw you as my slave
Put these clothes on
You will go to school in those clothes
But no underwear
I will be in the wireless communications room
I will check to make sure you didn't wear any panties or bra
If you do not comply you will be punished like yesterday
It is not good
that kind of appearance
It was a bad experience
Moreover
My friend's were talking about how you resemble a young girl from a cartoon
You came back so late, I was wondering if something had happened
I am sorry mother
I must not seem like that cartoon's heroine
You are to boring to be such
and not active enough
Therefore you draw this analogy
Yes, that is the case
Mother looks down upon me
You have turned into that rotten man's toy
I will be despised
because my daughter has become that man's toy to protect me
If that's the case I will not bother with that degree of man
These words sever our mother-daughter relationship
I do not care what happens now
I will now eat quickly and go take a bath
There is practice tomorrow early at 12
I need to rest before it
Mother has abandoned me
I can not live anymore
I hope I die soon
If I was dead, then that person
the matter with that person would be handled
What, ah
Quickly, stop, it's cold
Only letting you spurt milk would be unfair.
This time you can drink milk too.
Here is some more
Too fast, stop, I beg you
The icy cold thing is going into my ass, stop quickly
You do not mention the health benefits of milk
Especially in the bathroom
Do not, Stop, No, ah, it is already
If the meat slave still talks it will be filled more
It doesn't matter, I am already full
If you stop talking, then I will stop filling
To do such a thing
If you do not hurry your stomach will burst
I said stop, quickly
Please do not fill again
Then be an obedient slave and listen
You lied, you said you would stop
It's no good, I can't be filled anymore
This is not fair to me
Please forgive me
I will break soon, I am going to break
It feels good to be filled
You have been filled so much
It hurts, don't fill me anymore
I am need to go to the bathroom quickly
What will you do to stop the filling
I cannot bear this good feeling
Now you are fed, but cannot rest
Do not rest
Your master will award his lustful slave's body with his cock
Say thank you at least
Do not like, it hurts
You should say thanks
That is how you reply
Thanks
This is the proper response to your master
Remember it well
I cannot bear it already
Please let me go to the bathroom
Do not make fun of going ot the bathroom, semen toilet
It is very hard, do not insert
It will soon feel good
Do not put it in me like this
I said it will feel good soon
It feels good
Stop
I feel very good
I am going to cum
I am going ot cum in you and get you pregnant
I beg you, do not cum
I will get pregnant with a baby, ah
Are you saying...
Before you get pregnant with a baby I need to cum inside
Slaves have no choice
No, I do not want to get pregnant
Do not cum inside me
This is the second time I am cumming today
No, I do not want to give birth to a child
He is cumming
He is cumming inside me
I am really going to get pregnant
Do not, ah
No, quickly stop, ah, ah
It was so good you burst
I am not happy
You have no sense of honor worthless slave
We must continue
Do not come
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Yesterday's situation looked really bad
The situation is good this morning
She is almost completely captured
What game will we play today
I'm sorry I have been unfair
Considered us close to finished
Come in
You have the properly gone to school without underwear or bra
You must do anything
I want you to die
Die with me
Normal people do not try to kill each other
Why, how
In the uniform you cut a hole
How could
Die with me
I don't think so
I have not been good
I no longer have a place in this world
Origianally I was with my mother
That was the only place I had
I have been abandoned
There is no place for me to live
You say you were abandoned by the principal
That is what I said
Is that what happened
It is said I look like a cartoon heroine
who sold her body to a man to protect her mother
If so how do I become a
So she severed our relatioship
You talk so much I could die of boredom
Don't you know
It was my plan to have me be a teacher and work with my mother
I want my mother to be happy with me
I have  been working to this day, but was abandoned
I have no place to live now
Then die
It is your fault I want to die
Who is it
who did this to become a teacher for her mother
Your view is to simple
What kind of teacher would you make with that feeling
What can of teacher would you make if you did not consider your students views
I thought I said you could not do things without my permission
This
I did not give you permission to kill yourself or others
You want me and yourself to die
You want to die, then go, go, go and die
You didn't think I could be killed that easily, did you
Take the other side of the knife
It is very painful to cut open the stomach
It is hard to die while enduring such pain
To watch their internal organs fall out
It is a pain from hell
How is this
You aren't very smart
if this is how you wanted to die
I don't want to die that way
You don't actually have to kill anyone
The principal was very mean to you
You are more worthless than a dog
You are a pig who wants to die
What should I do
I have no will to live and nowhere to go
I can get you a place to live
You will be lower than a dog, a pig
You will live as my slave
There is nothing to consider
You only need to consider how to please me
Slave
Today I am your master
and you will be a good slave to me
Starting today you have a place to live
My place
This is the right place for you
Promise to be my slave
Or I will abandon you like your mother did
Or would you rather die
I do not want such a life
Okay I promise, I promise
Otherwise I will throw you out
Do not abandon me, I promise
I promise to be your slave from today on, do not abandon me
Who is the master
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, master
Today, I am my master's slave
I was already your thing
So do not abandon me
Your mother doesn't love you, but now I love you
Master
Very good
It is as if you were born to be a slave
Yes, ah
I was born to be my master's slave
Master do you feel good
Ah
Master's penis is hard and hot
I am going to make you cum with my breasts
I am using my breasts to make master's penis feel good
How does my master feel
Please feel good
I will serve you well with all my heart
So do not abandon me
If you are diligent
Whatever the master wishes it is my duty to comply
The master's penis feels good in my breasts
Penis feels good
Ah
I was complimented by the master
Master my breasts will soon shoot milk
Put the master's penis between your breasts and lick it
Okay, master
Is it good master
Be rougher
Your master is about to cum
Drink
I said drink
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, master
I don't care
Maybe I should throw you out
Please forgive me, do not abandon me
I will drink next time, I will drink
Do not abandon me, forgive me
There is a way for you to restore favor with me
If you do it, I will completely forgive you
Yes, Thank you
It is good to please the master
Please put your penis in your slave's pussy
Let the slave's lower hole serve the master
My pussy is twitching in anticapation
Shoot your semen in me
You do not care if I cum inside
You will get pregnant
It doesn't matter if I get pregnant
Master shoot all your semen in me
I will make the master feel good
This is the way of slaves
insert my cock into your pussy yourself
Thank you
Master's penis
The master's hot penis is in
Master's penis is in me
It feels good ,ah
Oh, it is good
Master's penis is twitching in me
I feel really good and strange
Not the nipples master
It's to good, It's to good, I am dying
I am going to cum
Master I am going to cum
My nipples are cumming
You are really cumming a lot
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, master
However, it feels good
No, There, No
Forgive me I am going to cum, master
No
The master's slave is really abnormal
I am perverted
Your slave is abnormal
To reward such a perverted slave
The master is to rough
Master's penis is growing bigger in my womb
Master is punishing my insides
This is bad, it will break my uterus
Here comes the semen you like so much
Please give me your semen
Give it to me inside my womb
Give me a lot of master's hot penis juice
Give me a lot of master's milk
Hot semen is coming
Penis is twitching
My womb is full of sperm
It was so good I came
It feels good
You have fully embraced the role of my slave
Ah, master
Yes, slave
Are you going to cum
becuase of your nipples
No, ah, master
You are cumming
I'm sorry master
You know what your master wants now
I know what to do
I've been very happy
Well this is no longer required
Oh please master, give me
Let me serve you well more
You really are an excellent slave
Master I brought you lunch
Hey, I would also like to lick the master's penis
Early morning is the best time to lick it
If it cums in the mouth there will be no baby
I won't be able to make milk like her
It doens't mean that much slave
Come lick it as well
Okay
You earned top honors
Although I have gained an additional piece it is not enough
In order to really be able to withdraw, the book drop -
I still need more pieces
Then who would be good next
Obey your master