My stepbrother came home
for our parents' funeral.
It had been six years since I last saw him...
...and on the night of the funeral...
No! Brother... You're terrible...
But on the other hand...
...I might have had feelings
for my brother as a man...
As I was getting violated, I
realized I was enjoying it...
I followed my brother's orders...
...and transferred to a
prestigious boarding college...
...where my brother had
been hired as a professor.
My brother won't tell me anything...
...but he seems to have his
reasons for coming to this college.
Perhaps it's a dark secret...
WICKED LESSONS
Part Two
Yes...
The choir members are next door. At
this rate, they're going to hear you.
It's fine. They're rich prissy girls.
They wouldn't know what they're hearing.
Oh, it feels so good...
I want this... I want your hard
cock. I want you to fuck me.
Not yet. You have to cum with this first.
The vibrator can stay. I want
you to fuck me up the ass.
I see.
Please... Hurry and give it to me.
Yeah. I'll stick it in in a second.
More... I don't care if it hurts.
Please! Harder! Fuck me hard!!
That guy has done an amazing
job at turning you into a slut.
You asked for this...
I can't believe you can suck my
cock when was just up your ass.
Did he teach you how to do this too?
Have you made up your
mind about getting revenge?
Well?
Well?!
Are you giving up?
Are you going to fuck
your way out of your pain?
If you steal...
Steal what?
If you steal it, my uncle's finished...
What is it? Tell me. What
am I supposed to steal?
I'll look at his schedule.
He's a control freak...
...so once he's in a campaign crunch,
he'll probably sleep at the office.
That's our chance.
Why? Why are you doing this?
Because you piss us off, transfer girl!
You think you're so much better
because you're the professor's sister!
You smell so bad! Especially here!
Huh? Did she just moan in pleasure?
Probably. Do it again.
Let's see.
That hurts!
It hurts? Liar.
The tip went in.
Shove it in more. Give
her the royal treatment.
Sure.
Please stop. What have I done to you?
Wow! Look at that!
Let me see! Wow!
I know!
Let me see too!
Hey, send that picture to someone.
Great idea. They'll love it.
Don't! That's so terrible! Please!
What should we do?
Brother!
You girls again...
Are you going to bring this
up at a faculty meeting?
If you're going to do
that, I have an idea too.
I'll send this embarrassing
picture to everyone.
It'll be everywhere. Are you
sure you want that to happen?
Brother! Make them stop!
What do you want to do, Professor?
Do whatever.
Brother!
She's my sister, but we're not related.
I could care less what happens to her.
B... but...
Go ahead. I'll get paid off by your
parents to keep my mouth shut.
That's the smartest way to do this.
No, we can't have that!
Our parents can't find out about this.
Please Professor! We'll never do
this again. Let us off the hook!
Let's see... What should I do?
Come on, suck my cock.
It's a contest to see who's best.
This is quite a view.
This is the first time I've been with triplets.
I'm going to enjoy it to the fullest.
It hurts... It hurts...
Please... No... No more...
I can't anymore... I'm going to die...
What's wrong? We're not done yet.
N... no...
No.
Noooo!
You'll never have to deal
with them again. Got it?
Thank you for saving me. But
you didn't need to do that...
Don't get me wrong. It wasn't
for you. I wanted to have fun.
It's not often you get to do
a foursome with triplets.
Thanks for creating the opportunity.
There's something I want you to do for me.
Citizens of the neighborhood.
We apologize for this announcement.
Vote for Daizaburo Takamine.
The elections are coming up.
Daizaburo Takamine is
working hard for you.
Vote for Daizaburo Takamine.
Brot...
Brother...
Do you like beautiful women?
I'd rather have them beautiful than not.
Yeah...
You did a good job today.
Really?
Yeah. You deserve a reward.
Brother. Fuck me!
Brother!
Sister, eh?
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Takamine College
Director, congratulations
on winning the election.
Being an educator worked
great in your favor!
Thank you. It was possible
because everyone took care...
...of the College while I was gone.
Where's Elena?
I saw her this morning, but
I haven't seen her since.
Director's Office
Where did she go?
Professor Kano?
I need to have a private talk with you.
What is it that you wanted to talk about?
What the... Elena!
What is the meaning of this?
Ten years ago, there was a man
who went heavily into debt...
...because he was deceived
by an evil moneylender.
In the end, the moneylender
seized the College...
...that the family of the man's wife
had been running for decades.
The man's wife was a beautiful woman.
He still owed interest to the
moneylender. So in exchange...
...the moneylender fucked
her over and over...
...although she pleaded for mercy.
No! Please! Don't do this!
No... No... Stop...
I didn't know dad let that happen...
That's not all...
Forgive me...
But the saving grace is
that he's still into you.
If you were an average woman...
...we would have committed suicide by now.
Just deal with it a little
longer, for our family. Please!
The next day, the woman
jumped off a nearby building.
The man was hated by his son...
Then due to his careless driving...
...the man died along with his new wife.
The one to blame for my
mother's death wasn't my father.
My father meant nothing to me.
The only one who I wanted
to get revenge on...
...was the moneylender!
But after he seized the College...
...he left the financial trade
and became an educator.
Now, he's a politician... Yes...
I'm talking about you, Daizaburo Takamine!
Revenge? Is that the reason
you're doing this to Elena?
What's that?
You're a very organized man.
Lots of fine print pointer tips.
The pictures are very graphic
too. Unbelievable you've been...
...doing this to your niece, who
you took in at such a young age.
The sex maniacs would love to
get ahold of your sex manuals.
This is a misunderstanding!
I haven't done anything to Shirone!
I only borrowed a portion
of your collection...
...but it's definitely enough to ruin you.
W... What do I... What do I have
to do for you to forgive me?
First, I'd like you to give me back
my mother's precious college.
B... but...
You have no choice but to agree.
Fine.
I agree, so untie Elena.
She's done nothing wrong.
Sure. You're a very smart man.
No wonder you were able
to become a politician.
Let's see...
Are you going to punch me?
Fine... Punch me all you like.
Suck it!
I said, suck it!
You promised you would let her go!
I only promised to untie her.
Well? You don't want to?
Something terrible is going
to happen if you don't.
If your dad's secret gets out, your
life will be completely changed too.
Stop it! How dare you!
Well?
Okay. Good... I'm going
to have a lot of fun now.
This isn't rape. She's doing
it of her own free will.
This is exactly what you did with my mother.
Use your lips and tongue
and suck the head.
That feels good.
Might as well, I have the sex manuals...
I'll use them everyday, see if I can
learn something... with your daughter.
That's good...
Don't spit it out. Swallow it.
This is the best! I've never
had such an awesome time.
Director, your daughter's very beautiful.
Just looking at her makes me hard.
I can cum over and over...
Father... Help me... Father!
Help me? That's what my
mother and Shirone said too.
How about it, Director? Have a
look at your daughter's asshole.
No father! Don't look at me!
It feels so good...
Father... I'm sorry... I... I...
Brother won't look at me anymore if he
can have someone beautiful like Elena.
He'll never make love to me again...
Something's wrong. I'm enjoying
it but what's this empty feeling?
I'm fucking the most beautiful woman but...
Goodbye, brother...
My revenge is over.
I need to take care of Noelle
and take back my normal life.
Now we can start over as real siblings...
No, we can start over
as a man and a woman.
Noelle...