Private Fuji the beautiful Palace Academy School.
Although the sound is wonderful now, it was once lost do to a shift in policy.
It was originally called the Elder School for Girls.
Several years ago, the rich council decided to merge with another school and form a male and female school.
This is a world full of political dealings...
This is thanks to the uniform of the girls which have four kinds...
Previously the school maintained only one uniform.
Students can now choose their favorite uniform.
Anyway, the students are also acclaimed abroad for
their fancy uniforms and large number of smart students.
However, it is precisely because it is such a popular school
that zealots who love the uniforms number 50000.
Photographed pictures are also in hot demand
I have a large number of these guys filmed and made public on the Internet
Needless to say there is a charge for membership
This world is very convenient
The school park camera is set up to photograph an endless source of material.
Which can also be used to threaten a woman to do crazy things.
Some of the photographs can be used as bait to net big fish
My popularity soared among adult sites but I will not be affected by the storm of money.
Parents treat me like a thorn in the side of the whole Academy
For me it is the opposite like a duck to water
However, there is one day I was called to the principal's office
Kawamura What is this
That was last week in my department at the headquarters of the wireless room
That is a scene of me teaching my slave Ayano
Fact of the matter is
Last month, there was an investigation on a girl who was gang raped
That girl later committed suicide
Seems to me some  of the people who raped her want the Academy to look bad
An anonymous sender sent these photos to the school principle
They intend to punish anyone who makes the academy look bad
Anyway, if you have noticed my bad mood, they think I am one of these people
Unlucky premonition, what a joke
They think I was involved with the first incident becuase the color of the unifrom was that of a drop-out
It is strange that they would think I am the only drop-out
It would be more troublesome if I break out of the Campus and obtain other sources of adult sites pictures
This is vital, but
resistance is futile
Although suspended one-month, I had already decided to withdraw from the academy
But it is still really strange
I can say it is a mystery they think I am connected to the drop-out color
I do not know the dead girl
Furthermore, I was accused of rape without any association of such rumors as the reason for be dropping
I had Naishi tortured but she had no information
She said no to everything I asked
There must be something I am missing
I harbored an idea to install a listening device in the principal's office
Then noticed that the real conspirator was the Vice-Chancellor
Those people planned to use the girl to bring up the school's old ghosts
Then establish the school as a place for prostitution
As the saying goes the fact is more naked than the novel
Once this incident is widely known no one will want to do busines with them
The suicide female student was actually sacrificed as the first offering
I had not thought that she would be able to commit suicide
Then the second is the color selection
But I started first just in time
So to be a hindrance to me that want me to stay away from the other colored uniforms
What a joke
The principle just wanted the extra security
I plan to give a notice of intention to drop out
I used his daughter as the principal leader of Team ...
How can ... drop out?
Hush Sound too big
Sorry
But that is a misunderstanding
It will be good to get the matter sorted out as long as it clears the principals
The principal and other teachers are just being deceived
I can only rely on a squad leader
I know Kawamura
I will talk directly with mother and will ask a favor
Cheer up, Kawamura
It does not matter wrapped in my thoughts
However, the next day her attitude completely changed
Good morning Kawamura
You lied to me, right?
You actually do that sort of thing to girls
I can say you are the one to blame
Even my mother gave me the evidence, I saw those fraudulent pictures
Of course you had to be expelled
Forget our original plans
I know it looks like me, but it is not
Then how should we do to
Ayano
I'm sorry master
I already told you not to nip me with your teeth
Keep sucking, Chuixiao
Sorry
However, the vibrations were strong ...
You have a lot of nerve to talk back to me
It is still more than enough to say they are strong
Please stop master
It was so so strong
You talk to much, what kind of punishment would it be, if it wasn't strong
This is your punishment for falling into my hands or have you forgotten
Do you want it to continue, Chuixiao
Right I'm sorry
However, this state ... ...
This guy is really troublesome
You will carry on until I am content Chuixiao
This is necessary to
Do not use teeth or there will be consequences, are we clear
Yes and suck it deep
Master ... It is very hard ...
Shut up, who told you to talk back
I'm about to cum, I must endure
How can ...
I'm about to cum
No ... no ...
Drink all I  give
You leaked it everywhere
Right I'm sorry, but I got so much to drink
Slave women do not talk back Ayano
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Clean up the spilled semen with your mouth
Yes ...
Main master?
Your butt twisting is tempting me
This is becuase the vibrator is on
I want, I want to
Please use the master's penis to punish the slave
What a characterless slave you are
I'm going to give you a good punishment
Please not there
Please, master, not there
There is ...
There is?
Where is there slave
The ... the ass ... ass hole ...
Please stop, it is dirty
Dirty? I just finished washing my slave's dirty intestines and asshole
Please ... Please do not bully me ...
Do not make me like being disgraced
The enema had better have worked and my dick has better don't get dirty
Please do not give me an enema again
Then the enema had better of worked, becuase here comes my dick
Master's...Master's thing
Ayano
I'm sorry I'm sorry
Master please insert your penis into me
Please enjoy the slave's washed insides and buttocks
Please let the slave be punished in the ass
That is a good slave, my slave
Not...Good...
It is very hard ... the master ...
It is hard to punish you slave
Please do not move ... so ...
How can I not move slave
How is the slave
Good... strange ...
It is painful but good in a strange way
That is how your asshole feels
You are the abnormal slave
The slave is...not abnromal
Not…Not…Feeling…
Yes
Please do not move so fiercely ...
If a move as such ...
Anyway, feeling powerless slave
I do not feel ...
However intensely you move...
My butt feels strange
What is coming
No
Do not pinch the nipple
What a feeling
The slave's butt feels
My butt feels strange from being bullied by the master
My first anal sex feels really strange
The abnormal slave is feeling strange
The master's hard penis feels very good violating my butt
I am strangely comfortable with taboo things
It makes you feel better
Do not know...penis...terrific
The master's penis is stirring my butt
It is so hard it might shatter
It feels like it will shatter
If further feeling, then we should go
Please ... please spare me master
I am going to climax in the slave's butt
Do not I do not want this
To climax in the slave's butt is really perverted
I beg you master
Please insert in front
Let me cum in the front
Do not move so intensely or the slave will cum
Please Stop do not want to cum do not want to cum
Spare me, spare me, master
Master's penis is to comfortable
Do not like, pull out...
Do not bully the slave's butt
It is not good I'm going to cum
Do not want to cum
Not the butt...  cumming... cumming
Cumming a lot
Master's semen... Is in the slave's butt... a lot came out
My ass is cumming
I like to mistreat my valueble slave
Hey clench your ass to stop the valuable semen flow
Hmmm she does not here
How should I attend the class leader
Really looking forward to tomorrow
This ...
Master...Did not want me to give you a reply, just bring this
After school, please put that into the chapel to
If you do not come, then we will spread out photographs of you
I am finished I must go
He asks that you come
Asked
You must certainly leave school
You had better to let me go
I do not like to beat around the bush
Really this suits me
You should not do such things Kawamura
Untie me
You have not been good squad leader
I remember you backing out on a promise we made
I have to teach you how to be very obedient
Too good too good too
My first time
Cannot forgive cannot forgive you
Why don't you forgive me?
Because of this, I will tell mother you certainly have to leave school
Let's make this interesting
I do not want
Do not do anything
Do not
Do not look at
Do not... Stop...
I am surprised, Such large and milky colored breasts
Do not suck them
No do not suck my nipple
No sucking
They smell good, like sweet milk
I don't like that dark look
Milk can come out
It really hurts, it hurts
Why would there be milk
Quick stop... quick stop
Kawamura you are overdoing things, do not do this
I forgive you for before
I will not tell anyone
I cannot forgive you
This is unlike you squad leader
It is easy for you to go back on your word
Do not...Do...
No that place is dirty
Squad leader is dirty here
You have a little dark urine stain
You go to far saying that to a girl
No, Do not lick
Let me help lick you clean...good...
Stop...Stop...Kawamura
I don't want... in that kind of place
Is the squad leader a virgen?
Do not say such things
I'm going to insert it
Insert in the ...? Do not
No do not insert that kind of thing
I said do not insert that into me
Quick! Stop!
I am a virgin. I am a virgin.
A virgen...
Looks like you are an outstanding woman
Does it really hurt
No, Do not move
It really hurts, really, really hurts, ah ah
Do not, I do not want this
It really hurts, it really hurts
Mom save me
Your obedience at the end of today will be becase your mom failed
Stop...
It really hurts, really really hurts,  spare me
It will soon be pleasurable
Your tight pussy will not be able to live without by cock
Stop, Do not move, it really hurts
No ...
Almost, I am about to cum inside
Fast...Stop...doing this... I will have a baby
Do not, Do not, ah
Inside... No... No...
Have you thought of the kid's name yet
I do not want to get pregnant
Absolutely not...No...Stop
I will have a baby
Do not cum
Cumming...Cumming...
In my womb ... a lot ...
A lot flows out...
I will be pregnant
If you are not obedient, I will show these pictures to everyone
You are very smart, so you know well enough
These photos can cause the dismissal of the principal
It will be strange if the principal is fired becuase his daughter was raped
Anyway, not my business
Do not... Stop
Didn't I say not to come here
However…This is kind of promiscuous…
The toy inserts there... incorrect...
I already put my cock in you this week, now let's insert more
Do not... Do not... Do not...
You need to understand your status
Good too...
This appearance is not good, it is shameful
You are not listening to me
Kawamura please refrain from doing such things
I will take every effort to have my mother not drop you from the school
You csn get on with your life
I can forgive everything you have done
What do you say...is that okay?
You put it really well.
It is probably becuase we are in the confession room
Your attitude towards everyone as more worthless than you has put me in a bad mood
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I will apologize, Please spare me, do not to have hurt me
For a long time you have been class leader...
There will be consquences if you dare to defy my orders.
No... Do not... ah
Promiscuous, or exactly the same as milk
No... Do not suck the nipple
If I get this way I become very strange
My nipples will do it...
How can ... Stop ...
Such breasts
Let's also do this down here
No
You became so wet when I touched here
Do not insert it
In inside…Moved in inside
I'm dying
I am cumming...I am cumming
What is...
Do not look at all of the milk
Did you get pregnant from that time...
No ... that it is not ...
Not you? Milk comes out
This ...
Born ...
When I am excited milk comes out
That is contrary to the matter
I thought it was so sick to see
Even my idiosyncratic mother does not know ...
Now oyu know... a male classmate...
I already could not live…I want to die…
Special quality ... die?
It's fun
You are very good class leader
Kawamura ...
Quickly... Stop... Kawamura
No
I have decided class leader
I must train you to be my special-purpose meat slave
My penis will make you exicted and you will spout mother's milk
It is something you were simply born with
I want you to continue to spout mother's milk
Do not... Stop... Kawamura... Fast
I do not want milk to come out again so soon
Spare me
Do not rub my chest or strange things will occur
Do not touch the nipple
There do not, do not
It is so intense
A very good feeling and then spray again
No milk.. I don't want milk to come out again...
It is not good, it feels strange
Chun Ye has become strange
It is deep
No... Kawamura... spare me
I feel strange and good
Obviously repugnant…Obviously repugnant…
My chest feels...
He is pinching me... it is coming...I do not want
It feels...
like I am a bad person
Coming again... coming out... milk is coming out
Do
I am urinating... that is not good...It came out
It feels good...It feels good being violated
It is not urine it is called love fluid
It is evident you are a woman because of your climax
Now I must shoot cum inside you
No...Not inside I will have a baby
I beg you shoot outside....not inside
I'm cumming
Do not...Do not inside
I will get pregnant
I don't want a baby, outside please
You already have a mother's milk for a healthy child
Do not... ah
So much...It is hot
There is a lot of semen inside
I do not want...I do not want a baby
This nasty guy shot his semen in me again
There is so much and it burns
Do not want
Do not, ah
Fainted
It is just the beginning
For the second round lets get you some new clothes.