Masao Sera, having
joined forces with...
the gangs
of Nightmare Campus...
saw their battle with the
Gods suddenly escalate...
and soon the entire campus
was plunged into chaos.
Student president
Shuichi Kusanagi...
having brainwashed the majority of
students into fighting the gangs...
forced Masao and his friends
into a deadly situation.
The now outcast Masao
was able to unleash...
the anger inside
him against the Gods.
Lacking this advantage,
Kusanagi tempted Yuuko Someya.
Although she
genuinely loves Masao...
she was drawn to Kusanagi
as though destined to.
Against her will,
Kusanagi had sex with her.
Meanwhile, the
captured Akira Mido...
learned the shocking
truth from the God Mikogami:
That the Gods had broken
the seal imprisoning the demons.
The revelation of the
reason behind this act...
was too horrible for
Akira's mind to bear.
And, finally, the time
for battle arrived.
At a campus assembly, Kusanagi
used Akira to expose Masao!
Masao Sera!
He is... a demon!
Upon hearing these words,
the brainwashed students...
shed the last of their humanity
and attacked Masao and his friends.
Once again, violence was
visited upon the campus.
Amidst the chaos, Kusanagi took
Yuuko, daring Masao to follow.
Enraged, Masao followed.
But then, before his eyes...
he saw Yuuko behave as a
willing partner for Kusanagi.
It was then that Kusanagi
revealed the shocking truth:
Yuuko was, in fact,
a God herself!
Masao managed to kill
Kusanagi with one blow...
but Yuuko refused
to come to him.
Now overwhelmed with despair,
Masao lost control of his power
and destroyed
everything around him.
The campus was closed as a
result of this incident...
and the growing chain
of events was broken.
And now, months later...
- Well, see you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Bye-bye
- Bye.
Prepare for data sampling.
Roger.
What are you doing?
This area's closed!
Didn't you know that?
S-sorry, I was just
taking a short-cut.
Are you a student
at Nightmare Campus?
N-n-no, I...
Have you seen the demons?
Or...
Are you a demon yourself?
Well?
What are you doing?
Help me! This man's...
What is it? Another demon?
No! Let me go! Stop it!
Stop it, please!
I'm not a demon!
Shut up!
You Nightmare Campus
people are all monsters!
Look! A guy in this home
went to your school, too.
He was a nice, quiet student.
Then it happened,
about a month after...
they closed the school
'cuz of that trouble they had.
He suddenly went nuts and
turned into some kinda animal!
He slaughtered his parents,
then raped and ATE his sister!
Kagami...
Oh, a friend of yours?
He went out after that and
killed dozens of people...
including eight
cops on patrol!
He took a chunk outta my
arm before he got away!
It wasn't just him, either!
There've been lots
of cases like that!
They just haven't
made it public yet.
Tell me!
Who are you people?
What are you
doing to this city?
Answer me!
Beginning data sampling.
The girl reads as normal.
I'm seeing D-factor influence
in the two investigators.
Should we get them away from...
the sampling subject,
Superintendent Sumeragi?
No, that won't be necessary.
Just continue
monitoring the situation.
Y-yes, sir.
But what about the girl?
I told you.
Monitor the situation.
Our purpose is data collection.
Is that clear, Mr. Kajiwara?
Roger.
What are you doing?
Come on!
Well, you sure look like
a normal woman here.
No! Stop it!
Please... Stop it, please!
No! No!
D-factor increasing
rapidly in sample subject.
Body temperature has
risen to 44 degrees Celsius.
Dopamine output increasing,
similar to samples B, H, and O.
Classify her as sample T.
Yes, sir!
Hell, she's really
getting into this!
A few minutes ago she was making
like the Virgin Mary, but now!
You're pretty tight!
It almost hurts!
D-factor rising! Over level E!
Hey!
Something weird's happening.
Reading a metamorphosis!
She's demonizing!
My...!
Shoot! Shoot!
She's crying...
What are we fighting?
Another one!
Someone just demonized!
Where is it, Kagami?
Near the campus.
I got it off the
scrambled police channel.
One cop and a lot of bystanders
are dead or injured.
Their target's
headed into the city.
What do we do?
We're going in.
Advance team, move out!
Right.
Martial Arts Club, move out!
We'll take it!
- Thanks.
- Right!
I'm going, too!
Assemble squad two!
Right! Let's go, you guys!
- What's wrong?
- The one who just demonized...
It's Yoko Nishima,
from section 1-F!
That's my section!
Another one of our students.
I don't get it...
What's going on?
They're really
putting on a show.
Well, we won't save
her by lying low.
Right! Guys!
Time to cut loose!
Sir! Everyone's here!
Situation?
It's retreated to a restaurant
on the sixth floor of that building.
The customers and staff
are out of there.
We don't have
an exact count yet...
but there are a lot of police
and civilian casualties.
We haven't been able
to get near it. Also...
What?
First platoon was wiped out.
Kajiwara died in action.
What?
Prepare for battle!
We're going in!
Hold on, Yuuki.
What?
Just have your men
surround the building.
What's going on?
My team will go in.
We're an extra-jurisdictional
team established outside of...
the police force and trained
to deal with this situation.
Since when?
Since our elite mobile
team was wiped out.
It was easy to convince
the Prime Minister after that.
You...! You set Kajiwara's
team up, didn't you?
Sir, don't do it!
Just observe the
situation, Mr. Yuuki.
This case threatens all mankind.
Shoot! Shoot it!
Quick! Get a sample!
No! No more killing!
Fire!
Okay, hit 'em hard!
Sir!
Shoot!
What the...?
They've come...
Sorry we took so long.
Good work, guys!
Hmpf! No sweat!
Don't let them go!
Concentrate fire!
Where are they?
All right, let's clear out!
Sir, what was that?
Withdraw our men.
The party's over for us.
Take care of the rest, okay?
Mr. Yuuki!
Those were more of our enemies.
Move it!
Get the fire trucks in here!
Sir!
Well, look at the
mess you've made!
I let you into my
apartment, thinking you're...
a decent type,
and you do this!
I'll make you pay for this.
Ai! Mai!
Right.
It's a little violent, but
we've gotta snap her back now.
Would you guys cut that out?
What...?
What are you doing?
Yoko...?
Don't look at me.
Thank goodness
you're safe, Yoko.
We're all your friends here.
You can relax.
I killed so many people...
I've turned into this monster...
I can't go on!
Don't say that!
You're wrong.
We have to live!
Yoko!
Come on, guys.
Get her into bed.
Right!
Okay, all men, get out!
No news reports
after all that happened?
But people are getting
more and more scared.
What are the Gods trying to do?
She'll be okay.
She's taking it hard...
but she's letting
Kagami stay with her.
She isn't ashamed to
let him see her now.
Must be really tough for her...
So, what's up with Yuuko?
She won't let me see her.
Is that so?
Aren't you avoiding
her for no reason, too?
You're so gloomy!
Blue balls?
Wanna do it with me,
like we did before?
If you don't do something,
you'll all go nuts.
You... Yuuko... Akira...
He spends every
waking minute doing it.
But he's at the end of his rope.
It's like he's running away from
something horrible that he knows.
They don't mind it.
They do whatever he wants.
The funny thing is...
Everyone's who's had sex
with him has gotten pregnant.
But, that's...!
All of them!
Is that even possible?
Does it mean anything?
Does it say what
he's so afraid of?
Tell me, Lord Esedess!
What's happening?
Does it mean you're
going to betray us again?
You...?
What?
What did you just say?
You heard me
just fine, Mr. Yuuki.
You and your unit are now
under my direct command.
The special anti-demon unit.
Are you people nuts?
Watch your mouth, Yuuki!
Naturally, the citizenry
won't be told the truth.
But the problem's spread outside
of Japan and across the world.
In Russia they had to destroy a
whole city because of the chaos.
Along with those things.
We have no effective
countermeasures here in Japan.
Unless we act, it's obvious
we'll end up like them.
But, demons?
In this day and age? That's...!
You've fought them several
times already, haven't you?
But they're originally
human beings, aren't they?
We don't know the cause, but...!
Mr. Yuuki, your
sentimentalism is irrelevant!
I told you already: This case
threatens all mankind!
Are you people
even human yourselves?
Isn't it too soon?
They're not ready.
The situation has changed.
We haven't much time left.
They'll be attacking soon?
Yes. We just got the
latest data from Katmandu.
Ironic, isn't it?
That in living so long we've
forgotten how to act quickly.
We've let too
much time slip away.
By the way, about that
young lady, Yuuko Someya...
If she becomes a liability...
kill her.
Yes, sir.
Masao, it's crazy!
If I'm not out in two hours,
come in after me.
Great! He did it!
Akira... Come back to me...
Otherwise, I'll...!
AKIRA!
Wake up, Akira!
Have some.
You haven't seen him?
Doctor, I... What am I?
I don't understand any of this.
If I'm really a God,
like you are...
then I should be
able to forget Masao.
You may never
be able to go back.
Not yet... I don't know
exactly what you are yet.
Our race's longevity has
harmed our ability to reproduce.
And there's no precedent for...
a life form like you
appearing among the humans.
To have done so now...
I want to see for myself!
Exactly who you are.
Now, awaken...
Show me your true form.
It can't be! You're...!
Akira!
Masao...
Masao, why did you wake me?
To show me hell?
So I could be destroyed
along with you, Masao?
What the hell is this?
I'm sorry,
you can't go in there.
Don't I have clearance?
I'm sorry, sir. They told me
only project staff is allowed in.
What the fuck?
What the hell
are you Gods doing?
Who are they?
What's going on?
Sir, big time trouble!
Now what?
The government just broke the
news on the demonization effect!
It's on the TV now!
WHAT?
We repeat, while it remains
unclear as to the causes...
or the possible treatment of
this genetic mutation effect...
the "Demon Plague" is highly
contagious and is spreading.
To prevent confusion and panic
among the city's residents...
the government has decided to
publicly reveal this sickness.
The Welfare Ministry is taking
this threat very seriously...
and is organizing the public
health authorities to cooperate.
Due to concern about
the disease's virulence...
top priority
is being given to...
isolating and
treating those infected.
That's ridiculous!
It isn't contagious!
While the symptoms vary,
the threat it poses...
to public order has
prompted the creation of...
a new special police unit.
In order to help the infected,
it has been necessary to...
use tranquilizer guns
to safely sedate them.
Hah! You mean mow us down!
In this exclusive footage,
we can see scenes of...
their first mission
to restore public order.
The victim of the disease shown
here is still unidentified.
If we learn anything
about who they might be...
A request from the government.
In order to contain the
further spread of the disease...
please contact police or
public health authorities...
in the event you
discover infected persons...
among your family,
neighbors, or co-workers.
The two clearest symptoms of
the disease are as follows:
One: A sudden increase
in physical abilities.
Two: Radical personality change
and emotional instability...
such as extreme
manic-depression.
Currently we're seeing
scattered rain storms...
clearing up tomorrow and
leaving a lovely autumn day.
Next up, tomorrow's forecast
for the rest of the area.
Tokyo, Saitama, and Kanagawa
should be clear.
Ibaraki and Chiba will
start off partly cloudy...
but clear up
by late afternoon.
Trouble!
People are demonizing all
around the campus neighborhood!
That weird force we felt
before must be causing it!
This isn't real!
That was good, man.
Lemme go! Lemme go!
Help me! Monsters!
Monsters! Monsters!
Police!
A-20, A-06! Confirm demon
sightings in the Motomichi area.
Take care of infected citizens.
Use standard equipment and
live guns to restore order.
They'll never stop this!
What'll we do, Masao?
There's one!
And another one, too!
What's going on here?
It started just after
the public announcement!
What do we do?
They're all waiting
for your word.
You feel the same as
we do, don't you, Sera?
We're the only ones
who can save them.
Fire!
Let's go!
Our objective is to
defuse this situation!
Try hard to save
the demonized people!
And avoid fighting at all costs!
Outsiders, into battle!
The chaos caused by
the demonization effect...
has caused fires
to burn out of control.
Doctor, what's happening?
The first step
of the Gods' plan.
It's only just begun.
It's begun!