When the ancient seal of
the Gods is opened...
the earth will once again
be covered by the fires of hell.
Evil spirits will dominate...
and men's souls
will rot with evil.
The earth will be drowned
in an ocean of blood...
and the flames will rise
up to scorch the heavens.
Civilization will
lose all reason...
and human society will
collapse beyond recognition.
But do not be saddened by
this, children of man.
Rather than destruction,
it shall be a beginning.
New life will be brought
to your decrepit world.
But it shall be life born in
pain, and all living things...
will be crucified on
the cross of fate.
Amidst this chaos, the true
nature of the world...
will be revealed in whole and
its true form shall be restored.
When this happens, man will,
for the first time...
be freed of the yoke of the old
gods and regain self-determination.
Many have tried,
but none can escape...
the destiny that
is called evolution.
The king of the underworld,
awakened from his long sleep...
tempts mankind towards chaos.
Here, human history ends.
A new age of
life is beginning.
Having heard that his
archeologist father had...
contracted an illness,
Masao Sera and his mother
journeyed to his new posting...
at some ancient ruins
in the Himalayan mountains.
It was almost as if
he'd become an animal.
Dad!
There, Masao saw a horrifying
demon resurrection ceremony.
You will be spared from seeing
the coming hell on earth.
Using an ocean of blood,
an ancient seal was broken...
and countless demons were loosed
to spread across the Earth.
The campus Masao attended,
Motomichi Campus...
has earned the nickname
of Nightmare Campus...
because it is overrun
with gang violence.
However, since the great
Himalayan earthquake...
people with superhuman
powers have been appearing...
and conditions there
changed radically.
What's happening?
Some began to see their
true, demonic forms awaken.
What's happening?
Over there?
And then, one day, Masao
Sera, who had been...
assumed killed in the great
Himalayan quake...
suddenly returned to the campus
in a violent blast of energy.
It can't be... That little
wuss Sera has power like that?
Two gang leaders, Abe and Reiko,
hoping to gain...
the power Masao possessed,
involved Yuuko Someya...
a young woman who loves
Masao, in their plans.
Look at how hard
her nipples are!
Stop it! Don't touch her!
Shut up!
Masao, who had lost his memory
of the events in the Himalayas...
learned that a demon named
Esedess now existed within him.
The battle going on within
him was almost too much.
Who are you?
My name is Esedess.
Release me.
That's it
Just let yourself go.
Releasing Masao's sexual desire...
the demon lord
Esedess finally awakened.
You'll pay for hurting Reiko!
The neighborhood
was covered in flames...
and Abe and Reiko
could only cower before...
the unstoppable
might of Esedess.
Little fool! You think
you can defeat Esedess!
And one other person was there...
to witness the rebirth
of the demon lord Esedess:
Akira Mido, Masao's best friend.
This is Esedess?
This is Masao's power?
Masao Sera, with the demon lord
Esedess existing within him...
now embarks
on a grand destiny.
Can we really get power here?
Really.
You all have hidden power.
Like what he has.
Now, then, let us begin.
What the...?
What's happening?
You... son of a...!
All that's left is you, Masao.
What the...?
Looks like you're okay now.
How long was I out?
- A week.
- I see...
Looks like he
really messed you up.
Anything happen while
I was unconscious?
Hyuga's guys are up to something.
And Masao Sera's coming
to class tomorrow.
S-sera?
Yes.
Whatever.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What?
It's Sera!
Masao Sera's on the campus!
Hey, did you hear
about Sera's house?
Yeah, it was caught
in that explosion.
He should be dead.
First he somehow gets back from
the Himalayas and now this!
And did you see how
messed up Abe is?
I hear Sera did that to him.
Yeah. Me, too.
Sera is coming!
Good... Good morning.
Sera, I wanna talk to you.
Is he all right?
This looks bad, man!
Do you remember what
happened, Lord Esedess?
I'm not Esedess.
I'm Masao Sera.
I know that something named
Esedess exists inside of me.
I don't know when he might
burst out of me again.
It could even happen now.
Look, I don't know
what you want from me...
but I just want
to be left alone.
Please.
Hold on a sec!
Are you saying you
control Lord Esedess?
I'll be damned if
I let him control me.
What do you think?
I like him. There may be more
to this guy than I thought.
Things are gettin' interestin'!
You're all right?
You're sure nothing
happened to you?
Yeah.
He seems a lot more macho now.
There's something odd about him.
Yeah.
Look, Masao.
You can still stay at my home.
Won't you change your mind?
What's with you, Akira?
You just keep saying that.
Masao.
You've changed.
Huh? You... You think so?
Yuuko!
Well, I'd better go.
What's up, Yuuko?
Nothing. I just thought
I'd make something for you.
Really? What are
you going to make?
Well, I have curry and...
My name is Esedess!
Release me!
Release me! Release me!
Release your desires!
I am within you!
I am Masao Sera!
What's wrong?
Lt... It's nothing.
Okay.
Well, see you.
R-right.
So, where to now?
What was...?
Why, Masao?
Why won't you accept
the demon within you?
If this keeps up,
then you'll...!
Would you check out those tits!
Oh, lemme taste those lips!
Isn't her hair beautiful?
Who is she, anyway?
Don't you know?
She's the new campus doctor.
Yeah. Dr. Yumi Mikogami.
Oh, she's so pretty.
Dr. Mikogami... She's beautiful
and sophisticated...
Why can't I be like her?
Satomi! Satomi!
She'll hear you.
Miss Someya.
Akira...
May I speak with you?
Sure.
The game's afoot.
So, what's this about?
Hasn't Masao seemed
a bit strange lately?
I know what you want to say.
That it's like...
Like he's been possessed
by a demon, right?
Then why do you stay with him?
Doesn't it scare you?
It isn't like I'm not scared...
but Masao's fighting
whatever it is inside of him.
That's why... That's why I...!
So, she's the obstacle.
Everything with Yuuko is just
Masao this and Masao that!
A... Akira?
She's Yuuko Someya's friend...
Great.
I didn't know he was here!
Miss Orikawa, you want
Miss Someya back for yourself?
Just like I...
want Masao.
No, not here...!
Finally! We're done!
- Let's go home.
- I'm beat.
Hang in there!
No! Somebody will...!
Don't worry.
They can't see us.
No...
and during the game the ball
caught her right in the face!
God, what an idiot!
Hm? What's this?
No!
Hey, how'd THESE get here?
- Gross!
- Whose is that?
You clear on this?
The big showdown's coming.
That's what we're
saving our powers for!
It can't just be these idiots.
Someone's pulling their strings.
Who...?
- What's up?
- Who's there?
What's up, Mido?
I can't use my powers!
Have a victory party.
Take her.
Hyuga?
No! No, Esedess! No!
Hey! Boss!
Boss Sera!
Boss, here!
Boss, wait!
What's going on?
Why was Yuuko...?
How or why's kinda beside
the point. It's done.
"We have Yuuko Someya. Meet us
in the main auditorium at 10PM."
Hyuga sent me this himself,
so it's on the level.
Masao, you're their target.
But, why Yuuko...?
Boss!
Reiko!
I know who's
behind Hyuga's guys.
It's Akira Mido!
A... Akira?
Well, Boss?
I'm their target.
I'll go alone.
Masao! That message was
a direct challenge to me.
There's no way in
hell I'm not going!
Besides, we had to settle things
with them eventually. Right?
Right!
Besides, I kinda like you.
Not 'cuz you're Esedess.
I like Masao Sera.
Thank you.
All right, people!
Plow the road for us!
Go!
It's begun.
Shit! Reiko, go!
Okay!
Masao!
We'll handle these guys!
Get going inside!
Keep them busy!
Sure! We've got 'em!
Haven't had to push the
engines to full for a while!
Akira?
I'm glad you came, Masao.
So, care to join in the fun?
Oh, yes. THIS is the woman
you want, isn't it?
Yuuko!
Be true to your desires, Masao.
Release your powers and the
entire world can be yours!
Akira... Are you really
the Akira Mido I knew?
Or has a demon taken
over your soul?
Masao.
You really don't
remember anything.
When the demons appear on earth...
their human hosts
aren't chosen by chance.
The demon chooses the human,
and the human chooses the demon.
Masao! You, too, have
been chosen by a demon!
Yes! By the
mightiest demon of all:
The demon lord Esedess!
Do you know how happy
I was when I realized that?
That my oldest, dearest friend was
host to the demon lord Esedess?
I realized it had to be fate!
But then you refused to awaken.
Why, Esedess?
Have you forgotten me?
I, who fought by your
side in ancient times?
I am the demon lord Aquifel!
I, who, with you, was one
of the shining jewels...
of the underworld!
The demon lord Aquifel!
Awaken, Esedess!
Or else I will bury you
with my own hands!
Why, Akira?
Still you call me by
that name? Very well!
Why, Esedess?
Why only this much?
You haven't awakened completely.
Very well!
Then I'll rip those
human feelings out of you!
This woman has become
a chain to bind you!
Stop it!
I will free you from
these bonds now!
Esedess, give me the power!
The power to kill him!
The power to save Yuuko!
Take my soul and
come to me! ESEDESS!
It’ll take more
than that, Esedess!
Do you know
this place, Masao?
It's the spot
where you returned!
Take in the demonic
energy and awaken!
Take it, or die!
What the...?
Masao!
It's all going as we planned.
You see, Esedess? You see
this incredible power?
Now that the Gods' seal is
broken, the world is ours!
What the...?
Yes, Esedess!
If he doesn't stop...
Esedess, if you don't stop,
you'll kill her!
Miss Someya
Please... Stop him.
Stop Masao.
Stop Masao...?
Akira, is that you?
It can't be!
Masao!
NO! MASAO!
Now you are truly
the demon lord Esedess...
Masao!