You, too, will give a
bit of your blood...
for the resurrection
of the demons!
What's happening?
What began for Masao Sera with
the great Himalayan earthquake,
now continues in the
violence of "Nightmare Campus."
It's all going as we planned.
Appearing suddenly,
the mysterious...
and handsome young man,
Shuichi Kusanagi,
and the campus
doctor, Dr. Mikogami,
have taken control of the school
and are driving the gangs out.
Masao and his gang
are the main targets.
Besides this, a strange
effect gave the...
martial arts club
superhuman abilities...
and their fight with Masao
and his friends grew severe.
STOP IT!!!
Amidst the tumult, Masao lost
the last of his reservations...
and allowed the demon lord
Esedess to fully join with him.
I follow the ancient
link of destiny...
and stand upon
the earth once more!
Guess you're on our side now.
But then,
as though to mock them...
Kusanagi and Mikogami
appeared in their true forms.
We'll be taking
your friend as well.
Wait!
Seeing the two of them left
Masao shaking with fear.
Our enemies... The Gods?
When the ancient seal of
the Gods is opened...
the earth will once again
be covered by the fires of hell.
Evil spirits will dominate...
and men's souls
will rot with evil.
The earth will be drowned
in an ocean of blood...
and the flames will rise
up to scorch the heavens.
Civilization will
lose all reason...
and human society will
collapse beyond recognition.
But do not be saddened by
this, children of man.
Rather than destruction,
it shall be a beginning.
New life will be brought
to your decrepit world.
But it shall be life born in
pain, and all living things...
will be crucified on
the cross of fate.
Amidst this chaos, the true
nature of the world...
will be revealed in whole and
its true form shall be restored.
When this happens, man will,
for the first time...
be freed of the yoke of the old
gods and regain self-determination.
Many have tried,
but none can escape...
the destiny that
is called evolution.
The king of the underworld,
awakened from his long sleep...
tempts mankind towards chaos.
Here, human history ends.
A new age of
life is beginning.
Stop it! Stop it, please!
I still don't understand.
Why are you still doing
this to Akira Mido?
He's already fallen into our
trap. There's no threat now.
We hold his fate in our hands.
I know we're using him in
another feint against Esedess...
but why supply
him with those women?
Isn't it time you told me?
What exactly is this plan
supposed to accomplish?
It seems to me you're uselessly
trying to stimulate him...
for the sake of
your own amusement.
Kusanagi!
Forgive me!
I spoke carelessly!
Understand this: A low-level
God like yourself...
doesn't need to know the plan.
All you need concern yourself
with is hunting them...
just as you've been doing.
Make Esedess suffer utterly
and then bring me his head!
Yes, my lady!
Yes... I need them even
more than I need you.
Their young, vibrant lives!
Stop it!
Save me, Masao!
Where...?
Father!
Mo... ther...
Ah, young man. Still not dead?
Then I'll keep on killing you.
Just like this one!
Aquifel!
Sleep in eternal
darkness, Esedess!
Taste the benevolence
of the Gods!
Thanks to you, the gang sweep
has been a spectacular success.
We pray that decency will soon
be returned to this campus.
We want all of you to help us.
Let us fight together,
for the future of our campus!
Miss Someya.
Why don't you accept my baptism?
He'll only bring you pain.
You're being deceived by him.
Who are you people?
We are they
who speak the truth.
If you wish to know the
truth, then come to us.
We will remove any
doubts you may have.
So, you're still conscious.
You apparently deserve
your title of demon lord.
You monster!
This warm pulsation is a
feeling we Gods lost long ago.
Now, let your warm
life force flow into me.
Just kill me!
Why humiliate me like this?
I desire a strong man, like you.
And like the other young man.
Damn it, what are you up to?
You want to kill
we demons because...
we broke free
of the seal, right?
We Gods created that seal.
Only we could have broken it!
That... That's insane!
YOU were the ones
who broke the seal?
Then what was the
point of the war?
That long, terrible war!
You cursed us by burying us
in the cold, dark earth...
for what seemed
like an eternity.
And now you finally allow
us back into the light...
simply so you
can amuse yourselves?
Answer me, God!
You wish to know the truth?
More than anything!
Then I will tell you.
It can't be...!
Don't.
You can't go back,
now that you know the truth.
Knowing what you do,
choose life or death.
If you wish to live...
Yes... That's the way,
demon lord Aquifel.
Faithful servant of the Gods.
Masao! Masao!
Shut up, you little shit!
Masao?
Masao, what are you doing?
At this rate they'll
take over the campus.
You're playing into their hands!
I'm scared. That she'll...
That she'll kill me again!
I think of Akira, and...!
Bullshit! You're the demon
lord Esedess, right?
Pathetic!
Just cowering in there!
They're planning
to expel the gang...
at tomorrow's campus assembly.
The odds are bad,
but we're gonna fight them!
We'll take some of them with us!
Masao?
Yuuko...
Hi.
What happened? You're hurt!
Oh, I see.
Yeah. Pretty pathetic, huh?
But I understand how Abe feels.
The campus has changed.
It was almost better when
they were fighting all the time.
If you don't do something...
I can't do it.
Stop it! Masao,
get a hold of yourself!
What?
Is something wrong, Yuuko?
Please, go back to
being strong. Help me!
Otherwise, I'll...
I'm afraid I'll change, too.
Yuuko...
Make love to me.
I'm sorry.
Masao!
It's all right.
Just hold me like this.
I thought you'd come.
What's wrong? Come in!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
What's the problem?
You came because you
have doubts, didn't you?
I'm going to remove them!
Take my baptism and
become my soul slave!
No!
Did that little demon
give you this scar?
It will never heal clean.
That little coward
drove you here.
So long as you carry that scar,
he will never make love to you.
That's it, isn't it?
He couldn't return
your love, could he?
No!
Wretched creature.
Your words reject me...
but your body
is much more truthful.
So, this is Esedess'
beloved woman?
She'll make a fine diversion.
I'm glad you came, Miss Someya.
Now you belong to us.
Akira!
No!
Her love juices
taste like our own.
No!
As I thought.
Allow me to fully awaken her.
Masao, forgive me!
Well, I'm going.
You're really doing this?
Yeah.
It's impossible! Even if
Esedess could fight...!
If I don't come back,
get outta town. Got that?
What? I thought you'd turned
chickenshit and weren't coming.
Will you let me come with you?
No backing out, okay?
Right.
We are the outsiders.
The ones who have turned away
from the "decent" path.
No matter who the enemy is,
there's no excuse for running.
As long as we live,
this world is ours!
Now, let's take back our
campus from those lousy Gods!
Go get 'em, Boss!
- We'll slaughter 'em!
- Keep at it!
There's nothin'
to be scared of!
You're the demon
lord Esedess, right?
Because of the importance
of the announcement...
to be made at today's
campus assembly...
all students are
required to attend.
Anyone absent without reason
will be punished severely...
for failure to appear!
Repeat, because of the
importance of the announcement...
to be made at today's
campus assembly...
all students are
required to attend.
Anyone absent without reason
will be punished severely...
Outta the way! Yuuko!
Yuuko!
Dammit, move! Out of my way!
Uh-oh, Kusanagi's got
'em all brainwashed!
Ladies and gentlemen!
There is only one reason I
have called you together today.
It was to reveal a truth
which must be told.
We of the student council
and the discipline squads...
have been working hard to
clean up this campus...
and restore its
tarnished name!
You all know which group is
responsible for ruining it!
It is the group we refer
to as the outsiders!
I believed sincerely
that our duty was...
to find a way to expel these
disruptors of our academic life!
However, in the
course of doing this...
we discovered
a shocking truth!
It is a truth which seems
to defy common sense...
but, as the truth.
It must be faced!
To confess this truth,
I have brought a witness:
Akira Mido!
Akira!
I stand before you all because
I must confess my shame!
Because I must confess it for my
best friend who stands here now.
It's something
I deeply regret doing.
When I saw that my friend,
presumed dead in the...
great Himalayan quake,
had returned safely...
I was naturally overjoyed.
But he wasn't the
friend I remembered!
Ever since he returned...
strange things have
occurred on this campus.
And, against my better
judgment, I became involved.
And now...
Akira!
Look at me!
This horrible form!
He began with me and
gave many other students...
similarly hideous
bodies and powers...
so that he could
make the school his own!
Masao Sera! He is...
a demon!
Demons... Demons... A demon...
Yes! Drive them
from the campus!
Careful, Masao.
Shit, there's no end to them!
I'll kill that son of a bitch!
Don't! It's too dangerous!
What?
So, you reveal your
true form at last, Esedess!
Kill him! He isn't human!
Killing him isn't a sin!
Kill him!
Kill! Kill! Kill! Kill!
Sorry, Masao.
You did that to save me!
Forget it! They were going
to try to kill us eventually!
Fight, you lowly worms!
Shit!
You've served your purpose.
Akira!
Guys, clear a path!
I'm taking him down!
Gotcha! Okay, guys!
Full power!
Come on, Masao!
Right!
What?
What's wrong? Try and breach
this wall of light to strike me!
You can't! Even the demon lord
Esedess is no match for me!
Fear me, demonic creatures!
Fear the light of my holy power!
We're in trouble!
Masao, do something!
Back! Back to your
eternal darkness!
In the name of justice,
we fight by your side!
Kano!
Asshole! Just had to wait
for the climax, didn't you?
Yuuko!
Damn you!
Look! Look! So hard,
even though she's unconscious.
KUSANAGI!
Masao...
Yuuko!
What's wrong, Masao?
Don't you want to kill me?
Follow me and I'll show
you something interesting.
Follow Masao!
They're trying
to slow us down!
Why don't you fight THESE?
Kusanagi!
Out of my way!
There you are!
Quite a fix, Esedess.
Try as you might,
you can't move in there.
Observe!
My magnificent form!
A demon like you may find it
difficult to gaze upon my glory!
Now bow at my feet...
and beg forgiveness for
your hideous form, Esedess!
Sacrifice your soul
and praise me with joy!
Do that and this woman's
doubts will be cleared away.
She has now accepted
the love of the Gods.
Her body can never
accept a demon like you.
I'll tell you why, Esedess.
She is one of us!
One of the Gods!
You're lying!
Why are you so surprised?
This is only the truth, Esedess.
I will say this in
her defense, though:
She wasn't lying in
order to get close to you...
because she didn't even
suspect the truth herself!
Yuuko!
It seems she's chosen to be
with her own kind...
rather than with a
filthy "thing" like you.
Tell me, do you want this?
Yes! Yes!
You son of a bitch!
Behave.
Esedess, she's chosen
me instead of you.
Accept the truth!
Although, the funny thing is...
the thing that made her
your greatest weakness...
wasn't even her
godly blood, was it?
What's wrong? Are you crying?
Accept the truth, coward!
Well, let me show you something
even more interesting!
She'll prove she does this
willingly! Now start!
This is her true face!
Moan for me,
like you did last night!
What the...?
That scream...
Cry! Scream, Esedess!
Ma... sa... o...!
Masao!
Shut up! Shut up!
KUSANAGI!!!
Impossible... How could
a demon... have beaten me...?
Yuuko...
No!
Please, stay away...
Yuuko...!
Please...
Miss Someya.
Come.
Doctor!
Yuuko!
Train yourself more, young man.
No, wait!
Yuuko! YUUKO!!!
What's that?
Masao...
Something's changed inside him.
Masao, you're not...!
You're not going to destroy
the world again, are you?
Say you won't!
You aren't the old Esedess!
You're Masao Sera, right?
So, please! Please!
When the ancient seal of
the Gods is opened...
the earth will once again
be covered by the fires of hell.
Evil spirits will dominate...
and men's souls
will rot with evil.
The earth will be drowned
in an ocean of blood...
and the flames will rise
up to scorch the heavens.
Civilization will
lose all reason...
and human society will
collapse beyond recognition.
But do not be saddened by
this, children of man.
Rather than destruction,
it shall be a beginning.
New life will be brought
to your decrepit world.
But it shall be life born in
pain, and all living things...
will be crucified on
the cross of fate.
Amidst this chaos, the true
nature of the world...
will be revealed in whole and
its true form shall be restored.
When this happens, man will,
for the first time...
be freed of the yoke of the old
gods and regain self-determination.
Many have tried,
but none can escape...
the destiny that
is called evolution.
The king of the underworld,
awakened from his long sleep...
tempts mankind towards chaos.
Here, human history ends.
A new age of
life is beginning.