Seiichi...
Seiichi!
Seiichi, where are you?
Rin, I'm over here.
Come here.
Wait for me, Seiichi.
I'm coming for you now!
What's wrong?
Seiichi, I can't come to you.
I can't reach you
chained up like this!
I see.
You don't want to come.
That's not true!
Really?
Really!
Hm... You seem
to be telling the truth.
You look like you want it so badly,
you could almost die.
Look.
Relish it.
Are you happy, Rin?
Seiichi...
Seiichi!
Who's there?
Dad!
Seiichi...
How could you do this to me?
Seiichi! Seiichi!
Seiichi?
The apartment manager.
Oh, my. You're all worn out
from your unexpected move.
I want to show you
around the Kazahana Inn.
So please get up, okay?
Maison Plaisir
The Queen of the Night: Part I
My name is Seiichi Itoh.
I'm studying for my second try
at the college entrance exams.
I came here for the final
stages of my studies.
At least, that's the polite reason
I'm here.
The truth is...
Well, you'll find that out
soon enough.
The second floor toilet is just
to the side of your room, Seiichi.
And as for the room
down the hall...
That door must never
be opened.
By that, you mean...
It just won't open
no matter how much you jiggle it.
This is where you hang your clothes
to dry or do a little sunbathing.
Must get them nice and soft, huh?
Wha...
Let me introduce you.
This is Hiro Haga,
the town council leader.
They call him
the Guardian of the Town.
Hi there!
Um, hello. How do you do?
Ah! Such a spirited
greeting you gave!
On patrol, Councilman?
M-M-Miyuki, is that you?
As you can see,
he's got the hots for Miyuki.
No!
Oh, no! Time for
my neighborhood patrol!
We shall meet again!
Why'd he jump
over the wall?
Well, I'm headed
back to the office.
Take care of the rest, Miyuki.
Sure thing.
Um, Miss Miyuki?
Is that Nagi Yukimura character
a guy or a girl?
I'm not really sure myself.
Hm...
And your chief councilman...
He's sorta "weird," huh?
You're asking...
if he's "weird"?
That's a difficult question.
What makes a person "weird"?
What makes them "normal"?
I don't think anyone
can answer that question.
Perhaps some stray
from what is accepted behavior,
but perhaps doing that
brings them happiness.
You think pretty deeply
about things, don't you?
I'm moved!
Oops. Sorry!
What am I babbling about?
Don't mind me,
just forget what I said.
"Normal," huh?
I'm not exactly
what you'd call "normal," either.
Seiichi...
I'm so happy.
Training my own mother!
Even if she is my dad's second wife
and not a blood relation.
Hmm? What's that sound?
Is this place haunted?
Hey! Keep it down!
I can't study
for my exams if you're...
Huh? It's not coming
from here, is it?
Wh- Who are you?
Sorry! I'm Kasumi Amamiya
from next door.
So, you're the guy who's
on strike two of his exams, huh?
Who cares
what strike I'm on?
Seiichi Itoh.
How do you do?
So, you're studying
for your exams, too, huh?
Um, well...
What's that?
Late night snack?
Nighty-night!
So, are you used
to the Kazahana Inn, yet?
Yeah, I'm settled in.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
It's thanks to your
kind hospitality, Miss Miyuki.
Even the way you got
my meal for me like this.
Huh?
Oh! I forgot!
We're out of soy sauce.
I'll go and buy some!
Oh, you don't have
to do it right now.
I'll be right back.
She's kinda impatient.
What's this?
Yo!
Holy...
Wh-what are you doing up here?
Is something troubling you, man?
No, not really.
Excellent!
Only by suffering
and overcoming that suffering...
can one truly grow!
Keep worrying!
It'll give you lots of worry lines!
I'm off!
That musclehead
doesn't know his strength!
Amou Family Grave
Thank you, Seiichi.
That's okay. I followed you
because I wanted to talk.
My late husband Heizou
died on this day of the month.
I visit his grave
once a month on this day.
You still love him,
don't you?
I'm sorry. I need to get
some groceries before I go home.
Go ahead
and go home without me.
What's this?
What the hell?
This is my room!
So that's what
the cucumber was for.
That technique won't
help you pass any exams.
Prickly...
Feels all prickly inside!
Still, she has
room for improvement.
Where does
this staircase lead to?
This is a training room!
I'm home!
Heizou, my love...
Heizou...
Heizou!
Heizou.
The man who trained her.
That notebook I saw...
It was the diary
Heizou kept of her training.
Their meeting
was inevitable.
His sense
as a bondage master...
Let him see the great potential
Miyuki had within her.
Shortly thereafter,
he began training her.
Perhaps it was due
to her natural talents,
but her training proceeded better
than Heizou could have expected.
They married,
but soon after opening
the Kazahana Inn,
illness took Heizou
from this world.
And Miyuki's training...
was left incomplete.
She still can't forget
about Heizou.
Heizou, my love!
You saw it, didn't you?
The secret of the Kazahana Inn.
Yukimura, why did you
bring me here?
To prepare you
for what has to come.
We wish for you
to complete her training.
The training of Miyuki Amou,
which was contracted
to my incompetent pupil, Heizou!
Who's there?
The chief of the Jonen Temple...
Sohun Chinen!
So, you are
Rin's adopted son, eh?
Y-You know my mother?
Indeed! And I know that
you ran away from your father...
after he stopped you
from training your new mother!
Master Sohun was Rin's master.
He also happens
to be the head...
of the real estate
company I work for.
You've read Heizou's notebook,
haven't you?
If you have,
then you understand.
How he only thought of Miyuki
as a tool for him to exploit.
How he thoughtlessly tied Miyuki
to himself emotionally.
She now sees him
as the ideal husband,
and she remains trapped
in that false world view.
Seiichi Itoh!
You must free Miyuki Amou's heart
from Heizou's control!
When you achieve that,
you shall...
reopen the path
to true bondage mastery!
Training?
What do you mean?
Don't try to fool me,
Miyuki.
I don't know what you mean!
What is it?
Seiichi, what are you doing?
You have to be more honest
with yourself!
Stop it, please!
I'll scream!
Then scream!
You do that.
Scream as loudly as you want!
No!
Miyuki, do you get wet
just hearing about training?
That's not true!
I wonder...
No, don't!
See? I knew it!
Stop it, please!
In short, this means you're
not a "normal" person, doesn't it?
You want it, don't you?
Your body can't help
but long for the touch of the rope.
Perhaps I had dreamed
for this day to finally come...
...since the moment
I first saw Seiichi.
I can't breathe!
Maybe because
your breasts are so big.
Does milk come out of them?
Of course not!
Well then, I'll have to squeeze
some of my juice out, instead.
No!
I climaxed from
the deepest core of my body.
He was just like Heizou.
And so, there was
no way I'd regret this.
I started to retrain her that day.
Hi. How's your studying
coming along?
Okay, I guess.
By the way,
have you been hearing
that weird sound lately?
Oh? Have you?
It bugs me so much
that I can't concentrate.
On your studies
or on your other activities?
The other activities,
of course.
You like that prickly feeling
a cucumber gives you, huh?
Huh? What are you
talking about?
No use...
I'm going to pop!
My ass is full!
Hold it in.
Please!
Let me use the toilet!
Do it from there.
I can't!
I'm too embarrassed!
Oh, it's coming out!
I can't hold it...
No! You shouldn't
waste food like this.
So just eat it later.
No, I couldn't!
Just hang in there
till I'm through.
Here I cum, Miss Miyuki.
The woman with
the day face and the night face...
Miyuki Amou.
By night,
a sex-crazed animal.
By day, an apartment manager
who shows none of that.
It reminded me of a flower
called "Moonflower."
It opens up in the late afternoon
through the evening.
In the morning,
it closes its blossoms.
Such a sad flower.
Its image overlapped
with her in my mind.
And in the language of flowers,
it means "illicit Love Affair."
I found it amusing how it echoed
her relationship with Heizou.
So I decided to use
Heizou's techniques on her.
I was confident that they would
have the best results on her.
Seiichi, this is what
Heizou used to do to me!
Stop it, please!
I'm afraid we can't.
Please! Don't!
Then how about this?
No!
It hurts!
Forgive me.
Please forgive me, Seiichi!
It's not your fault,
but I just can't do this!
What's wrong with it?
What's with that look?
Don't you want this?
I know I shouldn't be,
but I'm reminded of Heizou!
Please... untie me!
So you don't like it
when I do it?
It's my fault.
Heizou was Heizou.
And Seiichi, you're still naive.
So you're saying
I suck at this?
Seiichi...
I figured you'd
come to me eventually.
You're here to say that
unless you improve your techniques,
you'll never free Miyuki's heart
from Heizou's control, correct?
Am I wrong?
Hmm...
In that case...
Use this room
to perfect your technique!
Yes, sir!
Make your roping
techniques faster!
Go on!
Practice every trick exactly!
Don't neglect
any of the essentials!
And finally...
Train yourself!
At first, I was
very impatient with her.
But as her responses improved,
I responded to her in turn.
Councilman!
Hi!
Lately, when I'm with her,
I feel strangely at ease.
Even when we aren't training,
I always want to be with her.
It's as though
we were lovers.
That sweet feeling I had...
Of course, that's not what a bondage
master is supposed to feel.
I decided to modify the techniques
that had failed Heizou before.
Seiichi, no!
This technique is...
What are you talking about?
Your cunt is dripping wet from this!
But you're making me do it
in such an embarrassing way!
Okay, then we'll
go for a walk!
Let's go outside like this!
No! Don't!
Oh, no... I'm going to cum!
Not yet! Do it
where everyone can see!
Please, stop it!
Here we go!
No! I'm so ashamed!
No use...
Can't hold on anymore.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's snowing.
Come in.
Miss Miyuki.
What sort of special request?
You don't mean...
Hang you up in the snow?
Seiichi...
As you wish.
She was lovely.
The snow settled
softly upon her.
It was like she was
a natural part of the scenery.
Quite elegant, in fact.
But what did she
expect me to do now?
If we keep this up...
Miss Miyuki!
We should stop this!
Longer... Leave me
a bit longer, Seiichi...
Why do you want
to go this far?
If you keep this up,
you'll die!
Miss Miyuki! Miss Miyuki!
Are you all right?
Seiichi...
Heizou is finally vanishing
from inside of me.
What I loved was
his techniques, not him.
Let me say
my last farewell to him.
You're sure about this?
Heizou...Farewell.
Ta...ka...sa...go...
Sohun, really!
You're not a Shinto priest,
so quit it with that prayer!
- Oh, right.
- Yes, Master!
What a weird monk!
In any case, congratulations.
Right, Seiichi and Miyuki?
I hope it isn't
too shocking...
that I ended up
marrying Miyuki.
Okay, everyone! Come see
the results of our training!
Oh, Master Seiichi!
I love you with all my heart!
Here it comes!
The trainer
and the trained...
There must be a connection
between the hearts of both.
Perhaps it's love
that binds them.
Yes, that's what training is.
The ultimate
expression of love.
I had gained a flower...
that could greet the dawn
in full blossom.
And with it, the greatest
happiness in the world.
Master Seiichi...
Cold love is...
staring you in the eye.
It affected the other...
person in the other direction.
Reciting an...
explosive memory.
Discovering love for the first time.
Angry, angry last girlfriend.
Look at the back of the nocturne.
It's the sort of time when it drifted...
lightly, lightly.
Out in the country...
Love intended that one.
I could see from memory...
spreading out, spreading out.
I want to know...
someone very closely.