Preparing for my next attempt
at the college entrance exams,
I'd come to the Kazahana Inn
to finalize my studies.
But, before I knew it,
I was doing this...
and that...
...and all kinds of things.
At last, I ended up marrying Miyuki,
the apartment manager.
This all began because
I'd trained my stepmother, Rin.
I'm a bondage master, you see.
The path of a dominator
is a slippery slope.
And, to become
a true bondage master,
I had a lot more
studying to do.
Maison Plaisir
The Queen of the Night: Part II
You want this now?
If you do, tell me.
Just letting it drip down
like this is bad manners.
Master Seiichi... Please put
your treasure inside of me now!
Like this?
Master Seiichi!
Quick Study Guide
for Final Exams
Dictionary for
Chinese Characters
How does it feel?
Tell me how it feels,
using 20 characters.
You hurt me when you do it!
Master Seiichi!
That's exactly 20 characters!
Night after night...
I can't take it anymore!
How can I study
with all this noise?
For God's sake,
those two...
I just wish they'd
cut it out for once!
If I don't talk
to them about it,
I'll go out of my mind!
Master Seiichi, you bully...
Oh, yes...
I mean, this sucks!
It's okay for me,
I guess.
Here I cum!
Master Seiichi...
Study... Gotta... study...
I'm falling behind.
Okay, let's begin
our New Year's talent show!
Okay, what sort of stunt
do you have for us today?
Miyuki, more, please.
Sure thing.
...looking forward to it.
This is your host, John Birabira.
And I'm Hanami.
Pleased to meet you!
Yes, pleased to meet you.
Hee-ya!
Hi, man!
How're you doing?
M- Mr. Haga...?
Good evening.
M- Miyuki! What a surprise!
Big surprise...
You asshole!
See you later, man!
What are you trying to do?
What do you mean?
My ass! My anus!
Um, I mean...
Exams! The exams!
You haven't studied at all,
have you?
Um, I have studied
a bit, but...
Not a bit at night, right?
I can hear you
clearly enough!
Well... Yeah.
Miyuki, you have to crack
the whip on him a little!
He's gonna
fail his exams again!
Right, but we were
studying grammar before.
20-character sentences.
Jeez! We're just gonna
have to separate you two!
Oh? Do we have a visitor?
I'll go check.
Sheesh! No one cares
what happens to my ass.
What did you say?
Nothing!
Seiichi?
What is it?
Seiichi, you have a visitor.
I do?
Hi, Big Brother!
Kiriko!
- I'm here!
- But why? I thought Rin...
I mean, I thought Mom
forbade you to come here!
Yeah... I guess.
What do you mean,
you guess?
Anyway, come to my room,
so we can talk.
Ow! That hurts!
Big Brother, you're hurting me!
Shut up and come on!
Hey!
Dammit! Don't they
care about my ass?
This is my sister,
Kiriko ltoh.
My sister,
but not by blood.
Still, we were raised together
after the separation,
and I feel like I'm
really her brother.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is the first time we've met.
That's right!
It's nice to meet you,
Big Sister Miyuki!
I'm Kiriko,
Seiichi's little sister.
It's a pleasure
meeting with you finally.
Wait, are they
sisters-in-law, now?
Man, we have so many steps
and in-laws in this family.
Well, it's not like it matters.
So, what's the story, Kiriko,
showing up here like this?
Did something happen?
I am never, ever
going home again!
You had a fight?
Lots of them! I just can't live
with Mom and Dad anymore!
That's why I didn't
come to your wedding!
Whoa, whoa!
Don't get us involved...
in some stupid argument
with our parents.
What are you saying?
You're the cause of it!
I'm the cause?
Um, why don't I
make some tea?
Okay, you've got me.
You mind telling me
what this is about?
Look, Big Brother...
I... saw it all.
Saw what?
What you and... she... did.
I saw it!
I was so shocked to see
you taking her like that!
Because I love you,
Big Brother!
Kiriko, what are you...
I'm able to do this
for you, Seiichi!
Please... do to me
what you did to her!
I'll do anything you want!
I just want
to make you happy!
Is that how it is?
Well, I don't mind.
A halfhearted training
is hell for a woman.
I think it'd be best
if you handled this.
Hm... I appreciate
you saying that, but...
But the truth was,
I had mixed feelings about it.
Rin and Kiriko.
They both saw me as a man.
And there was
a reason for that.
Big Brother...
The truth is,
they aren't related by blood.
Kiriko was Rin's former husband's
daughter from a previous marriage.
After his death,
Rin adopted her.
If I trained Kiriko,
what about Rin?
They may be mother and daughter,
but they're both women.
It may sound strange, but lately,
they've become rivals.
Here... I want Big Brother
inside of me here!
In here!
We might not be related by blood,
but I still thought of her...
as my darling sister.
Should I open up
the path of bondage to her?
It's a path from which
you cannot turn back.
Hello, ltoh residence.
Seiichi? Have you seen Kiriko,
by any chance?
Yeah.
For now, there's an empty
apartment we can let her stay in.
Oh, that woman's hopeless.
Tell her to come home
in a few days.
And Seiichi...
Don't train her. All right?
You understand?
That'll be up to Kiriko.
No one can stop her.
No! No! Absolutely not!
You'd train your own sister?
The same would apply
to you, Rin.
You're jealous of her,
aren't you?
Seiichi!
In any case, I'll tell her
to come home as soon as possible.
Goodbye.
Seiichi!
I heard it all from Rin.
First the mother,
now the sister.
Your karma is deep
and twisted, my friend.
You don't have to say it
like that, Master!
Then why are you hesitating?
It's Rin.
What? Don't like eating
the egg with the chicken?
Stop talking like that!
It's not unreasonable
for Rin to try and stop you.
She is a woman, after all.
She's jealous of Kiriko!
As I thought.
Seiichi...
A true bondage master
can use ordinary jealousy...
as a tool to throw
the heart into chaos!
It is the definitive battle
between man and woman!
If you are ready to risk
your very life, then go for it!
Go! Go now, Seiichi!
I've decided! I'll do it!
Kiriko is a woman!
And it is my destiny
to train women!
So, I'll do it!
I feel sorta embarrassed.
There's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
They've grown so big.
And so lovely, too.
Nicely firm.
Let me get a good look at you.
This is so embarrassing!
Kiriko! If you're not up for this,
I won't do it!
Sorry.
All right.
Go lie down.
Let's get a better look at you.
Hm, you've been busy
down here, all right.
It's really red.
That's not true!
I haven't used it at all!
You're the first guy
who's ever seen it.
I'm the first?
I'm glad, Kiriko.
You're licking me.
Big Brother,
you're licking my cunt!
Kiriko, here I go.
Okay.
Big Brother is inside of me.
It hurts! It hurts, but...
But I'm happy!
It feels so good!
I feel so good!
That's the way, Kiriko.
Nice and tight.
Make it tighter for me.
You mean... like this?
Yeah... That's the way.
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum too,
Big Brother!
Here it comes!
It tastes like you, Big Brother.
So, what's up, Kasumi?
Oh, Nagi!
Hi there.
So, you're all finished studying?
About that...
Yeah...
Seiichi's doing it
with his sister now!
Kiriko, huh?
There are lines
you just shouldn't cross!
Wow. Way to go, Seiichi.
Honestly, the noise Miyuki makes
is bad enough!
Now it's gonna be
twice as loud!
Oh, God, I really can't
take it anymore!
What if you joined in?
Me? Oh, come on, Nagi!
You wanna see my ass
that badly?
Huh?
Okay, time to piss.
Ow! It hurts!
Big Brother, this hurts!
Ow! Ow! Stop it!
Hey! Be quiet!
It only hurts at first!
Rin was like this at first, too!
You did this to her, too?
Of course.
She did it gladly.
Then I'll do it! Do it again!
Come on.
Don't forget about this.
Go on.
You can let it out now.
Good, Kiriko. Well done.
You did a good job!
Um, Miyuki...
Are you sure this is okay?
What, is the rice burned?
No, not that! I mean the situation
with Seiichi and Kiriko!
They really get along well.
Not that!
You're really okay with this?
Having your husband
screwing another woman!
Kasumi...
Hm? What?
I trust Seiichi.
And so I don't waver,
in my body or my heart.
Seiichi, what's happening
with Kiriko?
Did you and Kiriko honestly...
I told you before, didn't I?
No, don't!
It's too much for her!
I am not gonna
let you beat me!
Kiriko's training
went unexpectedly well.
I imagine it was due
to her rivalry with Rin.
But, while it was
going smoothly,
I was trapped between
mother and daughter.
I couldn't favor
one over the other,
and in my heart I prayed
that they would make up.
Yes?
Seiichi, we've got trouble!
No way! I'm not going home!
Bleaugh!
Oh, you pain in the neck!
I'll drag you home
if I have to!
Go to it!
Hiya, man!
C- Councilman!
I want you
to hand over that lady.
Why are you doing this,
Councilman?
Well, I heard someone
was disturbing the peace.
Please obey your mother,
and release your sister now,
and I won't have to hurt you.
Big Brother!
Forget it! I'm not
handing her over to you!
Come on, man!
Be reasonable and give her to us!
No way!
- Release her!
- I said no!
Release her at once!
Then I'll do it by force!
Who did that?
Only a fool doesn't know
how to mind his own business!
Begone with you!
That voice!
It's Sohun!
Sohun Chinen!
You dare meddle in this?
I know what I'm doing!
Away with you!
I was just doing her a favor!
But if you're
challenging me, I accept!
Hee-yaa!
Simpleminded fool!
- Seiichi!
- Big Brother!
Both of you, come up here!
Sorry, Miyuki.
Could you stay here?
This is your punishment
for not getting along!
Each one of you gets half!
See? He felt so good at having me
lick first that he closed his eyes!
No, it's because
I was sucking on his balls!
Oh, like that would
ever get him off!
Kiriko, out of my way!
What a racket.
Um, maybe I should
turn on the TV.
- No, thank you! More, please!
Eat that much
and you'll get fat!
I'm still growing!
I'm not an old lady,
like you!
What was that?
Well, it's true, isn't it?
Would you two cut it out?
So, how are things
with Rin and Kiriko?
Nothing I try
seems to do any good.
They're both too stubborn!
Rin is so wild at heart!
And Kiriko's a grown woman.
It must irritate her.
Just dealing with one of them
is hard enough.
I can't handle both of them
at the same time.
What should I do?
Fool!
Did you not have the answer
from the very start?
You must forcibly heal
their estrangement by yourself!
There's no way!
There is one thing we can try
with them together.
Grilled Hot
octopus stew
Come on, it's New Year's.
You can smile, at least.
I am smiling!
Because I'm visiting the temple
with you, Big Brother!
Isn't Miyuki coming?
She'll be waiting for us later.
Let's go and pay
our respects.
Anybody home?
Sohun?
That's strange.
Must be out for New Year's.
Okay, let's have our first session
of the new year!
Strip down, both of you!
What, in here?
Seiichi, start with me!
No, with me!
Whoa, whoa!
Both of you, together!
You have to do each other!
"Do each other"?
You want me to fuck her?
- Forget it!
God, you two are
really stubborn women!
Hey! Miyuki!
Miyuki?
M- Miyuki, what is this?
Happy New Year, Mother.
Mother, I'd like you
to use this.
No, I'm not ready!
It's too soon!
But, Mother,
look how wet you are.
I'm getting to fuck
Seiichi's own mother!
It's in my ass!
I'm getting it from both ends!
I feel them both
hitting inside of me!
Okay, Miyuki. Let's do it.
Right.
Kiriko?
Now it's your turn.
How does it feel, Kiriko?
It feels so weird!
It feels real good!
Miyuki, switch places.
Okay.
Ready?
Lower your crotch slowly.
No! I don't want
to fuck my mom!
Kiriko! Your body is
so developed now!
You really are a woman.
And Mom, your body
is so soft! It feels so good!
Mom, forgive me!
I've been so bad!
It's all right, Kiriko.
I was just jealous of you
because you're in your prime.
All right!
Well done, both of you!
And now, your reward!
And a bonus!
See? Get them
to touch flesh to flesh,
and it loosens their hearts.
Well done, Master Seiichi!
No, it wouldn't have worked
without your help.
Thank you.
Okay, let's get some
real bondage action going here!
Oh, Master Seiichi...
I love you so much.
And so, it all ended well.
As a bondage master,
I was able to repair...
the relationship
between mother and daughter.
With this endeavor ended,
I look forward
to future challenges!
Cold love...
is staring you in the eye.
It affected the other...
person in the other direction.
Reciting an...
explosive memory.
Discovering love for the first time.
Angry, angry last girlfriend.
Look at the back of the nocturne.
It's the sort of time when it drifted...
lightly, lightly.
Out in the country...
Iove intended that one.
I could see from memory...
spreading out, spreading out.
I want to know...
someone very closely.