House of the Forbidden Fruit
Well? Have you found them?
Yes, Mother. They are surprisingly close.
The blood runs true.
It seems they are at the top of
their class at the university.
Perfect. I want you to proceed immediately.
I thought you'd say that.
I'm already on my way.
Then we will be returning
tomorrow afternoon, so...
Understood.
Hey, Kira, did you do something
to get called on the carpet?
Who knows?
No idea? Didn't lay a finger on
the professor's grandchild?
Quit it. You were the one who
made her cry, remember?
I just gave her advice.
Gave her advice and then ate her anyway.
It's my nature to savor the
delicacies put before me.
No matter what...
...be prepared for it.
Because of the generous donation,
it's just a matter of confirming your
choice of graduate students.
Then it is all right, is it not?
Well, here they are.
Miss Eterna Gloria, let me introduce you.
Kira of Akushi and Beowulf Heine.
Really? These two?
The Gloria family.
Do you know them?
Well, the name ranks high among
the world's richest families.
An invitation from that distinguished family...
Basically, this is the proposition:
As you two are consistently at
the top of your class here,
the Gloria family is asking you
to be their tutors.
I can't refuse such a beautiful,
commanding lady. Can I, Kira?
I am asking for the sake of
my younger sisters.
My own education has nothing
to do with this.
My mother will be returning to
the house tomorrow morning.
If you are interested, we ask that you
visit at that time.
Eterna Gloria?
She seems to be a very rigid person.
She's a fine woman, isn't she?
Women who are on guard like that
set my soul on fire.
It's my nature to savor delicacies
that aren't put before me.
See ya!
Miss?
I have decided that I shall undertake
to be your tutor.
I do not need one!
Well, let's get going.
You are a forceful person, are you not?
Don't you like forceful men?
No, I don't!
Cecil! Cecil, Sister!
What's wrong?
Oh no! Really? A tutor?
Don't make me laugh.
Who is that?
He's supposed to be Miss Eterna's tutor.
Hey, what about my teacher?
He's supposed to arrive tomorrow.
I wish he'd hurry up and get here!
Wow! What a huge house!
Please do not raise your voice.
Don't worry about it, Eterna.
I do not remember giving you leave
to use my first name.
You'll call me "Teacher", right?
Kira, this will be a super feast!
Yes, that's right.
It was so sudden, yesterday that...
Lisa?
Yes!
Is my teacher here?
Not yet.
I wish the teacher would get here.
I was so excited last night
that I couldn't sleep!
Madam hasn't returned yet, so please
wait in your room.
I'll notify you when they arrive.
Okay!
Assuming that they arrive safely.
That's it! I thought of something good!
I'm so smart!
Excuse me...
Are you Mr. Kira of Akushi?
Yes, I am.
I got it right then? Wow, I'm great!
And you are?
I'm Cecil. Please call me Cecil.
I've come to pick you up.
Sorry! It seems I'm late.
I...
Sorry!
Shall we leave then?
Yes!
I'm surprised it's a Volvo.
It's because they're very sturdy.
Mr. Kira, is it all right if I drive?
Of course.
Are you ready then?!
Ready?
Well, here I go!
It's okay. Volvo's are very sturdy.
It's not that!
They're very sturdy!
I understand why you were late.
Yes, I'm driving very safely.
You are?
That's funny.
Yes?
That car's following us.
That's creepy, isn't it?
Slow down a little. Let them pass us.
Yes! I understand.
That's the gas!
I'm so sorry!
Cecil, the wheel! The wheel!
I'm sorry!
It's not that I don't like these things,
but I don't think it's the right thing
to do while driving a car.
Mr. Kira, they're hitting us!
They keep hitting us!
Cecil, spread your legs and
lift up your skirt!
What? But that's...
Hurry!
Here!
Who are they?
Mr. Kira, you...
Cecil?
Isn't there something you should
take care of?
Oh no!
Announcing the arrival of Kira of Akushi.
I hear Kira's here.
Yes, they've just arrived.
Yes, it seems they failed.
Yes, I should observe them in detail, right?
Then excuse me.
That those two would let men into
the Gloria mansion...
Are they thinking of making them
their successors?
No matter who may intervene, this city
will fall into my hands.
And the Gloria family too.
Welcome.
We were saved, because the Volvo
is such a sturdy car.
It's strange that you were involved
in such trouble.
It was my fault!
You just be quiet.
Are you all right?
I can't believe I did that.
Please sit down.
Yes.
Maybe you're a bit tired?
Perhaps.
How do you feel about the
tutoring proposal?
Please accept it.
I would have to meet the girls first.
Madam.
Is that so?
It seems that my eldest daughter
has another tutor,
so I will entrust the other four to you.
Four?
I don't mind if you include me as well.
I was just jesting.
Cecil, please escort Mr. Kira.
Yes!
You've got bad manners, Miss Maid.
What scheme are you cooking up?
Me? Nothing!
Come on!
Why were you listening?
Nothing!
That's a lie, isn't it?
Since I've been here, I've seen you
acting strange many times.
What are you hiding?
You don't have to say if you don't want to.
But in time, you'll want to.
Wow! You're Japanese!
That makes me happy!
Mister, as a sign of our new friendship,
have a drink!
Naomi is from Sai.
Sai? Oh, you mean Saitama, right?
Come on now, don't say it that way!
You mean Miss Naomi is adopted?
Yes, that's the way it is.
Everyone except Miss Eterna is adopted.
Well, let's have a drink!
Well, just one.
Whoa, can you drink!
Hey, another one! That way...
Naomi, you're drinking too much.
Chance!
A big exhibition!
What?
Miss Naomi!
No!
There's no reason for you to work, Mister!
Cecil likes it when you do this!
No!
Gotcha!
Cecil!
Tickle, tickle!
Sister?
Gitchee, gitchee goo!
See! She feels hot when someone sees her.
No, that's...
You're so wet!
No! Don't say that!
No!
When you start crying out like that,
I feel so strange.
Say, you like stuff like this, right?
Look! You're sopping wet.
No! Stop!
Please stop, Naomi! I'm embarrassed!
Stop it, already!
Ouch!
Cecil doesn't want to!
There's no one that "doesn't want to".
Oh well, so I'm a slut and
a drunk, so there!
But, Mister, I like your type!
Is Miss Naomi always like that?
Well, yes.
You're one of the daughters of
this house too?
Yes, I'm the second daughter.
Why are you dressed as a maid?
It's my punishment.
Punishment?
It's okay! I kind of like dressing like this.
Cecil!
Yes, Miss Eterna?
Have you seen Beowulf?
No.
It's time to study. What is he doing?
Does he intend to abandon his position
when he was the one to volunteer for it?
No, he isn't the type to leave
someone like you alone.
What was that?
Tell me. Won't you tell me what
you're hiding?
I'll tell you. I'll tell you,
so please...
Tell!
Forgive me!
Beowulf, what are you doing?
Yo, Kira! You want some too?
You are the worst kind of man.
With Lisa?! How beastly!
Cecil, bring her a blanket.
Yes!
Mr. Kira is so kind.
Oh no! The teacher might be here already!
My other sisters are Mary and Charm.
But this doesn't seem like a good time,
so I'll introduce you to them later.
Were you surprised?
You mean about Mr. Beowulf?
But Mr. Kira was so kind.
Cecil, you don't have to do that.
Yes, I do.
I've been told to take care of
your needs, Mr. Kira.
But you're a daughter of this house too.
No, I want to do it.
You're a strange lady, aren't you?
Yes!
Dinner's ready. Please come to
the dinning room.
I'll come right away.
Mary!
Mary, we looked all over for you!
I was sleeping in the flower garden!
Teacher?
Yes?
Here! For you!
They aren't so fresh any more.
They weren't supposed to be like this.
Don't worry. If you give them some water,
they'll perk up.
Really?!
Yes, really.
Mary, it's time for dinner.
I'll call Mr. Beowulf.
Thank you for earlier.
I didn't do anything.
No, someday I will return the favor.
Please excuse me.
Charm! Charm, it's time for dinner.
She must be really tired.
Mr. Kira!
Mr. Kira, please wait in the dining room.
Is this area off limits?
No, it's not that.
But it might be a little dangerous.
Charm!
Who is it?
It's time for dinner.
I don't need any.
Well, do you have any need of a tutor?
What? A tutor?
I don't need one!
We'll save that for later, but you
have to eat dinner, or...
I'm really busy right now!
Don't bother me!
There, there. You're a good baby.
Plymouth?
Mr. Kira?
Cecil, are you afraid of this baby?
It's all right. Baby's got a cute face.
Is that so? Charm's still busy?
Really.
She just got back from South Africa.
You know it's dangerous to
push her too far.
Naomi!
Maybe I got a bit drunk?
Cecil, please take Charm something
to snack on later.
Yes, Madam.
By the way, Mr. Kira, how did it go
with my daughters?
They are all intelligent ladies, so I
don't know who to teach first.
Hey, don't beat around the bush!
You have to decide soon,
or you'll seem rude!
Tonight's dinner doesn't suit my tastes.
Excuse me!
Excuse me for just a moment.
Teacher?
Teacher what about me?
I'm first, right?
That's right. Why don't we start tomorrow?
Tomorrow?! I'm looking forward to it!
So, this is Charm's room.
Password: Charm
I didn't think so.
It wouldn't be that easy.
Well, let's go at it for real then.
Assuming all the rooms are networked,
Michelle's room...
What tight security.
Here it is!
This is...
The data for the Gloria family's estates?!
Such a young woman is handling this?
It seems Charm is a special member
of the Gloria family.
For some reason, she's trying to hide that.
It's odd that they chose
grad students as tutors.
Yes? What is it?
Cecil?
What brings you here in the
middle of the night?
Did something happen?
If it's all right with you...
I wondered if you would like to
have me with you at night?
Of course, that's only if you wish,
Mr. Kira, but...
Cecil...
No, Mr. Kira, please be still.
Mr. Kira!
How can you be so self-sacrificing?
It's just because I like you, Mr. Kira.
This is saying, "I want it."
Please don't say it that way.
Do you want me?
Yes, I do. I want Mr. Kira to be in me.
Come here, Cecil.
Mr. Kira...
Put it in me, Mr. Kira, again and again.
Deeper and deeper!
Cecil...
Mr. Kira. Mr. Kira!
Mr. Kira, you have to stay with us, okay?
There, right there.
I feel so...
Mr. Kira! Mr. Kira!
I feel like I'm going to melt, Cecil.
I'm coming!
If you want to see the rest of the dream
Approach me carefully
The moon rules the night sky
It enfolds both of us
In its tender beams
Forever
Tears scatter into the night
Please hold in your hands
The future that will be someday
The dream I saw last summer
The shining road I followed
If I am with you
I can walk it
Believe in me
With your whole heart