Somebody! Anybody! Please!
What's wrong?
Charm, what's happened?
Damn! What happened here?
Hold on! You've got to hold on, Charm!
A doctor! Call a doctor!
House of the Forbidden Fruit
And the blue-collar jobs have been
transferred State-side?
Yes.
Unofficially, we've called it an
administrative move,
so no negative publicity has resulted.
I see. Let's make this the last time we meet.
The South African Public Prosecutor
shouldn't be coming here so often.
However, this time I'm on
a private vacation.
That's true.
It seems that her nerves are worn thin.
Is that so?
At any rate, have her rest quietly.
Charm must be in pretty bad shape.
Please take care.
What does she do when she
locks herself in her room?
Do you know?
No.
Have you heard anything?
You'll know soon enough.
The automotive company was
just camouflage.
Their real goal is the South African
diamond mines.
Those are the lifeblood of
the Gloria family.
That's why it took such a
heavy toll on Charm.
Mother, we can't push Charm any longer.
I know that!
Say, is Charm going to be all right?
Mary, you don't have to worry, okay?
Everything will be fine.
But!
So what do we do now?
What should we do?
Well, someone will have to be our
champion in place of Charm.
Mother, I'll do it!
I'm sorry, but you aren't the right one.
But who else is there?
If not me, then who?
Yes. You are not the only candidates.
But their virtue is unproven, isn't it?
That's correct.
But I believe that one of them
will prove to be right.
What do you mean?
At any rate, I will handle the situation.
Please don't cause any needless scenes.
Then you aren't good enough?
Mother seems to be pinning her hopes
on you and Kira.
On me and Kira?
The two of you are also descendants
of the Gloria family.
Is that so?
If you'll only be our champion,
I'll do anything.
Anything?
Do anything?
No!
We'll be seen!
Good! It's so good.
I'm all right, so leave me alone!
Madam.
Mr. Kira, what's the matter?
What's wrong with you?
You're usually so calm.
Calm?
It's simply a front.
Being the "champion" of this family
is simply a front?
So you've discovered the truth.
Madam...
From the outside looking in,
it seems as if I rule this family,
but in truth it is all Charm's work.
I can't do anything on my own.
Please cheer up.
Mr. Kira, I have to apologize to you.
I've been keeping a secret.
You and Mr. Beowulf are blood relations
of the Gloria family.
When you trace your family line,
it is mixed with our blood.
Why didn't you say something earlier?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to coerce you.
I wanted you to think of
this family as your own.
So that's how it is.
I am related to the Gloria family.
Plymouth?
Hey, Plymouth!
What do you want?
How are you feeling?
Plymouth? Have you seen Plymouth?
He's gone.
Don't worry.
Plymouth thinks you're his mother, right?
There's no reason he would stray very far.
I know...
Here!
See, he missed your smell.
Don't look! Don't touch!
Don't come close!
Is that your computer?
That's...
It's my private computer.
I'll borrow it for just a bit.
Hey!
Don't touch it!
It's okay.
Maybe you could leave some of
this work to me?
Leave it to you?
What do you mean?
It seems that I have the
same blood as you do.
The same blood?
Yes, the same bloodline.
Teacher?
What about the next problem?
Oh yes, another problem.
It's about the diamond mines
in South Africa.
Yes!
A mining company wishes to layoff
a large number of workers.
The government decides the company has
sufficient cause and allows the layoffs.
Of course, the diamond output
decreases dramatically.
At this rate, the business will soon
become bankrupt.
What would you do, Mary?
Well, I would... I would...
Raise their wages and...
Oh, but the government...
It's okay. I don't know what to do either.
What are you doing?
First, you take it out gently.
Mary!
Wow! It's true!
It's getting bigger!
Wow! It's so warm and hard!
It's big!
Now, just like an ice cream cone.
Naomi told me that if I did this,
then Teacher would be happy!
Teacher?
Yes...
Mary!
Don't!
Stop!
You mustn't!
No, let me go!
I'm the one who's supposed to
do things like that!
Why? Why can't I do them?
Why not?
I won't be a virgin forever!
Mary...
Cecil, you're jealous!
You want to keep Teacher all to yourself!
It's true, isn't it? It's true!
Stupid Cecil!
Mary...
What is it about her?
Why is Mary so special?
Mary lost her parents at an early age.
It seems that something happened
to her afterwards.
She won't say anything about it.
Now that she's part of the Gloria family,
we've decided that she'll never
have to suffer again.
So that's how it is.
But you can't keep her in
the hothouse forever.
Mary is already trying to
get out by herself.
Besides, there's a wind blowing
that will destroy the hothouse.
It may destroy me as well.
Yo! You doing it?
Doing what?
It's obvious! Scheming to become
this family's champion.
Not interested in the job.
Don't play stupid!
Enough wealth to support a whole country
would fall into your pocket.
At the rate it's going, I wonder about that.
It's not only the wealth, it's the women too.
Isn't it?
It seems if you can save the family
from the pinch it's in,
you get to be the "champion".
It'll be ME or you.
And?
Kira's realized it too.
The quick way to save this family is to
find out how Boone's hidden money flows.
If I can bury Boone with my own hands,
then everything else will have
a happy ending.
It's not like you to try so hard.
Yeah? Well, it's for you too.
Oops!
Tight security after all.
No!
Mary?
What's the matter?
Well...
I'm sorry about this afternoon.
This afternoon?
Cecil said...
She said that Teacher is afraid
of the thunder,
and to come and be with you.
You're so kind, aren't you, Mary?
Teacher?
Just now, your tongue...
You didn't like it?
This is embarrassing!
That's...
No, don't!
You're beautiful, Mary.
Beautiful? I'm beautiful?
Yes.
Teacher, I'm scared.
Scared?
I feel like I'm not going to be me anymore.
That's right. You're going to change, Mary.
Change?
I will?
Yes.
Teacher!
Mary?
No, it's okay.
Continue, Teacher. Please.
It hurts!
It hurts, but beyond that...
Beyond that is a place that feels good.
That's the place. You go there, Mary.
Go there and change.
Change?
I will?
Change!
Teacher, are you awake?
Mary!
Good morning, Teacher.
Good morning.
Teacher, I've had a flash of inspiration!
Yesterday's problem, the diamond mine.
I know a really important person
in South Africa.
If I asked him nicely,
I think he'd help us out.
Really?
That sounds like a good idea.
Isn't it?
That person said, "Mary, you're so cute!
I'd do anything for you!"
I've wanted to tell someone that
for a long time,
but everyone kept telling me not to worry,
so I've been waiting.
Well, so who is this person?
He's South Africa's president,
or something like that.
Mary, is his name...
A dance?
Yes, please!
You may not.
I know you don't make many requests,
but right now the Gloria family...
Michelle, Mary is...
It's for the sake of the Gloria family!
I want to do what I can!
I'm Charm's big sister!
But you...
Please let Mary do as she thinks best!
But...
I can't just sit here and do nothing anymore!
It's all right! Teacher will be with me!
Right, Teacher?
Yes.
As long as Teacher's with me,
I can do anything!
We have been expecting you, Mr. Boone.
To think that Mary would throw a party!
Do you think it's his idea?
Just what is Kira planning?
Cecil! Where's Cecil?!
Are you the one who invited me?
Who knows?
Is it wise for you to be frivolously dancing?
I hear the mining operation is floundering.
Mary!
Ladies and gentlemen, I am the one who
invited you here tonight,
my name is Mary Gloria.
What?
That's the South African Prosecutor.
Why is he here?
This evening my friend from
South Africa is joining us.
Please welcome President Robert.
For inviting me here this evening
to this grand dance,
I thank you very much.
But in truth, I am standing here with
my soul in torment.
It has come to my attention
that the Gloria family,
with whom my country has strong ties,
has been the victim of a dire mistake in
regards to their commercial enterprises.
I regret to report that large bribes have
filtered through the bureaucracy.
It has been determined that the funds for
the bribes came from the Boone Company.
These bribes have cost the Gloria family and
the citizens of my country large losses.
As a representative of the government,
I promise that a thorough investigation
will be made and strict penalties applied.
Mr. President?
Was that all right?
Yes, thank you!
It was for your sake, Miss.
If something like this can help you,
then call on me anytime.
Bastard!
Was it you?!
You told them everything, didn't you?!
I had no choice!
Shut up!
Quiet, please!
This is the House of Gloria.
I'll just keep this for you.
Ladies and Gentlemen, I have something
important to tell you.
I realize it is quite sudden,
but I am engaged to Kira Akushino.
He beat me to it.
That's too bad. Or is it?
Miss Mary!
You've been charged with felony tax evasion!
Are the allegations about South Africa true?
Is there any truth in the rumors about
the condition of your business?
Just one comment!
Just one comment, please!
Mr. Boone, please comment! Mr. Boone!
You damned Gloria family!
Congratulations!
Cecil...
Mr. Kira!
Cecil, you and I...
It's okay.
Cecil!
Only...
Only?
Sometimes,
do it with me too!
You did well, Mary.
I couldn't have done it if you
weren't there, Teacher.
I thought I was going to faint.
No, that wouldn't have happened.
And I'm not "Teacher" anymore.
We're engaged now, aren't we?
You'll always be my Teacher.
I'm so glad! It's so great!
Mary is so pretty.
Yes.
Maybe it's time for us to retire?
That's true.
Let's depend on them.
Yes!
Mary's changed.
No, maybe it's that the promise
she already had blossomed.
Her way of making others happy
with her own happiness
and her ability to make people take action
definitely suit her for the champion
of the Gloria family.
And...
Above all, she moved my soul.