Harumi's Bad Play
What do I do? It feels good...
I feel so good. This makes me so good.
No, what shall I do? It makes me feel better.
No!
I'm so wet, but I can't stop!
Ah, it feels good, it feels so good!
This pose makes me feel much better.
It's makes me crazy!
It's slippery.
No, inside of me...
I feel embarrassed, but it feels good.
I feel so good.
Good, good... I'm coming!
Wha, what?
Is this my room?
Yup, I'm sure.
Uhh, why is this girl here?
Plus, she's naked and in a strange pose...
How are you?
Who are you?
I'm Harumi.
Harumi?
Harumi, I don't know her but she's cute.
I wonder how old she is.
Umm, she has a nice skin, like a baby.
She's way different from my classmates.
She has small breast, but she has cute pink nipples.
With cute eyes, small mouth, and nice hair, like a doll.
Hey Harumi, what are you doing here?
I don't know what.
I see. Well, what happened to your clothes?
I don't know that either.
What's your name?
I'm Wataru.
Wataru, can I stay here for a while?
Can I stay with you?
I know that you're a nice person.
Yea, I'm not a bad guy but...
Ah, I knew it! So, can I stay here?
Can I stay here, Wataru? Please?
Ah, wait... Don't move around...
Wataru, I don't have a place to go.
I like your place, so please let me stay.
Even so, this place is too small.
Her parents must be looking for her.
I should call the police, but...
Is that a no, Wataru?
Well...
You don't like me, Wataru?
No, it's nothing like that.
Then why? I will want to stay here.
I want to stay with you.
Oh man...
Please, Wataru. Please let me stay, please?
Harumi...
Please, Wataru. I can do many things.
I'll do anything to please you, so please...
Harumi.
Okay?
You're unbuttoning my shirt, Harumi?
I want to see your body.
Uhh, I have nothing to show, umm...
Getting naked and rubbing together feels good.
Naked? Rubbing? Umm...
You don't know? It feels good when we both get naked and hold each other.
Yea, you're right. It will feel good. Ha ha ha...
Umm, it's very exciting, but I don't know.
I even get a hard at a public bath.
I could get in big trouble if this happens.
But I'm not forced to do anything, and she is trying to have fun, so it'll be okay.
Ha ha, great!
Wataru, do you feel good?
Ah, yup, I feel good. Your skin is very smooth.
Your skin is smooth also, Wataru.
Ha ha ha, Harumi, don't move too much.
It tickles.
Huh? What's this?
No, I'm going getting excited.
Wataru, I feel something hard.
That, that's nothing. Don't touch it, Harumi.
What's this? What's this, Wataru?
It's growing up.
Ah... ha ha. That is...
Hey, it's moving.
Harumi, don't look at it so much.
It's warm. What is this, what is this, Wataru?
That's my pet. It comes out sometimes.
What? Your pet?
Yea. Be gentle with it.
Ah, it's cute. What's the name?
Umm, ah, I call it Pochi. It is Pochi.
Ah, Pochi. You are cute!
I'm Harumi. Nice to meet you, Pochi.
Ha ha, so cute!
Harumi, that's enough.
No, I want to play more with Pochi.
— Pochi, why do you move like that?
— Ahh... don't touch it too much...
I see saliva from its mouth.
I got a little too excited...
So cute. I'm going to lick it.
You are so energetic now. How cute.
Ah, no... What kind of girl is she?
She is so good!
Having this technique, she is some girl!
When I think about it, who is she anyway?
It's not normal for a naked girl to come in my room and suddenly sucking my cock.
Good, there!
Shit! She's good!
Her small tongue pinpoints where I feel it most.
Oh, I can't stand it...
Wataru, I'm starting to feel strange now.
Huh? Feeling strange?
It's getting hot under my stomach.
Under your stomach?
Here... I feel hot here and it's anticipating.
Do you know why, Wataru?
Wataru, I feel good. I feel doing this. Right here...
Harumi, try not to touch it...
Ah, feels good...
Harumi.
Wataru, Wataru? I feel so good...
Wataru, what's happening here?
Wataru, it's so hot. It's becoming wet.
Wow, I never seen anyone masturbate like this!
Since she shaves her pussy, I can clearly see all her juices.
Man, so lusty!
But this is real masturbation and she feels it.
So loud. She will break her voice.
I can't stand this, I can't stand this anymore!
It's okay. Who cares? I don't give a fuck!
How people say to "eat whatever you can eat".
I would not ever forget it if I passed up this opportunity to do with her.
Listen Harumi. Pochi wants to go in there.
Pochi?
Yes. Pochi likes you, so he wants us to be together.
Here, like this... Pochi will go inside, Harumi.
Wataru, I'm scared.
Don't be scared. It'll feel good.
Harumi, don't you think so?
No...
Like that and like this.
No! I'm so scared, Wataru.
Yes. You look good, Harumi.
No...
Your small clam is moving and getting so wet.
You nasty girl. See, it's full of love juice. How nasty!
No!
Ah, looks delicious.
No... It feels weird.
Umm, so good. Tastes good, Harumi.
No...
You don't like it? You're twitching because you like it.
No, please Wataru! I'm scared...
Nothing to be scared of. You can be good friends with Pochi.
Wataru...
Do you feel Pochi's mouth touching your pussy?
No, stop it Wataru!
I'm worried that your hole looks too small.
But Pochi want to go in there, Harumi.
How is it, Harumi? How does Pochi feel?
It hurts!
This little girl is coming and loving the feeling of it. She's like a toy, so small and so tight.
Her pussy is small, so it feels great!
It's good, it's so good!
Oh no, Harumi. Pochi is about to cum.
Pochi, Pochi is...
How do you feel, Harumi?
She is good. Like a toy!
Ha ha ha, I can jump into action anytime.
Pochi recovers quickly. Look, ha ha ha!
Ouch, it hurts Wataru!
Doggy style feels tighter.
See, Pochi is pleased.
It hurts! Ouch!
It's like fucking an asshole.
It feels good.
I'm sure her real one is much tighter.
Okay, I'll give it a try. I don't think it's going to rip.
No, Wataru. Please, don't.
You have a cute hole, Harumi. It's so tight, I barely can stick my tongue in.
So tight, and it opens and closes.
Pochi will like it, Harumi.
I feel embarrassed, Wataru.
Come on, it's for Pochi, right?
Don't you like Pochi, Harumi?
I like Pochi, but... No...
Pochi is going in Harumi's asshole.
No, it's impossible.
Pochi really want to go in there. His mouth...
Ah, so tight... Ahh! It's in now!
Wow, I'm holding you with only my dick.
You are a good girl, Harumi.
Don't be scared okay?
Wataru, no, it hurts. It hurts, no...
Okay, I'll fuck you until Pochi comes out from your mouth!
Ouch, ouch...
Ha ha. Great, great! So tight. It's so great!
Her ass swallowed my entire cock.
This is excellent!
Hey, moan louder. It feels good, good!
Not one adult female has this tightness.
I can't stop, I won't stop!
Harumi, Pochi is coming again. Ahh!
Huh? Blood?
This is some problem.
Harumi, I didn't do it.
Pochi did it. He likes you so much, he wouldn't listen to me.
Do you understand? He is so into you, Harumi.
Open your mouth more. Yea, that's right. You're drooling so much.
I can't stop to see Pochi go in and out.
So cute, Harumi. You are so cute.
Oh, I'm coming again. Harumi, Pochi is coming! Ahh!
Huh? What?
Wha, wha, wha, what, Harumi?
Pochi, Pochi, Pochi!
Pochi!
What are you doing?
It's in!
Don't be too rough.
Hey Wataru, let's do more.
I want to do more so I will feel good.
I like to play with Pochi.
I love Pochi. So more and more, Wataru.
Wow, Wataru! Pochi is pushing, pushing me...
I feel good.
Ah, Pochi is pushing me hard in my pussy!
I want to do many thing to make you happy, Wataru.
I was born for that.
Ah, more, more! Pochi feels so big inside my pussy...
Pochi's head is hitting my sensitive part.
I feel so good, so great!
Ah! Wataru, he is really coming up my mouth.
I feel if Pochi is mixing up inside my body.
It's great! Wataru, Pochi is great. It feels so good! What happened to me?
I feel good.
I see. It was a little rough, but training her as a sex slave seemed to work.
Her lusty conscious is awake now
Okay, If that's the case, I'll fuck you up, Harumi!
Give me more, Wataru! Fuck me more!
He he he, Harumi, you have a nice body.
What is this?
You need to try harder if you like to please Pochi. Do you understand?
Yes.
Okay, good girl. So you can endure for Pochi?
Endure?
No problem. You can do it.
I believe you can do it.
It may hurt at first, but you can stand it, Harumi.
Wataru.
All right. Let's get busy!
Wow, it's great! I can see her pure skin color change to red.
Nail marks on her white skin.
How nasty!
Ha ha ha... I'm so fucking perverted!
No. I don't like it. No...
Harumi, be patient. This is for Pochi, right?
This will make Pochi happy.
More, more, more! Make more noise, or else, Pochi won't get well.
Ha ha ha! Scream more!
Not done yet, Harumi. Pochi is still energetic.
Now's not the time to sleep.
Let's play more, Harumi.
Let's play more and more.
Good, good. So good!
There is no better toy than this.
Hey, stick your ass out more.
Pochi can't get in there.
Yup, you. Here you go.
No, stop it...
Hey, I see something coming from your asshole.
You are so nasty. Oh, it's my saliva.
There, it's in again. Ha ha. Pochi loves it! There, there!
Harumi, use your ass more. There, there! It feels good. He he he...
I'll give you my hot cum. How does it feels?
Feels good!
Very nice. Hey, tighten your pussy so Pochi won't tear up. Squeeze it tighter, Harumi.
Ah, yes. Pochi is making noise in you, Harumi.
Ah, it feels good!
Come on Harumi, where's your energy?
Don't you love being fucked by Pochi?
What happened to you?
What?
Wow, Harumi's head...
What's happening?
Wow... Who are you?
Harumi's head is cut off from her body. Hey, Harumi!
What's happening?
Uhh... Hello. Umm... Who are you?
We are from the outer space. We made that girl.
She has a self-destructive protection for an emergency.
A self-destructive protection? Machine?
But we got a lot of data about the sexuality of human beings.
Data?
Well, Wataru.
Let's have fun.
No way.
END