l'm always thinking of you.
l know nothing is going to happen.
But l'm still thinking of you always.
l know my thoughts will never reach
you.
They shouldn't reach you.
Always and forever.
You don't realize it.
Since our paths never cross each other.
But still l expect something to happen.
Expectation?
Hope?
lf my wish comes true,
should l be hopeful?
Are you aware of me?
l'll be waiting for you always.
On this same path.
l'm still sleepy since you called
me out this early in the morning.
All right.
You better use protection.
Now...
What do you wanna do?
What are you doing?
Give me some money if
you want it that bad!
How shrewd you are.
This is a freebie.
You wanna kiss me?
You idiot! What are you thinking?
You make me sick.
l haven't seen you for a long time
Hey Kumi. Good morning.
What do you mean hey? Hozumi!
Don't worry.
lt's not like l'm gonna
lose anything, right?
By the way...
What's going on with you and Asakura?
Did you do it with him?
Oh boy. Nothing happened
between you two.
He's my type, so can l tease him a bit?
Go ahead if you want to...
l want Asakura, but
l want you too, Kumi.
Enough!
You don't like me?
No, l...
Alrighty, l guess l'll
attend class for once.
Wait for me.
Hey, you shouldn't bring manga to
class.
How many times do l have to tell you?
Sorry we're late.
Ah, Sakatsu.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes.
Really? Then have a seat.
Asakura.
Well umm... This isn't mine.
Hey, hey, it's not mine.
Matsui...
Come to the teacher's
office during lunch break!
l did a very bad thing.
lt's not good to lie, you know.
Sakatsu...
l came here to see
what's going on, but it's boring.
Really?
Hey, is that a real gun?
What?
No, l was just wondering.
Ah, l knew you would be here.
Oh, it's you, senior!
Somebody told me
you were here this morning.
So l was looking for you.
What the hell, senior!
Now l have to tell Asakura to
keep his mouth shut from now on!
Oh, he wasn't your customer.
Sorry about that.
Are you okay?
She's fine.
She's always like this.
l better get going.
Thanks, Sakatsu.
lt looks like he's gone.
Let's do this thing, shall we?
Stop it!
Kumi?
This is just wrong!
You wanna join in?
Let's go, Yu.
Yu!
What do you wanna do?
l wanna do it.
Stop...
What's this?
Here we go.
l can't hold it, Sakatsu.
l'm gonna come.
Call me Hozumi.
Hozumi...
lt's Yu's cock juice.
Lick it up.
Ouch!
lt hurts!
lt's not fair.
l wanna shoot it inside you.
Kumi always liked you.
Liked me?
So she doesn't like me now?
Grandma, it's gonna melt
if we don't hurry.
Fireworks?
l knew something bad might happen.
Curse...
lt's a curse!
Nanmaida, nanmaida, nanmaida...
Do you have any regrets about all this?
Why should l?
l'm glad you chose to do this with us.
But l get jealous very easily.
So...
l chose to do this on my own.
l don't care what everybody else
thinks...
...but it wouldn't be bad for
all three of us to be together.
l'll never have sex for money again.
l'll only do it with you.
l wanna have a baby soon.
What?
Stay with me forever and ever!
Okay.
l'm sorry, l fell asleep.
We were watching you sleep.
You looked real cute, Kumi!
Matsui! Do you know what you just did?
l'm running because l know what l did!
Hey you! Come with me.
l'm talking to you!
You're coming with me, right?
Yes.
What's up, Yu?
Matsui, you...
l'm taking you all, as hostages.
l was told he was a
normal college student.
Even a person who seems normal can
suddenly change into a psychopath.
l don't want you to cause any trouble...
Chief, you better listen to this!
What is it?
There's been gunfire.
ls it that gun?
l'm not positive, but
one person has been killed.
The suspect took the hostages
and confined himself in a room.
Find out the number of hostages,
and get some back up!
But we're dealing with just one suspect!
l don't want to think about it...
But if it's that gun,
more people are gonna die.
Shit! l wanna do it before l get caught.
l can't get it up.
Matsui, stop doing this
and give yourself up.
What did you say?
This all started because you...
l got a great idea.
Yu, take your clothes off!
What!
Looking good there.
What are you planning to do, Matsui!
Those are fresh panties.
You should be happy.
Kikuchi! Nakamoto!
Get over here!
lt's all his fault.
Keep doing it until he dies!
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, Asakura.
You too.
What a weird chick.
Go, go, go!
Find out what you can
and get back to me.
Where's the rest of your team?
Over there.
Hey Misaki!
Suck my cock.
No!
Then l'll kill him.
Nevermind.
No!
No...
Wake up!
Yu!
l heard it's a very popular store.
Oh, then why don't the
three of us go there?
l'm sure you two will love it.
Then call me or e-mail me
the day you guys are free.
l'll let you know what day
is best for all of us.
You can't choose a path
where everyone can be happy.
Everyone knows that.
You don't choose a path for others.
But you choose it for your own good.
You choose the path
that is best for you.
You feel it's right, but in
your mind you feel it's wrong.
But you still have to
keep on making choices.
You can't go on living
without making any choices.
Things you can grab hold of.
Things you can obtain easily.
You lost those things by
choosing your own path.
Calm scenery.
Quiet everyday life.
Ordinary words.
What do you wish for?
What did you wish for?
Sight that's laid out in front of you.
ls that what you wished for?
But l'm afraid that's reality.
You regret it after losing something.
Or are you blaming someone else?
You're the one who screwed things up.
lt was all your fault.
Episode 3-Taboo