You're surprised by what comes
to your mind all of a sudden...
And try to remember them
by turning back the clock.
lrreparable time...
Things didn't go smoothly then,
but it's different now.
lf l can live with you from now on...
...then l'll have no regrets.
Now and forever...
Even if everything
happened in a split second...
l will always be here.
From then and beyond.
So l wish l could see you here again.
According to this report, we only
know that the suspect is missing.
l want to get a search warrant and
look around the suspect's apartment.
lt's just a gun, isn't it?
But it's true that the gun
has been used in the murder.
You want to hear my honest
opinion, Chief Morikawa?
What do you make of it?
The murder did take place.
But l don't think the entire department
should've been called out.
What do you think?
Yes, you're right.
But l guess we had no choice
but to make that move.
We'll assign four departments to this
case, and recover the gun secretly.
The file says to send in two members
from each department.
But we do things a bit
differently from time to time.
Make sure this doesn't go public.
l understand.
l'm amazed to see that the department
is sending two members...
To take on this scandalous case.
You heard me talking.
l just used the department
to take action.
lt's the new owner of the gun.
l don't care what you do, but
maybe you should take it easy.
Well, it seems you
care about me now, huh?
l'm not worried about you.
l'll come back if there's a new owner.
Kaminada.
Be careful with what
you have in your pocket.
You mean this?
To tell you the truth,
l'm an upright citizen.
My family is a bit weird.
They all know it, but
they don't speak about it.
We're all bunch of strangers,
but they say we're a family.
Family...
What is the meaning of family?
Yu, this will be your mother
from now on.
Nice to meet you.
You're starting to
look like your father.
Really?
Yes.
l don't really remember, but
was dad a really handsome guy?
Yes, very.
Yu, l hope you grow up and
look just like your father.
Thank you for this meal.
Mother!
What's wrong?
Aren't you gonna continue?
l'll keep on watching.
You wanted me to do this, right?
Mother...
Why?
Hey, you started treating me
as if l'm not your mother, right?
lf l was your real mother,
you wouldn't be doing this, right?
No matter how many years
we've lived together...
We're still just a bunch of strangers.
Well...
l'm heading out!
See you later.
l'm heading out...
What's wrong?
Ah, l forgot something.
Sorry to say this, but can
you go ahead without me?
Okay, sure.
Mother...
Yu...
l'm not your mother.
Misako...
Yu...
Aren't you gonna come soon?
Yeah.
l'm disappointed.
Yu...
lt hurts!
Bad boy...
And?
lt went just as planned.
l already told X about it.
That punk...
What do you wanna do?
You know what l'm gonna do!
That's my gun!
What are you gonna do?
Well...
l wanna know what will happen, so...
You wanna know what
will happen too, right?
Chief, where exactly are we going?
We're not going to that suspect's...
We're just on patrol.
lt looks like l won't be
getting a promotion soon.
Oh, you were expecting a promotion?
Just kidding.
Why isn't anybody picking up the
phone?
Yes?
My name is Mizutani,
and l'm Yu's teacher.
Wait one second please.
Miss Mizutani...
Thank you so much for coming.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello Miss Mizutani...
Are you feeling well?
Excuse me...
l just came to check how Yu was
feeling...
Goodbye.
Miss Mizutani,
you should stay a bit longer.
What did you...
Oh my...
Are you okay?
No...
How does it feel, Yu?
lt's a bit different from you, Misako.
Really?
Hey, can l release it inside?
No...
Don't release it inside.
Do whatever you like.
Then l'll release it inside.
Well? Are you satisfied?
l'm gonna get pregnant...
Miss Mizutani, are you
gonna have my child?
l'm gonna shoot it inside again.
You destroyed it...
l'm not gonna let this
woman have your child.
Yeah, you're right.
l'm gonna have your child.
Now, give me more...
l heard a gunshot...
Who are you?
l'm a hunter.
Haven't you heard?
l'm your partner, Angel.
l didn't know.
So we're in the same profession...
What are you doing here?
l'm here to take back a lost article.
That's terrible...
l can let you go, but they'll kill you.
There's rumors about that gun...
The one who possesses
the gun will go mad, right?
Hey, hunter.
Are you actually sane right now?
Who knows?
lf certain ideas are labled amoral
so society can repress them...
Then the parent and child might
have made the wrong choice.
Forget it.
What started it all
was an obvious truth.
After that, the choices were made
by no one other than the man himself.
But why does it always
have to be that gun?