Sex Ward
A Synopsis of Episode 1
I'm Satsuki Aoyagi. Pleased to meet you.
I'm Naho Ota. I hope to
get to know everyone.
They will be starting work
today as probationary nurses.
Mr. Kamiya!
Good morning.
What's wrong, Satsuki?
What are you doing?
Such a wonderful person like him?
I can't believe it.
Our job deals with people's lives.
This is unforgivable.
I'll do anything. Please forgive me.
Really?
Yes, really.
SEX WARD
Episode 2
PLEASE ENJOY A DIFFERENT
VERSION OF THE SAME SCENE
FROM THE PREVIOUS EPISODE.
This is great.
More... More...
I can't hold it any longer. I'm
going to put it in your pussy.
Mr. Kamiya. N... not that...
What do you mean, "No"?
You said you'd do anything.
Put your guard down and
let me open the gates.
Here I come.
You're starting to feel it.
Go ahead and enjoy it.
I'm going to take this
opportunity to be experimental.
No. I'm...
I'm the one who's
thrusting and enjoying it...
S... sorry!
I fell...
I can't walk well because it feels like
I still have something in my pussy...
Dr. Waka... Wait...
D... Doctor!
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not doing it because I care about you.
I'm only fulfilling my duty as a doctor.
Are you in love with that patient?
Huh?
Of course you're not...
...which means you're a woman
who'll sleep with anyone.
How could you say something like that!
But am I wrong? I caught you
in the act with my own eyes.
You were getting fucked by
that dirty middle-aged man...
...and screaming in ecstasy.
I'm disappointed in you.
I don't want to be lectured
by a guy like you.
What?
I heard it all from Naho.
You had passionate sex
with her, and the next day...
...you told her that you're not interested.
Th... that's...
LINEN CLOSET
That's terrible.
I can't forgive someone like
you, someone who'd do that!
He didn't even ask why I did
it, and he presumed I'm a slut.
I hate Dr. Waka! Who
cares about hlm anymore!
That's terrible. I can't
forgive someone like you!
Dr. Waka. Is the student guy really that bad?
Huh? Yeah...
Is it too late?
Yeah...
Really? Poor guy, but he's still so young!
Doesn't it make you feel like you
should enjoy life for him, too?
So on that note!
Why don't we do something next Sunday?
How about a movie, or
we go on a road-trip?
I told her I'm not interested.
What is this girl thinking?
She said giving the cold shoulder to
someone who's annoying you is terrible...
Is that so wrong?
Excuse me.
Satsuki. What is it?
The head nurse told me to bring
you Mr. Onda's medical chart.
Oh, thanks.
Just leave it there.
Put it down quietly, Satsuki.
Sorry.
Please excuse me.
Naho. This student needs to
be reexamined immediately.
Please tell the head nurse to make
the proper arrangements. And...
I'm up for Sunday's plan.
Because I'm not a cold guy
like your friend tells me I am.
Huh?
Satsuki, wait a...
Dr. Waka.
I hate to be redundant, but you just
promised me a date on Sunday.
What was that just now?
What happened between you and Dr. Waka?
Something happened, right?
The friend he was referring
to could only be you!
You have no right to say anything
about what's going on between us!
I already told you from the get go!
Are you listening? Why
are you being so quiet?
If you didn't have anything to hide,
you wouldn't be acting this way!
What do you have to say for yourself?
Nothing happened. Aren't you happy?
You have a date on Sunday.
Do you honestly think I'm happy
because I have a date, thanks to you?
What's wrong?
My stomach...
Oh no... What am I going to do?
Have Dr. Takebayashi look at you.
Dr. Waka has no idea how I feel.
If Naho wants the idiot, she can have him!
Leave me alone!
What are you saying? You have to
stay in bed like the doctor said!
Shut up!
Why are they making such a
scene? They need to shut up!
Excuse me. We can't have
people screaming in the hospital.
I'm very sorry about this.
It's all because he's being stupid...
...and saying that he doesn't
want to be examined again.
I see. I'm sure he's saying that
because he's scared of the exam.
Honestly! Men are such wimps, but
they like to act tough. They're liars...
They're unkind... They're idiots...
...and most of them have a mommy
complex. I really wonder if there
are any decent men out there?
A guy who's screaming and
wailing in a place like this...
A decent man...
A guy who's screaming and
wailing in a place like this...
A decent man...
...is just proving that he's a spoiled baby!
Ma'am.
You should fix him now before it's too late...
...because I'm positive he won't
be able to find a wife in the future.
THIS STUDENT
This student needs to be
reexamined immediately.
THIS STUDENT
Um... Doctor, what are you looking at?
Aren't you going to check
the area where the pain is?
A check up?
Lately, there've been a lot of people
complaining about sexual harassment...
So I try to stay away from conduct
that might give the wrong impression.
Oh...
You want me to check you?
Well, I was wondering if I'm going to
be OK with just a visual check up...
You're right. Then...
Let's do an enema.
I knew he was going to say that.
That's what you call sexual harassment!
Doctor, I hate to be
rude, but I can't do that.
I'm not the type of person who
can go to the bathroom...
...while someone else is watching.
I see. But the pain that's
ailing you right now...
Yes! The pain and suffering...
...like the fires of hell within your
stomach, burning your intestines...
That can only be relieved with an enema!
Do you understand?
Yes...
Let's get this...
...started!!
Let's do the special version today.
Now... Don't hold it in, let your suffering go!
I can't hold it anymore!
What an amazing sense of
relief and climactic sensation.
I just went to the bathroom while
someone was watching me...
...but what's this liberation I feel?
Dr. Takebayashi...
What just happened to me?
You have just set foot into
the realm of the unknown...
...and realized its magnificence!
Magnificence of the realm of the unknown?
Doctor, you're the one who taught me that.
Yes!
Doctor... You're so dreamy...
Do you want to keep on going?
Yes.
Then...
It's amazing, Doctor!
Doctor!! I can't anymore!!
I'm going to cum! Doctor, cum with me!!
I'm going to cum! Cum! Cum! Cum!
Doctor... You're amazing... I love you...
Thank you very much.
There's no need to thank me.
It's my fault for startling you.
Satsuki.
N... Naho?
Satsuki, I'm quitting my job as a nurse.
What? What do you mean?
I'm quitting, because I'm getting married.
Married?
You mean, with Dr. Waka?
That's not funny. Why would I marry him?
Then who are you going to marry?
Kenichi.
I want to make your wish come true.
You might think I'm being foolish, but...
Um... I'm sorry about the other day.
I said some stupid things,
without even considering...
...how much anxiety you must
have, waiting for your test results.
It's not like... I'm angry at you, so...
I bet you were pissed about something
that had nothing to do with me.
Well... You're right, but...
Then could you stop glaring
at me with such a scary face?
This is how I always look.
So don't worry about it.
Oh, really?
Give it to me.
Thirty-six point five. You're fine.
Nurse.
You know, right?
About my illness...
This student needs to be
reexamined immediately.
You're still getting tested, so no...
It's all right. You don't have to hide it.
I'm prepared.
Prepared?
Yeah.
But there's one thing I haven't done yet.
Until I do that...
AO YAGI
I can't die...
Nurse...
Then, that means I'm going to...
I told you, your results aren't in yet.
Don't worry about that now.
Then why?
Yes. That's good. You're doing great.
Stick your finger in...
Ok.
Yes. That's great.
It feels really good.
More. Faster. Thrust your finger in and out.
Nurse. I'm going to cum.
I'm really going to cum!
Don't cum yet.
You want to become a man, right?
Then...
You have to do it right.
Yes, right there. You're
in me. How does it feel?
I can't... I'm going to cum!
Wait! Thrust slowly.
Yes. You're doing well.
Don't be in such a hurry. Take your time.
Shit! I came in you.
That's all right.
All right...
What, Naho? Why'd you bring me in here?
This. A patient named Kenichi
Endo asked me to give this to you.
Huh? From that student guy?
Hey, it's open!
Naho, you didn't read it did you?
Excuse me!? It was open already.
But this...
He's calling me! I must hurry...
What was that? She's acting so creepy.
To Nurse.
Thank you for the other night.
I never would have thought
you'd do that for me.
It made me really happy.
I'm not saying I was able to leave
the hospital because of it, but...
I feel like I have a much
more positive outlook on life.
Huh? He's gone?
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
Apparently, I was misdiagnosed
wlth havlng a serious Illness.
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
What?
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
Someone handed Hideyuki
Ishikawa the x-rays of Mr. Endo...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
...room 308, who has terminal cancer.
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
APPARENTLY I WAS...
...FILE SUIT...
...REALLY...
...SOMEONE HANDED HIDEYUKI ISHIKAWA...
You did read it, Naho!
I feel bad about writing a letter...
...but I'm kind of embarrassed
to see you again.
Sorry, and thank you very much.
I'll never...
I did something stupid again...
I'm disappointed in you. You're a
woman who'll sleep with anyone!
I'm seriously ill, and I'm going to die.
Let me fuck you before I die, Nurse.
Want an enema?
You said you'd do anything... Anything...
Satsuki, would you like to
have coffee in my room?
Dr. Midori?
I'm sure a lot has happened...
...but if you want to bitch
and moan, I'm all ears.
I see. So that's what happened...
You seem to be regretting
what you've done, but...
You did it all out of
compassion for the patients.
True, you went a little too far as a nurse...
...but I don't think it's something
to be ashamed of as a person.
Do you really think so?
I wonder what that was earlier?
Dr. Midori is such a nice person.
You should be more proud of yourself.
You've done something good.
What she's saying is weird, but...
Anyway, what's wrong?
Why are you acting so reserved?
There's no need to be nervous.
Well, I've never worked
for the maternity ward...
...and I really haven't worked
especially close with you, so...
I was kind of wondering why you're
listening to me complain like this...
It's because I've fallen in love with you.
I'm in love with you.
I'm sorry!
I'm flattered about how you feel
about me, but I'm not a lesbian.
It's fine. That's what they
all say when they leave me.
I'm used to it, so don't let it...
Dr. Midori! Please don't cry.
You're such an amazing
person, you'll find someone.
Stop trying to comfort me!
I don't want your halfhearted sympathy.
That'll make me feel even worse!
You don't even mean it, so stop.
I'm going to do it again...
If it's only once...
It's my way of saying thank
you for listening to me.
Just for today, I'll...
Satsuki, are you sure?
I'm sure, Doctor.
This is the type of life
fate has in store for me.
Satsuki, you're gorgeous.
Your body is as beautiful as I imagined it.
And you're so wet down here.
Satsuki, do the same to me.
Yes... suck my pussy more... lick me.
I want to you to feel more pleasure...
What do you think? It's cold and slippery.
Doesn't it feel good?
It feels so strange...
We're just getting started.
Doctor. I feel like my body's going to melt.
Yes. Our bodies are melting into each other.
I knew this is what you
liked best. Be honest!
It feels good. Really
good... I can't anymore!
I'm not going to let you cum.
If you're satisfied with this,
you need to be punished!
More! More!!
Doctor... Doctor...
Doctor.
Huh?
Is it true that you're getting
married to Dr. Waka?
With Hideyuki?
Hideyuki and I have been
friends since college.
That's it.
Really...
He's in love with you. I know it.
He's a very good person.
He's very considerate and sweet.
He's great, but Hideyuki
has one terrible flaw.
A flaw?
His personality completely changes
when he drinks and sleeps with anyone.
On top of that, when he wakes
up, he doesn't remember a thing.
To tell you the truth, he raped
me one time when he was drunk.
He felt so terrible that he
asked me to marry him.
But I can't marry him.
And about yesterday, I want
you to stop asklng me out.
To be blunt, I'm not Interested.
I'm up for Sunday's plan...
...because I'm not a cold guy
Ilke your frlend tells me I am.
He only said that to get back at you.
He said it only out of desperation.
It's just proof of how much
he's in love with you.
Doctor, I...
It's all right. Don't say anything.
Go to Hideyuki. Now it's your
turn to fulfill your fantasy.
Yes.
He's not here. I wonder if he's at the lab.
Satsuki, do you need to see
Dr. Waka about something?
Yes, I do...
Dr. Waka is at Dr. Takebayashi's place.
Really?
Dr. Takebayashi?
Oh, and Naho Ota was with them too.
I wonder what she's thinking,
getting married to Dr. Enema...
Naho? Dr. Enema? Dr. Waka?
They can't be!?