I'm Satsuki Aoyagi. I'm going to
start working as a nurse today.
ISHIKAWA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Good morning, Mr. Shimizu.
I'm Satsuki Aoyagi.
I'm going to be taking
your morning temperature.
Huh? Mr. Shimizu's gone?
I wonder where he went?
No!
What are you doing? Please stop!
It was a dream.
How could I... I'm wet from that dream.
Oh no! I'm going to be late for my first day!
SEX WARD
Episode 1
Naughty naughty, Miss Nurse. You
should walk the hospital halls quietly.
S... sorry.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh my, please excuse me for that.
Oh what to do now? Your breasts
were so soft, my cock got hard.
Could you do something
about it, Miss Nurse?
Mr. Kamiya!
Oh hello, Dr. Waka.
Mr. Kamiya. I saw some kind of protruding
object there. I don't think that's funny!
No, what you saw was a big purse, sent
to me from my house in the suburbs.
I was just showing it to the nurse.
She's the nurse, so I
thought she'd like my purse.
Well, I'll be off now...
Good morning!
Morning.
That's something quite outrageous to see
first thing in the morning. Are you all right?
Y... yes!
Oh, good then.
Please excuse me.
I'm golng to work hard as a nurse!
I'm Naho Ota. I hope to get along
with everyone! No teasing please!
I'm Satsuki Aoyagi. Pleased to
meet you. I'll work very hard.
These two will be starting work
today as probationary nurses.
They'll need your guidance,
so please help them out.
Yes!
Director, we have a meeting next, but do
you have anything else you'd like to add?
No, I'm all set.
Hideyuki, let's go.
Yes.
Miss Kato. Come to my
office after the meeting.
Yes, I'll be there.
I'd like to report on the decisions made
during the administrative meeting,
concerning some problems.
That's Dr. Waka? He's pretty
hot! What am I going to do?
Please take a look at the
printout that was handed out.
Dr. Waka?
Good morning.
You saw something quite
outrageous early this morning.
Something outrageous?
Yes, it's outrageous! Can you please
do something about it, Miss Nurse?
What is it, Miss Aoyagi!? What
are you so surprised about?
S... sorry!
Jeez.
So how are the new girls?
What's wrong Yuriko? I'm
asking how the new girls are.
I don't understand the nerve
of young women these days.
They had absolutely no sense of
tension at their first morning meeting.
As long as they do their job, it'll be fine.
You just have to let some things slide.
Plus, they're both really cute.
What are you doing, Yuriko!?
I'm going down on you...
...and you're probably thinking...
...about naked young girls. Am I wrong?
Don't be foolish!
Those women are so young, they
reek of piss. They're not my type.
It's fine.
I know that one day you're
going to leave me, so...
What are you saying, Yuriko?
Come, Yuriko. Come
here and let me hold you.
Oh director, you're so naughty.
Director...
The way you smell and taste when
you're on duty drives me wild.
There's no way I'm going to let those
women take my sugar daddy away!
Director. Please only pay attention to me.
Yuriko.
Yes! It feels so good!
You like this, Yuriko? Then I'm going to...
Not yet, Director. I still need
you to fuck me from behind.
You're so good, Director! It's so hot,
I feel like I'm going to catch fire!
Okay, burn! Burn and burn away!!
I'm almost there, Director. Can you
please fuck me again in my pussy?
Yes... More... Fuck me harder...
Harder! Harder!!
Yes! This... this is it!
I can feel you all the way inside!
Director, you're going to be in a lot
of trouble if you touch those women.
Satsuki, can you check the stalls?
It's fine. There's no one here.
Thanks!
Oh, this? It's a smokeless
cigarette. Great, huh?
Why do you have to smoke in a place
like this? Let's go to the break room.
What are you talking about, Satsuki?
That'd be such a faux pas.
Probationary nurses like us can't
smoke in front of our seniors.
Plus, I bet they'd say something even if
we just took a break in the break room.
I think you're reading too much into this.
Hey, did you hear about Dr. Waka?
Huh?
He's the great surgeon
that's inheriting this hospital.
He's hot, sincere,
and on top of that, single.
You can't get any better than that!
I heard that someday, he's
going to marry Dr. Midori...
...who he's known since grad school, but...
I don't think that's happening any time soon.
Really...
Hey, is it true you met a
patient named Kamiya?
Yeah.
He doesn't have any serious illnesses,
but he's been here forever; and
apparently, he's a notorious pervert.
He hasn't done anything serious
to anyone yet, because he's
supposedly too weak physically.
But apparently, he has a huge cock!
Don't you wish we could take a look at it?
That's something quite outrageous
to see first thing in the morning.
Hey! You're all dreamy-eyed
because I said he has a huge cock!
N-no! You've got it all wrong!
Well who cares about that, Satsuki.
Listen.
I'm only telling you this because
we're from the same graduating
class at nursing school!
Tell me what?
Yes! I'm going to make Dr. Waka
fall in love with me for sure!
So, that's why you
requested external medicine!
Yup! And you're going to...
Internal medicine!
Um... Are you sure it's not just a cold?
No, just hold on a minute.
Nurse! Ready the thing! The thing!
Yes, Doctor.
Ms. Aoyagi, please bring
the enema equipment.
The... the enema equipment?
Yes. Now hurry!
Y... yes!
Doctor, what kind of treatment is this?
This year, the stomach flu is quite rampant.
Watching how your feces comes out is a
way for me to judge how healthy you are.
Does that mean we're
going to be doing it here?
Yes, but there's no need to
worry. We're very prepared.
You! Show her!
Yes, Doctor.
I've finished injecting it all in. Please sit up.
We're all set. Don't hold back, let it all out.
Your stomach seems to
be fine. Good. Good.
That was very good. Off
to see the next patient.
You poor thing, Satsuki. I'm
sure that was quite a shocker.
You're the type that has
mlsfortune knocklng at your door.
Dr. Takebayashi is also
known as Dr. Enema.
He gets pleasure out of watching people
take a shit. He's a complete pervert.
How about you, Naho? The
operation today was really long.
Yup. I was glued to Dr. Waka for six hours!
He's so amazing! He was so efficient!
There's going to be another huge operation
tomorrow, too. I hope it takes lots of time.
Happlness Is bullt upon other's mlsfortunes.
Dr. Waka... I wlsh I could
watch hlm all day long, too.
You're really good.
Dr. Ishikawa!
I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
N-no! I'm fine.
You're bleeding!
You ready? I'm going to lick it.
You're all fixed up now.
Okay. You're all good now.
Satsuki, what's wrong?
Yes?
Oh, thank you very much!
You don't have to thank me.
It's my fault for startling you.
Oh...
I did everything around the house
when I was young because my parents
both worked. So this isn't too hard.
I don't have any other talents, so...
That's great though. I like women like that.
Huh?
My mother passed away when
I was young, so the homey
feeling is kind of foreign to me.
A part of me really wants that.
Really?
Oh, come on!
I can't! How many times
do I have to repeat myself?
I'm not taking no for an answer.
I've already made plans to
have a drink with you tonight!
You're very persistent! Don't you
understand that I have things to do too?
What do you have to do?
Are you going on a date?
No. Not exactly, but...
It's useless. Dr. Waka is a real
square. He doesn't drink at all.
I can't count the number of female
coworkers he's turned down.
There's no way she'd be able to get him.
It's just a waste of time watching. Let's go.
The senlor nurses say that, but...
Naho is...
I've done my homework. I know
Dr. Waka doesn't drink. I'm sure
he has a really weak tolerance.
So... I'll just mix some
gin In hls orange juice.
Doctor, I'm sorry I forced you to come out
tonight. After you drink the orange juice...
Screw Driver!
...let's go home.
Okay, sure. Let's do that.
He'll be completely wasted
when he drinks a sip of that.
I'll take care of him and lead
him into a love hotel, then...
Dr. Waka... Yes! It feels
so unbelievably good!!
What happened to you? This is
totally not how I imagined you!
But...
It's so good!
I'm getting numb all the way
inside! Dr. Waka, you're too good!
Dr. Waka. I can't anymore...
I'm going to die.
Not yet!
I can't anymore...
Good morning, Satsuki.
Naho, good morning. What's wrong?
Why are you wearing sunglasses? If
you get caught by the head nurse...
The sun's just so yellow...
The sun's really bright.
What are you talking about,
Naho? What happened?
Fine. I'll tell you what happened.
Well, last night...
Last nlght?
Dr Waka and I...
Dr Waka and you?
...had sex!
Had sex!?
It was unbelievable! He just kept
going and he was so good in bed.
We did it for five hours, nonstop!
I'm so exhausted.
Morning. Is the head nurse here?
Good morning!
Morning. Have you seen the head nurse?
The head nurse? By the way, Dr. Waka...
How are you feeling this morning?
What's wrong, Satsuki?
Are you not feeling well?
No, I'm fine. The head nurse
is on the late shift today.
Okay, I see.
What are you doing?
Huh?
And about last night, I want
you to stop asking me out. To
be blunt, I'm not interested.
What?
When the head nurse comes
in, tell her to call my extension.
I'll be in the lab all afternoon.
Sure... But...
Thanks.
I can't believe it. A night with a
nurse doesn't mean anything to him!
But we were both so into it...
I'm not going to leave it like this!
I'm going to become the future
director's wife no matter what!
I wonder If Dr. Waka
likes women like Naho...
I know how pushy Naho can get, but I
can't belleve he slept wlth her that night.
How are you feeling?
Not too great. I feel sluggish,
and I don't have any energy.
I understand. I'll give you
a glucose injection then.
Satsuki, here's the drip infusion.
Yes, ma'am.
I can't belleve Dr. Waka Is such a playboy.
Such a wonderful person like hlm?
It's an emergency! Mr. Kamiya is...!
Mr. Kamiya?
Mr. Kamiya! Mr. Kamiya! Please calm down!
Mr. Kamiya! Calm down! Pull yourself
together! Mr. Kamiya! Are you all right?
Mr. Kamiya! Mr. Kamiya! Mr.
Kamiya! Pull yourself together!
Mr. Kamiya! Calm down! Pull yourself
together! Mr. Kamiya! Are you all right?
Mr. Kamiya! Mr. Kamiya! Mr.
Kamiya! Pull yourself together!
Mr. Kamiya!
Fortunately you injected him with
dietetic fluids, so the damage
isn't too great, but still...
If you'd given him a steroid injection
by accident, it could have killed him.
I'm really sorry. I must have
been spacing out, so...
Spacing out?
No, well...
Our job deals with people's lives.
You should think about that again!
Yes. I understand.
She really irritates me! She still
thinks she's a student! Jeez!
Oh, Director! Please wait!
I'm really sorry about what happened today.
I don't think I can make up for
it, but I will make sure it never
happens again. I'm really sorry.
This is unforgivable.
Huh?
What are you going to do
about it? I'm full of energy.
I've gotten used to my sickly body
over the years, and now I feel
like I'm in someone else's body.
I can't help but feel restless and tormented!
I'm sorry. This is all my fault. I'll
do anything. Please forgive me.
You'll do anything? Is that true?
Yes, really.
This is great.
A real nurse is sucking my dick.
This is amazing.
I'm going to cum!
Swallow all of it.
You taste and smell great.
Your pussy is one of the finest.
Very nice. Your nipples are hard.
Your pussy is dripping wet too.
Let's do doggy style next.
M...
More...
SEX WARD
Episode 1