I accepted her confession of love before the entrance exam of next year. She calls me Senpai though we are in the same grade. Still my every day life was boring.
Ah... We have morning lessons for the club since tomorrow, right?
Ah... Senpai, I don't mind about it.
It's a groper.
Sorry.
I couldn't make it.
Nope.
It's okay.
Senpai.
I love you.
Misaki-sensei!
Senpai's erection.
He * Me * Go * To
You always go to school with this crowd, don't you?
Misaki-sensei.
I must come here in this hour when I have a morning lesson.
It's rare you don't go to school in a car.
Yeah. My car is still be fixed.
Still, it's early.
I wanted to get on the train with you.
You didn't come with your girlfriend today?
We just met accidentally yesterday.
We don't meet everyday.
You were looking at me yesterday.
How did you feel then?
You got horny, right?
Misaki-sensei?
Keep quiet.
Same as yesterday.
Groper?
Misaki-sensei feel excited?
Can't it be true?
Being touched by a stranger...
Why don't you reject it?
It's painful if you hold my hands so hard.
It's crazy!
You're kind.
Crazy...
Hey, come on.
What?
Kind Takashi-kun. It's because of you. Take the responsibility, okay?
Sensei, we cannot do this in such place.
Don't worry.
Other teachers won't come here and students won't come so early.
Touch...
See? You know how I am now.
Sensei.
Yours can't wait either.
Sensei!
For now...
Wait a little bit.
Sensei! I can't wait! I'll...
I'll come!
He's late...
Yours is really wonderful.
Let's enjoy more.
It's your turn to let me come.
Kiss me.
Yes!
There!
Lick it.
Yes! You're good.
Hey, your finger... Use your finger.
Sensei. I can't wait anymore...
You can put it in.
You don't have to hurry.
Good!
Let me feel you more.
Sensei.
Feels good.
I feel here.
Good!
I'll come!
No. Don't...
I really feel it when you touch my boobs.
Sensei. I'm getting horny again...
Hey. Put it in from back next as hard as you want.
It reaches my inner.
Good!
I'll come again.
Come!
Sensei, I'll come.
Sensei!
What happened to him?
Was I disliked?
It was so nice.
Sensei, we didn't have to prevent pregnancy?
It's not sweet. You already calm down?
Eh? Not like that.
You don't have to worry.
What's up?
It's overflowing. Because you gave me a lot.
Where is tissue?
Come on. It's senseless. Let me feel you more.
But we have a class soon.
Senpai. Morning lesson of today?
Sorry. I had something to do.
My friend told me a good cafe. Can we go there this afternoon?
Sorry. I don't feel good.
Morning lesson! How about tomorrow's lesson?
I'm not sure.
Senpai.
Doors will be closed. Watch out your step, please.
What's wrong with her?
Touching her in such a place... What if I was mistaken for a groper?
Slowly.
Yeah, lick as if irritate me. To the center...
Tenderly.
That point was touched by you in the train.
I cannot control myself if I was touched in the train.
You know how much I felt horny.
Hey. You're the same as me.
You were excited when you touched me in the train, right?
Senpai.
He couldn't come to morning lesson today, too.
Sensei, I cannot wait anymore!
Not yet. You'll feel as much as you're irritated.
Same thing as a groper.
Yeah, tenderly.
Women feel everywhere.
This place isn't good. It's easy to be found.
Other men will look at me.
Pervert man may be looking.
You're talking like an adult...
Somehow, it's different today.
I feel too much.
Sensei, this is really hot today.
I cannot help it!
You're really pervert today.
Push me quickly. Please!
Sensei. Not yet. Let's go over there.
We cannot. Someone may hear.
Don't! Good!
Senpai? This is Tomomi. I feel lonely as if we got far apart after that.
I love you so much, though...
You're different from others. Quiet and cool.
I've never called you by your first name!
You're too far from me for that. So, I felt closer when you couldn't make it.
So, I felt closer when you couldn't make it.
You couldn't make it and I was worried. I tried not to but I felt you're cute.
I love you much much much more than when I confessed you my love. Then, good night.
Ah! It's Saturday. He doesn't have a morning lesson, does he?
There are too many gropers in this train.
It's forcible but very good.
Good. I cannot help...
You feel by anyone's finger, huh?
Takashi-kun!
Please.
I cannot wait anymore.
Let me come as it is.
You slut.
Senpai...
We don't talk a lot even during the club.
I left the message in your answering machine but...
You didn't call me back.
Senpai?
Don't make girls cry!
Sensei, your car...
I don't have to get on the crowded train anymore. Ciao!
What's wrong? Aren't we going home?
Let's go.
I was worried about my grades.
I felt lonely little bit, besides about that...
If you get close to me so much...
Senpai, I...
Shiii. Be quiet.
We are in the train...
Tomomi, we're okay.
You don't wanna do it?
I feel embarrassed.
Someone may see it.
Don't worry. You're pretty, Tomomi.
Senpai, I...
Let's get off at next station.
Roof?
I wanna stay just with you soon.
Such a place?
No one comes here.
But, Senpai?
Touch it.
I cannot wait anymore.
Senpai. It's a restroom...
Nope! That is dirty.
It's really beautiful, Tomomi.
Senpai! I cannot stand any longer!
I'll do it slowly. Be patient little bit.
Tomomi, look at. It's inside.
Inside...
Just a little bit inside.
Ouch, Senpai.
I love you, Tomomi.
Senpai, it hurts!
You all right?
Nope! I feel shy...
You're really pretty, Tomomi.
Senpai, do you feel good?
Good. It's so nice.
Snepai, I feel somehow strange.
I'm not available now. Leave your message after the tone.
Senpai, this is Tomomi.
Senpai...
Let's do it together... again...
Hello?
Senpai?