Carol, I've been thinking it's about time I
got you involved in the family business.
Oh, do you mean that, Father?
Yes. After all, by the
time he was your age...
...your oldest brother was already
running one of the companies
And? What will I be doing?
Right. That railroad
company I mentioned...
That one's a bit tricky.
I thought I'd put you in
charge of the takeover.
You're giving me such an important task?
I won't let you down, Father!
I know, I know you won't.
First of all...
...I'm going to send you
to a certain mansion...
A certain mansion... you say?
It's not just any mansion.
There was a time when it was...
...the symbol of the Burton
Railroad's Prosperity...
Now here's the deed to that mansion...
I wonder what's in store for me?
The allure of a glass doll
is its transparent beauty...
...and its fragile sensitivity.
All you have to do is dump
some cheap paint over it...
...and it's no more than a muddy troll.
One doesn't realize how beautiful...
...and fragile glass is until it's broken.
When the shards of the smashed
glass pierce your fingers...
...drawing a trickle of bright red blood...
...it's almost as if it's in atonement
towards the broken doll...
MAIDEN OF DELIVERANCE
Episode 1
Good morning, Miss Clair!
Good morning, May!
I would've made the tea,
ma'am, if you'd only told me...
That's all right. I really
enjoy doing this myself.
Anyway, where's Foster?
Yes?
Oh, good morning, Miss Clair.
Good morning, Leese. Well?
How does it feel to put on
that maid's uniform again?
Oh, it brings back memories.
This place hasn't changed at all, has it?
Well, I'm going to be
counting on you again.
By the way, have you seen Foster?
No, ma'am...
Hmmm. That's too bad, I've
just made some tea for him...
Flora, you always seem to be
having so much fun when you work.
Yes, ma'am.
Even though it couldn't be less fun.
That's not true. It's a lot
of hard work, but it is fun.
Lily...
If only I had a bigger chest...
Who's there?
Emit! Could you run an errand for...
S-sorry!
Please wait a moment...
Monica, do you think
you can fix that clock?
Who knows...?
I'm surprised it survived the fire at all...
It doesn't look like it'll ever work again.
It's like time has stopped... isn't it?
Emit!
I beg of you! Foster, sir!
Please make love to me...
You're a bold one.
I'm surprised at myself.
I've never felt this way before.
I... I... have feelings for you, Mr. Foster...
Emit...
Forgive me...
Clair!
I'm sorry...
Miss Clair?
Clair!
Are you angry?
No, not at all. You're kind
to all women, aren't you?
Well, if you don't need me...
Wow! You have to see this, Carol!
Be quiet, will you? Can't
you see that I'm thinking?
I'm very sorry...
What's going on?
What shall I do, sir?
Just open the gate for them, all right?
I want to speak with the
mistress of this house!
I'm sorry, but our mistress
does not see guests...
...without an appointment.
Oh, but I don't need an appointment!
Tell her that Carol Wellacuster
wants to speak with her!
I'm very sorry, ma'am,
but you'll have to leave.
Excuse me!
Are you saying you're not familiar
with the name Wellacuster?
Of course, I know it very well.
After all, it's the name of the most
powerful conglomerate in these parts.
You're certainly the rudest
person I've ever met.
But then again, you're
certain to change your tune...
...once you lay your
eyes on this document...
Well? Now do you understand?
That I'm to be your new
mistress as of today?
It certainly looks that way...
If you wish to remain on
here, that's fine with me.
I'll hire you all, including the maids.
If that doesn't appeal to you, then I
suggest you take your leave at once.
Everyone, did you hear?
Yes, May told me.
We're just working for
someone else now, that's all.
It's got nothing to do with us maids...
How can you be so callous!
Hey, what do you think is going to happen?
Clair?
May has told me everything.
I was not equal to the task...
Oh, no. It's not your fault at all, Foster.
I want you to decide yourself
what you want to do.
Whether we should stay on... or...
This mansion is not particularly
well-built, you know...
Hmm?
Still, I have a very good view of
my mother's cherished garden...
Just a fragment of a memory for me now...
Surely they can't all be good memories...
But it's still better than
no memories at all...
If you stay here, it will
be very difficult for you.
Yes, but I'm no stranger to hardship.
Just a little longer...
What?
If you could persevere a little longer...
Foster...
The truth is... there might be something...
...even more valuable than
memories of the past...
Come in!
Pardon me, ma'am.
Foster, was it?
Yes, ma'am.
Well? Have you decided
what you're going to do?
If possible, we would like to remain here.
I see...
...then I shall have to forgive you
for your rudeness a while ago.
Thank you very much.
Don't just stand there,
Liz. Introduce yourself!
Oh, I'm sorry. My name
is Elizabeth Bergerac.
Please call me Liz.
My name is Foster.
Welcome, ma'am.
Pleasure...
I've already done a
background check on you.
I've decided I want you to train Liz.
Using your special techniques!
Carol?
Her father failed in a
business venture, you see.
That's why she's been sent to
me as an indentured servant!
What?
Liz, as of today I order you to
work in this mansion as a maid!
Carol!
Liz... as of now you are to call me "Miss"...
Carol... Wait, what are
you talking about, Carol?
You're not such an idiot that you have
to be told more than once, are you?
If you disobey me, your
parents will suffer greatly!
Yes... yes, Miss Carol...
What do you think? If
you want to stay here...
...you must show me
how obedient you are!
This is the only room in the
mansion that survived that fire...
To think that once again...
...these old wounds are
to be ripped open...
Miss Carol... what's going on?
Shut your mouth! Just keep walking!
All right, why don't you
show me what you can do?
Mr. Legendary Trainer!
Yes, ma'am.
Don't just stand there!
Hurry up, for God's sake!
There's no way for her to escape, anyway.
Liz!
It's all right.
I... I... I... I...
Is that the best you can do?
No! Stop!
It's easier to pluck their
feathers while they're alive.
Since all you have to do is...
...ignore the pain of the
person you're plucking...
You look lovely from here, Liz.
Let me give you a little present...
What is that?
An aphrodisiac from the Far East.
Stop it! Please, stop that!
It should start working
immediately. But first things first...
Don't use your teeth this time.
That's right.
You've got to learn how
to use your tongue.
Well, now! This medicine of
yours is certainly effective!
She's positively drenched!
No, please, don't look.
I will do anything, so please don't do this.
What's that? What did you say?
Down there...
What's the matter, Liz?
You'll have to speak up!
Ahhh! I'm getting all hot down there...
...and I can't take it anymore!
Well, to think that a well-bred girl like
you would utter such vulgar words!
Open your eyes and watch!
N-no!!!
Don't close your eyes!
Unbelievable. I never thought
I'd see Liz in such a state.
S... Stop!
You'll have to cry out louder.
A loser has no choice...
...but to grovel at the feet of
her conqueror, just like that!
That's an age-old law
of the world we live in!
I want you to work on the other maids too.
You are to train them so that every
single one of them can entertain.
In return, I will pay them twice
what they've been getting till now.
You are to fire any maid
who can't pass muster.
Yes, ma'am, I understand.
Foster.
What is it?
I need to talk to you...
I'm sorry, but it'll have to wait till tomorrow.
I'm very busy right now.
Miss Clair...
You came at a bad time, didn't you?
You must go home tomorrow, Leese.
It's clear that this mansion
was confiscated unlawfully.
Just as I thought...
So, what would you like to do about it?
I'm going to reclaim this house.
Do you think it's possible?
Yes.
Yes. If you have about 4 pages of
documents I'm sure it won't be difficult.
However...
Judging by her personality...
...she'll probably take it back another way.
Yes. And if it comes to a pitched battle...
...it will require an
enormous sum of money.
Unfortunately, we don't
have the finances...
Still... there must be another way...
Good morning, Miss Carol.
It looks like you all decided to stay on.
That maid's uniform really
becomes you, Clair!
Thank you very much.
I have a favor to ask of you, Miss Carol.
My sister...
...Please don't do anything cruel
to my younger sister, Flora.
In return, I will do anything you wish.
Flora? Oh, you mean that short little girl.
You don't look like sisters, though...
Flora is my sister! My
only... she's my only...
Oh, well, I suppose it's all right.
But! Disobey me and the deal is off!
Do you understand?
No!
All right, then, shall I bring
in Flora to take your place?
You people are the scum of the earth!
Yes, but unfortunately, you must
bow your head to such scum.
I just have to do whatever you say, right?
Don't worry. I have no use for little girls.
All I'm interested in is
lascivious bitches. But!
Ouch!
I won't tolerate rebellious behavior.
Understood?
Yes.
Get down on your knees.
Put it in your mouth.
Don't forget to use your tongue, too!
Uhhh...
Drink every last drop!
As long as you pay me,
I'll follow any order...
All right, then open yourself
with your own fingers.
Yes, sir.
Is that all right, sir?
You'll do anything for money, won't you?
Then what about something like this?
Hot! Ow! Ow! Ahhhh!
Have you no shame?
I don't really find it all
that embarrassing, sir.
All right. Then put your
hands on that table...
...and get down on all fours!
Yes, sir.
You're submissive.
That's because I don't mind
doing anything for the one I love!
Sensitive, eh? Then how about... this?
That feels good too!
Foster sir!
This is ridiculous. The
rest is up to you, Foster.
Please don't!
Wasn't it your own decision to stay here?
Yes, but... I have no other place to go!
Ah! Please, please stop that!
So you can be feminine
sometimes, too, eh?
I can't take this anymore!
Just endure it. You'll get
used to it soon enough.
There's no way I'll ever get
used to something like this!
At the very least, you'll be able
to pretend you're used to it.
Enough with the words of compassion.
You're not being kind by offering
her comfort this one time!
You're working hard as usual, aren't you?
Yes, ma'am.
This tea is undrinkable!
L-I'm sorry... I'm so sorry...
Really! You can't even make...
...a descent pot of tea!
Pardon me, miss...
Have one of the other maids do it...
That's not the point!
If it's tea you want, I'll do it, ma'am.
Don't interfere! I'm talking to Liz here!
I know, ma'am, but there is
a knack to making good tea.
I don't really think that she'II...
...she'll suddenly get better at it
just because you shouted at her.
Clair!
Hmm! You dare to speak your mind to me?
Do you remember what your
position is in this household?
Of course I do, Miss Carol.
Foster, I want you to punish
this ill-mannered maid!
All right, I will speak to her harshly later.
That's not good enough!
I want you to rape her right here, right now!
What?
Well, what are you waiting for? Do it!
I don't think there's any need to do that.
You two are excused.
So you're defying me too, Foster?
No, but it's my responsibility
to discipline the maids.
Clair...
What's wrong?
Nothing, it's nothing.
There's really no use
in lashing out at Carol.
Leave me alone!
And don't forget this is what you wanted...
What I wanted?
I never... I never, ever wished
for something like this!
Calm down. You just
have to endure this now...
Do you think you can silence
a woman by kissing her?
Don't talk to me like that...
I'm tired of this! This kind of relationship!
And look at me... I do go
silent when I'm kissed.
Clair...
What was it... what in the
world was it that I wanted?