Even now I'm bound by invisible chains...
Once you get used to it...
...even everyday madness
can become a natural thing.
And what little pain there
was, is no longer...
What I've lost now looms ever larger...
...while even the little things
that have supported me so far...
...if I try to grasp them, they
just slip through my fingers.
Leaving only tiny shards of memories...
Ouch! Oh!
Please... please forgive me!
What are you talking about?
Your punishment has just begun!
You must learn to stay
still and endure the pain.
Please, please make him stop now!
I don't think so. She shirked
her duties as a maid, after all!
But... I'm the one who told her to rest.
You can punish me in her place.
Please, don't take it out on Liz...
This is your punishment.
You need to understand what
your actions bring about.
Take a good, hard look, now...
Foster! I beg of you!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Foster, you would never go
against my orders, would you?
No. As long as it's not
an unreasonable order.
You are a very wise man!
Exactly the kind of mind-set
a butler should have!
MAIDEN OF DELIVERANCE
Episode 2
Ouch!
Please, be brave now.
We have to make sure
these scars go away.
Doesn't it bother you at all,
Miss Clair? Any of this?
I'm sorry. It was all my fault...
Carol didn't used to be that kind of person.
She would get angry a lot...
...but she did have a
kind, caring side too...
Liz, I suppose one day you too
will learn how to stop fighting...
...and go along with the flow...
And then it will be just the same
thing happening over and over...
I've been investigating the
Wellacuster conglomerate.
It looks like they're planning
a hostile takeover...
...of the Burton Railroad after all.
Just as I thought...
However, there seems to be
something else going on as well...
You mean their plans to go public?
I didn't think you knew about that...
Father!
Good morning, Miss Carol!
All right, everyone, I expect
you all to work hard today too!
Yes, ma'am. Rest assured.
Monica! It's time to clean
the house, you know?
You don't have to tell me!
If this would only snap into place...
Emit, it looks like it's just going
to be you and me today...
What?
Foster!
Are you making any
progress training the maids?
Yes. Everything is going as planned.
Well, then, I suppose they're about ready...
...to entertain guests on their own.
No, I think that would be premature.
But we're expecting some
very important guests today...
...important to the Wellacuster Business!
Today, ma'am? Then we'll
have Clair or Leese...
No, wait. I think I'd rather have Liz do it!
But I don't think Liz has had enough train...
Why do you have to defy me at every turn?
I'm ordering you!
Understood?
How does it taste?
It's good.
Do you really mean that?
Yes, it's not bad at all.
It was Emit who made that, you know!
Foster!
Thank you very much!
No, it's because you
worked hard on it, Emit.
I'm so happy for you, Emit.
Yes, this is the first time someone's
ever complimented my cooking!
Foster!
Yes, what can I do for you, ma'am?
Isn't it about time the guests arrived?
I believe it's still early...
Never mind, I want you to come at once!
Yes, I'll be right there.
You're much too lenient with the maids!
You're going to have to run a tighter ship!
Mr. Foster seems to have
accepted Miss Carol completely.
It looks that way...
I wonder how Miss Clair
feels about all this?
Huh?
Is something the matter?
I just thought I'd make some tea.
You understand what it is
you have to do, don't you?
Y-yes, sir...
Pardon me.
Well, well!
That's certainly something
to look forward to!
Pardon me.
Well! You're right, she's
gorgeous. She's like a little doll!
Liz! Don't dawdle like that!
N-no, ma'am.
All right, I'd like to have a turn now...
Come on!
Come on, you need to stick out your hips!
What were you thinking?
What is it?
You shouldn't have made a
first-timer like Liz entertain 2 guests.
You went too far.
Don't you dare lecture me!
The problem with you is...
...have you forgotten what your
position is in this household?
I am very much aware of it.
No, you don't have the faintest idea!
There's only victors and losers here!
All the losers have to do is show
the victor absolute obedience!
Did you attain that position just so you
could trample all over other people?
I'm asking you not to inflict
such cruelty on the maids.
Stop it! Stop it! I said stop it! Let go of me!
Ouch!
Shut up and lie still!
Ouch! Stop it!
Stop it! Ouch! Please, please stop it!
I beg of you! Stop it!
Where are your parents?
I don't know...
What do you mean?
My father was running a
factory, but it got shut down...
And the next thing I knew,
both my parents were gone.
But I still believe that one
day they'll be back...
And when they do, they'll
fix that clock for me...
You're right.
Go back to your room, now.
You see, Flora... Flora isn't
really my little sister...
But we've been together for so long...
...that little girl's the only
thing that keeps me going.
You're from a wealthy
family, aren't you, Lily?
You don't talk like the rest of us.
Now I'm just the same as you...
I can't survive in this world
unless I sell my body.
Life isn't fair, is it?
Wh-what are you...?
No, not there! NO! Please, stop! Ahhh!
I really don't think Carol's up to the task.
Both her elder brother and sister were
running entire companies at her age.
But Carol is still very much a child.
That's not true! Father! Mother!
I'm not just a child!
I swear... I swear I'll live
up to all your expectations!
Perhaps she's not quite up to
carrying on the Wellacuster name...
It's because you spoiled her
so when she was growing up.
I'm so disappointed in Carol...
Please wait!
You're nothing but a child.
Father! Mother! Wait! Wait!
Hey! Take a good look! At
what a vulgar sight you are!
Don't look away, dammit!
NO!
Are you having the maids
entertain just to bully them?
And what if I am?
You'll never understand what it's like!
Having to win all the time!
What it's like to have to
win day after day, forever!
Is it so important for you to win?
That's right! A Wellacuster
can't afford to lose!
How dare you look at me like that!
How can you always be so
damned calm and collected?
I happen to be older than you, Miss Carol...
...and therefore better
able to hide my emotions.
Don't you dare treat me like a child!
If you're looking to cure your irritability...
...this is a very effective method.
Again...
What?
Kiss me again! I order you to!
Yes, ma'am, I shall do so.
The truth is... I never
intended to make Liz a maid.
Then why did you?
When you first met her, you
looked at her with such kind eyes.
I couldn't stand it... So I
wanted to destroy her...
Is something the matter?
Yes. Um... It's about Mr. Foster.
About the other day... I'm sure
you've been quite angry...
Why would I be?
I knew all about it...
...That Mr. Foster had
chosen you, Miss Clair.
Foster hasn't chosen
anyone, much less me.
But I... I've had my eye on
Mr. Foster all this time, too!
Mr. Foster is someone I
hold dear to my heart, too!
I see...
I'm not going give up on him!
Excuse me...
Well, good work!
Excuse me.
Can't you sleep?
When did you start drinking?
This is my first drink.
I thought it might help
me drown my sorrows.
But it's not working. It's
just as Aisha said...
You can't drive yourself to drink like this!
Give that back to me! I
want to forget everything!
I want to forget about this
mansion... about you, Foster!
Clair...
Miss Carol, are you bringing
the guests down here?
Just shut up and follow me!
Lily! Have you seen Miss Carol?
No, sir...
I haven't seen her either.
That's strange. I'm sure the
guests have arrived by now.
Don't tell me...
Are you all right?
Isn't there something
you'd like to say to me?
Clair!
Why won't you talk to me?
If I asked you to rescue me...
...would you come to my aid?
Or on the other hand...
...do you enjoy watching all
my suffering and humiliation?
What is it?
Excuse me.
Is something the matter?
No... But as long as you're with me...
...you're never going to have
much of a life, you know.
I suppose you're right.
So you're not going to deny it?
Well, but that kind of life
can't be all bad either, can it?
Actually, I have some news for you.
What?
The plan to take over the
Burton Railroad has failed.
Are you sure?
Yes!
However, I have reason to believe
that this was also part of the plan...
What do you mean?
They wanted to get involved in the
government's plans to go public...
...so that they'd have an edge
in all future developments.
In other words, Carol was nothing
more than a stalking-horse.
Yes.
You wanted to see me?
It's all over... I've lost.
All I wanted was to demonstrate
my abilities in this town...
...so that my parents and my siblings
would recognize me as an equal...
How can you be so unaffected by all this?
Excuse me?
Well, you're someone on
the losing side, aren't you?
Isn't that why you're serving me?
That is correct.
Well, then how can you be so arrogant?
You always act like you know everything!
You're inconsiderate! And haughty!
You're the most unpleasant
man I've ever met!
What am I to do?
In times of suffering...
...shouldn't you just accept the fact
that you have to ask someone for help.
But how do I do that?
Would you like me to teach you?
Yes...
Do you think you can do as you're told?
Excuse me...
Get out!
What are you doing? Just get out! Now!
Don't mind her. Stay and watch.
What... what are you
doing? Stop it right now!
You have a lot to learn...
I can't allow you to leave this room...
...until that rebellious look
in your eyes is gone!
What... you stop that! NO!
No! S-stop it...
Liz, what are you going to do?
Please... please stop it!
It was... it was terrible when
it was happening to me.
So it must be terrible for Carol...
Don't you dare feel sorry for me!
If I don't stop you from
mistreating Carol now...
...then that means that I've
accepted being abused myself...
I don't want any of your pity!
Stop being so stubborn.
All you have to do is apologize.
Are you telling me to
get down on my knees?
I was the same way.
What?
Even after I'd lost everything...
...I just didn't have it in me to apologize...
That's why...
That's enough... really, that's enough.
I don't think I can ever forgive you...
But I have no intention of
seeking revenge against you...
Liz...
You called her a loser, didn't you?
But someone like her, who
can take anything with tears...
...is far stronger.
Just give in and cry.
And after you've done that, you'll be able
to beg Liz for forgiveness, won't you?
Clair... I wasn't able to stop this.
What are you talking about?
It seems that Miss Carol will be
leaving this house tomorrow.
What?
They are going to tear down this mansion.
Oh... are they really?
I did everything I could...
It's not your fault, Foster.
What will you do?
Let me see...
...first of all, I'd like to have
a good cup of tea with you.
How is it?
It's delicious!
I'd forgotten that I could feel like this...
Excuse me...
What do you want?
We are ready to leave now.
All right.
Liz?
Yes?
You're a free woman now.
What?
I'm saying that all of
your debt has been paid.
I'm sorry.
Carol...
Foster, why don't you come with me?
What?
I'd like you to work with
me as my right-hand man.
I don't think it's such a bad proposition.
Thank you, but...
Are you thinking of Clair?
That's what I thought.
Is that woman so important to you?
Yes... more than anything else in the world.
Idiot!
Miss Carol...
It's the deed to the mansion!
Do whatever you want!
You just might have been...
...that important to me, you know...
Haaa!
I'm left with many scars...
...but these scars have taught me...
...that life is all about getting hurt.
I've made an important decision...
Beautiful, isn't it?
Foster...
Forgive me.
Don't apologize. It's not
like you to be apologetic.
I've lost so much over the years.
And yet... I was so close to losing
the one important thing in my life.
Never mind... you see, I've decided...
...that I'm going to live my
life with you the way you are.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Yes.
I'm a cruel kind of man. Are you still sure?
Yes...
...because...
...I'm a woman, you see...