lt's a beautiful day to be at the beach.
lt sure is.
Hurry up Ryo!
l'm trying but...
Are you okay Ryo-kun?
Don't worry about it.
What's taking you so long?
Hurry up and move it.
Jeez, Harumi-chan...
l can't believe she made you carry all this.
Sis, you're not carrying anything either.
Mama, you're so mean.
l'm sorry Ryo-kun. l'll carry something too.
Don't worry Kasumi-san.
l got this.
l'm sorry.
l thought you might feel a bit cooler.
Thank you Kasumi-san.
l feel refreshed.
You're just too much Ryo-kun.
l don't think that's nice.
You say that after making me hold your bag?
Well, that's because...
You said you'd carry it, so...
Plus l said l'll help you carry it, but you said no.
By the way, l wonder where Mio and Harumi-chan are.
There they are.
Look over there Ryo-kun.
Mio's just like a little kid.
Kasumi-san and l...
We've been doing it ever since that day.
Our thoughts and things that are important...
l sully it and stain it...
And we hurt each other's feelings in the process.
She knows it's that kind of relationship.
But still, she can't say anything about it...
The Hills Have Size Vol. 2 Mutual Feelings
Hey! Mio!
We're going home!
Okay!
lt was so fun.
l had so much fun and now l'm really hungry!
You had so much fun and now you want to eat?
You're simple-minded.
lf you play for a very long time, you get hungry.
Compared to you, l'm still growing.
Really?
l wonder what part of you is growing.
Mio, Harumi-chan...
Can you two go buy some food for dinner?
l don't mind.
l'm counting on you two.
You two pick out what you want to eat for dinner.
Choose what you want but be nice.
l want some meatballs!
Meatballs? That's why you're still small like a child!
When l become an adult, l'll have a great body like mama!
Kasumi-san, you want to talk to me about something right?
l'm willing to do whatever you want me to.
Kasumi-san?
Ryo-kun!
l received a phone call yesterday...
She said she was my husband's lover...
l know l can't say anything since l've been cheating on him too...
But l felt very sad and hurt yesterday...
l felt like my heart was going to burst.
l just wanted to forget about everything.
So you came to my room?
But, you know what?
lt felt painful when you were making love to me.
Why?
At the time, l didn't know why...
But l finally understood when l came to the beach today.
ls it because of Mio?
Yes.
l saw her smile and realized what l had to do.
l have to be Mio's mother before l pursue my own interests as a woman.
And the pain l felt was a warning since l tried to forget my duties as a mother.
Kasumi-san...
l'll talk things over with Hisashi-san.
l'm sure he'll understand.
lt's the best thing we can do for Mio.
You're right.
Ryo-kun...
We're ending our relationship today.
So l want you to do me real hard.
l want to feel you for the very last time!
Ryo-kun, more...
l want you to do me harder...
So strong...
Kasumi-san, are you okay?
l'm okay.
More, l want more...
l want you to mess me up!
Kasumi-san...
Do it harder.
Much deeper!
l want to remember this feeling...
Your hot, hard cock...
lt feels good Kasumi-san!
l think l'm about to climax...
l'm about to...
Release it inside.
l want you to release your milk inside me!
l want your hot, thick milk.
Release it inside.
l want to taste and feel your milk!
l'm coming!
l'm releasing it inside!
Ryo-kun...
You released lots of milk inside me...
Thank you.
Hisashi-san is coming back tonight, so l'll talk to him tonight.
l'll tell him everything and find out what his thoughts are.
Okay.
Don't worry, l won't mention your name.
Well l...
You shouldn't feel bad.
lt's all my fault.
That's not true.
lt's not your fault Kasumi-san.
l don't want to hear any excuses, don't mock me!
l let you live the kind of life you want.
But l didn't expect you to cheat on me.
l know l cheated on you.
But you also cheated on me.
You think a man of my status would be satisfied with just my wife?
Anyway, l want you to stop seeing this lover of yours immediately.
Got it?
What about you?
Me?
You want me to stop seeing my lover, too?
That's right.
That's how normal couples...
Nonsense!
Can't you tell? You can't satisfy my needs anymore!
End of conversation.
l don't care how much it costs.
l don't want you to see your lover ever again.
You got that Kasumi?
Ryo-kun...
Were you watching?
l'm sorry, l...
You don't need to apologize.
Once again, you saw me in an embarrassing situation.
No...
Ryo-kun...
l just want to be alone right now.
Please...
l understand.
l...
Man, it's morning already?
Sir?
Ryoji?
What are you doing at this time?
Where's Kasumi-san?
She's gone.
Look.
She even left this thing behind!
ls that what l think it is?
l don't know what kind of man she was seeing, but l didn't expect it to be this serious.
Ryoji!
Do you have any idea?
Like places Kasumi went or some man that came to visit.
l really don't know...
What a stupid woman!
She didn't even think about my situation.
Now how am l supposed to...
You're pathetic papa!
Mio...
What are you doing here Mio?
What do you mean ''situation''?
You only care about yourself!
You never cared about mama, that's why she...
Yeah.
lt's that time already?
No, it's okay. No problem.
l'll be on my way, so l'll meet you there.
Yeah, that's right.
l'll make it on time if there's no traffic.
No, l left the materials there.
Bring it with you.
Mio...
Onii-chan...
Harumi-san...
l need to talk to you Ryo.
lt's about my sister.
About Kasumi-san?
Onii-chan?
Wrong. lt's me.
Harumi?
Where's Onii-chan?
He went out, he said it was an emergency.
l see.
Don't be mad, Mio.
He said it was very important.
Harumi-san...
You said you wanted to talk about Kasumi-san.
Why?
Why does it have to be my sister? Ryo!
She has her husband and Mio!
l know.
But l...
You're serious about her?
Yeah.
Fine.
She's waiting for you at the beach we went yesterday.
l'll look after Mio.
Hey Mio, do you like Ryo?
Yeah.
He's really nice to me and mama.
l see.
So you like him, huh?
You like him don't you?
l don't know about that.
That's not fair.
l answered your question but you won't answer mine.
That's right, adults are supposed to be unfair.
Kasumi-san...
Ryo-kun...
You came for me.
l see.
Mio said that?
l failed as a mother.
l can only think about what's good for me.
What's good for you?
Yes, l think two weeks must've gone by.
l couldn't stop thinking about something.
Thinking about what?
About you.
From the moment l wake up to the moment l sleep...
l was always thinking about you.
But l thought that was because l felt lonely.
l felt lonely, so l needed someone in place of my husband.
l would be happy with any man out there.
That's what l thought.
But you were there for me.
That's all it ever was.
Kasumi-san...
But it wasn't like that at all.
My thoughts about you grew stronger.
l couldn't think about anything else.
l was very scared.
So l thought l had to do something...
While l can still go back.
That's why...
But it didn't work.
He wouldn't look at me as a woman.
l'm so stupid, l knew about it, but l stayed with him.
l had no place to go in the first place.
But you didn't have to leave.
Your husband had a lover.
You also have Mio...
l can't stay in that house.
lf l stay, you...
You'll be unhappy.
lf l stay in that house, l'll bring lots of misfortune.
l don't believe that.
No, l know it.
l know myself real well.
l can't hold back my feelings.
Your life starts now. You'll meet lots of people...
...and be happy with the one you love the most.
You'll get tired of being with an old lady like me.
l don't want to get in your way!
Kasumi-san!
Don't say such selfish things!
Don't you know how l feel?
Your feelings?
l don't want to live without you, l already found the one l love.
That's why l came to see you.
But l...
You don't have to say anymore.
l love you Kasumi-san.
l want to live my life with you.
Ryo-kun...
l love you too.
l love you very much.
l want to make love to you.
Ryo-kun...
Me too...
Wait a minute Ryo-kun, l have to shower...
l can't wait anymore, l want you right now.
Please.
Wait just a minute.
Kasumi-san, that's...
l forgot to leave it at home.
Okay, l'm ready.
Kasumi-san...
Ryo-kun, there's no need to rush.
l'm a bit worried.
l feel you might disappear from my sight.
Don't worry.
l'm not going anywhere, because you're here by my side.
l'll always be by your side.
Ryo-kun...
l want you to feel my nipples.
Over here?
Yes, keep going.
Yes, that's good Ryo-kun.
Ryo-kun...
l want you to touch all over my body.
That's it.
lt's very wet Kasumi-san.
You can hear how wet it is.
Don't say that, it's embarrassing.
Do it harder.
Kasumi-san?
Ryo-kun, l can't take it anymore.
l want your hard cock.
Your hot, hard cock...
it's going deep inside me.
lt feels tighter than usual.
Ryo-kun, your hot cock...
Your hot cock...
lt feels so good, Ryo-kun...
Do me harder!
Your hard cock...
l can feel it deep inside...
Ryo-kun!
Are you okay Kasumi-san?
l'm okay.
l want you to do me more.
Your cock feels so good.
So l want you to make me feel hotter.
l want you to melt me so we can be together as one.
Kasumi-san.
Ryo-kun?
Let's do it Kasumi-san, we'll be together as one.
Deeper! Deeper!
Kasumi-san...
l love you Kasumi-san!
Ryo-kun! l...
l love you too!
l think l'm about to climax...
Me too...
We'll climax together!
Let's climax together!
Please, come inside me!
Ryo-kun...
Kasumi-san...
The one you shouldn't fall in love with...
...is the one you ended up falling in love with.
She's standing right next to me.
l'm sure there'll be lots of things waiting for us.
But l want to keep standing next to this person forever.
That's how l felt in my heart.