Do me harder!
l want you to mess up my cunt!
lt's going in deeper!
l can feel your cock deep inside!
lt's amazing.
l want it...
l want it too...
l want your rock hard cock!
l think l'm...
l'm...
Kasumi-san...
The Hills Have Size Vol. 1 Erroneous Night
Matsubara
Onii-chan! Rise and shine!
Come on!
Come on, wake up.
Mio?
Hurry.
Come and eat breakfast with me.
Okay, Onii-chan?
Come on Onii-chan.
All right, just don't pull my arm.
Good morning sleepyhead.
Harumi-san? What are you doing here?
Eating breakfast.
Now you sit here Onii-chan, right next to me.
He's finally up mama, get him some food!
All right.
l'll get it right now.
What's wrong Ryo-kun?
No, it's just...
Good morning Kasumi-san.
Good morning.
Itadakimasu!
Eat it before it gets cold, Ryo-kun.
Yes, thank you.
Did you get your room cleaned up?
l'm almost done.
You know why Harumi didn't come yesterday?
She didn't want to help you move your things.
lt's not fair.
lsn't it obvious?
Even if l help him out, l get nothing in return.
Don't be mean, Harumi-chan.
Ryo-kun always takes care of you.
lt doesn't hurt to help him, you know.
You don't seem to understand, sis.
l'm taking care of Ryo.
lsn't that right, Ryo?
Well, l don't know about that.
Did you say something?
Well, um, no. You're right.
Anyway, l can't believe you'll be staying at my sister's place.
l'm the one who's really surprised.
But are you sure you're okay with Ryo?
l realize he was nearby, but if something does happen...
...l don't think he's reliable.
Harumi-chan!
When the burglar came two days ago, Ryo-kun was there to scare him off.
The burglar came in since you forgot to lock the windows right?
Well it's just that l didn't think we'd get burglarized.
lf you're careless like that, you're always going to get robbed.
ln fact, you've always been so clumsy.
Look at the bright side.
l know that Kasumi-san's jewelry was stolen, but the burglar didn't steal anything else.
Well, l guess you're right.
But what bothers me most...
...is the fact that your husband showed up two days ago only to say hello...
...even though we were burglarized.
He's a very busy person...
Thank you for the meal.
But papa's coming back today.
l see.
He said he might be done with his work.
You can stay for dinner right?
Yes. l don't really have any plans.
l'm glad.
Then tonight will be a welcome party for you, Ryo-kun.
l have to prepare a feast.
Really mama?
Yes, l have to do a good job.
Oh my, look at the time, Mio.
You have to hurry.
Oh no!
Well, see you later!
l'm late...
She's full of energy.
Hey Ryo, you said you have no plans today, right?
Yeah.
Well, l want to talk to you about something.
Can you come to that coffee shop later?.
Let's see... How about 1 PM?
The one in front of the university?
Sure.
Okay, we're good.
Don't be late.
Don't ask him to do too much, Harumi-chan.
l'm sure he's tired after moving in.
l'm not asking him to do anything.
l just want to ask him something.
lt's okay, Kasumi-san.
l'm almost done unpacking my things.
But...
Right?
He says he's okay sis.
Then l'll see you later, Ryo.
Thanks for the breakfast, sis!
l'm sorry about all this, Ryo-kun.
Don't worry. l'll be just...
...fine...
Plus Harumi-san is your sister, so...
What?
l mean, she's the sister of the person who takes care of me...
Well, l gotta go clean up my room before l go meet her.
The room is all cleaned up.
l guess l'll take a shower.
Kasumi-san.
l'd like to use the shower.
Kasumi-san?
Did she go out shopping?
Oh well.
Where's the shower room...
What? Wait, um...
Ryo-kun!?
Welcome.
Over here Ryo.
Ryo-kun.
Wake up Ryo-kun!
Are you okay Ryo-kun?
Kasumi-san!
Are you sure you're okay?
l'm okay.
Ouch!
Ryo-kun!
Ouch...
Ryo-kun?
l'm sorry.
lt was an accident...
l'm...
l'm really sorry!
Ryo!
What's wrong with you?
You came here all sweaty and now you're daydreaming.
Are you listening to me?
Sorry.
What were you saying?
l was saying...
What type of girls do you like?
What type of girls?
Why?
You have a preference, right?
Friendly ones, intellectual ones, dominating ones...
Then don't you know any girls that you like who are close to you?
Well?
Kasumi-san...
What's wrong, Ryo?
lsn't there a girl that you really like?
One girl who you constantly think about.
Well?
Ryo's an idiot.
He just doesn't know.
l was telling him all those things, but he still doesn't realize it.
So insensitive!
Harumi-san.
Ryo...
Harumi...
Ryo!
Harumi.
l love you Ryo...
l... l...
l love you Harumi.
l love you too!
Ryo!
l love you...
l love you!
Ryo...
l...
l'm coming...
l'll climax...
l'm coming!
Harumi...
l wonder what Ryo thinks of me...
Welcome back Onii-chan.
Hey Ryoji, welcome back.
We were waiting for you.
Long time no see, sir.
Are you done cleaning up your room?
Yes.
l see.
Well anyway, let's just celebrate.
We're going to drink a lot tonight!
Yes.
lt's been a long time since we drank together, l was looking forward to this.
Let's drink.
No!
Not before he eats dinner with us.
You can drink with him later!
You'll understand it when you get older, Mio.
Well, l'd like to go take a quick shower if you don't mind...
Sure.
l'll just start drinking while l wait.
Mio, l want you to take his place and drink with me.
What?
All right then.
But l'll be drinking some juice.
l think l drank too much.
Honey...
l was waiting for you.
But you already went to sleep, it's not fair.
What am l supposed to do?
l don't want to use this toy...
l want you to do me with your cock.
l'm getting so wet because l want it.
But you...
l don't care whose cock it is...
l want it.
l want someone to look at me.
Wait... Ryo-kun was looking at me.
He was looking at my naked body.
His cock was so big after looking at me.
He looked at me.
Ryo-kun looked at my naked body.
He was staring at me.
Ryo-kun!
l wish this was Ryo-kun's huge cock...
Feels good...
Ryo-kun's cock feels so good...
Ryo-kun, you're wonderful...
l'm...
Ryo-kun!
Kasumi-san!
Ryo-kun?
No!
Ryo-kun, no!
We can't do this!
No!
Kasumi-san, l just can't take it anymore.
Don't use a toy like this, l'll pleasure you with my cock!
No, this is wrong...
Stop...
Anything but that.
No!
You said you wanted me.
But this is wrong.
No, please don't.
Don't be so rough!
lt's so hot and feels great inside you.
l know it's wrong but...
Your hot stuff is inside me!
l can't hold back anymore!
l really want your cock.
So l want you to do me.
Stick it deep inside up to my stomach!
Harder, Ryo-kun...
Harder!
l can feel you deep inside!
Kasumi-san, l'm about to...
Come?
You're about to come, right?
l want you to release it inside.
lt's okay today.
Kasumi-san...
Ryo-kun!
l'm going to come too.
l'll come!
Amazing...
l can feel your hotjuice inside...
Kasumi-san, l...
Last night l...
You don't have to say anything.
You were drunk, besides...
...it's my fault for doing such a thing...
So you don't have to apologize.
But...
Let's forget about what happened last night.
l want you to forget everything that happened, please.
l want you to forget everything that happened.
Forget everything?
Ryo-kun!
l can't forget about it.
How can l forget about it?
Calm down, Ryo-kun...
Stop it Ryo-kun.
Please...
Please don't do this.
This is wrong Ryo-kun.
You're the one who's cruel.
l don't want to betray Hisashi-san anymore.
But he didn't have sex with you last night...
Well...
l'll never make you sad.
l can't believe you like an old lady like me.
You're better off with a pretty young girl.
l can't find anyone better than you!
l'm really serious about you.
Ryo-kun stop...
Not there. You can't put it in there today!
Please!
Okay. Then what about here?
What...
Not there!
lt's dirty...
That spot...
No, Ryo-kun...
lt hurts...
Ryo-kun!
lt's tight, Kasumi-san...
lt's tightening up, l've never felt this way before...
Ryo-kun...
l think l'll go insane...
l have to pee...
Kasumi-san, l can't hold it in!
l'm peeing!
There's no turning back now.
l can never go back.
lt's okay, right Ryo-kun?