So, when can I see you again?
Well... still, school starts today and all...
So skip it - skip school today.
No good...
After all, I'm such a serious high school student.
HOMEROOM
AFFAIRS
An 18 year old high school senior's affair with her homeroom teacher.
PART ONE: Hitting me will cost you dearly, teach!
Mr. Ehara... the truth is, for the longest time...
...I've been in love with you!
Kya! I'm so ashamed!
How sweet, these girls... they haven't lost their innocence...
Teacher!
Well, I've been in love with you, too!
So have I!
Me, too!
And me!
Teacher!
Just a dream...
Morning, Tokiro!
Oh! Good morning, super!
Today's the day, isn't it?
Right! The first day of my teaching life.
That's true, yes.
But the school you've been assigned to is a girl's high school, right?
Uh, yeah.
To hear the high school girls around here talk of it, the place is fantastic!
Makes me wish I were ten years younger.
Cut the jokes!
The school I've been assigned to, Mitsuba Girls High School,
isn't that kind of place!
Besides, I'm a teacher!
To even think such slovenly thought about my students is...
Forbidden!
Sheesh, that super... oh!
What an incredibly beautiful high school student!
Now, that type of innocence...
Yes, you can say it takes all kinds,
but that pure, unspoiled form is the true appearance of a high school student.
Mitsuba, Mitsuba station!
Getting off! I'm getting off!
Sorry!
No, it's my fault, I wasn't paying attention.
This... this small box is...
CONDOM!?
Oh my, come over here, sir.
You're still a high school student, for crying out loud! Why do you have...
I could hear you without your shouting!
How embarrassing! Use your common sense!
Anyway, besides that...
Well, mister, what do you think?
You, sir, are just my type.
Next time, let's go on a date.
See you later, my handsome prince.
That was a night mare, that was...
"See you later, my handsome prince."
Yeah, right. There's no reason to expect.
That... that girl...
Oh my God...
Miyako, what's wrong?
Nothing, nothing at all... Heh heh heh...
Oh no... he's one of the new teachers...
Somehow I've gotta make sure we never meet.
Hey, Miyako... Miyako!! You're been acting kind of weird today.
It... it's nothing.
Don't tell me you know our new teacher?
That's impossible.
Yeah, you're right. There's no reason to believe...
that a serious girl like you would have any relation with a guy.
Yeah...
Miyako Hase, huh... Well.
since I'm your homeroom teacher, there's no way I'm letting you out of my sight.
There's no help for you taking such an attitude!
I'm contacting your parents!
Oh, cut the shit, will you!
Sit still for one second and they walk all over you.
Who do you think you're talking to addressing your homeroom teacher in such a fashion!
I would never have believed that at a top school...
like Mitsuba such a student like you...
I wonder what would happen if I yelled out now while dressed like this?
You're not...!
Uh-huh, everyone who saw me like this would think the same thing.
Teacher, Mr. Ehara had his way with me over my protests...
A CURRENT AFFAIR - ARE OUR SCHOOLS SEX PALACES!? HOMEROOM TEACHER RAPES STUDENT!
AN ACT UNBE COMING OF AN EDUCATOR! "I'LL NEVER BELIEVE ANOTHER TEACHER AGAIN!"
A naked girl in a classroom - the evidence is gathered before you...
What kind of preposterous...!
An any rate, put some clothes on!
Oh, teacher.
Let's be more tactful, hm?
If possible, I'd like to avoid any trouble.
If we both keep quiet, then things will be totally peaceful, right, teach?
Next time, come to my house so I can thank you properly.
Good-bye, teacher!
God, that was scary...
It's a test.
This is a test sent from above to see if I'm fit to be a teacher.
I will definitely bring that girl around.
This is it.
Ah, Mr. Ehara!
You came for a roll already? Impulsive, aren't you?
This is a home visit! I'd like to meet your parents.
Hm... Well, then, please, come in.
C'mon, get a grip!
Pardon the intrusion.
Your family lives in one room?
Sorry, my parents are divorced. Please sit down.
Here.
In that case...
You don't have to be so formal, you know...
Really? Then I guess I'll be goin...
Now, you came all this way, so why not enjoy yourself? Besides, it's safe here.
Whoa! Will you cut it out, you idiot!
Stop it...
C'mon, you get undressed too, teach.
Hurry up!
Kyaa! T... Teacher!
What are you doing?
Be a little more gentle!
This is silk, you know! You're terrible!
Alleee!!!
What in the world...
That's right, yesterday...
I came over to her house intending to have a parent conference,
and was tempted by her. After that...
I don't remember!
But... I've still got on my shorts...
Still, like this...
Huh?
Whassup? It's too early t'be so loud.
At any rate, I'll be going now. We'll meet another time.
Are you right?
Just... a little woozy...
You should rest a little, you know?
Last night you lost an awful lot of blood...
Huh?
Mr. Ehara, you saw me naked and the blood came gushing out of your nose.
You blacked out, I was so surprised.
So... we... we didn't cross the student-teacher line?
Teacher, don't tell me you're a virgin?
You're kidding! At your age!? Embarrassing!
Leave me alone!
You'll be fine after some breakfast I'll make some now.
You made all this?
What do you expect? There's no one else here, after all.
You've got to eat a good breakfast.
It's a good start to the day.
An appetite for food and an appetite for sex are the foundations of good health.
Quit while you're ahead!
You could stay longer, you know.
There's time before school starts.
That's not possible.
If I relax at a student's house,
how can I distinguish myself as a teacher?
Mr. Ehara!
Next time let's get nasty, okay?
Tokiro!
These days you look as if you're going to die.
Yeah, going to work these days has got me depressed.
That's no good. It's only been a month and you're sighing.
I'd think you'd better be laughing heartily, surrounded by young girls.
Well... There's more to it than that.
Now then, in the case of past perfect, we... uh!?
Teacher, is something wrong?
Er... No, nothing...
Why, that...
Now then, read the answer to Example 3, Miss Hase.
Yes, sir:
"The concert will have started when I arrived at the hall"
Um... Very good, Miss Hase.
Flawless reports...
And good at sports, yet...
If only her personality were good, there wouldn't be a problem.
OW!!!
Sorry!
It shouldn't be like this.
I'm supposed to be send students along the straight-and-narrow.
An admirable high school girl should have such a pretty face.
What are you doing?
Miss Hase, how about quitting trying to give me a heart attack, okay?
If you don't cut it out, I'm really going to get angry!
You've forgotten already about that night?
Stop it!
If someone were to hear you!?
It would be a problem.
Damn right, it would.
Teacher, kiss me!
What?
If you kiss me here and now I'll be good from now on.
But here? In a place like this?
I see... 'bye!
All right!
She's so cute.
No, if she's lying, that's it! I can't work from feeling!
In order to escape from this day-to-day-hell,
I'll have to do what she says...
Gotcha!
Bye, teach! We'll play some more tomorrow, 'kay?
That's it, that's the limit!
I have nothing to be ashamed of!
Now I'll have to talk severefly to her!
This time I won't give in!
You're late.
She's at it again!
Hase!
Huh? Oh, Christ, what do you want?
Why do you have to go from one unrepentant act to the next?
Papa, no!
Teacher!
Mr. Ehara, great, he's coming around?
For a second there I didn't know what to think.
Ow!
I am so sorry.
Let me introduce you, this is my father.
Pleased to meet you. Thank you for looking after my daughter.
Father!?
Forgive me. I had no idea you were her homeroom teacher.
Still, to hit her so suddenly, I thought one of her jealous...
No, it's not like that!
Ah, you're embarrassed.
Nothing to be embarrassed about. Even I as her father...
can see she's the kind of pretty girl you'd like to take down and bed...
Papa, please.
Ah, that's right.
Before I forget, here's this month's living expenses.
Thanks, papa!
Paying at the bank is faster, but then we'd hardly ever meet.
What can you do? After all, papa, you're a busy man.
By, Miyako, don't get into any trouble!
You too, papa. Take care of yourself, okay?
Oh, teacher!
I'm going to make you pay dearly for hitting me.
I see... It's about Miyako's behavior.
Yes. I figured that her home life must be different, still...
I wish that she would hear it from you as well as from me.
There's a lot that I'm worried about too. Fine!
Next time, I'll definitely have a word with her.
"Always make sure you use the right contraceptive!"
That's not what I meant!
Now, now...
What's with this sipping? Down that sucker in one gulp!
Down it!
There's a lad!
Hey, Pops, one more, and make it hot!
Many things have happened in our family...
I've always tried to make Miyako happy, even when she was a kid.
You might see her as a hell-raiser, but she really is a good kid.
It's just that people tend to see things in black and white.
That's why she's readily misunderstood.
That's why, if something should ever happen to cause her pain...
I'd want you and you alone to be by her side, please!
Leave it t'me!
I'll take responsibility for Miz Hase!
Ask anythin' you'd like! Anytime!
Really? Would you mind terribly putting that in writing?
"I, Tokiro Ehara, hereby pledge that, as Miyako Hase's homeroom teacher,
I will look for her should the need arise..." Huh?
You want my signature, too?
Whoa, Mr. Ehara!
Hey, are you all right?
Don't go to sleep here, teacher.
Teacher? Teacher!
Time to get up, teach! Your breakfast is getting cold!
Huh? What's Hase doing here?
Sheesh, what a sleepyhead!
What's this?
Heh heh heh... Well, the main course.
Is li'l-ol'-me!
Just a dream...
Oh, teacher!
Shall I pour you some coffee?
Or...
Do you want some milk?
Hah hah hah! I like you, teach, you're so funny!
It... It's a dream! I still haven't woken up from this nightmare!
That's right. If this is a dream...
What was that for?
Payback for treating an adult like a fool!
Serves you right. Huh?
Huh? That hurt!
This is reality?
Damn right, it is!
How did you get in here?
I told the super I was your younger sister. See?
So, what do you want on a Sunday morning?
I just moved in.
Just moved in? That's nice...
What!? You just moved in!?
So, I'll be staying here for a while, all right?
I'm moving in. It's settled.
Settled by whom!?
Are you crazy, just blurting out suddenly you're...
I didn't say I was living here for free.
I'll pay the rent in advance...
Again with the...!
with my body.
Hey, cut it out!
I'll even throw in a lot of extra service.
No, it's no good!
What's the matter with you?
Get serious! A teacher and a student living under the same roof?
If anyone found out...
I'd definitely be fired.
If that ever happened...
My family back in the country...
Figures, you're just like the rest, teacher.
You use kind words but only think about yourself.
You don't want to get involved in any trouble.
You're the same as all the rest.
Miss Hase...
If that's so... If that's so...
you should stop messing in other people's business,
coming out the way you did for a conference!
I hate your guts, teacher!
Wait!
This... This is definitely what I wrote.
But what in the world happened?
I'm always going to have her around like this!
I hate your guts, teacher!
She didn't come back here?
Hey, come to see the apartment?
Huh? Apartment?
Yep, pretty young girl lived there.
Somehow her father's company went belly-up...
She left early this morning.
"I'd want you, and you alone, to be by her side, please!"
You don't think he knew everything then...
and was leaving his daughter in my care!
Hey!
I'll be staying for a while, all right?
That idiot! She really didn't have anywhere else to go!
So she came to my place with that paper...
I wrote while I was half-drunk, asking for help! And what do I do!?
Hase!
Welcome!
Stop it, here, all alone...
Well, we can't get down and dirty here...
It'd be just like her... with no place to stay.
She'd probably call to one of these guys and...
I... I don't have anywhere to stay...
If I could stay just for one night...
And then...
Ah! This is all my fault!
If I'd only been a little more...
That's right! Her stuff is still at the apartment!
Maybe she'll come back for it!
Hase!
She's not here...
God. I was rash...
If I'd known about her condition. I never would've done it!
"You should stop messing in other people's business,
coming out the way you did!"
MIYAKO!!!
Oh, teacher?
I must've fallen asleep...
Have you been in there all this time!?
I mean, after all, up and leaving's all well and good.
But I had nowhere else to go.
And when I came back you were gone.
I thought I'd scare you so I hid in here.
Why, you...
Aah, it's night already!
Come on, let's sort out your things.
Man, this room's going to be a lot smaller from here on in...
Teacher...
Well, there's no help for it, is there? The situation being what it is...
Hey...
If you'd insisted that it wouldn't work I was going to blackmail you...
with living in my school club's meeting room on assembly day!
I told you the price for hitting me would be high.
"High" is right... and there's still interest due...
Sheesh, what a day this has been...
Teacher!
I'll scrub your back for you.
Just my way of thanking you for coming back.
Idiot! Don't come near me!
Tah-daah!
How do you like my swimsuit?
Whew...
Hoping I'd come in naked?
Don't talk stupid!
Now get out of here!
What's wrong? It's okay every now and then, isn't ti?
A change of pace is interesting.
Doing it like this feels good, doesn't it?
Hey now, stop it!
And now, the bubble dance!
Yi... Cut it out!
Mmm... Just like at a soap palace...
She... She's so soft...
I'll wash all the places that feel good!
Well? Not bad, hmmm?
So... this is what a soap palace is like...
That's right, you're still a virgin, aren't you, teach?
All right, then I'm gonna pop your cherry!
Idiot! Cut it out!
My, they are close for a brother and sister.