Are you awake yet?
Uh... yeah...
Morning!
Breakfast is almost ready.
Well, I'll see you later!
Hurry home, dear!
Wait.
What's wrong?
I'd prefer this... to a kiss.
Hey!
Instead of a "good-bye kiss" how about some "good-bye" hanky-panky?
Idiot! What are you saying, this early in the morning...!
Aw, come on - it's okay...
S-S-Stop it!!!
Are you all right? You look like you're having a nightmare.
Hey! Teach, let up!
Just a dream...
Ah-hah! He's rock hard!
Idiot! Stop that!
That must have been some sexy dream. If that's the case...
how about continuing where you left off?
I'm Tokiro Ehara, in my first year of teaching.
Through a lot of different circumstances, one of my students, Miyako Hase,
has come to be living together with me. The past two months have gone by fast...
HOMEROOM
AFFAIRS
An 19 Year Old High School Senior Is Hot for Teacher.
Part 2: I Was Born Reckless!
Teach... I'll wash your back for you.
Okay, Okay. You're wearing a swimsuit again, right.
Uh-huh. You can't take me by the same way twi... yi!
And you can make me clean, too.
You must be kidding!
Oh no, come on, pull it together.
Ouch... Look, will you please out the pranks...
I'm sorry. Did it hurt?
What's with her, her attitude's changed all of a sudden...
Oh no, she won't trick me like that!
And stop teasing people too, while you're at it!
Trying to seduce me all the time. It won't work!
I wasn't teasing you...
I didn't think you'd be that dense, teach! And if you're going to be...
like that all the time then you should stay a virgin!
Hey!
Who do you think you're talking to like that? That's no way to talk to an older person!
Even though she's always kidding around,
she was really angry...
It couldn't be...?
Where do the lies stop and the truth starts?
Bye-bye! See you tomorrow!
Miyako! Let's go home together!
I heard the small shop by the station is having a sale.
Really?
Let's stop in on the way home.
Conference on the way home?
Oh, it's you, Mr. Ehara!
Ah, you're lucky!
I've got a teacher's meeting right now so I don't know what time I'll be getting home.
Don't be too late on your way home, ladies!
Yes, sir!
Hey, guys!
Don't you think Mr. Ehara's kind of cute?
Is Mr. Ehara your type, Emi?
Well, these days he's been wearing those worn-out shirts.
Whenever I see that kind of thing I just can't leave it alone!
I'd like to go to his house and iron his shirts for him.
You've got the mothering instinct, Emi!
How about stopping by his house?
That's all right!!!
I'll be careful to see that that sort of thing doesn't happen again!
What sort of thing will you be careful about, Miyako?
Now then, I'd like to hear the opinions of the teachers concerned with this problem...
That Miyako... I wonder if she's still angry...?
...your opinion, Mr. Ehara?
Mr. Ehara!!!
Mr. Ehara!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Ehara, you really shouldn't let your attention wander...
during a staff meeting. It slows things down.
Yes, sir.
Ehara, you too are a teacher in this elite school of ours, so give it your all!
If you can't, there will be trouble...
I'm sorry, sir.
Long time no see, Miyako.
Kou...
'Been looking all over for you, Miyako.
Well, let's not stand out here. We can talk more inside.
No!
Not here, not this room!
It'd be bad for your "older brother", huh?
I know everything. You've been flirting around with him here, haven't you?
Okay, if here's no good then follow me.
That was a long time ago...
It was a night when... Oh, I don't know why, I just didn't want to be alone.
So I went out for a walk.
Kou called out to me.
I don't need it. I have enough money so give me something tangible!
Whenever he chooses something to give to me he'll be thinking of me.
He'll recall everything about me.
My feelings of loneliness would then disappear.
And we continued on like that. Live and let live.
We're here.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about now, is there?
Looks like she's still angry.
Oh well, this will be the first time in a long time I can make myself at home.
Look, I just...
Shall I wait for you outside the school tomorrow?
That... That would be...
Trouble, huh? A guy like me hanging around the grounds of the...
high-class Mitsuba Girls' School.
Miyako, come over to my place.
Your pop's business is gone, you got no place, right? So...
won't you stay with me?
Kou...
I'm serious.
Hey, Miyako, is dinner ready...?
Yeah...
It's peaceful when she's not around.
Too peaceful...
Stop it!
What's wrong, all of the sudden?
I forgot it's that time of the month for me.
Even though you're not wearing a tampon or napkin...
How did he...!?
Why are you so unwilling? Is it the guy you're with now?
I've been with you longer. You may have forgotten that...
but I bet your body remembers!
Now relax a little more.
What's the matter with me?
Not too long ago I was bopping along without a care.
Not too long ago I was by myself but I didn't feel lonely, still...
Ever since I've been staying with Mr. Ehara...
it seems like I'm doing the worst thing possible.
Ever since I've been living with Miyako...
whenever she's not around I feel empty inside.
Teach!
I... need her!
Teach...
I gotta pee!
What!? Now!?
Please let me go to the toilet! Else I'm going to let go right here!
Hurry up and go!
At any rate, this buys me a little time. But what am I going to do now?
Uh... Hi there!
Miyako! How long are you going to be in there?
She... she didn't...?
I don't believe this!
This is the fourth floor!
Teach.
Miyako!? Where are you!?
SAGAYA STATION
Miyako!
Teach!
You're late, teach!
Miyako...!
You stupid idiot!
What in the world happened? You've got no shoes on, and in a place like this...
Would you crouch down for a sec?
What's wrong?
I'm not wearing any panties.
The truth is, just when I was about to be raped by the demon king up in his sky castle...
he traded me my shoes and panties in exchange for my body.
Who would believe such a ridiculous story!?
I'm looking like this cause I escaped in the middle of it, aren't I?
The only thing that makes sense around here is nonsense.
Anyway, let's go home. I can hear all the details later.
Okay!
What's wrong?
I'm so relieved that I can't stand up.
Teach, I'm not too heavy, am I?
Oh, for the love of Christ!
Say, Miyako... I realized something today. While I was waiting for...
your call, I was by myself for the first time in a long while...
Uh... How can I put it...? I've been thinking about your...
Miyako...? She's sleeping.
Figures I couldn't say it.
Look, uh... Miyako...
What?
About yesterday...
You don't have to worry about a thing, really?
Let's go! We'll both be late!
Yeah!
Aren't you the close-knit pair this morning?
Kou!
Who are you?
Miyako's "significant other".
You look like you had some success too.
Using a homeroom teacher's standing to shack up with one's own student.
I bet you had a good time last night, huh?
After all, Miyako's quite the little technician.
You put on such a proper face but what goes on underneath?
That's why you can never trust a teacher!
Stop it! I apologize for yesterday, all right?
Anyway, go on home.
"I apologize, so go home", you say?
How long do you think you can keep playing with people, huh?
Take your hand off her!
Hmph, it doesn't matter.
Today my business is with you.
I wonder if you'd meet with me this evening for a little bit?
I'll contact you later at school as to where.
I'll give you them back to you then, Miyakok's shoes, that is...
'Later!
Miyako... I want an explanation.
You went with him to a hotel?
Well, there was no help for it, was there?
If I didn't he said he'd come to the school.
But believe me... nothing happened yesterday.
Nothing happened... not one thing...
That's why I didn't have any panties on!!!
If I'd done it I'd have had my panties on and left the hotel!
You're a teacher...
and you can't even understand that...!
Jesus, that's not something you go shouting about like that!
After all, I was telling the truth. You didn't believe me so I had to.
Your appointment with Kou... please break it.
He used to be with a gang, he's got a rough disposition, too.
If you go he won't just let you leave unharmed!
That's all the more reason to go then. Don't worry.
So, she couldn't play false. That guy and Miyako have up to now been...
Mr. Ehara of Class 2-5, there's phone call for you.
Please come to the office as soon as possible.
We repeat: Mr. Ehara, there's a telephone call for you.
Hey, Miyako...
Miyako!
What is up with you?
You seem awfully worried about something.
You don't think, is it that time of the month?
Uh... yeah... maybe that's it...
Will you quit it, it's lunch time!
Oops, sorry!
Look! I'm not taking you with me!
Come on! If you go alone, Teach, I'll be worried.
If you're there I'll really be worried.
You know nothing about Kou, Teach!
Anyway, go home!
The meeting time is probably about five or six o'clock.
The place is some area where not many people come to.
"And make sure you come alone."
How do you know the content of our phone conversation?
That's the way his kind thinks.
Kou is a lot more dangerous than you imagine, Teach.
The reason he quit school was because he beat up his homeroom teacher.
So please don't go!
No, I have no reason to run.
Then, I must be there with you.
Miyako...
Who are these guys!?
Old friends of mine from school.
I see the student you've been blissfully banging has come to plead your case.
Heh heh... Look, he's got stubble.
You wouldn't think he could do it with a girl years younger than him!
And at a famous school to boot!
Uh-huh... His type is always arrogant. Well, I'm not putting up with it!
Will you get real!
How long do you plan on keeping up this ridiculous shit!?
Miyako!
Miyako!!
Teach!
Evil man, seducing a student from a girls high school.
Guys, punish this bastard!
Are you all right, teacher?
It's a little early...
to be taking a nap!
Stop it!!!
Please! Say something to make them stop!
Leave him!
What!?
He's got no guts. Come on, make it interesting!
Look at that clumsy body. He's got no strength, either.
Yet he's full of arrogance before everyone.
Teachers — they're all the same!
Kou... could it be like it was before...
Miyako...
Yeowww!!!
Not so fast.
It's not enough to just cut his arm. You still haven't paid for your sins!
Damn right!
Take him out! Yeah!
Hey, everybody!!!
Why that...!
Whoa!!!
Super!
Don't look!!
Oh, shit!
Somebody must've reported the noise!
Run!!
Hang in there, Teach!
Nooo!!!
Mr. Ehara...
Where... where am...
Emergency hospital. You're all right, you just got a light concussion.
I see...
Ow ow ow ow!
Uh-huh, you've got to rest.
There should be no complications.
At any rate, shall we contact the school?
Since it's a famous school like Mitsuba we should do it first thing.
Miyako, I'm sorry. I...
The truth is, I had to protect you.
Teach...
Well, I'm going!
Miyako, today's the same as yesterday, be careful.
Okay.
Jeez, your behavior is so reckless it's dangerous. Look, I'm on edge here.
Don't you ever pull a rash stunt like yesterday's again, understand?
Bye!
Th... that girl...
I was born reckless!
She had the nerve to do it then.
Still...
To get my first kiss at age 26...
What a homely face.
Pardon me.
No, the fault was mine.
Kou! Try anything funny and I'll yell "Help, pervert!"
Don't worry. So, now what happens?
I don't know!
Miyako, why did you strip down that time?
If the police hadn't come then...
you'd have been gang banged.
Didn't you think things out that far?
I was so carried away I didn't have time to think about it.
Well, you can tell him for me if he's going to protect you he needs to get tougher.
I mean, what do you see in him, anyway?
I mean, he's not rich, no ladies man, he's weak.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
Oh, come on!
I hadn't thought about what I see in him.
After all, he's always angry, he's clumsy, his serious nature is his one good point.
He's really not my type at all.
You know, I wonder what do I see in him.
Myoga Station. Myoga.
Bye, Miyako!
Kou...
"What do I see in him", huh? When you say you don't know what you like...
about someone it means you like everything about them.
Good-bye, Kou.
Still, it's funny.
That first time we met all I'd thought was to seduce him.
But since we've come to live together, since Dad's company went bust...
lots has happened in the course of things. Still...
All of a sudden...
Miss Miyako Hase of Class 2-5, am I right?
I'm Mr. Kishida, the vice principal.
You won't need to go to class today if you would come with me.
Okay...
Principal's Office
Come in.
Teach!
Miyako!
So you're Miss Miyako Hase?
Yes.
Now then, Tokiro Ehara, homeroom teacher of 2-5...
Last night, we were contacted by the police.
The two of you were attacked by thugs, it seems.
Yes.
And the reason?
That... I cannot say.
So it would seem.
Ehara, we know everything.
After yesterday's incident, various matters were looked into.
First, we know of the honorless tale...
which one of the thugs the police captured put Mr. Ehara in.
For the honor of the school, I made a confirming call to the super of your apartment.
After that...
the two of you are living together, aren't you?
This is a mess!
There has never been such a scandal in the entire proud history of our school!
If word of this ever leaked to outside sources our school's status would fall.
We could never face the PTA.
Finally the time I feared has come.
I don't care what happens to me...
But somehow, I've got to protect Miyako! But... but how... what should I do!?
Ehara, you will decide to quit this school, I expect.
As for Miss Hase, we'd like her to leave voluntarily.
But... but that's...
Let's take care of the formalities quickly.
Just one minute!
We... we are not just living together.
The truth is... we...
We're getting married!!
We started living together as a prerequisite to our getting married.
Her parents also agreed to this!
Certainly there is no school regulation...
which states "teacher may not marry a student"!
Well...
But if this leaks to the outside!!
If Miyako's expelled I'll inform them myself.
And the media will be laughing loud and long.
I don't believe it! I just do not believe it!
We are getting married! You would stay the first thing that came into your head!
At any rate, thanks to that little scene we got a temporary reprieve.
It wasn't the first thing that popped into my head.
There was truth in there, too.
Oh now! What am I going to do?
Uh, listen... It wouldn't work?
What I said back there... It wasn't just off the cuff. Really...
Won't you marry me?
Maybe it's unbelievable something like this could happen so suddenly.
But I never...
No.
Getting married at my age? You must be kidding!
I don't want to even think about things like that!
Yeah, there's that, too. Hah hah hah hah!
I said, didn't I?
Was it that much of a shock?
Miyako?
That was just a lie! If it's with you, Teach, okay!
Miyako!
After all, no one else has been so protective of me up to now.
Hey, look over there! Oh wow!
Whoa! Go ahead, girl!
Isn't that Mr. Ehara? Oooh, I'm so jealous!
Hey, that's Miyako and Mr. Ehara!
I don't believe it!
To behave so shamelessly in such a place!
If I'm going to be your wife I'll give you lots of service.
Idiot! Will you stop! Not in public!
Now, now. It's okay, isn't it?
If we're going to be husband and wife we can have sex unashamedly.
Oh, your face is red! You are so naive, Teach!
Hey!!
Will you stop making fun of people!
Hang in there, Mr. Ehara!!
Why'd you lock the door!? Let me in!
No, you'll peek.
I'm not going to peek!
No matter what you say the answer is no.