COLONY
In the year 199X, the earth was
engulfed in nuclear flames.
The XXX Tower is 4x higher than VERY HIGH
People were mortified by their own deeds.
OK, let's shoot!
The XXX Tower is 4x higher than VERY HIGH
OK, LET'S SHOOT
The holy dildo awaits...
You must awaken, Hero.
Rai!
GO! GO! HERO!
HOOLIGAN EPISODE 2
A SYNOPSIS
OF EPISODE 1
My slave Yukito, who's lacking
a bit in the brain department...
Who are you calling a slave!?
You got a problem, chabu!?
Damn right I do! All in all...
Ooo! Olga's tits always look so delicious!
Ignoring the idiot and
moving along, chabu...
Ooo! Olga's tits always look so delicious!
Ignoring the idiot and
moving along, chabu...
Yukito's sexual desires made the
mysterious experiment go wild...
...and time and space had gotten
all mumbo-jumboed up, chabu.
The only way to fix this situation is
to collect the seven holy dildos...
...that are scattered throughout the
world, via expedient arrangement, chabu!!
In the last episode, we didn't
get any real lines. Right, Yuka?
I hope we get a bigger
part in this episode, sis.
First Aid!!
Sorry, but the real main
character of this episode is me!
The song "1, 2 & Shampoo" I sang
during the last episode should
be releasing on CD soon.
Really?
You never know when lies can become true!
Anyway, if the Emperor collects all
the holy dildos, all of our dreams
will come true! Right, Victoria?
Yeast.
I meant it how "yeast" sounds
like "yes". You didn't find it funny?
COPY COPY COPY COPY
I meant it how "yeast" sounds
like "yes". You didn't find it funny?
COPY COPY COPY COPY
V... Victoria doesn't seem to have
the same sense of humor as me.
COPY COPY COPY COPY
Anyway! On with episode 2, chabu!!
That took way too long.
Isn't that the usual custom with
monkey adventure, ball collecting
martial arts-type shows, Yukito?
Damn it, I even got dressed again.
Do you really mean it?
W... what are you saying?
Sato-chan is poking his face out of your fly!
DON'T FORGET TO
ZIP IT BEFORE YOU
LEAVE THE HOUSE.
DON'T FORGET TO
ZIP IT BEFORE YOU
LEAVE THE HOUSE.
An aristocrat has made such
an embarrassment of himself!
Th... the booby trap caught my...
DON'T PANIC.
RELAX.
Th... the booby trap caught my...
DON'T PANIC.
RELAX.
You're way more of an idiot than I thought.
The outcome of this battle
seems pretty obvious!
I've had it!
My anger is one step
away from "Let's charge!"
H... hold on! You're just taking it out on me!
I've had it with you!
Help! I'm gonna be killed!
Wait! Marigretle!!
Just kidding!
Now he's wide open for my...
Rocket Punch!
Excuse me but, was the battle to win
the holy dildo supposed to be like this?
Huh?
She took off!!!
This is...!
Shock! I forgot to retrieve my arm!
If this isn't a Cinderella story,
what is? I won't let you go, baby!
This is what's called a pinch
and punch rendezvous!
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
The next move is the key!
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
Think. Think. Think. Think. Think. Think. Think.
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
Think. Think. Think. Think. Think. Think. Think.
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
Ding.
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
CRY AND ASK HIM TO RETURN IT-
DISGUISE YOURSELF AS A KITTEN SO HE LETS HIS GUARD DOWN
SCREAM "FRONTWING" INTO THE SECOND CONTROLLER MIC-
Sometimes I frighten myself.
When is Marigretle going to do her stuff?
Huh?
Ooo! It's a kitty!
Okay, Yukito. Let your guard
down. Wha? Wha? Wha?
And what kind of joke is this?
Aren't humans are supposed to let their
guard down when they see a cute animal?
No kitten is this big.
I thought I was pretty cute, myself...
You're going to get a
stern punishment for this!
Where's the mercy of a warrior?
Please. Give me my arm back.
Then give me your holy dildo.
I have no choice. As a request, I have
something I'd like to discuss with you.
Um, would it be possible
to take a picture with you?
Why?
Well... umm... as a souvenir?
If I do that, are you sure you're going
to give me all of your holy dildos?
I swear upon my conscience circuit!!
Tara taratta ta!!
Mobile Print Club Camera!
Oh, you're a cat-model robot!!
Come on, Yukito. Look this way!
Make me look good!
DON'T I LOOK GREAT!
Cheese!
Oh yeah!
DON'T I LOOK GREAT!
OK, now. Time for you to
hand over your holy dildo!
I'll try harder next time.
I'LL TRY HARDER NEXT TIME.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to give
the Emperor the holy dildo.
I'll try harder next time.
I'LL TRY HARDER NEXT TIME.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to give
the Emperor the holy dildo.
I'LL TRY HARDER NEXT TIME.
This is mine now, mambo!
Two holy dildos to go!
But Hiromi, who has one of the
swords, left by herself earlier.
Yukito, take this!!
Huh?
Tri-kick!
W... who are you?
Yukito. All the holy dildos
you possess shall be mine!
H... Hiromi. I thought you went home?
If I could've gone home, I would have!!
Oh, dear me. Hiromi can't
go home by herself?
It's such a funny joke...
Violence isn't the answer...!
How are we supposed
to get home from here?
Hmm. That's something I overlooked.
On top of that, I heard this is all your fault.
Who told you such a horrible thing!?
A person I just met, who was
shrouded in a black cape!
Apparently your friend Yukito
warped time and space.
Look at how sketchy this person
is! She's even wearing a mask!
Wearing a mask or not...
She promised me if I brought her
all the holy dildos, she'd send
me back home to our world!
Are you honestly going to believe
what someone this sketchy tells you??
Anyway, I'm going to take all
of the holy dildos you possess!
I didn't want to fight against you like
this, but I guess it can't be helped...
Prepare yourself!
What? The shape of her holy dildo...!?
Yukito... got you off guard!
Squishy and natural...
How do you like my dildo's power?
Go ahead and admit your loss, Yukito!
It feels better than expected! The tightness
and bumps are better than the real one!
A pervert like you needs to be punished!
I can't lose to a masturbation pussy toy!
If I lose in the middle of my mission,
I'll be called Kick-boxer Mamoru!!
...censored...
If I lose in the middle of my mission,
I'll be called Kick-boxer Mamoru!!
I don't want to fight a meaningless
battle. So please Yukito,
hurry up and admit you lost.
How dare you! That's my Trigun helmet!
You're being a sore loser, Yukito!
Y... Yukito. Please stop
your pointless resistance.
If you don't give in, it's going to be terrible!
It's getting more intense!
I have to hurry up and get out of here!
Y... Yukito, that's my...
North Star Pussy Nucleus!
Stop!!
Now's my chance!
I'm embarrassed, so don't stare, Yukito.
You're beautiful, Hiromi... I
just want to eat you up...
N... no.
Don't make those noises...
I can't help it. Your juice
keeps coming out down here.
I'm so embarrassed.
Then how about this?
Stop.
Hiromi, doesn't it feel good?
It feels... really good...
Then...
Let's do two fingers!
No, if you do that...
Your pussy is making so much noise...
Don't say that...
Look, my fingers are
soaked from your cum.
Yukito, you're being mean!
Hiromi, you're so cute.
My - can't wait anymore!
...censored...
Hiromi?
Hiromi, what's wrong?
I... I'm scared...
It's all right! You're all ready to take me in!
But, you want to have sex with me
because you want my holy dildo, right?
That's not true! I love you!
And you don't care who the girl is, right?
No! The only one I really love is you, Hiromi!
I believe you, Yukito!
You're in me! Your thing is inside me!
My what is inside you?
Your d...
...censored...
You'll have to speak up. I can't hear you.
Your -!
...censored...
Ding-dong! You got it right!
It feels so... It feels so amazing!
I'm getting so hot inside!
I'm getting hot too...
Yes, fuck me harder! Harder!
All righty!!
Yes! It's so good!
Your - is filling me up!
...censored...
It feels so good!
Hiromi, you're such a dirty girl!
Stop... You're embarrassing me!
Yukito!
Hiromi!
I love you, Yukito! I love you!
I love you too, Hiromi!
I'm so happy!! Yukito, cum in me!
OK, I'm cumming!
I can't anymore! I feel like I'm going to die!
Hiromi. I swear I will collect all the holy
dildos and return you to our world.
I'm suprised at how fast I was
able to collect the holy dildos.
One more holy dildo to go! Piece of cake!
We'll see about that, Yukito.
What?
I'm saying you won't be able to defeat me!
Big titties!
Oh, you don't like women with big breasts?
Of course not! There's no one in this
world who wouldn't love your breasts!!
Well thank you. But please call me Emperor!
Absolutely, Emperor! But my god, those
glorious boobs are just like Olga's!
H... how do you know my true identity?
Huh? Identity? What are you talking about?
I guess there's no point in hiding it now!
No, but I... What are you...?
Wh-what!?
She was Olga!?
"She was Olga?" But Yukito, I thought
you figured out my identity...
Well, I was distracted by your
boobs, so I had absolutely no idea!
Oh, you didn't figure it
out! Thank goodness...
But the fact that you
know now doesn't change!
Olga... Forget about that!
Hurry up and come down so we can fight!
You're the Emperor, so
do a cool jump down!
Sure!
But Yukito, you're
definitely going to regret it!
OK! Hurry up and jump!
Well I can't just jump... I'd be
lucky if I could walk away alive...
Damn. But hurry down!
I get your drift, sheesh!
The long, hard battles will
be over after this next one.
But...
What should I do naked,
while waiting for Olga?
I've been given free time,
and I don't know what to do.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Yukito.
Oh, that was pretty fast, Olga!
Well... I forgot about it a second
ago, but I have the power to
manipulate time and space!
So I can even change where
our last battle will take place!
What in the world!?
In front of all these people?
Have you no shame, Olga?
Oh dear, you're not too convincing when
your - is swinging around like that.
...censored...
Oh dear, you're not too convincing when
your - is swinging around like that.
How pathetic!
I guess even you can't fight in
front of a large crowd like this.
I hate to break it to you, but...
Getting naked in public
doesn't bother me one bit!
Even the director of this show walked
to the vending machine naked,
in the middle of the night...
...and unfortunately bumped into
a policeman who was on patrol!
Whoa! Yukito just dropped the bomb, chabu!
And why are you here, Isao!?
I'm doing commentary, chabu! Commentary!
And why the commentary?
Commentary will make it more interesting.
Well, if you say so...
Let's make him do a commentary
of you writhing in pleasure.
Same goes for you, Yukito!
Is this the beginning to the
cutting-board live action battle!?
Ladies first! This one's mine!
W... what just happened!?
Moly!! The solution that shot out of Olga's
holy dildo has constricted Yukito, chabu!
This is my holy dildo's special power,
"Silk String Bind"! This battle is mine!
If that's how you want to play,
I'll use my "Alter Ego" power!
La dee da!
Yukito has used his special power
as a counter attack, chabu!
Alter Egos, do your best!
Roger, sir!
Ohhh! And Yukito's Alter Egos
attack all at once, chabu!
Roger, sir!
Ohhh! And Yukito's Alter Egos
attack all at once, chabu!
No matter how many alter egos attack,
they're powerless against the Emperor.
I can't believe my eyes! She finished
them off in seconds, chabu!
Is this the power of an older woman!?
Don't worry, Yukito. I
won't kill you in seconds.
And now!! Olga is slowly walking toward
Yukito! Is this the end for Yukito, chabu!?
Sis, Yukito won't lose, right?
Well... it seems like this time...
You should be exhausted from fighting all
those battles, but you're so full of energy.
I know I'm in a pinch, but when I think
about your techniques, I can't help but...
Then how about something like this?
It feels so good...
The Dance of the Flying
Dragon with Golden Balls!
Dragon with Golden Balls?
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
Like a dragon playing with balls...
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
...all the fingers on the right hand
delicately massage the scrotum...
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
* Attention: The anus and scrotum are positioned
very delicately- If you wish to try this, please do so
under the supervision of an expert- *
...while two fingers on the left hand enter
the anus to directly stimulate the prostate!
It's a high-level technique the Emperor uses!
My, Yukito, your balls are starting to rise.
My weewee can't take it any more!
With Olga's irresistible Dance of the
Flying Dragon with Golden Balls,
Yukito has shot a load, chabu!
Yukito...
But Olga's attack isn't over yet, chabu!
It's the Super Hi-Speed Deep Throat!
And she's using her teeth
to add subtle pressure!
Moly! There's another cum
shot from Yukito, chabu!
Yukito, that's enough...
You're at the end of your rope.
Your cum is getting thinner.
D... damn...
Let's finish this.
Unbelievable! Yukito is still hard -
no, Olga is making it hard, chabu!
DIRECTOR
That technique is...
The Dance of the Butterfly!
The Dance of the Butterfly?
The three G-spots of the male
root, the frenulum, the sulcus
and the mucous membrane...
...are getting stimulated by the thumb
and middle finger. While the pointy
finger stimulates the meatus...
...the ring and pinky vibrates
the urethra and the shaft skin!
I can't anymore... I g... give...
Yukito! You can do it!
Yukito is fighting and I...
The only thing I can do is...
Go, rev the engine. I'm
gonna carve a beat...
My bursting emotions
are going to overflow...
and spark...
I'll never lose, whatever the situation,
What's going on?