Emotionally disturbed huh...
Hello.
That uniform...
Are you from Souka-gakuen?
Y..yes...
May I sit here?
Of course.
Are you feeling sick?
Err...yeah. Lately, I haven't been myself.
I have trouble sleeping...and lots of stress.
You being...bullied?
Well, um...yes.
You can tell?
Yes, but nothing to worry.
My sister is a teacher at your school.
Besides...
She's very strong!
I will let her know.
She will take care of you.
Your name?
Mizuki Hiromi.
I am Todou Mikoto.
Sister of Todou Honoka, the teacher of science.
Nice to meet you.
Honoka-sensei's...?
Sensei, please forgive me...
What's wrong?
I'm only making your wishes come true.
You should be grateful.
Hiromi-kun, hurry...come!
This medicine made by that science teacher, Honoka Todou, sure works great.
Medicine...?
Hurry...
I can't hold it, Hiromi-kun...
What's wrong?
Your favorite teacher is begging for you.
Forgive me...I can't do it...
Don't lie to me.
Oh?
You mouth lies, but your penis is honest.
Might it be thinking on it's own?
Looks like it wants to bury itself in her stinky piss smelling hole.
Still going to resist?
I can't...
I see, alright then.
Don't pull it out!
More...!
Since you don't want her virginity, it will be lost to...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Because of your pathetic attitude, Rina-sensei lost her viginity to a soda bottle!
I'm sorry...
So, now you want her.
Fine, lick Rina-sensei's cunt clean now.
Rina-sensei, I'm sorry...
Give me, give me!
Hurry, hurry!
Right there, there!
Great, great!
More, there...there, great!
So pathetic.
Great...harder...
Rina-sensei, I'm sorry!
Rina-sensei, no! I can't hold it, I'm going to cum!
Stick it in, Mizuki-kun!
OK.
Here I go!
Hurry, hurry!
It hurts!
It's warm!
Please, forgive me!
Forgive me, I'm going to...!
You are my slave!
It hurts!
It hurts, no...
Great, Yuichiro-san!
Feels great.
More!!
Amazing, great! Cuming, cuming!
I'm growing bored of her.
This is...
Todou Honoka.
Karate, Aikido...a mixed martial artist.
She is...
I almost forgot.
Here is the key for your room, Social Studies 2nd floor.
That gramps...
What's this?
What's wrong?
I'm only making your wishes come true.
You should be grateful.
Hiromi-kun, hurry...come!
This medicine made by that science teacher, Honoka Todou, sure works great.
Fucking bitches...!
First science teacher Todou Honoka.
Then...
This is dangerous, so each of you be careful.
When you're ready, start the experiment.
It's dangerous, Mizuki.
Get some rest if you're not feeling well.
I don't want to go to the nurse's office without Rina-sensei.
He's always been dazing.
But it became worse now that Rina-sensei isn't here anymore.
Anyway, Mizuki. Rest at the nurse's office.
I..I am alright.
Don't push yourself.
Today's experiment is dangerous.
OK...
You're picked on to?
Yeah...
Because of it, I became paranoid of everything.
My sister brought me to the hospital and I was diagnosed with manic-depressive psychosis.
I couldn't have guessed...
I'm grateful of my sister.
We're not related by blood, but she's very nice to me.
She saved me once when I was being picked on.
Honoka-sensei is very brave.
I can attend school soon.
Really?
Yeah, hope we have the same class.
I'm registering tomorrow.
Rina-sensei...
Great. This is great...
Who is it?
T..this is!?
Todou Honoka-sensei...?
Us?
She said she'll be waiting at the lab.
I wonder what it is?
I bet you did something again.
Nah, I've been a good boy lately.
Let's go see what she wants.
This should be it.
Alright.
Hurry and wake up.
There's no meaning without you being awake.
Todou-sensei, did you call for us?
Sensei, where are you?
Maybe in here?
We're coming in.
What...what are you guys doing...here?
It's hot...feels like it's burning down there.
What are you guys going to do to me...?
What do you mean, you called us here.
That's right, Yuuki Kaho-sensei told us.
Yuuki Kaho!?
I can't take this!
Sensei!
What are you doing!?
Guys, stop it!
Stop it!
Now!
Guys!
STOP!
Stop it...
Onee-san?
Onee-san, I'm done with registering.
Huh?
Over there?
Onee-san, you here?
Let me have some.
Stop, not my...little sister...
Little sister? That sounds sexy.
This is great!
No!
Not her...
Bitch, don't pull it out!
O..onee-san...
Sensei...!
No, Onee-san!
It hurts, stop, it hurts!
Something is strange...
C'mon, open that little mouth wide and suck on this huge cock.
Sensei!
Here I go.
It hurts!
Where did that bitch go?
Looks like you're looking for someone.
Nao!
T..this is!?
As they say, the lighthouse does not shine on its base.
What's going on?
Hey, don't be so uptight.
It only means she was the original master.
So, history repeats itself...
Nao!
Oh my, already done with your homework?
That sure was quick.
Hah, that's because someone told the students to study.
Looks like she wanted more so I gave her the shock treatment.
You didn't like it?
You sure are cautious.
How's this?
Cheers to the two alike.
Cheers...
You sure are rough.
You are going to be my slave like Nao.
Looks like you trained her well.
But I showed her a new world.
It's all thanks to you.
It didn't take long for Nao to cum.
She even wanted more.
More, more, give me more!
Please!
Great, it's so great!
More, more!
How is it?
Did you think I would become your slave and beg you to fuck me?
No undies...were you expecting this?
Girls are all the same!
This...what is...happening...?
You're cautious, but also easy.
A drug...?
We traded glasses.
When did you...?
It's a basic trick.
I put the drug only on half of the bottle mouth.
The glass didn't matter.
Shit...of all things.
Good night, boy.
C'mon, how long must you sleep.
Hurry and wake up.
S..stop it, Nao!
Don't rest!
Stop it, Nao!
Please your former master more.
Yes, Master...
What are you doing!?
Stop it! Now!
Nao, stop it!
Stop it!!
How does it feel to be tortured by your former slave?
How's this?
...l'm cumming!
Not yet, I won't let you off so easy.
C'mon, lick it.
Yes, Master.
Good...
Good!
Bitch, move it.