Hey, hold her still!
Sensei...you better not disobey Daito-kun, or else...
That's right, Daito-kun's dad has power in this city...just shut up and listen.
It's your fault Sensei, for wearing such provocative clothes.
It hurts...no...stop...
Like this? Or like this?
It hurts...stop.
Please...stop.
You tell us to stop, but you are wet!
Yeah, soaking wet!
Time to teach this teacher a lesson or two!
I will...stick it in!
I can't hold it!
Aye, aye!
I'm next.
Me too!
Stop it!
Let her go.
Date-kun...?
Stop it!
Y..you shit!
Fuck!!
Put it up!
Stop it right there!
Stop it! Oh my...what have you done?
He was attacking the teacher and we tried to save her!
That's...not true...
Date Yuichiro...you did...
Is this true?
Sensei, that was close.
That's...correct...
Backstabbed!?
Why...me...
Oh? It's you, Mizuki-kun.
Asakura-sensei...
What's wrong? You're hurt.
Er...well...I tripped.
I..it's not a big deal...
You sure trip a lot. Come, I'll put a band-aid on you.
OK...
Yuuki-sensei.
So you were here.
Your mom...I meant, the dean is looking for you.
Morikubo-sensei, thank you for letting me know.
Ohh...Yuuki Kaho-sensei.
Not only does she like to teach...her beauty...her knowledge...
Not just from the students, but us male teacher all respect her...
They say every rose has thorns...
Don't forget that she is the daughter of that cold-hearted dean.
A new student in my class?
Yes, looks like he is a trouble maker. Please take care of him.
Yes...
Oh...and...
Yes?
What do you think about the new nurse, Asakura Rina-sensei?
What do you mean?
Our previous nurse. What's her name...she...went to a mental hospital. What a pity.
Excuse me...
It stings, Sensei.
Stay still...Don't keep the problems to yourself. Talk to me, I will help you out much as I can.
What's wrong?
Don't move, let me put this on.
Watch out.
Why are you...so hard?
Sensei, don't touch...
Mizuki-kun...no...
Sensei, I'm going to...cum...
Not yet...hold it in.
Sensei...
Mizuki-kun, you are cute. Ever since I saw you...
It's dirty.
Well...that's because...
Hey, hold him still!
Please stop...
Hey, suck on it.
Hell no, it's dirty.
Why not use this then?
A twig?
That's great!
Stop! It hurts...it hurts.
How is this?
You are mean. Be more nice to him.
Hey, lick mine too!
Stop.
Hey, he looks disgusted. Have you been taking a shower?
Not for a week.
Hey, it's a pity that a guy can get hard even if he mentally doesn't want it.
I see...
Mizuki-kun, that's terrible. Let me clean you.
Sensei...it's warm.
Mine too...Mizuki-kun.
But...
Be gentle.
This is what is looks like...
So beautiful...
Smells great.
Sensei, no! I can't hold it! I'm cumming!
Oh...cum, Mizuki-kun.
Sensei!
Sensei...
Mizuki...
Mizuki-kun, you know why you are here?
Yes...because I wasn't able to answer your question in class.
Correct. The special lesson is just for you.
Open you book!
Y..yes...oh!?
Sensei, it hurts!
You don't need to study with me, if you don't want to.
But your favorite teacher, Asakura Rina-sensei might be expelled.
That's what you deserve for treating this school like some skanky hotel!
Let's start the private lesson.
Lesson one.
Yu..ichiro-san?
Nao...Shinohara.
Cafe Americana, no sugar, little bit of milk. Correct?
What a reunion. A home-study teacher like you...
...became a social studies teacher while I was hopping schools.
Yes...
Why? Why did you disappear from me without notice?
What's wrong, Yuichiro-kun?
Backstabbed...backstabbed...female teachers are all...
You are the same! Same as that bitch that backstabbed me!
Why did you disappear without telling me?
Because...corruption...
Corruption? What do you mean?
Because of me...I would corrupt you by being close to you...
Corrupt me, but how? What do you mean?
I can not explain...
You have no reasons and you backstabbed me!?
No, that's not true. I...I...
Be quiet! Shut up! Don't speak nonsense!
It hurts! Stop, Yuichiro-san!
Ouch!
Yuichiro-san...no, this is...school ground!
You're telling me what to do!?
No...Stop...please stop...
Yuichiro-san...!
Really? You really want me to stop?
Your nipples are already hard. Your pussy is soaking wet, begging for a cock.
Now, say it...'Yuichiro-sama, I want your big hard cock. Please stick it in my dirty hole.'
No, I can't...
You masturbated every day because you couldn't forget me, right?
C'mon, say it. Say it!
Yuichiro-sama...please...please stick it in.
Don't talk pretty! Say 'Fuck me' just like before!
Yuichiro-sama...please...please stick your hard meat in me...and...fuck me!
Alright.
I'm going to cum...cum...cum...cumming!
It's warm...your sperm...it's cumming inside.
Sensei...please forgive me. I can't hold it anymore...
What? You said you were thirsty, so I gave your favorite cola.
And now you want to use the bathroom?
I see...
It's not good to hold it in.
Stop...Sensei...
Stop...
As if it's alive.
It finally stopped.
Don't...stroke me...
How was Rina-sensei. Was she more gentle?
Oh my, what a dirty boy. First you piss, now you cum?
Anyways, has Rina-sensei done this to you?
Answer me. How far have you gone with her?
Tell me, or else...
She...used her mouth!
She didn't go further?
Yes...
She didn't let you touch down there?
Here, lick this. You haven't seen it before, right? Look closely, c'mon...!
Yes...
Open your eyes and lick it.
That's right...harder...
Yes...yes...great...higher.
Yes...now stick your tongue in.
Now, do what you wanted to do with that bitch.
It's...my first time too...
Why...why him?
Now this hole.
P..please...forgive me...I'll break...!
You are my slave!
That teacher...! There is much to prey on!