I have to run away!
I'm not going to feel
any pleasure from him!
Not from him!
A boat...
If I get on it...
I'm sorry, but I can't
let you on the boat.
I'm impressed that you carried it
all this way without dropping it.
I'll give you a reward for that...
...but first, I have to punish
you for trying to run away from me.
What's that look?
I guess you still have to
learn to be a slave, huh?
It seems like all that
training was not enough.
If you disobey me, I'll give
you a very harsh punishment...
You are not allowed to even breathe...
...without my permission.
Please someone help me...
...before I lose myself...
...before I break...
Chapter Two: Shoko Iyanagi
Damn, what is this? I can't
even scratch the surface.
What's going on?
Who is she?
This is a thermometer...
It looks like the inside of this
is filled with liquid nitrogen.
So she's been frozen and preserved?
Preserved?
Ryuichi...
What should we do, Mr. Oishi?
Well, I really don't know...
Come on young man, you're the
tour conductor, aren't you?
But we've never had a
situation like this before...
Of course! This is the craziest
thing I've experienced in my life!
I demand a cancellation of this tour!
I don't want to be on
this creepy island anymore!
Call the boat to pick us up right now!
Okay, okay, we'll consider
canceling the tour, so...
Please wait!
I'm sorry to inform you, but...
...the radio is out of
order at the moment, so...
...we have no way of
contacting the outside world.
What?
In short, we have to wait for
the boat to pick us up tomorrow.
How could you do this to us?
Hey, stop it!
Are you saying that you're
scared of a woman in a capsule?
What?
Do you really think that
frozen lady can hurt us?
She's not going to hurt us.
It's impossible.
Damn!
I understand this is an
unexpected incident...
...but we'll make
sure that you are safe.
So we would like you to continue
the tour. Is it okay with everybody?
I guess we don't have
any other choice...
But I can't believe I have to spend
a night with a hot-headed jerk.
What did you say?
Cut it out! Now is
not the time to fight!
You better thank him.
We appreciate everyone's cooperation.
Also, don't come back to this
hospital until the police arrive.
Emi...
Is something wrong?
Oh no, nothing...
By the way, how did you find this place?
I don't know if you'll believe me,
but I felt like I was being called...
I felt like this girl was calling me.
I see...
I don't know why...
Why did I feel like she was calling me?
This is the first visit to this
island for you and Wakaba, right?
Yes, but what does that
have to do with anything?
No meaning. I was just curious.
What are you doing here?
Everybody is waiting for you outside!
Sorry, I'm coming...
Is something wrong, Shoko?
Um...
Can I walk with you?
Yes, sure...
Thank you.
Ryuichi, what should we do next?
Oh...
Of course, we'll look
for the rest, right?
Wakaba, let's look for more chapters on
the beach before it gets dark.
Yeah!
Ryuichi...
Since I saw that naked woman in
there, I've been feeling horny...
Will you punish me like before?
Okay, I'll punish you
as much as you want.
I found it!
Where is Ryuichi?
Is my dick tasty, Hiromi?
Yes, your dick tastes so good.
Then why don't you suck
it until milk comes out?
Yes, please let me
taste your come, Ryuichi.
I'm coming, Hiromi...
You're so good at sucking,
you deserve a reward.
I want your dick inside of me.
Okay, I'll let your
pussy taste my dick, then.
If you scream like that,
Shoko and Takashi will hear us.
But I can't help it.
So I'd better pull
my dick out then, huh?
No!
I want you to fuck
me as hard as you can!
Please harder! I'll go crazy!
Ryuichi, please, can I come?
Not yet, Hiromi...
Oh please...
I can't hold anymore...
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Hiromi, you came without my
permission.
You are a bad girl.
You need to be punished harder.
Yes, please, I need more punishment...
Your pussy is so tight, Hiromi!
Yes, Ryuichi, please fuck me hard!
Ryuichi, I'm coming again...
No Hiromi, not yet...
But I can't hold it, I'm coming...
I'm coming!
It was your fault that they found here.
I'll have to punish you for that.
Ryuichi!
Where have you been?
I've been looking for
the rest of the chapters.
Oh, sorry.
It looks like you really believe that
your wish will come true when you...
...collect the 1 5 chapters and
offer them to Kotodama shrine, huh?
That's right! My wish
will really come true!
Did you hear that?
What is your wish, Shoko?
Me? Well...
What? What's your wish?
Wakaba! You don't need to know!
Umm!
I wish there were more flowers
or trees on this island...
That's true.
That's building 1 8,
where you used to live...
We may have passed by
each other 8 years ago.
Yeah.
I'm sure I've seen
this building before...
...but where?
Ryuichi.
Why are we standing
here? Let's go inside!
Okay, but don't jump on me like that!
Wakaba, you're always so cheerful.
Maybe Takashi likes a
cheerful girl like her.
This is the room I used to live in...
And the author of the story, Yutaka
Mizuhara, used to live next door.
What happened, Wakaba?
Look!
We finally found a plant on this island!
And this is really big!
What's this?
This is Ron.
It's aloe, isn't it?
This aloe plant is named Ron!
Aloe named Ron?
This is actually aloe.
It's pretty big, too.
But how can it grow so well
without anyone taking care of it?
I'll bring some water for Ron.
Hey, Wakaba!
It's getting dark! Be careful!
What is she thinking?
Hey, we found another one.
All right!
We just have one more to go.
Wakaba will be glad, too.
By the way, what kind of
person was Yutaka Mizuhara?
I don't remember that much
because I was little, but...
...he used to play with
me. He was a nice person.
What do you think his wish was?
I think he wanted to protect
who was precious to him...
How do you know?
I don't know...
It's funny, you talk as if you
knew somebody you never met.
Yeah, it's funny...
Okay then, let's do our best to
get the last chapter for Wakaba!
Yes.
I'll go look for Wakaba.
Come on, Tomoko.
Please stop, Mr. Ito...
Is that Ito and Tomoko?
I'll bet Ito is trying to pick
a fight with Shinohara again.
It's kind of cold to call
me Mr. Ito, don't you think?
I guess I should expect it from
someone who dumped me for money.
Don't say it like that, Hiroki...
After my parents died,
I had no choice...
I had to pay off the debt...
Tomoko and Ito used to be engaged?
I don't want any excuses!
Suck my dick.
You used to love this...
For 8 years, I've been waiting
for the chance to see you alone.
Good...
The way you use your
tongue hasn't changed yet...
I'm coming, Tomoko!
You still swallow it
until the very last drop.
You know that you're still mine...
Your body wants me!
That's not true...
You can't live without having
something in your pussy.
Please, Hiroki...
If Shinohara caught us here...
Shut up!
You are mine!
I'll take you back from Shinohara!
Even if it means I have
to kill him, I will...
Water, water!
You called him too, didn't you?
Wakaba!
Maybe she went back
to the hospital room...
Wakaba, I thought you came here.
Ryuichi...
Let's go. Everyone will get worried.
Okay.
That flashback again...
Who are you?
Do you know me?
My name is...
Akari Mitsuhashi...
Why do I know her name?
Ryuichi...
Hey Shoko, where is everyone?
They're still waiting
in Takashi's room...
I have something I want to tell you...
Wakaba, go back to Takashi's room
first!
Why?
You have to water Ron, right?
Boooo!
This must be about Takashi, right?
How did you know?
I can tell just by looking at you.
Oh yeah?
I'd never been in love my whole life...
Takashi was so kind and sweet to me.
And my heart starts
pounding when I'm with him...
I've never felt this way before...
I don't know what to do...
Why don't you confess
your feeling to Takashi?
I can't!
Hiromi said the same thing to
me, but I don't think I can...
I see. So you'll hide
behind Hiromi, huh?
I think all you need
is to have courage...
Ryuichi...
If you just sit and wait,
you'll never get anything...
Ryuichi...
I'm kidding!
As far as I know, he doesn't
have a girlfriend right now.
If you tell him how you feel,
he'll definitely accept it.
You think?
You just need a little courage.
Thank you...
It's your fault that
they found my doll...
You dropped it...
She didn't drop it when I
did the same thing to her.
Please let me try again!
Move on to the next step as we planned.
Kill anybody who is in our way.
Do you hear me?
You have to try again.
We'll do this until you can hold it in.
We did what we could do.
It's all up to Shoko now...
What are they doing?
Hey, tell me
what they're--
It's none of your business!
Takashi...
Well, I wanted to tell
you that I like you!
Thank you Shoko, I like you too.
But I can't be your boyfriend.
There is a girl that I like...
It's one-sided love, but I
just can't give her up, so...
I'm sorry...
I see...
I understand...
Forget about what I said!
Shoko!
You guys told me to confess my
feelings and look what happened.
You all knew this would happen, right?
That's not true, Shoko!
We really care about
you, and that's why...
I don't want to hear it!
Shoko!
Shoko...
Maybe I hurt Shoko...
What's wrong, Emi?
Tomoko told me that she couldn't
find her husband, Mr. Shinohara.
So I was looking around and...
I'm scared!
Was he killed?
Probably...
Oh my god...
Serves him right!
That's not something you
say about someone who's dead!
This is terrible...
Who would do such a thing?
Let's untie him first...
Emi, what happened to your hand?
Oh this...
I fell and got injured earlier...
Let me untie him, then.
His skin is burnt...
It looks like a murderer
is loose on the island.
I don't know who could it be, but...
It's not me!
Do you have any proof?
Let's try to stick together from now on.
Oh my God, Shoko is alone now.
I'll look for her!
You all go back to our building.
I'm glad that I found you, Shoko...
Shoko?
Don't come here!
If you come closer, I'll jump!
How could you say such a thing?
I'm not cute like Hiromi
or cheerful like Wakaba...
I don't have the right to be in
love with someone or even live...
That's why Takashi doesn't like me!
But you are cute, Shoko...
Don't tell me lies!
I'm telling you the truth...
You don't know yourself...
Then Ryuichi, will
you have sex with me?
If you think I'm cute, you
can sleep with me, right?
Shoko...
Okay, I'll have sex with you.
But we'll do it my way.
No, I can't do this...
This is what you wanted for, right?
But I didn't know you
would tie me up like this...
A bad girl like you deserves
punishment!
This is for making everyone worried...
This is for thinking you're not cute...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Do you feel good when I spank you?
No, that's not true...
Don't lie to me. See?
Please, donit touch those...
Your nipples are already hard.
You must feel good, right? Shoko?
I can't tell you...
Okay, I have to spank you again, then.
I'll tell you, so please don't spank me.
I'll ask you again. Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good...
I'll make you feel better.
Oh, please...
Please don't touch down there...
I can stop right now if you want me to.
Oh no...
What do you want me to do?
Please, touch it more...
Where do you want me to touch?
I can't say it.
Please touch my pussy.
Good...
Your pussy says that
you're feeling good...
You're a cute girl who can
be so sensual like this...
I am a cute girl...
Do you want to feel more?
I can't say such a thing...
Be honest, otherwise I'll stop it.
Please make me feel better.
I can feel you inside of me.
Shoko, I'm going to move, okay?
Please be gentle.
If you do it that hard,
my pussy will break...
Your dick is hitting my spot...
Ryuichi...
I can't take it anymore...
I'm...
You're such a pretty girl who
can please a man like this...
So, be more confident, okay?
Thank you, Ryuichi...
There's a murder?
Let's hurry back. Everyone
must be worried about us.
Ryuichi!
Wakaba! What are you doing here?
You didn't come back, so
I came to look for you.
I told you not to go out alone!
I wasn't alone!
I was with Emi, but I lost her and...
Emi?
Is that Hiromi?
Shoko! I'm glad that you're okay!
Hiromi, I'm sorry to have worried you.
But what happened, Hiromi?
Tomoko and Oishi...
Are they...
Yes, they both are dead...
They were killed like Mr. Shinohara...
No...
Tomoko, why did you leave me?
Who could be doing this?
To be continued...