You are so stubborn...
You still don't want
to listen to me, huh?
I'll never listen to you...
I guess you need more punishment...
I'll punish you as much
as you want, with this.
Put it in your mouth.
Now please me.
I'd never put that
filthy thing in my mouth!
I told you to put it in your mouth!
Listen to what I say! Do
everything I tell you to do!
If you disobey me, I'll
just force you to obey me.
That's good...
Suck it harder.
I feel good!
I'm coming!
Swallow all my come.
How dare you bite me?
What's that look?
Akari, you are my sex slave!
You can't run away from me anymore!
Be loyal to me! Be a loyal sex slave!
No!
I would rather die
than become your slave!
Okay then, I'll display
you like a doll...
...like a cold, dead doll!
Now you're mine.
You'll be by my side forever.
Please, someone help me.
Release me from this man...
Someone...
Chapter Three: Wakaba
Who would do such a horrible thing?
Ryuichi!
Shinohara had the same
burn on his skin...
What's wrong, Ryuichi?
Emi, you must be the
one who killed them...
What are you talking about, Ryuichi?
You have a bandage covering a
burn on your hand, don't you?
Tomoko, Oishi, and Shinohara,
they all had burns on their bodies.
It looks like the burns
are from a stun gun...
And the burn on your hand is also...
Yes, that's true...
I'm impressed, Ryuichi...
Emi, why did you do it?
All I did was eliminate the people
who got in the way of my master.
You bitch! You killed Tomoko!
Master Yoshimasa...
Yoshimasa?
He is my master, Yoshimasa Okouchi...
Okouchi? You mean the
owner of this island?
The nuisance must go.
Ryuichi!
Go now!
B-But...
Just go!
Okay!
Let's go!
Ryuichi!
Takashi!
Don't worry about us, just go!
Ryuichi!
Wakaba, we gotta go!
Shoko!
You'd better stop resisting.
Wakaba! Run!
Hurry! Please Wakaba...
You...
Since we did get new
slaves as planned...
...I'll forgive you for letting
them find this place, Emi.
Thank you, Master Yoshimasa...
No!
Shoko, please don't move around so
much.
I'm sorry Hiromi, but I can't help it...
Shoko...
Hiromi! Hiromi!
Who told you that you could come?
You must follow Mr. Yoshimasa's order.
Now, who's going to make this happy?
No!
We'd never do that!
You must not disobey Master
Yoshimasa!
Do you want more punishment?
You finally realized your position.
Here's a reward.
Who told you to stop?
The reason I planned this mystery
tour was to find new slaves.
And you two were chosen.
You should be happy.
The one who ran away will
have to join you later.
Lick up Master's come.
Don't come, Wakaba!
Run away!
Wakaba! Run!
Emi, what are you doing?
Come help me.
Yes, Master Yoshimasa...
Shoko!
I don't think you have time to
worry about your friend now...
You will be next, so just wait there.
You have what it takes to be my slave...
I'll take good care of
you if you obey me...
You must be jealous, Akari.
You could've been the one to serve me!
Enough!
Master Yoshimasa!
Wakaba! Takashi! Let's go!
Yes!
Master Yoshimasa! Are you all right?
You useless piece of...
Master Yoshimasa!
Screw it.
I'll kill them all!
Master Yoshimasa? Are you all right?
Master Yoshimasa! Why?
I'll kill anyone who is useless.
I'll kill anyone who disobeys me!
What should we do next, Ryuichi?
Let's get off this island
as soon as possible!
But Ryuichi, we can't even call
for help. What are we going to do?
There must be a way. Just think...
What's wrong, Wakaba?
I have to take Ron with me!
Forget about that aloe for now!
I won't go without Ron!
Wakaba! Stop being selfish!
I'm going to get really mad!
No! Ron has to go with me!
Wakaba!
Takashi, please take
care of Hiromi and Shoko!
Of course!
I'm sorry Ron, this is the
only piece I can take with me...
Let's go Wakaba...
The island that doesn't have trees...
Wakaba?
I wish I could see this
island filled with trees!
This island filled with trees...
Where are Takashi and the others?
We should have
picked a place to meet up...
We couldn't find the last chapter
to make our wish come true...
It's not the time to talk about it!
I finally found you...
You will pay for disobeying
me with your lives.
Brother...
Wait, please let Wakaba go!
Shut up! It's a waste
to beg for your life!
I'll kill you all!
Ryuichi!
Wakaba!
Ryuichi, are you alright?
You're crazy. Why you did that?
I'm okay if you are safe...
Don't speak now, Wakaba!
I remember you held me in
your arms like this before...
That's right.
I held Wakaba in my arms
like this a long time ago...
I'll protect you...
Don't speak!
I'll protect you.
Wakaba!
Wake up! Wakaba!
I'll send both of you to Heaven!
What?
You must be the one from 8 years ago...
I killed you back then.
Why are you here now?
Master Yoshimasa, I swear that
I'll be loyal to you all my life...
So please come with me...
Master Yoshimasa...
8 years ago
It's been a while since I
visited this island, Yutaka.
Oh yeah...
The view from here hasn't changed...
True...
Do you remember, Ron?
Two years have passed since
people left this island...
Although the weeds should
have covered this island...
...the plants couldn't grow
here because of the sea water.
Let's go to the Kotodama shrine
and offer these 1 5 chapters...
Yes!
So, what did you wish for?
It's a secret!
But you'll be surprised...
Well, Ron is a hint!
Finally, Yutaka.
Yes.
Who is it?
Help me, Yutaka!
Akari? Why are you here?
Is that your friend, Akari Mitsuhashi?
Yeah...
Akari! Are you all right?
She is my slave.
Don't bother me...
Who are you?
I'm afraid that I have to kill
both of you since you saw my secret.
Wakaba, are you all
right? Hang in there.
I don't think I can make it...
Thank you for taking care
of me like a real sister...
What are you talking about? I
won't let you go. So stay with me!
I've wanted to tell you
something for a long time...
What is it?
I love you. I've loved
you for a long time...
I love you as a woman...
Wakaba...
If you see me as a woman, kiss me...
This is my last favor...
Die!
All must die if they know my secret!
Run...
Please run, Yutaka...
Yes! I recall everything now!
I'm a reincarnation of Yutaka...
Those memories, dreams...
That's why I'm familiar with
everything about Oka Island.
Ryuichi...
Ryuichi, I wanted to see you..
I've been waiting for you...
I've wanted to see you again.
Wakaba...
Ryuichi!
Ryuichi...
Wakaba...
Ryuichi, that's my...
Ryuichi! Ryuichi!
Wakaba, let's become one.
Yes, Ryuichi.
Wakaba...
This is how Ryuichi feels...
I'm so happy...
I'm happy too, Wakaba...
Ryuichi!
Ryuichi! Ryuichi!
I'm coming!
Wakaba!
Thank you, Ryuichi...
I have nothing to regret now...
Ryuichi, I love you...
We were finally reunited...
...but I couldn't save her life again.
The last chapter...
What is the meaning of this now?
Kotodama shrine...
If my wish could really come true...
My wish would be...
One month later...
I can't believe this is Oka Island...
I guess Wakaba's wish came true...
Yeah...
Ryuichi...
I wanted to see you!
Wakaba? How?
Could it be...
Kotodama shrine made your wish
come true, too. Thank you, Ryuichi.
Wakaba...
Ryuichi...