Mr. Ichiro, I'm here to
pick up the item we ordered.
Just a moment.
I'm just making the final adjustments now.
Did you bring the materials I requested?
Oh, sure. Don't worry. I brought that for you.
But it was a little unreasonable
to ask me to get materials...
...that are not approved in the market yet.
Unreasonable business
is your specialty, isn't it?
Well, that's true.
Let's see... the color of her eyes
is supposed to be purple.
Perfect!
Locked in.
The last thing I have to do is
synchronize her voice and personality.
As always, this is great work!
I'm sure my boss will be very
satisfied with the product.
The payment will be the same as usual.
The next pick up will be 2 months
from today, at the same time.
Okay.
Until then...
Two months from now...
No, no!
This isn't what I want! Damn it.
Almost there...
I can create the finest woman
in the world by using this...
...new material and the data
I used to create other androids.
IMMA YOUJO
Sir.
Thank you for being so patient.
Yes! I'll do my best!
I'm sure you will.
Just like ants gathering for honey.
That why I can't quit this business.
Besides, our technology is on the cutting edge.
All the other play spots like us...
...are providing the jack-in type androids...
...and you can play anyway you want, but...
Can I have your ID number?
OMEKO 191969.
Loading the data.
Loading completed.
Enjoy your play.
Oh! Where have you been?
I was waiting for you all this time.
All the other places are doing
exactly same thing up to this point.
Yes. Up to this point... but...
Now you see the difference between
our Sodom and the other places.
Our androids have so many more
erogenous zones than regular androids.
You can get more sexual pleasure
from them than with real women.
And this is the best part of
our cutting edge technology.
Our androids can send feedback...
...of a woman's unlimited sexual
pleasure to the man's brain.
He can experience the same pleasures
that the android is having.
And the pleasure will feedback
into the android again.
Then it is doubled it and sent back
to stimulate the man's brain again.
This will repeatedly continue until they finish.
Has sex ever been this good?
Ichiro, the man who made this, is a genius.
This is good.
Don't blame me, Mr. Matsuyama.
Damn it!
Ichiro, you bastard!
Hey! What are you waiting for?
Go and get that asshole! Hurry!
I did it. Finally!
What's wrong with you? Be quiet.
Wait!
Hurry up!
Ma... ya...?
Yes. Your name is Maya.
And my name is Ichiro.
Nice to meet you, Maya.
Ichiro...
Ichiro... Ichiro...
Ichir-
Maya, what are you hiding?
What? I don't know what
you are talking about.
Maya!
Let me see.
Too bad, Ichiro.
I knew it!
Hey!
Wait! Hey! Let me see it!
Have you seen him around here?
Hmm... I haven't seen him.
Really?
Should you see him, please give me a call.
There's some money in it for you, if you do...
Maya! Where are you?
Oh, Maya, there you are.
Ichiro...
What's the matter?
You're up here by yourself.
I was looking at the stars.
I see... but, it's time to go inside.
You'll get cold out here.
No, I'm all right.
I feel like... My heart feels hot.
What? Where are you feeling hot?
Maybe something is wrong with your coolant...
No, it's not that.
Then, it might be some kind of an overload.
No, that's not it!
Maya!
The reason my heart is warm is...
...because I like you.
I like you, Ichiro, because
you are always sweet to me.
What do you think of me, Ichiro?
W- Well, I...
I know that nobody seriously cares
about androids. But... I... I...
I like you, too.
I put all my thoughts into creating you.
But, I only input the basic data.
I wanted to give you a birth
and life like a real woman.
Even if that meant you may
not fall in love with me...
Even if you loved another man...
No matter what, I've decided to
protect you all through my life.
Maya, you are not an android.
You are the only woman that I love.
Ichiro...
I love you, Maya.
Please be gentle...
You look beautiful. Very beautiful... Maya...
Please don't look at me so much.
It may hurt at first. Is it all right?
Yes. It's alright... I can take it.
Here we go.
I'm sorry. Did that hurt?
No, I'm all right. Please continue.
It's beautiful.
Do you want to take a look?
That's okay. Let's go.
Hey, what's wrong?
We can't officially marry,
but we can have a wedding
at home, by ourselves.
Now, let's go inside and
try that dress on for you.
Ichiro!
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
Sorry, but we want to be alone tonight.
Don't leak your oil, and
stay outside to guard us.
Let's see... what else do we need.
Ichiro.
You look wonderful, Maya.
Thank you. You look great too, Ichiro.
Huh? Where's Mac?
What? I saw him around just a second ago.
He must have gone out for a walk.
You're so beautiful, Maya.
Thank you, Ichiro.
I will treasure this always.
Then, let's pledge our eternal love with a kiss.
W- Who are you guys?!
I've been looking for you.
Matsuyama? Why?!
You of all people should know why.
Maya! Get out of here!
Ichiro!
Get out of my home!
It's foolish to go against an
expert criminal such as myself.
You're supposed to be a genius.
That's not like you.
Well, now I understand the reason.
It's true that a woman will
make a man do crazy things.
Stop it. Don't do anything to Maya.
Shut up!
Still, I never thought you would
have ran away with a woman.
If I knew that, I would have
found you much earlier.
You have very nice taste in women.
Cordless... and using that new material.
This must be your new product line, isn't it?
No! Maya is human. She's not android!
Well then, let's test drive
your new product here...
Ms. Android Bride...
I beg you! Don't! I will do anything for you.
Please don't touch Maya! Please!
Ichiro!
Maya!
Is this the feel of the new material?
Very smooth.
Ichiro, help me!
Stop it! All of you!
This is great!
It's getting wet even though it
isn't connected to the AC cord.
This really turns me on.
Your skin is very smooth.
But how does it taste?
Very warm and tight.
My fingers can go deep inside.
I will test how it works here.
Here! Open your mouth.
Yes, that's good.
It's time to taste it.
Here, here, here.
Stop it! Please!
Stop...
Oh! It's squeezing me!
No other android can do these kinds of things!
I can't wait any longer! I'm going to cum!
Me too... I'm gonna cum any minute now!
Wonderful... Wonderful!
This is a masterpiece. Totally
different from the other androids.
This can be sold for a very high price!
Maya...
Do you know what this is?
That's...!
Yes, this is the special vibrator
you made to erase all the data...
...without having to cut open the android's body.
Please, don't do it! Please.
Don't worry, Ichiro... I... won't forget.
How can I so easily forget the days
I spent with you for the past year?
Isn't that right, Ichiro?
Maya...
But, if I do lose my memory, please destroy me...
...because then, I'm not Maya anymore...
Please, Ichiro.
The test drive is over.
Let's do the final maintenance
before we give this to our client.
Stop it!
Maya!
It's been very successful.
It took only a week for that android to become...
...the most popular girl in this place.
Yes.
We made all the other androids cordless
as well, but still, Maya is different.
Matsuyama, when did you start
to call androids by their name?
W- Well...
It's alright... By the way, what
happened to that man, Ichiro?
Maya...
I took him back, but...
He isn't useful to us anymore.
Maya...
No? What a waste.
W- What? What is this?
No!
Don't look at me! Please!
Maya... as I promised you...
I will destroy you now...
Damn it!
Isozaki, that dirty old man...
Using his power for his own pleasure.
Does he want to buy that android?
It can't be... He wants Maya?
That's right. He likes Maya.
Maya is making ten times more
profit than the other androids.
Why would you sell her?
I know that.
But it's not a smart idea...
...to make the Isozaki conglomerate
unhappy in this town.
Yes, but...
Shut up! I've already decided.
Bring Maya here now!
Yes sir.
That android, Maya is a dangerous girl.
We aren't the ones who made her like this.
Cordless, new material...
We remodeled all the other androids like her,
but not one became like Maya.
All the men who play with Maya
start getting crazy for her.
They can't stop playing with her.
It's because we couldn't completely
erase Maya's memory of Ichiro.
Maya does anything with any customer,
but her mind is always with another man.
It must be a great pleasure raping
a woman who belongs to another man.
Men became crazy, one after another...
...when they see her eyes.
Maya.
Ichi...
Maya?!
What's the matter with you?
Are you all right?
I... I can't remember... What is this...?
Maya.
Yes. Your name is Maya.
Boss. I brought Maya.
A driver from the Isozaki
Conglomerate will be here soon...
Before that, Maya, sit down on the desk.
Yes...
Pull up your skirt, and open your legs wide.
Good...
This made us a lot of money, but we
have to say goodbye, as of today.
Well, you don't have to worry about anything.
Chairman Isozaki will take
very good care of you.
Now, before you leave here,
let's make you forget about Sodom.
No!
I'm the new owner.
I won't give Maya to anybody.
Who is it!?
You two!
I don't care who will become the owner.
I only care to take that android.
I don't think you are a fool.
Think well about which is a smarter idea...
Whether you become an enemy or a
friend of the Isozaki Conglomerate.
I get it...
I'm sure this will make
Chairman Isozaki very happy.
Well then, goodbye new owner.
Maya.
Maya...
Maya!
Huh? Ichi...
What's wrong?
Does the android have a headache?
I see...
I'll help to make you feel better.
Here, lay down and relax.
You are so beautiful.
I've wanted you, ever since I saw you playing.
This is our last chance.
Let's enjoy ourselves until we
arrive at the Chairman's place.
Here, lick it.
This is so good! You are doing great.
Now rub my pussy!
Hurry...
Thank you for waiting, Chairman Isozaki.
I've brought Maya.
Go on.
Oh! I have been waiting for you Maya.
Thank you, Ms. Reika.
My pleasure.
Maya, look at the night view from here.
Isn't it gorgeous?
Oh!
It's beautiful...
Now, Maya, it's time for you to show me...
Yes.
Here you are. Please look well.
This is great!
Maya, I destroyed all the other
androids after I met you,
because I couldn't be
satisfied by any of them.
I'm happy only because you are with me.
No!
Oh?!
It's no good. I can't stand it anymore.
This is an interesting play.
The is the best. An android and a real human.
I'm glad I lived a long life.
Maya...
Maya... Where are you?
Ohhh... This is the best.
C- Chairman... I can't breathe!
No!
I'm kind of tired.
Hey...
Well... What were you doing here?
Me?
Yes... What is your name?
Ma.. ya... Maya... Maya!
Ten years later...
The city became a much nicer place
after the new Mayor was elected.
Maybe it's only me who didn't
change and is stuck in the past.
Look at this.
See... Isn't she cute?
Maya... where are you now?
Well, I guess somebody's here for you.
Were you being good?
Where do you want to go, Madam Mayor?
Well... where should we go, Ichiro?
Since it's my day off, let's go to the lake.