What is this? This is unbelievable!
This is terrible...
This is terrible!
No!
This village is cursed!
It's poisoned by a devil!
The witch must be hiding
somewhere in this village.
Hawks! Check these ladies' bodies carefully.
You must find the witches!
T- There must be some mistake. I'm not...
I'm not a witch!
Ohh, you say you're not a witch?
Hey!
Yes sir.
Don't you realize you have a
witch's poison all over your body?
So you should understand that I am
purifying your body with my sperm.
There!
Suck it, otherwise the holy
water won't come out of me.
I'm coming. I'll purify you now...
Who are you?!
What a terrible and sad destiny
she carries on her shoulders!
I'm telling you this for your own good.
Just forget about that baby.
What do you mean by that?
If you get involved in her terrible destiny,
all will fall to ruin.
Count Calvin, I understand how you feel, but...
No, I will raise this baby.
Count Calvin?!
Count Nicklal, please let me keep this baby.
I found her outside of my mansion
the day my pregnant wife died.
I can't help but think that this baby
is supposed to be my wife's baby.
No matter how terrible her destiny is,
I will keep this baby as
a child of the Calvin family.
Count Pickingel! What is all this commotion?!
What do you mean by commotion?
We were sent to this town
to subdue the witches...
...that have been poisoning the villagers.
I have the King's direct authority
to burn down the village...
...as a warning to others.
Y- You bastard!
What's wrong Count Pickingel?
You have a problem?
I, Mayatola Calvin, the commanding
officer of the First Imperial guard...
...am not going anywhere!
IMMA YOUJO
It's Commander Mayatola!
He's so handsome!
Ohh... Commander Mayatola!
The Witch Purification Force has returned!
I heard they burned everything down.
Die!
Enter.
Regimental commander of the First
Imperial Guard, Mayatola Calvin,
returning from the inspection of the
witch purification of Donuve village.
Thank you for your help.
I'm the one who was supposed to go there,
but I'm too old for field work.
Don't say that.
You are still young, General.
Don't flatter me.
I crossed swords with your father,
and spent nights drinking
with him a long time ago.
How is your father?
He's not doing well.
He grows weaker every day.
I see.
Well, if it isn't Count Mayatola...
Did you already make
your report to the General?
You're really devoted to your work.
Count Pickingel!
It pained me to give that report!
He burned down the village before
even conducting an official trial.
He stabbed and killed men
who tried to run away.
And in front of their corpses,
he forced women to...
How long should Count Pickingel's
witch-hunt continue?
I just can't let it continue any more!
You don't have to say another word.
I've heard so many things about him.
But he's had tremendous results
with the witch-hunts so far...
...and he is the King's favorite.
And the King sent Isabel to
supervise the witch-hunt.
This also helps Count Pickingel.
As long as Isabel is with him,
I can't interfere so easily,
because her word is considered
to be the King's word.
I know that Count Pickingel's
arrogance has grown,
so I started worrying about you.
Me? What about me?
Don't you realize?
After I die, he will never be able
to get the General's position...
...unless you die or lose your position.
I'm not worried about myself
because I'm old anyway.
But I don't want you to
be in a dangerous situation.
You have a secret that may put
you in a difficult situation.
Look, be careful of Count Pickingel!
Never let him find out your secret!
Are you planning to have a fair
trial for the girls you captured,
Count Pickingel?
Of course.
The King has put me in charge of
the witch-hunt, Count Mayatola.
The way you were in Donuve village...
...was far from being fair.
I was just following the King's orders.
What's wrong, Count Pickingel?
Aren't you satisfied after
catching so many witches?
I'm... not a witch...
It doesn't matter whether
or not you're a witch...
Your destiny was already set
once you came to this castle.
You will never get out of here alive.
But if you want to live longer,
you'll have to work hard.
Hey, what are you doing?
Brand the witch's emblem on
their skin before they escape.
Even if they escape,
they will be caught and
executed as a witch, anyway.
Did you find out anything?
I'm sure we will be hearing good news soon.
I'm looking forward to that.
Here!
Oh, is that you, Maya?
When did you come back?
I'm sorry. Did I wake you, Father?
I can't always be asleep...
...since you're working hard
all through the night.
Father!
Are you all right? Father.
I hated the disease that took your
mother, with my heart and soul.
But I hated it too much, and now
the disease has come back to haunt me.
No it hasn't, Father...
Who's there?!
I- I'm sorry! I was here to
tell you the bath is ready.
But you were sleeping very comfortably.
I thought you shouldn't
catch a cold, and... and...
Ahh! I don't know what I was trying to say!
I'm sorry...
You don't have to apologize, Anne.
I appreciate you taking care
of my father while I'm not at home.
Please don't say that... I just...
I appreciate you very much, Anne.
Please keep up the good work.
Yes!
Be quiet.
Father will wake up.
All right?
Well, then let's go.
It's a nice smell.
I will leave your clean clothes here.
Um, shall I scrub your back?
Huh? Did you say something, Anne?
N- No...
I'm all right here by myself.
Why don't you go to bed now.
Yes. Then...
The more you try to fight against destiny,
the more the vortex of
the destiny will speed up.
It will swallow up everything
and crumble it into dust.
But there is a way to get away from it.
What? Is that true?
A new path may open up if you
bind another string on her destiny.
But it's very cruel for her.
You shouldn't let men get close to her.
She should abandon being a woman,
and live as a man.
You shouldn't let anybody
know she is a woman...
...and bind her destiny with new string.
If the string is cut, the
original destiny will return...
...and it'll become a great vortex,
swallowing everything.
Do you understand? You cannot
let her destiny awaken.
Count Mayatola...
Oh, Count Mayatola! I'm... I'm...
Maya boy, come on. Let's fight.
It didn't feel bad to live as a man, back then.
I don't remember when we met.
We naturally became friends.
We had fun together...
Got angry together...
Felt sad together...
We drank all night and talked together.
It was the happiest time of my life.
Until that day...
I wish that I were a real man.
I cursed my fate that I had
to hide being a woman.
Ah... wind?
After using impartial justice,
these people, who we captured at
the witch-hunt in Donuve village...
...have been proven to be witches.
If we let them live, it will
certainly bring disaster to our city.
Therefore, by the king's authority,
we sentence them...
...to burn at the stake.
Count Pickingel!
Start the fire!
Yes sir!
This is cruel. This is too merciless!
Count Pickingel, you must
explain this all to me.
I don't know what you are talking about.
Don't play dumb!
Explain the punishment you just did.
If you really did a fair trial...
...how come those women had bruises
and cuts on their bodies?
I guess you don't know anything.
The King ordered us to punish the
witches in the cruelest way possible.
Since you want me to be against the
King's word, that means you are...
...a traitor!
Now you dare raise your sword
to me, using the King's name!
You are the lowest clod that I know.
You must have forced these
girls to confess under torture...
...and burned them to erase the evidence!
You bastard!
I don't have any evidence right now,
but I will find the proof and expose you.
Do you understand?
What is wrong with you?
I can't take it if you're too rough!
Oh no! Not there!
Damn you, Mayatola!
No!
Your wound has opened up again.
The wound Count Mayatola gave you.
I wasn't fighting him seriously.
But today is the last day for Mayatola.
What?
Clory has found out an
unbelievable secret about him.
And now, he must be finishing up the job.
The wind?
Go!
Yes sir.
What is going on?!
What do you think you are doing?
Do you know who I am?
We know who you are Count Mayatola.
We came here because we received an order.
Whose order?
S- Sir, we have a problem!
C... Count Calvin is... Count Calvin is...
Count Mayatola, we are
placing you are under arrest...
...for the murder of Count Calvin.
Oh no, it can't be.
F- Father...
Count Mayatola!
Hey! Stop right there!
What are you doing?
Get away from him!
Don't worry Anne. I'll be back soon.
Please take care of the mansion until then.
C- Count Mayatola.
By the way Anne, my father...
Count Mayatola!
Hey, isn't that Count Calvin's son, Mayatola?
It can't be.
Why is Count Mayatola tied up?
Count Mayatola... I have been waiting for you.
Pickingel, why are you here?!
I'm here to arrest you.
Listen everybody!
Count Mayatola is a murderer,
who killed his own father.
Not only that, he is a witch
who tries to manipulate people!
A witch?
Count Mayatola is a witch?
I'm a man! I'm not a witch!
You can't hide it anymore.
I know the truth. You are really a woman.
You hid your real identity,
because you were scared...
...that people would find out
that you are a witch.
What kind of proof do
you have to say such lies!
Are you out of your mind, Count Pickingel?
You can't say that anymore.
And now!
Ah! Stop it!
Here is...
...the evidence!
You are charged with being a witch.
No! Count Mayatola can't be a witch!
No way! This is not true!
Count Calvin was already
dead when I found him.
I discovered that Commander
Mayatola's blade...
...was used as the murder weapon.
While I was taking him into custody,
Count Pickingel came and exposed
Mayatola as a woman and a witch...
...then he took her away.
I see. You are dismissed.
Yes sir.
Maya.
You look great, Count Mayatola.
No, I mean Lady Maya.
Now you can say nothing against me
because you're exposed as a witch!
Pickingel, you set me up.
You must be the one who killed my father too!
Just wait! I will escape here,
and prove my innocence.
Then, I will kill you!
You really have guts.
It's such a waste that you are a woman.
I abandoned being a woman long ago!
I am a man.
You abandoned being a woman?
That's right.
Go ahead!
I will tolerate any kind of torture,
and then escape from here.
That sounds fun.
Do it!
Take this!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Shut up!
You should accept your unlucky fate.
It is all because of that hermaphrodite, Maya.
Clory, don't go too wild.
Be careful not to destroy your toy
by too much wild play, like last time.
I'll come back later.
N- No! Don't do that!
No!
How is the taste of the whip?
You bastard!
What's so funny?
What is the matter, Count Pickingel?
You are acting strange.
If you get too excited,
your wound will open up again.
May I?
Even if the mind is a man,
the body is still a woman.
How is this? Do you feel good?
Relax and listen to your body.
Don't you feel good?
Do you feel your body?
Can't you feel your body melting away slowly?
Don't be in a rush. Slowly... slowly.
S- Stop it!
Stop...
Stop!
Don't touch me... you bitch!
Isabel.
Don't worry, I won't kill her.
How can I let her die so easily?
Maya, I've heard you are a
very skillful swordswoman...
Can you show me how skillful
you are, by using this sword?
Please...
Here... You can stab her with
your swords as much as you want.
Help me, Maya.
Please help me quickly.
I won't give in... I'm not a woman.
This is nothing...
I'm... I'm...
I'm...
Even if you try to think you are
a man, your body is woman.
I will slowly train you well,
starting tomorrow.
You are telling me to release Mayatola?
I can't believe these orders
are from General Nicklal.
Mayatola has kept secret
that she was a woman.
If she is not a witch,
why did she have to hide it?
W- Well, Count Calvin may
have had some odd ideas.
I heard Mayatola is the one
who killed Count Calvin.
Isn't that so, Count Pickingel?
That's right.
She must have used her magic powers
to manipulate Count Calvin,
and had him fooled ever since.
Well, I hope there was no one
else who has been manipulated.
I understand. I must be going.
Look. She seemed to have a
tough spirit in the beginning,
but I guess she gave up after having
lots of men, everyday, without a rest.
Well, she kept it up long enough.
I guess so.
Meal time.
Here you are. Don't spill it.
Oh, the sky looks threatening.
It looks like a storm is coming.
What good timing.
I was just about to bring you here.
No more silly talk.
Come. I'm escaping and
taking you as a hostage.
Would you like us to come with you?
I'm so disappointed.
Especially since I prepared this girl for you.
Anne?!
Why are you are here?
Put the sword down now...
...otherwise I don't know what
will happen to the girl.
Are you going to leave her behind,
so you can kill me and escape?
Stop it! Keep your hands off of her!
Can you really abandon her
and escape all by yourself?
Maya, you don't have to do
this if you don't want to.
Once you wear this brand,
you will never be able to escape.
Even if you did, people would find you
and execute you as a witch.
I know that! But in exchange,
you won't do anything to Anne.
Very well.
Hold her!
Look well. Your master is going to
suffer pain and writhe in agony.
Are you ready for this?
Just hurry up and do it.
Now you are neither man nor woman.
You are a witch.
I will purify the witch with my holy water.
Here, suck it well.
You are becoming a good girl.
Anne, stdp! Stdp it.
Well well... Your body's gotten soft,
so soon after you got the witch's emblem.
W- Why?
My body is...
Maya, here we go.
This is just the beginning, Maya.
Let's take our time and enjoy.
I feel hot. I feel like my body is
crushing me... from inside.
What is this?
Something is coming.
I'm scared... No, don't!
I think it's over there.
Let's enjoy her again.
That's enough.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
You are going to see Maya, aren't you?
What do you like about that hermaphrodite?
Count Pickingel!
It's been a long time.
Here is a little gift for you.
I haven't seen you since that day.
How long ago was it?
It's been over ten years.
I want to talk about the baby.
This wound...
I think of you every time this wound aches.
Oh, Maya...
I'm... I'm...
Maya.
Please don't stop, Maya!
I... Maya!
The reason your wound aches is because...
...you don't love Maya as a woman.
Here is the place you love very much.
You love Maya as a man.
I knew it.
You have been watching me.
Now, don't you really want to put it in here?
What's wrong with Count Pickingel,
and this castle?!
What's wrong with everything?!
Mayaaaaa...
W- What's going on?
What is this?!
Maya's a witch?!
That's right. She is a witch
who carries on a sad destiny.
Nooooo!
Let me go! Stop it!
Stop it!
Help!
Men will be drawn to her and
start desiring her greatly.
She can have anything and
anyone with her magical power.
Men will hurt and kill each other
until everyone is destroyed.
Nobody can stop it. Even if they
know something is wrong.
Her awakening as a woman was
also her awakening as a witch.
I saw the strong magical power from that baby.
Is there nothing that can be done?
The seal holding her fate has been broken.
The only way to stop it is to kill her.
If you leave it be, her witchcraft
will consume and destroy everything.
Clory, kill that hermaphrodite!
She tricked these men and tried to kill me!
Kill her with the same hands
that killed her father!
After Maya dies, Pickingel
will begin the witch-hunt again.
And he will need my help again.
I ask again...
Is that really the only way to save her?
If you truly care for her...
I understand.
I'm the one who protects Maya.
Maya is mine. No one can take her!
This is cruel.
Good girl, Anne.
Maya...
This sword belongs to Count Pickingel.
It can't be...
I don't need anything,
as long as you'll be with me.
Is this the magical power Maya possesses?
How dare you betray me
for this hermaphrodite!
Maya!
Please return to the Maya I know
before you become a witch completely.
You are overwhelmed by magical power.
I don't want this to happen.
If I let you become a witch, I would have to...
I would have to!
I would...
...have to kill you!
Forgive me, Maya!
Kill her!
Burn her!
Kill the witch!
Nicklal, the execution is over.
Yes madam. Then I will go back now.
Good work, Nicklal.
You must abolish these worthless
witch-hunts after this execution.
Do you understand?
There are so many other fun
things to do in this world.