And now, the top news of the day.
You're so good!
...sunny.
...week's...
We have southerly winds at 3 meters per second.
We ladies will need to watch our steps for a while.
We're not sure how much longer
these winds will continue.
Be sure to secure all your outside belongings.
No way!
Teachers were fired for engaging
in lewd acts with their students.
This year alone, they have victimized 175 students.
This is 1.5 times greater than last year!
Compared to ten years ago, the
rate has increased eight times!
Among the victims, 98 of them were
enslaved by their own teachers.
Teachers who seemed normal baring their evil fangs
on their students appear in case after case.
õðårts believe that the targeting if female
students has become a national epidemic.
3 meters per second...
Experts believe that the targeting of female
students has become a national epidemic.
Recently, many of the victims are recent transfer
students who just moved to the area.
Sometimes it starts with a teacher
admitting that it's difficult for him
to conduct class because a large
breasted girl sitting right in front of him.
Manami, if you bring that magazine to
class, the teacher will get mad at you.
Aw, don't worry about it.
Wh-Where do you think you're
looking, you horny old teacher!
When you realized I was a girl, you
lowered your eyes, didn't you!?
I... I would never do that...
Lookie.
Told ya, you're drooling and it's
super gross, you horny teacher.
So you're the type who hits first
and asks questions later.
You're planning on violating me now?
No, I was just...
I'm gonna scream...
I'm gonna scream, you know.
W-W-Wait a minute!
L-Let's go find some place quiet to talk...
Okamura-sensei?
I realize it must be thrilling to be surrounded
by such pretty young female students,
but you are a highly respected teacher
of a highly respected private school.
You must consider keeping up outward appearances.
But I wasn't really..
Fujisaki-senpai! Sense wanted
to do lewd things to me!
And what's more, he said he was gonna rape me!
Oh my.
Hey!
And then he tried to lure me to some
place with no one around!
If this is true, then we have a problem here.
You've just been recently scolded by the head
teacher and the school president, right?
My mother told me about it. Did you know?
My mother is in charge of the Decency Committee.
I will report today's occurrence to
her for certain, Okamura-sensei.
Say, aren't your little sister and him always fighting?
Maybe she's in love with him.
Yeah, right! That pathetic guy?
He's the frickin' science teacher.
Part 1  Special Lesson From a Nasty teacher
He ranked number two in the girls list of
Teachers I don't want to have for class.
I'd like to meet the guy who said that teaching is a
highly respected profession that helps children.
Or maybe...
I'm just hopeless.
You're disgusting. Die!!
It's so bad I resort to using this kind of thing.
People hate me on sight...
But if something like this really made girls hot for
me, no one would have any problems in life.
What are you doing all of a sudden, Sensei!
Sorry.
Sensei!
Do you understand? You mustn't
bring strange things into school.
And if you must bring things,
Then... you must inform...
Inform...
No... Oh dear...
What is this?
Fujisaki?
Dizzy...
Shon't do dat...
But you suddenly...
Fujisaki!
Shensei...
Whash oing on...
"What's goin on?"
Wll I..
What the...
What was that?
This probably cooled you off a little, I hope.
Fujisaki.
Oh no!
You look so sweet and innocent,
but you're really rough.
I wonder if all model students like yourself
spend their nights practicing like that.
Sensei... I rike it a lot...
You get good at things you like, you say?
Smelly!
The shwirling...
inside... won't shtop...
Body fluids are bitter to the taste.
The stink of a dick is a man's true mark.
But it helps cure a woman of her wetness.
Helps cure...
When it's medicine time...
you need to open your mouth wide,
and gulp it all down!
Understand, Fujisaki?
My body...
Dizzy... hot...
It is important to allow our students to
discover things on their own sometimes.
Huh?
Okamura-sensei?
Adachi?
Um, what are you doing in there by yourself?
Nothing.
Hey!
Don't tell me you're lusting over
Kyoko in her PE shorts!?
What's "lusting" mean?
Kyoko, isn't this what I'm always telling you?
If you tuck your shirt in...
You'll fall victim a nasty wolf! You'll become his prey!
Hey, I'm a teacher, you know.
Even so, Kyoko is still half-naked right now.
Especially to guys like this teacher, seeing girls
our age in our PE uniforms really gets them off.
Eh? But bloomers ride up my butt when
I exercise and they're just annoying.
Well that's just because your butt is too big, Kyoko.
Jeez, Manami, you're gross.
One hundred suns and moons come and go.
The passing years are all nomads.
Sensei...
Do you suppose someone else on this planet is
looking up at the sky the way I am right now?
If so, then that's very beautiful.
Let me give you some useful information.
Kyoko is nice to everyone.
So don't jump to the wrong conclusions just
because she was nice to you that one time.
Let's be plain. Ever since Kyoko and I were in
the same Baby Dear group  in kindergarten,
the Kujira group in first grade,
class 1-3, class 3-4, class 6-1...
Um... What class were we in together after that?
Anyway!
The one who fell in love with Kyoko first was me.
Well, let's go, Kyoko.
I suppose it's time to graduate.
Hurry... put it in right away!
This isn't exactly rape, is it...
I don't want it to be "the end" just when
we're getting to the good part.
I...
I love you, Shensei. I ahways fight
if you an make fun of you,
but... I love you...
So you won't make me stop halfway, right?
I won't. You can keep going to the end.
Shoot your cum all over my body.
Please! Shove your penis deep inshide of me!
Well when you put it that way,
I guess I've got no choice.
Oww!
Your attitude might be big,
but your hole is sure small.
So you're a virgin, eh?
Well it's about time to graduate.
I've been wanting to graduate myself.
Well, now you can play innocent all you want but
it won't change how you let me violate you now.
Ish too tight... it hurts...
You sure are a model student. You're so tight!
0w! Thash enough... Please...
Don' push too hard... I'll fall apart... Oww!
For a tennis player, your pelvis sure is weak!
What's wrong? You look really pitiful.
You want to stop already?
No...
That was your first time, after all.
So this is your limit?
Don't stop... Please don' stop!
It felt good. Inshide me deep...
Touching my uterus..
It felt really good...
You mean in your small hole?
Deeper! Stick it in deeper!
Oh no..
I'm cumming" is what you're
supposed to say in this case.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming... Ow...
Cumming!
It got bigger.
Your penis dug me a larger hole...
I'll fill your little hole completely full
No, no!
I'm your shtudent... What would everyone else shay?
That's right. You were gonna
tell Mommy, weren't you.
I-It's coming out!
Your dick... is throbbing inside of me...
My insides are melting together.. with your dick!
I fucked a student.. and she came on to me!
Even if it was just because of this stuff...
There's no turning bach for me now.
Normal, I guess? Two to three times a week, maybe.
Then I guess you like it, Kaho-chan.
What about you, Manami-nee?
Me?
I do it every day.
Not telling.
Meanie!
Leave it alone. Kaho.
You know I hate it when people talk
about things like that around me.
Hmm, well, I know something.
I know you've done it before.
Really? Is that true, Kyoko?
Did you cum all by yourself before?
I wouldn't know! I don't...
Mastur...
If you keep up like that, you'll never
get a boyfriend, Onee-chan.
You too, Kaho-chan. Unless you get rid of your
granny panties, no guy will ever want you.
But I like those kind of panties.
Feels nice when I'm playing tennis.
Y-You come into our clubhouse like that?
I-I don't believe it... You horny teacher!
Oh dear, oh dear. Sounds like you hate me.
Get out of here now!! You're grossing me out.
I wonder if it'll work on someone like her?
If you get any closer, I'll kick you!
I'll make it so you won't last a night alone without me.
I inhaled some of it!
Shit. What the hell was that?
R-Really?
Is that guy insane!?
I knew he was a gross teacher... but not that gross...
You really don't know how to respect
and obey your elders, little girl.
You... You horny old teacher!
If you're so scared you'll hide in the girl's bathroom...
Then you probably won't let me
chase you looking like this.
Pervert!
Huh?
My body ish hot...
My chest... ish tight...
Wha' the...
Oh no..
That's a nice reaction coming from someone
who only does it three times a week.
You were eavesdropping...
No! Geh ahway from me!
You shmell bad...
That makes two of us.
You smell!
Let's be smelly together.
No! Shtop it!
Looks like I found it. Your G-spot.
Oh no...
There!
No... Shtop it...
Fuck you... asshole...
You're such a bad girl. Where did
you learn all those dirty words?
I'm cumming...
NO!
No... not enough...
So I suppose you want to go all the way?
All the way?
Sex, of course.
My penis in your vagina, thrusting in and out.
You get it, right?
My vagina... thrusting in an' out?
But you know, it probably wont work.
Since you hate me and all.
No... I don' hate you...
Come on.
You called me a "horny old teacher".
I don' mind...
We can have sex.
But your precious first time...
should you decide on it in such haste?
Yes! I don't mind! If I don't, then I'll...
Oh no...
It came out again!
Please, do me! Sensei!
Please have sex with me!
I just realized something. This isn't the best place.
One, two! One, two! One, two!
The scenery is great out here.
Should be perfect for your first time.
Hurry. Your dick...
Hurry and thrusht it into my vagina.
My vagina... is hungry...
Fill it... Fill it full of your dick...
Good idea. I'll give you a sweat far more pleasing
than you get from playing tennis.
I'll give it to you.
Ow!
You sure are tight, Kaho.
Oh dear.
Since you're so tight-assed in your personality,
your vagina is so tight I can barely find it.
Oh phlease...don' hurt me...
But you have to go behind the wheel
yourself or you'll never learn.
That's not good enough. Scream for me!
Ow... amashing...
Amashing...
Oh no... Shensei, shtop...
Shensei... I'll die...
One. two. one, two, one, two...
It hurts... it hurts...
I'm sorry about it. So call me
"horny old teacher" again!
Shensei... I'm shorry...
I'm shorry I ever... said those bad
shings to you... so phlease...
Stop it..
NO...
You'll never be able to badmouth me again.
I'll fill your uterus full of me!
So much...
Amashing... that'sh sho...
Amashing...