Time to go, Kyoko!
Wear this costume and protect peace on Earth!
Okay.
Isn't it a bit short?
That's the best part about it!
I mean, it's the trend!
Female super-heroes these days tend to look
like they came straight out"of a dating sim.
Oh. I didn't know...
The penis in my heart is
always throbbing with desire.
But if she went to an event dressed like that...
Thå lîîks cast upon her like condensed milk will be
so sticky that she might get pregnant from them!
Um...
Are you listening to me, Manami?
That sweet voice of yours messes up my mind!
Manami?
I'm fine!
I won't let anyone lay a finger on you!
Lay a finger on me? Manami...
I don't want you to talk about that!
I mean... I am sorry that I made this
decision without telling you.
But I thought a lot about it. About a boyfriend...
What do you mean "boyfriend"?
Whether you like him or not, I already said yes.
Tomari-kun... asked me to be his girlfriend.
Girlfriend!?
That's what they all said. Well, Tomari-kun,
after class, I'll be waiting for you by the front gate.
Part 2 special Training Lesson
Ah...
Kyoko...
Up until now, I felt that you were so close to me.
Even now, you're still so close...
If I close my eyes, I can hear
her breathing, her heartbeat,
even the private sounds I'm not supposed to hear.
Manami!
Jeez, stop scaring me like that.
It feels like she's so far away now.
Right now, all I seem to have of her is leftovers.
Her smell is still warm.
Just a few seconds ago, Kyoko had
her naked vagina over here.
Are you sick in the head?
Following me in here...
Again?
You horny...
Gas?
No!
Wait a minute, this is a girl's bathroom!
H-Horny old teacher!
I know when I'm hated.
In that case...
Don't go!
What is it?
Sensei... your...
...Dick.
I'm busy, so I'm leaving.
I-I want it!
I want your dick, Sensei!
Eew! What're you saying Kaho-chan?
We don't have to. You hate me, after all.
That's not true! I love you!
It's okay. You don't need to lie.
I'm not lying! I want it!
I'm-not lying! I want it!
I want your beautiful, big dick all inside of me!
It's really smelly right now.
I love it smelly! I want my insides full of your cum!
Come on. Just take it out...
You're good at playing tennis...
But I think you're even better at playing penis.
It's cause your. penis is so big... and yummy...
Well, I suppose you can become an ace of my penis.
Yummy... yummy dick...
Oh dear. Stop talking dirty.
I'm sorry!
I'm just your dick-slave. Sorry for being so rude.
I'm sorry that I find your cum so delicious
even though there isn't a hair on my pussy.
That mist from earlier... I wonder if it came from this?
Did it make Kaho-chan go crazy like that?
I want your dick inside of me, Sensei!
I don't care if it's smelly!
Just take it out!
Manami!
Manami.
What is it, Kyoko?
Tomari-kun is walking me home today.
Okay...
Kyoko!
Listen.
What?
What're you doing all of a sudden?
Sorry, sorry.
Jeez, you scared me!
It's for good luck! So you can speak better.
It's really popular right now.
A cologne that helps love bloom.
Aw, cut it out, Manami.
I mean, we barely started dating...
Jeez. That's enough...
K-Kyoko?
Ma... Manami...
Infirmary
The doctor isn't here now.
My body... so hot...
My strength...
Leaving...
I'll stay with you.
You're so pretty, Kyoko.
You think I'll let a boy steal you from me?
Manami... Manami...
You're scared stiff.
But you're still pretty, Kyoko.
Why are your nipples so hard?
Don't touch... it's too intense...
You really are pretty, Kyoko.
Amazing. Your vagina is all wet.
I don't like it.
You don't like it, but you're wet?
You dirty girl.
Your clitoris is also stiff.
Stop it!
My body is going crazy!
It's throbbing... and hot!
You're just in denial. You always have been.
You've been a horny girl all along.
Not there! It's dirty!
There isn't a dirty spot on your body, Kyoko.
I'm sorry... Tomari-kun. I can't
walk home with you anymore.
And I also can't be with you...
Yeah...
I'm sorry... I really am..
I really am sorry.
Manami! Not there!
Don't touch that. It'll come out...
If you feel like you have to
pee, I don't mind if you do.
I won't stop until you do let it out.
You're mean!
It's your punishment for not noticing me before...
The one to be punished is you!
It's not proper to steal things.
Sensei.
Please. I'm begging you.
Please...
I am a teacher. You are a student.
You need to be the one to seduce me.
Please do it!
Please do what?
Please stop the throbbing tidal wave inside my body.
Vagina like being fingered...
But puttin this thing in feels even better!
No!
This thing should fit perfectly to help
calm down your throbbing vagina.
Fit perfectly...
You want it, don't you?
I want it!
You want what?
I want... you, Sensei...
Your dick...
In my vagina... into my vagina.
You aren't really making sense, mumbling like that.
You need to tell me straight or I won't understand.
Please! I'm begging you!
Your... your dick... inside me...
Please put it in!
I can't hold back any longer!
That's not right!
All you said was you wanted it "inside" you.
B-But that's where poop comes out.
Oh? So even pretty girls like you poop?
I'm begging you. Please stop teasing me.
In my vagina...
In my vagina, please put your penis in there!
Okay then.
I feel it.
Your hymen is blocking me...
My hymen...
The hymen I've protected for so long...
It's broken.
Warm, isn't it?
Just a few minutes ago, it was inside
your little sister's vagina.
Inside Kaho?
So both sisters became women by my dick.
Oh no... How cruel!
And now I'll make both sisters into mothers.
Men are...
So hot... thick...
And long...
I had no Idea...
My insides... are throbbing, and
In times like this, you say "I'm gonna cum."
You're so big... I'm not sure
if it hurts... or feels good...
So big!
It's coming... coming...
No!
Manami...
NO!!
Sorry about that.
Guess you missed watching Kyoko lose her virginity.
How dare you. She had just finished her period.
It's her most vulnerable time!
Watch as your beloved Kyoko...
gets knocked up by me.
Does it hurt, Kyoko?
I feel fine. It's so big, it fills me
up and makes me feel safe.
That's because your vagina accepts my penis now.
My vagina likes your penis?
That means my vagina belongs to you now!
No!
Wow!
It's so big...
It's wrestling around inside me!
Is that okay? Is that okay with you, Kyoko?
It feels great! Your penis feels so great!
Your vagina feels like it's going
to swallow up my penis.
I don't want you ever thinking
about another guy again.
Only your penis for me, Sensei!
My head is only filled with thoughts
of your strong and mighty penis!
Other penises?
They mean... nothing to me!
Oh god... oh god...
My head is going blank. I can't think about anything.
Move your own body up and down.
Let me see you be nasty.
Yes, sir!
I want it! I want it deeper inside me!
I want your penis to destroy my insides!
You want more?
Deeper...
Deeper... Deeper...
Put your penis deeper, all the way
into my vagina! Fill my vagina up!
My vagina... loves it! It feels great!
Are you gonna cum?
Is my penis making you want to cum?
I'm cumming! Yes, I'm cumming! With your penis!
Oh no...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Sensei, your milk has filled me up.
I'm so full, so warm...
...and so happy.
I want... I want you too, Sensei.
You want my what?
Your penis.
You mean this?
Yes! Your strong and mighty penis!
Manami, have you ever kissed a boy before?
No, I hate them. I hate boys.
I see...
Go!
Here's your first kiss!
I bet these other lips of yours want a kiss too.
Yes, sir.
What's up, Manami?
You're still a virgin?
Then maybe we should stop.
You don't even like me.
I'm fine with it! Please break
my hymen with your penis!
Please steal my virginity!
Steal, you say?
Like this?
Hard to believe you were so cold to me before.
Now you're warming me up.
Your penis... So hot...
You say you hate boys, but you're
enjoying having a penis in you.
I'm not. I hate boys...
Just admit it. Your vagina feels great, right?
Come on. Scream it out.
My vagina feels great!
Be more specific, so I believe it!
Sensei, your penis thrusting inside
of me makes my vagina feel good!
I love having sex with a pervert like you.
You really are a bad girl.
Yes. I've been a bad girl.
From now on, I'll be honest in
the presence of your penis.
Be honest, you say? You mean
you'll suck up any dick?
That's not it. That's not right.
My vagina belongs only to your perverted penis.
I won't let any other penis go in it!
Then let me spray my perverse cum into your uterus!
Please leave your mark inside of me!
One that'll never disappear!
Actually, I came here to discuss your
daughter's performance in school
Yummy.
How was that? Have I gotten better at fellatio?
You really are a nasty girl, Kyoko.
Where did you learn that?
Jeez. You taught me, of course.
I'm not even interested in any other penis.
I don't mind if you try just to compare.
He taught me...
...that the penis that turned you into
a woman is your guardian for life.
Mommy!
I've been a bad girl.
I called him names like "horny old teacher".
But I'm sorry about it. So I want him to punish me.
I asked him to punish me in front of
you so I'd really learn my lesson.
I've also been a bad girl!
Sensei told me I needed to
hold out until he came first,
but his penis is so thick that he
made me cum just by entering!
We need punishment!
Sensei! I'm begging you!
Thrust your penis in all the way so it hits my uterus!
Bury your seed in me too! I promise I'll get pregnant!
Get your milk deep inside my uterus!
How do you feel about this as their mother?
Taking care of the students
problems is a teacher's duty.
But I suppose letting your daughters sort out
their own issues is another form of teaching.