Hurry, hurry.
Wait up, Yuuka.
Shesh...aren't you the one who said lets eat outside,
Korin?
Yeah, but you don't need to run, Yuuka.
I guess...
Please go ahead and save us a spot.
Alright, I'll go first.
Thank you.
Wow, there's a lot of people. Might not be able to eat
here. Oh?
Lucky.
Excuse me, may I take this so...Oh?
Shi...Keisuke.
What are you doing here!?
I came here first and you ask me what am I doing here?
I don't think you need to bitch to me
about how or where I spend my lunch.
You don't even attend class, so you shouldn't be here.
Besides you...
Oh, Ms. Yuuki?
Ms. Izumi.
What's this fuss about?
Glad you are here. He's ditching class, but he's still in
school. Please say something to him.
Teacher? ......Teacher?
Huh? Oh, sorry.
Keisuke, please come to the music room later.
Teacher, please teach him some discipline.
What's so funny?
Yuuka! What are you doing?
Woops, I forgot.
Anyways, Keisuke. You better attend afternoon classes.
See you later teacher.
I'm so sorry.
Did you get a spot?
I forgot.
What? What do you mean you forgot.
Keisuke, please come to the music room...please...
School of Masochists
-Perfect Edition-
Class has already started. Didn't Ms.Yuuki tell you to
attend class?
Who cares, none of my concern.
Besides, you told me to come here.
Are you going to give me some private music lessons?
Don't fool around! You know why I called you here!!
I don't recall anything.
I have really bad memory. Please remind me...teacher.
If you don't remind me, what can I do?
This...
I still don't understand.
Please take this off me. I haven't been able to do
anything for five days and I can't take it.
Oh...that.
But you're already so wet.
Please...I can't take it...I can't hold out much longer.
I see, and what are you going to do after, teacher?
Your....your thing...
Stick it in my special spot...
Bitch! And you call yourself a teacher?
I'm...I'm sorry, but...
If you can cum like this, I'll take it off.
Oh my....are you alright?
I'm alright.
Yuuka, you are good at everything else but volleyball.
Leave me alone.
It's alright, by the way, did you look toward the boys?
Looks like Keisuke ditched again.
I told him all that and still!?
I think you should just ignore him, it's useless.
I can't say that. I have to do my job as a class president.
But...
Keisuke Shimizu, you better get ready. I'm going to teach
you straight until you get it!
How is it? You haven't touched your pussy for 5 days,
right?
It feels...good...
I see...I will give you your reward for holding it. You like
this, right?
Like it...I love it...
You are licking it very carefully...did you want a taste of
man that bad?
Yes...
Just as I thought. All girls will toss their morals just for a
man. You girls are all the same.
Touch yourself and turn the other way....I'll fuck your ass.
Yes.
Feels...good...more...harder...
Keisuke....stretch my....ass....with your....
More...more...
There he is
Wait up, Keisuke.
Not you again!? What do you want now?
I wouldn't be complaining if you attended your classes.
I told you at lunch, why do you still ditch classes?
Shit bitch, why do you have to keep pestering me?
Personally, I don't really care what in the world you do!
I am appointed class president by the teachers.
Otherwise, I wouldn't give a damn about your.
Huh?
Uh...wha, what is it?
You keep pestering me because a teacher ask you to?
That's so stupid and childish.
I don't know how it was at your old school, but a teacher's
word is everything here.
So, if a teacher tells you to take of your clothes, you will?
What about if they tell you to lick their toes?
How about if they tell you to stop breathing.
See, look at you. That's why girls are so stupid.
Don't be sexually discriminating me!
Sexual discrimination, you say?
Girl's can't do anything without fame and power. You are
all pathetic.
That's not true!
Yes, it is.
Your type are all the same. You all talk about dating and
love, but all you want is a 'man'!
T...that's not...!
Wanna bet?
If you win, I will become the good boy you want. If I win,
you leave me alone!
For the next three months, you will be my slave.
If you don't loose your sanity to lust and pleasure, you win.
I can't...!
You can't do it? Of course, all girls are creatures who are
weak to pleasure.
This is so stupid. Why should I even do that when I don't
even like you a tiny bit.
You're still a virgin, aren't you? Only a virgin would say
something like that.
You never got a cock up in here and came, right?
You can only see girls in that way? Don't you have a
heart?
Then....
Prove me that love is stronger than just lust and pleasure.
Keisuke...?
Despite what I'm doing, you don't look worried...
Huh?
You don't feel a thing even if I touch you, because you
don't like me....right?
Or are you going to admit that it felt good when I touched
you down there?
Answer me!
I accept...
I accept your bet! I will show you that girl's don't crave for
lust, I will show you that girl's can control themselves.
Don't forget your side of the bargain.
That' s fine.
AIso...
It...it's my first time, so please be gentle.
Heh, don't worry.
I will make you not forget.
Don't be so stiff.
...but......
It feels good right, look at your nipples.
It's not....
No...something is strange.
You have a cute voice. Don't you do this at home?
I don't.....do...
Homework, then?
Lets see here.
Look at this dripping.
No....embarrassing....
Something is...strange...my thing is warm...and I can't
think of anything else...
Alright...time for this.
Make this bigger with your mouth.
What!? No, that's so dir...
Shut up!
Everyone does it. Even your girlfriends suck on their
boyfriend's cock with a smile!
Ouch!
Heh, only if you honestly sucked my cock, I wouldn't have
hurt you.
How is it? You can feel it getting bigger in your mouth?
It's...getting so big...
My throat...
Ho...hold on!
No, I can't! It won't fit!
What are you saying!
There's no way I can stop now!
You want to be held, because you love him?
You'll teach me what love is?
How can you say that, you don't even know about guys!
Your love is nothing but a kid's dream!
....The impact...I can't...move...
Please...don't move...it....hurts...
You don't like pain? Let me tell you how to make it go all
away.
Keep saying the following statement.
I like guys, I like guys to fulfill my lust.
Ouch!
If you say it, your pain will go away...and you'll feel better!!
I....ike....guys....like....fulfill....my....
I like...guys....I...ike...fulfill my...
I like...guys...
I like guys...I like guys to fulfill....my lust...
I like guys...
Come here everyday from now on. Teach me what true
love is.
Keisuke.
How's school? Are you keeping out of trouble?
Aren't you the one...
who will take care of troubles?
Keisuke! Look at it from my point of view! Do you know
how much I spent on this?
Are you telling me what to do?
Heh, I don't think a sugar daddy like you should tell me
what to do.
This is all your fault!
Oh my, I didn't think such comments would slip out of your
mouth.
Hold it! Where are you going?
Where I go is none of your business.
You're going to him, aren't you?
Wait! Hold it! Wait up!
Fuck!
All girls are the same...she sure was stupid...
Why him....why did we....
Prove me that love is stronger than just lust and pleasure.
For a second...I didn't think he was such a bad person...
Guys are!
Yuuka? ....Yuuka? ....Yuuka!
Oh!?
Sorry, I was thinking about something.
Are you alright? You don't look fine.
I'm alright, it's ok.
There she is, Yuuka!
What, what's up?
Sheshh, why didn't you just tell me? Or were you
embarrassed?
What are you talking about?
This letter is from Keisuke.
Keisuke?
Be at the announcement room at 12:45. You can't
runaway.
12:45? That's really soon
Who cares, I'm not going.
I like...guys...
This is!?
You came quick.
What are you thinking!? What did you just announce!?
Oh, about that?
As an anniversary of loosing your virginity, I finished
editing the tape and wanted to show you.
See...look at this. My dick is deep inside your pussy.
Stop it! Is it fun picking on me? What do you want?
What are you talking about!? You said the bet is on and
that you will be my slave.
Master and slave...a smart person like you should know
who's on top.
I can't believe you...
Well, I won't stop you if you want out of this bet.
Huh?
However, as a promise, you can't say a thing to what I do.
Who ever turns on the T.V. in campus, they are going to
be surprised with what they are going to see.
Especially if they find out it's you. I wonder how many
would watch then? This is getting fun.
....I won't stop...
What?
I won't stop...the bet...
Don't you have a different way of saying it?
Please...let me....continue to serve you.
Well if you insist...why don't we have you masturbate as
you take a look at this?
That's too!
If you don't want too, I don't mind. Or would you rather
have me instead?
Well, which is it?
Look at this. your pussy is devouring my dick.
Don't you think you are a slut?
I can't believe you. You're getting turned on by seeing
yourself get fucked.
That's not...
Even your nipples are hard.
It feels good, right? You feel it, right?
See, even down here...
Look, you are dripping wet.
No...don't say that...
Here, check it out yourself.
See, you are so wet.
No...my fingers won't stop...
This part...feels good...
You won't stop...a slut like you must really like this.
You keep touching the same spot.
Look, it's being recorded beautifully. You touching your
own little spot.
Didn't you notice, or were you too preoccupied?
Maybe someone was looking at this live.
No...
What's this? The thought of other people looking turning
you on?
Something...something is...coming from...the inside...I'm
scared....
Hold it.
Not so fast. Sorry to spoil your fun, but...
The fun is just starting.
Cumming....cumming...
No....something...coming...I'm feeling...
I don't...want it...I though I don't...
Cumming, it's cumming!
I want to go home.
What!? You know what you are saying?
We're going to do something with sex anyway.
But, I though that's what our relationship is?
Then, what's that video for?
I always make sure to play it safe.
Don't be so stiff.
No.
How is it? You can feel it getting bigger in your mouth?
No, I can't! It won't fit!
What are you saying!
There's no way I can stop now!
Noo!!!!
If you brake any promises...
Wow, your eyes glare with hatred.
I don't mind if we do it here!
No...way...
I'm such a nice person, that's why I asked you to come
over.
No one is looking...or do you want them to look?
N..no...
Your embarrassing spot.
You look like you want people to see.
You're really going to do it? Here?
I'm so sorry.
Korin!
Yuuka? And Keisuke?
I knew it, you two were dating each other. I though
something was fishy since the other day.
Korin..I'm not really doing anything with Keisuke.
Korin, there's no way I can hide anything from you.
Keisuke!
Sorry. Keep this a secret.
You know how our school is with dating.
Also, since she's a class president, some rumors might
start.
Huh...what?....What....Inside...
Well, Korin, so can you please keep this a....
OK, I know when to keep my mouth shut.
No...I feel it.
Everyone in train is looking at me....even Korin.
Keisuke...please sto....
Yuuka, are you alright? Your face is red.
I'm fine...I just have a... slight fever.
A cold? You should tell someone about that right away.
My house is the next stop, so why not rest there?
Hmmm...I must agree with him, Yuuka.
That's right, relax.
It's here. Come.
Wow, I came to check up, but she really did enter
Keisuke's house...She's the first in our group....
Do your best, Yuuka!
Hold it, what are you doing there?
Yuuka...err, my friend went in to that house and...
That is Keisuke's house, correct Korin?
Huh?
Are you sure I can come in?
I don't care.
I'm so stupid....I followed him.
Hey, you have a dog or something?
A dog...That's hilarious!
He's laughing...it's my first time seeing him laugh so hard.
Well it is a dog....a wild bitch to be exact.
Keisuke, you like dogs? I use to have a terrier...he was
smart.
I'll show you, come.
You have it upstairs?
It's here. take a peak.
Why from a crack?
Cause it might bite you.
Here, here...
It's not a dog...a human?
Is that lady....your mom, Keisuke?
That woman...is not my mother. I told you...a wild bitch.
Keisuke's action up until now ...his feelings toward the
female gender.
It's all because of his mom!
Alright, enough of show and tell! You're going to end up
like that anyway.
Or what. Do you want to watch the Master bitch get gang
banged?
What should I...
Ms. Izumi! Why are you here?
I came to see Mr. Shimizu....Anyway, about that story.
What about Ms. Orie? Can you please give me more
details?
Ms. Izumi is a teacher and... Sorry Yuuka. I can't keep it a
secret.
Look are you, you are so wet. So you did get wet
watching that bitch being fucked by multiple guys.
T, that's not..
You are so dirty, Yuuka.
I have to punish a dirty girl like you...
What's wrong? You are so quiet today.
Is this not enough for yo u?
Start howling like you always do.
Look, there's a good example you can look at.
You're a bitch too...just like her.
Looks like she can't cum unless she's being DP'ed.
If you're a bitch, howl like a bitch.
Heh, the asshole...
Come!!!
Noooo!!!!! No...butt....
Looks like you like it.
I'll make you feel better.
No...my butt....
Why did this happen....with this guy ...doing this...this....
Don't...move!!
It hurts...it hurts!
No...amazing....
....It's...amazing...
How can this feel good...this....with this....
It feels so good....I'm going to..I'm going to cum!
Cumming...I'm cumming!!
You have a cute voice.
Can you feel it getting bigger in your mouth?
I can't do this...I'm cumming, I'm going to brake.
Feels...so good...
No...but....
Feels to...good...my fingers...
My fingers...I can feel them hitting each other...inside...
No...this isn't me....
Lets see...Mr. Shimizu isn't here....and Ms. Narita? That's
amazing.
He's probably ditching class, but I wonder what's up
Korin?
I haven't seen herforthree days...
Please....I can't be satisfied with a vibrator anymore.
You want this?
That fat and hard....
Looks like you're already feeling good, you don't need this.
Don't say that...
I'm so happy.
The balls, lick my balls first.
This...
Use the vibrator as you lick me.
Not that one!
It's not the pussy that you like, right!? Which hole do you
like it the best?
Show me!
I, it's this....
P, please...pull the vibrator out and stick your...thing
in....me
Please..give it to me...in the ass.
My butt....no...both holes...feels good.
Cum with the vibrators, then I'll think about it.
No...not with...this...I’m cumming...please...give...stick it
in...please....
Stick it...in my butt...my butt....I'm going to cum!!
You are boring...
Ma, Master...
I'm sorry if I did something wrong...so please...stick it in
my...butt...
You always want some. It can be anything, right?
Long as it's in your butt.
Master...
Master!
N..no...
Sir..my butt...I love this.
Sir, what did you just say?
What am I going to do...without my Master's...
It's that bitch...because of that bitch, my Master...!
I wonder what today's class is
Yeah, I wonder
I cant' wait
Yeah.
Yuuka?
Ms. Izumi?
Once that's done, I would like to have a word with you.
OK...
Ms. Izumi, what did you want to talk about?
It's about Ms. Narita.
Korin!?
Anyway...you...you had sex with Keisuke, correct?
Se...sex? Ms. Izumi?
What? Not here?
Yeah...Ms. Izumi called her out.
Remi?
Do you know where they went?
Music...no, they went to the lab room.
Shit, if I was thinking straight, I would've known Remi
would do this.
...So, you did...didn't you?
I though this was about Korin?
Korin? Oh, that girl.
Ms. Izu....
Korin!!
What? What is going on!?
What a trouble maker. This is all your fault. It's because
you took Kei...my Master away
I only taught her what is right. I didn't do anything.
I'll teach you that too.
This room has lots of cool devices.
Lets start with this.
What? No!!!
It hurts!
Oh my, you have bad manners.
Don't cum yet. We're just getting started.
I'll give it to you down here too.
Master!
Keisu...ke...
What the fuck you think you're doing, Remi?
I...I just thought...
I only did this for you...I wanted the old you back.
Master, you are not yourself right now.
So please give me a while. I will...
Ms...Izumi...
I will have the old you back.
Otherwise, my Master wouldn't abandon me...I will have
the old you back.
Yes, long as this girl isn't here...you are mine.
Excuse me.
Ms. Izumi, he is the one I was talking about, Keisuke
Shimizu.
This...boy?
These...eyes...
Is he really a student? Feels like a beast looking at its
prey.
N, no...I tried to forget about this...
Izumi...Ms. Izumi
For these reasons, we want you to take care of him. Are
you listening?
Yes...
What was I just thinking...
Nice to meet you, teacher.
Oh...yes...nice to meet you.
I'm so happy that my teacher is beautiful.
I though I forgot about it...those nightmare...that demon....
That sensation....that...
I'm getting wet.
Really? What I really want...is those days....
No...my fingers aren't...
I want it...now..stick in...something..,!
I want to touch it...I want that...fat and long...
Yes, yes!
More...more!
I knew it!
Until recently, there was a sex craved maid at my house.
You look a lot like that bitch.
Hurry and get out! This is a teacher's restroom, on top of
that, for females!
And who's the one that's masturbating in that bathroom?
Stick it in? Bitch, I don't think you deserve to talk!
These eyes...these eyes...it makes me crazy
The way he degrades me....his eyes....
Stick your ass up higher!
Sir...
It's going to cum out...my butt...!
Hold it, Remi. The more you hold it in, the better...
Please..don't hurt me...you can do what you want...
Do what I want? Don't you mean...do what you want!?
Say it. What do you want?
I want it...up my butt...
Now you are my bitch!
I'll do anything for this...Anything to penetrate my butt!
I'll do anything....I'll become your pet...your slave.
So you like it up your ass! You filthy whore!
Come to think about it...she was already once a slave...I
don't know everything about her.
Feels good...my thing down there...it's warm.
Touch me more...Ms. Izumi, touch me more...
Remi did this?....All of this?
Great....great job Ms. Izumi...
Remi!
I take back what I said, you are my cute pet!
No...more...give me more...
Give me more, Make me squirm.
Korin...
As your Master, I have to get things straight.
Remi!
Yes, Master.
What?
A pet must listen to its Master. Get ready.
Can't be...that was in Korin...?
It's such a pity to be you....a girl's jealousy is scary...I will
coat you with your friend’s sweet honey.
Well, if you're this wet, it will go in easily .
No, stop...no...stop!
Remi, hold on to her tightly!
No, it, it hurts! I'm going to split!!!
Hey, Korin. Your favorite toy is right over here.
Korin...Snap out of it, Korin!
Ko, Korin...
Ko, Korin....Please, stop!
Please stop...Korin, snap out of it...Korin!!
Feels good...
My thing...its all the way inside me.
What's wrong, don't you feel it too?
What a boring slut. Because of you, my pussy is dry.
I punish you. Lick it and make me wet.
I can't....Noo!
If you don't lick it, you will have trouble breathing.
Remi, she's normally a masochist, but looks like she can
be a sadist too.
Hurry up and lick it.
Yes...more up...use your tongue...
Why am I...
More, more! Make me wet!
Master!
Show Yuuka what kind of girl you really are.
Good...look, look at it penetrating....my butt!
No...at this place...doing this....
Master, your thing is cumming in. Good...It feels
good...my butt feels good!
Feels good...My butt...it feels good!
I...I don't care if I break apart...my butt...my butt...it
feels...good!
You don't care if you break? You slut teacher...I hope I
don't become like you.
Hold on...I'll give you a treat.
No!! Stop, Keisuke!! If I do this, she will...she will...
Teacher...! Teacher!!
You don't look like your in pain...this smile, you just want
more of this!
My hands are inside the teacher! Can't be...it can't
be...who will be happy with something like this...
Great, it's great...
What's going on...everyone is crazy!
Or...am I the crazy one?
I don't know anymore!
(Teacher...)
My Butt...
(Korin...)
(I can't...any longer...)
How is it Korin. Isn't the real thing better than a dildo?
Beautiful.....delicious....I want it...
Ko, Korin...
Korin, it's your turn. I'll give a taste of a real one.
Real...Areal one...stick it in...stick a real one in me.
It's coming in...me...A lot...
Real one...good...
More..give me more...
Ko, Korin...
Master...
Don't stop.
Please give me some too.
I'm already...so wet.
After Korin is Yuuka's turn.
But...!! Y, yes Master
Until then, use that and keep her wet.
Don't break her.
Yes!
Please...give me...give me...
No...teacher...why?
Why...
Listen to...
Keisuke....
Because it's the orders by the Master
Principal, it's almost...
Ohh, it's already late.
Look like there's still a class with its light on.
Huh? Oh...I think that's the lab room.
I think Mr. Sugai is cleaning up. Lets drop by .
Korin, call me Masterform now on, OK?
What do you mean Master, you mother boy!!
You complain about girls.
But, you just want some love from your family!
Don't talk to the Master like that!
You're no different than a kid who's trying to
get attention!
Bitch, how dare you talk like that!
What do you know?
Those fuckers are not my parents! I don't want their love!
And what about you? You're born from them and you're
doing the same thing!
Who do you think you are!?
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Whore...you fucking whore...
I will make you shut up!
Remi!!!
Yes, Master!
No! No! Not my butt!
Awhore like you deserves this!!
Remi, stick it up in her pussy even more!! Give it to her
faster!
Bite down on that slut's nipples! Make her scream!
Break her in!!
My breath...My body is twitching...feels like I have two
hearts.
Why am I...huh? Where, was this...?
What am I doing? My body...feels heavy.....like it's not
mine.
My lower half feels like it's melting...what's happening?
Wha, what?
That's right. Keisuke's thing is in my butt....
That thing...is in my butt...that thing...
Athick thing is also in my vagina...
My vagina is being...huh? My butt is being....my vagina is
being...huh?
Something is spreading in me...it's taking over me.
What is it.....it's not pain or something of it...it's just....
Crazy....going crazy!
That's it! Go crazy! Break, break apart!
Cumming, cumming! My head....cumming! I'm loosing it!
Pri...principal...this is?
Mr. Shimizu....what's it going on...
Sup, Principal. Would you like to join?
Wh, what are you! You are all expelled!
Have you forgotten who my dad is?
We...well....
How would you like to anal fuck...no, DP a honor student?
Her inside feels really great!
So this is what a honor student tastes like.
I can't believe I'm doing this with my students...
Hertongue...
I'm going to cum...
They always say what not to do....
In front of lust...all that is gone....
Yuuka, don't be so selfish.
It's just not girls...the guys are the same shit too.
Don't you want to feel more?
You want more fun?
I....
I.....want....to have...more fun....
I want to feel better.
Here, here...you have to ask politely.
P....ple...please?
You want to be treated like Korin, right?
I'm cumming...cumming!!
I...I am...a slut..who...loves it in any hole...Please...
Teachers, please...please give me your..
What's wrong?
Stick...it....Stick it in!! Stick it in and make me go wild!
Please stick it in now! Please!! I don't care what hole,
hurry! Hurry!!
Hurry! Hurry! Give it to me!!
Principal...your dick is......delicious.
Gym Teacher...yours is magnificent.....English
Teacher....so long....
Wait...so a lot....
More..I want to swallow more...
Oh...again....
If you're done, hurry up and trade.
Sorry.
What if someone catches us...
That's good...lets show everyone. I want people to
see...my pussy being filled up....
Look at my pussy. My pussy is devouring your dick...cum
inside me!
My pussy....has lots of cum....my pussy, my pussy....
I love it more than anything in the world! Give it, give it,
give it to me!
They sure came a lot.
My mouth and pussy is filled with delicious sperm. But....
What, you still want more?
This is my dessert.
So, you're telling me that you are full?
I was going to get some full course meal ready.
Do you mean?
Yeah...Remi is probably convincing my dad right now .
Sir, did you think about what we talked about?
Oh that? Don't worry a thing about it.
Anyways, lets...
Sir, you are so eager.
You have such a great ass.
Because you have these two thick dildos in you
You are so wet.
No....don't pull it out.
Don't worry, I'll stuff you right away.
Sir...don't lick...I'm sensitive...there....
What are you talking about. Your thing is twitching for a
man.
My butt....
Your ass is great! Any man can enjoy this piece of ass!
Yes, I can feel it all the way! It's thick...my butt...it's going
to stretch!
This...this is it...my butt...it's wonderful!
You guys are together again.
What are you doing!?
The teachers call you in because you're always with him!
Yuuka's been ditching school lately too.
What's up with your hair? It's hard at some spots.
Oh?
And...what's this smell?
(It still smells....)
Oh, I'm a bit sick and
I didn't take a shower...last night.
So dirty!
Hey, where's going to go see Yuuka right now .
Would you like to come...
To Yuuka?
I though we were going to go see Yuuka?
That's right.
Yuuka, how are you doing? You must have been lonely.
I brought a friend over today.
Yuuka?