You are being very good, Janne, opening your ass on command.
Even if you have my body you will never get my soul
I will never forgive you.
What do I care, I can not enjoy your soul.
Do not get depressed.
I will find a solution
to return us to before.
E-enema?!
I have already been emptied of my feces.
It's very dirty!
It is so perverse it makes me look like a monster.
I won't give you this treatment. Celine...
Let us see if you have improved.
You still do not go?
Show us your technique.
Doing something like this to a girl... she is not even old enough to marry.
It's too cruel.
Now slowly push up the bottom to make her feel much more pain.
Pour it all!
That night
the two of us became their personal slaves.
Please forgive me, I can not stop him!
We were forced to perform acts day by day that brought more and more shame.
The happy moments of the past were quickly forgotten.
I beg you!
Do not look!
I think I have a good idea on what this is.
Do not look at...
Kiss...
Even though I know I'm only at the beginning of a long torture
I want to die anyway.
However, when I think what usually happens I remember they have taken two hostages ...
One of the two is immediately eliminated
while the other receives a fate even more brutal than death itself.
Do not behave like the poor victim, princess.
Not so hard!
So strong ... I will not!
Please forgive me, father ...
We are going to be dominated by savage beasts and become indecent.
In my body... has been inserted so deep.
I am so ashamed!
But this warm thing that swells in my ass
strangely gives me a great pleasure.
I have completely lost reason.
You seem to like it in the behind a lot, Janne ...
No. .. no it's not!
It is not possible ... not true!
Do not stop!
Then you move a little ...
Has already...can not bear...
If you want to continue you must tell me: "I feel good"
I ... ... Janne anus ...
not good ... I enjoy too ... so I can not think ...
He also speaks ...
By pushing so hard it will not take long to cum.
My ass ... I feel ... good!
Well said Jeane, my good sex slave.
Louder! Harder!
This will not do well?
Push it with more strength!
My ass is not so fragile.
After all this time it has expanded to fit your size!
Now what if your beloved prince heard you say that?!
Geese? No no, how could I not?!
How could I say such a thing to him?!
Get up!
I want to cum all the way to the ass!
Hot ...
My gut is full of your hot seed.
It feels so nice!
G-good!
We must continue, Janne
Now our purpose is fully met with our jailer's.
Doing these things with my mother baffles me but at the same time makes me strangely excited as hell.
So much semen would cause any woman to lose strength.
Try it with gusto.
This taste should be remembered!
The taste???
The seed of Kido-sama is.. tasty.
More so than a human's it is thicker and stickier.
Even if it looks the same in appearance and it is delicious.
Well done!
It seems that mother and daughter have performed equally well.
Then came the most terrible day of all.
Oh, do not look at me!
But who is watching? Just me?!
I can not forgive them for the shame that I feeling!
Shame? I?
This looks greatly excites me!
No, do not evaluate me with those vulgar eyes.
The feeling of being so intensely watched makes my pussy get wet!
No, and certainly an impression!
I hear sounds like thunder in my brain!
No, it's as if all their thoughts passed through my head!
No, I will not! my breathing becoming more labored, no!
Princess!
Your Highness, the Princess why is she so unfriendly?
Recently she seems very distraught and locks herself in her room for days.
This concerns me greatly ...
Besides coming so often to pray in this place can be too ...
Do not worry about her.
With her sincere prayers the angels will give us their blessing.
That is the commitment that women in our family have decided to make.
If Janne saw me in this position it would make her very jealous.
Please understand me, I just wanted to know about the Princess because I am concerned for her.
I really hope that the princess is revived through the prayers.
I'll let you know, Geese.
If you would show your support, I'd be very happy.
Then you said "if you show your support, I'd be happy."
You must be stupid to think of helping your daughter in things so unnecessarily
Banning servants to urinate every day
is really cruel!
Orgadiam has a parasite in our vagina
also called "Angel Killer".
not only increases sexual desire, but also transforms the genitals
which grow out normal.
I have been deprived of my power the moment I stopped being a virgin.
It's as if I had the organs and lust of a male but at the same time.
the heart and the feelings of a woman.
Having a penis is so nice!
I enjoy so much!
I am unexpectedly infatuated with this monster because he treats me as a slave.
I am a really shameless woman.
Kido-sama, I want to pee.
My vagina needs to be free.
Do not look, Janne.
Mother, after urinating does it feel good?
No. .. do not ask me those questions!
I also want to feel good ... ...
The mouth of the mother is hot!
The penis should be ...!
I never thought that my mother's breasts were so big and soft.
It is so good!
No my penis needs to be stimulated more.
More ... Cum!
Mother ... I'm dying!
Do not lick it again!
After all this, and yet so hard
and hot ...
No, I'd be much better by putting it in little thing of a woman
Mother ..
I ... I ...
No. .. not you ... Janne ...
Mother ...
You must not!
Janne, I beg you, I can not ... ..
I know, mother ...
Celine, taste the hot horny cunt of your mother.
Stop right there! Janne!
But, you have an odor so intense.
Forgive me, mother,
I can not resist.
It's hot, mother, your contractions are squeezing my penis!
And I entered in only part of the tip.
I want to put it ... all!
Janne this is a  wrong thing to do.
Why do you do such a thing?
I love you a lot, but we are mother and daughter!
B-beautiful ... and hot.
Mother within you ... is so incredibly hot!
Now I finally understand.
I know how to please a penis!
Incredible!
That's a vagina.
Pushing in the penis mixes your juices.
With the penis ... the uterus ... the uterus ...
Janne's penis and a vagina!
How are you feeling Celine?
Your physical changes should now be complete.
Now even the smallest amount of sperm can get you pregnant.
You'll have a beautiful belly!
I love this penis vagina ... I love this!
Now I'm raping this bitch my mother!
No, you are losing your mind!
Do not, do not forgive!
My Mother, you should be ashamed to have a vagina so wet.
Inside I can not move without problems.
I can not pull out his penis from your vagina!
You know what will happen if you cum, Janne?
Of course, I will make my mother pregnant with my child.
Janne!
Disgusting, how much?!
If this much were fired inside me, then I ...
Right, I have to come in the pussy of my mother because then this penis disappears.
Why am I doing this?
Can not be like this
Do not put it to the bottom of the vagina, stop immediately!
You're pushing on my womb!
against my uterus!
Pregnant, please, get pregnant and raise my son.
My Mother, I am at the limit.
The penis ... my penis ... I can not move like before!
No, you can not give up right now!
If you want to get me pregnant so much then push harder ... please!
Janne's penis in my vagina and so wet!
No, I can not!
This is the penis of my daughter, this is incest!
Angel of mercy, please forgive me!
I'm going to cum!
So hot. Something is coming out from my penis!
So much sperm will hit my womb
because they are so deep I know I will get pregnant.
My dear, I am sorry, I about to be pregnant.
By our child
We will be two very good mothers to our children.
No, how can I be considered a good mother
after what we did?!
In the name of the holy father, let me give birth to a beautiful baby.
How much I enjoy!
I ... my children will grow up in your body!
My God, my they be born healthy
nd with a penis as beautiful as mine!
Janne!
Dear Janne, I offer the gift of the vagina and my whole body!
Now I am completely willing to accept your seed inside me!
How nice, I have fertilized, my mother ...
He will be born.
My mind and my body are totally infatuated with your penis, Janne dear.
Here is where our son will be Janne.
Because you came back a normal woman, Janne.
In the battlefield the invincible guardian angel is already gone.
At this time no one would ever think to forgive what you did.
Now let your uterus feel the pleasure to make you a Mother.
W-why is it  so hot?!
My insides feel so good.
and the pleasure of being a sex slave?
I-incredible, and so fierce!
The punishment of this monster is incredibly fierce!
Incredible!
His penis can solicit sensitive areas that I did not even know!
About to cum!
I passively accept inside me.
For me, there is only this pain and those of other Orgadiam.
All others things do not matter.
You're losing your senses?
Yes, soon.
I feel I'm losing my mind, I am going to cum!
Are you ready?
I'd love to hear you say "I want to cum" just before orgasm.
No, impossible!
Although I have become this oga's woman...I can not say it.
Also, if you keep pushing so strongly
I will not last another minute!
Take a look at her face.
Does that look like the face of the heir to the throne?
Forgive me, mother.
I am really very sorry father
Although I am the princess of this country...
Although Keith takes care of the country's security...
I ... I have now lost its pride and honor.
Sorry, sorry, I became an indecent princess!
I forgive, I am ashamed to have my flaws so obscenely open!
So I beg you, please allow me to cum, I want to cum.
I am cumming!
After which I finally become a father!
I'm cumming!
Cummming!!!!!!!
We will now depart on a crusade against the barbaric oga.
Princess.
Before sleeping, as usual pray to the Almighty Lord.
We pray to the Lord that nothing happens to your father.
Forgive me for I have sinned!
A man ... a man has entered my body!
You are little thing for a human woman and I am very close!
Do you feel disgusted by my big thing?
No, it feels strange ...
compared to times with my husband I now enjoy thus much more!
I am going to shoot a lot of semen inside, I am cumming!
Dear, dear.
No!
Do not cum inside!
I beg you, spare me!
Please!
Stop she is going to get married soon!
So enjoy my cum instead!
What a pleasant night.
The city is full of obscene screams of women.
Janne, to celebrate the town
here's a nice gift, filling
both of your obscene holes with semen.
Yes, all the holes of Janne can be used at your leisure!
I sign, as Celine Boufard, sovereign ruler of the kingdom...
renounce total management of this country
and declare the royal family forever faithful slaves to Kido-sama.
I promise with my daughter Janne to engage in this glorious task!
I ... I have something to add ...
Now it does not matter which hole ...
is used by the penis of Kido-sama ... I want him to continue to rape me!
Princess, how large ...
Look at them.
It 's time to feed your children with the milk of our dicks.
How is the feeling of being pregnant?
No, my holes are only to be raped by Kido-sama!
I am going to make you happy and shoot inside.
Yes, I love this feeling.
When you pull out and reinsert it firmly it feels good!
Kido-sama can enjoy with me but I want to cum, so ...
push with more strength!
But I do not want this solid penis always within me.
You can also use my mouth and I can massage with my soft breasts!
You don't have to continuously entering into my dirty hole I still have the rest of the body!
How about you?
You still have the energy to stand up?
I'm coming! I want to be shameful!
I too am going to come, I'm coming with a monster inside!
Please, cover my baby with your seed!
Princess ...
Geese, look at me.
Finally I am proud of myself.
I am going to be a mother.
This is the greatest happiness of a woman...
please remember that.