Copter 1, Copter 1.
Give us your altitude.
Our altitude is currently 600 feet.
Please confirm our target.
Copter 1, you are currently right on target.
Confirmed.
Location confirmed.
We will land as soon as possible.
Confirmed.
Send a seven-man team
to investigate, as planned.
Roger that. Out.
There's debris in the air.
It's coming from the ground.
The ground?
What could it be?
School of Darkness 2
Report!
Ready, sir!
Prepare to land!
Yes, sir!
Lower the ropes!
Lowered, sir!
Attach your clips!
Equipment check!
Ropes, check!
Harness, check!
Three: Gloves, check!
Seat, check!
Other equipment, check!
Report!
Number one.
Number two.
Number three.
Number four.
Prepare to descend!
Let's go!
Team one, head west,
team two and three, head to the north.
Yes sir!
Whoa!
What is it?
Something has caught my leg, sir.
I need more detail, give me a report.
Yes sir, it's a vine of some sort, sir.
A vine of some sort?
A report, sir!
This whole area is covered
with these vines, sir.
What?
This area was battered by a storm
two days ago.
Did that have anything to do with this?
It looks like blood.
Maybe this was the debris we saw in the air?
I have never seen anything like this, sir.
Continue, but be very careful.
Sir!
Did all you guys have to dress like that?
But you said we could wear
what we wanted!
I heard you say that, too.
I heard that, too!
We're going camping
in the mountains, girls.
I heard you say that, too.
You guys just don't get it.
It's so damned, fucking hot.
Yuko, can't you do something about it?
Now, what makes you think I have control
over the heat?
Kyoko, all you've done is complain.
But it's just too damned hot!
Just get over it.
You said earlier that you didn't like
the air conditioning on.
We'll stop for a break soon,
so be patient, okay?
Damn it.
I can't stand it anymore!
Kyoko!
Hi!
She's a slut, as you can see.
Her name is Kyoko Sahara,
the troublemaker.
She likes video games and picking up men.
She'll try anything, as long as it's fun.
She's has a lot of experience with men.
I don't know how she does it.
Check this out!
She's known for her fresh
and healthy beauty.
Yuko Koizumi.
She's brilliant, and athletic.
She's also got a great body.
Tons of guys are after her.
She has absolutely no interest
in men, though.
Shit, I quit!
Akemi, take my place.
I'm not any good.
This is Akemi Yashiro, the quiet one.
She's really shy.
Akemi and Yuko have been
best friends for a while...
and Akemi's always hiding behind Yuko.
Here, put down this card.
Thanks!
There's something going on with these two.
That's not fair!
It's not fair to help her out like that!
And, this is me.
My name is Shiori Tachikawa.
I'm very popular, and sweet.
I'm cute and I'm smart.
I'm the most popular girl in school!
Okay, enough self-praise for now.
We have a storm moving in
from the western coast.
Please expect unpredictable weather
in the west and south counties.
The mountains should expect
some severe weather.
By nightfall, they should expect heavy rain
and thunderstorms in that region.
Please use extreme caution
if you are heading out this weekend.
Will we be okay, Tatsuya?
We'll be just fine.
The forecast is never right
when I go camping.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Sorry about the delay!
These two are the main characters.
This gorgeous lady
is our high school teacher.
Yayoi Mizuno.
Her beauty is like the beautiful flowers
on our campus.
Her smile is innocent, like a young girl.
Her figure is lean and very graceful.
She's understanding and kind.
But there's something else about her.
She is undeniably very sexy.
She is our idea of an ideal woman.
We want to be a wonderful teacher,
just like her.
But she is about to be married soon...
to Tatsuya Kubo, the biology teacher.
Who knows what she sees in this jerk.
We really can't believe it, but...
she's getting married to this stupid idiot
this summer!
So, us four members
of Ms. Mizuno fan club...
have decided to crash their camping trip
this weekend...
as a farewell party for Ms. Mizuno.
But Ms. Mizuno looks very pretty today.
And very happy.
We're here, guys!
How pretty!
Hey, let's go check out the lake!
Yeah, I want to ride on a boat!
How about it, Akemi?
Sure!
Let's go, then!
Not to rain on your parade, but...
You guys need to start unpacking
your things first.
Shoot, I forgot!
Well, let's go.
Have fun guys!
You too, Kyoko!
Damn it!
I need to go pee.
They'll take care of it.
I didn't come here to raise tents.
I can get other things to rise up, though.
Wait, I really have to go pee now.
I'll do it here.
You shouldn't pollute nature.
I don't like to hold it in, so bug off.
You don't have any paper to wipe yourself.
Then clean it with your tongue.
What!
Hey, I meant down there.
You're a demanding slut.
Smells like piss!
Don't you like it?
I haven't tasted enough to know.
More!
You can't have all the fun.
Suck on my cock, for a change.
I'd love to.
You have a nice, big one here.
I know.
I'm coming!
Here!
Got it.
Let's see.
Hi there, do you need a hand?
I'm fine, thanks.
I know that pail is probably really heavy.
We can handle it just fine.
Let us help you.
Here, hand it over.
Look, you're bleeding.
Want me to lick it clean?
No thanks.
Don't touch Akemi!
Let go, you asshole!
Akemi!
Let go, and don't you dare touch her!
We'll take good care of her.
You guys suck at picking up women.
Fucker!
You are...
Tetsuji!
Are you okay.
Akemi, are you sure you're okay?
I'm all right.
Thanks to Tetsuji!
Yuko...
Let's go, Akemi.
Before any more creeps show up.
Yuko.
Pervert.
You're a peeping tom, aren't you?
That was a coincidence.
Whatever.
You're the easy, cocksucking, little slut.
You're the one that's getting
the enjoyment out of this.
You're having fun, too.
Maybe!
You're too damned good.
You've fucked a lot.
How about this?
That feels fucking awesome!
How about a golden shower.
Wait, hold it!
Did I scare you?
That wasn't funny!
Yes, yes!
How about I play with these?
Yes!
More!
God!
Yeah!
I've brought something very special
for you today.
You want it that bad?
Here, take your time and enjoy it.
Now, you've also learned the taste of blood!
We were preparing dinner at that time.
Nobody had any idea of the terrors...
that we would face in the near future.
Wow!
This is beautiful, it's really pretty.
I thought you would like it.
You're so beautiful.
That white flower looks good on you.
Thanks.
White flowers are my favorite.
I love you, Yayoi.
Me too, Tatsuya.
You're gorgeous.
What's wrong?
I felt like someone was watching.
Your mind's just playing tricks on you.
You think so?
So, Yayoi.
We should head back now.
We can't keep the girls waiting for us.
All right.
That night...
we were finally finished
with all the cooking.
It looked okay.
Although it could have
probably tasted better.
Thank you, everybody!
Thanks, guys.
This guy here is Tetsuji Tsuchiya.
Kyoko's boyfriend.
He's known as a troublemaker...
but he's nothing compared to Kyoko.
She asked him to come...
so he rushed over here with a gift.
Thank you, Tetsuji.
The champagne must have been expensive.
Not really. It's no big deal.
Here, Akemi.
Thanks!
Hey, let's open it!
Okay, hand it over.
No, I'll open it.
I said hand it over!
No way!
Shiori!
I like Ms. Mizuno the best, so there.
No, you liar, give it up!
If you shake it, it's going to...
Explode like this.
It was a really great, fun party.
Everyone lost track of time, partying.
We laughed, and joked around
with each other.
We must have looked like one big,
happy family.
But...
that was to be our last dinner together.
Hey Yuko, did you notice?
What?
Tetsuji kept looking at you
since this afternoon.
Really?
I think he likes you, Yuko!
Men are such a pain in the ass!
I really could care less.
You really mean that?
Not even Tetsuji?
Really?
You swear?
Akemi...
Are you worried?
You're silly.
Yuko!
Will you?
You are.
Before any more creeps show up.
Bitch!
I wonder what those two are up to by now?
Who?
Mr. Kubo and Ms. Mizuno.
I'd bet you money that they're doing
it right now.
Doing it?
I'm going to go out.
Wait, Kyoko! That's a bad idea!
You sicko, I'm going to go pee.
Okay.
You scared me!
Until Kyoko said it...
I never thought of Ms. Mizuno like that.
I never saw her as a sexual person.
All of a sudden...
Ms. Mizuno felt so far away...
as if she was in
a completely different world.
I immediately felt like I was abandoned.
I felt as if she had left me behind.
Ms. Mizuno.
You look pretty.
I can't wait.
Yes!
You're so wet, Yayoi.
Look at my fingers!
Jerk!
Yayoi!
I promise to protect you forever.
Tatsuya!
Ms. Mizuno, my favorite teacher.
I worshipped her.
It was only an illusion...
but I thought we would
all be together, forever.
Please, Ms. Mizuno!
Don't leave me behind!
I soon found my fingers...
furiously playing with my wet pussy.
Promise, you'll never look at anyone
else like this.
That's my...
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
No, Yuko!
Forgive my weakness.
No, that's not true.
What?
I like you just the way you are.
Akemi.
I swear I'll do anything for you.
Yuko?
Yuko isn't interested in you.
What?
Now you know.
Yuko only sleeps with women.
Kyoko, did you know about this?
Akemi!
Yes.
I love you.
Look, isn't this your favorite?
Yeah, will you?
Cry out if you want to.
Please, don't torture me any more!
I love that expression on your face.
Yeah!
You're so hard and big tonight!
This is the very best!
Yuko, come for me!
Akemi, yes!
I'm coming!
Yes!
I'm going to come!
Yuko, come with me!
God!
Shit, it's a thunderstorm!
We need to get everyone.
Yes!
The storm was fierce.
It happened so suddenly.
We were battered by thunder,
relentless rain and blistering winds.
Shit! Run inside the forest!
All we had were our clothes.
We left everything behind.
We were just trying to find a safe spot.
We wandered through the dark forest.
We eventually lost our way back...
and could not get back to the camp.
We sat down, exhausted and scared.
Akemi, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
All right, we need to gather anything
that's edible.
If anything at all.
Gross.
Tatsuya?
That's...
That was the very last
of my emergency food.
I didn't have enough to share.
Look, we are their teachers.
We're the only ones that can lead them.
We have to stay healthy.
We still need to look for more food.
Sure.
We gathered as much as possible...
but it wasn't very much.
Was that all you could find?
Go back and bring back more food, damn it!
Tatsuya, stop!
We were worn out from exhaustion
and hunger.
Mr. Kubo unleashed his temper at us.
He started to scream at us
for the smallest things.
What's in there?
What is this?
It's sweet.
Tatsuya!
Yayoi, I found a flower in this cave.
It's dripping with sweet nectar.
Go and have some.
Tatsuya, you're acting strange?
What's going on?
Just come with me!
Stop, Tatsuya!
What's wrong?
What has gotten into you?
Yayoi, let's fuck.
What are you talking about?
Come on, we're going to be married soon.
I want to.
Stop it, Tatsuya, please stop!
Let go, Tatsuya, please don't!
Yayoi!
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Did you have any of the flower's nectar?
The flower? What flower?
Excuse me, but will you please
untie this rope?
What was that for?
I can give you some food.
I don't want it.
What a fine body.
Please stop, don't touch me!
I haven't had a woman in ages.
No, stop it!
Please, let me go now!
Let me go, just stop it, stop!
No!
Why are you...
I'm going to teach you the taste
of the Garanta, too.
No, don't touch me, no!
Just let me go, and get away from me now!
- Get away from me, let me go!
- Yayoi!
Tatsuya!
You can nibble on this.
Is this is it, don't you have more?
If you want food,
then you need to do as I say.
You can undress this woman.
No!
What, aren't you hungry?
Tatsuya!
What are you doing to me?
You can endure this.
No, stop it Tatsuya, stop!
Here!
This is the nectar that I was talking about.
Don't!
Stop!
Once this enters the bloodstream...
it will highly increase your sexual appetite.
Stop, don't, please let me go, stop!
I like fighters.
No!
You're getting so wet already.
The flower will eventually call to you...
and you will mate with it.
Fifty years ago,
I worked for the government.
I was researching biological weapons.
I was cross-breeding different plants, and...
made countless number
of genetic mistakes, until...
I succeeded with the Garanta.
Once inside the human body...
it clouds the mind and changes
the genes of its hosts.
A perfect weapon, it eventually developed
defense mechanisms.
When we were transporting
the first specimen...
an accident occurred.
The plane crashed into this mountain.
I was miraculously, the only survivor.
Since then, I've lived with that plant.
Fortunately...
this climate was absolutely perfect
for the scattered samples.
Living off of various plants...
it continued to evolve.
Finally, it became the creature it is now!
The Garanta has never seen
a human woman.
I'm going to make sure the Garanta
really likes you.
No!
Yayoi?
Yayoi!
It's no use.
You can't escape from Garanta's forest.
Yayoi!
Go away, go away!
No!
Tatsuya!