My name is Shiori Tachikawa.
This is my favorite high school teacher...
Ms. Yayoi Mizuno.
All of us worshipped
and admired Ms. Mizuno.
We loved her as our teacher...
and spending time with her made us happy.
We thought those days would last forever.
However, Ms. Mizuno was recently engaged!
Her fiancee is our biology teacher,
Mr. Tatsuya Kubo.
So the members of Ms Mizuno's fan club...
went on a farewell trip.
Members include the slutty Kyoko Sahara...
the athletic Yuko Koizumi...
Akemi Yashiro, Yuko's best friend,
and myself.
Kyoko's boyfriend,
Tetsuji Tsuchiya, also came along.
The first day was a real blast.
Especially at night!
Everyone was having a lot of fun
with their partners.
I didn't have a partner, though.
Tetsuji's feelings for Yuko wasn't mutual.
In the middle of the night...
a storm tore through our camp.
With only the clothes on our back...
we ran into the forest for cover.
Looking for food,
we wandered through the forest.
We were soon separated from our teachers.
Deep inside the forest...
a horrible fate was waiting for us.
We were oblivious to the impending terrors.
What was that for?
I can give you some food.
I don't want it.
What a fine body.
Please stop!
Fifty years ago,
I worked for the government.
I was researching biological weapons.
I was cross-breeding different plants...
and made countless number
of genetic mistakes, until...
I succeeded with the Garanta.
The Garanta has never seen
a human woman.
I'm going to make sure the Garanta
really likes you.
No!
Go away!
Tatsuya!
School of Darkness 3
Yayoi...
Yayoi?
Yayoi!
Yayoi! Yayoi!
Yayoi.
She didn't fall from here?
Where am I?
What's happening to me?
Someone...
come get me!
Hurry!
Please help me.
That's...
it's Tatsuya!
Please Tatsuya...
Please!
Please hurry!
Help me get out of here!
No!
Wait!
Don't go!
Wait, Tatsuya!
Don't leave me here!
Tatsuya!
Help me!
I wonder where our teachers are.
Everyone's asleep.
They must be really tired.
I'm really exhausted, but I can't sleep.
Ms. Mizuno...
please, come back to us, soon.
Shiori!
Morning.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Our teachers haven't come back yet.
Don't tell me you stayed up all night?
Yeah.
Get some sleep, now that I'm awake.
No.
We need to find food,
and look for our teachers.
I can go look for food by myself.
I'll help you.
Let's go together, then.
Kyoko, time to get up.
Wake up, we need to go look for more food.
I'll go, too.
You need to sleep.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Tetsuji will bring back more food.
Shit, get up you lazy bum!
I haven't seen Tetsuji at all
since last night, either.
Don't worry about Tetsuji.
Even a bear couldn't kill him.
The guys will be fine,
but I'm worried about Ms. Mizuno.
We should...
split up into two pairs and gather more food
and find Ms. Mizuno.
Yeah.
Let's plan on meeting back
at this spot in two hours.
I'll look after the fire, so have fun!
You're coming too!
Yayoi...
Yayoi.
Where did you go?
Yayoi!
No, please stop!
Why are you?
No!
Stop!
Let me go!
No, stop!
Stop!
No!
Wait, maybe she's still there!
Stop, I'm tired!
I'm exhausted too.
Don't be such a wimp.
I can't walk anymore.
What is it?
Look, Kyoko!
What could this be?
It looks like some kind of hut.
Maybe somebody lives in it.
Excuse me!
Is anybody home?
Maybe it's abandoned.
But it looks like it's being used.
That means there might be food here!
Right!
There's lots of nuts in here!
Kyoko, look, there's food over here, too.
We did it!
See, there's potatoes, and dried fish.
What about...
Wow, it's canned food!
There's so much food, let's go get everyone!
Whoa, it's you two.
Mr. Kubo!
Good. I'm glad at least two
of you are safe.
Progress, at last.
We at least found Mr. Kubo,
and enough food for everyone for a while.
We heard about the man
that owns this cottage...
and the horrible event
that occurred last night.
I couldn't stop shaking for a few hours.
So, do you know what happened
to Ms. Mizuno?
Don't know.
I thought I might possibly find her
here, but...
I'm worried about the others.
That creepy guy is still wandering
the forest, right?
They might be in danger!
We have food now,
so let's bring the others over here.
Yeah, we should go.
Yes, but Kyoko should stay here.
Shiori should be able to find them...
but I'm going to need your help here.
Sure.
I can't do this!
I just can't walk anymore.
What?
At this rate, we're all going to starve
to death out here.
Hey, cheer up.
Hunkering down isn't going to
solve anything.
Wait!
Yuko, was it Mr. Kubo?
No, but it was a person, for sure!
Excuse me, please wait!
We got lost during that horrible storm
several days ago, and...
I thought...
you might have enough food
to share with us.
Not on me,
but I do have some in my cabin.
So you must live close to here?
And if I did?
Could you call the local police for us,
so we can get help?
Unfortunately, the phone lines are out.
I can't call for help.
I understand.
I can give you some food, though.
Will you, really?
But...
only if you agree to help me
with my experiment.
What experiment?
It won't take too long.
Follow me.
No thank you.
Hey wait, I have something here.
You must be hungry.
No, that's all right.
Don't worry, it's not poison.
It's a stimulant derived
from the nectar of a plant.
It'll give you energy.
See, it's not poison.
This is all I have,
but it should be enough for you.
Here, take this with you, okay?
Just come by the cabin
if you change your mind.
It's near the waterfall, you can't miss it.
Is it okay?
- It's sweet.
- Really?
Akemi, have some.
Wait, make sure you don't spill it!
Let me have some more!
What about the others?
There isn't enough for everyone,
so we'll just have to finish it off.
I agree.
Tickles!
It's all gone.
We can go look for that old man's cabin?
No, he was a creepy bastard.
You're right, he'll probably
do weird things to us.
I bet it's probably a trick
to lure helpless women.
I'm scared!
We won't fall for that one!
What the hell happened here?
What did this?
As you can see...
You are?
I see!
So, it finally happened, I can't believe it!
You aren't exhibiting any side effects,
like skin rashes.
It has not affected your beautiful body!
This is beyond my wildest expectations!
What did you do to my body?
Why does it matter now?
There is no way to reverse the changes.
Tell me!
Tell me now!
Why can't you reverse the changes?
I never imagined such perfect results!
Result?
Is this another crazy experiment of yours?
Correct.
I'll oblige, since you insist.
The Garanta has succeeded
in genetically merging with you.
The Garanta evolved,
and it became more than a plant.
It just needed a highly intelligent animal...
I needed to merge it with a human.
However, that was not a simple task.
The Garanta genes are extremely dominant.
It quickly overpowered the hosts'
genes and took over.
Every single test subject...
suffered from severe side effects,
and died from shock.
You are my first successful outcome.
You are proof that my theory was accurate!
Your DNA was suitable for the Garanta.
It's an honor.
You are now the ultimate biological weapon!
This isn't over just yet, mind you!
This is only the beginning.
As a biological organism,
you need to reproduce.
As you can see...
the first generation Garanta
has completed its job.
Yes, now it is your turn.
Your progeny will descend
upon this planet...
and completely conquer
the miserable human race!
Stop it!
What are you doing, Akemi?
Stop!
Here!
Take this!
I'll get you!
I've been feeling really strange.
I'm tingling deep down inside there,
and I'm feeling very horny.
Me too, and I can't take it anymore.
Let's do it!
Yes, let's.
Yes, Yuko!
It feels so good!
Wait.
What is it, Akemi?
I'm not comfortable doing it in the water.
Come over here, Yuko.
Where did you learn
to be so sexy and seductive?
Not telling.
Naughty girl!
Just like that!
More, lick harder!
Yes!
I love it, Yuko.
I don't think I can take this much longer!
Yes!
So, does this feel good, Akemi?
Yes, yes!
Louder, I want to hear you!
God, you make me feel so good!
I think I'm going to come!
Yes, I'm going to come hard, too!
Akemi, come, come for me, come with me!
I see.
The hot stud decided to show up!
So, are you just going
to stand there like that?
Well...
I was looking.
Look at his face, Akemi.
Just like a deer in headlights.
He does!
I'd bet he's been watching us
have fun all this time.
How rude of him.
I'll leave you two alone!
Wait a minute.
You really want to join us, right?
We honestly don't mind at all, you know.
Stop it, don't fuck with me.
Now, don't be a party pooper.
I know you want me.
It's so obvious.
Here, you can do what you want
to my body.
Yuko, why?
Say something?
What's gotten into you?
Nothing's wrong.
Let's have some fun.
I'm not stupid.
Here Tetsuji, I have a treat!
Stop it!
Don't play me for a fucking fool, damn it.
Is he okay?
Tetsuji, I thought you wanted me
for a long time?
You bitch, I did. Damn!
Wow, that was quick.
See, guys just suck.
I'm hungry again.
We were supposed to be looking for
food and Ms. Mizuno.
In that case, let's look
for that creepy guy's cabin.
Yeah, he did say that he would
give us some food.
This is unbelievable.
Her powers are just amazing!
Yes, rage is good!
Anger is going to be the fuel
for your new power!
You're going to kill me?
You idiot, that won't help you!
We still don't know
what's going to happen to you!
How are you going to live on your own?
No, listen to me!
Ms. Mizuno!
Do I look like Ms. Mizuno to you?
It's just you.
Yeah, it's just me.
I see. The hot stud decided
to show up!
Yuko and Akemi are late.
I've been waiting for them forever.
A weird old man lives around here.
He kidnaps women, so I'm worried.
I saw them earlier.
Where?
On the lake shore.
Were they okay?
I thought they were acting
kind of strange.
Were they acting really horny?
You could say that.
No!
What if Mr. Kubo was telling the truth?
Now it's not just Ms. Mizuno.
What?
Damn him, why do I have to do this
kind of shit?
What an asshole.
Mr. Kubo!
You're eating all of the canned food.
Idiot, I'm not eating all of the canned food!
You don't have to get so pissed off.
That creepy old guy could come back here.
I need strength to protect you.
All right, I believe you.
I'll leave the water here.
You want some of this?
What do you think?
If you give me some...
I won't tell the others you ate most of it.
Good, we have a deal, but first...
But first?
You'll let me sample your body, too.
What?
Well...
What now?
What about Ms. Mizuno?
She'll never know!
Mr. Kubo!
Okay, I'll do it.
Don't be so rough.
That's a good girl.
Food won't be the only thing
you'll swallow today.
Suck on it baby, I know you're hungry.
I'm sorry, Ms. Mizuno!
That's very good.
That's right, keep sucking my hard cock.
Yeah, just like that.
Shit, I'm going to come!
Yeah, I want you to come inside my mouth!
You'll have plenty to swallow.
Hurry, I want to taste you!
Do you like it?
Yummy, thank you.
But, I'm just getting started.
I want more.
Damn it, you selfish little girl.
Tatsuya.
What wrong, you want it, right?
But, this is embarrassing.
Shut up and spread them wide.
Like this?
That's perfect.
Why are you making me do this?
Men need a break
before we can get hard again.
How lame!
Just shut up and spread your pussy more.
You pervert, do you make Ms. Mizuno
do this kind of thing?
What?
I'll put you in your place, girl.
Not like this!
That's a nice view.
Stop it, you sick bastard!
No!
That's it, I can't wait anymore.
Not yet.
Give me!
Then tell me do you want!
Fuck me!
With what?
Your cock!
Where do you want my hard cock?
Put it in there.
Put it in where?
My pussy!
Shove it deep in my wet pussy!
You are such a dirty slut.
Don't make me wait, please.
I want it!
You asked for it.
God, this feels amazing, yes!
Yeah, keep doing that, keep going!
My god!
Now fuck me harder, much harder!
Yeah!
More!
Good, I'll come with you!
Yeah, I'm coming, now!
Ms. Mizuno!
Having fun, my Tatsuya?
I can explain everything, Yayoi.
Don't bother, because it doesn't bother me
to see you have fun.
So, would you mind if I joined you two?
Ms. Mizuno?
I hope you don't mind?
I don't know...
Let's have lots of fun.
Right, Tatsuya?
Yayoi.
Ms. Mizuno!
God!
I'm losing my mind!
Ms. Mizuno!
I've never felt so good!
You're the best, baby.
No baby, you're the best.
Thank you, Tatsuya!
So this is what it looks like.
I've never seen it this close!
What is this?
Ms. Mizuno?
No!
Stop!
Please, don't kill me!
You don't need to be afraid.
I already got what I wanted from him.
I do have a special gift for you.
Will you accept?
No!
Don't!
What was that noise?
That sounded like Kyoko!
Let's go!
Kyoko!
Ms. Mizuno!
Is everything okay?
Get out, run Akemi!
Yuko!
Akemi!
Ms. Mizuno, your pussy tastes
like that nectar.
Akemi, no, get out of here!
Akemi!
Ms. Mizuno?
Shiori, I haven't found Yuko or Akemi.
What's up?
I heard Ms. Mizuno's voice.
Hey! Wait up!
She isn't here.
Let's keep looking.
What's wrong?
For some reason,
I thought she would be here.
Why?
Ms. Mizuno adores white flowers.
I thought...
- What the...
- An earthquake!
- Let's run!
- But, Ms. Mizuno!
Just run fast!
Shiori, run!
No, stop!
Please!
Stop, Ms. Mizuno!
Ms. Mizuno, why are you doing this to me?
Shiori, that's not Ms. Mizuno!
You monster!
Ms. Mizuno, I really liked you!
No!
Stop, stop!
What did I ever do to you!
Here, put this on.
We both made it, Tetsuji!
Yeah.
Let's go.
We've located
a mummified body, male!
Three bodies, all female.
The female bodies are nude,
and covered in strange rashes.
Approximate time of death within 4 hours.
Team 2 here!
We've found 2 bodies,
one of unknown origin, and one human.
Sex, female.
We've located another body,
male, possible owner of the motorcycle.
We've found a survivor, young female!
Looking for identification.
The Garanta has survived!
It survives inside that girl now!