Who are you?
I'd like to see your experiment.
What?
Is this it?
No...
W-Woman...
W-What are you doing?
If you do that...
No...
This is the bioborg you created
through genetic engineering...
It is the strongest soldier ever made.
I see...
It's fucking powerful.
No...
No!
Stop it!
You only think about sex.
No!
N-No!
At this rate...
Stop this!
If this continues...
W-What is this?
Incredible.
A sex beast...
I'm afraid I've created a crazed monster.
This is a profane act before God's eyes!
What I did was...
A man cannot become God...
...though he may become a devil.
Good...
Incredible.
I'm so horny...
Come inside...
So good...
More...
Harder!
So good...
Come!
Inside of me!
Anne?
Boss.
Sounds like your mission is completed.
Yes.
I just finished off
that counterfeiter, Lee.
I've already disposed of
all the counterfeit securities.
The damage to the
national treasury is minimal.
Good job.
I wish you could take a break
and enjoy Hong Kong tonight, but...
Priority command, right?
National Security Code Level 4.
Level 4!
I'll call Layla and Shion.
I'll need Q Section's help.
Roger, I'll go back right away.
Sweet...
Very, very hot...
It's up to my bellybutton!
I'm coming!
I'm...
l-I'm coming!
Roger, Boss
Sorry, I can't take care of you.
The CIA will take care of you for me.
You might as well
confess who the contact is...
...for that hacker who got into
the Pentagon's information network.
They're not gentle like me.
Très bien, you're so artistic.
Go ahead, keep your dick inside...
Hello?
Shion?
Understood.
H-Hey!
What the hell?
I wish you could've come
before being arrested, but I have to go.
I admit your false
bank notes are artistic...
...but you shouldn't cause
trouble for the government.
Everybody here?
I'm glad to see you all again.
Oh, that's quite a surprise.
What is it?
We didn't think that
you worried about us.
Right?
You always say you
don't care if we lose our lives...
...while on duty,
because we're your women.
I don't forget my manners for anyone.
Please don't worry about us, Boss.
Just give us the orders.
As expected of a lady in Q Section.
Here's the scenario...
The Defense Department hired a private
company to secretly develop a cyborg...
...what we call the Bioborg
Project, but someone stole it.
They're very skillful.
They must be pros.
The experimental
cyborg's name is Dragon...
But it was also known as
the "sex beast" at the facility.
Sex beast?
A failure in the gene manipulation...
...caused the cyborg to have
an uncontrollable desire for sex.
It's a monster that
continually rapes women.
The government assigned us
to dispose of the Bioborg Project.
You got it?
If it is discovered that the cyborg
was developed as a military weapon...
Or, if somebody discovers that
the mutation created a sex beast...
...the government will be
criticized all over the world.
And lose the world's confidence.
Listen, Q Section!
Find the kidnappers, and get rid
of them along with the sex beast!
Yes, sir!
S-Stop!
No!
The sex beast is an
unsatiable serial rapist...
How can he control himself?
That's the point.
Layla, locate all incidents
of rape during the last two days.
Okay.
No good!
It's impossible,
there's too much data!
You're so useless.
What was that?
This is no time to quarrel.
We should ask a professional.
Stop it, Dragon!
Not here.
Good boy.
Follow me, and I'll get women for you.
W-Women!
Women!
G-Good Dragon.
You're the best!
Excuse me, Mister,
may I ask you something?
This is my question...
Talk afterwards.
I'm so horny 'cause somebody
took my woman last night.
We know you make a
business out of raping women.
What do you mean,
somebody took your woman?
It's for your own
good to tell us everything.
Y-You're police?
Unfortunately not.
They'd be a lot more gentle.
Hurry up, or I'll break your neck!
I-It happened...
...last night in Yokohama.
We took a woman as usual...
Fuck her, video tape her, and threaten her...
That was the plan.
No...
Stop!
But if that...
If that monster hadn't have shown up...
Monster?
Y-Yeah.
How's that?
Feel good?
If you don't want us to show this
embarrassing video, just do what we say.
Please, let me go...
No way!
You're our slave!
Thank you so much.
What the fuck?
That woman is ours!
Are you ignoring me?
Are you listening?
It's a monster!
Fuck, they saw!
I've never seen an animal like that.
We're tough, but even we ran away.
No...
Stop!
Unbelievable.
How can they keep
doing one after another?
Bottomless desire...
Maybe the sex beast
was originally a human.
This is the last one.
Found it!
Please, let me go...
No way!
You're our slave!
Are you ignoring me?
Stop.
Seems like this is the one.
It looks like the sex beast is evolving.
It's a monster!
Rewind a little!
Okay.
Stop.
Vanessa Hammer.
What?
She specializes in
stealing top secret information...
...and selling it to whomever she can.
A radical nonpolitical terrorist.
I'm sure.
I can tell the
technique is definitely hers.
Mister...
Don't you know them?
No, I don't.
Oh, that's too bad.
If you had told me,
I would've given you a special surprise.
No!
Shut up!
S-Stop it...
We have a right to fuck, too.
We can't stand just
watching the beast fuck everyday.
Could it be...
This bimbo is so wet.
All clear.
The sex beast!
Vanessa, too!
I found them.
In a cargo ship at Yokohama Port.
Babe, what are you doing?
Don't give us trouble.
You know we're private eyes.
Yeah, right!
Shit!
The bitch!
She's something!
Here she is!
Come here.
Shit...
W-Woman...
T-The sex beast...
N-No!
Stop!
Dragon, stop it.
You can enjoy her later.
Layla!
Layla, what happened?
Find her?
She must've been caught by Vanessa.
Really.
I hope she's as smart now as
when she's using a computer.
Which cargo ship?
This is Layla's...
She's cute.
V-Vanessa!
Knowing my name
means you're a Japanese agent.
I figured you would
start to investigate soon.
Who could've
expected such a pretty girl?
Wonderful.
All right.
Enjoy her as much as you want.
N-No!
Stay away!
W-Woman...
No!
S-Stop...
Your body is responding
in spite of what you say.
Tell me the truth or
you'll end up like him.
Is Vanessa on this ship?
Won't you tell me, please?
Thanks.
This must be it.
So good...
It's so good, Dragon.
If you follow me, you can
fuck women all over the world.
Who's there?
What's wrong?
W-Who the fuck are you?
Shion!
It seems like your
friends have shown up.
Anne...
Shion...
Layla!
No!
Don't come!
Shit.
Vanessa!
It looks like some more
responsive ladies are here.
If you fuck this, you'll
feel good beyond description.
It's time to leave.
Let's get out of here!
Vanessa!
Don't you realize?
The sex beast is too
dangerous to control.
I don't care.
It's just one more
piece of merchandise to me.
The sex beast only has
desire for sex and destruction.
If he loses control, you won't be safe!
Your advice is useless!
He is my slave!
You'll die here!
After my cute sex beast rapes you.
He's out of control.
He's finally a complete sex beast.
Why?
If you follow me, you can...
Layla...
Layla!
Too late.
Layla...
Why did you have to
die in this awful place?
Let's go.
Layla's death shouldn't be meaningless.
Anne...
Come on.
This vessel will be under the
control of the sex beast soon.
He'll drown with the ship.
But, we can't explode it in Tokyo Bay.
Leave it to me.
When the ship sails into the Pacific
Ocean, every single bomb will explode.
I'm sure that'll sink the ship.
All set.
It'll be completed after
I attach it to the gas tank.
Okay, let's go.
Anne!
Shion!
Go!
Finish this...
Kill the beast!
Shion...
Hurry up!
You have no time...
Layla, I'll be joining you in heaven...
The last magazine.
M-Monster...
This is the end...
Shion...
Layla...
I-I can't die here...
Damn it...
One last bullet.
But the gun isn't enough to kill him.
What should I...
What should I do?
For the sake of those
two deaths, I have to win!
Shion...
I'll carry out the mission.
Layla...
I'm coming to see you!