Who? Let me go!
Stop!
Somebody! Please!
No, stop it!
Don't!
Stop, please!
Fuck me like you used to.
No!
Stop!
Please don't!
Don't!
School of Darkness
Coming!
Who is it?
Me.
Yuko!
What happened to you?
I'm sorry to bother you so late.
Yeah, come inside.
Yuko, what happened?
It's Taki.
You broke up with him.
I'll talk to him for you.
No, Ayano. This is my problem.
I'll take care of it.
But...
I was such a fool to waste my time
on the bastard.
Besides, it's my problem.
Yuko.
This is the ancient scroll?
A professor asked me to work on this,
but it's going to take time.
And this?
The box came with the dagger.
It stinks!
What does the scroll say about it?
I don't know the details yet.
According to the legend...
it was sliced off from a demon.
The weapon used to exterminate
the demon was that dagger.
So, what was this demon, really?
We might know, once we analyze
that sample.
I'm a biologist, I can do it for you.
Thank you, that would help me out!
I'll work on it after school for you.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
My students don't have to worry about me.
But Ayano told me...
I know.
Tell your older sister I'm fine.
Tell her not to worry.
Okay.
Wait, it that the box with the mummified
demon part?
That's right.
Can I please see it?
Sure, but it might be too graphic for you.
It reeks!
It looks like a weird penis!
I'll see you later.
It was fucking awesome.
She's on the track team,
so she had a nice ass.
You did her, too?
That's right.
But I thought you were seeing a girl?
See, that's why you're still
a goddamned virgin.
You've got to take every chance you get.
Sex isn't fast food.
Don't you get the urge to fuck Reika
when you're alone with her?
Of course I do.
She's 17, so she's got to be curious
about fucking by now.
You have to take the lead to get the pussy.
Take the lead!
Yeah.
I'm going to get me some action.
What action?
Koji, don't give him any ideas.
Why would I?
You left your umbrella here, Reika.
Stop it! Let go!
Come on, don't be such a bitch.
You've fucked me before.
Go away!
I just want to make you come
like you used to.
You know you want it.
It looks like you got yourself a toy.
Let's have some fun with it?
No!
Wait up, Reika!
What are you so pissed off about?
When I said I was going to...
Get some action! You jerk, you pervert!
Let me explain.
Reika!
My umbrella!
Rain?
You had it with you after class.
I forgot it!
There's no need to struggle,
you'll want me soon enough.
Stop it!
Stop it, or I'll scream!
I dare you to do it.
You'll just embarrass yourself.
Your pussy should be wet by now.
Right, Yuko?
No! Go away!
No, let go of me, no!
She was getting what she wanted.
I wouldn't say anything if I were you.
Act like you didn't see anything.
Ms. Tsudo?
Go away!
Promise me that you won't
say anything to Ayano.
Yes.
Now, please leave me alone!
What the...
So, you're not pissed off at me right?
I just can't believe I lost my umbrella.
You're not acting like yourself.
Reika?
What is it, Naoto?
Stop acting like a jerk, and get off me!
Come on.
No!
Stop it, Naoto!
You're a fucking bastard!
He's such an asshole.
Shit!
Yuko!
What do you want?
I want your cock.
Will you fuck me?
I knew it. Get in.
Thanks.
Yuko, you like my cock?
Polish it.
Yeah!
Goddamn.
God, yeah!
Yuko.
I'm coming!
Fuck!
Yuko, I can't anymore.
It's sucking me dry!
A grotesque demon appeared...
and entered the body of a maiden.
The beast will overpower her spirit...
and this maiden shall become
a shell for the beast.
The beast shall use her body to feast
on the life force of men.
The people greatly feared this beast,
and called it the Lust-demon.
Hello, this is Ayano speaking.
Hi, Reika.
What's wrong?
Nothing, really.
What is it?
I'm calling about Ms. Tsudo.
How is she?
Fine. Is Yuko all right?
It's nothing, really.
She wanted to talk to you about the mummy.
I was planning to call her later
about that, anyway.
Good. Well, then good night!
Lust-demon.
Does this have anything
to do with the mummy?
Where is Ms. Tsudo?
She took the day off for an emergency.
Thank you.
Maybe.
She had on sexy panties.
It means she's interested.
Hi, Reika!
Look, Koji just got his ear pierced!
What a freak!
Reika?
So, did you guys get into a fight?
Of course not.
My god!
I just heard this!
Mr. Taki's missing!
Are you serious?
That means it's study hall instead of P.E.
The school has filed
a missing persons report.
But, he's still missing, though.
That's a lie!
Ms. Tsudo's missing.
What about Ms. Tsudo?
Nothing.
I hope she's really all right.
You've reached my answering machine.
Just leave me a message after the beep,
and I'll call you right back.
Yuko, where the hell are you?
Call me back as soon as you get home,
it's important.
Call me.
Check out that hottie!
Is that one of our teachers?
Hey, isn't that Ms. Tsudo?
My god!
Good morning, everyone.
Today's topic is proteins.
I'll explain the chemical structure
of proteins.
I'll also explain the chemical process behind
the breakdown and assimilation of proteins.
She's changed so much.
She's next.
You're fucking crazy, she's a teacher!
Why let age and jobs get in the way?
Yeah, but...
That's one hot pussy I've got to sample.
You'll see. She'll be riding my cock.
If that's what you want, go for it.
Time to go!
Class dismissed.
Next week, we will be in the lab.
Can I speak to you in private?
Sure, step inside.
What is it, Reika?
About the other day...
Don't worry about it.
I'm doing just fine.
Are you sure?
But, that was horrible.
This is perfect.
Can you do me a favor?
Hello.
Hi, Ayano.
Where have you been?
I wanted to tell you what I've found
out about the demon.
Yuko, are you there?
Hello?
Hello, can you hear me?
I want you out of my life.
What happened to you?
Wait, Yuko!
You didn't have to rip the cord out!
Ayano will get in the way...
of what's about to happen...
between you and me.
I have to go now.
Do you have a minute, Ms. Tsudo?
What is it?
I had some questions about the lecture.
All right, Koji.
I'll be happy to help you.
Lucky!
My, is this for me?
Ms. Tsudo!
Stop, don't make me come yet.
Your cock is so hard.
Do you want more?
Yeah!
Come here, and lick my wet pussy.
Yes ma'am!
She ripped the telephone cord out?
That's a bit extreme.
Ms. Tsudo and my sister have been
best friends for so long.
What she said on the phone,
it's not like her!
She did change. She's acting all sexy!
And, she really scares me now.
Maybe she's got multiple personalities.
Naoto, I saw...
What now?
Getting hot and heavy?
We were just talking.
If you say so. Have you seen Koji?
Koji, not since class ended.
He's gone.
Damn it! He was supposed to attend
the meeting after school today!
I think I saw him as I was leaving
Ms. Tsudo's office.
So he was serious about fucking her!
Like she'll let him! No way!
Ms. Tsudo...
Your pussy's so tight!
I'll show you the meaning of pleasure!
God!
I'm about to come!
It's sucking me dry!
Hey, Koji!
Koji, where are you!
Are you in here?
Get away from me?
Ms. Tsudo, stop!
Please don't!
Get off of me, no!
Let go of me now!
You're in for a real treat.
Yeah, I love it!
This is the best sex I've ever had!
Please, don't stop!
Just like that!
Yes, I'm coming!
Yeah!
I can't hold on!
Yes!
Wait!
Not yet!
No, wait!
This isn't the right girl.
Reika, the virgin, will have our child!
Reika, your body will soon be all mine!
What? Taki raped her with the mummy?
I should have told you sooner.
Yuko started acting strange the next day.
Yeah, she was trying
to get rid of that creep, Taki.
Don't worry about this, Reika.
I'll take care of it, so get some sleep.
The police found a vehicle...
that was later identified as the car of Mr.
Shuuichi Taki, 26 year-old.
A mummified body has been found
inside the car.
Police have started a formal investigation
of this case.
Taki, a mummy...
Demon.
I think she has already left for the day.
She's not answering her office extension.
Could I leave a message for a student there?
The school closed early today.
I'm really sorry, but I can't do it.
You've been quiet all day today,
what's wrong?
Strange things have happened.
Ms. Tsudo's acting weird, the police found
a mummy, and Koji's disappeared now.
I thought maybe all these cases are related.
Koji probably flaked out or just forgot.
Can't be.
I really hope so.
Reika!
Ms. Tsudo...
she really wants to talk to you today.
Ms. Tsudo?
I think you should go talk to her.
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding.
I think it would help, you'll feel a bit better.
You think so?
I'll go with you.
Yuko, are you home? I'm coming in.
Yuko!
What is this smell?
She's been possessed by the demon!
The demon will grow inside the maiden.
It uses the life force of men to serve
as its nourishment.
The victims will all wither and die.
I know!
Thank you for coming, Reika.
Ms. Tsudo, where is Koji?
He's right here.
Koji!
Did you do this to him?
Now, don't be so scared.
You won't end up like him.
What has gotten into you?
I'm having a baby.
Baby?
I need your virgin body for my baby
to develop in.
This is crazy!
Reika!
This is complete madness! Stop!
Come over here and have fun with us.
Stop!
Damn, not again!
Naoto!
Ayano!
Where is Reika?
Ms. Tsudo wanted to talk to her at school.
What? Yuko!
What's going on?
Get in!
Hurry!
Okay.
A Lust-demon?
You're joking, right?
I don't want to believe it.
But I saw it!
There were mummies of men all
over Yuko's apartment.
You think Ms. Tsudo's...
The demon has possessed her.
Why does she need Reika?
To reproduce.
The scroll says that the demon needs
to impregnate a virgin.
Then, Reika's in trouble!
Yes!
That was good, Reika.
Ms. Tsudo!
What is that thing?
No!
Yuko!
Reika!
Let go of Reika, right now!
Yuko, put those kids down right now!
Shit! Take this!
Reika!
Reika, are you okay?
Ayano, since you're here,
I'll show you the ultimate pleasure.
You're not Yuko anymore!
What can you do about it?
I'll kill you!
Take this!
Freak!
Ayano, fire!
Ayano.
Help me, I'm burning!
Yuko!
Yuko, get up, Yuko.
I don't know if I'll make it.
It's all over now.
You'll make it.
I won't.
Yuko, you have to hang on!
Stop!
That disgusting demon violated
my body, Naoto!
It's okay.
I still love you, Reika.
Naoto.
Reika.
Naoto, please be gentle.
Wait, not there.
Yeah.
Naoto.
I'm ready.
Reika, can I?
Will you please come inside me!
Yeah!
I'm coming!
I did it!
Five Years Later
I'm your new instructor for this class.
Call me Ms. Reika.
I teach biology.
It's nice to meet all of you!