Fixed star diary, space calender 996.5.
After the research duty of
newly found mineral at Planet Kerun...
...we received an SOS
signal from cargo ship Zogne.
We were heading to
rescue the survivors right away...
There was no visible
damage on the Zogne's body, but...
...we had no response from the crew.
We had no clue
what had happened inside.
It's very quiet here.
Too quiet.
It's like a ghost ship...
Hikari, how's the air quality?
Oxygen rate is normal, internal
operation system is normal, too.
Well then, no need for this
goofy space suit anymore.
No, we don't know
if this area is safe yet.
Hilda is right.
Watch out everyone.
Hilda, Kieth, Annie and Lindo...
...you guys continue
searching for the survivors.
Hikari and Yuri, you two work
on the main computer system.
Something must
have happened in this ship!
Sara, this is like haunted house.
It's so creepy.
I want to leave now!
Keep your squeaky voice down
and check out the cargo room!
Who do you think you are...
I can't take any more!
Is she alive?
No, raise the body.
What is this bruise?
It doesn't look like something natural.
Besides, what is this sticky liquid?
It's only on the women's bodies.
I can't take it anymore!
Everybody's dead!
Cut it out, what are you, six?
Come on.
We haven't checked
the other half of the ship.
No, no, I won't go anywhere!
What the hell...
Lindo, you can go
back to the docking gate.
Let's go.
No, this person is no good, too...
Really...
Maybe there isn't a single survivor.
What happened here...
Oh, it's a capsule...
This is...
Yuri...
What?
Where did it come from?
It's terrible!
It's just like embryo in a bag.
It's too awful...
Hikari, Yuri, come here.
There's a survivor
in the cold sleep room.
Really?
Let's go.
It's a girl.
Her name is...
Flair Mytomeyer...
Is this girl alive?
Yes.
She is very beautiful...
Bring her to ICU now!
What the hell have
happened to the Zogne...
The girl we saved from
the Zogne is now conscious...
...and she has stabilized, but
she is suffering from amnesia.
What?
She has no memory at all?
Yes.
She doesn't even remember
her own name is Flair Mytomeyer.
What a poor girl...
So she doesn't know what
happened to the Zogne then?
Right...
Well that sucks!
At least she's happy!
Look who's talking.
Remember who was weeping
like a baby a few hours ago?
Hilda, you keep an eye
on that girl's condition.
Hikari, you analyze the
disk we got from the ship.
I actually for a while, but it
seems to be password protected.
No way!
The Zogne is just
regular cargo ship, isn't it?
That sounds like...
...they had some kind of special
task from the government, just like us.
That's true!
I am sure they were after something...
Oh, I found a capsule
of Metrogria in Zogne.
What!
Could it be?
Metrogria is synthetic destroyer
of regenerative cell systems, isn't it?
Production of it has also been banned.
Let's keep it in here.
Then, is that the cause of the
death of the Zogne's crew members?
No, it's not.
Death from Metrogria is very different.
So you mean...
Hilda, you keep it, ok?
Yes.
My command is to destroy the Zogne
after releasing the connection to our ship.
What?
But, we still haven't found out
what happened on the Zogne yet.
To uncover the cause of
their death is not our main task.
But as the captain, the safety of all my
crew members is my top responsibility.
But we might still find
more survivors in there.
Absolutely!
There are humans there!
Let me go and search one more time!
It's not like you at all!
I am so touched, boo hoo!
Excuse me, but I am a humanist,
not a meat head like yourself!
Captain.
After one hour of rest,
we will move out quickly.
The time we have
is two hours and a half.
It should be enough
for us to set the bomb.
Something is
strange about Captain Sara.
Don't you think so, Einstein?
She seems to be
little upset or even scared...
Usually the Captain would do
more research on this kind of incident.
It's not like her at all.
No, not again!
You always want to hide in there!
No, it tickles!
Einstein!
What are you doing?
Good timing Yuri, help me here.
Look what you're doing, shame on you!
B-But, it's because
Einstein got in my bra again!
Einstein!
Close the door!
Whoops, it was too late...
Now that he's out he
will be impossible to catch!
Sorry...
You are more passionate than usual...
What's on your mind?
I can't hide anything from you.
I heard something before
and it's still bothering me.
I hope nothing bad will happen...
How is Flair's condition?
She's the same.
No, not there..
It's so good, I love you Sara.
I love you too, Hilda.
Let me do it now,
I'll make you forget everything.
Oh, no...
Hi there, Flair.
My name is Annie.
It's so sad,
you don't remember anything.
What beautiful hair you have.
I can be your special friend.
Are you there, Einstein?
Where the hell are you?
Einstein, come out, Einstein!
Annie?
Have you seen Einstein arou--
Hey, you Einstein, come here now!
Or I will punish you!
Here you are, I was looking all over!
Hey, you're shaking.
Don't worry, I won't punish you.
We were still searching for the survivors,
even after all the explosives were set.
But all we found was room after
room of cruel, creepy dead bodies.
The ship was just
like a haunted ghost ship.
Okay, it's done.
How are you doing, Annie?
Annie!
What's wrong, Annie?
Everyone, come over here.
Something's wrong with Annie!
Annie!
It's terrible...
It's just like the Zogne's crew...
I can't believe it...
Sara, Annie is dead.
We don't know for sure...
...but the cause of death it seems
like whatever got the Zogne's crew.
What?
Everyone, return
to the Muse right away.
What about Annie's body?
Leave it there.
What?
Hurry up!
In twenty minutes,
we must detonate the Zogne.
Fixed star diary.
To protect our crew member's
safety and to destroy the Metrogria...
...we detonated the Zogne...
Our crew and I went
back to our normal lives.
But the fact is that we are all
still in shock from Annie's death.
Hey, you are working out really hard.
Maybe I can entertain you a little.
You want to get rid
of some stress, right?
Looking at your face makes me sick!
Oooh, that's scary,
that's why I hate butch types.
Your type never has a sense of humor.
Sorry.
I really have to work on this disc code.
I will play with you in a little while.
No, Einstein!
Did you see Flair?
No, is there anything wrong?
She stepped out when I
turned my back for a minute.
I hope she will return soon.
I will inform you if I see her.
Please do...
Excuse me...
I like that.
You are really pretty.
Don't make fun of me like that.
Your hair is getting long.
Let me do your haircut next time.
Oh no, Einstein!
Einstein!
Where are you?
Where did you go?
Einstein!
Hey, I found you Einstein.
Don't make me so worried.
Here, I got you!
What is this?
T-This is Metrogria!
Why is it here?
Who put it here?
Oh, it's you Flair.
What are you doing here?
Hilda was looking for you.
Oh, I am sorry.
Hey, be a good boy!
Since when did you
become such a bad boy, Einstein?
Sorry...
Uh, Flair?
Who's there?
Flair?
Why are you here?
You got lost or something?
I will call Hilda for you.
Why couldn't I move when I saw Flair?
Besides that, why Einstein
also got upset when he saw Flair?
Why is Metrogria on the ship?
I need to translate the disk.
Which one of us would
bring Metrogria onto the ship?
What's wrong, Hikari?
Nothing, I was just
wondering what happened to her...
Who?
Oh, Flair came back to medical
center and is sleeping like a baby now.
Um, isn't she hungry at all?
You are pretty concerned
about her, is she your type?
I just have
something I'm worried about...
See, you do care about her...
Hikari, how are you doing
with the translation of the disk?
It's not done yet.
I can't handle this by
myself so I asked for Elle's help.
Also Captain...
Can we talk later?
You look pale, Kieth.
Are you sick?
You are always the first
one to come for the meal.
It's once in a blue
moon that you aren't here...
Kieth?
Kieth, what's wrong?
Are you--
What's really going on with you, Kieth...
Take her to the medical room for now.
What happened to Kieth anyway?
I have no idea...
How's Flair doing?
Nothing special.
But after she went out
yesterday, she looked little tired.
I suppose she is
not fully recovered yet.
Well, it's time to take
care of another patient.
Will this help?
When Kieth wakes up,
she's going to go wild again.
What did you want
to talk about with Sara?
There is Metrogria on this ship!
No kidding!
I saw it in the cargo room.
I'm positive.
But, who brought it in here...
I have no idea...
Hikari...
I finished the
translation of the Zogne's data.
Thank you Elle, I am on my way.
Now that should answer our questions!
I will inform Sara about this,
you go the computer room first.
Okay!
Come with me!
K-Kieth, what's going on?
Unbelievable!
Hilda, is there a gun here?
It's in the drawer.
I will draw her attention.
You get the gun.
I can't!
Hilda, the gun, get the gun...
No, no...
Kieth, stop it, Kieth...
The gun is in the drawer...
Kieth, stop it now or I'll have to...
Kieth...
Kieth, why did this happen...
What?
Flair, was that you...
Kieth, Annie and the Zogne's crew...
Did you kill them all, Flair?
What the hell is this?
No way...
Elle, give me the data on the Zogne.
We, the Zogne, were waiting for
contact from another space ship, the Muse.
The Metrogria had already
been moved from Fenkel.
But along the way we rescued it,
and our ship was turned into living hell.
It was some kind of monster.
It's a monster!
It is just like a parasite,
hatching eggs in other bodies.
The woman sucked the life from the male
crew members and grew into a monster.
Stop it, monster!
And then she laid her eggs in
the female crew member's bodies.
However, all of their bodies
rejected the eggs and ended up dying.
We must destroy her soon.
What?
I have to report to the Captain.
Stop!
Oh, no, no...
Sara, Hilda...
No!
If Sara and Hilda are in the medical
room, it's going to be big trouble.
I really have to tell
everybody about Flair!
What happened Yuri?
It's scary, there's a
monster in the medical room.
A monster?
And also Hilda...
It must be Flair.
Now she is showing her true nature.
And what happened to everybody...
I don't know...
I was chased by
tentacles and ran away...
Anyway, we must beat Flair.
Flair?
I'll explain later...
Now we have to beat Flair
and help Hilda and the others.
Let's go!
You always skip the important part...
How are you going to beat that thing?
It is definitely not a normal creature.
I don't know yet, but there must be
some kind of weapons in the cargo bay.
So, what you were saying
about the monster was?
Flair is the monster.
She killed the crew of the Zogne.
So if we don't terminate her...
Our ship will end up
just like the Zogne did.
Okay!
Ready?
I am ready.
I will open the door now.
All right.
What?
The monster and Hilda are gone...
What's going on?
Where did they go?
Someone's over there!
K-Kieth...
She's been shot.
Look, there's the mark on her belly...
Hilda, are you all right?
What are you doing?
Stop, Hilda!
Don't shoot!
Oxygen rate in residential
area, decreasing rapidly...
Einstein, keep your head inside!
Emergency outer wall,
residential area wall closing now...
Oxygen rate normal.
Why did it happen?
I won't forgive that Flair monster.
What happened to Hilda?
Let's go back to the bridge and ask Elle.
Elle, check all vital signs on the ship
Roger.
Results are on screen.
In D-2 cargo block, two vital
signs and in E-2 block, one vital sign.
Where should we go?
Lindo and Sara must be in D-2 block.
Okay, let's get there.
Elle, shut the
emergency doors as I instructed.
Understood.
Let's go!
We need to get extra
weapons on the way.
Here we go...
Sara, Lindo.
Captain, Lindo!
It sounds like Sara.
C-Captain, is that you?
S-Sara!
Your face!
That monster can't be
beaten by any weapon.
Escape from this ship now!
It's awful!
What the hell is that?
It must be Flair.
Eat this!
Now, run!
Elle, Lock up the
safety door on D block!
Lockdown completed.
That was close, thanks Elle.
This door can hold for a while.
Let's go now.
To where?
Lindo must be in E block.
After finding her,
we must escape from here.
What about Flair?
Sara, Hilda and Kieth,
everybody was killed by her.
I must destroy Flair.
But how?
What did Sara say?
No weapon can beat it.
There must be some way!
Let's go.
Hikari, hurry!
Is that you Lindo?
Shit!
Lindo, you are alive!
Hey guys, what are you doing here?
You didn't know
about the Captain and--
Don't move!
Lindo...
Have you also been...
What are you talking about?
You are not...
Wait, the place she is standing...
What's that?
This?
It's Metrogria.
So, you are the one who
brought it from the Zogne!
That's right!
Well, drop your guns.
Don't be a fool.
The monster's in our
ship and it killed everybody!
What monster?
You remember Flair, she is the monster.
She also killed the Zogne's crew!
Do you think I will buy such crap?
Don't fool with me!
It's true, believe us!
It's not a lie!
Well, if that's true, that
saves me from killing you all.
Drop your guns!
What are you going to do?
Just go back to the original plan.
Original plan?
I am taking over this ship and
waiting for the buyer of the Metrogria.
Are you going to take over the Muse?
I was freaked out about
what happened at Zogne.
The Muse was supposed to
send an SOS message to the Zogne...
...and they were going to take over
the Muse when we went to rescue them.
After all, our ship
belongs to the government.
That makes it easy to smuggle
this Metrogria over the border.
Do you have any idea how Metrogria
can be used to kill other people?
That's none of my business.
What?
I can't let you do it!
You don't do anything funny...
If you do, I'll...
What the hell is that?
It broke through the emergency door!
Monster, go to hell!
Stop, Flair!
Shit!
Take this!
It doesn't work at all!
Sara was right, let's get out of here.
Sister!
My leg...
I can't get it off, shit!
You can't, just leave me here.
No, I can't leave you!
Hikari...
I will save you...
Hikari, it's okay...
...you escape now.
Let her go!
I will get you free, I will...
If we can get out of the room, it
will be cut off by the edge of the door.
No...
Don't try to save
me, you just run away.
Hurry!
No, we have to go together!
I will save you, sis, I will!
I just have to save you.
Thank you, Hikari.
But you should just go without me...
I can't just leave here, I can't!
I will take you with me!
I'll definitely save you!
Hikari, go now!
Sis!
No!
Sister Yuri...
Sister...
I can't forgive you...
I'll never...
...forgive you.
I will destroy you!
Elle, open all the
safety doors in the hallway.
Opening now.
But, how am I going to fight with that?
There must be
something, something strong...
Let's see...
Yes, the Metrogria.
With this Metrogria...
To shoot this, I am going to
have to get close to the Alien.
When I beat it,
I will play with you again.
So, wait for me.
You wait for me, alien!
Here I am, alien.
You want me, right?
Fine, but I want my sister back now!
Lindo...
Where is Yuri?
What happened to Yuri?
You did your thing to the other girl?
Now you want to
do it to me, don't you?
Well, come here.
You are getting closer, almost there.
Now!
No!
Leave me, let me go!
What are you going to do?
No, no!
If I could just shoot it...
Einstein!
Captain, Kieth, Lindo,
Hilda and my sister's revenge!
Gotcha!
Come on, Einstein...
We must get out of here before
the Metrogria gets into the air.
I am sorry, sis.
Air level dropping, oxygen level
dropping, emergency door sealing...
Sister...
Who is it?
Sister!
You are alive!
Thank god!
Sister!