Beast City...
No one knows when they
started to call it that.
The Beast Clan had
settled into this city.
They tempted people with pleasure
to transform them into beasts.
As the Beast Clan numbers grow,
so do the city's citizens' fears.
But someone who has defied the
Beast Clan has come to this city...
Vampire Madonna.
Vampire Madonna is a huge threat
to the Beast Clan's existence.
Vampire Madonna also has a voracious
appetite for sex with humans...
because her clan has
their own needs as well.
Karma, who headed the Beast Clan,
fought against Vampire Madonna.
The war between these two clans,
of which humans are no match for...
ended because of Vampire
Madonna's overwhelming power.
The war concluded with Karma
being destroyed by the Vampires.
I felt the power from his death,
and I knew which path to take.
Yes, it's coming.
The new world order is
beginning & I'm ready.
Why...Why has it come?
The Beast that destroyed our home is
here!
Why is it here?
Worthless beast!
Where are our comrades?
They were chasing down beasts, and
haven't come back from section 7 yet.
Guess they're doing what
they always do, right?
No, please let me go.
Let me get some of this sweet stuff!
How does that feel, huh?
Please stop it, please.
Hey there, lady, I'll play with you.
You won't be lonely anymore.
Now let's get a look at everything.
No!
We're gonna protect
you from the beasts...
That's why we're keeping you here.
Yes. There are a lot of
beasts roaming the city.
The people of this area
cannot live without us...
And our protection.
So then...I guess you would have to say...
We're better than having the beasts
around, wouldn't you say so, huh, baby?
Get off.
Wait, dude...
I'm gonna come soon...
ldiot! What makes you think I
have to wait for you?!
Who are these females?
Who are you?
Hey, hey! We're here to
make you feel good, right?!
Stick around creeps,
the party is just about to begin.
Huh? What? The party? What's that?
Yes. Our little sex party.
And your very excited endorphins...
Endorphins?
Are you..?
Beasts?
You're beasts?
It was you who wanted us.
You can't reject us.
Now, you give me your...your...
I don't know about you but I'm
not interested, Anne.
It's okay for the
beasts to keep doing it...
But self-control keeps us
from getting some ourselves.
We've got few options
left because of this.
Let's go get some guy's
blood to keep us busy.
I'm falling.
Aine!
Shit! What's happening?
Why? Here I go again.
You crazy thing. Are you okay, Aine?
It hurts a lot.
What's happened?
Beasts? Come back!
Bat...Some kind of bat.
Flying...all around.
Hit against some kind of wall...
And fell down.
Oh, I see...
Damn it! Well it looks
like we've got trouble.
We can't get out of this city.
This barrier was put
up by the beasts.
Us, the humans and the beasts
can't get out of this city.
What are they up to?
What is going on in this city?
We must find out quickly.
A transfer student?
What's that?
You don't know anything, college girl.
A transfer student is someone who
comes from one college to another.
Tatsuo.
A transfer student is someone who
comes from one college to another.
Hey, Tatsuo!
A transfer student is someone who
comes from one college to another.
TAT-SU-O!!!
Aine, what are you doing?
Megumi, do you know
you've got a few cavities?
Tatsuo is peeping into your skirt.
Megumi, do you know
you've got a few cavities?
Tatsuo is peeping into your skirt.
Two in the back,
and one in the front.
- Do you get enough calcium?
- You know, he's a pervert!
Everyone take your seats!
Quickly now...
Allow me to introduce a transfer
who'll be joining us.
Her university closed down,
so she transferred to this one.
Her name is Seia Kannazuki.
She is an excellent student.
Study hard, everyone.
I'm Kannazuki...Hello everyone.
- It is nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you too
I'm Tatsuo.
My pleasure.
Here!
Take a seat here, next to me, please.
Damn you, Tatsuo!
What are you talking about?!
Nobody wants to sit next to you!
Who do you think you are?
Shut up!
- You've already got a woman, me!
- Miss Kannazuki.
Yes?
You'd be better off not associating
with these kind of people.
You know, I'd really like to but
I don't mind...
No way. Especially him,
being such a bad influence.
There's a seat next to Kubota.
Why don't you take
your place over there.
Let's begin our studies.
Everyone, be quiet.
Megumi, 'cause of you
I couldn't talk with Seia...
What's the matter?!
What's your problem, huh, Tatsuo?
Seia is just Seia!
I'm Megumi, you idiot.
I'm the only woman you'll ever need!
I have to interrupt your
little love quarrel.
Excuse me, can you spare
some time to talk?
Mina has something to say.
Hey there, you're that fox I met before.
Stop that!
Megumi.
I'm interested in talking with you.
Huh?
Me?
Why? What's up?
Stop...
Which group are you with?
Feels good, doesn't it Professor?
Miss Kannazuki, you're...
Professor, I wanted to sit next
to that cute guy Tatsuo.
But you kept him from me.
No, I didn't know, I didn't mean to.
I do not believe you.
I will not forgive you for that.
I'm going to give you punishment now,
Professor.
Don't do that to your professor.
I'm your professor,
why are you doing this to me..? Don't!
Take this and this and this!
Say that you're sorry!
Say you're sorry!
Everything's ready, Seia.
Stop this!
What more do you want from me?
I want you to apologize to Seia.
I want you to swear your undying
sexual loyalty only to me.
Why? Seia.
Apologize, apologize to me.
Apologize to Seia.
I am sorry.
Please stop this, Miss Seia.
I promise I'll do whatever you want.
Is that right?
Will you swear your undying
loyalty to me forever?
I want you to be my slave and do
my bidding forever and ever.
What..What are you doing?
No!
You lucky slave!
You're going to be a slave...
...and belong to Seia just like us.
How very nasty.
Professor, you sure know
how to make these roses grow.
Now, it's time to wrap this up
and get everything prepared.
Yes, Master Seia.
No, stop!
Leave me alone!
Feel...Feel more.
Give me all of your feelings.
Yes, you're going
to be a good pet.
I didn't know that this
city had such a place.
I've been thinking that this
building was kind of strange.
But, I guess I never thought that...
You've been here
before, right?
Oh, have I?
Yes.
Aine and Anne caused
you to lose some of your memory...
But you can still remember.
No, your blood has the
remnant of you being a beast!
What are we doing here?
Tatsuo and I are going
to make love here.
We're going to make love forever.
I love you, Tatsuo...
I love you.
What..What are you talking about?
Do you think I used to be a beast?
That I was killed
because I attacked Tatsuo?
Are you kidding me?
What?! What are you?
I am Mina.
My home was destroyed by the Beast.
I was born only to destroy the beasts
and all their ugly hosts. I'm a vampire.
Monster!
You're a monster
just like the beasts!
You may think I'm a monster.
But I'm not a beast.
I don't carry the
evil the beasts do.
They exist to fulfill their desires
and kill to feed their lusts.
I..I can't believe it...
What..?
Beasts..?
Vampires..?
I have nothing to do with...
- No! Let me go!
- Why?!
I can smell the beast in you!
Your very nature gives off this scent.
Tell me, did Karma call for you or...
Did you call for Karma?
Tell me, do you crave the
desires the beasts have?
Why have the beasts come here?
Tell me! What are
the beasts up to?
No! Stop it!
Who are you..?
A beast?
A human being?
Or...
What?
What is this power?
Tell me, how did you do that?
Please, don't ask me.
Keep away from me.
I don't want to fight you.
I was born only to fight against
the power which will destroy this world.
I only...
I only want to love Tatsuo...
To be with Tatsuo...
Stop. I didn't want to hear that.
That wasn't what I asked you...
I...love...him...
Oh, how unfortunate for you.
Your destiny has
splintered into two.
One is for the one you love,
while the other is...
No...
It can't happen...
It can't be...
So...
You couldn't meet with the male?
I'm sorry, Father.
There weren't any chances
for us while at the university.
Father, please don't worry about it!
The Professor has been
now brought to our side.
In a few days...
Silence!
In a few days?
How dare you suggest that?!
Do you understand why
you are still able to exist?
You can't live without me.
Forgive me, Father, please.
Please forgive us, Father.
That's enough, Father.
You may leave them alone.
They've done well.
Both of them have done well
as my slaves...
And they have pleased me as my pets...
But...Seia
I really hate having
such a nasty father, you know.
All right, as you wish, Seia.
However, you've failed to keep
your promise to me Seia, right?
Oh, Father, I know I will do
as I promised you faithfully.
I'm sorry.
The university is very interesting.
Why didn't you have
me attend sooner?
If something were
to happen to Seia...
You worry too much about me, Father.
But, Tatsuo...
That really sexy guy you recommended?
I don't believe he is worth
receiving Seia's love.
Oh, but...
I'll just do it for you, Father.
Thank you, Seia.
I love you much more
than anyone else.
I created the Kannazuki Group,
and I created these beasts.
Everything I do, I do
because I love you.
All of this comes
from my love for you.
Seia, I can do everything
and anything for you.
Prepare for injection!
Father, give it to me...
please give it to me...
What's that?
Please..Please give it to me...
Bitch!
You just can't figure it out...
What am I going to do?
What should I do with this city,
with this world, and what's to come?
Who are you?
The procedure here is that you should
talk to the Assistant Dean first.
Get out!
This is my seat.
Sit in your own seat!
I don't care if you're new here.
Shut up!
Don't worry, miss, you can sit
wherever you want.
Hey, you, how about sitting in
Megumi's seat?
Oh, miss...Right, Seia?
What's that?! That's bullshit.
- I'm so happy.
- You can't just do that to me.
Seia's sitting next to me and
that fucking Megumi is absent...
It's my favorite seat.
Now you think you can just move me
around like a cow...why I'll.
And...And..!
Will you shut your foolish mouth!
Why do you insist on
interrupting my group?
Professor...
Miss Seia wants to sit in this seat.
Be quiet and just let her have it!
What's the matter with the Professor?
How did she get so strong?
How scary...
Anyway, now you can sit
next to me in peace and quiet.
Please be good to me,
I'm such a gentle soul
I feel the same way.
Please be good to me, Tatsuo.
Excuse me.
I've just transferred into this
college today, and my name is Mina.
Please be good to me!
Mina! How did we get so lucky?
What? A new transfer?
Why the hell didn't I hear
anything about you...
Sorry if he didn't tell you about this,
"Permit" .
but I got permission
from the Dean himself.
So, now that we got that out of the way,
is there an extra seat
for me to sit in, Professor?
Mina, you're so forward...
You don't like women like me?
Of course I like them.
Promise me you'll keep away from
all other women except for me.
Don't you know that I've been so excited
to get you ever since I've met you?
You have?
Me too...
Really?
Check!
Bingo!
Tatsuo, get it up!
- Get it up!
- No! Not here!
But, ejaculating here at college...
Oh, Professor!
What are you doing here?
Try to act properly
with the other people.
What's going on with you two?
No, nothing's going on.
Everything we're doing
here is innocent...
Nothing out of the ordinary,
just a little...
Bingo!
I'll play Bingo too!
Here?
I'll let you touch my...
All right!
I won't forgive this.
Ah, yes! Yes!
Feels so good...
Kill them.
Bingo!
Finger Click!
So, you're a beast!
I knew you would show yourself if
I started getting close to Tatsuo.
Get out of here, Tatsuo!
I'm going!
I will never forgive anyone...
Who keeps me from my prey!
He is none of your business! Take this.
Beast!
Beast, beast, beast!
Oh, my God!
Our professor turned into a beast
when Mina and I were fooling around.
I can't believe what I just saw there.
You're not going to believe it either.
This place is really dangerous,
isn't it?
Tatsuo, I have another idea. Why don't
you come to a safe place with us?
Who am I?
Am I possessed by the beast?
Am I no longer an ordinary
human being now?
I like Tatsuo, I really love him...
But did I attack and
try to kill Tatsuo..?
No.
I don't want to change.
No, I don't want to.
Not now...
Beast!
The professor of
Room 3 is a beast!
This power you possess doesn't
come from the Beast world.
You're getting in
the way of all our plans.
Who are you?
I'm Mina.
Our home was destroyed when you
attempted to resurrect the Beast.
I'm a vampire!
I shall destroy you, beast...
You chicken!
I'm not done talking yet!
Shut up!
I have never heard Seia mention
anything about vampires before.
But if you want to fight...
I will show you no mercy.
Aine!
Oh, please show mercy...
What's that?
Will you quit it with that thing!
I'll kill this woman if
you get in our way again.
Oh, Aine.
I will never let you escape.
Seia's room?
Right?
Yes, Tatsuo,
it certainly is safe here...
And now we can do something
that'll make us all feel good.
Wait...
You've got such a nice piece.
Why do you want to sleep with me?
Just play and have fun with Seia.
I'll make you feel real good.
You are so cute.
You can touch me here.
Feels so good, Tatsuo.
More, for Seia.
S..Seia.
I'm feeling good too.
You're mine forever.
You're feeling good, right, Tatsuo?
Wonderful, so wonderful, Seia.
You really are good, daughter.
My dream will finally come true.
I will attain that awesome power.
What's happened?!
Miss Seia!
That woman who calls herself a
vampire is trying to ruin your...
Miss Seia...
What's that?
Kannazuki has been amassing a
huge amount of power these days.
Why do the beasts
head towards there?
Miss Seia!
Something terrible's happened!
That woman who calls herself a
vampire is trying to ruin your...
How rude! Barging in
here without knocking!
A woman interfering with my plans?
I will never forgive anyone who
interferes with Father's plans.
Let's go, Nozomi, Hikaru.
lntruder in the tower!
Attention, all guards!
Execute them on sight!
Repeat!
Got them!
You cover here.
Stay in front of Seia's room.
Nobody leaves.
I want a shot at some action.
Who's there?
Tatsuo...
Me..Megumi.
Tatsuo.
You poor thing.
It just began right before I got here.
What's going to happen to me?
H...Help..Help me, Megumi.
I'll stop it.
I'll help, Tatsuo.
Only I can stop it, Tatsuo.
Megumi.
Where have they gone?
Damn. Look for them.
Shit!
Searching for Aine in this
place, it's too difficult!
So, what are you
going to do with that?
Are you going to make
trouble in our house?
Master Seia said you need to be
disciplined by us!
Right?!
We will not be reduced to being
disciplined by ugly beasts like you!
Wait up!
You...
You made the Professor kidnap my Aine.
Not only the Professor, you vampire...
but these two as well.
No, all of the people in the world
will pledge their loyalty to me.
What?
I need Tatsuo's power to do so.
Tatsuo...
The man...
You...
I hate you, you monster.
I cannot allow you to
get in my way. So...
Who's the monster?
What, vanished?
Nobody is permitted to bother Seia.
M...Megumi.
Don't worry, Tatsuo.
I'm going to help you.
Tatsuo, I was born and exist....
Only for you, Tatsuo.
To become one with you, Tatsuo.
So Tatsuo, give to me what is yours...
Tatsuo, please give me what is yours.
I was surprised to hear
that you're a vampire.
But this is pathetic.
You'll learn your lesson.
I'll show you what's going to
happen if you go against me.
How stupid you are, Seia.
You've made Mina get
really angry with you.
Now you're gonna see Mina's true power
in your ugly face.
T..T..True power?
You can do it all by yourself
if you wish to rule the world.
You can change into a beast
if you don't have enough power.
But..!
Sister!
Hey, who are you..?
We're Vampire Hunters!
We will never allow you
to take the lives of others.
When the moon burns with anger...
When the power flows through me...
It will be the end of
your miserable life!
Energy overload in the tower!
This is a red alert!
Evacuate the tower immediately!
Finally, the power will be
awakened once more...
This wonderful event is starting.
A new and wonderful
world is about to begin.
M...Megumi...
I...I'm changing...
I...I...
Tatsuo...
You're finally...
Seia, we're collegemates, but
I will show you no mercy!
How unpleasant!
You really are unpleasant, bitch!
I won't forgive you!
The same goes for you!
I shall show you the power
my father has bestowed upon me.
I will rip out your guts!
Are you so stupid you think you
can kill me, Seia?
Do you think you are
stronger than I am? Do you?
Uh, oh...Here comes stupid.
I am not stupid.
How? It can't be...
Everyone is stupid.
You...
You've defeated
the beautiful Seia...
The masterpiece my father created.
You must apologize to me...
Apologize to Seia...
Apologize to my father...
W..What?
FATHER!
What's going on? What's that?
Something is coming out.
Is that you...?
Tatsuo?
Is it you?
Yes, it's coming.
The new world order is beginning.
Why...Why has it come?
The Beast that destroyed
our ancient home is here now!
Why is it here?