This is all madness.
What the hell has happened...
...to this peaceful town?
That woman...
IMMA YOUJO
What's that tower for?
How cute...
I guess you're homeless too?
That makes two of us.
My name is Maya.
Let's be friends.
You can be friends with us, too.
What do you want?
You look like you're new here.
I'll teach you the rules of this town.
Forget about the ugly cat.
Why don't we do something
more enjoyable, huh?
Ouch! What are you doing? Stupid cat!
You bitch!
Get her!
This feels good.
S- She's great...
W- What's with this girl?
Where am I?
What's going on?!
W- What's...
No!
So, you're awake?
Where am I?
Who are you?
My name is Halda.
I will take care of all your needs.
Once you have rested, I would
like you to begin your work here.
What?
You can take it easy for now.
You were sold to this place.
You were purchased as a
prostitute for this tower.
This is a house of pleasure.
Any and all kinds of pleasure
are made available here.
Our master is looking
forward to seeing you.
You were purchased for the highest
price this tower has ever spent.
Come in.
Here's your guest.
Enjoy her to your heart's content, Sir.
I assume you are new here.
You already forgot about me, Maya?
How come you know my name?
It's me, Chaos, remember?
You! Why on earth...?
I've been thinking about you a lot.
Don't tell me you were the one...
Don't be mistaken. I didn't sell you to this place.
Yeah, right.
Just because I had grudge against you,
doesn't mean I would do such a cowardly thing.
Still...
...I enjoyed watching how you got here.
That's bad enough!
Just go away! I don't
wanna even look at you.
I paid for your service.
That means you'll have to
give me my money's worth.
N- No!
Don't...
Have you seen the master of this tower?
N- No... I haven't.
The people in town haven't either, or rather...
...they don't want to talk about it.
Why do you wanna know
about things like that?
Something smells really fishy.
I have nothing to do with it.
You have been always like that.
There are strange things in this town.
I don't see any young women.
I only see girls and old women.
Why does...
...that bother you?
Don't you get it?
I figure all the young women
were forced to work in this tower.
Besides, all the men in this town...
...are either blind or...
...they're just too greedy to care.
They seem like they're scared of something.
I told you. It has nothing to do with me.
I figure this tower is hiding something.
When it comes to this tower,
the people here suddenly get quiet.
I have nothing to do with it...
I already told you.
Until I find out the secret of this tower,
I am going to come back quite often.
Besides, I've got some more
business with your body, too.
Don't come back!
See you soon.
You have gotten accustomed
to life here, I presume?
Maybe... I can enjoy good food here.
I don't like being forced
to sleep with men, but...
...as long as I put up with it,
this place seems pretty comfortable.
Tonight...
...the Master would like to
see you in his chambers.
Once a month, every woman in this tower...
...has the honor of being
tenderly loved by our Master.
Like a caged cat,
I don't have a choice, huh?
Our Master has been looking
forward to being with you...
...after last month.
After last month?
Hey Halda, I don't remember
meeting our Master last month.
You were unconscious when
you were first brought here.
This is the chamber that our
Master, Bazus, resides in.
Go right in. The Master is waiting for you.
The Master is this way.
Lord Bazus, here is the lady you so desire.
He's saying, "Come in. "
What are you doing?
Hurry up. Go right in.
No!
No! Don't!
N- No...
No!
So, how's business?
Shit. Just as unfriendly as ever.
The Master seemed so pleased to have you.
He favored you so much.
Can I really have it?
Certainly.
Hey. Is this all?
It's not what we agreed to.
Well then... take it or leave it.
What?!
You're taking advantage of us...
Alright, I get it.
Hey, good to see you again.
Relax and enjoy.
You didn't bring the cat?
No, I had some business to attend to.
I am beginning to understand
how this town works.
I like this much better.
Did you know that the people in this
town are all addicted to a drug...
...that the Master of this tower sells?
With all the profits they make,
they've bought a small army of guards.
I'm sorry, but our drug is not easy to produce.
This drug is not as cheap as you might think.
Ugh... This is terrible.
The drug they are producing is not
like any kind we have ever known.
By the way I see how people are addicted,
this must be a very powerful drug.
Hey, are you listening?
That man is quite dangerous.
We will turn him away next time he comes.
It's my job to sleep with men, isn't it?
Come here.
Now I've got it...
They process the thing
that monster ejaculates...
...and turn it into the drug.
That explains why I have never
seen anything like this before.
Still, it's a disgusting drug.
Stop right there, Chaos.
Hey...
It's just one sample out of so many? Can't I...?
No, you may not.
You are so inflexible.
I'm sorry, but they are very costly products.
We might be able to offer
you a discount, though.
I don't do drugs myself.
Particularly not after seeing where
this disgusting drug comes from.
What you mean is...
I didn't want to, but I happened to see it.
I saw you doing it with the master of the tower.
My mind and body, everything
is yours, Lord Bazus.
It was like watching a nightmare.
Shoot! Kill him!
Oops.
You cannot escape!
Don't let him go. Kill him!
Make sure he's dead!
Huh?
Get away from him!
His body fluid, which is being sent
underground, is going to back up.
The monster is going to explode soon.
What?
A face like yours doesn't scare me.
Give me the woman and make it quick.
Since you are about to explode,
I could just get her afterwards,
but I am in a hurry.
I want get out of this town...
...and make some money from
this drug, so I can live with her.
Chaos...
Hold it!
I'm surprised that you escaped
into a place like this, Chaos.
I'm surprised you found me.
You must have been planning to...
That's right, Maya. It is all for you.
Something went wrong since you came here...
...with Lord Bazus and with myself!
Die!
Now, no one is in our way, Maya.
That's right. Everything is your fault, Maya.
Freeze!
Next time you move,
you'll be a dead man.
Right now, in front of you, I will rape her.
Then, I will slowly torture you to death.
W- What the...?
Stupid monster!
Take this!
Are you okay, Maya?
This woman is mine.
M... Maya...
Maya...
I won't let you go.
A woman and man have escaped.
Capture them!
Guard the front of our Lord's Chamber!
Maya... Come... back...
Who goes there? Stop!
Somebody's escaped!
Get them! Follow them!
What the...?
We're in trouble.
They've to decided to kill us,
rather than get back their drug.
No shit!
Maya...!
Damn! We're too late.
I will go myself.
Get my vehicle ready!
Yes sir.
I'll get Maya back.
What are we gonna do? We can't win.
Well then, let's go for broke!
What?!
Jeez! You drive like a maniac!
This is as far as you go!
Maya, you are quite a woman.
Maya!
Mmm... it smells like the drug.
That monster smells of the drug.
Look! His blood is the drug!
Get out of way! Go away!
His body is full of the drug. Kill him!
Maya!
And... push!
Maya.
What?
What's got into you all of the sudden?
Stop it, Chaos.
What's wrong with you, doing this now?
Nothing is wrong...
I just want to make love to you.
That must be it over there.
Okay. Stop around here.
Huh?
I am going on alone, from this point.
Maya...
Halda?!
Now, come with me.
Maya, don't go.
That man is finished.
It's my turn to take you away.
Maya...
Maya... What are you doing?
What?!
You!
Maya... I have found you.
Why?
That's...
Maya...
Stop it! Maya is mine!
Any man who loves her, risks their life...
Vengeance? It's just the same as before.
When that woman came to my
town, everything changed.
The men became so horny,
they raped other men's lovers.
While all of that happened,
that woman was just smiled.
It's pathetic...
I can't hate her, however much I try to...
That monster is the same as me.
He can't resist that woman's body either.
Truly, men are such...
Maya...
Get away from Maya! You ugly monster!
You are mine... Maya!
Maya!
So cute.
Maya. You are...
Excuse me. I hear there's
a town named Samgun...
Huh? Yeah, go straight
ahead and you can't miss it.
Thanks.