What are you doing here?
Yes... well, I'm...
I was sent by the household
service agency to work here.
Are you the new maid?
What is your name?
Y- Yes! My name is Maya.
IMMA YOUJO
Welcome back, Master.
Oh?
Tomoka, why don't you help
her change into her uniform.
Y- Yes.
Wow!
Is this the bathroom?
I'll leave your change of clothes here.
This is gorgeous.
I've never seen a beautiful bathroom like this.
Hey, hurry up and go inside.
I have other work to do.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry.
Please don't make a mess.
I get excited too easily.
It's a bad habit of mine... Oh well.
This feels great.
I can't believe I can work in such
a big mansion. It's like a dream...
But...
I'm not sure I can do well here.
Hey! How long are you going
to take a bath in there?
Y- Yes!
I'll be out right away!
Come in.
I'm Maya.
I'll do my best in your service.
It's a pleasure to work for you.
Thank you for coming in such heavy rain.
If you have any questions, please ask Tomoka.
Yes, thank you.
Our master's business is importing
and selling art and furniture.
This is the living room.
There are many valuable pieces
of furniture and art here.
Please use extra care when you clean this room.
Right! Oh...
This is the atelier for our master's son, Masao.
Really, so he's an artist?
Masao prefers to eat his meals in the atelier,
so always be sure to bring them here.
Right!
This is a portrait of the master's late wife.
Masao was the one who painted it.
Um...
How did she die?
Dunno...
This is the wine cellar.
The master enjoys having wine at dinnertime,
so be sure to bring him some.
Okay!
Huh?
Don't!
What?
You can't go in here unless our
master gives you permission.
Do you understand?
I... I'm sorry.
Well, come with me.
Y... Yes!
This is our room.
I put your things over there.
Oh, thank you very much.
Umm... Master Masao?
Leave it over there.
Ah... o-okay!
Maya, I brought warm milk for you.
You can sleep well after you drink this.
Thank you.
It's really warm.
And it tastes good!
I'm glad you like it.
I drink this every night.
Let's drink together from now on.
Can we? Wonderful!
It's a nice day, Tomoka.
It's hard to believe there
was so much rain yesterday.
Be quiet...
Please let me sleep a little more.
Oh!
Good morning, Master Masao.
I'm Maya.
Um... I brought your dinner
last night to your atelier.
Oh, that's a beautiful flower.
What is the name of this flower?
I like flowers very much!
Although, I don't know the
flowers' names very well.
Butjust looking at them makes me very happy.
Ah... Master Masao?
Have a good day.
I brought your meal.
Um... Master Masao?
So, this is an artist's room?
I wonder what's inside this box?
Don't touch!
D- Don't touch it!
M- Master Masao!
I... I said don't touch this!
I- I'm sorry!
I'm planning to hold my next party
on the 15th of next month.
Really? I think that's a good time.
Anyway, how is your collection coming?
It's coming well.
I can't wait to show it in front of people.
You sound very confident.
Well, I look forward to seeing it.
Master Masao, I brought your lunch.
Master Masao.
Maya.
Welcome home.
Tomoka?
I don't know why, but I feel dizzy.
Rejoice Tomoka... It's time for your debut.
The party is the 15th of this month.
I'm sure you will do well, Tomoka.
No way... What is this?
Tomoka... Mr. Hagiwara... and Master...
Soon I think Maya will be
ready to prepare as well.
I understand. Then I will
take care of it tomorrow.
Do a good job, Tomoka.
Maya, Maya!
Tomoka.
What is wrong with you?
You seemed like you were having a nightmare.
Tomoka... umm...
What?
No, it's nothing.
You're acting strangely.
I guess you must have had a scary dream.
Are you alright?
Dream? Was that a dream?
Have a nice day.
Huh?
Master Masao, I brought your meal.
May I come in?
I will leave your meal here.
W- Well, if you'll excuse me.
Hurry... and escape from here. Maya.
You did a really bad thing, Maya.
I'm very sorry!
Of all the art, how could you break
the vase that Master liked the most.
It's a foreign-made vase.
You can't get it in Japan.
You could never pay it back,
no matter how long you worked here.
M- Master!
I'm really sorry!
Even though you apologize,
the vase can't be fixed.
I'm sorry, I will do anything I can.
Please forgive me!
Maya, lift up your face.
Yes...
Will you do anything I say, Maya?
Y... Yes...
...Master.
Nd way...
No! Let me go! No!
No, help me! Please!
Tomoka.
Yes.
Maya, I will tell you what our real job is.
The maids of this mansion will become
part of our master's collection.
Maya, I will make you just like Tomoka.
I will add you as part of my collection.
First, I will show you the beauty
of my master's collection.
Watch carefully.
You will be just like that, soon.
Don't be afraid.
Maya, this will be your pleasure, too.
Tomoka, why don't you do Maya next.
Yes.
Now I see...
So, you are a virgin.
Let's give this to our master now.
No! Stop!
No! No! Please don't!
Here it comes, Maya!
No!
Maya...
Master Masao, I brought your meal.
I will leave it here.
Maya!
She's not here!
Maya.
How is it, Maya?
I will make you into a
woman like Tomoka, soon.
Maya!
Damn it!
You look beautiful, Tomoka.
Now it's time for you to debut.
Thank you very much, Master.
Maya.
Maya!
We can see Mr. Ayanokoji's
collection at the show tonight.
I can't wait to see it.
How did your collection come out?
It came out great.
I'm sure you will be very satisfied.
Well, it seems you have a lot of confidence.
How do you like it?
It's not bad, however...
However?
I got this from an importer the other day.
I wanted to add a little
spice to your collection,
so I brought them here.
Master Masao... I... I...
Maya.
S... Stop that, Maya!
The importer asked me to finance his company.
I'm thinking about it.
But I can't finance any more companies.
So I've decided to make a deal...
...with the company who has a better collection.
It's no good.
I can't take it anymore.
Master...
I thought your collection
could do a little better than this.
Master Masao, I... I!
You humiliated me, woman!
You disgraced my name!
Let's go, Hagiwara!
Hagiwara, I will hold a party a week from now.
What?
I will debut Maya.
This is great.
It's very warm.
I'm... I'm...
I'll never let anybody take you, Maya...
Masao! What are you doing?!
Masao!
Maya!
Hagiwara, lock up Maya in the room.
In one week,
I will make Maya the best of my collection...
...and prove to him what I can do!
Maya!
Shut up!
No!
Masao, stay in your room.
Paint your pictures as usual, understand?
Your wife has a nice one...
All right, I think I can take care
of your company's financing deal.
Thank you very much.
Please don't cry, Mother.
I will protect you.
Mother!
Mother.
Maya.
Maya!
Please... Master.
Please let me in.
I feel crazy out here.
I will... Please!
Are you ready, Maya?
Now... Wake up, Maya.
I put everything I know into you. Wake up!
You are now reborn as a new woman, Maya.
Maya... Maya!
Welcome to my party, Count Mayuzumi.
I brought my collection as you requested.
Are you sure you want them to join?
You may regret it.
Please, don't worry about it.
You look beautiful, Maya.
I never expected you would
become such a beautiful woman.
Master has put all his hopes on this party.
Your debut is at such an important party...
You must be happy, Maya.
How prized a collectible have you become?
I will taste you.
Mother, they came here again.
What can I do?
They'll take Maya away from me now.
But, I won't let them do that.
Watch me, Mother.
So, this is your new collection.
I'm on my way, Maya.
Well...
How do you like it?
It's getting very exciting.
You might regret this, Ayanokoji.
Let's see how long your collection will last.
How do you like my Maya?
If you like, I don't mind letting you have her.
Really, Ayanokoji?
Let's not play these silly games anymore.
I found something more important than this.
I want Maya. I need nothing else.
I don't want money or status.
I only need Maya.
Maya is mine!
Nobody can have her!
What?
Master Masao?
Maya... I won't let anybody have Maya.
I'm the one who should be standing there.
Maya, if only you didn't come to this place...
Don't, Tomoka!
Maya!
I will protect Maya.
What are you doing here, Masao?!
Nobody can stop me.
Nobody can take Maya away.
Maya is mine!
Maya is mine.
This is a wonderful collection.
Would you please let me have him?
Of course, I will pay you a desirable sum.
Well, all right...
...but only because the request
is from Count Tachibana's wife.