Princess, I feel like I'm in heaven.
Hurry! Splash your life inside of me right now.
Give me your vigor...
Maya... Are you there?
Come over here.
Y- Yes...
Have you been watching us there?
Yes...
So cute... come to me.
Yes.
I will give it to you too.
There, Maya...
Yes...
MAYA
IMMA YOUJO MAYA
If you're a dead body, why don't
you just lay dead on the ground?
I'm too hungry to be a dead body.
I'm Shinbei, a foot soldier
of Katsuyori Abe. And you?
I'm Jyurota, a vassal of
Nobutsuna Mochizuki!
So then we are enemies.
Let's not bring it up. It's not
worth fighting in such a place.
But if you really want to fight,
let's do after we eat the rice ball.
We can't fight on an empty stomach anyway.
Is that all you want to say?!
Hey!
Eat!
So long!
Abe and Mochizuki don't mean
anything to us anymore.
For us, there's no worth in fighting.
See you again if I have a chance.
Hey! Wait! Hey Jyurota!
What do you want now?
Do you have any idea where to go?
Not particularly.
I see! I see! I'm glad to hear that.
Have you ever heard about Lord Takeda
in Kai, over those mountains?
Lord Takeda?
Yeah, I've heard he is very powerful now.
People are saying he could
become the next Shogun.
Lord Takeda in Kai...
He might buy my services for a good price.
All right then, let's hurry up and go.
We can reach Kai soon after we
cross over these two mountains.
Excuse me, young men. Are you
planning to cross this mountain?
Yeah, we are.
Don't do that.
Stay away from this mountain.
No man has ever crossed this mountain.
What do you mean by that?
A demon comes out at night on this mountain.
She captures and eats
the men who cross here.
A demon?
Are you saying a demon
exists in these days?
Hey old lady, don't try to trick us.
I'm not trying to trick you.
This is the truth.
All the men who went to this
mountain have disappeared...
...as if they were spirited away,
and they never came back again.
I'm telling you. Go down to the
base and take another route.
Damn it, I don't care about a
demon or men being spirited away.
I don't have time to deal
with such a worthless rumor!
I'm in a rush. Hey Jyurota, let's go!
Damn! Weird old crow.
Wait little girl!
Let's have fun together!
You better wait for me.
Nooo! Let me go! No!
Don't resist little girl!
I'll make you feel good right now.
No!
Hurry up and get her clothes off!
I know that!
What's wrong, Jyurota?
Hey!
This is more than we expected.
That tattoo! I can sell her
for a very high price.
Look there, girl.
His thing can take you to heaven.
Women go crazy over it.
I'll let you suck it with your mouth first.
Oh... This is so good!
What are you doing?
Let her go!
Who are you?
Who cares. Kill him!
If you let her go now, I won't kill you!
I guess you have some skill...
...but if you kill me now, you'll
end up killing this girl too.
If you don't care, go ahead and kill me.
Coward!
Bandits don't have any honor!
Why are you hesitating? Come on!
If you won't do something, I will...
Shinbei!
They must be the bandits around here!
Hey, Jyurota. That demon, the old lady
was talking about, might be them.
We won't cross the mountain until
tomorrow if we keep standing here.
Oh, you're awake?
Don't come near me! Stay away!
And we're the ones who saved her life.
She is still scared. Forgive her, Shinbei.
If you say so... you're the one
who got injured by helping her.
What?
It's just a small cut.
I guess my sword skill was
not as good as I thought.
Oh, please excuse me.
I didn't know that you were
the the ones who saved me...
Don't worry about it, um...
My name is Maya.
I work at the palace nearby.
Please come and let me treat your injury.
My master won't be happy
if I allow the people who...
...saved my life to leave,
without showing my appreciation.
Well, I appreciate it, but we have
to cross this mountain tonight.
Oh, then can you at least have dinner with us?
The Princess will be so glad to have visitors.
Dinner?! Princess?!
Hey, Jyurota!
Don't be rude to Miss Maya!
W- What are you talking about Shinbei?
What do you mean, "what"?
Lord Takeda isn't going to run away.
Well... but...
You are so impudent.
How far is the palace?
We are almost there.
Hey... The palace can't be so big,
being in the middle of nowhere.
Here, please come inside.
This is good.
My master will be here soon.
Only you and your master live in this palace?
Yes, my master is the daughter
of a nobleman and his mistress.
She was sent to live on this
mountain for political reasons.
I am Akina, the master of this palace.
I heard that both of you saved my servant.
Thank you very much.
I would like to show a little appreciation.
Please stay here and relax overnight.
I never expected I could meet such
a beautiful princess in this area.
What luck!
I will take the princess.
What?
You fool! They've been hiding on
such a secluded mountain, all alone.
That means they haven't
had a man for a long time.
You don't mean...
Why don't you take Maya.
Don't you like her?
W- Well...
All right! So we're in agreement!
Princess, I'm coming for you.
See you later.
Princess Akina, I won't
let you sleep tonight!
Hey! Wait, Shinbei!
Ouch...
May I wash your back?
Miss Maya.
Jyurota! What is wrong?
Is your wound hurting?
I guess the hot water made my wound reopen.
Oh, your cut...
Miss Maya.
Jyurota...
I see the moon has graciously
hidden behind a cloud.
Oh... Who is it? Is anybody there?
Cats don't live on this mountain.
It must be cold outside.
Why don't you come inside, and have
sake to make yourself warm, Shinbei.
Ahhh. You've got me.
I can't fool you, Princess Akina.
It's really cold outside.
Oh! Sake?
Huh? You don't have sake cups here.
Oh! I'll go and get some!
No need to do that. The cup is right here.
Here, Shinbei, drink up now.
Oh, yes! Suck everything.
It's dripping deeply inside of me!
Princess Akina!
Jyurota...
Miss Maya.
How big and strong it is!
Please give it to me. Please.
Well, It's my turn.
This is too good, Princess...
P- Princess!
It's still hard like this... Now, Shinbei...
Princess Akina.
Have you been living with the
Princess all your life?
Yes.
Don't you feel lonely,
just the two of you being here?
Don't you ever feel like leaving this mountain?
I can't leave this mountain.
That's my fate.
Fate?
Is that something to do with this tattoo?
Is that why you can't be free from the Princess?
Maya...
Jyurota, I like you.
So... please leave this mountain!
You have to get out of here
as quickly as possible!
Maya! Wait.
Maya! I like you too...
Damn it...
Stop it!
It can't be...
A- Are you...
Shinbei, is that you?!
Jyurota...
Get away from here... A monster...
A monster?
I guess you finally found
out who I am, young boy.
This is a palace of cobwebs
to capture men like you.
I absorb the life-energy of
the men who visit here.
Then, I turn the men into spiders
after taking their life-energy.
Come to me. It's your turn.
Let me be fulfilled by your young vigor.
M- Maya!
Escape from here now!
Maya...
Please, go now!
What happened to you, Maya?
Don't come near me!
Maya, take him now.
No. I'm... I'm...
What are you going to do?
Do you think you can leave with this man?
You know very well that you
will never be able to do that.
L- It's...
Maya, give me the spear!
I will take care of this monster...
No!
The... tattoo!
Please, Princess Akina...
You can do anything to me!
Just don't hurt Jyurota... Princess Akina!
Oh, there, there. You are getting so big.
Maybe it's because you
have Maya's young vigor.
But Maya is in love with this man,
and is trying to leave you.
And she even aimed a spear at me...
...the person who raised her after
she was abandoned on the mountain.
Yes, just like me...
I was left on this mountain.
I'm the child of a noble's mistress.
I didn't even know I was being abandoned.
They took me out from the house and
separated me from my foster parents.
I had to move to this mountain alone.
But that was not everything...
The men who were supposed to
guard me took advantage of me...
They raped me over and over.
When I came to, I was walking
on the mountain by myself.
And then...
I saw eyes staring at me in the darkness.
The eyes asked me,
"Do you want to take revenge
against all the men in the world?"
I nodded, and made a deal with it.
I made love with the demon.
It was a mysteriously erotic moment.
As if I was in another world.
And I...
I gained the magical power
to take men's life-energy.
I turned all the men who
raped me into spiders.
Then I turned all the men
who visited here into spiders.
And one day, I found you on the mountain.
I wanted for you to succeed me.
To continue my revenge against men.
I placed the tattoo of the forest
demon on your back, and raised you.
How can you do this to me?
Look Maya. I will show you what a man is like!
Absorb the life-energy from Maya
that she just got from him.
If you really like Maya, you
must be able to take anything.
N- No. I can't let her do this.
How can I reach there?
I need to get that spear.
You are taking it pretty well, but
I wonder how long you'll last?
How is it? Aren't you feeling good inside of me?
You don't have to hold it in.
Let your life pour out, inside of me.
Here, suck it. Here... Here...
That's good. Yes that's it!
Maya, did you see it?
The man that you love just splashed
lots of his life inside of me!
See? Now you must understand
what a man is like.
They will take any woman
just as long as it's a woman!
What?!
Damn it! Get off of me!
You bastards! Trying to kill me!
You bastard!
Why? Why do men take
everything away from me?
Maya! Maya!
Maya!
Maya, the spear! Give me the spear!
Jyurota!
Maya! Stop!
Jyurota...
Maya!
I'm glad, Jyurota...
Please don't die, Maya.
It's time to for me to go...
What are you talking about?
But, I'm happy.
The demon on my back is
gone, and I'm clean now.
You helped me, Jyurota.
Maya.
Can you hold me again before I die?
Maya...
After that, the girl who had the demon
woman's tattoo on her back...
...became the demon.
Now, she captures men crossing
this mountain and eats them.
On this mountain?
And is the girl who became
the demon is good looking?
She becomes young every time
she takes a man's life...
...and she has been living for a few
hundred years on this mountain.
That sounds good!
I can let her take me!
Well, let's punish her with
the swords in our pants!
Then, I'll go first.
Hey, I'll go first!
Even now, men will never learn.