The less fulfilled, the more
beautiful a dream...
Wished, but never reached.
Fragile, but soiled...
If I keep winning at this rate...
in the final round I will meet the
charismatic queen of the Card game...
Reina Sasajima
At whatever cost...
I want to beat her!
International delivery
for Mr. Daisuke Kousaka.
Why doesn't it have
the sender's name?
I ordered that one.
You. That means,
inside this box...
the Shadow Items!
What's this?
INMU
The Wandering Flesh Slave
Episode 1
"The Shadow Card"
You mean, I can use this one
and win the championship?
Do you like them?
You actually are the Spirit
of the Shadow Cards
It was worth all the trouble I had,
signing a contract with you.
Thank me after you have
enjoyed these cards.
Enjoyed these cards?
Master.
Master?
I'm so happy you're seeing me
in this embarrassing position!
You just came ouf of the card.
Yes.
My name is Capil, and I have been
sealed in that card.
You were sealed in the card?
Master, watch me masturbate
some more!
You are...
Master, yours is getting big!
I'm getting so excited!
Deeper. Deeper.
Master!
I'm so happy!
I'm Capil, and I'm coming!
Hey, hold on!
Shit, she just satisfied herself.
What am I supposed to do
about myself?
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
I am sorry I came out so late.
Mesomiai is my name.
Please use me in place of Capil.
What're you doing?
You're going to vanish, too,
aren't you?
Then hurry up
and make me come.
Yes, I understand.
Not bad, are you?
I'm so happy, Master.
Are you going to come
between my lips for me?
I'm so happy!
What is it? Hurry up!
I was just ready to come.
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
Whatever. Make me come quick.
I shall.
More! Faster!
No, not like that
How can I explain it?
WJow do you like it?
Does this feel good?
I told you not to stop
in the middle!
I'm sorry.
It's may fault.
I'm not good at this.
Why does it have to be like this?
I was getting aroused just fine.
I see. Her speed value
is set to too low.
Then I shall rewrite it.
If you do that, my overall
performance balance would be...
Good! Awesome!
All right, now that I know what
to do, I'll give her more!
Now, finally, I can come!
She's vanished, too.
I could have used!
some more attention, but...
oh well.
What's going on? I'm bound!
My dear puppy, I'll punish you
to your heart's content.
Who the hell are you?
The named is Netirus.
Well, how do you like it,
when you can't move?
Wow, awesome!
You're such a slut.
You're already getting aroused?
Already, you're this hard.
If you stroke me, I'd just...
No! Not yet.
It's too early to come.
Lick me first.
Tihat's good. You've got
a great tongue!
No more.
What a baby. So, you want to
come inside me?
Yes, please let me. Please.
Good. You need to beg.
Oh, it's so good!
Your cock is crawling
around inside me.
Your cock is pulsating inside me.
I'm coming.
Good. Come.
Come all you want inside me.
Okay. Mow I see.
That blank card
must be not used yet.
Which means I can seal a girl
in this card?
That's it, isn't it?
What an awesome card this is!
Wait a moment.
You're carrying a dangerous card,
aren't you?
A dangerous card?
A Shadow Card,
to seal away human desire
Mind your own business.
Looks like you can't
see your own back.
I did warn you, though.
Mr. Daisuke Kousaka...
Isn't it about time you conceded?
I don't want you to waste my time.
Kashihara, Asakawa, Imaizumi!
Clean up this place and get ready
for the celebration party!
-Yes, ma'am!
-Wait!
You mean you still have
a trick up your sleeve?
Here is my wild card!
What would you want to do
with a blank card like that?
-Where are we?
-In the world of Shadow Cards
Reina Sasajima, you'll never be
able to leave this place.
You'll spend the rest of your life
in this place as a flesh slave!
No!
Kashihara, Asakawa, Imaizumi!
Don't waste your time.
They won't be able to follow you here!
Bastard! Let me go!
Miss Reina, play a game with me.
If you give in to my caresses,
I just might let you go.
-A game?
-If you make a single noise, I win.
First you suck my cock,
and then I'll plunge it inside you.
What a ridiculous rule!
I don't accept it.
It's too late now. The game has
already started.
Don't touch me
with your filthy hands!
Hate me scream at me,
cry all you want, but you can't fight me.
See, you can't move
In this world,
I am the game master.
You will receive my caress,
without being to move your body.
When you fall, you'll fall
spectacularly hard.
I won't ever lose to you.
You're opening up, opening up.
Even though your underwear
I can tall your labia are opening up.
No. Don't talk dirty!
I see now you want me
to lick you.
What is that noise?
You're wet, aren't you?
ffi* because you wet me
with your tongue.
It's about time you
take my cock, isn't it?
Why don't you go ahead
and make noise?
Who'd ever make noise for you?
Don't you dare grub that filthy thing
against me!
Remember the rule
I mentioned earlier?
I lied.
No. You coward!
I did it! I finally plunged
into her maidenhead!
Are you satisfied now?
It's you again.
Congratulations. From this
day on, you'll reside in this card.
What? That's not funny.
I'm sealing this bitch in this card!
Idiot.
This card seals
the one who uses it.
What? Wait!
What's the use of sealing a man?
In that case, be a woman.
What?
What's going on?
Stop! Stop it!
I'm...I'm not...
No! Don't!
DAISUKE! Don't seal me in the card!
Not a bad card, is it?
Does the sunset hide
a voice from beyond?
Within its brilliant particles?
Episode 2
Drowning in a Summer"
Please stop, Stepmother!
Wonderful.
You can do it right with this.
You have matured while I
wasn't paying attention.
You're all the way inside me
now. Open your eyes and look carefully.
Does it feel good
to be inside me?
Ilto going to mate you
feel even better.
Incredible.
You're already so hot
Go ahead. More.
Feel even better.
Wonderful. A young man.
Please, move.
We can't, Mother, not me ...
It's all right.
We're not related by blood.
Everybody does it.
Nobody talks about it.
Do you mean to tell anyone?
I can't tell anyone.
Good, just like that.
You're so good.
No, if you move that hard, I'll...
What? You'll do what?
I'll come.
It's all right. If you
can't hold back any more...
come whenever you want to.
Give me a lot.
Come inside me.
Give your come to me.
Wow, you're coming.
You're coming a lot.
Wow, I'm inside. I'm inside you.
No, stop.
Not like this.
Butv I can't wait. You like it, too,
don't you?
No, stop
You're hurting me.
Stop it already.
No, no!
Wow, I'm coming already.
No...
I'm coming inside you again.
Please, forgive me.
No, I can't wait any more.
You do it right, or...
I might end up being violent again.
Go ahead, move faster.
Make me come right.
Great. It feels so good.
That's right. Make it more slimy.
That's right, take me in deeper.
All the way.
Suck me harder.
Great. Just like that.
l'm coming already.
I'm home, Mother.
That's my new mother?