Good, you're awake now.
You're...
Kotomi!
You scared me!
You suddenly collapsed
during phys. ed. class.
That can't be.
I was sure we were
in the old building.
Inside the old school building?
What?
That was just...
a dream?
That can't be!
But...
I was surprised.
Miyuki....
I didn't know your breasts were so big!
Wow, and it's really soft!
It's sensitive, too!
Stop!
Isaku would really enjoy playing with you!
You know...
I trusted you.
I thought I could trust you!
Kotomi, I tried!
He saw everything.
All of my private parts!
Isaku did it.
So, Miyuki, I think...
you should join all of us.
No, don't. Stop it!
We're all waiting.
What!
Miyuki, let's remove your gym shorts.
Let Isaku see you naked.
You would feel so much better.
No!
That's crazy!
Your nipples are getting hard.
Cute underwear.
It's soaking wet now.
No, not there!
You know that you really want it.
You want Isaku to...
violate you, too.
No, I don't.
No, I don't, no!
Isaku: Episode 3 "Miyuki"
Miyuki!
What's going on here?
You've been waiting for this.
Munemitsu?
That boy was helping me with my plan.
He wanted your body...
so he told me he would help me.
Thanks for your help, Munemitsu...
but I'm going to enjoy her by myself now.
Wait, Miyuki, where are you going?
Just chill out!
This isn't like you at all.
What else can I to do now?
Tell me what I should do!
I can't....
It's my fault that Kotomi was captured.
It's not your fault!
If I...
If I was stronger....
Kenta....
Kenta, see this?
It looks like a door.
Come on!
Lift your ass higher,
so I can get a better view.
Don't touch me!
Are you enjoying this show?
Want to see more?
See, your panties are soaking wet again.
Just let me go!
Your body obviously wants me.
Be a good girl, and scream for me, baby!
No, stop, I'm begging you!
Your nipples are already perky and hard!
Just be honest!
Kenta!
How is it?
Do you like the way a cock feels?
No, pull out!
Jinpachi!
Jinpachi, you too?
No!
Just shut up and suck on his cock.
Come on!
I said, suck his cock!
That's good, your pussy's getting tight.
You have a pretty face, but your pussy...
is the real prize.
Now, you can call yourself a woman.
Thanks to me.
So, Kenta.
If you found Kotomi instead of me,
would you have....
Yeah?
Never mind.
That's good, very nice.
You're getting better.
What?
Kotomi!
What is this?
Kotomi, stop listening to him!
She can't hear anything you say.
Kotomi's concentrating on sucking me off.
Isaku, you shit!
Let Kotomi go!
You bastard!
All right, you can stop Kotomi.
You can say hi to your friends.
Kenta!
Show them the special present
I bought, just for you.
What!
I thought wearing piss-soaked panties...
would be uncomfortable for her.
Girls that wet their pants
in front of people...
should wear children's underwear.
You're sick!
Isaku!
When I was pounding her little pussy...
she was crying and calling out
your name the whole time.
Well, you seem to be popular with the girls.
You enjoy spreading your legs
for your sweetie?
No, don't say that!
Why don't you show him how wet you are!
No!
Don't look at me!
Stop it!
I'll take her place!
So, let Kotomi go, now!
Very interesting!
Get on your hands and knees.
Lick this.
You weren't able to protect
your little friend here, were you?
Lick my fingers clean!
Don't, Miyuki!
Come on, hurry up!
Now, are you happy?
I don't know, let's see.
Are you happy?
Was that all she deserves
for betraying you?
What do you think, Kotomi?
I can't hear you unless you talk out loud.
I want to watch Miyuki urinate...
in front of us.
Kotomi!
That's what she wants,
so go ahead and do it right now!
Kotomi!
I'll do it.
Only because she wants me to.
Make sure Kenta can see you, too.
Spread your legs so he can see you.
You looked down of me
like you were something special.
You deserve this!
Do you like people watching you?
It's nice to get attention.
Isaku!
Jinpachi!
Why did--
Kenta!
I'm not done with you yet!
Jinpachi, tell me why.
I had no other choice, Kenta.
This isn't over.
Kotomi went through a lot more than that.
Tell me, what do you think should happen...
to that traitor bitch, Kotomi?
Name her punishment.
Kotomi!
An enema.
You have to speak louder!
I want her to...
suffer through the discomfort of an enema.
Just like I did.
All right!
You'll do it, right?
Stop, Kotomi!
Shut up!
This is what Kotomi wants, right?
I understand.
Good, now turn around
and show us your ass.
Kotomi...
do it exactly like I taught you to.
Yes.
Don't do it, Kotomi!
Jinpachi, but why?
Did you know that Jinpachi
was obsessed with Miyuki?
For a long time...
he was hiding, and taking photographs
of Miyuki at school.
So I caught him one day at school...
and told him that all women
needed to be forced.
They don't know the difference
between sex and force.
Kotomi gave up almost instantly.
Miyuki looks like a tough one.
I think I'm going to enjoy playing with her.
Lift your hips a bit more.
Don't worry, the pain is temporary.
Stop, Kotomi!
What?
You know you can't change
your mind now?
If that's what...
Kotomi wants...
then I'll do it.
But, not right here.
Why?
I can't do this in front of Kenta!
Miyuki!
Kotomi wasn't given a choice.
I remember, she cried the whole time,
calling out Kenta's name.
No!
Stop, please stop!
I think a single dose isn't enough.
You've gone too far, Isaku!
I can't let you do this anymore!
Jinpachi, make him shut up!
No, don't hurt him!
Kenta, Kenta!
Miyuki!
Rika?
Where's Kotomi!
Miyuki!
You're doing well.
It's always worthwhile to save
the very best for last.
You're trying so hard to hold it in.
It's only making it much better for me.
Isn't this fun!
Kotomi only needed a single dose.
Kotomi, please.
Please, don't watch this.
Look away!
First Kenta, now Kotomi.
Kids are just too damned selfish
these days.
Go, Jinpachi!
Got it.
No, Jinpachi, go away!
I can't hold it.
If you just...
let it all out, you'll feel much better.
Can't hold it.
Kotomi, don't.
Come on, you need to watch
until it's finished.
Hey Munemitsu, snap out of it!
Tell me how to get out of here!
Shit!
Damn it!
Watch this.
All women are whores.
Some just pretend not to be,
but all women are sluts.
No, Rika!
Don't look away, damn it!
Get it inside your fucking head.
Women are willing to fuck any cock!
That's not true!
Look at that.
What a nasty little slut.
They're all being forced to do this.
You're a stubborn girl.
Then take a look at her!
Even sweet, innocent virgins...
will beg for any hard cock...
once they've been fucked by one.
No, you're wrong!
Ha!
Are you telling me that you're different?
Stop!
Look, your pussy is dripping wet already.
What is this?
No, just stop it!
I'll teach you right now to beg for cock!
This is great!
You're a bitch,
but your pussy is super tight!
No!
You might be a virgin,
but your pussy seems to like fucking!
You're Kotomi!
Kenta!
I know that...
I can't expect you to forgive me.
I'm sorry, I was so angry.
While Isaku raped me, Miyuki got away.
I just couldn't think straight.
I just....
What I did was wrong.
There is no excuse for what I did.
But please...
you have to help Miyuki!
I'm trying.
See, Miyuki...
likes you a lot, Kenta.
I have to go.
Stop, just stop!
Hey, Jinpachi,
here's what you've waited for.
Miyuki, I'm sorry!
I....
I thought you were much better
than your sister!
Are you her rapist?
My god!
You're....
You animal! You sick,
psychotic, piece of shit!
You haven't given up yet, have you?
No!
Looks like...
you need something extra
to put you in your place.
What do you mean?
No, not there!
Stop, please stop it!
You'll see, you'll learn to like it soon.
Several kids were inside the old building.
One of them brought a candle,
which apparently started the fire.
The building was destroyed.
All the students perished in the fire.
I couldn't have thought of a better plan.
Now, here we go.
No!
You stupid cunt!
You'll pay for this!
Kenta!
Are you okay, Miyuki?
Is that really you, Kenta?
Everybody's waiting for you!
I have to stay.
Miyuki?
I let him violate my body.
He raped my sister!
I wasn't able to...
get revenge for her.
Just forget about this, it's not your fault.
Let's go.
We have to get out before it's too late.
Kenta!
Miyuki!
I have the keys to the emergency exit.
Everyone's waiting.
Damn, I should have had more fun.
There's Kenta!
You're all okay.
The raging fire ended this horrific
nightmare for all of us.
We're sure Isaku perished in the fire...
but his body was never found.
Like a bad dream...
maybe it was only an illusion,
brought forth by the dark desires...
inside every human soul.
We forcefully believe
in that possibility...
to save our sanity.