Last summer...
Miyuki's sister was raped
in the old school building...
and discovered in a horrible state.
Afterwards...
the old school building
had its windows boarded up.
The building was condemned.
Isaku : Episode 1 : "Rika"
Kenta, do you have any cool plans
during your vacation?
I wish I had some girl to spend it with.
Shit, I know, we're surrounded by hotties.
You don't have any plans?
I'm flat broke, so I'll probably watch
videos in my room.
Kenta, does that mean you came across
some good porn?
Maybe.
Can I come over tonight and watch some?
No, you can see it after I'm done with it.
Come on, don't be such a jerk!
Let's check it out together tonight!
Shit, don't grab me like that, asshole!
Having an intimate moment?
Hi Mio. Hi, Kotomi!
You're both such perverts.
Right, Kotomi?
What do you mean?
I guess your room's full
of tons of porn videos.
Shut up, not in front of Kotomi!
What's the matter?
Maybe you want to shoot a video
using Kotomi as your model?
Damn it, shut up Mio!
Don't listen to her, Kotomi, I don't--
Hey, Isaku!
Don't stare at Kotomi, you freak!
He's creepy.
I'm sure he's a sick deviant.
We know about you!
I'm sure you're the motherfucker
that raped...
Miyuki's sister.
Shut up!
Look!
Miyuki.
Soga Academy
I just bought a brand new car.
Let's go for a drive.
Are you sure you want me
to go with you, Munemitsu?
Let me go with you Kotomi.
I'll make sure he doesn't try anything funny.
You know, I'm a perfect gentleman, girls.
Shit, he's such a show-off.
He is the son of the owner of this Academy.
Let's go to the Karaoke bar later.
With you?
They're coming.
Really?
Both Rika and Miyuki?
Miyuki hates guys,
why would she agree to that?
I'd rather not.
But Rika wanted me to come.
So, you're both coming, for sure.
Kenta, are you going?
Sure. Rika's coming along, right?
This is awesome!
We'll meet you later.
You're good at getting girls
to come along.
Ms. Kumi, please don't cling
onto him any more.
It's pathetic.
But, Akemi, I'm not....
I'll be blunt.
You're clingy, and he hates that about you.
You don't have to say it like that.
He doesn't want you in his life
at all anymore!
That's all I wanted to say to you.
Don't push me!
Shit!
Whoa!
What are you looking at!
I'm sorry, Ms. Kumi!
Just admiring the view.
Jerk, apologize!
You both like looking up
old women's skirts!
Akemi!
Why are you being a bitch!
Isn't that sweet?
You have two boys defending you.
Akemi, I didn't...
I have to go.
Here!
I'm going to serve now, okay!
So, why is Akemi such a bitch to Ms. Kumi?
Look at their bouncy tits
and nice, long legs!
This is great!
Where's your camcorder?
Getting fixed.
Hey Kenta, look over there!
That's Isaku!
Don't touch that, scumbag!
Go away, you dirty old bastard!
Damn, hear that?
What are you guys staring at?
Hey, we're just hanging out over here.
I was looking at your ass.
What!
You have a really nice ass.
I want to grab it .
It looks really tight and toned,
like a supermodel.
Is that meant to be a compliment?
Yeah, why wouldn't it be?
This is a public place.
Next time, I'll be more discreet.
That was kind of bold.
Honesty is the best policy.
I've got to go.
Hey Kenta, what's that?
Love letter?
Don't know.
Don't lie to me, you bastard!
Come on, tell me.
Hold on, I haven't read it yet.
I'll read it later.
See you!
Wait for me, Kenta!
What a dick.
Let's see. At 5:00...
meet me in the music room
in the old school building.
I am a stud, after all.
Sorry Jinpachi.
The girls just seem to like me more!
I don't think this is just a joke.
What a fucking freak.
This place gives me the creeps.
MUSIC ROOM
Here it is.
What?
What are you guys all doing here?
Kenta, was this one of your bright ideas?
No.
I got this letter.
It's the same letter.
I'm not buying it.
So you didn't write this note, Kenta?
Of course it's him, Rika.
Why did you do this?
I didn't do it!
Miyuki!
Jinpachi!
What brought you here?
I assume everyone's here
for the same reason.
So, you received the letter, too?
Correct.
Same here.
Kenta, just admit it.
Nobody else would do this.
Now, wait a minute.
Isaku was hanging around.
Isaku?
I saw him near the entrance, too.
But, I don't think....
I'm getting scared!
This is stupid. I'm leaving.
Akemi...
I don't have time for this kind of bullshit.
What was that?
Fuck!
Hey, this isn't funny.
Hey, Kenta.
You scared me!
What's wrong?
Kenta, I thought....
I thought you wrote that note,
to tell me something.
It's not me.
I was happy.
Rika!
Stop!
What?
Not here.
Right.
Rika!
I need to go!
Hold on!
We can, after Karaoke, okay?
Sure.
Later!
Kenta.
Are you okay, Rika?
I need to use.
Yes?
The bathroom.
Sure, be careful.
Yes!
What's up?
It's you.
The door's nailed completely shut.
I'll give it a shot.
Shit, it won't budge at all.
We'll have to find another way out.
Okay, let's split up and look.
Okay.
Kenta!
This is kind of embarrassing, Kenta.
I'm soaking wet now, what should I do?
I can't control myself, Kenta.
Kenta, Kenta!
I can't wait anymore!
Kenta, look at my pussy!
You're making me so wet.
Punish me for being a bad girl.
Please, punish me!
I want you so bad!
Have you found a way out yet?
Not yet.
The stairs to the third floor
has been blocked.
Does that mean that we have no way
of getting out of here?
There's got to be a way out.
Where's Kenta?
He's not back yet.
Do you know if Rika's back
from the bathroom yet?
Jesus!
Please don't tell me you let her go
to the restroom by herself?
Jinpachi, let's go look for Rika.
Yeah, let's go.
Please, find her for me!
Don't stress out.
Don't worry Ms. Kumi, we'll find her.
That's right.
We'll also bring Kenta back, too.
Damn it, this place is completely
boarded up.
What is this?
A videotape?
View in the media room, Isaku.
That bastard!
You look cute like that.
No!
It's a great view of your pussy.
Stop!
Who are you?
You deserve this.
What?
Hi Rika, how are you feeling?
Jinpachi, but why?
Wait, who is he?
What, you're Munemitsu!
But why?
Untie me and let me go!
Somebody, help me!
What's wrong with you,
why don't you say something?
You did say, "Look at my pussy," right?
Please stop, Munemitsu!
No, why are you doing this?
Stop!
What did I do to you to deserve this!
Make him stop, Jinpachi!
Don't film his face.
The problem is,
you know what we've been doing.
Don't kill me!
Kill you?
A good idea.
Please don't, please don't kill me!
Good, will you do anything we want?
Yes!
Good girl.
Repeat what you said
in the bathroom for us.
No, I can't!
Stop!
No, pull it out, right now!
You're soaking wet, but you can't repeat it?
I can't.
You're pulling too hard!
That really hurts, please don't pull on it!
You know what to do, right?
Look at my wet pussy.
I can't hear you!
I'm a naughty little girl.
Please punish me!
I see, so you want to be punished!
Yes!
You slut, you'll get your punishment!
All women are dirty, filthy,
piece of shit whores!
What?
Now, your punishment!
You whore, you slut, you filthy bitch!
Hey Munemitsu, that's enough!
Move!
It hurts, please stop!
It hurts!
Don't!
Can't breathe!
You want more punishment, right?
Yes, I'm a bad girl.
I need more.
Not so deep!
It's too big!
Stop!
I only want Kenta!
Not this!
I'm sorry!
God, it's filling me up!
Don't stop, keep going!
Rika!
Isaku!
That sick pervert!
Ms. Kumi, what should we do now?
I really don't know what we should do.
Kenta, you were gone for a long time?
I was!
You found this videotape, correct?
I found it in the hallway.
This no longer sounds like coincidence.
What?
You were gone for so long.
What are you trying to say?
Are you sure you didn't film this?
How dare you!
Or you're the one raping her.
Fuck you!
Wait, Kenta!
Damn it, let go of me now, Jinpachi!
Kenta, I hear you're really fond
of porn videos.
Jinpachi, you!
I haven't said anything!
I don't think Isaku can do all this by himself.
Maybe you're working with him?
Cool it, Munemitsu.
So you're accusing me?
You were no longer satisfied
with just watching porn, right?
You fucker!
Stop it, both of you.
He had no right to accuse me.
I always thought you were a fucking prick.
You both need to stop.
You're making matters worse by arguing.
You really are completely useless.
Ms. Kumi.
Everyone stop fighting, right now.
I'm going to find Rika.
Hold on, Mio!
At this very minute...
something even worse could
be happening to Rika.
Don't go, Mio!
Somebody stop her right now, it's not safe!
Are you okay, Ms. Kumi?
Let's go Jinpachi!
Yeah.
Nobody else leaves the room.
Isaku, you sick fuck!
Where the hell is Rika?
Rika!
Scream if you can hear me!
-You take that side.
-Sure.
This wasn't my fault!
It really wasn't my fault!
Everyone knows it's not your fault,
Ms. Kumi.
If that's what you want to believe, go ahead!
I can't stand this any longer.
No, Akemi!
Move, I'm leaving!
I guess I don't have a choice.
Shit!
Where could they have taken Rika?
Are you, Isaku!
I was sure I heard a noise.
Maybe I'm tripping.
The masquerade of shame has begun.
Who will be the next victim?
The tragedy has just begun.