No!
Don't!
Stop!
Let me go!
No!
Stop!
Isaku, stop!
Please stop!
Munemitsu, where's Rika?
Where's Rika, let her go, damn it!
Munemitsu, why are you doing this?
Hey, Rika!
Your friend's calling you!
Rika!
Rika, are you okay?
Stop, help me!
No!
Isaku: Episode 2 "Kotomi"
Stop!
Don't!
Somebody!
Please stop!
Stop it!
Help me!
Please!
Kenta, help!
What's wrong, Miyuki? You look upset.
I'm all right.
Really, I'm all right.
Just making sure.
The guys are really late.
That's true.
How was it, Jinpachi?
Were you able to find Mio?
I haven't found her yet.
I hope she's okay.
Kenta?
Where's Kenta?
Where's Kenta and Munemitsu?
We split up, so I don't know.
Let's go back to the music room.
This room reminds me...
of that stupid video, so let's leave!
Akemi....
Hold up, Akemi!
Akemi despises me so much.
That's why...
I don't think so, Ms. Kumi.
Let's hurry back to the music room.
Wait!
Where's Miyuki?
No!
Not Miyuki, too?
Can't be, it's not my fault!
It's not my fault!
Ms. Kumi!
I didn't do anything!
Ms. Kumi, wait!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to barge in!
I heard a noise in here.
And....
That's fine, just leave, okay?
Sorry!
Whatever.
Help me, Mommy!
Anybody here?
Is that Kotomi?
I thought that was you.
What happened to you?
Miyuki, and Kenta!
Kotomi!
How are you feeling today,
my little precious princess?
I forgot.
You can't answer me, can you?
Don't you dare scream
or make a lot of noise, got it?
I knew it was you, Isaku!
You sick bastard!
I almost forgot.
If I remember correctly, you hate me.
Maybe...
I can do something special
to make you like me.
Stop, don't touch me!
Please don't!
I'm sorry I was mean to you.
I'm sorry, I mean it! No!
Please, just stop it!
No!
Damned slut, you sound like
you're having a good time.
No, just let me go!
Enough!
I said that's enough, Isaku.
Munemitsu!
Thank god you're here!
Get this bastard away from me.
Untie me.
I'm really curious.
What makes you think I'm here
to help you?
What's wrong with you, Munemitsu?
A filthy scumbag can make you get wet.
You're no different from other women.
You'll fuck anything, as long as it's a man.
Disgusting bitch!
Now you know...
that deep inside, all women are whores!
They pretend to be a prim and proper lady.
Remove their mask,
and you see their true colors.
Rika, Mio, Kumi, Akemi and Miyuki, too.
Even your precious Kotomi.
Kotomi....
No!
Stop!
Goddamn it!
But Kenta, that tape.
It's not worth watching.
It probably shows Mio...
getting raped.
Are we going to be okay?
Hey Kenta, let's go!
We'll be next if we stay here.
Hold on!
We need to find Isaku first.
Well...
before he finds us.
Just slow down, Miyuki!
Wait for us!
Wasn't that a lot of fun, my little princess?
I thought you might get a bit chilly.
This should keep you warm.
I can't!
No more!
Kenta?
Yeah?
About the restroom incident.
Just forget what you saw.
It was embarrassing.
You promise, right?
Wait for me!
Don't leave me!
Please!
We weren't going to leave you.
Good.
Let's get going, guys.
Sure.
Yeah?
What happened?
Is she okay?
It's nothing.
So you can't tell me?
It's not that.
Kenta!
Come on, we need to hurry.
Yeah, we're coming.
It wasn't my fault.
I didn't do anything.
It really wasn't my fault.
Shit!
It won't budge.
Have you tried all the other exits?
How about emergency exits and windows?
It's been nailed completely shut.
I doubt it.
So that means Isaku's still somewhere
inside this building.
I'm scared!
No, no more!
Please don't!
Do you like me a lot more, sweetheart?
I do!
I swear to god I do.
Can't take it anymore!
Say it!
Why don't you say it like you really mean it!
Bitch, cry!
Ms. Kumi!
No!
Ms. Kumi, I've been waiting
for you to arrive!
What's going on?
No!
Ms. Kumi...
Isaku taught me something.
Use force to get what you want.
Only then will I know its true value.
No, stop this, Jinpachi.
Stop it!
No!
Don't touch me!
Go away!
Get away from me!
No, not there!
Why don't you scream out loud...
just like your sexy teacher over there.
We haven't checked out this office.
Let's check it out.
It looks like it's empty.
Where the hell could Isaku be hiding?
Wait a minute, Kenta!
What, Kotomi?
What is it?
I need to pee.
That's fine, but...
we should all go with you.
Come on, let's move on!
Can you wait there for a bit?
Sure, that's fine.
I don't think this is the time to be shy.
I can't, if Kenta comes.
Fine, just do it in here.
What's going on?
I need to talk to Kotomi in private.
All right?
Okay, that's fine with me.
Please don't tell Kenta about this.
I know.
I don't want him to think I'm the type
to do this...
in front of people.
What's wrong, Kenta!
Hey, Kenta?
Hide!
Yes.
No, get away from me, and let me go!
You know, I was planning on enjoying
you as my final victim.
In my original plan...
Kotomi was going to be next.
If you tell me where that girl is hiding...
I might set you free for the time being.
Where is Kenta?
What did you do to him,
you fucking psychopath!
I guess you decided to protect your friend.
No, let me go!
On my way here, I found a neat toy
in the science lab.
What is that?
I think internal cleansing
will benefit you greatly.
That means....
No, stop it!
Don't you dare, stop it right now!
This is much better than living
with the shame of betraying your friend.
It'll be a shame...
if I don't film this for Kenta's personal
viewing pleasure, don't you think?
No, stop, don't you dare film this!
Don't show Kenta!
Now you don't have to be shy,
little miss, right?
Please don't tape this!
How about it?
So, where is Kotomi hiding?
I don't know.
Is she there?
No, don't, you're wrong!
Run now, Kotomi!
I knew it.
No!
Stop, please don't touch Kotomi!
Don't!
An innocent girl wouldn't be wearing
such sexy underwear.
It's not about--
You reek like the smell of a ripe
and ready woman.
Stop, I'm begging you to stop right now!
Just stop, Isaku!
Why is that kids have no clue about
shameful behavior in public nowadays.
I didn't mean to!
See, you're soaked in your own piss.
I'll clean it up for you.
No, please stop, that's really disgusting!
No!
No, get away!
Kotomi!
You taste like milk.
Go away!
You should blame your so-called friend
for giving you away.
What happened?
Where's Kotomi and Miyuki?
It's just you and me inside here, little girl.
I'm the only person that can see
what's happening.
As you promised, you're going to empty
everything out completely for me.
Please...
promise me, don't say anything to Kenta.
I don't want him to know!
You should be worrying
about yourself right now.
No!
I can't take this!
Kotomi!
It hurts!
No, don't!
No!
This is just as I've planned.
Everything is going perfectly,
like I imagined.
Very good.
I love to see the look of shame...
on women's faces
while they're getting degraded.
No!
Previews
Isaku : Episode 3 "Miyuki"