Winner of 2nd Annual Vanilla
Original Story Contest
Original Story by Manmaru
Issun?
What? What? What?
Liz.
Issun!
You have such a cute girlfriend...
...but you're fooling
around with the professor?
You're such scum, scum, scum!
You... You...
Japanese playboy!
Wait a minute Liz...
It's not what it looks like...
There's a reason for all this...
I don't want to hear it!
Liz?
Could you stop?
Issun?
Wha... Wha... Wha...
What?
Issun?
What happened?
I don't know if you'll believe me or not,
but...
The Erotic Adventures of Tom Thumb
Part 2
I was writing a report last night,
but I fainted because I was hungry.
Then a guy who claims to be my
ancestor appeared in my dream.
He said he'll make my life a little better.
When I woke up, I realized
that my body had shrunk.
I was bewildered, and Masumi
appeared all of a sudden.
I tried to hide, but she found me.
She ended up helping
me write my report...
...and when she went to
the university to drop it off...
I don't know,
maybe she's got a weak bladder.
She fainted.
Then Liz and the professor saw me...
...and they thought I was
some kind of a toy...
...and they fought over me.
I finally ended up
at the professor's place.
When we arrived at her
place, she got really drunk.
She was out of control.
Then somehow, I returned to normal.
So I escaped while the
professor was still drunk.
That's how it was.
Anyway, what do you think I should do?
I can't just go home like this...
Issun?
Yes?
You're going to owe me big time.
After all, it's too high to pay.
What? But...
Oh, it's a joke!
Give and take for my sweet darling?
Umm... Why did you call me darling?
Well, the reason for that is...
It's good to be young, eh?
When I was young, I was delivering
brain busters almost every night.
They called me "Dangerous K."
Don't make me unleash Tigerdriver 9!
But I'm nothing but a worthless guy...
I'm so tired...
Liz!
Stop!
Issun...
I can't believe I knew a celebrity...
Yeah...
You normally wouldn't think about
going to grad school if you weren't rich.
What am I going to do now?
Issun?
Just listen!
Yes!
Earlier today, I called you darling.
Do you understand my feelings?
But look at my size...
You make it sound like you're
fine when you're normal.
That was uncalled for.
I'm sorry...
I don't care about your
appearance, status, or wealth.
You'll always be Issun.
My feelings for you will never change.
Liz...
We're very close to each other,
but I feel farther away from you.
It's sad.
Liz...
It tickles...
I give up, Issun.
Liz?
Are you still ticklish?
Your nipples are getting hard.
That's because you're
playing with my nipples!
And does it feel good?
Should I keep going?
Of course.
I always wanted you to do this to me.
Keep going!
I'm not a graceful Japanese
woman, but to you...
I'm sorry, Liz...
I know... I know.
Issun?
Something hard is pressing
against my cheek.
Issun...
I want you to stay still...
I want to feel you as much as I can...
Issun?
Watch me. Okay? Okay?
I was always doing indecent
things while thinking about you!
Playing with myself like this...
I always saw you looking at the
professor's boobs with lecherous looks.
I... I wanted you
to look at my boobs too...
I was playing with my boobs
thinking about those things.
Then my boobs became more sensitive.
I feel embarrassed since
you're watching me...
I feel embarrassed but...
My bean...
I mean my clitoris...
It got bigger...
It got bigger!
My ear... my ear!
It's flowing out!
I'm sorry, Issun...
I can't sleep!
Okay, tie her up.
Okay.
Well...
...if we can reach an agreement with your
father then we'll let you go without any harm.
Just stay still...
My... you're one scary girl.
If we don't keep you tied up,
you might end up biting us...
Listen up, girlie.
If you keep messing with us,
then you won't be going home safely.
As long as we keep you alive,
your stupid father is gonna pay...
Brother.
I want to do it with her...
I want to play with her cunt
while she has her panties on...
Then I want to smell her stained
panties and do her in and out.
I love the smell of urine!
Hey, girlie.
You heard what my partner said...
Can you do what he says?
Damn.
Isn't there anything I can do?
I just love a girl's panties!
Don't even think about running away.
If you try anything funny,
I'll make him attack you.
What do you think you're doing?
You idiot!
Don't lay a finger on her until I say so!
So you better pray that
you go home unharmed...
I won't lay a finger on her.
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Where is he? Where is he?
I really want to have
my cock in and out...
Liz!
Be quiet!
Listen.
There's going to be a
chance for you to escape.
So...
I can't take it anymore!
My cock is starting to ache...
Huh? What's going on?
No! I don't want this!
This in-and-out is so good!
Liz, hang in there.
Am I gonna climax?
Am I?
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
No more...
Help me, Issun...
No!
I love boobies too.
Can't you release any breast milk?
Can't you?
No...
Help me, Issun...
No.
It's getting wet.
Huh? It's not going in.
My eye... my eye!
It burns!
My eye... What happened to my eye?
My eye...
You're supposed to be a grad student.
Can't you even keep quiet?
Useless fool!
I didn't want to hurt you,
but you leave me with no choice.
You couldn't even follow
my simple directions.
So...
I'll bust your knees
so bad that you can't escape!
My life was really short...
Nothing good ever happened...
Well, finding out Liz likes me and
doing it with the professor was good...
The only things
I can recall are erotic things.
I'm a no-good human being...
Huh?
If you think about it, there's no way
I could've stopped that steel pipe...
...with a body this small.
My ancestor was useless
till the very end...
Idiot.
I'm starting to lose consciousness...
Ah, useless guy!
I might be willing to help you and the girl.
Really?
Since I'm a kind person.
Then hurry up!
Please help us.
I can't just let our clan die out like this.
Then hurry up!
Issun?
I'm really glad you're alive...
Issun ran head-on into the
pipe and there was a flash.
You went flying and...
But after the flash,
you returned to your normal size...
I'm really glad...
I guess that ancestor
was useful after all...
Issun... I can hear your heart beating.
Same with me...
You're right, Liz.
Your heartbeat...
Your cock got bigger.
Wait a minute, Liz!
No way. No one will get in our way now.
Nothing to obstruct.
It's time to have sex.
But right here?
Plus, people might see us.
I'm lovin' you, Issun.
Did you mean those
words you said to me?
I like you...
I like you, but...
Then it's natural to have sex.
Your cock is getting all sticky.
Wait a minute!
Don't you want to do me?
It's not that...
It's my first time doing it with you, Liz...
So you know...
Oh, so you want to do
the missionary position?
She doesn't seem to get it, but...
Oh, well.
Don't worry...
No, not that...
It's tight!
Your hot stuff is coming out!
Sorry. I released it inside...
You're sorry?
I was happy...
Your cock is still rock hard!
Never tapped.
I can keep going too...
Again.
Once more.
It's going all the way in...
Deep inside...
No...
Issun... Issun...
My boobs... no...
Liz, lift your legs up and
try moving on your own.
My private area is exposed.
I'm embarrassed.
But it feels good right?
Yes.
I'm about to climax.
No, not doggy style.
Hey, Issun?
When should we get married?
Oh, yeah...
Let's do that when we graduate.
This is embarrassing, but I have no
confidence nor money to make you happy...
Money is no problem...
It's not like that.
I have to make you happy on my own...
Okay, if you say so...
Tomo! Issunbashi!
Tomo!
Why did you leave without me?
My spare panties...
Who are you supposed to be?
His wife!
Well, you see...
Issunbashi!
What do you mean you got married?
I like you so much that
I dream of having sex with you!
So I thought I would tell you my feelings.
I came here to tell you how I truly feel...
It's just not fair!
Well, you see...
The marriage hasn't been finalized yet...
But I guess we're engaged...
Issun!
Why aren't you speaking confidently?
You told me before in bed that you
want to marry me after we graduate!
What?
Now calm down, people...
Then who's it going to be?
What?
Well?
It's nice to be surrounded by
rich and beautiful women right?
Nevermind that.
Help me get out of this situation!
What's wrong?
You're good for nothing!
That's not necessary...
Not again!
Tomo?
Where did he go?
Issun?
Tomo!
Issunbashi!
Issun!