Mommy...
Stop it!
G-Spot Express
Rail Two
Did you touch her?
That provocative college girl, right?
I was scared at first,
but she responded well.
I sensed danger, so I left right away.
Violence isn't our thing.
Everyone was impressed
with you the other day.
Maybe you can check out
the other guys' work too.
Good luck.
His specialty is college girls.
That girl is something else.
My butt...
He's putting his finger in my butt...
Yes...
It feels good.
Stir me up like that.
I'm coming...
She was totally waiting for it.
Yeah.
You don't seem well, Katsu.
I'm fine.
So tell me...
Are there a lot of girls like that these days?
Yeah.
It's no fun when they
come looking for it.
There's no thrill in it.
I saw something on the web...
You mean the guys who commit violence?
Are times changing?
I won't allow that kind
of stuff on our turf.
His specialty is older women.
Check that woman out.
That look is priceless.
Katsu?
Shit.
Hey you!
It's okay now.
That cop woman is a pain in the ass.
What's wrong, Katsu?
No...
No!
Please stop! No!
No! No!
No!
My butt!
My butt is going to split!
It hurts! It hurts!
Katsu, look.
Hey, are you okay?
Stop it!
I'm so sorry, sir.
We'll be more careful from now on.
Thank you...
You shouldn't go over
board like that, Katsu.
It was okay because we
were saving someone...
But it sure is strange
to have them thank us.
How stupid.
You!
Why?
It's fun to get groped.
Why'd you call me out here
in the middle of the night?
You know the girl Yumi?
Yumi?
Sure.
I want you to tell her to stop.
I'm not a counsellor.
That's your job, isn't it?
She won't listen to me.
Besides, I think she has a crush on you.
If she that's what she
wants, why stop her?
Besides, some people want to be groped.
You liked it too, didn't you?
Enough to make you pee.
Hang on a second!
Katsu, look the other way for a bit.
These guys want revenge for
their buddy being busted.
What do you think?
It's none of my business.
Stop it!
Do you think you'll get away with this?
No!
This is a crime!
Do you think...
Do you think that this kind
of thing will do us women in?
I will never let you beat me!
No, that's my butt...
What are you doing?
What's that?
Stop...
Don't do anything stupid.
It's so cold!
Please, you can still stop.
I'll forget about the rest of it.
It's going into my stomach!
Stop!
There's no more room!
It hurts!
No!
My stomach hurts!
It hurts.
Will she lose it?
Please go away.
I can't bear it anymore.
It's going to come out.
Please don't watch.
Why are you guys doing this to me?
I won't forgive you!
I swear I won't!
Oh no, it's coming out...
I'm going to bust every single one of you!
I'm surprised that she lasted
this long after three loads...
Lots of hot stuff inside of me...
Aren't you going to arrest me?
I'm going to catch you
in the act and arrest you!
Just you wait!
I'm looking forward to it.
What is she doing?
In an empty train like this...
Yeah, you're right.
What the hell?
Damn...
Fine.
If that's what she wants...
Hang on, Katsu!
Oh well.
What's this...
This is stupid.
I'll make her come.
Stop messing around.
You both want this, don't you?
Enough!
Next!
Wow...
I'm going to come! I'm going to come!
Yes!
I'm coming!
Me too! Me too!
It's hot...
Lots of hot stuff inside of me...
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
Stop!
What are you...
Let go of me!
Let's see, what am I going to do...