No way!
No...
No.
G-Spot Express
Rail One
It happens more in the summer.
You've encountered it too, haven't you?
What are you talking about?
Takaoka, what is this week's topic?
Perverts.
Per-verts!
Yes, yes.
Sometimes it happens to me
too and it pisses me off.
They say you should be flattered.
I don't know about that.
Well, today, we're talking
about the gropee, not the groper.
There is a theory that even
women like you want to be groped.
Please don't out me like that!
Data says that more than half
of the women who get groped...
...either enjoy it or actually
even want it to happen.
Young people these days would
complain if they didn't want it.
Let's see, what am I going to do...
All right!
In other words, there are women who
want to be groped in a crowded train.
If you don't fight back, that's
as good as saying "it's okay".
There is a train approaching
track number three.
Please stand behind the yellow line.
Don't try to scare me.
There's that woman again.
This isn't good.
Shit!
Just my imagination.
No!
What?
No! Stop it!
No...
Someone...
If you do that...
It's almost my stop...
I can't...
That was so-so.
I'm sorry.
That girl.
Don't worry.
I wasn't paying attention.
But I bumped into you...
I'll put the rest of these back.
I'm really sorry.
She doesn't even realize.
Silly thing.
I see.
There's nothing you could've
done if you couldn't move.
There's no point in
catching the wrong guy.
Yeah, besides...
I couldn't just leave that girl alone.
What is it, Sayaka?
Um, well...
I have to go to the bathroom.
Are you okay?
Our jurisdiction ends in two stops.
Hang in there.
See you later.
Can this train go any faster?
I should have gone at the last stop.
No!
You've got to be kidding.
That guy!
Why now!
If I move now, I'll pee in my pants.
No way!
We'll be at the next stop
in just a little while...
Then...
I have to...
I have to hold it.
I can't pee here.
If I didn't have to pee,
I'd bust him right now.
No, no way!
No...
I can't...
I'm going to pee...
No!
She peed.
That was unexpected.
I bet she learned her lesson.
Shameless girl.
You made her pee.
Very impressive, young man.
What are you talking about?
I wonder if that guy is a cop.
But he didn't catch me in the act.
There's nothing wrong
with being more careful.
How did he...
Shit, he's been watching me.
He's...
No, no way!
No, not my butt!
That old man...
I've been watching you.
Me?
It was such a pleasure watching
you it made me feel competitive.
Have you been doing this long?
What do you mean?
Your groping history.
That's none of your business.
You sure embarrassed that
female cop the other day.
So she was a cop...
Your guts, your technique, you
seem like an experienced veteran.
It's a natural talent.
So...
I've had my eye on you.
An OK gal?
They're famous on the railroads.
They're waiting for guys to grope them.
In other words, perverts.
Why are you telling me this?
Even just watching you at
work sends chills up my spine.
My name is Ginji.
People call me Gin.
Sounds interesting.
All the other guys are watching you too.
We all want to see how you're
gonna cook up that girl.
Let's see, what am I going to do...
Express
She stands there knowing that being
close to the door...
...is the most likely place to get hit.
We'll make a wall around
you, so you can go for it.
That woman...
Yes yes...
Sometimes it happens to
me too, it pisses me off.
She's that TV announcer.
We all want to check out your
technique.
Voyeurism and groping
aren't so far removed.
Are you scared?
I won't force you.
That a boy.
Just like the old man said.
No bra, huh?
She's for real.
Not bad.
What an announcer.
No...
Not that!
Oh my God.
Amazing...
It feels so good.
I'm going to come.
N-No...
I'm coming!
Hot stuff...
Inside me...
There is a theory that even
women like you want to be groped.
Please don't out me like that!
You just proved it first hand.
He came inside her!
You boxed her.
Boxed her?
In other words, you did it in the train.
Oh.
Not that many guys pull that off.
Brother, you are good.
To be continued...