What are you so down about?
Well...
lf you're gonna be like this,
what the hell are you gonna do?
Have some attitude.
You hold the key that will
change the world.
But...
l think l drank too much.
Right. This is it. Right here.
Get us a drink, boss!
Comin' up!
What's with this guy?
Looks fuckin' depressing.
What a dumpy old man.
l stuck these fingers up you.
Have a taste.
Hey, how about you spread it open
with your own fingers...
...nice and deep.
l knew a woman like you once,
a while back.
A masochist who loved
to be teased.
Not true...
Then, how do you like it there?
Yeah, just as l thought...
You'll take all the fingers
l can give you. Nice and wet.
You want it? Huh?
You want me to stick it in you?
Yes...
Say ''Please''. Say,
''Please give me your cock.''
Please stick your cock in me...
You're a real nympho, aren't you?
Feeling yourself up and
moving your hips around.
Well, l guess
l'll just have to do this hole too.
l moved your daughter to
another place.
Looks like you were just a bit too late.
Are you dead yet?
Cut! All right, well done!
Good work.
That's it for you, Koji.
Pretty impressive there.
We've got the takes
everyone else said were impossible.
Pretty dependable guy, this one.
He's the one who's pushing to do
these dangerous stunts.
lt's a fine line between a
daredevil and a fool.
We found a
brutally murdered male body!
All units report to the scene at once!
That's pretty bad, l tell ya.
Chopper unit is on its way.
You think it's the same as the
Bay Bridge incident?
There better not be another one
doing stuff like this.
Wow!
lt feels great being near the sea!
You can smell the salty air.
We're not here on vacation,
you know.
Lighten up a bit. Don't be so uptight.
Right, Miko?
What are you doing?!
There's nothing like a woman's crotch!
Good morning, Detective.
l'm only letting you on site because
of direct orders from the Chief.
l understand that. And l don't
find this one too interesting.
Let's just say
it's part of our dirty business.
Yes. ln regard to that,
we can clear it up by tomorrow.
Doctor, please rest assured that
l'll take care of this.
The damn politician's dumping
all over me on this.
Come in.
Chief, l've dispatched them to
the Bay Area crime site.
l see. Good work.
So that means
he's the only one not here?
You guys looking for me?
Good morning, Mr. Yamada.
l hope you're not behind this.
l don't have the kind of
artistic sense you see there.
Then, are you telling me there's at
least another responsible for this?
lt looks like this is a job where
you might have to risk your life.
l can only wish.
All right, we're bringing down the body.
Get in touch with the chopper.
No!
Hold it! That body falls
under our jurisdiction.
Don't you touch it!
What the...?! You guys?!
Come on, Detective.
lt's just for a short while.
Why are you so stiff, huh?
Wh-What are you doing?
Well then, Ms. Takamizawa.
lt's in your hands.
Hey!
lt's done, old man!
Let's just see how good
they are at solving this.
Shh! You're too loud.
What if someone hears you?
You sure can be small-minded.
l can't do it. l can't do
something so horrendous.
What are you talking about?
lt's too late for
second thoughts now.
No! l don't want to!
Don't be so shocked.
You did that.
l did...?!
l don't know about that.
Well, it's not like l don't like you.
l think you're very intriguing.
You don't have to worry.
l know very well that...
...everyone calls me ''zombie
woman'' behind my back.
Well, uh...
Who'd want to sleep with a
woman that looks like a corpse?
This is work. lf we know what
happened in his last moments...
...it might give us a clue to
solving this crime.
But, you know, no matter what
anyone does to me, l won't come.
Won't come?
Or rather, l'm not able to come,
so don't feel too bad.
l understand.
Go on in.
Koji!
Wh-What the hell is this
smell of blood?!
No! You mustn't transform now!
Wh-What's the deal with
this house, anyway?!
Well...
l-l'm sorry...!
l can't stand it any longer!
All right. Let's begin then.
Hey, take a look.
Oh, yes...!
lt feels so different this time!
Why's that?!
That's the first time l came.
That's what it feels like
to be alive.
Take these and you'll get a
taste of something so amazing...
...you've never had in your life.
What do you think?
Don't know...
Hey, how long does it
take this drug to hit me?
Where the hell did he go?
Never mind that.
We didn't pay for it.
lf it doesn't work, big deal.
More! More! More!
Are you going to kill me too?!
Koji! Please, no!
K.Y.? What the hell is this?
Koji.
What is it?
You forgot this.
Oh, damn, l left it. Thanks.
Wearing the ring of some old flame?
That's none of your business!
That person... lt's like
she's calling out for help.
She's suffering,
in very difficult circumstances.
Are you saying Yuki's alive?!
Well, it's the first time l felt
something when touching an object.
l'm not sure myself
what to make of it.
Touch it again!
We're supposed to have a
professional relationship.
lt's not right to mix
our personal lives in with it.
Just once more!
Please check it out again!
Don't you listen!
You really are a zombie!
You don't know anything about
the human soul!
That's right.
l am a corpse after all!
Stop it!
Well? Can you see any visions?
l see nothing now.
Honey, are you going to be
able to take next Saturday off?
Sure, no problem. We can all
go out together as planned.
Where are we going?
Where would we like to go?
l'd like to go to the seashore!
l wanna go to the amusement park!
You too, right, big sis?
Yeah!
All right! We're going to the
amusement park then!
Darn. So, l'm going to be
surrounded by brats all day, huh?
The victim wasn't aware at all
that he was in danger.
The assailant approached
from above...
...where the victim wasn't looking.
Either he has some superhuman power...
...or perhaps he's able to fly.
The victim was taken by an enormous
force that he couldn't resist.
He was only able to flail his limbs
about in futility.
The assailant is...
...a bird? An animal?
No, he appears to be somewhat human...
...but the victim was dead before
he had a chance to see his assailant.
What he saw after that was...
...an image of his own body
as he faced his death.
As he was played with like a toy...
...l wonder how he felt.
...can you believe that?
Oh, look. There he is.
He's not even a student but always
wondering around doing nothing!
There're a lot of
men like that these days.
l hope he doesn't commit
some weird crime.
You have to keep an
eye on men like that.
l wish they'd be more subtle
with their gossiping.
Hey, it's Yuta. Wow, what an
amazing gun you've got!
Grandpa bought it for me.
Yeah? You sure have a
good Grandpa.
Yeah. But you know...
...he always brings home
the same toy.
Hey! lt's Mom!
l'm back, Yuta.
Oh, Mr. Yamada.
On your way home from work?
Yes.
Let's go home, Yuta.
No way!
l wanna hang out with Koji!
Come on, Yuta. Don't be
difficult on your mother.
That's quite some underwear
she's got on.
Die, you evil demon!
Aghh! You got me!
Come on, Yuta, he's a busy man.
l'm sorry, Mr. Yamada.
lt's all right.
Yuta...
When l have a day off,
we can spend more time together.
Yeah!
Good day, then.
Good day.
Koji!
Bye!
Huh?
The key's gone.
l'm sure l locked the door though.
Wha...?
What is this?
Sneaking into my place like that?
Lighten up. A pretty woman is
here to see you, after all.
lt would be nice if you showed
a little more enthusiasm.
l don't have much interest in
skanky bitches like you.
Oh? Now l know why you were
getting excited by some housewife.
l saw it, right through the window.
Apparently her husband's been
missing for six months.
How do you know all that?
lf you listen to the ladies talk...
...you can find out about
everything in the neighborhood.
Koji...
You think you have a chance,
don't you?
Well, she's not at all the kind of
person you think she is.
Really...
Let me give you one piece of advice.
You know, the ''natural'' types...
...they're the ones you
have to be most careful about.
When you strip her from that shell,
you could be in for a shock.
Shut up!
How scary.
What are you doing
in my apartment anyway?
l got into a fight with my boyfriend.
So, can l spend just one night here?
lf you let me stay, then
l'll let you have me just once.
Who'd wanna do it with you.
Oh, really.
Don't tease me. Hurry!
You just wait.
Hurry up!
Get on your knees, bitch!
Upsy-daisy...
What are you doing?
You mean this?
l don't sleep very well unless l do
a handstand before l go to bed.
That's pretty different.
Oh, no...!
The walls are thin in this place,
so keep quiet.
My chest hurts...!
After this...
...tomorrow will be all lovey dovey.
This is boring.
Strong will power.
Wh-What is it, Koji?
Don't you have your period?
Why do you ask?
l should be getting it any day now.
l smell blood.
What? Then that's a problem.
l don't have any tampons.
Oh, what a drag. l just got it now.
What?
What's the matter, Koji?
What's wrong?
Stay away!
What?!
l know you wanna do it, there's
no need to get all freaked out.
l told you that at the beginning.
lt's not like that.
Who'd do it with you anyway?
What is this stench of blood?!
lt's as if there's blood
splattering all over me!
What's the matter?
Stay away!
The multiple murders must be his doing!
What should we do?!
Get in touch with everyone!
l'll try to hold him here!
Uh, all right.
This is an emergency!
Everyone, please hurry!
A monster possibly the multiple
murderer sighted near Koji's!
He's going after the monster!
Everyone, head over to the site!
lt's finally started.
lsn't this just
what we were hoping for?
But one or the other will die.
That can't be helped.
Otherwise there's no way of
knowing who's stronger.
Come right over here.
l'll set up a great stage
just for you guys.
Wha...?! What is this?!
Let's... Let's go home.
No! You just watch carefully!
lt's strong...!