The burgeoning metropolis
of Tokyo...
Of those who lurk in the
dark underbelly of this city...
...some cower in the
darkness itself...
...while others seek pleasure
to escape the darkness.
This man may very well have been
a victim of the forces of darkness.
ln response to such unusual cases,
Police Chief Kanzaki had...
...gathered up a group of people
with unusual abilities.
A man who regularly
risks his life in movie stunts...
...in order to forget his past...
...Koji Yamada is a
member of that team.
This loner of a man found some
happiness in his friendly relations...
...with a female neighbor
and her son.
Koji was chosen as partner to Jun
who has the clairvoyant ability...
...to see the last moments of a victim's
life as she climaxes during sex.
The sex was supposed to be
loveless and dry...
...but Jun was mysteriously
aroused and...
...had become
emotionally drawn to Koji.
However...
...the anguished soul of Koji...
...who had taken the life of a
former lover with his own hands...
...was closed and unyielding.
Meanwhile, from the visions
as seen by Jun...
lt was clearly determined that...
...the perpetrator of the multiple
murders was not human.
But there were no further leads.
Also, their leader, Chief Kanzaki
had been monitoring the lives...
...of the team members
for some unknown reason.
Then there's the mysterious entity
that oversees the murder...
...and Kotani, the man
which the entity possesses.
As Koji seeks to get to the
root of the first murder incident...
...a second murder had taken place.
The perpetrator that
appeared before Koji...
...was a savage and evil monster.
At the end of the battle...
...the monster had
disappeared without a trace.
The sex murder investigation
team on the trail of the monster...
...was able to use Jun's abilities
to discover a suspicious old man.
Meanwhile, Kyoko Tamachi, who
has left for town with her son...
...was met by a groping pervert
on the subway.
She was not able to control her thirst.
Following the old man, the team
was led to a subway station...
...where they came upon a
sexually enslaved Kyoko Tamachi...
...and her son Yuta.
As Koji and team stood
in blank astonishment.
...the monster appeared once again...
...this time reducing the
subway station to a killing field.
That bastard!
This time it won't be like the last.
Koji!
That bastard!
Koji...
Koji... Koji...!
Please stop this. lt's a massacre.
Quite a show, huh? Humans
seem to like to hurt each other.
But you started it all.
Shut up!
A pathetic old man like
you shouldn't be complaining.
Koji...
Don't die, Koji!
l've never seen a
case like this before.
A very powerful toxin is being
released from that object in his arm.
The toxin is in the process of
spreading at the cellular level.
We will have to amputate
his arm immediately...
...or his life will be in danger.
Amputation?
Yes.
There's no other way.
l'm sure he'd give up
an arm to save his life.
l don't understand how he's
keeping himself alive so far.
And l don't know...
...how effectively surgery will
prevent the toxin from spreading.
Does that mean he's going to die?
He could go either way.
ln other words, we can only hope
that he's got a strong life force.
He was the first man who was
able to give me an orgasm.
Koji...
You're the man who could remind
me of what it means to be alive.
So...
So, please don't die.
l don't want you to die.
Koji...
Koji... Koji...!
Koji, we came together.
l'm alive, Koji...
l'm alive...
Chief, lnspector Shibuya is here to see you.
What is this?
l can't accept it.
l don't think l can handle my
responsibilities given the situation.
You are doing a great job.
lt's awfully inconvenient when
you can't make any moves...
...until a monster appears.
We've picked up one suspicious man...
...and we're hoping that
he will give us a lead.
Right. Well,
l'm counting on you.
l can't accept this letter.
l need you on my team.
Y-Yes, sir!
Now, get back to work.
Excuse me.
Chief, why would you let a
man like that off with his pride?
lt's not pride. That position is
perfect for a lowly man like him.
lt would be inconvenient
if he had any sort of ambition.
This guy's useless.
l think he just lost his mind after
seeing that monster.
Thank god.
l thought for sure that
you were going to die.
Don't be stupid.
You think l'd die so easily?
You were in a coma for five days.
Even l was worried.
Five days, huh?
You'll get used to it after a while.
Yeah, l suppose l'll manage.
The amputated arm has been
properly preserved.
With some further research,
we might re-attach it one day.
l won't get my hopes up.
Where's Jun?
Actually, l haven't seen her.
l guess she's just a
heartless woman in the end.
After that incident...
...l thought that happiness
would never come to me.
Brother!
No... no...!
No!
l'll show you!
Mother...! Sister...!
Mother!
Mother! Mother!
No! Ow, ow...! lt hurts!
lt hurts! No!
Oh, yeah! Nice and tight!
That's good...!
Yeah, make it tighter!
Make it tighter!
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, it's about time we got outta here.
That's too bad.
l was supposed to have been killed.
But for some reason...
...l couldn't go where my
mother and father had gone.
But, Mother, Father...
An important person in my life has
returned from the edge of death.
l've never thought l'd be as happy
as this day since that time.
You're here.
Yes.
The flowers were wilted.
l'm out soon. Why bother?
Not yet though.
l don't think you realize it...
...but you were pretty much dead.
l don't think there're any more concerns.
Here. l'm returning this to you.
Did you have a vision?
Well?
You know, Koji...
l think you should forget about
that woman you call Yuki.
l feel that you'll become
unhappy chasing after her.
Jun...!
Anyway, it looks like the monster
problem has subsided...
...so you should take advantage
of the time you have off.
Otherwise...
Stop fucking with me.
Say it.
l don't have anything to say.
Say it!
Jun...
Do you know why
l was inclined to join our team?
lt was so l could search for Yuki.
Why? Yuki's...
The one who told me Yuki was dead was...
...Kanzaki.
l never saw her remains.
That's why l can't
truly believe that she's dead.
Kanzaki knows something.
l figured that if l stay near him,
l might come across a clue.
l see.
But l'm being honest when l say
l don't know anything.
l see...
l'm a 28-year-old housewife.
l have plenty of time on my hands.
lf you are looking for casual sex,
give me a call.
Multiple partners are okay too.
We're pretty lucky,
finding a woman like this.
lt's gonna be a major league fuck fest!
And she's got a pretty damn good body too.
l wasn't like this before.
You liar.
A woman like you could only
be a nympho from birth.
But it's true.
Please, put it in here.
lt's all because of that man.
He's the one who turned me
into a woman like this.
Stop! Please stop!
That hurts! No!
Stop it! Yuta will wake up!
Your son isn't going to wake up this late.
Please, stop...!
You just have to obey what l say.
That man is now dead.
He died at the hands of his own father.
l despised my husband.
There's no doubt he's the one
who lured me to this world.
Just as he once told me, l should
be thanking him for this.
Oh, l can't escape from this pleasure...
This is getting really bad.
Since the only people who're
getting killed are men...
...l feel we should just
leave them to themselves.
Stop spouting that nonsense
and get back to work.
All right...
What's the matter, Koji?
Yuta!
Yuta! A stretcher! Get a stretcher!
Who's that?
Looks like a young man.
l don't see any wounds, but be careful.
Yes.
That old man?
What are you talking about?
All right. l'll be there soon.
Let me go! Let me see my Yuta!
How did you know that
your grandson was here?
Yuta...! Yuta...!
ln the subway incident, that old
man was at the station Yuta was at.
You think he can read
his grandson's movements?
Yuta! Yuta...! Yutaaa...!
Yuta!
They'll find us out.
Don't' worry. Nobody can see us.
We've gotta go deal with the son.
Well, let's go see what's
going on, and then just go home.
All right?
You're the one who found this son.
l think you could show a
little more concern for him.
You're awake.
Where's my Mother?
Huh?! Well...
Your mother's gone far away for work.
She'll be back soon, so let's do
our best to manage on our own.
lf you have any problems, you can
always come to me, all right?
Well, how's Yuta?
No change.
You said you know him from before?
He lives in my neighborhood.
l don't understand how a mother
could just leave her son like that.
She didn't seem to be that
type of woman to me.
ls she beautiful?
She seemed very sweet.
Mo-mo-mo, Mother!
What's the matter, old man?
Koji...
Damn...!
What the hell...?!
Yuta!
Koji!
What is it?
Was that young man really the monster?
Looks that way.
Hurry up! Or we're gonna lose him!
Don't worry.
As long as we've got the old man
here, we'll know where he went.
He's headed for his mother's.
l can't imagine where else
he'd want to go.
His mother's?
You see, l'm here to protect my mother.
l get it.
This is how the son
protects his mother from danger.
Your cock stinks a bit.
So you say. But you sure seem
to be getting off from sucking it.
The smell of smegma is strong.
l'm sucking on a filthy thing.
l'm so hot inside,
l'm just dripping all over.
Hey, lady. Are you for real?
You must be insane.
Let's see that hot pussy of yours.
Let's have a look.
Let's see...
Looks like you sure get around.
You must be a real pro.
Ever taken a look at your own pussy?
Your pussy lips are all black.
That's such a terrible thing to say...
l...l can't take it anymore.
Please, hurry...!
Hurry...!
l've never fucked a woman
this dirty before!
Hurry, l want your...
...big cock...!
lt's right in!
This big cock is getting shoved into me!
Wh-What a find she is!
lt's so damn good to fuck the
brains out of a total slut!
Shove it in nice and deep!
lt's so deep! lt's so deep!
M-My clit...!
lt feels so good!
l'm gonna cum...
l'm gonna cum...!
Sh-She's cumming!
Mother!
Wh-Who's that?!
Mother...
Christ. What the hell are you
bringing your son around for?
Cramps my style.
Mother...
Yuta!
Why are you in a place like this?!
Why? Well, that's 'cuz l'm here
to protect my Mother.
So l can get those guys that
try to hurt you.
Don't be stupid!
Hey, come on. Don't be so
fuckin' cruel to your son.
Mother.
Let's go home, Mother.
A...A monster...!
Mother...
Stop it!
Huh?!
Yuta!
Yuta! lt's me! Remember?!
Koji?
Mother?
What on earth has happened to you?!
Why do you look like some
horrendous monster?!
Mother...
Am l so strange?
No! Stay away!
Mother?
Listen Yuta, you are to never
come near me looking like that!
l'm living my life the way l want!
You're going to have to do that too.
No way! l don't want that!
l want to be with my Mother forever!
l can't have that!
But... Don't you love me?
When l think about it now, l
couldn't care less if l had a son.
Sons are inconvenient and
they get in the way.
l hate them!
Mother...
Yuta...!
Who the hell does she think she is?
You think l want a son that
looks like that?
Don't ever show your face
in front of me again!
Mother...
Mother... Mother...
No! Yuta!
Oh, no!
Koji!
Koji...
Yuta, stop this now!
Koji!
lt's finally happening.
l'm getting excited. Hey,
who're you betting on?
Bet? You're kidding?
At this rate it's never going to end.
You've gotta enjoy some more.
Hey, it's you.
Good work.
Yuta...!
Yuta...
Koji!
He's trying to do a mind meld.
Mind meld?
Koji's trying to enter Yuta's consciousness.
Yuta...
Yuta!
Koji...
l can forgive you, Koji.
You don't do bad things,
so l can forgive you.
l'll forgive you. But...
Your rear gets nice and tight
when l fuck you in the pussy.
Your asshole's puckering up
nice and tight.
Let's just see
how much of a slut you are.
Ow...!
Spread open my asshole for me...
More, more...
l'm gonna cum!
l'm gonna cum...!
Help me! Help me! Help me!
No! Yuta!
Koji, l'll forgive you
if you don't get in my way.
Stop this now!
Yuta...!
l protected my mother.
l've done good.
They haven't moved in a while.
Shall we give it a go?
No, just leave this one to me.
She's gone in.
Koji's now at one with the monster.
She's trying to help him from inside.
Can that Jun do stuff like that?
Yuta...
l want you to hear me out.
You'd have a lot more fun playing
with the toy your grandpa gave you.
Don't you think?
l don't wanna play games.
l wanna protect my Mother.
l can't do anything with those things.
lf you want to protect your
mother, l can help you.
You just have to wait at home.
l want to stay with my Mother forever.
But that doesn't mean you
can go around killing people.
Come over here.
No!
Yuta...
Yuta!
Mother!
Mother...! Mother...!
Jun...!
Mother, l got the bad guys!
l got them for you!
Really? What a hero.
Let's go home together.
Yeah!
This could be a problem.
What's the matter?
His mind's resonating with the son's
and the son is starting to relax.
Do something about it.
That woman who went after
him has done something.
The bitch.
What's wrong, Mother?
You're not my Mother?!
Mother...? Mother...?
Where's Mother?!
Yuta!
Mother...!
l want you to disappear from my life!
Mother... Mother...
Mother!
Koji!
Yuta! Don't do it!
What a crazy bastard, that Koji.
Very well done.
l'll be letting him know that
you've done good work.
By the way, have you made
preparations for the next?
Of course.
Very well.
l'm looking forward to it.
What a pompous bastard.
And he doesn't even realize
that he's being used.
The old man was cleaning up after
the mess left by his grandson.
That's why he was always
at the crime scene.