The burgeoning metropolis of Tokyo...
Of those who lurk in the
dark underbelly of this city...
...some cower in the darkness itself...
...while others seek pleasure to
escape the darkness.
This man may very well have been
a victim of the forces of darkness.
ln response to such unusual cases,
Police Chief Kanzaki had...
...gathered up a group of people
with unusual abilities.
A man who regularly
risks his life in movie stunts...
...in order to forget his past...
...Koji Yamada is a
member of that team.
This loner of a man found some
happiness in his friendly relations...
...with a female neighbor and her son.
Then there's Jun Takamizawa.
Also burdened by a sordid past,
she is one of the undead...
...unable to die as she exists
with the darkness of her soul.
Koji was chosen as partner to Jun
who has the clairvoyant ability...
...to see the last moments of a victim's
life as she climaxes during sex.
The sex was supposed to be
loveless and dry...
...but Jun was mysteriously
aroused and...
...had become
emotionally drawn to Koji.
However...
...the anguished soul of Koji...
...who had taken the life of a
former lover with his own hands...
...was closed and unyielding.
Meanwhile, from the visions
as seen by Jun...
lt was clearly determined that...
...the perpetrator of the multiple
murders was not human.
But there were no further leads.
Also, their leader, Chief Kanzaki
had been monitoring the lives...
...of the team members
for some unknown reason.
Then there's the mysterious entity
that oversees the murder...
...and Kotani, the man
which the entity possesses.
As Koji seeks to get to the
root of the first murder incident...
...a second murder takes place
in his own neighborhood.
The scent of blood takes hold...
...and causes Koji's abilities to
burst out of control.
And finally...
...the perpetrator of the murders
makes its appearance...
...it turns out to be a savage
and evil monster.
Able to metamorphose on his own,
Koji attacks the monster
leading to a fierce battle.
As Kotani lurks in the dark shadows...
...and Chief Kanzaki spying
on the subordinates...
...the work of Koji...
...and the sex murder investigation team...
....has only just begun.
Goddamn monster!
What are the twins doing
at a time like this?!
l can manage without
counting on you people.
This isn't the time for talk like that.
We're going to be in big trouble
unless you people power-up.
What?!
Thank god. Nobody died.
What's the matter with you?
Why would you say that?
Eventually we're going to
have to settle this.
Sooner or later, someone will die.
Yuta.
Good morning.
Good morning, Koji.
Where's your mother?
She just went home to get
something she forgot.
l see.
What happened to you?
Did you hurt yourself?
Yeah, just a little.
l was bitten by a dog.
Does it hurt?
No problem.
l'm a man so a scratch like this
doesn't hurt at all.
lt's just a little irritating.
A woman would've been
crying long ago.
l know that men have to
protect the women...
because they're weak.
Are you going to kill me too?!
Koji! Please, no!
l wasn't able to protect Yuki.
l could not save her.
What's wrong, Koji?
Oh, it's nothing.
Wow, you're pretty smart.
You see, l'm here to protect my mother.
l guess you have to take over
until your father comes back.
That bastard should never come back!
Yuta...
Yes?
Yu...Yuta.
Father...
l have to go to work now.
You don't like your father, Yuta?
Yuta.
Oh, good morning.
Hello.
So, you were having a
chat with Koji. That's nice.
Let's go, Mother.
Huh?
What's wrong?
lt's nothing.
Let's go.
l suppose.
Bye.
There's no smell of blood in here.
l don't want you to wear
yourself out because of this work.
Don't you worry.
l've closed up all the rooms
that may be a problem.
What's happened in the past
in this house?
l don't remember the past too well.
Oh, yeah, nice and wet.
ls that all the information regarding...
...Koji Yamada?
Y-Yes...
That's information
l already know from the monitors.
l don't think you have any idea of
what's expected of you.
Chief.
What are you doing?!
No! Please, no!
No! No!
Please stop!
No!
Huh?
Well? lt's about twice the average man.
No... No...
You're exposed for everyone to see.
Let's have everyone take a
good look at you, right here.
Please stop.
lt seems like your clit hasn't been
properly stimulated yet.
lt's too perverse.
Mako will be stimulated
by leaps and bounds.
l can't take something
that's so big...!
l'm gonna die...!
This is too much...!
l-l'm coming...!
l can't even stand anymore.
Good work.
l permit you the use of the
equipment for 24 hours.
Thank you so much!
Mother, how is your cold?
Oh? lt's better now?
Thank goodness.
Listen to me, Mother...
My plan is coming along very nicely.
l'm sure that soon the world will
become just the way l want it to be.
Just be patient a little longer.
You'll be able to go outside soon.
Flowers, huh? Wouldn't dried
flowers be better suited to you?
l hope you're not mistaking me
for some kind of lover.
Don't be a smart ass!
Just finish what
you've got to do and leave.
l know that already
without you telling me.
What's wrong?
That's pretty pathetic,
at such a crucial time.
l'm just not in the mood.
Do you need the smell of blood?
All right then, l'll oblige you.
Hey. What do you think
you're doing?
Don't worry...
My body's been long dead.
l can stab myself or anything
else, and it won't hurt a bit.
l guess dead bodies don't bleed.
Don't worry...
l'll make you come even
without the smell of blood.
Right. Like you're any use.
How about with these?
Fingers aren't going to do it for me.
We can only find out if we try.
Stop it.
Come on.
lt's getting nice and wet.
Nice and juicy.
lt feels so good.
Good, isn't it. Say that it's good.
lt's...good...
lt's just pouring out.
lt's getting good and hot.
lt's so hot and deep inside...!
Yes, yes...!
You like it?
You feel it?
Yes, yes...!
l'm alive! l'm alive!
l'm alive!
Yuki!
l'm coming!
You know?
What?
Can you try again and see if
you get any visions?
Please.
Please leave.
How's the sex with Jun?
She's quite the special lady...
...you know, with the cold touch?
Gen...
Why doesn't Jun die?
That's a difficult question.
Let me ask, why is it that
you can metamorphose?
lt's the same thing. No one knows.
Jun has some reason why
she cannot die even when dead.
Hey.
Hey, listen...
Let's do that again.
Don't be stupid.
Huh?
l don't mix work and pleasure.
Good morning, Chief.
lt appears that Jun has some
special feelings for Koji Yamada.
More important is the issue of the ring.
We don't want him to know
about his lover.
l know that.
l want you to keep a close watch on him.
Yes, sir.
Nothing but bits and pieces of clues.
l'm sorry that it was of no use.
lt can't be helped.
He is a formidable man.
Not the type to
leave himself unguarded.
What's the matter?
Just wait a sec.
There's something in common
between the two incidents.
What?!
l see it!
There.
Yamada!
l'm sure he was the old man who
was looking at Kyoko and Yuta.
l'm sure of it.
l hope those two are all right.
After sending out the sketch
to the various police stations...
...we've heard back from the
police station in District No. 4.
Get there as fast as possible.
Mrs. Tamachi! Mrs. Tamachi!
Mrs. Tamachi left to go
to the department store.
She took Yuta.
Department store?
Are you sure it's this old man?
lt's not a photo,
so l can't be completely sure.
This face and the fact that
he uses a cane...
He looks a lot like the loner
who lives in the 3rd district.
What kind of lifestyle
does this old man have?
l've never really seen him
talk to anybody.
He just looks kind of blank. Like
there's nothing going on up there.
Maybe a little senile?
Maybe. But he's never
caused any trouble.
Come in.
Yes?
Where are you going?
Before there's another victim,
l thought l'd try to beat him to it.
We found that old man.
He's headed toward
Ginza on the subway.
Ginza, huh?
Mom, l love trains.
Really?
You're so lucky you get to
ride on a train everyday.
When l go to work, there are
many more people riding...
...so l get tired just with the crowds.
l can't say l like it.
You don't like trains?
Well, l don't know...
Oh...
Mother! Mother!
Don't worry. Lots of people will
get off at the next station.
S-Stop...
No... No, you mustn't...!
Oh, no...! lt feels so good...!
lt's so big.
l want it in me.
l want it shoved into me.
S-Stop...! Please stop...!
What's the matter all of a sudden?
You were enjoying it.
l'm about to come soon.
Come on, keep going.
Please stop!
Mother, l don't think this is
the department store station.
l know. l just have something
l have to take care of.
Like what?
Yuta, you be good and
wait for me here, all right?
l'll be back right away,
so you just wait here.
All right?
Mother?
Hey, check it out! She's pretty hot.
All right, l've caught up.
There he is.
The old man's sighted.
On the subway,
headed for Awaji-cho station.
Gotcha. l'll get ahead of him
so we can trap him.
You think so? You sure
we're not being suckered?
Don't worry about it.
lf some bastard comes around,
l've got this.
What are you doing? Hurry...
Looks like something
interesting's about to happen.
l can't take this anymore.
l don't care what happens to me,
but just let me leave this place.
How can you be so irresponsible?
You sowed the seeds for this.
l...l did?!
Hurry, hurry, please hurry it up.
Wow, this is incredible!
She's totally soaked!
Hurry, stick it in me.
Stick your fat cock in me.
All right then,
l'll stick my cock in you.
Harder... Fuck me harder...
What are you doing?
That's not going to do it for me.
Deeper, deeper, go deeper.
l've never met such a
dirty woman in my life.
Let's give her the time of her life.
Hey, let's switch.
Oh, yes...!
Oh, yes... Keep going...!
What a woman.
l've never had this before.
Hey, lady.
How about two cocks at once?
Yeah... Do anything you want.
Drive me crazy...!
lt's that man's fault that
l've become like this.
Keep going...! Keep going...!
Yes... More, more...!
Wait a minute.
l feel as though
l've heard that voice before.
What's the matter?
Uh, it's nothing. Let's go.
Yuta!
Hey, it's Koji!
Where's your mother?
She said she had something to do,
so she told me to wait here.
But it's been a long time, and she
hasn't come back yet.
Oh, yes...! More, more...!
Mother's late.
l'm going to go look for her.
Wait.
Listen, Yuta.
You're mother's not the kind of
person who'd lie, right?
l'm sure she'll be back soon.
So, let's just wait here a bit longer.
But...
She could already be on her way back.
What if you miss each other?
Hey, Yuta!
Yuta!
Huh? He's gone!
Hey, lady...
l'll give you my cell phone number...
...so, when you're in the mood,
you can call us.
This could become a regular thing.
Unlike your husband...
...we've got a lot more energy,
so anytime's okay.
Do l look like
l don't get very many men?
Well, you were sure lovin' it.
Hey, lady.
Let's get out of this place and
go to a hotel for some more fun.
Please stop.
l'm sorry to say this but l just used
you to fulfill an immediate urge.
What?
l've got to get going,
if you'll excuse me...
Hey, wait a minute.
Come on, lady, you've gotta be fair.
We do you a good service and
you just dump us like that?
l'm not interested, now let go!
Cut the crap, you nympho.
You really want more, don't you?
No, stop it!
Stop it!
Pl-Please stop!
What are you going to do to me?
l'm getting real horny
lookin' at you like that.
Don't fight us, and we'll
treat you nice and gentle.
l'm begging you to stop this!
What do you mean ''stop''?!
You couldn't get enough of it
a little while ago.
The sound came from over here!
Hey, stop it. Stop it.
No!
Hey, wait!
Yuta! Yuta!
Koji! We got the murderer!
Murderer?
Two dead in that toilet over there.
There's no doubt it's the same assailant.
He was at the crime scene...
so at the very least he's a good witness.
What a terrible thing.
Go, go...!
You said you caught the murderer?
Well, uh...