I'm so sorry.
What're you doing here?
Mika?
You're so pathetic, Big Brother.
You're drooling all over yourself.
Mika!
Urara! Here I come!
Urara...
So, she's Mika's friend.
Boy! Spring's come to young lovers across the world.
But for me, it's always winter.
This sucks!
Hey, Hiromi!
Ha Nanahoshi!
You wanna go for a cup of coffee?
Maybe next time, I've got a prior engagement.
Excuse me! Could you wrap these?
Next time, huh? It's been three years since the first next time.
It'll always be this way for Hiromi and me.
Yo, Nanahoshi!
Doda?
All alone?
Well excuse me for being alone.
Catch ya later, Nanahoshi!
Where shall we go next?
Asshole!
If he takes her to a hotel or something, I'm gonna...
Mom! I asked you to shorten my skirt!
Now I can't go to commencement! It's too embarassing!
Hiromi!
Catch me if you can!
Hey, Hiromi! Wait for me!
Don't look...
But you're...
Urara-chan?
Please be gentle, this is my first time.
Urara...
Is this okay?
Yes, softly now...
...so softly...
It was just a dream... I'm really losing it!
Will I spend my senior year just dreaming of girls?
What's up?
Are you lost?
Yes... are you Mika's brother?
I'm sorry about the other day.
No problem.
Which class are you in?
I'm in 1-A.
Oh, that's my sister's class, too.
Follow me.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Urara, I've been looking for you. Oh, Big Brother.
See you later.
What was that about?
Your big brother is so nice.
You think so?
He's just a slob who bums around the house all the time...
Man, my sister's so rotten!
Compared to Urara, they're as different as night and day...
And Urara's light shines so brightly...
Get outta here!
You useless bums have gotta go!
When girls become seniors, they're not so cute and sweet anymore.
Compared to girls like Hiromi who've been corrupted, underclassmen are so pure and innocent...
If I'm not pushy, they'll fall under my control...
I wish!
Kakeru, wanna come to my place?
Excuse me!
Doda!
What an asshole!
Doda! Hey, wait for me, Shuichiro!
She even calls him by his first name, "Shuichiro", and you know what that means...
Man, screw him! Screw Doda! He's got his hands on Hiromi already!
It's not just a hobby anymore. He can beat the pros now.
If you want, you can have some of these.
Want some coffee, Kakeru?
Sure, thanks.
No way! He must like Mika...
He found out!
Mr. Big Brother!
Mr. Big Brother, please!
Get away from me!
Mr. Big Brother, please give me your approval to go out with her.
You! She's my little sister!
Idiot...
Coming!
Oh, Urara.
Good evening, Mika invited me to spend the night with her.
I'm pleased to be here.
Mika! Urara is here.
Well, let her in.
Thank you for having me over!
Let's take a bath together before dinner.
I brought some extra clothes.
You have a great body.
Thank you, so do you.
Thanks, but I could stand to lose a few pounds.
I won't get horny over my sister's body.
Let me wash your back.
Thanks!
Mika, you're in the way! I can't see!
It's so hot! I'll open the window.
Ah, it feels so good.
Hello...
Hiroma? This is a surprise.
Nanahoshi, can you come out now?
So, what's up Hiromi?
I know that you've liked me for a long time, Nanahoshi.
I've felt it...
What are you saying?
You can do whatever you want with me now.
What? Oh, yeah!
Hiromi...
What are we doing here?
Hey, Hiromi!
I like you too, you know, Nanahoshi.
But don't you think this is a just a bit sudden?
You know...
...girls don't function as smoothy as boys...
...when we have to operate our heads and bodies simultaneously.
But...
Her body that I've dreamt about...
...is right here in front of me.
Are you sure about this?
This is like the dream chance of my senior year.
Hiromi...
Oh, Shuichiro!
Ah! Right there!
You're making me crazy!
Shuichiro!
Nanahoshi?
You just got dumped by Doda, didn't you?
You're trying to forget him by sleeping with me, aren't you?
Sorry, I can't do that.
I won't take you on the rebound.
I'm so sorry!
Come on! This isn't the Hiromi I know!
You'll forget all about him by tomorrow.
Trust me.
Maybe I shouldn't have been so conscientious.
It was my first real chance and it would've been with Hiromi!
Urara...
Nope, I was right!
Uncorrupted, innocent Urara!
She should be my first!
Doda!
Nanahoshi?!
Don't even think about it with this girl!
Don't get your panties in a wad!
I'm just trying to recruit her into my club.
He's telling the truth.
Then keep your hands off her!
Are you jealous?
Big Brother, please don't!
See ya later, losers!
Listen, that guy is a snake!
Okay, but why...
Why are you so worried about me?
Because...
...you're my little sister's friend and...
...I mean...
...I think of you as my own sister!
What?
So pretty!
Look!
Boy! She is sooo cute!
Kakeru!
You're late, Takeshi!
Never mind that!
Mika went to the dirty lingerie resale shop!
What?!
Hey! There she is! There!
Urara-chan?
Oh! Mika's big brother!
Where's Mika?!
Oh, she just left.
Mika!
Takeshi must really like her...
Oh yeah!
Come with me!
Ouch! What's the matter?
Your curiosity will lead you down the wrong road! You understand?!
We just went in there to turn them down!
What? Turn them down?
You thought we were cooperating with them?
I can't believe it...
We just went in there to tell them not to follow us around...
...because a friend at my previous school kept bugging us to join them!
I'm sorry, I thought you were...
But I'm glad you're worrying abouth me so much.
Urara...
Yes! Now Urara and I have bonded!
I guess I should stop ridiculing Takeshi.
Coming!
Good afternoon!
Oh, hi!
I'm supposed to study with Mika today.
The sky looks kinda weird, doesn't it?
Please come in.
Mika went to my aunt and uncle's place with my mom.
They should be back any time now.
Okay!
The forecast for the Kanto area is sunny, turning partly cloudy.
There's a 30 percent chance of rain.
They're running late.
The phone!
Hello, Nanahoshi residence.
Oh, Mika, Urara's here now.
Here, let me get her...
Hello...
Hi, Urara. I'm so sorry.
There's a gale wind in this area and the trains aren't running.
My uncle insists we stay here.
I'm sorry Urara, we'll have to cancel our session.
That's okay.
There's a spring storm here. How about there?
It's not too bad, but...
We should stay inside untill the wind dies down.
Right!
Oh shit!
Sorry! I took your picture without asking you!
Urara...
I've had a crush on you ever since...
I saw you at the commencement.
I really like you!
What'll I do now?!
This situation wasn't covered in any of the manuals or videos!
Ouch!
Sorry!
Please be gentle with me.
Urara...
This is my first time...
But it'll be okay since it's with you.
What do I do next?
I've watched a lot of pronos and read a lot of magazines but...
I feel like I've been swept away!
According to those pornos, I should...
Don't look at me.
It's okay! It'll be okay!
You're driving me crazy!
Nooo!
Sorry!
No, it's okay.
But please don't hurt me.
It's okay! It'll be okay!
No! Don't look!
Please don't stare at it!
Oh, sorry...
That feels great!
Here I come...
Ouch! That's not he right place!
Sorry, this was my first time, too.
I'm happy... I'm very happy.
Urara...
No regrets, okay?
What's wrong?
No way! It's back already?!
That's a quick comeback!
Let's try again, Urara.
Let's try again.
This time I'lll...
Urara...
I'm scared!
It hurts!
Urara!
I'm so happy... I've got no regrets.
Good morning!
Oh, good morning!
Big Brother...
When I daydream while looking at the enternal flame...
I feel the whispering of wind...
The reflection of your smile in my eye is so dazzling...
Shining seasons come and go.
Times overlap again and again.
Loving each other...
Hurting each other...
As we slowly become adults.
I'll never forget...
Those precious moments.
I'll look at you from so far away,
Just as I did in those days.
You're smiling at me in my fading memory.
I still remember that innocent promise...
When I finally met you after so many days and nights.
I wanted to hold onto you forever...
From those days...