Come on!
This is Calcutta, India.
I'm at Victoria
Memorial Hospital.
A miracle is about to
happen at this hospital.
A woman who has been sleeping
for more than a thousand years...
...is going to wake up now.
Her name is Surya.
She is a princess of the
Guptas that ruled northern India...
...from the 4th to the 6th century.
I'm going to be interviewing...
Dr. Aikawa, an archaeologist studying
the Kama Sutra, the one who found her.
Doctor, would you tell us
how you found Princess Surya?
And that was the story.
I see, it must have
been a difficult experience.
Oh no, compared to the troubles the
princess had, it was nothing.
Now, I'd like to ask
several questions about her.
It is difficult to thaw frozen meat
or flesh because the cells are fragile.
How can you restore the body to life?
I don't know, myself.
Not with modern technology, I mean.
What do you mean?
Semen and love juice.
Love juice?
You know, you got wet when you did
something with your boyfriend...
Well, you know now!
Grandpa!
Oh, Ryu!
I love you, Ryu.
What's the matter?
I felt Yukari kiss me.
That's impossible...
Who is he, Doctor?
My grandson, Ryu.
Nice to meet you.
And this is my assistant, Shakty.
I'm Yakko!
You can call me Indy, though...
...if you'd like to...
Most of the ice around
her has been removed.
The preparation for revival
is in its last stage now.
Doctor, I suppose
this is the hardest step now.
Shakty, give me the cup.
Yes sir, it's ready.
What's that, Doctor?
The Sex Cup...
This is the answer to
your previous question.
What do you mean?
The legendary cup
that gives eternal life.
We put semen and love juice into this.
Semen and love juice?
That's right.
And, look what happens.
Doctor, is she...
Just pray to God.
Prayers are unnecessary.
The power of that cup is
not given to just anybody.
It can only be given to
the ones that God loves.
And that is Surya.
And, the one she weds.
Doc!
Look!
Gopal...
He's dead now.
My father, Beshuma,
the old shaman of our tribe...
...has just passed away.
From now on, I, Rudracin will succeed
my father as the head of the Naga Tribe.
Surya and the Sex Cup will be ours
soon after the mourning period expires.
It was my father's unrealized dream.
Follow me!
Eternal life will belong
to the snake tribe, Naga!
Ryu!
Take a break and have some donuts.
We're going to take Surya downtown.
Will you help her to the car?
Okay...
But, are you all right Surya?
Thank you, but you worry too much.
I can even walk now.
See?
Sorry, Ryu.
You've been sleeping for
more than a thosand years.
Take it easy on yourself.
It's all right, I just took a wrong step.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Miss Surya.
Watch your step.
See you later!
It's time to learn, Ryu.
Learn about what?
Doc asked me to teach you.
In Japan, they go like this...
Come on baby, I'll teach you how.
Come on!
Is this what I'm going to learn?
The actual skills of the Kama Sutra...
If you love Surya,
you must become a man yourself first.
But, I...
You're such a wimp.
I'm going to pinch you.
This is the missionary position.
This is the chamber of
the missionary position.
We can't take any other position.
How can we get out?
If you keep moving your hips to shake
the floor, it will part and let us out.
My hips?
Right.
First slowly...
Don't rush.
Slowly...
Harder...
Deeper...
This is the chamber of
the female-on-top position.
Enjoy the feeling of my skills.
Shakty...
Forget the skills...
Okay, let's go for it!
This is the chamber of
the sixty-nine position.
This time, enjoy my tongue.
Shakty...
You must have missed this.
Yes, it has not changed at all.
Truly...
Doc.
It's the press, I'm a famous man now.
Famous among lechers.
Hey, here they come!
Hi!
Naga!
Yakko!
Got it!
Think you can escape?
Mommy!
Something to throw,
something to throw...
Wiper on!
Boss, we'll be in the
shopping district soon!
I know that!
This game is over!
I have come to take
you back, Princess Surya.
Damn it...
Ryu, take it easy.
Yeah.
Yes, yes...
It's for you.
For me?
Yes, Ryu speaking.
Ryu, it's me, Yukari!
I've just arrived at the hotel.
I waited for you to call but you didn't.
So, I came after you!
I want to see you now,
will you come over?
Damn it, I'm too busy now!
You're so mean!
I've come here all the way from Tokyo!
All right, I'm jumping
out the hotel window.
Hey, wait a second, um...
You can use the
telephone in Surya's room.
Hold on, I'm changing lines.
I envy young people.
That's the reason.
You see?
So, I'll call you in a few days.
I promise.
I'm hanging up now, okay?
Is it my imagination?
Ryu!
A-A snake...
There aren't any snakes.
Oh, stand up already.
My legs...
It's surprising that you have no guts.
He hates snakes by nature.
Anything long is...
Doc!
I was just joking.
Get on the train bound to Cuttack
leaving at 9:30 A.M. tomorrow.
Be sure to bring the cup, if you report
this to the police, Surya will be in trouble.
Come in.
Oh, the porter.
We don't want any food.
W-Wait a minute.
Where is the cup?
Is that the real one?
What about you, did you bring Surya?
You are quite dashing.
Woman, my man is waiting outside.
Go with him.
Come in!
Surya!
Shakty!
I was so worried.
That's close enough!
Business first.
Hello.
Hello, Shakty?
Oh, Ryu, Surya is safe!
I see, I'm glad.
You want to talk to her?
Yeah.
All right, wait.
Hello, Ryu?
Surya!
Ryu, I knew you
would come to help me.
Just hold on, we'll have
a happy ending soon.
Ryu...
Surya...
How romantic...
That's enough, give me the cup now.
You should listen to this first.
What are you doing here?
Police!
You're under arrest!
You never meant to trade
from the beginning, didn't you?
How embarrassing...
You must pay for this.
I won't bargain with the price.
Good.
The final blow!
Yeah!
Hi, you made it, Ryu!
It serves you right!
The drama has just started, Mr. Ryu.
I got the cup.
I'll come back to get Surya later!
Surya!
Ryu...
Ryu!
Where am I?
In the hospital in Calcutta.
You've been unconscious for two days,
it must be a shock losing you lover--
The doctor said you have to stay still.
The policemen are keeping watch
outside and we'll be taking turns staying here.
Well tonight--
I'll stay!
For Ryu, I'll do my best!
Doc...
Please take care of her, Yukari.
Will you keep an eye on Yukari?
Don't worry!
Do you want to help Ryu?
In that case, we'll trade him for Surya.
I can't do that, never!
I see.
Oh, no, how terrible!
You know what to do, right?
Forgive me, Surya.
I have to help Ryu.
Women will do anything for love!
Hello, Yukari!
It's too easy.
Boys, let's get going!
W-Wait a second!
Where's Ryu?
You promised me!
I know that, come on out!
What's this, a fake?
Yukari!
What are you doing?
Gee!
Wait a minute, Yukari!
I love to hear screams.
What?
Did some bird crash into this?
Ryu, we've got Surya.
What?
I brought you your lover instead.
Have a nice time!
But just a short while.
Bye-bye!
Ryu, I missed you so much!
What's this all about, Yukari?
I couldn't help it, they
said they would kill you.
You mean you...
I couldn't help it...
I just couldn't...
Do you know what you've done?
It's all over now.
They don't have any
reason to let us live now.
Oh, no, what will we do, Ryu?
I don't know...
Open the door!
You will be as flat as a pancake!
Take off your clothes!
Put them between the walls and
the floor to stop them from moving.
Hurry up!
Okay!
Shit!
How about your side?
No, it won't stop!
What's going on with your body?
Well, it's kind of a reflex.
I'm in...
Is this our last...
Y-Yeah...
We're gonna die...
Is that you, Yukari?
You can't die, hold on--
My goodness!
Just help us out!
We'll be crushed, hurry up!
Okay, guys!
Here I go!
Good thing I can piss high!
It stopped...
How's the drug?
It will lose its effect soon.
We'll hold a wedding until she is awake.
We're already prepared.
Eternal life will be ours.
Oh, Grandpa!
Oh, you're safe.
But how did you...
Yukari brought us here.
Huh?
We planted a tracer on her shirt.
We put them on everyone, just in case.
It's started!
We have reported to the
police, too, they're very quick.
Let me see.
Indian Police sure
like to put on a show.
They aren't the police, they're soldiers!
Where's Surya?
I'm sorry but we
cannot get married today.
It seems we thought too
lightly of your friend.
Princess Surya, we must leave now.
What if I say, "No"?
Then I must act disrespectfully.
You already are disrespectful.
This way.
Ryu!
Over there, it's Surya!
What?
Surya!
Where are you going?
I'll go ahead and save Surya!
Wait, Ryu!
Shambala?
Yes, the underground
utopia, Shambala.
This cup will lead us there.
What is it?
You can go to Shambala, but
you cannot have what you desire.
What I want is eternal life.
Only the one who gets
married to you in Shambala...
...and drink from this
cup can have eternal life.
Isn't that right?
That is correct, however...
Surya!
Ryu!
He's still alive?
What is that?
The entrance to Shambala.
Surya!
Drive through it!
Don't be rash!
Just do it!
Ouch!
Just drive through it!
The sun is underground?
That is the cosmic egg...
The birthplace of the gods...
The egg of the new world...
The best place to
consummate our love.
All right, that's them!
Can you swim, Ryu?
There aren't any boats here.
I'll walk across if I have to!
Do you wish to cross
over to the island?
Yes...
It's expensive, can you afford it?
What about me?
The sidekick can go later.
Sidekick?
One, two, three...
Forty-eight?
My condolences.
Please go up to the altar.
Let me go!
Hold it, you damn snake!
Don't lay a finger on her!
Ryu!
Mr. Ryu, you are as
tenacious as a snake yourself.
I hate snakes!
I meant to compliment you.
Please stay here, I will take care of him.
Choose your weapon.
Weapon?
This is Shambala, if you want
something, just imagine it in your mind.
That's not fair...
Fool, this is the right
way to arm yourself.
Too bad, you missed.
Ryu, behind you!
It must have gone all
the way to the outfield.
Where did he go?
A snake!
Remember your previous life, Ryu!
You were a knight before!
This is for what
happened 1,500 years ago!
Human beings.
Your fate is decided.
Surya will fall into a long sleep
again after she has made love.
It is done in order to save mankind
after the world is destroyed.
In order to save good people.
This truly is eternal life.
The pure nature of life is destructive.
Human beings are so good.
So good...
Yukari!