Help me!
Please, something terrible happened.
Please, is there somebody
who can help me?
KAMYLA 3
From the information we gathered
from the victim...
we're sure Lead is hiding out
inside this hotel.
The objective is to find Agents
Agatha and Koyomi...
and arrest the criminals.
One of us will enter
the building first...
and give the signal for us
to raid the building.
l want to volunteer, Tsubaki!
Lily, are you sure?
l don't have much experience.
My teammates, Agatha and Koyomi,
are in that building!
lt's my duty to get them
out of there!
All right.
Be careful, Lily.
What's up?
She was snooping around!
I'm sure there's more
of them around here.
Let's see.
Put her in the show
for the time being.
Don't worry about the others for now.
I got it, don't worry!
Let's go!
No!
Your pretty friend is about to become
the main attraction in my show.
One million, two million!
Any more bids?
Sold, for two million dollars!
Congratulations!
The high bids tonight reflects
everyone's exquisite taste.
Tonight, we have a special show
prepared for your viewing pleasure.
Presenting the Special Agent
Rape Extravaganza!
We would also like to present
the fabulous...
effects of our latest drug...
called Bram Walker, also known as BL.
This will knock your socks off.
lt promotes amazing muscle growth...
and functions as a powerful
sexual stimulant.
Over here.
They've been taking BL daily,
for 30 days.
BL has the power to transform anybody
into an inexhaustible sex machine!
These men have not been allowed
to ejaculate for a month!
Right now, all they can
think about is having...
their way with
the Special Agent here.
Enjoy tonight's program
of a Special Agent...
and two, rock-hard studs!
His tongue feels amazing!
No, no!
lt's thick and sticky,
just like warm yogurt!
He's huge!
Stop! lt's so warm.
Feels amazing. lt's so warm.
Wait!
No, not in my ass!
They're watching!
I'm getting fucked up the ass...
in front of an audience!
l'm coming!
No!
People are watching!
My legs are spread...
so wide apart.
so they can watch
the cock fuck my ass!
The special agent couldn't handle
the furious sexual action!
BL, the drug for the best sex
of your life!
Special Agents! Get your hands up!
Thank god, they're here!
Dear, Agatha!
Good, l'm glad you're both awake now!
You've been sleeping for two days,
since you've entered the hospital.
ls that true?
We were out for two days?
You both still need to stay
in the hospital.
l've been doing research on Kamyla.
l almost have it figured out!
lt shouldn't take very long.
l'm almost finished!
Sure, thank you.
Thank you, Lily.
Bye-bye!
They should be coming
to get me soon.
My lovely, little sexy pets.
lf my theory is accurate,
l was right!
Koyomi?
What are you doing?
So, how is my Agatha doing?
They're fine!
Agatha and Koyomi are both recovering
from the effects...
of that evil drug, Kamyla.
You're naive.
l'll tell you something about Kamyla.
Kamyla is a drug that works on
many psychological levels.
lt initially works as a
powerful sexual stimulant.
No different from other aphrodisiacs.
But, it also stops
cognitive functions...
so they can only follow orders.
You can program the user to become
instantly aroused with a keyword.
There's more to it than you could
ever believe.
You can program them beforehand,
and when the time is right...
they will automatically
carry out their orders.
That means Agatha was part of--
Yeah, of course.
You mean the raid
was just a part of your plan!
We let one of our slaves escape...
to lead you to the hideout.
We cut down on security.
As a result, we were able to
get our men more weapons...
and programmed slaves
inside this Special Forces building.
Well, there's your lecture
for the day.
Good job, babe. You'll be
rewarded later for your work.
What a beautiful sight!
Look at all the special agents
kneeling in front of me.
l've locked the other officers
in the jail.
Very good.
lt looks like they're about done.
All right, everybody, wake up!
Agatha, Koyomi!
How does it feel to betray
your fellow officers?
l don't know what's happening now.
All that programming,
and you still have resistance.
Don't worry.
You can make it up to them.
Let your fellow officers
watch you masturbate!
That's not funny!
No way l'm going to do that.
Look!
Look at them, see the look
in their eyes, Agatha?
They're looking at your tight,
sexy body...
and getting a big erection.
Kamyla's has taken over
their mind and body.
Think about it.
A fantastic orgy
with your fellow officers.
Your shameful fantasies
will intensify your pleasure.
Come on, show them
who you really are.
Right now, you slutty whore!
I'm being watched.
They're staring at my large,
erect, hard nipples.
I like it!
It's getting me
even more excited and wet!
Agatha's licking her own nipples!
My god, look at her!
Damn, check out
those fine set of tits!
l want to fuck that pussy!
All right, you can remove
their handcuffs.
Agatha.
Koyomi?
Koyomi, we want to fuck you.
We watched the tape.
You like swallowing come?
Suck my cock!
No, please, no!
Let me do you, Lily! Please!
No, stop it!
You want a hard cock
up your ass, right?
No!
Come on, blow me!
Like that, baby!
l'll get some of this!
Wow, it's shaved and tiny, l like it!
Stop!
She's tight!
Lily, why don't you
give me some head?
l want you.
Hold it!
You belong to me.
You follow my orders.
l'm going to come.
Yeah!
Time for some ass-fucking!
l'm not finished yet, Koyomi!
Yes!
You like it in the ass!
l love it!
l love being fucked up the ass!
Come on,l want more!
Come on, give me more!
Come in my mouth!
All right, l've got some, baby!
That's so yummy, l love it!
Yeah, keep pumping my ass!
l'm coming!
This is my kind of entertainment.
You want to come with me
and go see your boss, Agatha?
l'm taking the other two.
Sure, what about all these guys?
Bring them more women
to keep them entertained.
Good idea.
Stop it!
Let's have fun, Tsubaki!
Here l come!
l love it so much!
How is it?
Are you getting excited
watching your friends fuck?
You can't have any just yet.
You're next, Koyomi!
Chief!
I'm going crazy!
I want it so badly!
My pussy's dripping wet!
I want a hard, thick cock fucking me!
l'm fucking you in the ass, Lily!
l like that, Koyomi!
l'm going to shoot a load!
l want you to come inside my ass!
You know, l think l'm finished.
Five times might be too
much for this old fart!
Hey, Koyomi!
Look here, there's more of this left.
They're taking more!
Goddamn sex-junkie fiends.
My body still wants more, baby!
Give it to me, give me more!
So, Agatha, want to join
your friends for an orgy?
Yes!
Then tell them exactly what you want,
so they can hear you.
Koyomi! Lily, please!
l want you!
l need you now.
Come over right now and fuck me!
Do whatever you want with my body!
Please, right now!
Sure, Agatha!
You need more of this!
Yeah, squirt more milk on me, Agatha!
lt's so good.
Jesus Christ, Koyomi!
My glasses are completely covered
and sticky from your pussy juice!
l think lt's about time
that l joined this orgy.
lt's thick!
Your cock's totally filling me up.
Deeper, deeper, fuck me harder!
Fuck me!
Yeah!
l'll give all of you a dose
of my special sauce!
Yes, come all over me! Right now!
That was a huge load!
Don't think l'm finished just yet!
Now, lick my cock clean
with your tongue.
What's going on?
Did Kamyla wear off already?
All right, it's working!
What the fuck did you do, bitch?
l gave them a different substance,
not Kamyla!
l didn't get the chance to test it,
so l wasn't sure.
l know it was a big risk.
Dammit, there's no antidote
available for Kamyla!
lt's not an antidote.
When this drug combines
with Kamyla within the human body...
it cancels out Kamyla's
mind-control properties.
That's bullshit!
How did you find this drug!
l found it
in your hideout, Lead!
lts effects are similar
to Kamyla in some ways.
Similar effects to Kamyla?
lt has to be Bram Walker,
the new drug!
Shit!
l'm back, too!
Your keywords won't work anymore!
What was that?
Shit, hold it!
l'll go after Lead!
Go get him, Agatha!
This scene is familiar.
Just like our first meeting!
But now, you don't have
a hostage helping you!
l don't need one!
l'll be back to capture you
one more time...
to make you mine again!
l love you, Agatha! My baby.
Damn, Agatha.
That was a great kick.
Nailed me.
You don't have
any other choice, Lead.
Surrender, now!
You know l won't do anything
of that sort.
l'm not going to end my
life in this goddamn shithole!
-Freeze!
-Later, Agatha.
THREE DAYS LATER
The main headquarters...
were severely destroyed by the bomb.
The building is being rebuilt.
Both criminals and officers
lost their lives in this bombing.
However, Lead's body
was not found in the rubble.
He'll be committing crimes again,
in the near future!
l'm sure of it.
Agatha, we need to go on patrol!
You're right, let's go.
Do you want to drop by
the donut store?
You bet, that sounds
like a great idea.
Koyomi, this is yummy!
Hello, Special Forces.
Don't worry, we'll be right there!
Agatha!
We've got to go!
Okay.