This is headquarters.
Suspects have kidnapped a woman...
...and have held her hostage in
the third warehouse since this morning.
Police vehicles are on the way
to the scene now.
I repeat...
Suspects have kidnapped a woman
and held her hostage in the third warehouse.
Late 21st century.
Rampantsocial corruption.
Violent crime is quickly increasing
at an unprecedented rate.
A criminal marketin human sex slavery
had become increasingly common.
In fact, Japanese law enforcement
created a specially trained task force...
...to combat these crimes.
Special agents here!
l want you to release
the female hostage and surrender.
lf you do not cooperate,
we are prepared to use force.
There you are!
But there's only one of you!
Agatha, l'll take the second floor.
Thank you.
l'll take care of what's down here.
This shouldn't be that hard!
You bitch!
Let's get her!
So, who wants to get
their ass kicked next?
Agatha, behind you!
Take this!
Thank you, Lily.
You're very welcome.
-This way!
-No!
Hey Agatha, the suspect is moving towards
the rear exit with the hostage.
Roger!
Koyomi, please follow him.
We'll corner him.
Okay!
Stop right there!
You're not leaving!
Protect me.
What the....
Stop!
l'll say. l will kill your friend
if you try anything funny....
This one, too.
Don't you dare follow me...
...if you want them alive.
What are we going to do, Koyomi?
We'll think of something!
No!
Very nice view.
l'll show you something.
-Lick this.
-Yes.
Suck on this.
l don't get it...
She's supposed to be your hostage!
Kamyla.
A special formula.
A mind control drug
triggered by a keyword.
The victims look and act normal
unless they've been triggered.
The drug's control
over the mind is complete...
...so the victim will do anything.
Like...
Fuck yourself with this.
Yes.
lt's cold!
These mind-controlled slaves
sell for a very good price.
So, this is Zepeche,
the human slavery trade ring...
...and you must be Lead Suits.
That's right.
You would sell at a very good price.
Hey, if she resists, kill yourself.
Yes, master.
These are big!
l really love women with big tits.
No!
Stop it now!
Big tits usually aren't sensitive.
Yours are.
Let's see what's down here!
No, no!
lf you don't want it, why is it soaking wet?
Let's spread this pussy wide apart.
l can see deep inside!
Stop!
You're so wet after only
having your tits fondled.
No, Stop it!
You suck on this.
No!
She'll kill herself.
Use your tongue more.
Move up and down.
An agent that's supposed to put me
in jail is sucking my hard cock!
Here, just for you!
A special surprise.
Time for your medication!
Don't do it!
This is great!
l wonder what would happen
if l shoot this into your sensitive tits!
No!
l'll show you a piece of heaven.
Don't!
My breasts...
...feel numb!
She came again!
A special agent doesn't
look so menacing now.
This?
What do you want with my cock?
l'm begging you....
Fuck my pussy...
...hard, with that hard cock, please!
Please hurry!
lf that's what you want.
Lick this.
Yes.
All right, l'll give you
exactly what you want.
You're going to get fucked hard.
Yes!
This bitch is a damn good fuck.
Damn, woman!
She comes with her tits.
lt can't just be the drug;
l've never seen this.
Fantastic!
Great fucking tits!
l'll keep her for myself.
Yes, l'll be your slave!
Just fuck me more, harder!
More...
Pinch my nipples more!
Now hold it.
A slave doesn't order its master around.
l'm begging you!
Please pinch my nipples harder, master.
l'm coming!
She passed out after squirting her tits.
l'll teach her a thing or two...
l really don't think so.
l know these are just plain rubber bullets...
...but they pack a punch.
Are you all right, Agatha?
l think so.
Thanks a lot!
Koyomi, Lily!
Now l won't get sold to some asshole!
Don't worry about it.
You can buy me lunch sometime.
That's right!
A few days later
Agatha, hurry!
l'm coming!
What?!
What the hell are you doing!
There's my special agent!
What makes you think
you can walk out of here?
Oh, Agatha...
Unfortunately, he is being released today.
You're kidding!
Please calm down, Agatha!
During a drug scan of his body,
the lab found something unusual.
ls it....
They found Kamyla.
During interrogation, he claimed that
he was given Kamyla against his will.
The crime was not his fault.
That's bullshit!
That's what happened.
How could they fall for such lame bullshit?
lt's not bullshit. l'm also the victim here.
Agatha, you did write on your report...
...that Kamyla was a powerful
drug capable of total mind control.
Unfortunately, we have to take his word.
Although we all know he's lying.
Later, special agents.
Agatha, l don't want you
to take it the wrong way or anything...
...but you shouldn't worry about it.
Yeah.
We'll get him for good
on irrefutable evidence the next time.
Right?
You're right.
Will you wait here for me?
l'll get us both something to drink.
More solid evidence...
...then we can get him for good...
Good running into you earlier!
What the hell do you want?
An attitude!
I wasjust calling you to give you a gift.
lnformation about your crime group?
It's not anything boring like that.
It's more information about the drug.
Huh?
Even if you feel normal again...
...keep in mind Kamyla has
a long-term effect on the mind.
What do you mean?
A keyword will trigger the residual Kamyla
within the body to reactivate.
I'm going to tell you your keyword.
It's ''I'Il show you a piece of heaven.''
Heaven...
I'Il show you a piece of heaven.
That's good.
How does it feel to be in heaven?
You're going to feel like that for a while.
Hope you have a fun time with it!
No...
I think I'm going to lose my mind!
My body is reacting to this!
I can't....
The building is under construction.
Please do not enter. YYC Construction Co.
l can't believe l'm doing
this to myself during work!
But l can't....
Why are my breasts so sensitive?
My nipple are so hard and erect.
It feels good.
I'm coming!
Hey, check this out!
A police officer masturbating
in an abandoned building.
An officer masturbating
in an empty building.
That's something new!
Stay away.
Are you going to arrest me?
l thought l might be able to help you.
What would your write in your report?
l'd like to see that report!
No!
Stop it now!
Shut the fuck up!
l can't believe she came already.
l was only fondling her tits!
Hers must be super sensitive.
Let's see...
She's got a nice, tight pussy!
Let's see what these tits can do for me.
Stop, stop it!
No!
Stop, don't!
Every time you play with her tits,
her pussy tightens up!
Don't squirt on me!
l like these huge tits.
l can't believe we're fucking
a special police agent!
Especially a slutty one with huge tits!
Look, she's so wet her juices
are squirting out!
Her tits look like they're about to
squirt again any minute!
l think l'm going to dump
a huge load inside her!
Yeah, and l'm going to come all over
this slut's face!
All right, your tits can come
and squirt all over now!
No!
That was a good one.
She's soaking wet
all over with jizz and milk!
See you around, special agent.
lt was over way too soon, but bye bye!
We'll be around here if you want more!
That's a good one!
Thank you very much, boys.
I can't believe I was able to come
so hard while being raped like that.
Whatis wrong with my body,
am I losing my mind?
I love you, my sweetAgatha!
Whatsweetsurprises
should I send her next time?
Where on earth are you hiding?
Whereon earth areyou hiding?