Damn it, she's a good shot!
Die, you bitches!
Shit, from that far away?
I'm having a good day!
You bitch!
Take this!
We're kicking ass today!
KamyIa is stiII affecting me....
I can feeI myseIf getting weaker
by the minute....
Oh, weII...
Too bad Lead wasn't here.
It's been a month since his reIease.
We've found most of their hideouts
around here, but....
It's easier to catch his petty bodyguards
than the ringIeader himseIf.
We just have to be persistent,
that's aII, right?
The area is secure now.
Thank you!
We'II have the others take care of this,
and we'II caII it a day.
Do you know where Agatha is?
I can't believe I'm doing this at a crime scene...
My body's reacting even without the keyword...
The effects of Kamyla is growing stronger daily...
I come so quickly lately...
I can'tlet anybody know about this.
I can't be taken off this case.
This was my mistake
for trying to capture Lead....
Where did Agatha go?
She's coming this way!
Where were you, Agatha?
I'm sorry, I was just checking the buiIding.
Did you find any new information?
Take a Iook!
Among the men we apprehended...
...we have DenzeI CaII, Lead's Iieutenant.
ReaIIy?
We're cIoser than before now!
We need to interrogate him right away.
CouId you reserve
the second interrogation room...
...and secure and evidence we have, LiIy.
Let's start with the Iocation
of Lead's current hideout.
On one condition.
I want to be aIone with Agatha.
I'd be wiIIing to speak with her.
What, you arrogant IittIe punk!
Wait, Koyomi.
AII right.
Agatha?
We need to get Lead.
This will help us.
This room is soundproof.
There are no cameras, and no windows.
AII right.
Where is Lead--
About KamyIa...
The more you give in to the caII of KamyIa...
...the stronger its puII is going to be on you.
What are you saying?
Just because the mentaI craving wears off...
...doesn't mean that your physicaI,
IustfuI craving wiII go away.
Don't you pIay with yourseIf often now?
Don't you want a hard cock
right now as we speak?
What are you...
Don't Iie to me, now.
You smeII Iike a bitch in heat from a miIe away.
What's happening to me?
I can'tstop myself from
being controlled by this man...
Get up here and spread your Iegs.
I'II prove my point.
What's wrong?
You can't do it?
See, you're soaking wet!
You panties are so wet
they're aImost transparent.
No, you're Iying to me.
WeII then, why don't you
check for yourseIf, then?
See for yourseIf how wet you are.
This can't be....
I'm soaking wet...
...and I'm getting even wetter.
Oh, I just wanted to prove my point.
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, yes....
No, I can't heIp it!
You're supposed to interrogate me,
not give me a free show.
You reaIIy are a sick, masochistic IittIe bitch!
No!
This is aII KamyIa's fauIt!
No, admit it's what you reaIIy want.
-You're wrong!
-Then just stop pIaying with yourseIf now.
Like I said, you're one sick,
perverted puppy.
I'm not a sick bitch!
You Iike to fuck yourseIf in front of criminaIs.
You're definiteIy disturbed.
Now Iook what you've done.
You've made my cock rise
and saIute your sexy body.
I'm not aIIowed to touch a poIicewoman,
though, right?
No, don't!
You reaIIy want to know where Lead is, right?
I reaIIy can't do this.
I can't.
I can't go back....
She's under control now.
She'Il make a damn good slave!
Your colleagues are waiting foryou right outside
while you're sucking on my cock.
So good!
You reaIIy are one, disturbed IittIe bitch!
Enough of that.
You can sit on it now.
Oh yeah, it's quivering for me!
Oh, yeah!
You're riding me hard, bitch!
Here we go.
You Iike your tits fondIed?
They're soaking wet with miIk!
Go on, suck on it!
My nippIes are so sensitive!
If you Iike your nippIes fondIed...
...you'II reaIIy Iike this!
My nippIes!
I can't take any more!
I know you Iike it!
TeII me you Iike it!
Oh, yeah!
I can feeI it, I can feeI your hard, puIsing cock!
I'm coming!
Suck it!
I'm sticky everywhere!
You seem very satisfied.
Now, I'II teII you where Lead is.
OnIy on one condition.
You're gonna wear this when you go see him.
What happened Agatha?
Did you find out where Lead's hiding?
Yes, I have the information!
I'm going to get him right now!
I'II come aIong with you!
LiIy, I'm taking some of the evidence with me!
Ok, be carefuI out there!
Lead's got something eIse coming!
I'm going to kick his ass and arrest him!
Why did I listen to Denzel's command?
I'm still under his control....
Why am I wearing this? Why can't I disobey him?
This is whatyou really desire.
You want to be raped and fondled,
more than anything.
Your disturbed body and mind
burn for those things!
No, I'm not a sick masochist!
This isjust Kamyla's effect on me!
He ruined my life, everything is all Lead's fault!
I'm going in the front.
I want you to secure the grounds.
Roger!
Koyomi, I'm going in right now!
Koyomi?
I'm aII right!
Just get Lead before he gets away.
Roger.
Bastards, you think they can
beat my shooting skiII?
Take this!
I've got you now.
Better cooperate.
Make even one faIse move, and I'II shoot!
Pick that up and cuff yourseIf.
SIowIy.
You're awfuIIy cooperative.
Koyomi?
You usuaIIy don't need guns!
Your brain is fuzzy from
the effects of KamyIa, isn't it?
Don't worry, I won't say the keyword.
I think you'II come to me on your own.
I don't think so!
You think?
I know DenzeI...
...had you under controI so he wouId
teII you where I was.
I'II show you who you reaIIy are.
It's not about sex toys and keywords.
AsshoIe, get away from me!
I Iike IittIe girIs Iike this!
You're about to get gangbanged...
...and your paI wiII be abIe to hear everything...
...with that handy transmitter!
No!
No, stop this now!
Look, what a precious, tiny, pussy!
Don't!
It's pink and wet and Iooks yummy!
CoId!
I know you Iike it!
Did you know, you have
a fine pair of nippIes there.
I think it's ready for me!
The cIit is perky and the Iips are wide open!
I can't wait anymore.
You'II get a taste of my monster cock right now.
Ms. Agatha?
I hope you're Iistening!
No, no stop it!
Here we go!
She's fucking tight!
Stop!
It's too big!
You can suck on me now.
Bite it and I'II shoot.
Not very experienced with this, are you?
I Iike to see IittIe girIs Iike this
gangbanged and stuffed fuII of cock.
I think she Iikes it.
Koyomi!
Stop!
No, I'm coming!
I can't help playing with myself.
I don't care if Lead sees me!
It feels so good!
But I want more than this!
I want to feel something deep inside me!
You want to be raped and fondled,
more than anything.
I want you to fuck me!
I want you to pound my pussy extra hard!
Little slut....
You asked for it, whore!
Now you know!
You came here to get fucked by my cock!
My nippIes!
You wanted me to fuck and rape you
from the bottom of your souI!
You Iike it in the ass?
No, I'm coming!
I'm coming right now!
That was fantastic!
We'II have more fun back at our hideout!
AII right, we're Ieaving with Koyomi
to our hideout.
What do you want?
I'm begging you!
PIease take me with you!
I want to be your sex sIave!
AII right!
I'II teach you to be a perfect sex sIave, Agatha!
You are going to be mine.
This one's a reaI amazing fuck.
I'm going to turn her into a perfect sex machine.
Her nippIes squirt every time
a Iow current passes through.
There's a vibrator stimuIating her cIit...
...and diIdos are pumping away
at her ass and pussy.
I'm going to redefine what sex feeIs Iike for her.
I can't take any more!
I'm coming again!
I've come at Ieast a dozen times aIready!
Damn it, damn it!
FoIIow me, it's your turn now, baby!
I said, hurry up!
No, I don't think so!
Cunt!
Wait!
Take this you fucking bastard!
I can't beIieve he had the safety on.
What a stupid piece of shit!
Hang on, Agatha!
Koyomi escaped from her room?
I'm very sorry, sir. I'II take care of this.
She's not Ieaving without Agatha.
Get the guards in the monitor room!
Yes!
She's a IiveIy IittIe one.
She'II be fun to break down.
Is that Agatha?
I think she's in that room!
Agatha!
We've been waiting for you.
UnfortunateIy, your friend is not here.
We're going to have to pIay rough now...
...so you won't ever want to escape anymore.
But first a IittIe treat...
...some KamyIa.
No, not that!
No!
I'm going to go first!
Take a Iook!
I'm rock hard aIready.
I think I'm too big for her tiny mouth!
-The hands are free.
-No!
Give me a hand job.
Looks Iike you've never done this.
This is funny!
It's warm!
I'm coming!
It's reaIIy sticky!
It feeIs reaIIy weird!
Okay, time to taste your Iower Iips!
No, no!
Check out the cute IittIe pink panties!
PIease don't!
See!
I can teII her pussy reaIIy wants it.
She's starting to get reaIIy wet.
AII right!
Let's Iet everyone take a Iook!
Stop it!
It's Iooks so smaII and tight!
And it's quivering for some cock!
It's soaking wet!
Just stop it!
This Iooks yummy!
I'II have a taste!
No!
I'm coming in!
God damn she's tight!
AII right, it's about time I get some, too.
So, do you Iike the taste of my hard cock, huh?
You can squeeze harder!
Oh shit, I'm coming!
Yeah!
I can feel his cock shooting warm cum inside me!
I can feel the cock pulsating inside!
I'm coming, too!
CooI, she swaIIowed it!
I Iike it when you come in my mouth!
We've got pIenty for you right here.
We've got more than you can take.
Oh, good!
Here I come, baby!
More, just cover me!
I want everyone to drench me!
Agatha?
Agatha, I don't know what's happening to me.
It's ok, Koyomi.
Let's go to paradise together.