So late...
My name is Sakimi Endo.
I'm a normal college girl.
I mean, I should have been...
Good bye! Professor!
Hey! Donґt run in the hallway!
Dumb make-up class! I'm getting late for my
part-time job!
Hey! Watch out!
Oh, Sorry about that! Are you all right?
He was my only dream boy.
The soccer team captain, Takuya Kakizaki.
I was supposed to be just like any other girl
who dreams of love.
This is the first contact of my new life that has
just begun.
ripped and encoded by
mASSIVe
Thank you for coming, Sakimi.
Senpai...
Have a seat.
Yes.
Did you expect this room was messier?
Hah, no...
Iґm very neat. I always make sure my
members to be neat as well .
Sorry...
Thatґs OK. Something to drink?
Please donґt bother. By the way, what did you
take me here for?
You often came to see me practicing.
Oh, that was just...
Iґve been feeling your eyes so much.
Iґm sorry.
No need to apologize. I was glad. Thank you.
Well...
You were shinning brighter than anyone else.
I was feeling your heart.
So...
I just want to accept your heart.
Senpai...
Is it OK?
Stop it, please!
Whatґs the matter?
This is not what I was thinking.
What are you saying? We are attracted to each
other. This is just supposed to be.
Sakimi... I wanna go all the way.
I`ll be gentle.
Ah, no...
Hey! Be quiet!
Itґs all right. Relax.
Oh, yeah. Itґs the scent of virgin.
Grab mine.
Oh, feeling so good. Great!
Here comes.
Ouuuuch...! It hurts! It really hurts!
You will soon start feeling good.
Hurts! It hurts!
Shut fuck up!
Perhaps that was the time. Maybe I should
have known real him at that time.
But, it was my first time. I believed it was
supposed to be like that, and accepted it.
Takuya kept loving me for long time until I was
covered by darkness.
Love...
I thought that was what we called love...
at that time...
I and Takuya had a long relationship based on
sex.
I donґt know why, but I couldnґt escape from
him.
It was something I couldnґt put in words.
That phone call was to tell goodbye with him,
and take me to the living hell.
Hello. Endo speaking.
Is this Ms. Sakimi Endo?
Yes.
This is from Sukkiri Finance. Weґd like to let
you know that you are past due for a payment.
What? I never made debt.
But, we actually financed 1.5 million yen under
your name.
Then you got a wrong name!
Who on the earth?
Can I borrow you student ID? There is
something I want to buy with student discount.
I donґt think you can use mine. It's female
student ID.
Donґt worry!
It canґt be... Takuya!?
This number is no longer in service...
No kidding...
Yo! This is GOKURAKU Credit! Return your
debt!
This is YAMITSUKI Finance! 2 million plus 1
million yen! Pay us back every penny!
Hello neighbors! This person doesnґt pay her
debt.
No...
This person is street trash or menace to the
society!
No...
Hey you! Open up!
Nooo!
He never loved me... Moreover, it was never
love I had for him.
It was not him who were there.
Men for money. But, I was getting same
pleasure as I got from him.
What was it I was really looking for?
After I finished, it brought me back to the
painful reality...
This mature business denied all my life and
humanity.
One or two each day isnґt enough. Loan is
increasing everyday. How many more will I
have to do?
I heard the rumor that you have about 3
million yen debt from another 3 more
institutes.
You should pay us off before you break
yourself.
SUBJECT: Angel's Evening.
Tomorrow 5PM at the park. 100 thousand yen.
No more...
No more!
He is so late.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
You are the one who gave me the message?
That`s right. The condition is as written in the
message.
There is a place we can relax.
Is it really all right?
This is it.
Club Canary?
Go in.
Good girl.
Not quite impressive. This doesnґt look any
special so far.
Where is the bath room? I want to take
shower.
Sakimi Endo.
Why do you know my name!?
Itґs your guardian who took over your debt.
Itґs impossible.
They donґt care who pays your debt as long as
they can collect it.
What do you want from me?
Very simple. I just want you to work for this
high-class club.
A "high-class" club?
This is the place for the high-class people. No
explanation should be necessary.
No way!
Yes way! You are no more than a traded slave!
You must obey my orders now on forth. Is that
understood?
Now, suck it up!
Noooo!
Donґt pretend to be naive. You have sucked so
many cocks by today havenґt you?
That is not true. It wasnґt me.
You slut donґt have a choice!
Go ahead, suck it up!
Much better. Keep it going.
Here I cum!
Donґt spill it out! Swallow it!
OK. Round2!
You became obedient. Did you like sucking my
dick?
No, I...
Are you really rejecting me? You got a drain
pipe.
Itґs...not...what you...think...
Itґs about time.
No! Itґs too big! I can' t take it!
Itґs tight.
No... It will break.
This is a good-feeling cunt you got!
Your tits are erecting. You are feeling good
arenґt you?
Itґs hitting...Ah, my womb. Itґs hitting!
Do you want to cum? You gonna?
No...
I canґt hold it!
Cum!
I'll bring your roommate. Take shower and
wait.
There is another girl like me?
This is for you.
Thank you. Are you my roommate?
What was that? Strange.
She is Mana Fujidoh, your roommate.
Get along with her.
Well, the dress looks OK on you.
What is...your name?
Asamiya. You use the bed in the down stair.
The upper loft is for Mana.
She hates to see people, so donґt go up there.
Thank you for the dress.
You go to bed.
Iґm tired.
Weґre sorry about wait.
Greet the client.
H..How do you do. My name is Sakimi. Itґs
pleasure to serve you.
Well, is she the new face?
Yes. Today is her first day. Would you like to
try her?
No doubt. Iґve been waiting for a new thing.
He seems to be gentle. Iґm eased.
We prepared your usual room. Please go ahead
and have a good time.
This place is always well-organized. Sakimi, Iґll
be in the room, so get yourself ready and
come over.
Go and serve the client.
You never have a choice.
Yes.
Oh! Wonderful!
Th..This is just...
To tell you the truth, I am a priest.
How can a priest do something like this?
Iґm just a human after all. I get crappy
confession every day, which brings me stress!
I come to this place to kill my stress.
Now! Serve me with your mouth!
With your mouth, suck out the evil fluid that
inhabits inside my body!
Go quick!
Y..Yes.
M, My Lord...
Oh, Iґm... c..cuming... cuming!
cuming! ! !
You may not!
Swallow everything and purify inside your
body!
Now, Iґm going to take you to the Lord.
Now, in front of the God, be natural as if you
were just born.
Beautiful! This is the most superior craft the
God ever created.
Well, letґs see how the secret garden is.
No! Donґt look!
A lot of sweet nectar gives nice scent.
Stop it.
Look at you. Itґs flooding and never stops.
Ahhh! Not there!
Caaaan't!
This is the first step to get closer to the God.
Now, donґt hold yourself. Just let it go!
Please take me to the God this time.
To my Lord!
Ahh! Itґs hitting...ahh...my womb...
Oh, itґs the God! I feel the God!
Donґt you feel the God, too?
I..I feel...
Ah! My Lord!
Now, I'm coming to you!
Caaanґt!
Why do you look at me like that?
You are doing the same thing, too, aren't you!
Whatґs gonna happen to me...?
How do you like two injections?
P..Please... Itґs the limit.
Itґs OK. You can explode.
No nurse lets me do this far in my hospital.
In every dayґs repeated action, my body was
developed gradually.
Well, the third injection is white, strong fluid.
No! No!
My body is getting out of control... I feel guilty
that ecstasy is beating me.
My soul that is colored with pleasure and my
will to resist it conflict.
Your anal makes me feel so great. How about
you?
Yes... I...feel...good...
My mind is raped, then Iґm just a slave doll...
No... No...
Cumming!
Noooo!
ripped and encoded by
mASSIVe
Why do I get this....
No...
Do you have debt, too?
How dare you ignore me?
You donґt care about others.
You only think about how to satisfy clients
again tomorrow.
P..Please...
Tomorrow... Please let me have a day off
tomorrow...
You still donґt realize your situation.
Look. Body wonґt break so easily.
I will judge whether you need a break or not.
You just do what I say.
That is... like this... I will be...
Sense of time is lost in life underground...
The length of hair tells me that the season has
changed.
Mana?
When youґre gonna faint, squeeze this and you
will stay conscious.
For me?
She understands me now.
Thank you...
Well, well, well...
Mr. Asakura arranges it the way I prefer.
Come over here and suck what you love.
Yes.
The tunnel without light at the end...
Sakimi, You are the next. Get ready.
No.
What?
I wonґt listen to you anymore.
I pretend I didnґt listen that. Get ready quickly.
I said no more.
I don't have any more debt, do I?
Are you done?
Hey, Mana. Wait a minute.
You heard that. You take care of the next
clients, too.
Yes.
Are you insane? She canґt do anymore. Can
you see it?
I canґt keep the clients waiting. Get ready
now.
Yes.
A, All right. I was wrong, so give her rest.
Do you worry about Mana? Interesting. OK. I
will coordinate todayґs show.
Mr. Asamiya, Is she the todayґs girl?
No. She is just an objet.
Please enjoy this one today.
Iґm Mana. Itґs a pleasure to serve you.
Ohhh, How lovely!
She is even younger than my daughter.
I canґt wait any more!
What? Is it different from you expected?
Pardon me Gentlemen. Can I get to watch
here? I will give you discount today.
Sure. Sure.
Mana...
Mana, you are so adorable.
Looks delicious.
You already kissed her.
Yeah, it tasted just like a peach.
Now, I want my cock sucked.
Me, too.
I want to eat her.
Mana, you make me feel so good.
Mana, suck me, too.
Mana will break her jaw.
Ah, I canґt hold it. Iґm gonna put it in!
Iґm gonna screw her ass.
I put it in her mouth, then we fill all her holes.
I put it right here.
Stop that. Mana will die!
Sakimi, take a close look at the consequence
for challenging me.
I tell you why Mana is so obedient.
Her family was rich, but went down the hill in
depression today.
It happened when they bankrupted and the
night before they had to leave their house.
Nooo! Father!
He was in desperation. He raped his own
daughter...
But, Mana tried to forgive him.
But, what Mana saw next morning was...
Father...?
He did it for getting insurance money to pay off
debt, or having regret for what heґs done to his
daughter, I donґt know.
Either way, Mana believed it was her fault.
Are you Miss Mana Todo? I am...
That was the time. I met her when I was still
doing loan exaction.
She doesnґt belong here for money like you.
She is here to make up her sin.
How much have you done? I canґt do more
than 3 times.
Iґve done 7 times. Her anal makes me feel so
great, so I canґt stop it.
It looks like you are awaken by anal.
I love her anal, too. I myself screwed it twice
already.
Well, Mana, let her see how much cum you got
in your womb.
If I pull her both legs behind, it will spout.
No...
Noooo...
Mana...
Mana... Cґmon, open your eyes...
Oh, Mana... I'm glad you're all right.
Why are you crying?
Mana
Hey, Mana, listen up.
Letґs get out of here.
You shouldnґt be here.
I heard about your father. It is a sad thing.
But, I donґt think your father wants to see you
in pain because of him.
So letґs escape together.
You already paid for you sin more than
enough.
Sin?
You will become free from now.
Mana...
Iґm sorry.
Ha?
I... I canґt go.
Mana?
This is... the only place I can be...
Mana...
I will have to do this...
Here comes.
Sakimi, Mana, letґs go.
Todayґs clients take both of you. So donґt be
rude.
Letґs go.
You are so obedient today.
Now I know that challenging you never works.
It makes me a lot easier.
Only today. I have to bear only today...
Using your tongue, lick the edge thoroughly.
Hey the big one, you!
Me?
Your light sucking sucks.
You little one, make her more active.
H, Hey, Mana.
You this way!
I knew you could do it.
Here cums!
You two, lick and clean each other.
Youґre not very wet. Letґs have your friend
make you feel good.
No! She canґt!
Mana!?
Lick her pussy thoroughly.
Thatґs enough. Get out of the way, little girl!
Use it and thank her for making you feel good.
Mana...
Sakimi, please...
Mana... I put it...
Hey you, you canґt please her with such a slow
movement.
Give me your ass!
Not again!
No question! You bitchesґ holes become really
worth only when used by men!
It gets moody when we do it faster like this,
huh?
N,No...
Iґm cumming...
Go ahead, cum!
This one is the last.
Thank you for coming today.
Sure. Weґll be back.
How much longer do I have to wait? Hurry up.
Please be patient. Itґs gonna be ready soon. I
will take you to the room.
Shitty days... will be over... today...
Did I miss?
Itґs too easy, Sakimi. I know everything about
you including your anal.
I know what youґre thinking.
Itґs too bad. I thought I could get along with
you.
Sayonara, Sakimi.
Mana!?
Is there really a place I can be?
Of course there is!
Mana, letґs go!
What about Mr. Sakimiya?
Donґt even think about him. He got what he
deserved.
We made up our sin enough. He must be
punished, too.
Sunset is so beautiful.
I havenґt seen it for while, but I didnґt realize
that it was this beautiful.
Mana...
Manaґs peaceful smiling face. The face I was
waiting to see...
Now, I have someone important...
We have nothing to be afraid of...