A nostalgic memory...
...comes back to a tipsy head.
The warmth of soft skin...
...and a sweet whisper.
It was an old story.
For a long time...
...I have been trying to rub
an old wound with lost blood...
...and...
...to forget something.
Now I know how
precious the thing I lost was...
Hey, you're late Aisha!
We've been waiting for you!
I won't lose today!
I don't know about that.
Hey, let's start!
Yeah, yeah!
I haven't seen you around here.
I'm very busy with work.
Aisha, come on!
Yeah, yeah!
Don't you guys
have any patience at all?
Huh?
Who brought it?
Clair can't go out of the mansion.
It can't be...
Hey, Aisha?
Are you done already?
I'll stop humiliating you for tonight.
Be prepared for next time!
These are carnations.
You're waiting for a no-show?
Nobody is coming.
I'm not expecting anyone.
I lost again tonight.
I don't seem to have much luck lately.
What do you want from me?
I was just wondering
if I could have a match...
...with you!
Aisha, see you next week!
See ya!
Looking forward to it!
Okay!
Sorry...
...but I don't have anything to bet with.
It's right here.
If I win, you give me these flowers!
And if you win...
...you can take me as you like.
That's very impressive.
Thank you.
Let's play!
I'll keep mine.
You're not exchanging any cards?
No.
Wow, you must have
some pretty good ones.
Okay...
Now, let's see yours.
Oh, I lost!
I really don't have any luck left.
Well, a promise is promise.
Let's go somewhere else.
Hurry up!
Come on!
Okay...
I'm Aisha Farfaris.
Call me Aisha.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm sorry...
...but can I stay like this a little longer?
Don't play tricks
on strangers next time.
What?
Then, you knew?
Yeah.
You're awful.
Wait!
Hey, wait!
What is this?
I didn't do it for money!
It's for my losing the game.
It's too much!
Take it as your bonus,
since I enjoyed your company.
I prefer something more lasting!
I don't like it if it's
the last time with you.
What do you want then?
One more night.
In your place this time!
Suit yourself.
Wow.
You live here?
Amazing!
Huh?
Mr. Foster...
Welcome back, Foster.
Who is the lady?
She's my guest.
Show her a room.
Clair.
Yes.
Your punishment is over.
Thank you, sir.
I will leave you to
take care of the guest.
Yes, sir.
Isn't your punishment over?
So why don't you...
...take it off?
Ma'am...
Please don't...
I noticed you were walking funny.
Can I take a look at it?
Come on.
Whoa.
So, this is no ordinary mansion.
I'm coming in.
Welcome.
Mr. Foster!
Well, it's all right.
My, she looks delicious.
What a nosy girl!
Mr. Foster, this is...
Go back to your room.
Mr. Foster, it was an interesting show.
But she is just a cheap whore after all.
I apologize.
Well, she's got good
qualities, just change her content.
Why did you do that?
I felt bad staying here for free...
...so I wanted to make it up to you.
That's very kind of you.
I changed my mind.
I'm staying here for a
while, to be near to you.
You are asking to be put in a jail.
Oh, I think I am hitting
a jackpot, my prince charming.
Mother!
Mother, how are you?
Very well, Clair.
I'm afraid of Father.
Don't say that.
Your father is a very kind man.
Then why does he treat you so coldly?
It's my fault, so don't be spiteful of him.
Mom?
Mom!
Wait, please wait, Mother!
Mr. Foster!
No!
Good morning, Mr. Foster.
Very well, do your job as usual.
Yes.
Clair.
Today, teach Aisha the basic work.
Understood.
You've been here for
a long time, haven't you?
Why do you think so?
Well, you seem to be trusted by him.
He's taking good care of you, right?
Please concentrate on your work.
Yes.
Clair.
Why are you in this mansion?
I-I'm sorry if I offended your feelings.
But I'm concerned.
Is it because of the debts?
I sold myself to retain this house.
What?
You used to be a princess, then.
Don't bother, I am a maid now...
...just like you.
It sounds complicated.
Wait for me!
Ren, no!
It's not break time yet!
It's cold!
Myuha, how's Aisha's training going?
Well, she's showing some progress.
I see.
She always looks so stunning.
I even feel bad tying her up.
But, it is also a talent
to look beautiful like this.
Isn't it too tight?
It should be good for her.
Aisha.
I will teach you what's missing in you.
Patience.
It's not my taste but
my customer likes it this way.
I understand.
Take care of it.
They are very fine candle stands.
Thank you.
It's very hard to choose from, but...
...l'll choose this one.
Come on!
Well...
Don't!
Don't touch me!
I'm sorry.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not angry at that guest, but at you!
What?
You don't understand anything!
Foster has special feelings for you!
You're thinking too much.
Mr. Foster has feelings for everybody equally.
I'll get some water.
Clair...
I'm sorry, Clair.
I said too much.
Foster.
Are you well now?
Don't try too hard.
I'm...
...leaving here.
Just kidding.
I'm not such a weak woman, you know.
Sorry to disappoint you!
I must say I like you, so I want to stay.
I don't ask you to just look at me.
But...
...at least let me stay with you.
Just let me stay.
Huh?
You are so shy!
I'm not giving up!
Never!
Any jewel has to be cut and
polished to sparkle its brightest.
So, you might as well get hurt...
...to shine more beautifully.
You're jewels in a box, jewels...
The last flower of this season.
Right.
Ren?
Yes?
Do you know
the phrase of a carnation?
Uh...
Passionate love.
Pure love.
I'm impressed, Aisha!
Is that correct?
Yes.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
It's okay.
I have a memory in that flower.
Tell me one thing.
Sure.
Is the person who loved
this flower somebody you knew well?
Yes, very much.
It's my mother who loved this flower.