Snow?
It's snow!
Wow!
It's almost spring now.
Are we going to be here next spring?
Maybe nothing will
change while he's around.
Even a stone on
the street has some meaning.
I recall such a saying
from a long time ago.
This kind of nostalgia doesn't suit me.
If it was like before...
If I was as I was in those
days of vanities and greed...
I wouldn't have taken notice
of a girl shivering in the snow.
Welcome.
Leese, have you ever
seen a mansion before?
No, sir.
Welcome.
She is beautiful.
Our master is expecting you.
Please, this way.
Thank you.
Leese!
Yes, sir.
Then, Mr. Dred, to the
prosperity of the Dred Foundation!
And to our country's future!
Did you call me, Mr. Dred?
Come in.
Mr. Foster, let me introduce my friend.
This is Mr. Leed.
Oh...
You are Mr. Foster.
I heard a lot about you.
Thank you.
We're going to take her
for a while upon his request.
She's not very clever or pretty.
But, could you train her properly?
I will do my best.
What's your name?
It's Leese, sir.
Do you think you
can bare to work here?
I'll do cleaning or laundry,
and work as hard as I can!
Take off your glasses.
What?
Hurry!
Stand straight, towards me.
Step forward.
Huh?
I said step forward!
Y-Yes, sir.
Oh, no...
I'm terribly sorry.
How about that.
Can you train her
to be a presentable lady?
Even a dog, if it is an order.
It's been a long time.
Since the Curey Port
collapsed ten years ago.
You ought not to mention it...
...for our own sake.
But I hear you are well-to-do now.
And you're a loan shark, aren't you?
Sort of.
But I have a plan.
What?
That's right.
I'm going to get my
success back again.
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to help me?
You seriously think it's
possible to revive the organization?
You've changed.
Of course.
Since I've gone
through that painful time.
Why not help me, then?
I'm content with the work here.
I'm disappointed in you.
But, let me tell you...
...you are just like those birds!
Well...
Think it over, which is
more beneficial to you.
Forgive me, Leese.
I have no choice.
Don't worry, Mother.
You have nothing special...
...but if you work hard,
there will be a reward for you.
Sister, don't go!
Sister, sister!
Good morning, Mr. Foster.
From today on,
she is working with you.
My name is Leese.
Please to meet you.
Teach her the work, everybody.
Yes, sir.
Here I go.
I have such a hangover this morning!
You don't look too good.
I'll do it, so please go get some rest.
You don't mind?
Thank you.
Oh, my head!
I'm done.
Already?
Really?
You're going to be okay
without me teaching you what to do.
We all welcome hard workers like you.
I'm not pretty like you...
...so the only thing
I can do is work hard.
You didn't use clothes pins, did you?
What?
Oh, no!
What are we going to do?
Got it.
I-I'm sorry!
Oh, no.
We just finished cleaning!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
If you work too hard from the
start, you'll be exhausted in no time.
You have to take a break.
But...
What's wrong?
I've always been
working, so I never took a break.
Why don't you learn from her, Aisha!
Yeah, yeah, it's your fault!
I'm so sorry.
I was just kidding.
You are so tense!
Don't be so serious.
Come on now, smile!
I'm sorry.
Good.
Smells good!
Tastes good!
You are a really good cook!
Really?
Hurry up!
What's taking so long?
Yes, sir!
Ouch!
What are you doing?
You useless!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Hey, you don't have
to slap her like that!
I told you not to talk back to me...
...if you want to stay here.
But, you overreacted!
Please, Aisha.
I know.
I'm such a useless person.
Maybe she needs
some rough treatment.
Don't be so nervous.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Go inside.
Look carefully.
This is your work.
What?
Why don't you come here?
I can't do it!
Go!
Come on.
O-Ouch!
Sir, she is not yet...
Shut up!
No!
That hurts!
No, please don't!
No, no...
No...
No!
No, please don't...
No, no, no...
This girl could be a find.
Don't punish me.
Shut up!
Meah, help her undress.
Yes.
Take your hands off.
What?
Cross your hands behind
your back and stand straight.
Take those off.
Your body is not bad.
But, too overweight!
Don't sob!
Open your legs over there.
I can't do such a thing.
Leese.
You still don't
understand your situation.
This is the training for you to stay here.
If you can't obey me, get out of here!
I see.
Meah.
Yes.
Now, lift your legs and show
me how you take your customer.
You don't even know how to use it.
Don't move!
Don't!
No...
Sir...
Isn't she trying too hard?
Not yet.
What happened?
Foster has gone too far.
He has?
Somehow, he gets
too intense with this girl.
I see.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wow, it's beautiful!
An angel...
Angel.
What are you looking at?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm...
You can have it, if you like.
You like books, don't you?
If you want to read more
books, you can come back anytime.
Thank you very much.
I didn't attend school full time...
...so I never was
allowed to have books before.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
Anything wrong?
Ms. Myuha let me have this book.
Before putting on knowledge...
...try taking off some
pounds from your body.
Hi, Leese.
What's up at this late hour?
Mr. Foster ordered an evening snack.
It's good for you,
Foster seems fond of you.
L-lt's not that.
Like you didn't know.
When he's harsh on someone,
it's his way of showing affection.
Aisha!
You know we're not allowed to drink!
You're annoying, leave me alone!
Stop!
Aisha!
Aisha...
Mr. Foster is taking time with
Leese because she's slower than others.
You should know that!
If Foster takes
more time on someone...
...he takes less time
with somebody else!
Being jealous is not a nice thing.
Are you really okay
with that know-it-all attitude?
You don't even know
what your real feelings are!
Maybe you're right.
Good girl...
What's next?
You never know.
Now Leese is a popular one.
Isn't it about time to return her?
No need for that anymore.
What do you mean?
That man went broke.
Therefore, we don't
need to send her back to him.
I see.
It's not a big deal to
make somebody go broke.
You are not thinking about
whatever he was trying, are you?
It's long time ago.
You seem to enjoy reading.
Mr. Foster.
I-I'm sorry.
Don't be so apologetic.
Good news.
Your debts are recouped.
What did you just say?
I said you don't owe anybody anymore.
You have been patient enough.
Now you are free.
Free...
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy?
Wherever I go, it's
going to be difficult anyway.
Have some confidence!
You'll be okay wherever you go now.
But, I'd like to be here.
This book is very good.
At least until I finish
this book, let me stay, please.
That sounds like you.
Leese!
It's time.
Yes!
Hurry up!
Oh, you are so clumsy!
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay?
Let us help you stand up...
Are you really okay?
I'm fine, thanks.
I'm just like those birds.
I know...
But...
What can I do now?
What do you want?
Please tell me...
...what happened...
...between you and my mother, Fahm?
I heard from Ren.
You were saying
my mother's name in your sleep.
Actually...
...I had been in love with Fahm.
Then, I dumped her.
Why?
Please, tell me the reason.