There are two
meanings for time passing by...
...it means to forget the past...
...and it means...
...not to be able to undo the past.
If I put my hand on my chest...
...I can feel that
there is a hole in my heart.
It's already over, so I don't feel pain...
...but my fingers are
still looking for a place to go.
I try to remember but I can't...
...yet I want to believe that I remember.
So I hold out my hand...
...and just keep doing the same thing.
I know that...
...it's just a fantasy I imagine.
If this is a punishment...
...at least, make it worthwhile.
Clair.
Mom!
Mom...
Who are you guys?
We were ordered to take
you with us no matter what.
By whom?
If you see him, you will find out.
No!
Stop it!
Hold!
Please, step out.
What does anyone want from me?
Thank you so much for coming.
Well...
Really...
You're stunning.
Pardon me.
That's a sudden move.
Oh, it's a regular greeting.
Meah!
That's not your job!
Pardon me for bringing you
here in a rough manner, Mr. Foster.
My name is Dred Barton.
Dred Barton!
You know me?
In this country,
everybody knows your name.
So, what does a railroad tycoon
want from a ruined man like me?
I have the perfect job for you.
For me?
I've done some research on you.
I know you're very
good at training women.
Excuse me.
What?
This girl owes me quite a lot of money.
Well, no need to give you the detail.
I want you to train her to
be able to make a decent profit.
You must be kidding me.
I want you to think it over
whether or not to take this offer.
I hope you will give me a good answer.
What's your name?
It's Clair, sir.
Can you take off your blindfold?
Yes.
Take it off.
Was Dred correct in what he said?
Yes.
Will you obey my orders?
Put your left leg on the table.
What?
Now!
Yes.
Spread your legs.
Now!
Wider!
Okay.
You passed.
I hear you are an expert on women?
I can tell by just looking at them.
You're a very confident man...
...for an ex-government
special forces agent.
I will have to train you, sometime.
I will look forward to it.
Welcome to my castle.
Now Clair is one of us.
Clair.
Are you shaking?
How sweet!
Doesn't this feel good?
Don't be shy.
You're so beautiful!
Well, how about if I touch here?
Well...
Let me hear your dirty voice.
Louder!
Let's see your skill.
What?
What's wrong?
I'm not in the mood.
What?
Don't worry.
We have enough time.
Plenty of time.
Nothing changes in this town.
In those days, when I did
nothing but wasting away...
...I didn't think anything would
be impossible to accomplish.
But, now what...
With just one piece of paper...
...I was hunted down as criminal.
I will never forget that humiliation.
No!
Use the tip of your tongue!
Concentrate on the tip!
Y-Yes.
Master.
I brought him here.
What is it?
This afternoon, a very
important customer is coming here.
How is Clair progressing?
It is a little too early for a customer.
Some like adolescent girls screaming.
There's a risk of ruining her,
like a fragile glass artwork.
If it happens, it happens.
In this kind of
business, it's not so unusual.
Also...
...don't ever talk back to me.
I only want an obedient reply.
Yes.
I will get her prepared right away.
Come in!
No need to be scared, missy.
Ouch!
That's enough, dismissed!
Just as I thought,
it was too soon for her.
That was bad.
But you knew it
was going to be like that, didn't you?
What are you trying to say?
Why do you hate her so much?
Are you still thinking about Fahm?
You talk too much!
I apologize.
I shouldn't interfere with your past.
How are we going to take care of her?
It's not fun since she's not struggling.
Looking good, Clair.
You are such a well made instrument.
If someone plays you well,
you make a beautiful melody.
Oh, you are becoming like this.
Very honest.
Don't make a sound from now on.
You've been very patient.
I will give you a treat.
N-No...
No!
Not yet.
Now, Clair...
Look closely.
Take a good look at yourself.
Remind yourself...
...that you are just a plaything...
...and nothing more.
Why don't you run away?
What makes you so helpless?
Please.
I must live.
So teach me how to.
There are easier ways to make a living.
But that is meaningless to me.
That was such a dry kiss.
I'm sorry.
It gets better when you get used to it.
Take care.
How is she?
She was just overworked.
She's been very
serious about something.
I see.
She should take a good nap for now.
How could the master
treat his own daughter like this.
His own daughter?
Oh, didn't you know?
What's going on here!
You sensed it, no?
But you didn't want to admit it...
Fahm?
Yes.
What is it?
I have the right to know.
About Clair.
She's a good girl.
Then why?
That's why I don't like her.
I owned Fahm for a long time.
And a smart person like you
can understand what that means.
You and Fahm are both
criminals in this country.
You should admit that.
Any other questions?
Some days are good,
and some days are bad.
Are you all right now?
I'm sorry for the trouble.
You can tell me your real story.
This is where my memory lies.
The money I owe is
the price for this mansion.
I sold myself to
have this mansion back.
I get the picture.
Clair.
As much as you want
this mansion, I want you.
If you can belong to
me, I will help you in return.
I am...
...yours.