Based on these materials...
...I can't help but tell you that
this business plan is reckless.
I think we need more time...
...to develop such a huge
railroad construction plan.
I'm concerned if we
even get the permission.
We should examine this
plan once more, shouldn't we?
I would like to hear your opinion.
You've become smart enough
to talk back to me, haven't you?
Mr. Perkins.
You guys, too.
When did Barton's
executives become so cowardly?
We have overcome this
kind of risk many times so far.
There is no mistake in my plan.
Just consider how to carry it out properly.
Do it like you have done so far.
The flightless birds' lament...
Why is it so difficult to grip
something with their hands?
Why is it so difficult to walk?
Because they are born to fly.
They don't know how
beautiful their feathers are...
...and they are afraid of
spreading their wings.
If so, I will make
them open their wings...
...by humiliating them...
...in order to let them dance.
Stop, stop it.
No!
Stop tickling me!
Hey, stop it!
No!
You are lucky.
What are you doing?
I told you not to bring
a dog in the mansion.
We are sorry.
It's just a dog.
He got wet in the rain and looks pitiful.
And he is like me...
...lonely.
What are you talking about?
You are not alone.
You have us.
That's right.
Well, I will overlook it for today.
Don't tell the master.
Yes!
Thank you very much.
You're very kind, aren't you, Foster?
Don't be impudent.
It is my job to make you happy.
Yeah, yeah...
Excuse me.
Mr. Dred.
Fahm...
Fahm, I am the master of this castle.
I will protect you definitely!
Why do you look so sad?
Why didn't you protect me back then?
I'm sorry.
There was no way
to disobey my father.
I couldn't help accepting my father's
opinion that we weren't a good match...
...because you were a servant.
But he is gone.
Nobody will disagree with me.
It's too late now.
It's too late...
Fahm, Fahm, Fahm!
I'm sorry.
I woke you up.
Never mind.
If I take a rest, the development of
railroad construction will be delayed.
I'd like to say
smoothing about the plan.
Are you going to say
the plan is reckless, too?
No, I'm not...
I'm just worried about your health.
Tell me if you have
something in your mind.
Yes...
Your conglomerate has
already grown big enough...
...and acquired so
much fortune and power...
...so what more do you need?
It seems like...
Seems like what?
Seems like you are
cornered by something.
Give me a break.
I am sorry.
That's enough.
You're dismissed.
What else?
You are tired.
Please take a rest today.
Please let me give you comfort.
I'm not tired.
Don't worry.
I can't replace Fahm, can I?
Why don't you understand?
I love Mr. Dred so much.
Myuha, you are...
Hey, hurry up!
Wait for me!
Understand, Perkins?
Yes, sir.
Chairman, please take care of yourself.
Yes.
How long do you want to bow to him?
You are going to ignore his
tyrannical behavior, aren't you?
No...
The union is getting stronger recently.
I'm afraid that Burton Company
will break down if you leave him alone.
Although you say that...
I have an idea.
If you value your lives you have now...
...please come together
to my room this afternoon.
Hold!
What's going on?
Don't be so stingy.
Hey, guys.
Give me something.
Get out of here!
Com'on!
Beggars.
Mister, give me something!
Sister, please!
Shall I give them small change?
Uncle, give me some.
Give me money.
Whoa!
Please buy my flower.
Such annoying kids.
Mr. Dred.
Why don't you run away?
I'm not a beggar.
Please buy my flower.
What is your name?
What?
I am Cherry.
Nice to meet you!
Take care of this girl.
She is too young to work for us.
Make her handle chores.
Yes.
I'm Ren, nice to meet you.
Oh, you are so dirty.
Let's take a bath right now.
Who will host my guest today?
Aisha will.
Okay.
Foster...
I'm wrestling with a big development
project like nothing I have ever tried.
So, I will have a lot of chances to
entertain important clients from now on.
Please take care of them very well.
Yes, please don't worry.
By the way, I have a question.
What?
She looks like a girl
who lives in a poor hamlet.
Why did you bring her here?
It was a momentary caprice.
Anything else?
No, excuse me.
Washing is one of our important jobs.
And don't forget to use clothes pins!
Thank you, Cherry.
Wow!
Stop it, Cherry.
All right.
You'd better take a rest.
Yes, don't move.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Good boy.
Can I go in?
No, Why don't you run along?
Are you drinking in the kitchen?
I am sure I prohibited you to drink.
Just one glass.
Today's client was very demanding.
I'm so tired.
I haven't forced you.
You hoped for that, didn't you?
Why did you say it like that!
Can't you say
anything good to me?
You did a good job.
You could give me
more affectionate words.
You are very important to me.
Not like that.
I don't need those words.
You are drunk.
Go to bed.
The client...
...wanted to take care of me.
He said he really loved me.
Is that so...
Congratulations.
You are tired.
Go to bed.
Mr. Foster, Mr. Foster!
Mr. Foster!
What is going on so late?
Ren is...
Ren, Ren!
The dog went out of the mansion.
Ren tried to catch him, but...
Ren, let's go back.
You'll catch cold.
Why donнt we go look for him?
I guess he hasn't gone far away.
What do you think?
We don't have to.
What?
Ren, why?
Why do you say that?
He went back to his home.
I'm sure he went back to his home.
So...
I want to go home, too.
Ren!
Ren, are you okay?
Ren, Ren!
Is she better?
Yes, but she still has fever.
Is that so...
She got a shock, didn't she?
Give her some rest until the fever leaves her.
Yes.
Daddy, Mummy...
I'm afraid of Father.
Don't say that.
Your father is really a very kind person.
Why does he treat you coldly?
It's my fault, so don't be spiteful of him.
Did you call for me?
Yes, come in.
Take her away.
What?
Clair.
Yes.
I decided to throw a party in ten days.
Yes, sir.
By the way, it's been
a while since Ren was ill in bed.
How is she doing?
Actually...
...it's not good.
Is that so...
It doesn't make sense
to keep her in this mansion.
What?
You mean...
Are you going to let her go?
She doesn't have
anybody she can count on.
Are you sure of driving her out?
Clair, stop it.
Please give me an answer!
This is business.
Do you think only about business?
Don't you have a heart?
How about my mother?
Why did you treat her so
badly when she was sick?
Shut up!
Stop!
Stop, Father!
Don't hurt Mommy anymore!
They will go wrong if left as they are.
I told you I was facing
a very crucial moment.
I don't have time
to worry about the maids.
However, Clair is
your daughter, isn't she?
I haven't talked to you about
why I hired you in the first place.
Her mother, Fahm,
called your name before she died.
After you ran away...
...I brought her back from
the authorities to this mansion...
...but she didn't love me any more.
I got you here in order
to take revenge on you a little.
Are you all right?
Mom told me not to have
a grudge against my father.
I don't know.
What happened between
Father, Mother, and you?
I met Fahm more than ten years ago.
I used to a member of a political party.
I met her there.
I remember my mother
disappeared suddenly when I was little.
Maybe at that time...
Fahm was so attractive.
I fell in love with her
at a first sight and won her.
I flattered myself, thinking I could
control the government as I hoped.
Fahm and I loved each other.
But...
...some scandals were revealed
and the party was disbanded.
And I was wanted by the authorities.
At that time, I
abandoned Fahm and ran away.
I didn't understand how
deep Fahm loved me in those days.
Until I came to this mansion, I didn't
realize that how deep her love was...
...nor Dred's true nature.
I understand you hate Dred.
But Dred loved you and Fahm
from the bottom of his heart.
Only if I didn't approach her...
Please tell me one thing.
Mr. Foster, you treat me
kindly because I look like Mother?
You must be kidding.
Good morning, sir.
As you understand, today's
party is especially important.
Take care not to be impolite!
Yes!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Although I feel dizzy a little bit.
Don't overwork.
Thank you.
Cherry, Ren, quit playing around.
Yes.
Those two...
This is amazing.
They are very powerful politicians
and businessmen under their masks.
Really?
This party shows what an
influential person Mr. Dred is.
Thank you for coming...
...to our company's new
business announcement party...
Please.
...even though you are busy.
Young girl, why don't you come here.
Come on!
Excuse me.
We have prepared
another lady to service you.
Oh, is that so?
That's enough of the formal speech.
Everybody, please
enjoy this evening completely.
A toast to our country's future.
Cheers!
Leed!
I heard you went bankrupt.
What kind of scheme are part of now?
I can come back any time.
But I will never forgive Dred.
I'll bring about his downfall.
With Perkins!
Come to my side.
Join us.
And then...
Why you laugh?
I used to be supported by a
gorgeous vision of the Curey Port...
...but that time has gone already.
Stop sympathizing with yourself.
Sympathizing with myself...
...no I sympathize with you.
Go ahead and keep dancing.
Shit!
Ladies and gentleman,
sorry to keep you waiting.
This is the main dish for tonight.
Please, don't rush.
I will present a great show.
His days will be numbered soon.
Let's see the big star shining brightly
just before going out, with our own eyes.
Oh, you're dripping so much.
You're so horny.
What?
I see.
Call Perkins to my room.
Yes, sir.
They are wet enough.
Please...
...taste them to your hearts' content.
You're kidding me!
The union and the board of
directors have already decided on.
Since when did the board of
directors have the right to talk back to me?
Our company's size is too
big for you to control as you like.
Please think about this seriously.
And then...
...only if you offer us
information you've collected...
That's enough.
Dismissed!
I see, excuse me.
They demanded the
resignation of the master?
Yes.
Did they kick him out
of the company?
No, but he has no voice
for the company from now on.
Keep this in mind.
I don't think that guy has
the ability to take over Dred's job.
Foster.
Please help Dred.
I can't do anything for him now.
Hey, why don't you join us?
Sir, I am not...
I collected this
information with desperate effort.
How can I let them have it so easily?
That's it.
Give me any other papers.
You decided to
cooperate with Perkins, Mr. Leed?
Take it if you want it so much!
Fire, fire broke out!
Perkins!
Fahm...
Clair is getting to look like you.
Mr. Dred!
Stop!
It's too late.
No...
It's burning.
My house will be burnt up!
Dred, Dred...
Dred actually loved
you and Fahm very much.
Father...
Everything is finally over
and everybody went back home.
Ren went back to her sister, whom
Foster found with a private investigator.
Aisha went with her new
patron who only loves her.
Mother!
Leese went back to her family.
An old couple in a
town took care of Cherry.
And for me...
There's no place...
...for me to stay
except this burnt up mansion.
But...
I am not lonely...
...anymore.