Hurray, hurray To-Ai!
Hurray hurray To-Ai.
What's wrong with you guys?
You sound dead out there.
You need to have more spirit out there!
Do you understand?!
Ryo, we can't keep up with you anymore.
What?
Shut up,
you're not the captain of this squad!
Everyone wants to quit
the cheering squad along with me.
Huh?!
You demand too much from us.
You're not serious?
Yes...
We can't take it anymore.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Wait, wait.
lt would look bad for you
if we quit in middle of a game.
The squad's long ninety year history
end with you, captain.
Wait!
Please, you really aren't serious about this?
lt's too bad that the district head
of the cheering squad is watching.
What?
Don't do this.
l promise to be a better captain.
lf you insist.....
Get away!
l see...
You're supposed to be this tough girl,
but that's just an act, isn't it.
What do you mean.....
lf you want us to accept you
as our captain...
you'll have to prove yourself.
Can you finish the rest of the game
with this vibrator inside you?
lf you can keep waving the school flag
and cheer perfectly...
we will accept you as our captain.
Right guys?
That's right.
I can't let them win like this!
I have to do this.
l'll do it.
That's all l have to do?
Hand it over.
No, we'll help you, captain.
-Right?
-Right.
Wait a second...
Don't fuck up by having an orgasm.
We have to go back out there now.
Hurray, hurray, To-Ai.
Hurray, hurray, To-Ai, hurray, hurray, To-Ai.
I can't...
The district head...
Mr. Akagi's watching me.
I have to finish this.
Cheering Squad
You guys were kind of sad
during the first half...
but you really got going
during the second half...
when Ryo really started waving the flag.
Thank you!
No, thank Ryo.
Yes.
You did well.
Waving the flag for 50 minutes
is a lot of work.
Just like the captain tryouts.
Yes.
This squad is usually only
reserved for the guys...
but you waved the flag the longest,
beating everyone else.
There were a lot of objections.
lt was a great decision, though.
Thank you very much.
l have to go; l know you will continue
to be a great squad captain.
Of course!
Continue as captain...
Can I really continue to lead the squad
effectively after what happened today?
What?!
Captain, we really have to talk.
l think it can wait!
lt's really urgent.
Fine, l'll get dressed right now.
Shit, what a bastard!
Wait...
Where's my uniform;
what is this doing here...
l think you would look much better
in that uniform.
Dojima....
You had better give me my regular uniform
for the squad right now!
l mean it!
What's wrong with that?
Shut up! Give it back!
Besides, we need you to do something
important for the squad.
We want you to join the cheerleading
squad for just a few days.
l'm not a cheerleader!
lt's really not that different.
The fundamental concept
is the same, right?
What do you...?
You don't feel that
they are as legitimate as we are?
l didn't say that!
l think it's best for both squads...
if we improve our relationship
with the cheerleading squad.
Stop that!
l don't think you're in a position to argue.
You can't have us all quit, can you?
Besides, you really are the only one in the
squad that can do this, am l correct?
lt's the captain's job
to improve squad relations, Ryo.
Isn't that Ryo?
I thought she was part of
the Male Cheering Squad?
Did she switch to cheerleading?
I think she looks pretty hot
in that uniform, don't you?
Captain, you're walking kind of funny.
What?
l know you're not used to skirts;
you must be uncomfortable.
None of your business!
No, let me help you.
-This should help you out.
-No, Stop!
How are you, Ryo and Dojima!
Hi Aki.
Ryo, you look good!
lt's cute on you!
lt's easy--
just do what they want you to do.
l'll keep your captain's uniform safe.
We're counting on you, captain.
Ok, 1!
Okay, stop!
Come on, Ryo!
You have to kick your legs up
higher than that!
Just like this!
Waving flags does absolutely
nothing for your flexibility.
Would you two show her
flexibility exercises?
Sure!
Ryo, flexibility is really important.
You can't cheer properly
if you're wooden like this.
Don't!
What are you doing?
We're not hurting you!
We have to do the other side now.
Wait!
Oh my Ryo!
You're not wearing any underwear!
And you're all squishy!
What were you thinking about?
l think we can take care of this.
-Over here.
-Yes!
This is how we punish bad conduct!
Stop!
No, don't!
Please!
Hey Ryo, is this vibrator yours?
That's not!
l'm not done with you yet!
No!
Stop!
You're still soaking wet down here,
you little slut!
l think l'm coming!
Ryo, eat my pussy.
What?
You don't want to taste my pussy?
B...but...
lf you don't, l'll stop what l'm doing.
l'll pull this out.
Your choice.
l'll do it!
l'll eat your pussy, so please don't stop!
Okay, l love getting my pussy licked.
Just like that,
tongue fuck me just like that.
l'm going to come!
You're really starting to like this,
aren't you?
l can't take anymore!
l'm... l'm coming!
l'm going to come, too!
Few days later
More, more!
l think you did a great job
at improving squad relations, captain.
You know about the rugby team, right?
They're at the bottom of the district.
They have not won a single game yet.
They need to win a game
for the athletic department...
to get full funding of
all the teams and squads.
Part of that money goes
toward supporting our squad.
l have a great idea that would make sure
we get full funding for everybody.
Rugby Team
Excuse me,
but l have an announcement to make.
The cheer squad has an offer to make.
Huh?
To all the players that score in the game...
our captain will gladly reward you
after the game with her body!
Right on!
l...l didn't agree to this!
You'll be helping the whole school out.
l can't.
You don't want the squad
to get fully funded?
They're losing....this might help.
Captain, hey, look over here!
She's waiting to reward you guys!
All right!
Hurray, hurray To-Ai!
Hurray, hurray To-Ai, hurray, hurray To-Ai!
Does she need vibrators on her nipples?
l thought the guys might like it.
See, they're winning the game now.
I can't take this any more!
I think I'm going to faint!
No more!
You're awake now!
Thanks to you,
the rugby team won the game!
l think someone needs to
keep their end of the promise.
This is fucking great!
No, Don't!
l never would have guessed
that she was such a hottie!
You think she can handle all of us?
She's good at blow jobs.
She's really tight.
l'll try out her ass!
Wait, not there!
Her ass is super tight!
She's really starting to get into this!
She likes sucking cock!
l thought she was a frigid bitch,
but she's all right!
This feels good!
l want more!
Fuck me!
Please, fuck me!
I don't know why...
this feels so good.
Shit, l'm gonna come!
Am I just a slutty whore?
Have I become corrupted?
Few days later
l don't know about joining the squad.
Me too....
l heard the captain was really tough.
Don't worry about it.
l've got the captain wrapped
around my finger.
Excuse me, l'm coming in!
Hi, l'm here to enlist new recruits
for the semester!
We're really not....
We both haven't really decided.
You can't even handle
being a recruiting officer!
Uh, l'm really sorry!
Our squad has to cheer as a united team.
Unity is the most important thing here.
For you to join the squad...
Wow!
l need to get to know you both very well.
l...l'm going to join!
Me too!
Great, let's start!
I think I'm starting to
get the hang of being a captain.
I think this works best for me.
It's important to know
my squad members well.
I think it only helps me
become a better captain!