Kamiya Hospital
Amasato-kun.
Doctor.
Your body is always so sexy.
Doctor!
It feels wonderful.
Good girl.
You're already wet? You're really sensitive.
You taught me everything.
Everything...
Doctor...
No!
No.
I'm embarrassed. Don't look at me, Doctor.
No!
Doctor...
Oh, please...
Doctor!
Doctor...
I'm cumming. Something's coming...
Doctor! Doctor!
What do you mean?
I wanted to tell you earlier,
but I had a hard time bringing it up.
I'm sorry.
I'm engaged. I can't get out of it.
Is that... what this is about?
Welcome back, Onee-chan.
Tsukiko, what's wrong?
Youre late,
so I was worried.
How's Kenta?
He's trying his best to stay awake,
because I told him you were
gonna buy him a video game.
Oh. I must apologize to Kenta, too.
I...
just quit the hospital.
Keibiin
Episode 2: The Indecent Security Monitor
Still far away...
Um, I'm sorry!
No, it was my fault.
Shit.
There she is!
I'm sorry,
but can you come with me for a minute?
Manager.
Ah, Minomiya-kun.
Is something the matter?
Good timing.
At a closer glance, she's a prize!
Shit, if only the witch weren't here, I could get her.
Security Room
I-I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
Well, since it's your first offense,
I'll let you off with a warning today.
The start of the hunt is the most crucial.
I must mark my prey myself.
Too bad, but I guess I have to give up on this one.
She has a big sister, too?
This might come in handy.
Oh, no!
Stupid woman.
My, my, I guess I can't let this one slide.
May I help you?
Th-Thanks!
That shocked me.
But, oh well, I guess it wasn't that
big of a deal once I did it.
Jeez. Why am I so bad at balancing my budget?
There are so many days left until payday.
I guess... just for this month...
I'd better do something.
No way.
Wh-Why did she do it?
This is the item she stole.
But that's...
You're currently unemployed, right?
Your sister told me everything.
What a heartbreaking story.
She wanted to help buy her little brother
a game without bothering her big sister.
But you see...
I'll pay for the game! Just don't tell anyone.
One million yen to keep me quiet.
But I don't have that kind of money... not on me.
That's what l'd like to say,
but you're the head of your household.
And you're unemployed.
So you see...
This isn't a joke! How dare you!
I'll turn you over to the authorities!
Go ahead. Be my guest
But if you do,
then I'll tell the police about your sister.
If you care about your sisters future,
isn't giving yourself to me just once a fair trade?
You're worth about a million yen.
I guarantee it.
Don't bother. I'll undress myself.
Not so fast.
If you want to take off your clothes,
there's a proper place for doing it.
This is a department store, after all.
This is such a big store.
So what if I steal something little?
It won't hurt them a bit.
Yes, that's true.
What's going on?
What am I supposed to do here?
Like I said, undress. Right here.
You can't be serious!
Oops. I wouldn't yell if I were you.
Business may be slow on a weekday afternoon,
but it's not like there's no one here.
You are insane.
So you finally get it?
That's a good idea. Something for summer, too.
Just make it quick.
Enjoy your pride while you can.
It's too late anyway.
I've already lost everything.
You're pretty small.
H-Hurry.
If you wanna do it, just do it.
Spread your legs.
I'm hard, see?
And you're all wet.
You're enjoying it, aren't you?
N-No, I'm not.
What was that?
Just now... I heard a strange voice.
Turn around and show me your butt.
What a great angle.
Take a look at yourself.
Don't you like it?
You're too loud.
Or do you want to be caught?
No.
Oh, no, my voice...
If you wanna scream, then scream.
No.
No ones here.
I guess that should do it. Time to go home.
No...
Excuse me!
Shit.
Oh, no.
Now for the other problem!
That was really scary.
I should go home now.
Miss, may I talk to you?
But I didn't really...
I didn't.
That didn't pass through the register, did it?
I've been waiting for you, Miss.
A nice view, isn't it? Quite stunning.
A great view even for a security guard.
Why did you bring me here?
Well, I wonder.
Will you really keep quiet for me?
Yeah.
I'll stay quiet about your shoplifting.
Um...
but why did I see you in the dressing room?
Well.
She was the same as you.
So you see...
You're not a little girl.
I'm sure you knew all along why I called you here.
Stop It!
Please stop it!
I'll take off my own clothes.
That's a good idea.
You wouldn't want your clothes torn.
Your husband would find out.
Um...
All of it?
Of course all of it.
In this kind of place?
The lights are off. No one will see you.
We don't need to hold back.
Hold back?
What are you...
Oh, no!
No!
Someone, help me!
Miss, you're too stubborn.
Ow! Not so suddenly!
I don't like it!
Ow!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry. Please forgive me!
No!
No... No!
Answer it.
Hello?
Darling!
What's wrong? Where are you?
You can't sleep?
In that case...
No. It's nothing.
There's brandy.
On the top shelf.
Don't worry. I have plenty of alcohol...
tucked away.
Yes.
I will.
I'll come home as soon as I can.
I'll be careful.
Yes.
Go to bed without me.
Good night.
Was that your husband?
That's a fine expression.
That's a married woman for you.
Great at moving her hips.
Makes me jealous of your husband.
Yes. I love that face.
No!
Please.
Please let me go.
Let me go!
I'll cum very soon.
Inside? No!
Be nice, wifey. I'll shoot plenty of stuff into you.
No! I don't want to!
Please! Anything but that!
Please. Cum outside.
No! No!
I'm cumming, wifey.
No!
It 's all my fault
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
darling!
To Be Continued...