No...
Don't!
Forgive me.
Please, something's happening to me!
K E I B I I N
Episode 1: Department Poaching
23 | 63cm | Not very tight
Yes?
Manager, what brings you here?
Minomiya-kun, did something nice happen to you?
You're smiling.
Aw, cut it out.
Nothing's happened, really.
Oh?
Manager, the store is still open.
You caught a shoplifter, didn't you?
So here's a reward.
Ever since you started working here,
more thieves have been caught.
You said the man who used to have my position...
got in a horrible accident or something?
I guess so.
But it doesnt matter. He was useless anyway.
It was actually a blessing.
Are you sure you should be talking like that?
I-It's okay.
I'm only interested in useful men.
Yes. In useful men.
Yes. Good...
Who wants an easy lay?
Women are best if they have to be hunted.
I'm a bad person. Oh God, help mе.
Miss,
is something the matter?
Nothing.
You look quite pale.
Um, I'm fine.
Sorry to bother you!
Um, miss!
Oh. Oh, nо...
That stupid clerk was in the way.
Oh, well.
I'll watch her for a little while longer.
I can't do it.
That's not like me.
S-Sakiko-senpai?
Yo!
Hey, why are you looking so pale?
I'm getting good results myself.
Senpai!
I just... can't do it!
I'm too scared... too scared.
But I was hoping we could experience the rush together.
Next time, I promise.
I promise I'll go through with it!
So, please... So please, don't hate me!
Very well.
Don't do that. What if someone comes in?
Don'tworry. As long as you're quiet...
по опе will notice.
So that's what's going on.
What fun.
Y-Y-Yes... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
You're already so wet. How cute.
I'm sorry.
Looks like you'll be needing new underwear.
You understand?
Y-Yes.
You mustn't do that.
This is bad.
Youre still so young.
Okay?
Y-Yes.
You too.
Thanks for your business.
I'm wiped out.
What a drag. I know he suspects we're in cahoots.
I wonder if he's a peeper? That pervert.
No, I'm sure that's not it.
He must be trying to steer me to the correct path.
I think he's a messenger from God.
That's bullshit. What are you talking about?
We'll be okay next time. Okay?
If you're so against it, then I won't force you, Koyume.
No...
No!
I'm disappointed in you.
Why don't you pray to your beloved God?
Senpai!
Senpai...
That girl is resisting mе?
I'm not putting up with that shit!
Excuse me, Miss.
Yes?
I apologize for interrupting you, but...
See?
You we're caught by the camera.
l've had my eye on you for a while.
Though I'm sure you didn't notice.
Well, then.
W-Wait a minute!
Don't do it... Not the police.
Don't talk crazy.
You committed a crime.
It's a third-degree crime.
Those who steal the belongings of someone else...
shall be convicted of theft,
and sentenced to a maximum of ten years in prison.
That's what it says.
Are you the only guard here? You are, right?
If you promise to keep quiet,
you сап do with me as you please.
I think this arrangement benefits
both of us, wouldn't you say?
That's a nice idea.
I knew you'd understand me.
That's too boring.
You're boring.
You're too fucking boring!
I don't like your irresponsible attitude!
Someone help me!
Now that was much more thrilling.
Senpai?
Was it... a dream?
No!
Stop it.
Don't be so rough!
Please...
Shut up, bitch.
No!
You probably used this tactic to stay out of jail before.
N-No.
O-Ow!
No!
No...
Why?
I like to get footage of it.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Your pussy is all wet. What do you mean, "Stop it"?
No.
No. S-Stop it...
Don't... No!
Don't! Not there. Please stop it!
I'm almost there!
Don't do it. Please, stop it!
Not inside of me!
Like l'd listen to you.
I'm gonna cum inside of you plenty.
No! No! No!
You're horrible.
Now you'll erase the video tape, won't you?
I don't think so.
Why not!?
As long as I have that tape,
you'll never escape me your entire life.
As long as you do what I say,
I won't show the tape to anyone. Got it?
You coward!
You bitch. Don't you know your place!?
Hey.
Where's your answer?
Yes.
I wonder if she'll call me today?
Hello?
Koyume? It's mе, Sakiko.
Senpai!
Listen, we're too different to be together.
Why?
I think I was wrong to make you do that.
Goodbye.
Wait! Don't hang up!
What is it?
I сап... do it too.
The same thing as you.
So... So...
We'll be closing the store soon.
Please make your way to the
register as soon as possible.
Just doing my job.
It's your second offense.
I can't let you go with a warning this time.
Will you accompany me to mу оffice?
Yes.
Security Room
I'm sorry. You were sent here from God to save me,
but I betrayed you.
I don't know about the God part,
but I'm a little hurt that you betrayed my trust.
I'm a bad person.
Please. Please call the police.
For now, it seems you're sorry.
So I'll let you off today.
Well, let me take you home.
The path home at night...
sure is scary.
Really?
I'm used to it myself.
This is...
What's wrong?
Well, it looks like something that belongs to my friend.
Oh, I know that woman.
She was caught shoplifting.
She wasn't remorseful about it
so I had to punish her a little.
S-Senpai!
Why?
Koyume, I'm sorry.
Wh-What's happening?
She's my slave.
I arranged it so that you would shoplift again.
You arranged it?
Sakiko told me everything. It's your first time, right?
Don't worry.
I'll make your punishment light.
No way. This isn't happening!
You're that kind of sick person?
I don't want to believe it.
You just said so yourself, didn't you?
You're a bad person.
So you must confess your sins...
and atone for them.
No!
Don't fuck with me!
No.
Save me!
Senpai!
I guess she lost consciousness.
Minomiya-san...
This feels wonderful.
Where... am I?
Wow!
Oh, по!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
So you finally woke up, Koyume-chan?
It sure was tough carrying you here.
No! Don't look at me!
Well then,
should we begin?
No!
Don't worry.
Isn't it your first time, Koyume?
What a great opportunity!
Don't say that.
I can't do that.
You still don't understand the position you're in.
Sakiko,
would you please tell this girl what she should do?
Very good, Koyume.
For her first time, she has nice technique.
I taught her how to use her tongue well.
But she's never sucked an actual penis before.
I guess lesbians don't like dick.
Koyume, put it in.
Didn't you hear him?
Put it in your mouth.
Okay...
Move the whole thing inside of your
mouth and use your tongue, too.
Your teeth are brushing it slightly. Keep that up.
Good for you, Koyume.
We'd better make you ready too.
Hey, not so roughly.
We haven't even started yet.
Please, stop it.
No! That hurts!
Ow! Stop it!
She's really tight.
But it feels... really great!
Young lady.
Not this.
No!
Please... stop... it
Koyume...
That hurts!
Stop.
N-No!
That's great! It's perfect!
Koyume,
you've become a woman now. Just like me.
If I'm like this...
will I...
be forgiven?
To Be Continued...