Thank you for shopping at our store today.
Hello?
It's me.
You were amazing.
I need your help again.
No way. I'II never go with
a pervert like you again.
Don't call me ever!
But I'm already here.
I'm waiting for you by the exit.
Y-You've gotto be kidding me.
Keibiin
Episode 3: The Lustful, Final Encounter
I've gotta get out of here!
Untie me!
Tying me up? You never mentioned that!
No need to be scared.
Don't worry. I'm just gonna love you.
Okay?
Wh-Whats that for?
You act all experienced,
but you're still tight here.
You really are young.
Don't worry.
It doesn't hurt.
That's cold!
I can see everything inside of you.
Deep inside, all the way to your womb.
How does it feel?
To have air flowing all the way inside of you?
Isn't it wonderful?
It sucks! Stop it!
You're so pretty, Chiyo-chan.
There's still more.
Become more embarrassed for me, Chiyo-chan!
No!
Just stop it already!
I'm begging you!
But there's still one more very tiny hole.
This is a very fun thing.
Against your will, your pee is flowing out!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Tell me, aren't you embarrassed?
I don't care!
Oh dear, don't move.
See?
It fell out.
You pervert!
Why did I let him talk me into that?
Nothing unusual, eh?
Guess I'll go back.
That girl... from before.
What should I do?
That's right!
I'll ask one of the employees
to let me out the back.
Um,
excuse me...
Is anyone here?
Anyone...
Wh-What the hell!
What's your problem!?
Someone help me!
Chiyo-chan, you won't play with me anymore?
How dare you. See?
Didn't you have fun with it last time?
Let's use it again.
Come on, come on.
See.
Come on, come on...
No! Stop it!
I'm begging you, please stop it! Please!
No!
You get it, don't you? Do as I say!
You're amazing!
Don't... No!
Don't be so formal.
I'm the guy who looked through your
private place to your internal organs!
N-No. Stop it!
The other day, we had to stop half way through,
so let's take it nice and slow today!
Nothing abnormal today, eh?
Maybe I should call one of the older girls.
Yeah, like that wife from the other week.
Golden Shower
Doing something like this
is perfect, isn't it?
Here I come, Chiyo-chan!
That's great!
Chiyo!
That's my property.
What an interesting way of using it.
How dare you interrupt!
Those police sure are nosy.
Are you okay?
Thanks, Mr. Security Guard.
But that stalker of yours sure was sloppy.
That sucked.
I never had a client like that before.
I figured he wasn't your boyfriend,
because he's much older than you.
Wait a minute! I'm not in
the mood for a lecture!
Huh? Why would I lecture you?
When people find out what I do,
they all lecture and condemn me.
Like they wouldn't do the same.
You've got a point I guess work is work.
Isn't it though?
Thank God.
I'm glad someone like you rescued me.
I'm not as nice of a guy as you think I am.
Sure, sure.
Hey, Mr. Security Guard!
Can I come visit you some time?
I guess you can, but I'm off now.
Oh, really?
Then for your shift today,
I'll bring you a snack. Like it?
Really? I'd love that.
I'll let you in through the back.
It's a promise then.
She stepped into the net herself.
What a stupid girl.
Video tapes?
They were in here yesterday.
Who took them?
The Caribou's Glitter?
What's a security guard doing with this?
What a big mouse you are.
Until yesterday they were in my office.
Who took them?
I don't think they'd be here, but...
You horrible woman!
Manager?
Tell me.
Who are you?
I guess you don't plan on confessing to me.
If you think I'm an ordinary woman,
you're in for a shock.
You're right.
You're using your position
as store manager...
to steal precious jewelry.
An ordmary woman wouldn't
do something like that.
Oh. So you want to die that badly?
Tell me!
Who are you!?
You're a tough one.
But I wonder how much longer
you can stay so tough?
Oh, dear.
A man's thing...
and a woman's nipple are
quite similar, aren't they?
Well?
Do you feel like talking now?
The Caribou's Glitter.
What?
Half a year ago, it was stolen
from an overseas museum.
I can only imagine how it ended
up in your possession.
Why, you...
If you're going to put up
that strong of a protest,
then perhaps you'd rather not
live as a woman anymore.
You're okay with that right?
What are you...
No! Don't!
It's even crueler when a fellow
woman does it to you.
Oh my, oh my. You've pissed yourself.
What a gross woman.
Who's there!?
It's me, Manager.
Ah, Minomiya-kun. So you were here.
I overheard your conversation.
Well, that's all right.
Minomiya-kun, you have no means
of blackmailing me now.
What do you mean?
Do you think I'm completely oblivious?
What?
You capture female shoplifters
and treat them like toys.
I see.
So you stole my video tapes.
That's right. And if I feel like it,
I can turn them over to
the police at any time.
I figured someone was bound to
discover them in time, anyway.
No matter what you do,
it doesn't concern me.
What a good boy.
Well, I'm glad you showed
me something interesting.
It was good luck that you were
the one who caught me.
Can you watch over this girl for
a little while, Minomiya-kun?
You want me to be your accomplice?
Surely you're not satisfied
with your current wages.
All I have to do is watch her?
Go ahead and do whatever you want.
I'll turn a blind eye.
I guess that's a nice assignment.
I have a date tonight!
So, who the hell are you?
Well...
I guess it doesn't really matter.
Hey, you want to make a deal?
If you help me escape,
I'll give you money.
I don't care about money.
I know where the tapes are.
The tapes?
You mean the video tapes?
They're in white cases, and only
the side labels are written on.
Where are they?
I'll tell you if you agree to help me.
If I betray my employer,
you'll give me my tapes.
Doesn't seem like a great deal to me.
That's why I mentioned the money.
I'll pay you as well.
What did I say before!?
I don't care about money.
Then what do you want?
Your... body, I guess.
I'd like to just fuck you here.
But if you give in to me of your own
free will, maybe I'll help you out.
Can you do it?
Will you really... let me escape?
Okay then. Let's do it.
Why are you holding back?
I don't feel anything at all.
B-But...
it's my first time doing this.
Then I'll give you a special lesson.
Just this once.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Your technique is awful, but I actually
like how your teeth are scratching me.
I'm cumming. You'd better drink it!
Idiot, I told you to drink it.
Are you satisfied?
Don't be ridiculous. We've
just barely started.
I understand.
I guess you're into it now.
Women sure are scary.
I feel... I feel wonderful!
I love it.
Yes!
I... I...
Yes.
In the end, women are creatures...
that will do anything to survive.
Hey!
Just relax.
Not there!
I guess it's your first time from behind.
No. Stop it!
As I thought, it's really tight.
That hurts!
Relax your butt. It'll hurt less that way.
It's all the way in there.
Ow!
It hurts!
You're tearing me up!
I'm thrusting all the way inside.
You won't get pregnant this
way, so you should be glad.
You can't escape naked.
There are plenty of store clothes in here.
Wear whatever you want.
You're letting me... escape?
Hurry up.
Thanks!
Okay, all clear.
It seems we can't exit out the front.
I never thought you'd betray me.
Shit.
Well, regardless of what I did,
are you really okay with killing her?
Yes, I am. Right?
Murasame Shizuna-san.
Murasame?
She's the granddaughter and heiress
to the Mizukoshi Group.
She stands to inherit the entire
Company and fortune.
I thought she looked familiar,
so I looked up my rival Company's
file and found her.
For my own sake, I can't let her survive.
You... Why did you go to these lengths?
I couldn't let the media find out
so I decided to act alone.
But I had no idea it would
blow so out of proportion.
I had no idea that she was in with Mitsuyo!
I'm impressed.
You acted as your own private detective.
I wouldn't have expected less
from that old man's heir.
But you see, it's already too late.
Time to die.
I guess it's over.
Hey, who was that woman?
Just a dangerous, crazy woman with a knife.
You're Minomiya-san, aren't you?
I'm impressed, young heiress.
What's going on?
Why is the security guard...
I hope we meet again.