Kekko Kamen
Volume 1
The Toenail of Satan's
Spartan Institute of
Higher Education
Hey, hey! Do your best!
This Midnight Concentration Camp is
the most effective way to learn to
handle school pressures!
That's an advantage you get in an
educational institute like this!
The time limit is sixty minutes!
You must solve one question a minute!
Hey, hurry, hurry!
You're all a bunch of worthless, lowly slugs,
and the student with the lowest score
is going to spend some quality time
in the punishment center!
Hey, hey, do your work!
Welcome to the Spartan Institute.
I am your principal, known to all
as the Big Toenail of Satan.
Ms. Gestapoko, I have heard much about your
performance at the Auschwitz Academy.
As I'm sure you're aware, the Spartan
Institute's policy is...
To go beyond the standards and disciplines
of so-called progressive schools
and to train an elite order
of malleable minds.
These objectives have our highest priority.
Anything's justified if it serves those goals.
Correct. I don't accept that students
have "human rights."
Short of killing them, your students are
yours to do with as you please.
I love it. I love anything thorough.
Before you start settling into your new post,
I would like to ask you to do one little thing.
We need a "Special Punishment" for the
student with the worst grade
in today's special class, the one who
most disgraces our school...
That shall be your first assignment
as Punishment Teacher.
You make me happy right away.
Hey, hey! Thirteen minutes left!
Urge yourself onward! Urge!
Oh no! I mustn't fall asleep...
Hey, hey! I'll hit you if you're dull!
No! I mustn't sleep, not now!
No, it didn't help...
Takahashi!
You dare fall asleep in my class?!
I'm sorry! It was just for a second!
Please forgive me!
I will never forgive you!
It's proof you're a slacker!
I don't even need to grade you now!
You're going to receive the full
"Special Punishment!"
No!
Episode 1
Here I Am: The Messenger of Love and Justice!
"Here I Am: The Messenger
of Love and Justice!"
Episode 1
Here I Am: The Messenger of Love and Justice!
Special Punishment Room
Teacher Ben, this is Ms. Gestapoko,
our new Punishment Teacher.
Well, well!
What, not this student again?
The former Punishment Teacher
was overindulgent.
She had no guts at all!
I see.
What do you want me to do?
This student is dull and listless.
Please sharpen her up and
bring her up to speed!
Speed up her reflexes? Roger.
No!
No whiners allowed!
Ms. Gestapoko, please be kind
enough to teach her this!
Let's go!
Escape from my whip if you don't like pain!
This special training ought to
improve your speed!
Let's go!
I said try to escape.
Or do you enjoy this sort of thing?
Help me!
You're too slow! Go faster!
The path to becoming elite is no picnic!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
If that was good enough, there'd be no
work for the Punishment Teacher!
Let's go!
I'm so happy. Go further! Go faster!
Here!
And next... There!
Let's go!
Oh boy!
Are you happy, Teacher Ben?
Oh yes! I'll follow you all my life!
Please forgive me! Don't rip off my panties!
No! Ms. Gestapoko, go for it!
Are you ready?
The last one.
All right!
What?
A power failure?
Who's that?
Who the hell are you?
What is that?
Go and get her!
Yes!
What is it?
Here comes the
great hero!
Wow!
Very interesting...
There's something different about this school.
Who... Who are you?
That punishment last night...
Was it all a dream?
It wasn't a dream.
Ms. Takahashi?
You're Mayumi Takahashi, Grade 1, Class 1?
Yes.
Uh...
The teachers in this school are the worst.
However, don't let them get you down.
Got that, Ms. Takahashi?
Uh... Sure.
Excuse me, but may I have your name?
Names aren't important.
Just know I'm your upperclassmate,
and I'm on your side.
Bye.
But...
She might be the...
I see... Isn't this interesting?
Teachers' Lounge
Just let me touch a little bit.
Principal!
What the? This is my break!
Can't we talk about business later?
Oh, please don't say that!
I've found out whose panties these were!
Huh? What?
Take a look at this.
Wow... This is...
She's an honors student with the
top grade point average,
Chigusa Yuka, Grade 2, Class 2.
You have evidence those
panties belong to her?
I, Teacher Ben, know the smell of all the
different panties of all the girls in this school!
I'm impressed.
So, Principal, I have an idea
to discuss with you.
Yeah... Yeah... Ummm...
I see. Teacher Ben, you are pretty perverted.
What're you talking about?
Principal, you're the most perverted of all!
Yeah, yeah! That's the truth!
To the student body of this Spartan Institute...
Last night, one of you betrayed this
school's sacred policy.
This criminal committed the heinous act
of obstructing the punishment
which is our school's most honored tradition!
I now ask the guilty student who
did it to come forward.
All right then, I'll try something else.
Mayumi Takahashi, Grade 1,
Class 1, come on down!
What? Why?
No! Let me go!
Here we go!
In front of everybody...
How humiliating!
If the student I met last night does
not come forward immediately,
then the lovely Ms. Takahashi here
will be shamed even further.
Well? No? Not coming out?
That's it, then. Go to it, Ms. Gestapoko!
All right!
I'm on fire!
The woman from last night better come out!
Don't treat this situation lightly!
Come forward quickly!
Hey!
Mother...
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
Oh, what shall I do?
What? Are you so full of fear
that you can't fight me?
Wait a second, wait a moment, Ms. Gestapoko.
What?
I want to add my own touch
to this punishment.
There we go!
Oh ho, I see.
No!
There!
Come out if you still want to call
yourself a "Great Hero!"
Around and around!
Round and round and round she goes!
Everybody will see everything if I keep turning.
Now nobody will ever want to marry me.
Go!
What are you thinking of out there?
This is the last one...
It's you...
Stop it! This is just too much!
So, you've finally shown up.
You kept us waiting quite a while.
Wrong! I just couldn't stand to see
Ms. Takahashi abused any longer!
So, Chigusa Yuka, you finally
show your true colors!
Principal, I don't know anything about this!
You don't know when to give up, do you?
Your panties are all the evidence we need!
Those are...
I do love a farce, but the time
has come to finish this!
I'll make you dance, you insolent bitch!
Peel her down!
Hold it right there!
What the?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Nobody knows my face, but
everybody knows my body.
God has sent me to bring justice
to this school from Hell!
My name is Kekko...
Kekko Kamen!
I hide my face but expose all else!
Ben, I am very satisfied!
Oh yes, Principal!
Corrupt teachers exposing a helpless
maiden in public...
Abusing your students to further
your own dirty ambitions!
Even if the Board of Education does,
Kekko Kamen will never forgive you!
You're...
Mayumi, now that I'm here, you've got
nothing else to worry about.
Don't make me laugh!
Go, bodyguards!
Nice shot!
Principal Toenail of Satan.
Have a peek at my secret technique!
Open...
Jump!
Next technique: Muff-o-cation Wring!
What shall I do?
Kekko Kamen, that was great!
Thank you very much.
Me, me, me, me too...
What're you waiting for?
What, what, what? Why, why, why?
Gestapoko, I can't forgive you, even
though we're both women!
You're pretty good, but I'm not
knocked over by your presence
like some stupid men I could mention.
You talk too much! Come on!
Can you escape the taste of my whip? There!
I read something once...
Got it! An S & M queen is...
Hey, hey, hey!
The S & M queen is...
The queen secretly wishes to be beaten!
Hey, hey, hey! Do you feel good?
How was that? Who's the queen now?
Good!
Here! I'll give you the coup de grace!
Feeling good!
Students of Spartan Institute!
Kekko Kamen will be anywhere, anytime,
where evil exposes itself.
Gee, I guess I'm just a little self-conscious!
Good-bye, everybody! See you again!
Kekko Kamen! She's so gorgeous!
The Principal and Teacher Ben were
excited about a pair of panties
that were stolen from my room
three days ago.
Why did Kekko Kamen have them,
and what is her secret identity?
Please watch the next episode
if you want to know about it.
Promise me!