Kekko Kamen
Volume 2
What's the matter?
Aren't you having fun?
Why do you run away from me?
Stupid frigging...
So, how's that? It doesn't hurt, does it?
Aren't you scared, cutie-pie?
You know this is to improve your
academic performance!
Why, no matter what I do, won't
your grades go up, eh?
Why's that, eh?
I really don't know myself...
I really do study as hard as I can.
Liar! If you were really struggling,
your grades wouldn't be so pathetic!
Okay then...
You'll change those sloppy study
habits soon enough,
or your cute little body will
be torn in half!
She's going to... She's going to...
She's going to say IT...
Oh yeah!
No!
Episode 1
Mystery! The Legend of the Evil Android!
"Mystery! The Legend of the Evil Android!"
Episode 1
Mystery! The Legend of the Evil Android!
Takahashi!
You dozed off again, you brainless twit!
No! I didn't!
I'm so sorry!
I'll forgive you this once.
And now, everyone!
We have a new student transferring
to our school today.
My name is Hanoko Tanaka.
It's very nice to meet you.
What a beautiful girl!
Ms. Tanaka's grade point average
at the last school she attended
was extremely high.
I expect her to continue to distinguish herself in
the same fashion here at the Spartan Institute.
And I sincerely hope you will all do your
very best to keep up with her example.
Announcing the Big Toenail's
Top Honors Student!
First Place
Hanoko Tanaka - 10,000 Pts
Awesome!
That honor student is so gorgeous!
All done!
Very good. Now you know how to factor.
You did a good job.
Thank you for teaching me.
It's no trouble.
I'm just not very good at math.
Hanoko, can I ask you something?
What?
You've only just come to this school.
Why do you help me with my homework?
Why are you so nice to me?
Who else would help me?
Could you be...
Kekko...
Mayumi, are you still awake?
Yes!
I'll be back tomorrow to finish your lessons.
You look strange. What's wrong?
Nothing at all!
Grading Notes
- Mathematics -
Junior Class
Principal, our success is beyond
our wildest expectations!
It's fantastic!
Tanaka has stimulated the other students,
and test scores are rising rapidly,
oh revered one!
Of course, of course...
and test scores are rising rapidly,
oh revered one!
Of course, of course...
It's to be expected.
I AM a genius, you know.
And how is the problematic
Ms. Takahashi doing?
Uh... Um... Oh, where is it?
Wait one second! Let me take a look at it!
Mayumi Takahashi...
What? She's still at the bottom
of her grading class?
In fact, she's doing worse than ever before.
And her grades are actually getting worse!
I guess there's been no improvement!
None at all? Not even a little
itsy bitsy increase?
That's just not possible! Teacher Ben!
Yes sir!
Summon Hanoko Tanaka at once.
Your grades dropped THAT much?
Yes. I don't know what to do.
I'll be punished again, I know it.
What can it be?
I don't understand this. You are studying.
So what's the problem?
Don't you have any idea why
you can't concentrate?
Mayumi?
I know what it is. It's her!
Mayumi!
Everything's A-Okay!
There we go!
Oh, Principal, the Total Tune-up
has been completed!
Fantastic! Push the button, Ben!
Yes sir! Right away!
That's where I thought it was!
I'll do it myself! I can't resist!
Poke and listen for the "click."
We did it! We really did it!
The Tune-up worked!
All right! Hanoko Tanaka, a.k.a.
Tougenkyou Unit #1...
What is your prime directive?
To improve all students who perform
below expectations.
Yes, that much you already knew.
But what do you do NOW if the targeted
student doesn't improve?
Punish them and punish them.
Endless perpetual punishment until
their grades improve.
I am the ultimate punishment machine,
Tougenkyou #1.
Exactly. You're an android developed
for the purpose of
encouraging students into producing
better grades.
But, I made a fundamental error
when I designed you.
Because of your great beauty,
certain students can't study,
and consequentially, still get bad grades.
That error has now been corrected!
Go forth now and punish them.
Do whatever you wish to those
students who fail to perform!
I expect nothing less than success!
Oh, Principal, thirty years of research
has finally paid off!
Yes, yes. I'm a genius!
Tougenkyou #1, you've been given all
the additional powers and skills
necessary for your new task.
Your target is Mayumi Takahashi.
Go forth, Super Punishment Android!
What, really?
No, really!
Miss Tanaka?
Miss Tanaka, please leave Mayumi alone!
What's that?
What do you mean? I wasn't doing anything.
Well, what were you going to do then?
Yuka, please stop.
We weren't doing anything.
Don't be such a bitch.
If you'll excuse me.
Why did you...
That new student.
There's something wrong with her.
Don't you feel it?
I think you'd be better off not
being so close to her.
What? What're you talking about?
Are you jealous because we're getting
along or something?
Hey, I'm not jealous!
I'm just worried about you.
The fact is, since she came to this school,
your grades have gotten consistently worse!
But...
I am NOT jealous.
I wish I had big breasts like yours.
Mine aren't...
My shoulders are always stiff
because of these things.
My designer is a pervert.
What?
Oh, nothing...
Hanoko, you... You do have
such big breasts.
Are you HER?
What're you talking about?
I mean Kekko Kamen.
You're Kekko Kamen, aren't you?
That's why you help me, right?
I'd prefer seeing your answers to
listening to this silly babble.
I think I'm probably right...
Shut up.
What's the matter?
All your answers are wrong!
What?
You really are a moron.
You're so cruel.
Here it comes, you pathetic little twit!
You're not Kekko Kamen!
How can you be like this?
Because she's Super Punishment Android
Tougenkyou #1, that's why!
What?
Those luscious tentacles course with
tantalizing tidbits of electricity!
How's that, Mayumi Takahashi?
Do you like that?
No, I don't!
Whips! Electricity! Massaging tits!
Three forms of attack at once!
What an irresistible set-up!
Yes! I've studied this extreme
combination for over thirty years.
Her grades will improve by
this method... Or else!
Stop it!
Chigusa...
Cease and desist with this vicious cruelty!
What excellent timing!
You, too, will be a victim of Tougenkyou #1!
She's certainly got enough extra
tentacles to handle you!
Teacher Ben, peel off her clothes!
Yes sir!
It's my pleasure!
Oh no...
That's Kekko Kamen!
Kekko Kamen!
Huh? Where is she?
And now, for all of you,
Spread-Eagle Jump!
She's great!
Oh, what a feeling!
The defender of Love and Justice...
Kekko Kamen is here!
Tougenkyou #1!
You've sown much evil in the name of
improving this girl's grades!
Worse than that, you've betrayed her trust!
Even though others might, Kekko Kamen
shall never forgive that!
There're too many bodies in here.
Let's take this outside, you
breast-fixated robot!
All right.
Yuka, take care of Mayumi.
Yes ma'am!
Can you escape from my twisted
tentacle technique?
Come on!
Hey, hey! My electrical cables will shock you!
It's not over, not by a long shot!
Not there!
She must have a weakness, but what?
She's got to find a way to counterattack!
And this rain doesn't help either.
Kekko Kamen's only human.
If this fight goes on too long,
she'll be at a major disadvantage!
Come, Kekko Kamen!
Let me take you to heaven!
What is her weakness?
That's it!
That's got to be it!
Your weak point...
This is it!
What?
Here I go!
The secret "Switch Off" technique!
Did she kill her?
I should've known what those
perverts would do.
It's only logical they'd put her
switch on her private parts.
Mayumi.
Yes ma'am?
I hope you continue to do your best.
Yuka, please take care of her.
As always, I'm on your side.
On the other hand, I'm a little embarrassed.
Good-bye!
Thank you, Kekko Kamen!