Kekko Kamen.
Kekko Kamen 2
Please, forgive me!
I'll study as hard as I can!
Please help me!
There will be no negotiation!
There... Yes...
No!
Stop! Stop!
No way!
There, there... There, there...
Episode 2
Crisis! Kekko Kamen Only Lives Twice!
"Crisis! Kekko Kamen Only Lives Twice!"
Episode 2
Crisis! Kekko Kamen Only Lives Twice!
Spartan Institute of
Higher Education
This girl, Freshman Class 4, Yoshiko Satou,
has been punished by having her
clothing torn from her body.
From this point forward, all those who
have grades as bad as hers
will receive the same punishment.
Of course, I hope each student
will do their very best,
but as we're not interested in the male
students, I don't really care what they do.
Signed - Your Loving Principal,
the Big Toenail of Satan.
What am I going to do?
Yuka.
What's wrong? You look pale, Mayumi.
Those perverted teachers haven't changed.
Yuka, what am I going to do?
Mayumi...
Help me...
No!
Stop it!
Why do you have to do stuff like that?
Like what?
I give you a beautiful house on campus.
I pay you lots of money for being
the Punishment Teacher.
I just don't think you should glue the paper
on the umbrella yourself, like some pauper!
It is a tradition of Ronin to
glue paper on umbrellas.
I might also add that I have
punished a lot of students
but have yet to see this
Kamen what's-her-name.
When I'm bored, this is something to do.
Principal, we need Mayumi Takahashi.
I guess so. I should've chosen Mayumi
Takahashi at the beginning.
Hey, I want you doing your job
punishing students,
not gluing umbrellas.
What is it this time?
Freshman Class 1, Mayumi Takahashi.
Her grades are really, really bad,
and she has a nice little body.
Principal, we were not talking
about her body, Sir.
Oh, really?
I don't like performing these
cruel punishments,
but for educational purposes,
I suppose I must.
Besides, are you really sure the Naked Kamen
will appear this time if I punish this girl?
We're sure, we're sure!
Principal, I want to make it clear
that although I took this job, I don't enjoy it!
And besides, if I punish that girl,
are you really sure the Naked Kamen
will appear this time?
We're sure, we're sure, we're sure!
Principal, I want to make it clear
that although I took this job, I don't enjoy it!
It is only for the purpose of education...
And...
And what?
I am very interested in this
Kamen what's-her-name,
whom you have both described.
I can not resist fighting against such
a strong enemy as this Kamen.
By the way, you do remember that
the fight will cost you extra?
Have I made myself clear?
I knew that already.
Tomorrow will be the day I shall cut
her into teenie weenie pieces.
And if the Naked Kamen appears, I will
show you my deadly technique.
Oh, you are a bad one, aren't you?
I may be bad, but I'm not a pervert!
Huh? What did I do?
Oh nuts!
Are you saying you witnessed everything?
Yes. What should I do?
I know I'll be punished again,
and if not, they'll do something to me
because I'm a witness.
That's quite a problem.
I wonder if there's any way to drive out
that outdated samurai?
No, Yuka. Please don't do
anything dangerous!
If you were hurt because of me,
I couldn't handle it!
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
But, the only thing left to do is to wait
for Kekko Kamen to help us.
Mayumi, waiting around for Kekko Kamen
to show up isn't a solution!
We must find a way ourselves!
Yes...
This is no ordinary umbrella.
I've got it!
There's only one way to help Mayumi.
Are you Mayumi Takahashi,
Freshman Class 1?
Uh... Yeah?
You are!
Yes?
I have heard that you are very stupid.
I have no personal conflict with you,
but this is my job.
No!
All of this is purely for the purpose of a
dignified education for today's youth.
Are you ready?
No!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What the?
Yuka!
You show nice form!
Stop this!
Mayumi, stay back!
Yuka!
You're the Sexy Kamen, aren't you?
No, I'm not!
Now stop acting like a total ass and
leave this campus immediately!
Sorry, I can't do that.
Yuka!
Stay away!
You shall be next!
I can not forgive you, woman
who caught my sword!
Are you ready?
It's her!
It's Kekko Kamen!
Where are you, Pervert Kamen?
Nobody knows my face, but
everybody knows my body.
I am the messenger of Justice, sent by
God to this school of perversion!
My name is Kekko.
Kekko Kamen!
You're here!
Mayumi, Chigusa, everything will
be okay now that I'm here!
All right, you jerk in the employ of
perverts, are you ready for me?
What a fashion statement!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Of course I am.
However, this is for Love and Justice.
Punishment Teacher, what do
you call yourself?
Name? What is my name?
I am the Puddle Strong Man,
Mizutamari Tsuyokarou!
Okay! Punishment Teacher
Puddle Strong Man!
You've strayed from the path of Bushido,
and you cut little girls' clothes
off besides, you jerk!
Even if God himself does, Kekko Kamen
will not forgive you!
Let's do it!
I'd love to.
Hey, Teacher Ben!
Yes sir!
We just made it! She hasn't done
the jump attack yet!
Yes sir, thank God!
Come on, Sexy Kamen!
Secret Technique Open Thigh Jump!
Oh, nice!
It's so bright.
Censored!
Censored
Open Thigh Jump Defense!
What?
No! I can't see it, you idiot!
How's that?!
Kekko Kamen!
Oh no! I never expected a defense
to that maneuver. I've lost!
Stop!
Oh no.
What shall we do?
Help me!
Principal?
What, Teacher Ben?
I'm bored of always punishing
Mayumi Takahashi.
Why don't we change subjects today
and peel Chigusa Yuka this time?!
Oh, that might be a good idea!
What a pervert!
Please stop it! Don't do anything
perverted to Chigusa!
Shut up, you worst-student-
in-all-of-history you!
Listen up. We do not have time to
bother with such little things.
That Kamen is already close by,
with her great big breasts!
There she is!
Puddle Strong Man, you social
anachronism, listen to me!
Gluing umbrellas is a part
of the way of Bushido,
but you've used that umbrella
for evil purposes!
You used it to defend against
my secret technique.
Now, your Bushido is worthless!
Prepare to feel the wrath of heaven,
Kekko Kamen!
Are you ready?
There you are, Big-Breasted Heifer!
I was a little careless last time!
However, I won't lose this time!
I can't lose in the name of Love and Justice!
Let's go!
Come on! You're destroying this school's
moral fiber, you big-breasted female!
Who's destroying whose
moral fiber, you twit?
Hey, hey. You can't use the
Open Thigh Jump.
So, what are you going to do?
You are finished now.
I can only cut your body since you
don't have any clothes on!
Here I go!
No, don't!
Do you have to do that?
Hey, don't kill her!
If you kill her, we'll never get
to see her jump again!
Shut up!
This is a blow for pure and
righteous education!
How about this?
What the?
Secret technique: Tornado Attack!
Oh crap!
What the?
Open Thigh Jump!
Censored!
Censored
I'm sorry!
Mommy!
Tomorrow's classes will all be self-study!
Don't slow down!
Mayumi, are you okay?
Yes ma'am.
Are you both all right?
Thank you, Kekko Kamen.
Oh, Kekko Kamen, your left arm!
It's no big deal. I'm fine.
I enjoyed today's fight because I
was able to use my best trick.
I'm embarrassed, though. I wonder
whether I should wear panties?
No! I've no choice but to be naked for
the cause of Love and Justice.
I'll be seeing you!
Kekko Kamen, thank you.
Thank you, Kekko Kamen.
So long, Kekko Kamen.
Good-bye!
The crisis at the school is over for now.
However, if the sales of this video are
really good, she will return!
For now, good-bye, Kekko Kamen.
Thank you, Kekko Kamen.
What a nice set of buns,
set of buns, of buns
That's our Kekko, Kekko Kamen
Kekko Kamen
By the name of God
So high up above
In the highest heights
She's the one who in the name of
Love takes off her clothes and
Always fights
That Open Thigh
Jump Technique
Is just too extreme
Her Great Big Pair
Of Huge Knockers
Are suffocating
In a heart beat
Wink of an eye
Fly up to the sky
A hot flash
Like the light of truth
Except it's shocking pink
So let's show off the naked truth of her beauty
She's the heroine who shows
everything, Kekko Kamen
Kekko Kamen
That Open Thigh
Jump Technique
Is just too extreme
Her Great Big Pair
Of Huge Knockers
Are suffocating
In a heart beat
Wink of an eye
Fly up to the sky
A hot flash
Like the light of truth
Except it's shocking pink
So let's show off the naked truth of her beauty
She's the heroine who shows
everything, Kekko Kamen
Kekko Kamen