Kekko Kamen
Volume 1
The Toenail of Satan's
Spartan Institute of
Higher Education
Hey, hey! Do your best!
This Midnight Concentration Camp is
the most effective way to learn to
handle school pressures!
That's an advantage you get in an
educational institute like this!
The time limit is sixty minutes!
You must solve one question a minute!
Hey, hurry, hurry!
You're all a bunch of worthless, lowly slugs,
and the student with the lowest score
is going to spend some quality time
in the punishment center!
Hey, hey, do your work!
Welcome to the Spartan Institute.
I am your principal, known to all
as the Big Toenail of Satan.
Ms. Gestapoko, I have heard much about your
performance at the Auschwitz Academy.
As I'm sure you're aware, the Spartan
Institute's policy is...
To go beyond the standards and disciplines
of so-called progressive schools
and to train an elite order
of malleable minds.
These objectives have our highest priority.
Anything's justified if it serves those goals.
Correct. I don't accept that students
have "human rights."
Short of killing them, your students are
yours to do with as you please.
I love it. I love anything thorough.
Before you start settling into your new post,
I would like to ask you to do one little thing.
We need a "Special Punishment" for the
student with the worst grade
in today's special class, the one who
most disgraces our school...
That shall be your first assignment
as Punishment Teacher.
You make me happy right away.
Hey, hey! Thirteen minutes left!
Urge yourself onward! Urge!
Oh no! I mustn't fall asleep...
Hey, hey! I'll hit you if you're dull!
No! I mustn't sleep, not now!
No, it didn't help...
Takahashi!
You dare fall asleep in my class?!
I'm sorry! It was just for a second!
Please forgive me!
I will never forgive you!
It's proof you're a slacker!
I don't even need to grade you now!
You're going to receive the full
"Special Punishment!"
No!
Episode 1
Here I Am: The Messenger of Love and Justice!
"Here I Am: The Messenger
of Love and Justice!"
Episode 1
Here I Am: The Messenger of Love and Justice!
Special Punishment Room
Teacher Ben, this is Ms. Gestapoko,
our new Punishment Teacher.
Well, well!
What, not this student again?
The former Punishment Teacher
was overindulgent.
She had no guts at all!
I see.
What do you want me to do?
This student is dull and listless.
Please sharpen her up and
bring her up to speed!
Speed up her reflexes? Roger.
No!
No whiners allowed!
Ms. Gestapoko, please be kind
enough to teach her this!
Let's go!
Escape from my whip if you don't like pain!
This special training ought to
improve your speed!
Let's go!
I said try to escape.
Or do you enjoy this sort of thing?
Help me!
You're too slow! Go faster!
The path to becoming elite is no picnic!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
If that was good enough, there'd be no
work for the Punishment Teacher!
Let's go!
I'm so happy. Go further! Go faster!
Here!
And next... There!
Let's go!
Oh boy!
Are you happy, Teacher Ben?
Oh yes! I'll follow you all my life!
Please forgive me! Don't rip off my panties!
No! Ms. Gestapoko, go for it!
Are you ready?
The last one.
All right!
What?
A power failure?
Who's that?
Who the hell are you?
What is that?
Go and get her!
Yes!
What is it?
Here comes the
great hero!
Wow!
Very interesting...
There's something different about this school.
Who... Who are you?
That punishment last night...
Was it all a dream?
It wasn't a dream.
Ms. Takahashi?
You're Mayumi Takahashi, Grade 1, Class 1?
Yes.
Uh...
The teachers in this school are the worst.
However, don't let them get you down.
Got that, Ms. Takahashi?
Uh... Sure.
Excuse me, but may I have your name?
Names aren't important.
Just know I'm your upperclassmate,
and I'm on your side.
Bye.
But...
She might be the...
I see... Isn't this interesting?
Teachers' Lounge
Just let me touch a little bit.
Principal!
What the? This is my break!
Can't we talk about business later?
Oh, please don't say that!
I've found out whose panties these were!
Huh? What?
Take a look at this.
Wow... This is...
She's an honors student with the
top grade point average,
Chigusa Yuka, Grade 2, Class 2.
You have evidence those
panties belong to her?
I, Teacher Ben, know the smell of all the
different panties of all the girls in this school!
I'm impressed.
So, Principal, I have an idea
to discuss with you.
Yeah... Yeah... Ummm...
I see. Teacher Ben, you are pretty perverted.
What're you talking about?
Principal, you're the most perverted of all!
Yeah, yeah! That's the truth!
To the student body of this Spartan Institute...
Last night, one of you betrayed this
school's sacred policy.
This criminal committed the heinous act
of obstructing the punishment
which is our school's most honored tradition!
I now ask the guilty student who
did it to come forward.
All right then, I'll try something else.
Mayumi Takahashi, Grade 1,
Class 1, come on down!
What? Why?
No! Let me go!
Here we go!
In front of everybody...
How humiliating!
If the student I met last night does
not come forward immediately,
then the lovely Ms. Takahashi here
will be shamed even further.
Well? No? Not coming out?
That's it, then. Go to it, Ms. Gestapoko!
All right!
I'm on fire!
The woman from last night better come out!
Don't treat this situation lightly!
Come forward quickly!
Hey!
Mother...
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
Oh, what shall I do?
What? Are you so full of fear
that you can't fight me?
Wait a second, wait a moment, Ms. Gestapoko.
What?
I want to add my own touch
to this punishment.
There we go!
Oh ho, I see.
No!
There!
Come out if you still want to call
yourself a "Great Hero!"
Around and around!
Round and round and round she goes!
Everybody will see everything if I keep turning.
Now nobody will ever want to marry me.
Go!
What are you thinking of out there?
This is the last one...
It's you...
Stop it! This is just too much!
So, you've finally shown up.
You kept us waiting quite a while.
Wrong! I just couldn't stand to see
Ms. Takahashi abused any longer!
So, Chigusa Yuka, you finally
show your true colors!
Principal, I don't know anything about this!
You don't know when to give up, do you?
Your panties are all the evidence we need!
Those are...
I do love a farce, but the time
has come to finish this!
I'll make you dance, you insolent bitch!
Peel her down!
Hold it right there!
What the?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Nobody knows my face, but
everybody knows my body.
God has sent me to bring justice
to this school from Hell!
My name is Kekko...
Kekko Kamen!
I hide my face but expose all else!
Ben, I am very satisfied!
Oh yes, Principal!
Corrupt teachers exposing a helpless
maiden in public...
Abusing your students to further
your own dirty ambitions!
Even if the Board of Education does,
Kekko Kamen will never forgive you!
You're...
Mayumi, now that I'm here, you've got
nothing else to worry about.
Don't make me laugh!
Go, bodyguards!
Nice shot!
Principal Toenail of Satan.
Have a peek at my secret technique!
Open...
Jump!
Next technique: Muff-o-cation Wring!
What shall I do?
Kekko Kamen, that was great!
Thank you very much.
Me, me, me, me too...
What're you waiting for?
What, what, what? Why, why, why?
Gestapoko, I can't forgive you, even
though we're both women!
You're pretty good, but I'm not
knocked over by your presence
like some stupid men I could mention.
You talk too much! Come on!
Can you escape the taste of my whip? There!
I read something once...
Got it! An S & M queen is...
Hey, hey, hey!
The S & M queen is...
The queen secretly wishes to be beaten!
Hey, hey, hey! Do you feel good?
How was that? Who's the queen now?
Good!
Here! I'll give you the coup de grace!
Feeling good!
Students of Spartan Institute!
Kekko Kamen will be anywhere, anytime,
where evil exposes itself.
Gee, I guess I'm just a little self-conscious!
Good-bye, everybody! See you again!
Kekko Kamen! She's so gorgeous!
The Principal and Teacher Ben were
excited about a pair of panties
that were stolen from my room
three days ago.
Why did Kekko Kamen have them,
and what is her secret identity?
Please watch the next episode
if you want to know about it.
Promise me!
Kekko Kamen.
Umm, thanks...
Uh... Ah... What?
I can't move.
What? You want me?
I'm so glad!
You stupid imbecile!
I'm here to punish you!
Oh...
I'll punish you in the worst way
a man can ever be punished.
What?!
Oh, it's still there! I'm so relieved!
Shit! Now she's even in my dreams!
I will fight her though, I will fight!
Come and get me, Kekko Kamen!
Episode 2
Crash! Kekko Kamen
vs Muscular Monster
Episode 2
Crash! Kekko Kamen
vs Muscular Monster
"Crash! Kekko Kamen vs Muscular Monster!"
Episode 2
Crash! Kekko Kamen
vs Muscular Monster
Grade 2, Class 2
For today's lesson, I'm going to explain the
differences between men and women's bodies.
The thing that separates human gender between
male and female are the reproductive organs.
Hi there! I'm Yuka Chigusa, and
I was in the last episode too!
Ever since Kekko Kamen first appeared,
the Principal's been mighty tense.
You know how one little doubt can cause
a lot of other doubts, right?
What do you suppose will happen next here at
the shockingly violent Spartan Institute?
I'm a little excited myself!
Wow! Look at him!
He's so cute!
He's very gorgeous!
Hi, everybody! I just joined the school today.
Shuwarutsu
Negataro
My name is Shuwarutsu Negataro.
I'm your new physical education teacher!
Now, let's go running under this
beautiful, lovely sky!
Yes sir!
One, two!
Oh, what a nice teacher he is!
Mayumi is so happy!
Wait 'til you get an eyeful
of that, Kekko Kamen!
He's got a great body, sure, but he's gay!
Teacher Ben, you're too quick
to see the obvious.
The only things that're important
are his big muscles.
Say what?
Didn't you know that beautiful
women with great big tits
always have a thing for
really muscular men?
Is that true?
A demon never lies.
Principal, please let me leave the
Institute for just a bit!
This will finish off that Big-Knockers
Kamen once and for all!
In 1853, Admiral Perry of the American Navy
appeared just offshore of Uraga, Japan.
Because of this, the Tokugawa Shogunate was
urged to open the country to foreign intercourse.
Teacher Shuwarutsu...
She's strong...
Hi!
Teacher Shuwarutsu... He smiled at me!
Ah, I'm so happy!
I can't take it...
Nurse's Office
Teacher Shuwarutsu!
Hi, Mayumi. How are you feeling?
Here you go.
You know my name...
You already remember me, Teacher!
I can tell the name of a beautiful
student just by seeing her face.
It's a gift.
Please don't say I'm beautiful.
You should have confidence in
the fact that you are beautiful.
Your smile is almost as beautiful as
my bulging, bronze biceps.
See?
You're so gorgeous!
So are you.
Look at my chest muscles.
They're shaking because of your beauty.
And now, the teacher shall make
you more beautiful yet.
Teacher, what is this?
To improve your muscles, we must
first massage your whole body.
Made it just in time!
Mr. Shuwarutsu, I expressly told you
to wait for me! You're mean!
I'm so sorry, Principal.
Well, let's begin.
What? Stop!
Ms. Mayumi, the world is seldom
as simple as it seems.
I pretend to be the new gym teacher,
but in truth,
I'm the new Punishment Teacher,
Shuwarutsu Negataro!
Now, I shall massage your
muscles, Ms. Mayumi!
Let me go! Mayumi doesn't... No...
I can't believe this!
I'm so happy, Mr. Shuwarutsu!
Thank you. It's my pleasure.
The elite student should have a beautiful body.
You said if I punish this student,
SHE would appear. Are you sure?
Oh, that's right! I forgot the real
purpose for all of this!
Come here, Kekko Kamen!
Mayumi Takahashi is being punished now!
Come on, Kekko Kamen!
Mayumi Takahashi is now being teased!
Shut up already! I'm here!
But...
But there was no theme song!
I usually omit the theme when
there's no audience.
Punishment Teacher Shuwarutsu
Negataro, are you ready?
Now you're trapped, Knockers Kamen!
Wrong! That's Kekko Kamen!
Take a look at this.
Go, Mr. Shuwarutsu! Beat the shit
out of that great-looking broad!
So, the lady with the big tits has a
weakness for my muscular beauty, eh?
You're dizzy and unable to fight, aren't you?
Hey, hey, hey!
Too beautiful.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
Here goes MY special fighting technique.
How about this?!
How about that? What do you think of
this beautiful trained body?
It's great!
Heh, heh, "It's great..." Really...
Kekko Kamen, please don't fail!
Mayumi...
Biceps!
Don't you think this is beautiful?
Too beautiful!
Back muscles!
What do you think of my trained muscles?
Like a statue of a naked god?
And how about this...
Deltoids!
Triceps!
Lots of lats!
I can't resist! I'll come soon!
My lady is...
We won! We won against her!
Principal, our battle has just begun.
Please stand ready.
Right!
I can't win.
How can I handle muscles like that?
There is a way.
You're...
Please, protect that girl.
You can do it, Kekko Kamen.
But I don't know a way to go
against that much muscle.
There is a way.
The only way to win against that ridiculous
muscle monster, Shuwarutsu Negataro...
Is...
This.
That's...
I call it "The Ribbon of Love and Justice."
Special Punishment Room
Well, let's train your muscles as
an early morning refresher.
Calling all students!
Wake up!
Somebody, help me, please!
Now we shall train your body with some
aerobic suspension, Ms. Mayumi!
Help!
No!
Hey, Kekko Kamen!
You're out there watching a
monitor somewhere!
Come out!
My lady! Ouch!
What's the matter? Can't come
because of a little muscle? Eh?
Nobody knows my face, but
everybody knows this body.
I don't mind showing my body in
the name of Love and Peace.
My name is Kekko...
Kekko Kamen!
I'm hiding my face but
baring everything else!
It's Kekko Kamen! All right!
Way to go!
Ta dah!
My lady!
You came, Kekko Kamen.
Here I am, Toenail of Satan!
Come on and fight, Ligament-Taro!
That's Shuwarutsu Negataro!
That so?
Do you think you can protect yourself
from my splendid attack?
You stay here.
I'll get revenge for you.
My lady, hold out!
Come on, you crazy, overbuilt,
perverted narcissist.
Shut up, you bare-bottomed floozy!
Let's go!
Front Chest Muscled Meat Ball Attack!
Hold on, my lady!
You move very quickly!
You trifled with this girl's heart, you bastard,
doing evil with that beautiful weapon!
I, Kekko Kamen, will punish you in the
name of Love and Justice!
Are you ready?
What?
What's that?
A new trick!
It's called "Just a Blindfold, Stupid!"
That's it?
That's a stupid name!
My lady, it's great!
Do you...
Do you really think you can find
me with a blindfold on?
She can't see where her opponent is!
How?
How could you tell where I was?
I gave no indication...
Every time you move, your big fat
muscles make a squeaking sound!
I've known where you were
from the very beginning!
Here! Finishing Open Legs Jump!
Oh! Good!
I came, I lost.
Wait up!
Yes ma'am!
Are you going to ban the ridiculous
punishments at this school?
Answer me!
Good.
Principal!
I've trained my muscles!
Now I can do anything to that
big-breasted babe too!
What'cha think?
Principal? Principal!
Get a grip on yourself!
The Toenail of Satan says he'll cease the
punishments, but we can't trust his word.
He may start again, but I'll be there.
My lady!
Who are you?
I'm...
I'm a little embarrassed!
I'm the envoy of Love and Justice. That's all.
Farewell!
My lady!
She's much more gorgeous than Shuwarutsu.
Kekko Kamen...
The crisis is over, for now.
We still don't know who Kekko Kamen is,
but if you really want to know who she is,
please sing along with the theme song.
I'll be seeing you!
No one has ever solved the mystery
of her unknown face
On the other hand, everyone's seen
her completely nude!
Kekko Kamen, that lady is
A hero to all, and she's also not a prude!
She comes in like a roar of
thunder with a crash
And she won't leave until we've
all seen her flash!
Kekko Kamen, just who the heck are you?
Kekko Kamen, who you are we want to know!
No one has ever solved the mystery
of her unknown face
But everybody knows all about
her physical attitude!
Kekko Kamen, that lady is
A hero to all, and she's also not a prude!
She attacks with a yell and
by spreading out her legs
Then she cold-cocks evildoers by
socking them in the eggs!
Kekko Kamen, just who the heck are you?
Kekko Kamen, who you are we want to know!
No one has ever solved the mystery
of her unknown face
But everyone here knows the
sight of her nipples, dude!
Kekko Kamen, that lady is
A hero to all, and she's also not a prude!
She uses her nunchaku and a six-foot stick
Are you ready Satan's Toenail,
you lousy little prick?
Kekko Kamen, just who the heck are you?
Kekko Kamen, who you are we want to know!