- Do you see anything?
- No, nothing.
Come on, move it!
Don't cross the tape!
The cops are here.
I heard it was a little girl.
Who's that?
Did you see what happened?
Stop! No admission.
Excuse me!
She's still a kid.
Lieutenant, there's a girl over there.
Kenzo! Time for work!
All right.
Look at me.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Kekkai
Report 1: Nature Clinical Interrogation
General Hospital
I have her sleeping on analgesics.
But she's in an abnormal state.
Abnormal?
Yes. She is very disoriented,
and there are signs of amnesia.
If you can, it's probably best...
to have a professional psychiatrist
have a look at her.
A professional psychiatrist?
I found this in her pocket.
Kyoko.
Doctor, it feels so good.
Damn it.
You sure took awhile. Sleeping in?
Wish I was you.
It's you, Kaoru. I'm busy right now.
Busy? Today's your day off, isn't it?
I'll be over there soon.
I'm about to leave. I'll talk to you later.
Liar. I know you.
Sorry, but today's examination is over.
What? Come on, Doctor!
No!
Doctor, so you are in.
"I don't want any trouble"
is written all over your face.
I don't see how you work as a clinical
psychologist with that attitude.
There's half-naked
police officers, so why not?
You know, that's a pretty flashy car
you have out there...
and you're still having a guy
drive you around town in it?
That has nothing to do with this!
I came here on business!
I got it! I'll listen to what you have to say...
but do something about that car
parked out front.
It doesn't help business at all!
I'll make sure you listen to every last word.
It's me. I have a favor to ask.
It's going to take a little while.
Drive around the block a couple of times.
Yes, that's right. Could you do that?
I'll call you later.
Now, then.
Look at these.
No identification,
cause of death is due...
to loss of blood,
and the object of the crime was...
Rape?
Right. Currently the leftover semen
found inside of her is at the lab.
The problem is the girl we took
under protection at the scene.
What I want to ask of you is to treat her.
I see.
This is the background report.
You should definitely read it first.
I don't feel like it, you read it.
It'll take a while, you know.
Thanks to you, I have plenty of time.
Okay.
Do you always cross your legs
like that when talking to someone?
Well, most of the time. Why?
When you move around like that,
I can see your panties.
You were looking?
I see that you're still into pink.
Does it make you horny?
Hey, wait!
This is too sudden.
I'm horny, just as you said.
- Wait!
- You asked for it.
But, I have work.
Don't stop, please!
Now for work. Tell me all about it.
Where was I now?
Did you find out the identity
of the girl under protection?
Currently she is still unidentified.
The only lead is a picture.
This is it.
Looks like Kyoko.
Probably the girl's name.
Can't say for sure, though.
So, is that girl also a victim?
I don't know. Maybe she's a victim,
maybe she's an assailant.
At the very least
there were no signs of rape.
Plus, there's something that bugs me.
There's scars all over her back
and her chest.
Most seem to be childhood scars.
There's also a tattoo on her right shoulder.
A tattoo of a rose.
Childhood scars?
You mean, from child abuse?
I don't know. Haven't got a clue.
That's why I've come here for your help.
If she's a witness, then she may be
the key to solving this case.
This will be a tough one.
General Hospital
I never did like this hospital.
It's like any other hospital.
No it's not. This place is heavily secured.
Of course it is. The culprit may be after her.
How's she doing?
She's been asleep the whole time.
The pain-killers should
have worn off by now.
I see. Could you leave the room?
Okay.
It's too bright in here.
Wait, Junichi.
She doesn't like the dark.
She's afraid of it.
Thank you.
Good afternoon, Kyoko.
Glad to see you're awake.
You're Kyoko, aren't you?
I'm Junichi. I'm a doctor, you know.
Kyoko, we're on your side.
We want to help you. Believe in us.
Hey, can you hear anything?
Hey, Kaoru!
What did you see there?
You saw something!
What did you see? Tell me!
Kaoru, stop that!
No!
What's wrong? Calm down.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's okay, there's nothing to be afraid of.
Kyoko?
That's not your name?
Kyoko's gone, she went over there.
Who are you?
Sachi.
Sachi?
Yes.
Sachi, how old are you?
I'm nineteen.
I see. So where did Kyoko go?
I don't know.
I'm becoming really sleepy.
That's okay.
There's nothing to fear,
so you can rest easy.
What was that?
That wasn't acting, right?
Is that what they call multiple personality?
Disassociative disorder.
That's the official name.
Do you think she contacted that
because of me?
No, it didn't seem like
this was the first time.
Sachi was there before that.
And don't say or do anything rash
during our sessions.
I'm sorry about that.
So, what do we do now?
It's possible to cure her.
But I can't do it here.
Don't tell me you need to move
her to your place.
It's better than here.
Hold it! There's no way
I'd get permission to do such a thing.
In a stuffy place like this,
her sickness will only get worse.
But still.
You want clues, don't you?
If I treat her at my clinic,
I may be able to get something out of her.
I understand.
I'll try and convince them
to move our out of here.
I'll do it as soon as possible.
Quick to take the offensive as usual.
Don't joke around.
You better make sure you cure her.
I'm a professional. I'll do my best.
I'll take your word for it.
What's wrong?
You can't sleep?
I'm not Sachi, for your information.
I'm Ryo.
Ryo?
That's correct.
And so have you been there all along?
Yes, I've been here since long ago.
Then you already know who I am, right?
Yes, I have already heard about you.
So why do you decided to come out?
Because Sachi was sleeping.
Do you have anything to tell me?
Yes.
Sit down over there.
Kyoko is asking me for my help.
You said that you're Kyoko's
friend, didn't you?
Yeah, that's what I said.
Please protect Kyoko.
Protect?
Kyoko is being targeted.
Targeted? By whom?
I beg of you, protect Kyoko.
Wait a second, Ryo.
What's that supposed to...
Ryo?
Is that you?
Pee-pee.
I go pee-pee.
It's you, Sachi. Come here, it's this way.
Okay!
Good night.
No! Stay here.
Okay. I'll stay here,
you can sleep tight.
You promise? Goodnight.
Good morning.
You're Kyoko, right?
I want to have a little chat with you, okay?
Kyoko, there's no need
for you to be nervous.
Look.
Quiet, isn't it?
The ticking of the clock, your breathing.
What else do you hear?
You can hear something else?
What sound do you hear?
What is it?
Footsteps.
Footsteps?
Those are your footsteps, aren't they?
Where are you trying to walk, Kyoko?
It's very dark.
Somewhere dark?
You're going someplace dark?
A dark street.
Are you walking by yourself?
A dark street between buildings.
Then let's find a brighter place.
Look for the light.
Look for light.
Dark, dark, it's so dark!
Kyoko! Open your eyes!
Wake up, Kyoko.
I'm sorry about that, Kyoko.
For putting too much strain on you.
Who are you?
Kyoko.
No, you're not.
Maybe I'm Ryo.
You're neither Kyoko nor Ryo.
Who in the world are you?
Tell me.
Yoko.
Yoko, is it?
Can we have a little conversation?
I've something I want to ask you.
What's that?
Hey...
Have you been having sex lately?
Listen, here...
Why don't you tell me
how long you've been inside Kyoko?
If you listen to me, I'll tell you.
Fine, then. Go ahead.
Look.
See, Doctor?
Put on your clothes.
Doctor.
You're Kyoko's friend, right?
Then save me, too.
What should I do?
Hold me. Protect me.
Doctor.
Doctor, fuck me!
Fuck me!
Hello, ICP Japan Office.
Yes, I understand.
What was that?
- She's dead.
- Who is?
The hospital.
Calm down!
What was that for?
The nurse at the hospital was killed.
What nurse?
The nurse that was in Kyoko's room.
Let's go then. Now!
It's the same.
You think it's the same culprit?
Probably.
But why was Kyoko's nurse
the target this time?