Kigurumi Sentai Kiltean
All right, let's begin.
High dimension scanner initiated.
Locked on to target coordinates.
Start scanning!
Polyester Private Academy...
So she's here, huh?
I've found you, Tenjikudo Aya-san.
Episode 1
Transform! Kilteans!?
Invaders in a peaceful school!
Episode 1
An evil team attacks the beautiful sisters!
Y-You got me!
Are you serious?
You only have a week until the tournament.
You need to try harder!
Okay, next!
All right, I'll go next.
Sarasa, it's about time to go to the next club.
Oh, is it? Hold on a sec!
Let's go!
Are they...
Huh? What's the matter, guys?
You should go a little easy on them.
Our motto here at Polyester Academy is,
"Encourage students to excel both academically and athletically."
All the clubs are training hard for the summer tournaments.
Yeah, I can tell.
Oh yeah, there's another club in need of your help.
What's the schedule like?
It looks a little tight.
I can tell.
Which club is it?
The basketball club.
Really? That means...
Yep. Captain Kaga-senpai wants to talk to you about it.
Oh, my God! I'm gonna go shower right now!
I've got to do this.
Please fit it into the schedule.
Okay.
She's going to the shower room like that, huh?
I'm sure she won't notice that until she's back here.
Rina?
Yes?
Isn't that Sarasa running half-naked down the hallway like an idiot?
Yup.
How embarrassing.
She's my older sister, even though she was born just thirty minutes before me.
Are you going to your club, Mayura?
Yup.
You'd better stop putting on airs, at least when you're wearing a white coat.
Girls should always be well-dressed and well-groomed.
Besides, a white coat is the uniform for people who love science and truth.
Right there.
Nice shot, Captain.
Kaga-senpai!
I've brought Sarasa!
Thank you for making time.
No problem at all.
The star shooter for the girls team is hurt.
So I was wondering if you could be her replacement.
I know all the clubs are busy working towards their tournaments,
but is there any way you can help me out?
Sure! I'll do my best, Senpai!
Thank you.
It's time for me to go to the Student Council meeting.
I know Tenjikudo Mayura as one of the members of the Book Committee.
She's my younger sister. We're twins.
Research Club for Chemical Experimentation
Club President: Tenjikudo Mayura
So what do you want?
Sorry for calling you in here.
If you're looking for more money to fund experiments or new drugs,
I can't help you there.
I'm just a science teacher.
I'm sad that you think I called you here for that.
T-Tenjikudo-kun...
Please call me Mayura.
Wh-What are you doing?
I've been in love with you for a long time.
You're beautiful, Mayura.
Wait.
Here. This is a special one that I made with jelly.
How is it special?
This condom will allow you to stay hard longer and feel more pleasure.
Let me put it on for you.
M-Mayura-kun, do you always do things like this?
I only do this for people I like.
Sensei... Sayama-sensei, please...
I need some more drugs for my experiments.
So could you help me on that?
Don't worry about it.
Really? You're so nice!
Please stay there like that.
Mama? Is everyone okay?
They're bruised all over.
It'll take ten to twenty days for them to recover.
How many people are you going to put in here before the tournament?
I wouldn't tell you to be just like Mayura,
but why don't you behave more like a girl?
I'm sure you have someone you like.
Don't you?
Perhaps one of these guys?
Of course not.
There's a huge difference between these guys and Kaga-senpai.
President of the Student Council
and Captain of the Basketball Club, Kaga Inari, huh?
Not bad.
I get that you like him,
but I don't understand why Mayura likes that kind of guy too.
Wait a second.
What do you mean?
Hey, did you see that?
What?
The pheromones from my body seem to be spreading in this room.
Everyone is injured, but they'll be fine.
I'm going to take a shower.
So as the leader of the Discipline Committee suggested,
in order to create good memories during this summer break, students should...
He excels at both sports and school work.
One of the top students in the history of Polyester Academy.
The invincible president of the Student Council.
In addition, he's got the looks.
Despite all that, he's not involved in a relationship with any particular girl.
He's not even affected by the powerful pheromone I inherited from my mother.
Senpai is so cool.
Please wait for me.
Mayura-kun?
I'm going to be a more attractive woman,
Library Club President, Tenjikudo Mayura-kun?
and in this campus...
Y-Yes! I will do my best, Senpai!
Th-Thank you...
Now excuse me, everyone. Something just came up.
Let's discuss the other agenda items next time.
See you.
Aya-san...
I don't care that you're married or the mother of my schoolmates.
I... I...
I feel like I'm being watched.
What? What happened?
I was almost there.
What's wrong?
Kyomoto-sama, fixation of the portal from different space has been completed.
Okay.
The Toidora Fortress now floats into normal space.
It's coming from outside!
Shit! It's not opening.
I'm afraid of dark, cramped spaces!
There's no time for this.
I'll fix the monitor first so I can finish what I started.
What's that?
Sarasa?
It stopped.
At last, it's time for Toidora to take its first steps towards world conquest.
Ribbon Dora.
Yes.
Doll Dora.
What is this?
It's kinda amazing, isn't it?
It's a nice day today.
Let me start over.
It's sunny today.
No, I mean...
What did he say?
It must be some kind of public relations stunt.
They would do so much for that?
What else could it be?
You think they're an evil cabal that has a scheme to take over the world?
That's right!
You see, ladies...
We will use perfect science to lead humans towards the new century.
And to do that,
we'll give some tough-love lessons to the people who play with scientific technologies.
That's the reason we are here.
Now it should...
Damn! Aya-san has left already.
What?
Remember that in the past, we used to have clear blue skies.
We longed for the vast universe
and believed in the infinite possibilities of scientific technology.
[Environmental destruction, over-population, north-south issues, economic disparity...]
[The problems we have on this planet this century are...]
They got heatstroke?
Well, they're just part-time workers after all.
[The problems we have on this planet this century are...]
This is what he gets for being cheap.
Now it is time for us to rise and...
Kyomoto-sama!
Have you forgotten why we're here?
Dr. Tenjikudo is here at this academy.
— Yes, the reason why we are here is...
— I get it already.
You guys are too noisy.
There you are, Aya-san.
You look even more beautiful than the last time I saw you.
Anyway, we...
"We want you to work with us," huh?
Exactly, Aya-san.
You've been babbling about this for a long time.
Don't tell me you think you can conquer the world?
With you ugly androids, useless soldiers,
insanely big aircraft, and infantile technology...
No, if you think that's still possible, I'll just laugh.
You've...
You've said enough!
Rise, tin soldiers!
Get that woman at any cost!
Very well.
If you defeat me in this battle, I'll be yours.
Battle?
That's right.
I thought something like this might happen,
so I created these power suits, the Kilteans, with my husband.
Hey, Mom?
What are you doing up there?
Who are those people?
Well, well, so you are Tenjikudo Sarasa-san and Mayura-san.
I'm Kyomoto Yuzan.
I've known your mother for a long time.
I got it!
Based on my experience, he's a faggot!
Oh, is he?
He isn't!
Like mother, like daughters!
Tin soldiers! Capture them all!
Now, girls, if you don't give it your best shot, Mommy will get taken away.
And if I were to help them conquer the world,
it would only take three years to do that, and Japan would only take a month.
Huh?
How can you be so proud of that?
All right, we'll do best.
Even if you say that...
So anyway, here you go!
What? Do we have to put this on?
Now, shout "Chakudatsu!"
What?
No idea.
What's taking you so long?
The suits will recognize your voices and activate.
Come on, together!
One, two... Chakudatsu!
Chakudatsu?
What the hell?
Young ones are good, too!
What's the meaning of this?
That's right. You can't escape me by using your daughters' naked bodies.
You guys be quiet!
And you can't start fighting until they're done changing, got it?
Sarasa, Mayura, you two are going to fight as Kilteans in those suits.
Hello? They've got zippers on the back.
Of course. That's how you get inside.
These powered suits will synchronize with your brain waves alone.
Otherwise, they'd just be ordinary full-body suits.
But why did we have to strip naked?
To establish a strong connection with the suits, it's best to be naked.
Now, get inside!
Go! Dress-up Battle Team Kiltean!
All right, I'll get in.
H-Hey, Sarasa!
With these, we're going to protect the freedom and peace of all humankind.
You too, Mayura!
What's this?
This is a power suit?
Amazing!
— Wh-What are those suits doing?
— Hold on, Kyomoto-sama.
They both hold enormous potential.
They may be formidable opponents.
What?
Go! Tin soldiers!
That was a bit mean of you.
What are you talking about?
It's your turn, Sarasa.
Okay, here I go!
Take this, you bad guys!
Now who's mean, huh?
That's my girl, Sarasa.
You can do it too, Mayura.
I can't stop!
Mayura!
Are they here to play around?
No, they just haven't figured out how to control their power.
It stopped, finally.
Yeah, sorry about that.
It's hard to control the power, isn't it?
Hey, don't touch me in strange places.
What's wrong, Mayura?
No. I said stop.
That's tickles!
Ouch.
Sorry, Mayura.
But it really tickled.
I see, Doll Dora.
Apparently we don't need to be afraid of Kilteans.
Kyomoto-sama...
I see. I got it.
Go!
Dora Monster #1, Daruma Dora!
Daruma!
Something strange showed up.
It'll be a piece of cake!
Daruma!
Or maybe not.
Who said it'd be easy?
Daruma!
Now!
I have you!
What?
Mayura!
I'll take care of you, little bunny.
Something is wrong.
Oh my, aren't you sensitive?
Their suits enhance the girls' five senses as well as their power.
That means the suits transfer stimulation from outside to the pilots quite well.
Mayura!
Let's see how sensitive the kitten is.
Tin soldiers, tickle her!
Daruma-san's Daruma Beam!
Isn't it time for you to throw in the towel?
If you don't stop now, your daughters are going to suffer from Gestaltzerfall.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Wh-What?
What's that?
I'm sorry.
What just happened?
It's unanalyzable.
However, I see that their power is becoming even stronger.
This is the hyper-mode of Kilteans.
I'm cumming!
What are you doing?
Daruma!
Bravo!
I want the suits along with the girls.
All right.
Giant Dora Robot #1!
Sewing Machine Dora!
No way! A giant robot?
Super cute!
futari de yokatta
[It's good to stay together]
ima kokoro kara tada arigatou
[Thank you, from my heart]
massara na kokoro hora yukkiri somatte yuku
[This pure heart colors little by little]
sweet heart kimi ga egaku yume
[Sweet heart, the dream you hold]
sweet kiss issho ni tsumugitai
[Sweet kiss, let's make it come true]
zutto konna shunkan machikogarete ita
[I've been waiting for this moment for a long time]
sekaijyuu ni hitotsu shinjitsu no ai navigation
[There is only one navigation to true love]
michibikarete iku yo unmei ga ugoki hajimete iru
[Lead me to the fate that's beginning to unfold]
hageshiku hikarete iku
[I'm greatly attracted to it]
shinjitsu no ai navigation
[The navigation to true love]
umare kawatte iku yo wasurete ita
[Changing from who I am now]
hontou no jibun e
[to the person I almost forgot]