I see it!
Open the gates! Open the gates!
You look suspicious, who are you?
Fools! Don't you remember my face?
What?
Come to think about it, I've been gone for 8 years.
I am the prince of Asteria, Distol El Asteria!
You mean the prince who is the hostage of Bastarauge?
I will explain the details to my father. Please tell him that
I am back, immediately.
Y, yes Sir!
Prince Distol is back.
Isn't he a hostage?
Why now?
Distol! Is it really you, Distol?
Father, I am back.
Yes, you are Distol. Glad you came back safely.
Dear King, this isn't something to be happy about.
We haven't heard anything from Bastarauge that the
hostages will be back.
What about the treaty? This is trouble.
That's right! Prince, did you come without permission?
You are still a coward, you haven't changed a bit in the
past 8 years.
But if the treaty is broken, our Asteria will be...
Bastarauge has already gathered an army to destroy our
nation.
What!?
That's not good!
We have to write a letter of apology immediately.
We don't have much riches to bribe them out.
We need a new hostage to give them.
No, you guys better not be handing me to them.
Dear King, however, that is the only option we have left to
save Asteria.
Father, we need to fight back!
I know about Bastarauge very well!
Please lend me an army and I will win!
Really?
Gather all the army and townsmen!
Hurry, or else, your heads will be chopped off!
As you wish, Prince.
Hurry and give the orders, our life is on the line!
This kingdom is pathetic... that's why Mother has died.
Slutty-Princess Diaries
Episode 2: Obedience Lesson
People of Asteria, I thank you for coming
I am the prince of Asterial, Distol!
Listen carefully. Bastarauge has broken our treaty and is
commencing attack on our land!
I have returned to bring you this news.
I promise this! If everyone stands up with me,
I will show Bastarauge our justice and we will win!
We have to protect our nation, our land, with
our own hands!
Lets listen to the prince!
Victory for Asteria!
I'm sorry people, but I have to save Qoona.
Continue in!
Follow the prince!
We've won!
The fight continued day after day, but there is one thing
that never left Distol's head.
That is, of course, about Princess Qoona.
She is imprisoned in this Tower of Ceremonies and taking
her beyond the magic field is near impossible.
Qoona...
Is it Eleanor?
Yes Master, what are you thinking?
It's nothing. We must attack another fortress tomorrow
morning.
I'll get some rest.
Sir Distol.
I'm just an ordinary merchant.
I was just here for business, please let me go and
I will give you this in return.
What is this?
It is called the Potion of Milk. You can even milk a virgin
with this potion.
This for me?
I would think that you have many reasons to use this.
Alright, I'll take it.
Get a pass from one of the guards and do as you wish.
Thank you very much.
You are always quick with what you do.
Eleanor? Show yourself.
Yes... Looks like you're tired.
Of course.
I've been doing things where an ordinary man can't
accomplish... or should I say I have to.
That proves that you are the chosen one to
have these powers.
And you're happy that I'm that one?
It is not my business, how you use the power is up to you.
It doesn't matter. I will do anything to save Qoona.
Such great words.
Today, I have received a wonderful gift.
My...
I'm thinking about using this on Elena.
That must be fun.
We'll see.
Di, how rude of you to enter without knocking.
You are not a guest.
It seems like you still don't understand your situation.
What are you here for?
I have something fun in store for today.
Something fun!?
Don't need to be uptight.
What is that?
Stop it!
What are you going to do...!!?
Looks like you're powerless to resist.
What did you make me drink?
Don't worry, you'll find out soon.
W, what?
What's wrong, Elena?
No, nothing...
What's wrong, does your chest hurt?
I told you nothing...
Looks like you're in pain.
No, don't touch me!
Sto...
Your chest are big, I can milk you like a cow.
Be quiet.
What? What is funny?
My chest...
What about your chest, Elena?
It hurts, feels like it's going to burst. It hurts.
It'll feel good soon.
Stop it!
Feeling it?
No, I am not...
Seems like you're liking it more than usual.
No, please don't...
What is this?
The fun is just starting!
What...?
What is this?
What are you talking about...
You're a female, don't you know?
And you don't even have a child.
That can't be, not from my chest...
You like it when I touch your chest and on top of that
you're squirting milk. What a slut!
This is... so it's that medicine... that's causing this.
Correct, let me give you a reward.
Have an orgasm while I squeeze your chest!
No, not like this!
No, I'm cumming.
Don't worry, I'll make you cum.
Cumming!!!
My chest...!
This is enough for today.
This is...
Accept me...
Accept me...!
What!?
I'll give you pleasures out of this world.
Let me say it again, accept me!
A dream...?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Where to?
There's something I want to check on. I'll be back.
Qoona...
Brother?
Sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.
I had a dream about you, Brother.
I can't leave you here alone forever.
But it's my duty as a Holy Maiden.
I will get you our of here as promised.
Yes, but that's impossible as long as the field is up.
You think so? I think I can break it.
Brother...
Qoona, lets try it. Get in my mantle.
Shit!
Brother...
Qoona, you hurt?
I am OK because you held on to me tightly.
So I can't... I'm sorry to do something dangerous.
No, Brother. I'm very happy for your kindness.
Don't worry, I will rescue you. I just have to do it as
planned.
Brother, I'm already happy enough by seeing you.
For now... but don't you get lonely, Qoona?
No, because you are always with me, but...
But?
But I want to be connected with you not only
mentally, but physically.
Qoona?
I know I'm a Holy Maiden, but I can't lie to my feelings.
Qoona, you know what you are saying by being
connected physically?
Yes, as a Holy Maiden, I wouldn't mind spending the rest
of my life in this tower...
But... But... I don't want to forget the touch of
my beloved Brother.
Qoona...
I'm sorry... I'm not a worthy Holy Maiden.
Qoona, you care about me so much...
You're the only one.
Qoona, are you sure?
Yes, but I don't know anything. Please teach me, Brother.
Brother, that's my...
Don't worry, relax.
Yes...
Brother, it feels strange. My heart is racing and my body
is warm...
Qoona, it means you feel it.
Feel it?
That's right, let me make it better.
Qoona, we're going to be a one.
Close your eyes, it'll be better.
OK...
Does it hurt? Want to stop?
Brother, please... not until the end.
Qoona, we are finally each others.
With my brother...
That's right, you and I are a one.
I'm so happy...
So happy.
Here I go.
So tight!
I'm scared!
Don't worry, I'm here.
Brother!!
I'll cum outside.
No, don't stop! Don't let go!
Qoona...
Brother, I don't want you to let go, so please.
You sure?
Only if it's you.
Your's inside me...
This is your...
It's proof that we are meant to be.
Brother...
Come! Once we get through this fortress, we'll be at
Bastarauge's fortress!!
Motivated by Distol's heroism, army of Asteria has
conquered many of Bastarauge's fortresses.
However, they are no where near in conquering
Bastarauge itself and their battle continues on.
Now, they are about to face a great foe, the elves.
It is rumored that there's a sorcerer in this village.
Once we get passed through this village, the castle will be
soon. Everyone, follow me!
Follow the prince!
For Asteria!
Charge!!!
Prince, help us!
What is going on!?
Be careful, these are elves. They are tough.
I see, that means I have to fight Yuno.
Do not worry, I'll take care of her.
You're saying that your magic powers are greater
than the elves?
Please wait a while, Master.
Why am I running away from humans?
I need some rest...
Why aren't the trees of the forest talking to me?
Is it because I can't concentrate?
The forest is crying?
My magic powers... they are draining.
What's this!?
Please stay put.
How was I not able to detect your magic? Who are you!?
You look cute, Yuno.
Did you think you could get away?
What are you going to do?
You are always so pushy. You are my hostage, I can do
what I want.
Then let go of me. I'll be your stupid hostage.
That's not how a hostage should talk, Yuno.
You think we should punish her, Eleanor?
As you wish, Master.
Punishment?
Although you're an elf, I'm sure you know what happens to
female hostages.
No, I won't let you!
Why!?
What were you trying to do?
This must be your doing.
Master, I'll see you later.
Magic powers greater than the elves...?
Shall we get started with the fun?
W, what!?
I heard elves are delicate.
You are my first elf.
S, stop!
Let go, don't touch me!
If you want me to stop, why not use your magic?
No, no!
Your nipples are hard, Yuno.
Does it feel good?
Shut up, you puny human...!
Stop, don't pinch!
No... I can't!!
What's this sweet smell?
So this is what an elf smells like when they are wet.
No, I can't... no...
Lets see how it feels.
No, don't touch me down there!
You are already so wet. Elves must be a horny race.
Don't say that!
I... I...
No matter what people refer to you as, a bitch is a bitch.
S, stop... please!!
Stop... this!?
No!!!!!!
No, it hurts!
So this is your first.
Great!
How do you like a humans penis, you elf!
Stop, please!
What's wrong? I thought humans are looked down upon?
It hurts... Please be gentle...
I'll make you feel good.
No, no...
You say no, but your clitoris says yes.
No, don't touch me right there...
You like it, don't you!?
A human is forcing himself, but why does it...?
How do you like a human man?
More... more.
It's warm... It's so amazing.
You slutty elf.
It's hitting me inside...
Does this feel good?
No, stop... not the ears...
You are cute, Yuno.
No... I'm going... crazy...
I... this... feels good...
It's tightening!
Right there, it feels good.
It's getting bigger inside!!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!!!
How is sex with a human? Did it feel good?
Now make me feel good... suck on this.
This...?
That's right, I want to know how an Elf
sucks a cock. C'mon.
Damn, you elves are good. Keep up the pace.
I'll touch you too.
It feels good...
Elves will even take it from behind, amazing.
Here I cum!
It was great, Yuno.
Looks like you had fun, Master.
Were you looking, Eleanor?
Of course not, I don't do such things.
It doesn't matter, but what to do with her?
Her powers will be a great use to us, Master.
Alright, lock her up in the cell then.
Master, as you wish...
Maybe it's because I had intercourse with an elf, but my
body craves for more lust.
Distol, are you here to embarrass me more?
No matter how many times you violate me, I will
not give up!
No matter how many times you try, you can not
corrupt my soul!
What are you doing?
I said, what are you doing, Distol!?
You sure talk a lot, Elena.
What did you say?
Well, this isn't your first. When I have sex with you...
scream like a dog.
Talking so much, you must be thirsty.
What is that? What are you going to do?
Don't worry, it's not poisonous. Although it does have
some side-effects.
Stop. Distol, please stop.
I though you said you don't care.
I didn't say such...!
Lets see how long you can resist.
Stop, Distol!
You won't be saying that soon.
W, what!?
You think you can make me your slave with a drug?
What is this, Elena?
Stop, don't bite like...!!!
Oh, what is this?
This is strange, my body is becoming warm...
How is it down here?
Stop it. I am...
Amazing, you are soaking wet.
Why... this isn't like me...
You want this right, Elena?
Fool... I don't want such a...
If this continues, I...!
I'll give it to you, Elena!
No. Stop...
I only inserted but you already came, however, the fun is
just starting, Elena!
Please... don't... move...
You are getting more wet.
You see...
It feels too...
Again... cumming.!!
You came twice in a row, what a slutty little princess.
If this continues, I'll lose my mind!
But of course. That's what I want.
Take all of this!
That's right, fall into the abyss of pleasure.
My wish will be granted then!
I will have both Bastarauge and you!