Kininaru Feeling, Sheltered Wife
Thank you.
Why hasn't anyone noticed?
Oh man, we're completely trapped in here.
Pardon me for asking,
but where is your husband?
He's left on an important business trip to Osaka.
Oh, I see.
You know, we just might be stuck in here
until the landlord comes in the morning.
This must be punishment for secretly
throwing out the trash this late at night.
No, I must be the one being punished.
Huh?
The truth is...
Everytime I look at you...
I keep imagining you naked.
What?
When I look at your cleavage,
I imagine the largeness of your breasts.
When my eyes come across your nipples,
I imagine their shape and color.
I follow the seams and wrinkles on yourjeans to
imagine what you're like down there.
What do you mean down there?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, let's see.
I think about how the hair grows,
and if it's the shape of a flower
I bet since you're a married women,
it must be all hanging out, loosely
And if I enter, it wouldn't be too tight, or too loose.
Instead, it would wrap around me,
like a skilled married women.
That, that's what I imagine.
So, wait a sec.
Let me get this straight...
You've already entered inside of me?
You're very very imaginative.
Yes, when I focus my eyes like this,
I can see you completely naked.
I know this sounds strange, but since I'm being punished, I might
as well just rip off my pants and take you in this elevator now
No, no wait...
You can't do that, you can't do that...
Aww come on, don't you get it?
If no one has even come to rescue us by now
then that means that noone is watching us.
You know what I mean?
So tell me, wouldn't you like to try handling a penis
other than your husbands?
Come on, don't be shy
What?
No, no, stop...
No...
So, this is it.
Smells good.
It's just as I imagined it would be in my mind.
You get wet pretty quickly
I could enter now.
What do you say? Are you ready
to have a cock inside of you, huh?
No, you can't. No...
Excuse me...
Oh no. Please, wait...
I'm going inside.
No, don't do that!
Let's just moisten this up a bit.
Oh yeah...
See? How is that?
Doesn't it feel good
with a different penis once in a while?
Yes, yes, it feels good, good...
Let me take a look at your breasts.
Come on.
They're big as I have imagined.
The color of your nipples are all so tantalizing.
Your husband is a lucky man
to be able to do such a sexy person every night!
It's too deep, it's too deep, god!
If you liked it from behind,
why didn't you just say so earlier?
You're like a dog.
A female dog in prime heat!
No, no...
Then how about this?
Oh, that's nice.
Amazing hip work.
Wow, yeah...
Gonna cum...
You always get on top of your husband, huh?
Gonna cum, gonna cum...
You wanna finish like this?
Oh, I want the bottom, I want the bottom...
Oh, I see.
Give me the bottom.
What a spoiled little wife!
Do you do it like this all the time?
On a stranded, on a elevator with a stranger?
No, no, no...
Amazing, you're amazing.
Can't hold it!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, cumming!
Me too!
Can I let it out inside of you?
Can I?
Oh yeah, do whatever, whatever you want!
The elevator started moving.