Chief Kusaki got promoted?
Why all of a sudden?
I heard he succeeded in finalizing the
contract with Sugimoto pharmaceuticals.
Maybe he's a successful
business person after all.
With that ugly face?
Unbelievable!
What's happening?
People look at me
differently all of a sudden.
Hey, you wanna invite
Kusaki for some fun?
What the heck is going on?
Invitation
Kusaki, I'm having a party at the cottage
to celebrate your recent success...
So please come.
You're kidding...
Well look at that, that cunt invited
you since she can't get enough of you.
I think I'll pass.
What?
This is some kind of mistake.
It's too much of a burden for me.
Huh?
You're just a cunt, I won't let you die!
Here I come!
No!
I've never been banged
so rough by a man before...
I'm so wet...
Kisaku Spirit
The Letch Lives Vol. 3
Lost Savage, Pure Faction
Then we have a problem. You
have to attend the party.
Yes, the thing is...
Are you sure you want me to go?
Of course.
Many people are going to be there
to congratulate you on your success!
Please?
I see...
You're just a puppet
for me to play with.
You just do what she tells you to.
I got lost.
You're so silly.
I think I'll have some lunch.
I understand.
I'll attend the party
for you, Ayano. Goodbye.
Hey, if you just stick your ass
out nicely, I'll treat you well!
Be a good girl!
Please stop. Don't do it here.
It's exciting to do it here.
It's shaped beautifully
like a chrysanthemum.
It sure smells like it.
Please stop! It's embarrassing!
People are going to see us!
Don't worry!
No one's gonna think
we're doing this here!
If I remember correctly, you've
never had it up your ass, right?
It's not a bad idea to have
it up your ass like Shoko did.
No! Not here!
Someone might see us!
I'm telling you that's the best part!
The thrill you get from being watched
takes away the pain you feel up the ass.
Come on! Stick your ass out.
No! Hurts!
It hurts!
Yuuri...
Well look at that, Shoko
looks like she wants some too.
No, that's not true.
That's really not like you at all.
Now, it's your turn.
I want you to clean my
cock with your mouth.
No Shoko! Don't lick it.
What's wrong?
I'm trying to teach
you Yuuri's technique!
Would you rather have it up your
ass in the bathroom as usual?
No! I'm going, I need to go!
You're already gone!
You really like the bathroom Shoko...
In the end, you're just a piece of ass!
You really like to go to the bathroom.
No, I don't want that...
Then suck on it!
Shoko...
What the hell? You call that sucking?
Put it deeper inside!
Does Yuuri's ass taste good?
Is it much tighter down here?
Stop! No more!
You should just enjoy this
and take it like a cunt!
Next, I'll do...
Mister, please let us go!
Your ass is mine forever!
Hey, spread your legs!
No! Stop it!
Are you disappointed that I'm not
doing your ass in the bathroom?
I'm not disappointed at all...
Don't hesitate to say it!
Your face says you want more!
What the hell?
You are...
S-Stop!
I finally came back from the dead!
I'm not going back!
You're really annoying.
You can't force me to go back!
Get the hell out of here!
We're not through! I'm
just getting started!
You took off from work all of a
sudden, I was worried about you.
I'm sorry that I hurt your feelings.
I didn't have any choice that
time. He wouldn't let me go...
If I didn't do what he told me to.
After all, I like men better!
It's great to be banged
with that hard cock!
It feels so good!
Ayano, how could you!
Let's have some fun tonight
to make up for that time.
Okay?
Not tonight Ayano...
What are you saying Hiromi?
I really need you...
No, stop it Ayano...
I'm glad, you're feeling
it just like before...
No, Ayano!
Now, do you want to try this?
My, what's got into you? It looks
like you're sucking on the real thing.
I want to see that man...
Hiromi, you didn't...
No!
I don't want you to go to him!
Hiromi, I can be a man too!
Feels good right? Just like that man!
Hiromi!
Kisaku!
Huh?
It's a fine-Looking cottage.
Those women really like to show off.
Their crotches are all wet
and about to explode.
I'm so happy that you came, Kusaki.
Yes, well thank you
for providing a ride.
You don't need to thank me.
Now come inside.
Everyone's waiting for you.
W-What is this?
They came to the party since
they were interested in you.
Me?
Yes, they just can't
forget about that man.
Please tell me where is he right now?
I'm afraid to go to the
bathroom without him.
What do you mean "him"?
Kusaki, you're not really Kisaku?
But you look Kisaku in some way.
Who is this Kisaku?
He's the man that I'm supposed to
marry.
What?
Engaged?
Please, I want to see him.
I don't know.
I don't know any person named Kisaku.
What are you scared of?
Those women want you.
Just do them all.
All right!
I'll do you all at once!
Kisaku, I'm so happy...
So it was you Kisaku.
You two are just like sisters,
and you got better at sucking cock.
This is like a dream come true.
Hey Hiromi, let's show
that man we get along well.
I want to be banged
by that man once more...
No!
Ayano, please stop.
How can I make you understand,
Hiromi?
You're pregnant. You
should take it easy...
But...
I heard it's the last
time I can see him...
So I just had to come...
My, who told you that?
A woman sent me an
invitation to this place...
What a coincidence. I too
received an invitation.
Please don't do that...
Why am I doing this? My
hands just move on their own...
I wasn't always like this, you know.
It seems like you're all
acting differently than usual...
...since today's the last day to see him.
You're right.
That's what that woman said too.
Invitation
This is such a great orgy!
I can just do whatever I want, huh?
It's sad to see you cunts like this.
You keep releasing your juices
since you desperately want a man!
Yes Kisaku!
Yes!
I want some too...
Hey there, girlie.
You want me to clean your ass with
this?
No!
Stop it!
Here we go! It's a
huge hypodermic needle.
It's so tight!
You!
You're gonna stick that up my ass?
I was just thinking
of getting back at you!
What?
You're one stubborn zombie!
Get your hands off my
precious little cunts!
If I see something
that I like, I take it!
This is a great opportunity for
me to show you my best technique!
What?
What are you gonna do?
Your luck has just ran out!
I'll thrust and send you
all the way to the moon!
I see.
You cunts want me to
do you that bad, huh?
I'll just do you cunts in order...
What?
Why is this happening?
It's you again!
I told you I'm not going back!
What the...
Why can't I go back?
What's going on?
What was I doing until now?
Why are you all naked?
They all had it up their cunts!
You can't do it!
If I don't go back, he
won't be able to do them!
You're very big, Kusaki.
Yes, you're just as big as that man.
Wonderful.
You don't find a cock
like that very often.
I don't want to let go!
Please stay by my side!
Me too!
Well?
They really want you, you
should be very happy to be a man.
Well I...
You don't want to do us?
But...
This is a chance for you
to be a whole new person.
A chance?
Yes, you can be reborn
and start a new life.
Amazing! This is amazing!
What the hell?
What's going on?
Does this mean he
stole most of my powers?
Damn it! Give them back!
What are you doing?
Stop! Don't take me away!
Let go!
Let me go!
Did you cunts forget what I did for you?
You bunch of cold-hearted cunts!
I'll just flee from this place again.
I can't flee?
Yes, this is the Kusaki company.
Thank you for your
assistance yet again.
12 dozen of savage set?
Yes, the savage costume play?
I'm sorry, we're out of stock right now...
Excuse me.
President Kusaki, our sales for this
month surpassed last month's figures.
President...
No, we're still working...
I'll do the workers again...
Got you!