Mister, Please forgive me...
Whether I forgive you or not...
You're still going to be walking
the path to becoming a fine cunt!
That's not the path I
want to take in life...
No...
I don't want that!
Now, what delicacy would
you like to have next?
Well well! You don't like either one?
Personally, I like the vinegary
squid, also known as squid legs!
No!
Let me see what this
delicacy tastes like.
I don't want any delicacies!
No...
It's hitting the spot...
No!
Yuuri! Where are you? Help me!
Your companion Yuuri
is waiting over there!
No...
New Secretaries, Torture Squad
More women to be sacrificed.
It's feeding time once again!
Yuuri Himeno
Shoko Sugimoto
Yuuri!
Right now, your companion
Yuuri is extremely satisfied.
Let's see if she can hear your voice.
Why is this happening...
Ever since that unpleasant
event Shoko hasn't been the same.
In order to forget the horrific
experience and get back on track...
We decided to go on a vacation
together.
I thought Shoko could
use some fresh air.
And to ease her suffering...
We decided to go to a hot spring.
Kisaku Spirit
Yuuri! I had lots of fun today!
Me too!
It's good to see Shoko happy again.
Hey come on.
Let's go to the hot spring again!
Hold on, I'll be ready in a second.
The Letch Lives Vol. 2
Life is Full of Savages
I'm sorry Shoko...
I didn't think it would be like this...
Let's see...
Looks like things are
heating up over there!
I think it's time for us to
get things started as well!
Get things started?
Since your ass isn't getting any action,
I thought I might give you a present.
What are you gonna do?
No!
I don't want that!
I had enough from that man!
No! It hurts to take it up the ass!
Stick it in there!
If you stick that in
there, my ass will tear!
My ass will be torn!
It hurts!
It's gonna rip...
Hey, why don't you move as well?
It hurts...
My ass is gonna rip!
My ass!
Double the pleasure from front and
back!
My savage ways have just begun!
No, my ass...
No!
For Shoko and I...
Our nightmares still won't end...
Now please spread your legs.
Relax your legs...
You're fine.
There's a small wound but you
have nothing to worry about.
Take care.
Nadeshiko Minami
Aoi Akimoto
I can't believe Kisaku is back...
Is it...
True?
Mysterious woman
Well, are you getting used
to the secretarial work?
Yes!
That's good.
Ever since you came,
you've been a great help.
So it was worth talking to
personnel to get you in.
No, this is all because of you, Ayano.
That terrible thing happened...
And I thought I couldn't
work here anymore...
I was deeply hurt too.
But that man is gone
and everything is over.
We have a bright future ahead of us.
Yes.
Second conference room
You switched to
garter stockings too?
Yes...
I wanted to be just like you...
That's really nice of you to say.
It's not clean down there...
I just love the smell of your feet...
Don't even think about
climaxing yet, Hiromi.
Ayano...
Your tits are so soft.
Yes...
If you squeeze them like that I...
Feels good doesn't it?
I want to feel good too!
Kisaku!
Huh?
Mail?
I wonder who...
This is...
Is something wrong, Ayano?
No, it's nothing.
Shoko is supposed to be
on vacation with Yuuri...
Sender-Shoko
Hello, Shoko?
No, guess again.
Who are you?
You'll find out very soon.
What?
I'm not gonna say a
thoughtless thing like...
I'll kill the hostages
if you don't comply.
But juices will be flowing out of Shoko's
cunt and her ass will be filled as well.
You coward!
You're wrong...
I'm a savage.
Listen up.
There'll be a guy named Kusaki heading
over there for a business meeting.
You're gonna have sex with him.
Excuse me.
My name is Kusaki...
You...
You must be Kusaki.
I've been expecting you.
Come this way please.
Well you see...
I came here today to
introduce a new product and...
Umm...
Let's not talk about serious
matters, let's do something more fun...
Please stop!
What an idiot...
But what the hell...
I'm really sorry...
It's okay...
You don't like women like me right?
You hate me right?
No, I think you're a wonderful woman...
That's good to hear.
I think I've fallen in love with you...
Miss Kashiwagi!
Don't worry...
You can count on me...
But I'm not good at these things...
It's okay, don't hold back.
I'm gonna be doing you, punk!
But...
You're very impatient.
Miss Kashiwagi, stop!
Shut up!
Just shut up and make it erect!
Well? Feels good doesn't it?
I've never felt this good in my life...
I need you to make it much bigger.
You're gonna feel much better...
Along with me.
Now, you have to do
some work from here on...
Miss Kashiwagi...
I wonder if this huge thing will fit...
It's so thick...
It's amazing...
It feels sticky and it won't let go...
Don't just sit there, move your hips.
Yes...
Here we go...
It's so intense...
It's deep inside me!
Strange things have
been happening lately...
I'm sure this is a dream...
Otherwise, I wouldn't be doing
this with such a beautiful woman...
What's going on?
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
It's just not fun watching it!
All of a sudden...
It can't be...
Kisaku Ito?
Reception room
I was told you were here, Ayano...
After all, I like men better!
It's great to be banged
with that hard cock!
It feels so good!
Ayano...
Slut!
How could you?
Hiromi!
I feel hot stuff coming inside me...
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened...
No, it's not him...
I had some fun today but the
business meeting didn't go smoothly...
I feel like nothing is
going right these days...
I can't believe Ayano was...
I can't believe anything anymore...
No!
No...
That was...
It's my turn now!
It was wrong for me to think that I can
live just like any average person.
I'm so impure...
I can never lead a normal life...
Father, mother...
Forgive me...
For going before you two!
Hold it right there!
Wait, wait, wait!
You are...
You're just a cunt...
I won't let you die!
No!
Here I come!
It's been a while since you did it with a
guy, but you certainly know what to do.
No...
Take it out...
I don't like men...
They're so dirty...
What a thing to say!
Huh?
Don't tell me what to do, cunt!
I'll have to punish you!
I'm sure people are watching
you do it on their TV by now...
It's so erotic that I wanna
release my stuff inside you...
No!
That vibrator was inside Shoko's ass.
Eat it with appreciation.
Take a look.
This vibrator was stuck inside your ass.
Looks like it's a bit sticky.
Let's clean it up with an enema...
You bunch of idiots...
Why can't you keep your assholes
clean?
No, it's coming out again...
Stop looking at me...
Don't watch me perform
this shameful act!
I finally got Hiromi's cunt.
Got you!