As master of sex slaves, I can't neglect
training my girls. - Kisaku Itou.
The Letch
Nadeko Minami
Momoko Shiraishi
Sex Slaves
Episode 3, Screw the Gorgeous
Receptionist on the Beach!
I decided who should
be my 4th sex slave.
Since it is our wedding
anniversary today...
...you'll come home early today, right?
Call me when you leave work, okay?
Neighbors say that she is a
kind and very social young wife.
See you later, honey.
Her name is Nadeshiko Minami.
Now I have to spend another day
waiting for him to come home.
You'll never know what will
happen if you leave me alone...
Yes...
Umm?
That's strange...
The Way of the Pervert, rule one...
When you approach a married woman,
conquer her by your strength.
I don't feel like going to work today...
He screwed me so hard, and...
Now he's meddling with other
woman. I can't take this!
No, I'm not the one
who should fall in love...
I want someone to fall in love with me!
Maybe I should take a day off...
Oh my God! Oh my God! Oh my God!
Oh my God!
Good morning!
How do you like it?
No!
Well, well...
Maybe you're not satisfied because
I didn't come inside of you...
Don't worry, we have plenty of time.
No!
Please forgive me.
Whether I forgive you or not...
...depends on how
things go in the bedroom!
No!
The Way of the Pervert, rule two...
To make women obey, you have to
go all the way until she craves it.
No!
You'll break my pussy!
Hey...
Should I tell Mr. Minami
that you raped his wife?
How is the taste of the meat
stick you were waiting for?
Trying to threaten me like that...
It seems like you've fallen
in love with my joystick.
I can be yours...
I can...
So, you should be only mine...
I'm very sorry...
...but you are nothing but
one of my sexual slaves.
Not fair!
You bastard!
Oh...
Please protect me...
Well, well...
It's nice to see you again.
The Way of the Pervert, rule three...
You should not stop screwing
her until she's broken in.
I felt bad that I was the only
one who enjoyed this afternoon...
Please, stop this...
It's not good for you to hold it in.
No!
Come on, don't be shy.
What?
A recreational trip?
Yes, it's the joint event
with the personnel section.
We are going to the beach this year.
Of course you are expected
to participate in this.
I see...
This sucks. I was going to play
with my slaves this weekend...
Wait for me!
Why don't you jump in the water?
Sorry, but a pervert like me
doesn't like to be under the sun.
What a cute looking couple!
You are jealous of us, aren't you?
Yes, I'm very jealous of you.
Hey!
Nice ass.
Say, do you know her?
Welcome to Sugimoto Medicine.
How may I help you?
That's Momoko Shiraishi.
She's cute, so she
is popular among guys...
Actually she does look cute...
Very good! Don't you think?
Ladies' Room
Oh no, it's disgusting...
This reminds me of my hometown...
I thought I felt warm breathing...
No way...
It can't be!
My fifth sex slave!
Lock on!
Ms. Minami!
Having fun?
Yes, I had a little...
I always envied housewives.
They look so hot in their kimonos.
Oh...
Please stop it!
It's a party, let's have fun!
Please!
I'm surprised.
I've never seen my husband so cheerful.
He's sort of a workaholic
and not a very social, so...
He's been giving me some useful
advice regarding my business plan...
...and we became close.
I hope you remain good friends.
Of course, since we are like brothers...
...since we share the same horny hole.
No!
Please stop it! You're
going to break me!
Stop it!
You two would be even happier if
you had a kid, don't you think?
I've been through a lot for this trip...
...but I feel like I
could wash everything away!
We spent all the money we made
at part-time jobs, though...
I'm sorry!
What was that about?
Maybe she got involved with a murder
case that took place at this hot spring!
You!
Two disposable sex slaves... got you!
I think it was Mr. Minami's wife...
I saw something I shouldn't see...
Hello Miss.
Are you here by yourself?
Why don't you stop by our restaurant?
The owner will be mad at us
if we don't bring customers in.
What?
Wait...
Master! We've got a customer!
Hello Miss.
Isn't it delicious?
This is Master's special drink!
That's right, it's
not an ordinary drink...
but a quick-acting aphrodisiac.
Are you all right?
It's really hot out today...
Maybe you should have
some rest in the back.
I'm fine...
Let me take care of you...
No!
We know how to take care of you.
Why?
Why am I like this...
Because that's what
you really are, Miss...
...a sex slave...
What?
Otherwise...
you wouldn't be
getting horny like this.
Your body looks so delicious that
my dick's getting hard as a rock.
No!
If this is about last night...
I promise I won't tell anybody!
It has nothing to do with that...
You are destined to be a sex slave...
to my dick.
What is this feeling?
I'll be pregnant...
In that case, I'll fuck you as
hard as possible for an abortion...
If I had a baby...
We would have to marry...
Huh?
After registering our marriage...
we could plan the
ceremony and honeymoon trip...
Got you?
Under the summer sky, don't rush, don't
spill, the hot load. By Kisaku Itou
Until the next episode...
Viva my sex life!
To be continued...