Cunt...
I smell cunt!
Where...
...am I?
Huh?
Did I die?
I smell something...
I can smell...
Those cunts are calling for me!
Kisaku Spirit
Yuuri Himeno
Shoko Sugimoto
No!
Don't worry Shoko.
The scary-looking man is gone.
See you later, Yuuri!
Bye Shoko.
Shoko's not the only one
under some sort of spell.
Honestly, I'm also...
It can't be...
Old man, old lady, are you two okay?
I see...
So you're having trouble with your
legs?
I never thought he'd
be kind to the elderly...
Chief Kusaki is doing it again.
Helping others out?
Only if he was good looking...
Yeah, if he's just kind-hearted...
Hey, let's go!
Wrong person...
Yeah, that's it.
It's over.
I don't have to go through that again...
Those indecent acts...
You're very kind.
No, that's not true...
It's true.
What do we have here?
That's Yuuri!
So the smell of her
cunt brought me back?
You reminded me of a
person I knew, so I...
I'm looking forward to it...
You might look like him, but now I
know that you're not like him at all.
What is your occupation?
Me?
I'm just a worthless company employee.
Stop messing with me.
Mysterious woman
Well, could you just tell me your name?
My name is...
What is your name?
I'm sure you know me...
I'm Kisaku!
The Letch Lives Vol. 1
Dinner at the Ito residence
You still remember what
I taught you, Yuuri.
Does my cock taste that
good after all this time?
I just love that look on your face!
It's coming out...
I can't believe I'm
doing this in public...
What a great view!
If those cunts find out I've returned by
borrowing this guy's body...
They'll be so happy to see me.
Kisaku!
Momoko Shiraishi
I'm glad!
I knew you were alive, Kisaku!
I was searching for you, since I didn't
want to believe that you were dead.
And now I was able to see you again.
This is all because of god...
It's all part of fate!
Let's head down to city hall.
I already have the
marriage registration.
We'll only invite our close
family members and get married...
...in secret!
What?
That's enough, you stupid woman!
Kisaku!
You're not acting like a real cunt.
I'll have to teach you
how to be one again!
Here we go!
I can't believe I'm doing
this here standing up...
Don't grab them so hard, it hurts.
Liar!
You're really enjoying this!
It's getting really tight.
Sorry to disappoint you, Momoko.
Normally, I'd have an
elaborate plan before I do you...
...but I'll just do you today
according to my instincts.
You don't have to worry about that.
I think you should do it the normal way.
You're nothing but a cunt, I
wasn't asking for your opinion.
It's so tight.
You're not too bright, but
your cunt was pretty good!
Kisaku, let's head down to city hall.
No, you must be mistaking
me for someone else!
Hey, come back here!
Kisaku!
Huh?
What's going on?
Today's a weird day...
Are you okay?
Thank you so much.
Kisaku?
I'm sorry, I mistook
you for someone else.
Nadeshiko Minami
Hey, that's Nadeshiko.
Well, look at that huge stomach...
She did a real good job.
I can't!
Please don't.
I can't let a stranger
like you be all nice to me...
What are they doing?
You can't walk with your foot like that.
Let me take care of you.
Minami
Let's see...
Thank you so much, Kusaki.
I did what anyone would've
done in that situation.
Are you sure you don't
need to go to the hospital?
Yes, it's just a light sprain.
I see...
Then I guess I should get going.
Hey!
She invited you in here, and
you're gonna leave so soon?
Come back here!
Are you really a man or what?
Hold it right there!
Kusaki?
Is something wrong?
I'm so happy!
I'm back again!
You are...
That's right! I'm Kisaku!
It can't be!
It might be difficult
to do you from the front.
No, not that...
It's so tight...
So meaty...
After you got pregnant, you
haven't had much action, huh?
What a waste...
Your cunt's in such good condition!
No...
It's so intense...
I'll keep on increasing the intensity.
It's amazing...
You seem to be enjoying it.
Did you forget that
you were a fine cunt?
That's not true...
You're doing this as if
you don't have a kid inside.
What position did you do
it in when you were mating?
I don't remember...
Maybe it's my kid inside you.
No, don't say that!
You're probably
thinking it's mine, right?
Does that feel good?
Hey, I felt something kicking inside.
I think you're asking for it.
I guess I'll climax inside then.
No, anything but that...
Don't worry about it.
You're not gonna get pregnant again.
Here's a present from a brutal man!
I got me some cunt from a married
woman!
I'm really sorry, honey...
I'm sorry Yuuri.
I'm still scared to go
into the bathroom alone...
Don't worry about it.
What's wrong with me?
What the hell is going on?
He's such an idiot.
He's definitely not cool.
People who can't succeed
in life are miserable.
Hey, they're talking
crap about you Kusaki.
Those cunts are making
fun of you. Do something!
I'm back again!
The manager of the materials
department is so annoying.
What an idiot...
A tier of two cunts!
Let's see what it feels like.
Feels so good...
You two climaxed already?
Can't you cunts last a bit longer?
I'll use this and close
up your loose cunts!
No, it's too big!
Even though your cunts are loose,
after I'm through with you two...
You two should just act
like the cunts you are!
Who in the world sent me these
pictures?
It was me.
Mister...
There!
Stop it...
I'm scared of the bathroom...
That's why I brought
you to the men's room.
That's even worse!
Stop whining!
You want those pictures to go public?
Don't worry. I'm not a fool like Sada.
I'll give you great pleasure.
Now take off your clothes!
But what if someone comes in here?
That's the thrill we're seeking!
If you're not gonna take them
off, you want me to rip them off?
Then you'll have to go home streaking.
What's streaking?
Don't you know anything about the
world?
Anyway, just take them off!
Fine...
This is what you've been waiting for.
You're really tight.
Are you that excited?
No, I'm not...
No...
Let's see, I feel like releasing myself...
No, release it outside...
Are you telling me what to do cunt?
No...
I'm going, I need to go!
You're already gone!
You really like the bathroom Shoko,
in the end, you're just a piece of ass!
I'm going, I'm going!
Take this!
You really like to go to the bathroom.
Now I think I'll pee inside you.
You're peeing inside me?
No!
Shoko has now become
a fine piece of ass.
As one of my newest acquisitions,
I'm expecting a lot from you, Shoko.
Got you!
To be continued...