There!
Shoko!
You're an excellent player!
I envy you.
Me too.
Don't flatter me, please.
Are you sure that you
don't need a ride home?
Yes, I'm okay. I had a
great time with you today.
Let's do this again.
Then, good bye.
Good bye.
It's not so easy hanging
out with high-class people.
I'd rather hang out
with my school friends.
Yuri!
It's been a while, Yuri.
Yes, since your last birthday party.
Oh yeah!
I'm having my birthday party
at my summer house in Karuizawa.
What are you looking at?
Yuri, there's something
different about you.
What?
I would say you became more mature.
Your waist is smaller
and your hip is bigger...
Your bust is bigger
than B cup, isn't it?
Well...
Do you have a boyfriend now?
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
Where are your manners, Miss?
Ms. Katsuragi.
That's called a petty-minded suspicion.
A Promotional Video?
I'm fed up with our president's taste...
He insists on playing the
video at Shoko's birthday party.
Also, he asked us to wear gym clothes
at the company's Olympics and...
...he made us participate in
the company's beauty pageant.
He's already offended
some female employees.
Who was the one that won the title
at that pageant, and bragged about it?
Well...
Besides, I understand why he wants
show off his cute granddaughter.
I think making you wear
a swimsuit is too much.
Come on, I'll show people
that I'm not a kid anymore.
It's true. She is already in bloom...
What should I say...
She is glamorous for her
age, and attractive...
I can't believe what I'm thinking...
You gotta make me look nice and cute!
I'll shoot you all day if you want.
She doesn't even trim.
She is just a pampered little girl.
But...
...you can't stay that
way for too long...
The Letch
Shoko Sugimoto
Sex Slaves
Episode 5, Screw the daughter of your
boss at her birthday party! Part 1
When I go to sleep?
Which do you think I wear when
I sleep, pajamas or night gowns?
I don't think I'm sexy enough
yet to wear a sexy night gown.
It's pajamas with teddy bears...
Did you think I would wear that?
You're wrong!
The answer is, I'm naked when I sleep!
I just wear panties.
I'm just teasing.
I think I have about 30 of them...
I don't know, I've never counted them.
How many do you have?
I have them in cream
yellow, lavender, and...
I like the printed ones too.
I wear this when I have
a physical exam at school.
Because this is not too sexy...
Which one do I wear when I go on a
date?
Let me see...
Well, the only person who'll know all
that is the one who takes them off me!
Is it okay for you to
talk about this stuff?
I don't care, it's fun.
These aren't secrets.
But I can't tell you my real secrets...
...not even you, Yuri.
I'll leave the video to you, Yuri.
Make it fun and cute!
O-Okay...
Good night.
You have to give the tape to him...
Do we really have to?
He knows your weakness too, right?
Then, we have no choice.
If I give this to him,
what will happen to Shoko?
Cleaning
I hope nobody saw me...
I don't know why I get excited
every time I go to the bathroom.
I was so embarrassed when I
went in front of other people...
But I also felt strangely excited.
I hope he'll go away...
It's embarrassing enough
when someone hears me do it...
No...
But it feels good.
I didn't know there where people
who would take pictures like these...
It's me!
Pure white panties...
I like an innocent girl.
Nasty girl...
Should we make her take
a pee in front of us?
Oh, don't move...
It's good manners to wipe
yourself after you take a pee.
I know you don't want people to
see those embarrassing pictures...
You look pretty when you cry...
I can feel your tears running
from the mouth down there...
See?
Or...
...is it drooling?
Have you noticed any changes
recently?
Do you get horny every
time you go to the bathroom?
Bingo...
No, no way...
It's not true!
I did something to you that night...
Your hips were so lovely...
...I put a lot of
love drug in the enema.
Love drug?
A drug that makes girls go crazy.
Himeno...
You get so horny that you can't wait
for someone to do nasty things to you.
You're addicted to enemas!
E-Enemas...
He is out of control, you see.
He wouldn't stop giving enemas to
us even though we begged him to stop.
He continued torturing
us like that all night.
She had an orgasm while going number
2.
What about you? You begged him to
give you enemas one after another!
Your crotch is getting hot, Yuri...
Let me cool it down.
I can do better!
Right?
No...
No!
Mr. Kisaku!
Letch
Where the hell is she?
I want it...
Please, don't stop...
Please!
Stop begging me like
that, or I'll knock you up.
I don't care...
I want it so much!
I want it!
Well, well...
You're a troublesome wife, aren't you?
You're so tight...
You want another round?
No...
Please, no...
I'm sorry...
...but Kisaku is mine...
So you'll have to
have fun with this guy.
But I just did it...
We won't stop giving
you an enema until...
...you get addicted to it.
No...
Oh right, we're having a
physical exam at school today.
Then I need to wear these.
I wish I had bigger breasts...
Looks like I need to pick
up the pills after school...
You are so cute!
Wake up, sleepy head!
Good morning, Jinno.
What are you doing, Miss Shoko?
I'm playing your wife...
Well, Jinno, are you afraid?
Is it because you might get fired if
I told my grandpa that you kissed me?
Um, that's...
I can't tell anybody
about our relationship...
Oh no!
You shouldn't visit
a single guy's room...
...if you make a fuss like that...
I didn't make a fuss!
I was just surprised because I
saw something I didn't expect...
I know what it is. It's
called morning wood, right?
But does it go back to normal
after it gets swollen like that?
Or do you need me to help you?
My dick is sensing something.
I bet some corny soap opera
is going on behind my back.
I'm the main character
of this show, damn it!
Do you need relief?
I'll help you!
Today's physical exam was cancelled.
Oh no, I just changed
into my gym clothes!
Why?
Don't ask me, I don't know!
But somebody came and took
Shoko somewhere, though...
Let's see...
Why are the other students gone?
Why am I alone here?
Answer me!
How long have you been taking
these pills for your constipation?
What are you talking
about? I have no idea...
Ms. Sugimoto, you've consulted
with the school nurse about...
...your irregularity when you
entered this school, am I correct?
How long have you been
using this product exactly?
I don't know!
It has a serious side-effect...
I said I don't know!
How long has it been?
Well, I started using
this 5 years ago...
For 5 years. It's like a fine wine...
No!
Don't be stupid, Miss...
The real examination hasn't started yet.
I'm telling you this because I am
really concerned about your health.
Wonderful!
So you've been doing this for 5 years?
I couldn't ask anybody to do this...
I bet there are some things you
don't want anyone to see, right?
For example, your wonderful
facial expression...
...the moment it is
inserted into your anus...
No way...
I have to shoot you if you lie...
Got that?
Tell me how you feel.
How?
I feel excited...
The school nurse did it for me the
first time, and I remember it sometimes.
I feel relieved and strange at
the same time when I release it.
I even dream about wetting myself.
Even when I masturbate, I
find myself touching my anus...
Is this one of the side-effects
you were talking about?
I assume so.
Jinno...
Oh no!
Considering your condition,
that tiny pill is not enough.
I'll take my time and
give you an enema...
...in front of your boyfriend.
That's terrible! You're so mean!
These must be tears of joy.
No! No!
Don't cry yet.
You have to save your tears for later...
This special enema has already
changed one girl's life...
Shiraishi
Looks like Momoko is
out of the game now.
Maybe it was a little
too rough for her...
No! Stop it!
Everything should be fine since
Momoko found a sincere boyfriend.
Don't even think that this
is the end of the story...
I'll be back in the next episode...
Viva! My perverted sex life!
To be continued...
Rape is a crime
punishable by law.