Yuri...
Please, let me go...
Come on, what are you talking about?
Oh, no...
Look, your nipples are so hard...
You must know the
reason why I called you.
Miss Hiromi Kimisaki.
Well, no.
Yesterday the accounting manager
reported to the chairman that...
...the sales department accumulated...
...ten thousand dollars of
unexplained expenses in one month.
I really don't...
The sales manager you slept with
has already admitted everything.
He was granted a leave
of absence without pay.
Ms. Kimishima...
I don't think that using the
female body as a weapon...
...to get promoted is such a bad thing.
Since this male dominated world
has limited women's social rights...
...we don't need to worry
about how we get back at them.
Good girl. Keep up the good work.
Let's say this money is a
fund for our future together.
Who are you thinking about now?
The accounting manager?
Or...
Mr. Sada?
I can't stand being used.
Please, you can help us...
The Letch
Shoko Sugimoto
Hiromi Kimisaki
I'm the fucking main character!
Episode 6, Screw the daughter of your
boss at her birthday party! Part 2
One year since Kisaku appeared...
Hiromi!
Is that...
Don't tell anybody yet.
Is he the one?
Let's take a look.
What am I doing here?
No, I can't think anything.
I just...
You want me to stop?
I'm not satisfied until I satisfy you...
We came to meet him a few hours ago.
My name is Hiromi Kimishima.
We came to ask him to
take care of our wedding.
He suggested that we stay
over since it was late.
And...
You'll wake him if you make any noise...
No!
You don't need to hold it in.
Constipation is bad for a
young lady's beauty, you know...
Tell me when you want to let it out...
Trust me like you trust your parents.
We need to know each other well...
Oh no...
You can't go to the bathroom, yet.
No...
How do you like the enema?
You'll be addicted to it, soon.
And the outdoor play, too...
Just let it out...
Hey, just release yourself...
No!
Of course, I want to be relieved...
If I think that I'm doing this outside
because I can't find the bathroom...
Then I feel much better...
Mr. Sada is a freak.
He waited that moment
and came inside of me.
He raped me only one night,
but it still made me crazy.
I can't believe that you
could stand him for a year.
I was kind of addicted to it...
You look pretty.
You made me excited.
No! Get out!
No!
That's not going to work.
I stuck the lever.
No!
People will come in if
you make noises like that.
Damn, a virgin's ass drives me crazy...
It's dirty there!
You just washed it clean.
No...
No! You'll tear it
I'll give you a milk enema!
No...
I feel like I'm going to the bathroom...
No!
I just took a pee before!
The baby who wets
herself needs a diaper...
No, that's not a diaper!
Hide your ass and show your pussy...
I told you to come here
wearing no underwear, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
Don't be mean to me.
Help me to take off my underwear.
I don't like childish underwear.
I want to suck it too.
Well, well...
Me too...
I loved the way Madoka sucked my
dick. She is very experienced.
But still, younger is better...
I guess it's the time
for some deserts...
Here is a special dish with assorted
mushrooms and horny young girls...
I hope you enjoy it.
Oh no, that's a poisonous mushroom.
My body is numb...
I'll cure you with more of the same...
Aw! No...
It's too thick for me.
Well, let me use this mushroom...
...to make you senseless...
No, it's twitching...
It's yummy.
I like the bigger one...
No, it's reaching deep inside of me...
Deep inside of me...
I love fall. It's a great
season for mushrooms...
Master, we want some milk...
I want you to shoot it out.
I bought some juice...
Good girl.
How optimistic can you get, huh?
Oh, Ms. Ayano...
You gotta get in the line you
want to receive my service.
Somebody is already eating your
dessert.
W-W-W-What
did you say?
Jinno...
You know what?
I visited your grandfather
when you were little.
I used to change your diapers...
I've never forgotten how
cute your anus looked...
No more!
Please don't put it in me...
Men are givers and
females are receivers...
That's the way we are...
That's the rule for lovemaking.
I'll go crazy if I any more gets in me.
I'll suck your dick, so
please don't screw my ass.
It's big...
I can't believe this was in my ass...
I never took a poop this big before...
If he screwed my anus again,
it would become too loose!
I have to make him come before that...
Once he comes, this will be over.
Ew, it stinks...
But I have to do this...
Oh my, it's getting excited...
Don't let it out yet!
I will suck and swallow all of it.
I'm good at this, aren't I?
I want you to shoot more of it.
Let me swallow your come.
I can't believe you're a virgin...
You know how to use your hands...
I'm not naughty. I've
been practicing for Jinno...
Well then...
I'll make you a woman in
front of your boyfriend...
No! It hurts!
Would you prefer an enema?
Please forgive me...
I swear I'll be a good girl!
So why don't you kiss me...
Yes...
It's getting bigger...
It's so hard.
A girl from a rich family
always has a tight pussy...
No...
Ow! That hurts!
What are doing? No!
I can't...
I feel strange...
So strange...
Your thick and hard dick is
hitting deep inside of me...
I can't do this
anymore, you'll break me.
You can't come inside of me...
No, I don't want to get pregnant!
Please don't come inside!
Here we are.
I've got you!
Kisaku Kick!
You fake pervert, don't
even try to steal my game!
You too!
How dare you give
yourself away so easily...
...to such a loser!
This way, Ms. Kimisaki!
There they are!
That fat guy is also
his partner in crime!
I guess things should be settled soon.
What the?
I didn't even finish yet!
What good timing!
Start the car!
But I...
I said, start the car!
That was close.
Listen, I...
I don't have a driver's license!
Shit!
You should've told me that first!
Hey, Mister!
Where the hell am I?
It looks like Heaven, doesn't it?
Why you are naked?
We are just like Adam and Eve...
Where is this place?
Who cares?
Let's make love like Adam and Eve.
H-Hey...
Oh well...
Come on...
I've got you!
The End