A generous bosom.
A killer body.
And a superior intellect.
Her name is Sara Iijima.
A Stunford graduate
in psychofeed theory.
She is a brilliant psychotherapist.
She has teamed up with
me, her assistant, Tamine...
to fight the Japanese education
system and correct its flaws.
What are you doing, Tamine?
Sara! Well I was, ah...
What is it?
Nothing at all!
Come on, I want to know.
No really...
What are you hiding?
What's the matter with you?
The anxieties of people
in modern times.
Unsure of who they are
or where they are going.
What on earth are they searching for?
It's so good!
I hate them!
To help guide these lost sheep...
a D-cup angel of mercy appears.
Her name is Sara Iijima.
The secret Omote Sando
psychofeed therapy!
She is a brilliant psychotherapist.
She uses her ample bosom
to penetrate the subconscious...
and to employ her psychofeed therapy.
She opens the doors to
the souls of those people...
who have stubbornly kept them closed.
How old are you, Yuri?
Three.
Sara confronts their
fears and anxieties...
She probes deep into their insecurities.
To challenge their demons...
she encourages them to
use their own strengths...
so they can understand
and overcome their problems.
Only then do they
discover their true selves.
The lesson is over.
Today, Sara is at a college
with such troubled students.
And together with her
assistant, Tamine...
she'll save the souls of the students.
Sara, was Erika Shimada
such a brilliant student?
Yes. We attended Dr. Chang's
lectures at Stunford.
She's very diligent and talented.
Sara, you've finally come.
She saved my butt a few times,
with papers and labs.
Well, that's quite something...
I can't imagine you needing help.
Up until 2 or 3 years ago,
this college was full of delinquents.
Erika became counselor,
and the problems disappeared.
That's what concerns me.
She may be brilliant, but
students can't change so easily.
I have a feeling there's
something crooked about this.
Don't let your guard down
just because she's my friend.
I understand.
Erika!
Sara.
- It's been so long.
- How have you been?
- I've wanted to see you.
- Me too.
"Don't let your guard down
just because she's my friend."
Look who's talking.
Your breasts are sublime.
Is your boyfriend here making
them bigger every night?
Me? Boyfriend? What the...?
No way! You're wrong there.
He's just my work colleague.
Doesn't have to spell it out.
I'll show you around college.
And Mr. Colleague there
can come along as well.
Well, actually I have
to contact headquarters.
I see.
Shall we?
I was surprised, getting your
call out of the blue like that.
I was the one who was surprised.
You could have told me
that you were back in Japan.
I'm sorry. But I've been so busy...
Why would you give up
your practice in New York...
to come back to Japan
and work in a college?
I have my reasons.
Hello.
Everyone's so well behaved.
It was quite a feat to get this far.
So I've heard. Since you
became a counselor here...
academic standards have risen,
and there's no more fighting.
That's right. And no
need for reprimands.
Do you have some
special counseling method?
I've just applied
Professor Chang's theories.
Plus there are the special
lessons in this lecture hall.
Students who fall behind
come here after class...
for an additional lecture.
It's based on a
curriculum that I've set.
That's amazing.
It's hard to believe all
this equipment is for teaching.
Erika, have you considered my offer?
You mean, to join your
team and work together?
I want to make use of your talents.
It's a nice offer, but I can't
just abandon my students.
Oh, I see.
Sara...
Thanks for asking me.
Well, I'd better get back to my lecture.
See you. Let's meet again.
Sara...
Come on, Sara.
Tamine. How did the preparations go?
I've set up a hidden camera
and microphone.
They'll be impossible to detect.
Each variable is calculated
based on the mean...
Now, our lecture is coming to an end.
You must concentrate,
and listen carefully.
What's this?
A hypnosis video.
It suppresses the consciousness
and hypnotizes viewers.
It's for brainwashing!
Brainwashing?!
I'll analyze what they're
hearing in their headphones.
It's a pulse signal outside
the normal hearing range.
An ultra high frequency
that penetrates the subconscious.
Erika...
Sara...
Erika!
Erika, stop it!
Why are you doing this?!
You were spying on me.
What you are doing here
is not psychotherapy.
You're turning them into robots!
I cannot allow you to do this!
What'll you do about it?
Inform headquarters
and have me arrested?
I won't let you destroy my system.
What are you doing?
Stop it. No!
No...!
These students are in
a hypnotic state.
They will do anything I say.
You have nice breasts.
The maternal equipment for
your psychofeed therapy.
You were the best in
Professor Chang's seminars.
No matter how I tried,
I couldn't compete.
I have a psychofeed method
that's at least as good as yours.
I use these frequency pulses.
No! Stop it!
You should know very well, Sara...
the effect of a rape simulation
psychofeed session.
No! Stop!
You'll destroy who I am!
It's your fault.
Criticizing the method I
worked so hard to develop.
This is not counseling!
All you're doing is
destroying their personalities!
You've seen what can happen.
The problems with lame,
one-on-one treatments.
My method will stop students
dropping out because of fights.
It'll be a level playing field,
with no bullying.
Parents, teachers and employers...
want good students
who achieve high marks.
I'm just making that a reality.
What's wrong with that?
Erika, you're wrong!
You'll be destroyed
when you climax.
No!
The only thing that'll
remain in you is my will.
You must cooperate with me.
I want you to understand.
You love me, don't you?
Sara!
Everything will be fine!
Are you alright? Hang in there.
Better eat something,
or you'll get sick.
I don't want to eat.
I understand how you feel, but...
You understand?
Yes.
Bullshit.
You couldn't possibly understand.
But I...
What is it you understand?
How could you say that?
You don't even know Erika.
There's no way you could
understand how I feel!
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
No.
I shouldn't take it out on
someone who cares for me.
Don't worry about it.
At least she thinks about
what I have to say.
Anyway, get some rest,
and leave Erika to me.
Wait, Tamine.
There must be something
more behind this.
Wait till we figure it out
before you tell headquarters.
But if we wait any longer,
she'll brainwash more students.
Please! Give me more time.
I understand.
Sara, we've got to put
a stop to that brainwashing.
To Professor David Chang,
Stunford University.
From Sara Iijima, Japan.
Please answer some questions
for me as soon as possible.
At least I can destroy
the brainwashing program.
That'll stop Erika Shimada
from ruining those students.
The gymnastics club?
What the...?!
Stop it!
What?
The baton performance!
Baton performance, she says!
And now the ropes.
What?
Nothing to be shy about.
Just lie back and enjoy yourself.
That way, I can take you
to my world of psychofeed.
No way!
Forget Sara and become my slave.
You'll forget your troubles
and live a life of happiness.
Forget about Sara?
I'd rather be dead!
How... how can you love
someone so much?
That can't be. In this filthy world...
people are selfish, and
only think of themselves.
That's right. People can't be trusted.
I'll teach you, Sara.
I'll show you how
people will betray you.
So that's it.
That's what happened
to Erika in New York.
Yes?
Erika?
I've got your stupid colleague here.
If you want him, meet me
at the Cosmo Institute rooftop.
So, Sara. Have you decided
to team up with me?
Professor Chang told me everything.
He told me what happened in America.
About the delinquents
you were counseling.
And one of them, called Alex...
Yes, he raped me,
and after that...
he committed suicide.
The counseling was going well.
We trusted each other.
He betrayed me.
That's when I realized it.
The extent to which people
cannot be trusted.
I also realized that in order to help
people such as Alex...
Professor Chang's psychofeed
theory is insufficient.
So you developed
your brainwashing system.
I could have saved
Alex with this system.
With this program that I created...
I could have saved him
by controlling his mind.
You're wrong!
You were so traumatized by Alex...
you became terrified of building
trusting relationships...
with patients on a one-on-one basis.
You felt you had no choice
but to arbitrarily control...
your students' minds.
That's quite a brilliant analysis.
Might as well find out
whether you're right.
Tamine!
This is what happened to me.
I bet you'll change after you've
experienced what I have.
No!
Stop!
How does it feel to be betrayed
by someone you trust?
Perhaps you can
think of a better theory.
Owww!
Were you conscious?
No, I just came to.
Cut out the act!
And get off me you pervert!
We're surrounded
by brainwashed students.
Play along with me here.
That's it. And soon you'll
be my loyal partner.
We'll see about that.
She's under.
Erika, open your heart to me.
Stop it, Alex!
How can you do this to me?
Forgive me, Erika.
I have no choice!
Wait, Alex! Listen to me.
Take me if you really want me.
Erika, do you mean that?
Of course. I believe in you.
If you honestly want me,
I'll give you everything.
Erika.
I'm sorry!
Alex!
I was powerless.
I thought we'd built
a trusting relationship.
I thought I could save him.
But it was all an illusion.
I'm so sorry, Alex.
If only I'd been a better counselor...
I wouldn't have led you
to commit suicide.
He didn't kill himself.
You should know that.
His murderer was caught.
But you blame yourself for his death.
You denied the truth.
What're you doing?
I'm going to make you see the truth.
Alex was going out on his own...
but he ran into his gang
and they threatened him.
Said they'd kill him
if he quit the gang.
He was told to rape you,
to prove his loyalty to them.
But they caught him running away.
They killed him and made
it look like a suicide.
So it's the same as my killing him!
- It's my fault!
- Listen to me!
You did the right thing!
However terrible the ending...
Alex was bound to
his life on the streets.
But after he met you, he
decided to leave the streets.
He was determined to
start his life over.
That doesn't change the
fact that it's my fault.
Erika.
Alex.
Erika. We finally meet again.
Thank you, Erika.
I've wanted to thank you for so long.
You believed me in my time of need.
It was the first time
I ever felt truly happy.
Alex...
Erika, listen to the
rest of my analysis.
You suffered from
a traumatic experience.
But you didn't abandon
your profession.
And you tried desperately
to recreate him.
But I was wrong.
Your method was wrong.
But I'm glad.
I respect you for your
kindness and diligence.
Sara...
Don't worry. It's not too
late to start over again.
Thanks to your help...
the students were
successfully de-programmed.
That's great.
It's important to see
things through to the end.
Give my regards to Dr. Chang.
Take care.
Sara...
Erika!
I envy your having someone
you trust so close by.
Well...
Don't push yourself too hard, Sara.
Mr. Colleague, Take care of this lady.
With all my life.
With all your life?
Take care. Bye.
The lesson is over.
There she goes.
Listen, Sara.
I have my own theory about Erika.
Could you hear me out?
Sure. What is it?
I've been thinking about
Erika losing confidence...
and coming back to
Japan from New York.
I think maybe she wanted
to be closer to you...
since you got along so
well when you were students.
Perhaps all along she was hoping...
that you would come to her rescue.
You're going overboard.
First of all, I'm just a novice.
I'm not so good that people
can depend on my help.
Yeah, right.
Pretty humble, considering
you're a psychologist.
You don't even understand
the feelings of your colleague.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Just forget it. It's nothing.
Tamine here... I see.
Another project?
Right. Let's get on it.
Of course.
Like lovers!
What are you talking about?!