You've got to be kidding!
Our college has no problems that
warrant an investigation!
There's no need for such frivolity!
It's up to us...
to decide whether it's necessary.
We've received information
that one of your students...
works for an escort service.
Moreover, the clientele
aren't even students.
Even if there were such a problem...
we would address it ourselves!
We don't want you to come here.
Actually, we're already here.
What the heck's going on?
I'm with the Special Office of
the Education Committee.
Sara Iijima. At your service!
Sara Iijima is a brilliant
psychotherapist.
She opens the doors to the
souls of troubled students...
and confronts their anxieties.
She probes deep into their insecurities.
To challenge their demons...
she encourages them to
use their own strengths...
so they can understand
and overcome their problems.
Sara uses the psychofeed method...
to help them unlock their true selves.
The lesson is over.
Today, Sara is at a college
with such troubled students.
And together with her
assistant, Tamine...
she'll save the souls of the students.
A student at this reputable college...
prostituting herself for an
escort service! What a shame!
Here she comes! Our Kranke.
Come on, Tamine.
Don't say things like Kranke.
Why not? It's German for patient.
It's the proper term, isn't it?
I just don't like it.
Sorry.
Yuri Saito, freshman at Saint
Sakuragaoka College.
Works for the escort service every day.
Sure is a cutie.
White! Thought so!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Just that white's proper.
She certainly doesn't
seem out of the ordinary.
Hard to believe she's a prostitute.
Appearances can be deceiving
with women these days.
That's strange. That bra's
way too big for her.
It'd be just about
right for you though.
Yup, perfect fit.
Remember what you're here for?
Yes!
Oh no!
Off to work she goes.
Did she do this?!
One... two... three... four...
five... six... seven... eight...
It's so good.
Oh yeah!
Yes! Yes!
That was delicious!
Why would she do it?
She looks so innocent.
Couldn't be for the money.
I wonder why.
What would make her do it?!
Panties!
Sara! Should we go in?
Let's leave that to the police.
I'm more interested in
that incident with the bra.
What could have gotten into her?
Maybe it's her small bust.
She could have a complex.
She's not exactly small.
Couldn't be that.
There must be another reason.
Telling me to come to
the gym, wearing gym clothes...
I'm not into weird fetishes.
Really? Well, sorry.
You're my client?
That's right.
Alright. I don't have
a problem with that.
Let's have fun.
Yes, let's get to know each other.
Deep into our souls.
You really know what you're doing.
No one knows a woman's
body like a woman.
My God!
Not there! That's my
most sensitive part!
There's nothing to be
shy about. Just let go.
If you keep licking me so hard...
I don't know what...
You mustn't feel a thing.
Not a thing.
You're a psychotherapist.
You're her counselor.
It feels so good!
This is terrible!
I shouldn't be doing this!
I'm supposed to be helping her!
Sara's taking a long time.
Shouldn't take her that long!
Good. I'll make you cum
over and over again.
How come your breasts are so big?
Know what?
Big breasts like these...
I hate them!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
I'm gonna slash those big tits of yours!
Sara!
Tamine...
I've done something awful.
Sara! Are you okay?
Sure you're alright?
Positive. Don't worry.
Go home.
Okay.
Her eyes told me she
was in need of help.
I lost control.
I was overcome by my feelings.
I'm a failure as a psychotherapist!
How can I have a
crisis in this racket!
What an ungodly hour!
It's Dr. Chang!
Professor! Huh?
Down here!
My beloved student!
Been a long time!
David Chang! We haven't met
since my Ph.D. At Stunford!
I'm here for the international
psychotherapy conference.
Professor, your hand!
Never mind that.
Since I'm here, I thought I'd see
my best student's boobs...
I mean face.
Your "best student"?
I'm afraid I can't live
up to that anymore.
I see.
A great psychotherapist like
you made your first mistake.
I've lost confidence and
I'm thinking of just quitting.
What?!
What are you being so childish for?
You can't worry about
every little mistake you make.
That student's troubles run
much deeper than your own.
And the person to help
her is Sara Iijima!
Only your psychofeed
method can help her now!
Professor...
Think back, Sara.
Remember when you
were studying at Stunford?
Back then, you had
a real breast complex.
You were so pessimistic.
You couldn't reach your full potential.
I helped you overcome that complex.
We used my psychotherapy
method to explore your mind.
Even as a child,
you had large breasts...
and you were almost
raped by a breast fiend.
Fortunately, a policeman
came and saved you.
Before you knew it,
you had subconsciously...
repressed the memory of the assault.
But you were left
with a breast complex.
Thanks to you, I was able
to overcome my complex.
I studied the psychotherapy
methods you developed...
so that I could help others like me.
Think back to that enthusiasm.
Don't think of them as
sick people or patients.
But as individual people.
Yes, Professor!
What's most important is
to confront that person's soul.
You have a certain
compassion with people.
People recognize that in you.
What matters most with our
philosophy is a warm heart.
Yes, Professor.
Right, a warm heart.
Let them feel your heart.
Thank you, Professor!
As long as you understand.
Let's start with the secret of
psychofeed therapy.
What?
The secret?
I thought I was gonna die.
Watch me closely and do as I do.
Right. Close... open... close... open...
Close... open... close... open.
That's right, now open wider!
Professor. Sure you're not
enjoying this too much?
Concentrate! Forget my gaze,
or you won't grasp the secret!
One, two, three, four.
Put your hips into it! Yes, that's it!
Good! Hold it right there!
The secret Omote Sando!
You again.
You got it.
This time we can have a good
time and nobody will interrupt.
I thought I told you
I hate breasts like yours.
Doesn't matter.
I can't forget your technique.
Do it to me again,
just the same way.
Only this time, forget the Exacto knife.
Alright. I'll give you the full
treatment this time.
Follow me.
In here.
No one will bother us here.
This is well thought-out.
Hurry!
That's good!
Oh, that's good!
I can't let her get to me!
The secret Omote Sando psychofeed
therapy!
Feel the sexual energy from my body!
Okay Yuri.
Now it's my turn to give you pleasure.
That feels so good.
I've never felt this way before.
Oh my God!
This is the moment for my psychotherapy.
Yuri, why do you hate big breasts?
Nobody likes me because
my breasts are small.
Everybody hates me.
Nobody hates you.
Besides, your breasts aren't small.
They are. That's why they hate me.
Large breasts are a symbol of maternity.
You must have been traumatized.
We're going back in time now, Yuri.
How old are you, Yuri?
Three.
Daddy, you promised
to take me to Playland.
Sorry, Yuri. I have to work today.
It's Parents Day at kindergarten today.
You're coming, right?
I have to work today. Sorry Yuri.
Daddy hates me.
He doesn't think I'm pretty.
Or is it because I killed my mommy?
She didn't receive enough
love when she was a child.
She subconsciously blames
herself for her mother's death.
That's why she feels she's hated.
Her disdain for large
breasts is actually...
an expression of the feelings
for the mother that left her.
She prostitutes herself as punishment...
in an act of self-destruction.
By getting strangers to
show her physical love...
she tries to make up for
the lost love of her parents.
Yuri, your mother died
because she was sick.
You didn't kill her.
And your father doesn't hate you.
When your mom died, he was
so upset he couldn't think.
You're wrong!
Both your parents loved you
when you were born.
There are no parents
who don't love their children.
You should know that.
What a cutie!
Hi sweetheart!
I'm your mommy!
You're finally here!
I'm so glad!
I'm so glad you're here!
We love you so much!
More than anyone!
You're my jewel!
You're our precious little jewel.
See Yuri?
Remember how blessed you
were when you were born?
Mommy.
Thank you mommy and daddy!
The lesson is over.
Those are expensive.
Sure you wanna do that?
I'm sure. I don't need it.
What?
You have such big breasts.
Sorry.
I love women with large breasts.
Uh, have we met before?
No.
Well, goodbye.
She doesn't seem to remember you.
I erased her memory of me.
That reminds me. How about
we teach that Dean a lesson?
Good idea.
I'm telling you to do whatever it takes!
I just want you to get rid of those two!
I'm running this college to make money!
If word gets out, this college
will lose its standing!
I just got all of that on tape!
You're a failure as an educator!
I suggest you submit
your resignation, Dean.
Wait!
See you!
I'll change my ways!
Don't tell anyone about this!
I'll pay anything! How much?
How much do you want?
My, my! That Dean never gives up!
This is what I think of people like him.
Here goes.
Oh, that feels good! I'm coming!
On to the next job!
Oh no! I'll have to explain this.
She did it again! My best disciple!
The secret Omote Sando!