Oh, that's what it is.
Professor Kayama, good bye!
Good bye.
G... good bye...
I know... I know what you
women think about me.
He's so depressing.
I bet he has no friends.
He probably has a thing for his mommy.
Is he a virgin?
You guys hate me, and I hate you.
I hate my job as a professor, too.
But the world doesn't
turn the way I want it to!
I wou1d have rather stayed at
the university as a researcher.
C... campus is closed already...
Punishment: Part I
I'm sorry I'm late.
Come in.
Yes.
Sir, you're so impatient.
I can't help it. You made me wait
three days. Don't be so mean.
I just bumped into the weirdo,
so I'm not really in the mood.
Weirdo?
Professor Kayama.
Oh, him. You shouldn't call him a weirdo.
He's very brilliant, and he graduated
from a first rate university.
If he were brilliant he wouldn't
be a college professor.
He'd be working at a famous corporation
or a university, as a researcher.
True, but society needs
people like him, too.
Like someone to close up the building?
Exactly. You have to take good care
of the people who do tedious work.
N-no.
Stop.
This is embarrassing.
I should take off my glasses...
Keep them on. It's very sexy.
You said you're not in the mood, but listen
to how wet you are. You're so young.
No, sir...
Sir...
Your pussy is getting hotter and more
sensitive. Look, my fingers go right in.
Stop, don't say things like that.
You're so young and full of life! Your
pussy won't let go of my fingers!
Sir, you're so good! It feels so amazing!
Finger me more!
Does it feel that good?
Yes, it feels great. When you touch
me there, it makes me feel so good.
What am I to do with you? You're
going to prune my fingers.
Oh stop it, sir.
Yeah. This is amazing. Maki,
I'm going to give you an A+!
Sir, this feels so good.
More! Fuck me more!
Yes. This is amazing!
Your pussy is so tight!
Oh yes! Your cock is all the way in
me! I can feel it all the way inside!
Yes, sir! it feels so good!
I can't hold it anymore. I'm going to cum!
Me... me too! I can't anymore!
I'm going to cum. I'm going to cum!
I want you to cum in me!
They're all scumbags, even the
ones that are paying attention.
Who knows what they're really
doing behind closed doors?
Hey you guys!
Y-yes!?
What are you guys doing there?
Campus is closed already.
Hurry up and go home.
Yes sir.
But, uh...
Is there something in the window?
Well, umm... Can we keep
this a secret between us?
OK.
Hinata...
Rieko, you're so sensitive.
You're wet already.
No...
Look, your nipples are so perky.
You're such a dirty woman.
Hinata, don't say things like that.
You're so adorable.
You're getting so wet.
Your underwear is soaked.
No, Hinata. I'm so embarrassed.
You want it so bad. You're such a pervert.
Not yet! You can't cum
yet. We've just started.
No! Hinata, don't be so mean. Please!
I'm not being mean.
I'll show you a great time.
No...
Your pussy tastes so good. The more I
eat your pussy, the more cum comes out.
It's amazing. It feels so good.
Oh Rieko, you're getting all the
pleasure. I want you to eat me out too.
OK.
It feels great. You're really good, Rieko.
Thank you.
No, don't do that, Hinata. If
you do that I'm going to cum.
No Rieko. Don't stop.
Let's cum together.
OK.
Hinata. Hinata, I...
I'm going to cum. I'm going to cum.
Me too. I'm going to cum too.
H-hey!
is it mine?
No you dumbass! Run!
Hey!
Umm... I...
Professor!
Umm... And you are...?
I'm Miki Watase, a first year student.
I'm not as smart as my sis,
so I doubt you'd know me.
Huh?
There's something I'd
like to talk to you about.
S-sure.
So you came to me?
Well, you're the youngest
physics professor in the school.
I figured you'd know much more about
recent information on grad schools.
That's true, but still...
When I was in elementary school
I read Hideki Yukawa's work, and
decided I wanted to study physics.
Professor, please. Will you help
me so I can pursue my dream?
Sure. Your senior year isn't for a
while, but I'll help you as best as I can.
Thank you very much!
Um, professor?
Huh?
You can have some of
my lunch if you'd like.
I just ate during the last break and I'll
eat again after club activities, so...
Thanks, I appreciate it.
Professor, can I ask you something weird?
Huh?
Is it true what everybody
is gossiping about?
Well... About the peeping...?
Huh!?
It's not true right?
Of course it isn't!!
It’s my job to close up the campus.
I just happened to walk by and they
thought I was peeping on them.
Of course you weren't. Thank goodness.
To be honest, I was thinking that if it
were true, it'd be bad to seek advice
from you about my education.
I didn't know this school had
such a good student like her.
She's a great young woman who's
seriously thinking about her education.
Physics 1B Report
Composition of the Doppler Effect with Reflectors
Class A Maki Watase
This is a fair score I gave you.
The quality of the research papers from
the entire class was pretty low this time.
There were only a few
students who got an A-.
I'm not saying 1 want an A. I'm
asking if I can do a make-up until
I can raise my grade to an A-?
I can't give you special treatment like
that. Just work hard for your finals.
With your grades, I don't
think one low score on your
research paper is going to hurt.
That's not the point! It’s a matter of pride!
I can't be satisfied with
myself with such a low score!
I can't do much about it, though.
I'm not asking you to change my grade.
I'm saying I'll rewrite my paper, and
I want you to grade me on that.
M... Maki.
Please, professor?
Hello? This is Kayama.
Yes.
Really?
At Professor Masaoka's
lab from the fourteenth?
Yes! Thank you so much!
Yes, we’ll discuss the details later.
Yes.
Oh no. Thank you so much!
Professor Kayama is going to quit.
Sachie. You know you're the
only one that's upset about this.
You're such a weird girl.
Everyone hates him at school,
so I bet he's ecstatic to take off!
Hey guys.
Why don't we have a going
away party for that professor?
A party?
There's no need to have a going away
party for such a lame pervert like him.
Ditto!
He had a boner when I got close to him.
He was trying his hardest to hide it though.
I just thought of a great idea for his party.
Woo-hoo! I only have one more week
left of babysitting those fucking brats!
In ten days, I'll be a
researcher at a university lab!
Huh?
Yes?
Who's there?
It’s Maki. I'm sorry about
the research paper earlier. I
wanted to apologize to you.
Oh.
Hold on, let me open the...
Coming in!
Professor, hurry up!
L-ladies...
Sachie, you sit here.
Oh, thanks.
Do you think we have enough booze?
There's more than enough.
And? And?? What kind of research
are you going to be doing
at the university, Professor?
Are you going to get a
Nobel Prize in the future?
Oh, I doubt that.
At the moment, I'll be happy
if I can just work on projects
with topics that interest me.
That's so cool! You're starting
to talk like a real scientist!
Sachie, pour him some booze.
Here you go Professor!
No. I’ve had enough.
I guess you're someone that
has other things to do than
deal with students like us.
Oh, come on. I’ve always felt
guilty about my boring classes.
That's not true, Professor!
Oh, come on. I’ve always felt
guilty about my boring classes.
That's not true, Professor!
Yeah!
We're being honest!
Now that I’ve sat down and had
a conversation with them, they're
actually nice, good women.
Maybe I misunderstood them.
Come on, Professor! Drink up!
Yeah.
I want to drink too!
Give me a little bit!
Huh? Oh no. Am I drunk already?
OK, let’s do this.
This doesn't have much of a
shock factor, especially his dick.
Sachie, why don't you play with it.
You like the guy, don't you?
Yeah.
Just do it!
Whoa!
I think it'd be faster if you
do it with your mouth.
Or...
Maybe she wants to take her
time to play with his dick.
What?
It was a joke. He's not going to wake
up from the drug until tomorrow
morning, so there's no need to hurry.
Wow, Sachie. You're a
lot bolder than I thought.
If Kayama were awake,
he'd be crying with joy!
I bet he'd go limp with shock!
Hey!
Good morning!
Morning.
This is so lame.
It’s from our first class.
I brought my lunch and...
Yeah, I saw it.
That's got to suck.
...That professor...
We felt really bad about the peeping thing.
You ended up taking all the blame.
Oh, don't worry about that anymore.
Anyway, if you know something,
I'd like you to tell me.
Maybe I'm imagining it, but I think
the way the students look at me is
completely different than before.
Did something happen? I can't
think of anything, myself.
Well...
25 year old virgin!
How
pathetic
Tiny
stub
of a
penis
Apparently there's a
bunch of them circulating.
Professor, are you all right?
This is so... so wretched!
Can something this malicious be forgiven?
They need to be punished!
I'll do it!
They're all going to feel the
wrath of a scorned teacher!
Time limit is five minutes. If you don't cum
it's your loss. You're not getting a refund.
Arisa, this is amazing!
Sir... Why do you like
it so much down there?
A male dog licks a bitch's anus.
It’s the natural thing to do.
I can't anymore... I'm going to cum.
Really, Professor?
Professor Kayama. Professor Kayama.
Professor, I'm cumming!
Hinata...
You're so good.
Rieko, does this feel good?
It feels so good.
Me too.
You took pictures of us?
No! Forgive me! I'm sorry!
No! You women defamed
me with those pictures!
That's why I'm doing the same to you!
Please, don't do this. if you do, I won't
be able to come to school anymore.
I won't be able to marry anyone, either.
And that's not all. Your father is the
CEO of a famous corporation, right?
There are a lot of people
hoping for his downfall.
Meaning, there are a ton of people
who wou1d kill for those pictures.
You won't be able to come
to school or stay at home!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
From now on, I'll listen and pay
attention. I'll be a good student.
Please, give me those pictures.
That's a wise decision. Now, it’ll depend
on how much you can satisfy me.
You're pretty used to this.
But it's going to take a lot more
to heal my wounded heart.
Put your heart and soul into sucking my
dick! Like when you fuck those girls.
Yes.
Put your heart and soul into sucking my
dick! Like when you fuck those girls.
Yes.
That's more like it. But
we've only just started.
Come on! Take it!
Suffer. Suffer more!!
OK, I'm going to cum! Take it!
How is it? isn’t it better
to fuck a guy than a girl?
And if we work hard, we’ll have a
cute baby that'll look just like us.
N... no... I don't want to get pregnant.
I have a clear shot
where we're connected.
Your pussy is loving it and it's
not letting go of my cock.
Wow, this is amazing. You're soaked.
You're twitching inside. You're
about to cum, aren't you?
No! Please stop! Professor, I'm sorry.
No! I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!!
Professor, I... I can't anymore.
I have to do something like this to make it
a punishment for a lazy woman like you.
Professor, not there!
No, please! Please Professor! Please!!
Yeah! it’s nice and tight. You should
be relieved, you're not going
to get pregnant this way.
It hurts. Professor, it hurts!
How do you like it? Aren't you honored
that you have my dick up your ass?
Noooo!
This time I'll cum where you like it.
No! Stop! Professor, no!
There's no need to be shy!
Take it!
It hurts! It really hurts!!
Oh really? You want it that much? You'd
better beg if you want me to pull out!
Well? if you don't hurry
it's going to be too late!
Give it to me! I want you to
give me all of your cum!
Now suck it.
I'll cum in your mouth.
Professor, please forgive me.
No!
All right! I'm going to cum!
Swallow it!
No, you have to swallow all of it!
One down.