Yeah, it's nice and tight.
Is this the first time you've been fucked up
the ass? You look like you're enjoying it.
It hurts, Professor.
Not there...
Please stop...
All right. Then suck it.
I'll cum in your mouth.
Professor, please forgive me.
No!
OK. I'm going to cum!
Swallow it!
No, swallow all of it!
I'm just a mere physics professor.
True, my personality is a bit
somber and perhaps a little nerdy.
The students and fellow
professors all look down on me.
But I’ve been shy ever since 1 was
a kid. What do you want me to do?
I take responsibility for jobs that
I don't even want to do. I’ve been
working hard as a professor!
But...
It was so evil!
Can something that malicious be forgiven?
Those women severely defamed my name!
Those women deserve to be punished!
Before they enter society...
Before I leave the school...
They need to have an educational
correction to reflect what they did!
So that they understand
other people’s pain!
They need to be punished.
It... It hurts. Stop.
Please, take it out! 1t hurts!
One down.
Punishment: Part II
BROADCAST ROOM
Welcome.
I'm Kazutoshi Omori, second year.
Are you sure fifty bucks is OK?
Time limit is five minutes. Even if you
don't cum you're not getting a refund.
Arisa, this is amazing!
Make sure to tell me when
you're going to cum.
I'm going to cum!
BROADCAST ROOM
Thanks for your business. Come again!
What a great angry face. It's really cute.
When your angry expression turns
to pain, then to humiliation and to
ecstasy, I'll have it all recorded.
Feel these huge knockers.
This is the mouth that earns you
your spending money? You’ll
have to show me later.
Anyway, look at this! You may be a virgin,
but you're like a fountain down there.
I heard that you're a
masturbating machine at home.
You want to stay a virgin
until you're married?
You're pretty prissy for a woman
that skips class to suck cocks
for spending money, Arisa.
But I bet your boyfriend isn't satisfied
with just blow-jobs. Sex is important.
Oh yeah. Hinata told me this.
Sachie felt bad for your boyfriend.
When your boyfriend asked her, she felt so
bad she agreed to put out on your behalf.
I guess you're the last to know.
Well, that's a female friendship for you!
OK, why don't we get started.
You don't mean to use that, do you?
I was thinking this one's smaller,
so it wouldn’t hurt as much.
Better than this one, right?
You're a member of the broadcasting
club and you're violating the broadcast
room! You need to be punished!
No! No! Stop! No!
Here we go!
I'm begging you...
Please stop...
The time is now after six o’clock.
C... campus will be closing.
All students still on campus...
...should finish up and close up.
Make sure to head straight home.
Ow! Please excuse me...
Students should swiftly go home.
I... I repeat...
TENNIS
CLUB
Campus will be closing.
Miki!
I'm going to head home.
Oh. I'm going to clean the locker
room a little, and then go home.
OK. Then can you make sure you lock up?
Sure. I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye-bye!
Yamamoto
I wonder what this is?
Professor!
Please leave the campus.
What a shitty broadcaster.
It hurts...
I can't anymore...
Help me...
Home Economics
Room
It feels so good, Professor.
Yes...
Professor, I'm going to
cum. I'm gonna cum.
I'm... I'm...
You shouldn’t be here...
Campus closed a while ago.
You don't even have the
lights on. It’s dark already.
Weren't you listening
to the announcement?
No, umm... this is...
Well, I was able to get
good footage of you.
Guess what I heard!
Apparently you masturbated and came in
front of your friends when I was drugged.
You're such a pervert.
And you took pictures on top of that.
No, that was Maki...!
Well, that doesn't matter now.
You look innocent, but I hear
you're a big whore underneath.
Look at you masturbating
with my pictures.
Is that what it is? You want to
have sex with me that bad?
But before we do...
P... Professor. It’s hot! It’s hot! Stop!
A cake needs its candles, right?
Professor.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll do anything, so please forgive me...
You seem to have earned your
lesson, so I'll take the candles out.
Professor.
I'm going to savor my cake now.
Look, it's your favorite. Lick it.
I wonder how this will taste?
Professor.
I'm... I'm going to cum!
Professor. I'm going to...
Give it to me. I want your cock inside me.
I can't wait any longer.
Professor. Please...
No!
Are you still in love with me even
after what I’ve done to you?
It was our fault to begin with.
And I...
I’ve been in love with you for so long.
Professor. Don't hate me.
I'll do anything.
So please...
Come to the cheerleading
club tomorrow afternoon.
If you help me, I'll fuck your brains out.
Yes!
Ok... now make me cum.
Professor, um...
Huh? What's wrong?
You're not yourself today.
Well, I...
Oh, that's right. I haven't told you yet.
Huh?
I'm actually leaving the
school after tomorrow.
Huh?
I got a job working at the university lab.
I'm sorry. This all happened so suddenly.
But even after I leave the school, I'll still
help you with your future education.
I made a promise to you.
Thank you very much.
W... what's wrong?
Oh it's nothing. I just...
I was just thinking how much
I'll miss you when you're gone.
You're welcome to visit me
at the university anytime.
The university has a lot of
resources and research papers
that this school doesn't have.
And it’ll be beneficial for you to talk
to the other professors yourself.
Yes, thank you.
I still have to pack up, so...
Oh yeah! Didn't you have something
you wanted to talk to me about?
N... no... This is enough for today.
OK. I'll see you later.
This has to be some kind of mistake.
It’s probably someone's nasty prank.
But who would pull a
terrible prank like this?
This handwriting...!
I'm coming in.
Hinata, you're late.
S... Sachie. Why are you here?
You and 1 are going to give a
lesbian show for Professor.
What?
Sachie is ready whenever you are.
Yes.
Start it.
Yes...
Hinata, your kiss is so
sweet and delicious.
Really...? Thanks...
No! Not there!
Yes.
Yes!
I lost. The reward is all yours, Hinata.
Huh?
No. Stop! Don't cum in me! Stop!
You've been screwing
around with a bunch of guys.
If you get pregnant, you wouldn’t
have a cue who the father is.
No. I'm begging you. Don't cum in me!
Loud bitch. Sachie, shut her up!
Yes, Professor.
Hinata, Professor is giving you a reward
by cumming in you. You shouldn’t refuse.
W-what are you talking
about? I'll get pregnant.
It’s Professor's child. I'm so jealous.
Sachie... You're...
insane...
Professor, your cum tastes so good.
It’s so good. Professor...
S... Sachie.
Professor, me next.
I want you to pour your hot
cum into my pussy. Please...
Yes.
Hinata...
Ow. What was that for!?
I said don't come talking to us!
Do you have any idea what we had
to go through because of you?
Don't ever show your
face in front of us again!
Sachie. What's going on?
Don't worry. Today it's your turn, Maki.
Huh?
Hey, wait!
What's going on?
You want to know?
Why don't I tell you all about it?
This question...
Hmm. Maki, please solve this question.
Y-yes.
is something wrong?
N-nothing.
I'm sorry.
Huh? Did you hear something?
Not really.
Did I imagine that?
They're going to find us
if you moan out loud.
P-Professor...
I'm sorry...
Please stop...
Please stop this...
Not yet. OK, moving on.
No!
Look how wet you are in a place like this.
No... S-stop.
Don't make a sound.
No... Stop... Please.
Maki, does it feel good? I'll
make you feel much better.
No! I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Not there!!
Here?
I... I'm going to cum...
How do you like the medicine 1 prepared?
It was only a finger, but wasn't it amazing?
I thought regular sex wouldn’t
do much for you because you're
used to getting fucked so much.
Professor, rub the medicine
on me and fuck me.
When we start our new life together,
I'll use it on you all the time.
But before that, 1 need
to teach Maki a lesson.
Stop. Please forgive me.
Where'd all your spirit go?
You're the last one, so I want to make you
cum over and over until you can't stand.
I want to give you so much
pleasure that you'll lose your mind.
He's right, Maki.
You won't be able to walk normally
for about two or three days.
Why don't we continue?
N... no... Stop... Please... Stop... No...
Yes Professor.
No...
Sis, what's the meaning of this!
This is your handwriting. How could
you pull such a horrible prank?
Explain yourself!
Miki.
Sis, stop crying and explain
to me what's going on.
Hinata, Arisa, Sachie and I...
We were all raped by that professor!
We did it so we could get back at him.
It can't be... Professor?
I'm going to campus!
Dummy.
Physics Preparation
Room
Professor!
Physics Preparation
Room
Oh... You're Miki, right?
Why are you here, Sachie?
W... where's the Professor?
Professor is out getting some stuff.
What did you need at a time
like this? You're so flustered...
What about you? Why are you here?
Have you calmed down?
Yes.
Anyway, are you sure the
Professor didn't do that?
At east, he hasn't done that to me.
But... My sister was crying so much.
And I can't believe that the
pictures were superimposed.
If Maki is telling the truth, I'm
sure Professor had his reasons.
He's such a tender person.
Yes... But if it's true,
he's committed a crime.
How slow...
Yes, he's really taking his time.
No, I'm talking about the medicine.
Huh?
I wasn't raped.
I'm in love with Professor.
M... my body is...
I can do anything for Professor.
Seems like it's starting to work.
I didn't want to do something like this
to you, but you left me no choice.
We already put this behind us. It’s
your fault for bringing it back up.
I don't want any more problems with this.
So I'll need something to blackmail
you with, to keep you quiet.
How is it? Are you getting used to it?
This medicine will paralyze your mouth and
body, but will also keep you conscious.
You’ll be feeling the
most amazing pleasure.
Professor, the camcorder is ready.
All right. Let's start then.
Don't worry, Miki. We’ll be nice
and gentle. Right, Professor?
No...
Don't worry, Miki. We’ll be nice
and gentle. Right, Professor?