The advanced genetic engineering was
affecting the politic and show business.
The Gene Corporation gathers
superior genes to create superior beings.
We, the Andromaid Aki
series, were created by Gene...
...to procure these superior genes.
Our method is to flash
freeze men's vital essence...
...in the storage receptacles in our
bodies and bring it back to headquarters.
We've been programmed with various
techniques to accomplish our duty.
And we occasionally do jobs for
promotional purposes, such as this.
Do you, Aki, swear to give
your body to our participants?
I do.
Please color me your color, Master.
Master...
Please...
My name is Aki.
I'm an Andromaid.
Serving my master is my duty.
Please color me white
with your semen, Master.
Semen hair ornaments...
Semen rouge...
Semen necklace...
Semen earrings...
I'm wearing your semen...
I swear to give my life to you!
Master!
I, Aki...
I, Aki, swear to...
I swear to give my life to you.
This bathing suit...
My master gave it to me...
...but it's not that cute,
and it's too small.
My master is going to
teach me how to swim today.
I'm looking forward to it!
He thinks I can't swim.
So he's going to
teach me hand in hand...
It's going to be fun!
I'll pretend I'm drowning...
...and cling to him.
"Aki, are you all right?"
Oh, Master, thank you for saving me!
That's my plan!
Let's get changed!
What's this?
This is so tight.
And it's making me feel funny...
Oh no...
I can almost see my nipples.
Master...
I'm going to come...
I'm coming!
Master...
Is Aki a bad girl?
Aki can be upgraded to
suit Master's desires.
Master, I have attached the part.
This...
...is kind of embarrassing.
When I touch it, it makes
me feel very lonely...
My body is hot...
I'm getting hot.
Wow...
It feels so...
Does Master feel like this?
I can't...
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm going to change your cartridge.
Wait...
I have to confirm its function.
Aren't these parts amazing?
Milk comes out when I come.
Let me test them with
the new part of yours.
It's going in...
I can feel it going in!
This is just the beginning.
Oh no...
It's going in deeper!
The real effect of the red cartridge...
...is still to come.
If you do that...
...I'm going to break!
Don't worry.
The limiter is set just a
little higher than normal.
It's so big.
You're new, aren't you?
I can teach you all sorts of things.
Good, I'll make you feel even better.
I want to come.
Please let me come!
You can't.
Not unless I say so.
We have the same frequency.
I can send you the command
to come anytime I want.
I have total control over your body...
But we have to study how we
can make our masters feel good first.
Yes, harder...
Pinch my nipples harder.
I'm going to come soon...
I can't hold it anymore!
No.
I just came...
This is where the fun starts.
I'm going to...
I'm going to come again.
It's okay...
Let it come.
I'm coming!