My name is Aki.
I'm an Andromaid.
If I were human, I would be nineteen.
I would be in college.
When I go shopping for my master...
...I see girls in their school blazers.
They are talking about boys or
gossiping about their teachers.
It looks like a lot of fun.
But it is a world far from mine...
All I'm allowed to do is
to please my master.
My duty is to be a sex
slave to my master...
...24 hours a day, every day.
My name is Aki, I am at
your service, starting today.
Pleased to meet you.
Excuse me.
D-Down there?
Right away.
Excuse me.
I-It's getting hard.
I'm sorry, Master.
I promise I will swallow next time.
My eyes sting!
Yes!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Welcome home, sir.
Oh, you have brought guests?
Excuse me.
Here you go.
I'm going to wash down there now.
I will be very, very careful.
Good morning, Master.
I look forward to
serving your penis today.
Please come in my
mouth this morning...
...and let me swallow your
load of white semen.
After my morning greeting, I pull
out Master's morning erection...
...and give it a soft kiss.
From the tip of his
penis, to his erect shaft...
...and to his balls...
I gently hold his penis and
lick it all over with my tongue.
As I look at Master's satisfied face...
...I take his penis even
deeper in my mouth.
And while bobbing my head
between his legs, I tell Master...
Master's penis tastes good.
Master's penis tastes so good.
Of course, with his penis in my mouth,
he can barely understand me...
But I know he loves
watching me work hard.
With all my courage, I ask Master...
Does it feel good?
Your semen...
Please give me your semen.
Master's semen is for me...
Please give me a lot
of Master's hot semen.
Master...
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Master.
T-Those are...
No...
Please don't...
Forgive me!
N-No!
Please don't...
You are a bad girl, you are being
punished and you are getting turned on.
N-No, I'm not...
You want these, don't you?
No, please forgive me...
You are going to break me!
What's going on here?
They're hard.
You are making my nipples hard...
Again...
You are making my nipples hard.
It feels good!
My nipples feel good...
Stay still!
Welcome.
I am the maid of the house.
My name is Aki.
I'm here to entertain you today.
I may be inexperienced,
but I'll do my best to serve you.
Thank you very much for coming today.