Please punish me.
Kowaremono II - Fragile Hearts II
Heaven-2
Otakki Sasaki
Golden Boy
Otakki Sasaki Otakki Sasaki
You want me to do it?
It is finally time
for my lifelong research to bloom!
Yeah, but...
What, are you discontent with that?
You will fight evil for justice
as Super Andmaid Aki!
Super Andmaid, like...
Here I go!
Professor, you sure there aren't any quirks?
Leave it to me!
Kowaremono II - Fragile Hearts II
Heaven-2
I'm Aki! An Andmaid.
Actually, I should scrap by now...
...but Professor claimed me,
and I live here a his research facility.
He is a very kind person, but...
...when it comes to his research,
his screws are a bit loose...
...but I'm grateful that he picked me up,
so I'll do my best to serve him.
Is this...
Aki! Come over here!
Yes!
I'm coming!
I'm coming right now!
What is this?
Forty-eight years of toil...
...much research, it's finally done.
The fruit of all modern science!
Don't worry, just put that on your left wrist!
Yes!
Like this?
Professor! It stuck to me on its own
and now won't come off!
I made that bracelet...
...so that unless I say the keyword,
it won't come off.
No way!
Please, say the keyword, Professor!
Listen up, Aki! Raise the bracelet high
in the air and repeat the following!
Here comes Aki!
Protector of Justice;
evil is unforgivable!
I will defend world peace!
Super Andmaid, Aki!
I'm supposed to say that?
Shut up and just say it!
Yes. Like this?
Here comes Aki!
Protector of Justice; evil is unforgivable!
I will defend world peace!
Super Andmaid, Aki!
This is! But it's a bit risquй.
That bracelet utilizes a highly rare element
as its source of energy...
...and allows you to transform
by reconstructing your molecular structure!
And then? What happens after I transform?
Don't tell me that all I can do is transform.
So then what?
I get to fly, gain superhuman strength...
...and shoot beams from my eyes, right?
It's not impossible for you to do that, but...
What am I supposed to do?
For that, I need to do some modifications...
Modifications?
Dick! Clit! Ass!
Professor...
Well, simple modifications like that
will only take 2 to 3 days.
All right, that being that,
time to get back to work!
Professor! I'm cheering you on!
Okay! Leave it up to me!
I don't have much faith, but this looks fun.
Super Andmaid.
Professor. I brought you a late-night snack.
You shouldn't push yourself too hard.
It's bad for your health.
Good night.
All right! It's finished!
Congratulations, Professor!
Now, when you transform,
you should be able to display new abilities.
Thank you!
Do you best for the sake of world peace!
Yes, Professor! But I don't think
you'll be seeing me in action much.
Well, let's hope so.
I have prepared for you
instructional videos and data...
...so be sure to read them!
Yes!
Let's go, everyone!
Otakki Rangers, go!
Professor, is this really data?
Good morning, Professor!
Look at this, Aki!
"Robot Strikes Bank"...
Professor, this is...
It looks like there is someone
who is trying to disturb our peace.
Now is the time for Super Andmaid Aki
to rise to occasion!
But, don't you think the timing
is a bit too good?
You think so?
It's the drive-in down below!
Go! Super Andmaid Aki!
Yes!
Here comes Aki!
Protector of Justice, evil is unforgivable!
I will defend world peace!
Super Andmaid, Aki!
Then, I'm going!
I'm counting on you, Aki!
Yes!
Looks like she's gone.
Yes, Professor?
Just as planned, Aki has headed over there.
Proceed as planned.
Roger! I'm supposed to lure her
to the base, right?
Yes. Make sure you don't arouse her suspicion.
Understood.
You, wait up!
Those who dare disturb the world's peace
are unforgivable!
Super Andmaid Aki will serve you!
A bit strong, aren't we?
What should I do? It even has a gun.
That's right! This has some sort
of transceiver.
Professor! Professor!
The caller you have dialed
is currently unavailable.
I'm researching,
so please leave a message after the beep!
Professor!
Worse comes to worse,
actions speak louder than words!
Service Punch!
Incredible! I really am powered-up!
Your evil-doing days are numbered!
Hey, wait up! So can I!
Come back here!
So this their secret hideout!
All right.
Intruder alert!
All hands capture the intruder!
It looks like it's over for you.
Who are you?
The dead need not to know.
Super Andmaid Aki, so long!
Where?
Have you come to now?
There you are!
My, my, what a lively young girl we have here.
You still seem to have spunk,
so next why don't you have fun with this.
This is...
This.
This has no end.
Plus I feel kind of weak.
I'm losing my strength!
No! What are you?
No!
That's, no!
It has begun.
Stop it
No! Not there!
What is the matter, lively young girl?
You!
It looks like you have grown weak.
Slowly fall into the pits of ecstasy
in this underground dungeon.
Professor.
It has been a week since we captured Aki.
Yes.
Yeah, it feels good.
It feels so good!
It seems like the time is right.
That's good! Yes! Oh, yes!
Let's go!
You're...!
You look great.
How does it feel to be raped
for one week straight?
Your energy should have charged.
Why don't you transform into a super heroine?
Here comes Aki!
Protector of Justice; evil is unforgivable!
I will defend world peace!
Super Andmaid, Aki!
I won't let you have your way!
So you can at least transform.
But do you really think
that you can fight with that body, young lady?
That face is superb!
Now, I think it's time
for your body to serve me.
I will thoroughly enjoy this.
Yes!
My ass! My ass feels so good!
The same person who said
she was going to defend world peace...
...is in ecstasy being fingered in the ass.
What a shameful protector of justice!
What's wrong? What do you want me to do,
protector of justice?
Please, in my ass!
It looks like you don't understand your position.
Beg for it!
Say that you are a slutty whore!
I say that, I will defend world peace, yet...
...am a slutty whore who...
...loves it up the ass!
Please, please stick it in my ass!
Do you pledge your loyalty to me?
I will, for your dick. So please!
I'm your loyal slave.
All right.
Since you vowed your loyalty,
here is your reward.
Master!
My ass feels good. I'm so embarrassed.
It's over, Aki!
Professor!
Well, that was fun wasn't it Aki?
Why did you do this?
It's just my taste.
No way!
Hold it there!
What?
I won't forgive those who disturb
the world's peace!
What is this chick saying?
Hey, what're you doing?
Let go, hey!
Let go of us!
What the hell are you?
I defend world peace!
Please, both of you...
...rape me.
World peace feels good.