Polluted Earth and its environmental
hormones were feminizing men...
...decreasing the
sperm counts on men...
...the birth rates were declining.
There is a company
operating in the black market...
...buying and selling
genetically superior sperm.
The major talent production
company, Gene, is one of them.
In order to procure superior sperm...
...they initiated a secret project.
This city is the capital of this country.
But the people who control this
country don't live in the city.
They live on this little mountain,
away from the rest of the world.
And their children go to this school.
Sort of an elite academy.
People here have no poverty,
nor doubts about the future.
All they in their minds is...
...sexual desire...
In short, everybody here is oozing
with the pubescent desire for sex.
I too attend this school.
But I don't get it.
What's so good about
those crass bitches?
Hey, Amamiya.
We heard you parents
are out of the country again.
Y-Yeah...
You're all alone with
that old maid of yours.
Yeah.
You must be happy.
Why?
What's so funny?
Is she a good teacher?
You know what I'm talking about.
Huh?
Tell the truth.
Come on.
You know, sex-ed.
She does all sorts of things, right?
Does she jerk you off?
Does she suck your boner?
Oh, Kenichi, you pervert!
W-What are you saying?
Why would she do that?
I know you like old lady's pussy.
You're into old women, huh?
Why is that?
Because you're not
interested in normal chicks.
You don't even like high school girls.
That's not true!
You're getting really
defensive, so it must be true.
Kenichi, you're always so
quiet, but the things you do...
Cut it out already!
Is it better with an
old hag than yourself?
How should I know?
Why would I do it with a maid?
Give me a break.
I'm home.
I'm sorry!
Welcome home!
Um...
Is something the matter?
Who are you?
I'm Aki.
Aki?
I'm a maid sent from the agency.
I just started today.
But wait, what about our old maid?
Old maid?
Our house keeper.
Oh, I'm replacing her.
What do you mean?
Well...
Ken, you're home.
Yeah.
Wait, something's
wrong with the phone.
Mom?
Mom!
Damn, what the hell?
I'm in Germany.
The phone isn't working very well.
What's wrong?
This is horrible.
Ken, can you hear me, I have
to tell you something...
Our maid's daughter had a car
accident, so she took some time off.
We've had someone
come in to replace her, so...
With that static, he
probably can't hear you.
You're right...
Well, Ken, take care of yourself...
...and study hard.
We'll call again.
Mom...
My father is a politician
and my mother is an actress.
They are both so careless, it's a
miracle they maintain their jobs.
I bet they have no idea such a young
maid came to replace our old maid.
Anyway...
Um...
M-My mom told me
what happened, so...
Thank you!
Oh no!
I left the pot on the stove!
Oh my gosh!
She's pretty cute.
I must confess, she is my type.
Ouch!
Oh those are...
I'm sorry.
Have I done something wrong?
Am I hanging them wrong?
Did I wash them wrong?
No!
Um, I'm really sorry!
I must have done something wrong.
No, it's not...
I studied all about
housework, but I'm still new.
Please forgive me!
Um, that's not what I'm...
But...
No, you haven't done anything wrong.
It was my fault, I'm sorry.
You do it however you want.
Thanks.
Yes!
That kid is a virgin.
But he cannot resist Aki.
When Aki was created,
she had tears in her eyes.
She might have a bug
in her emotional system...
But she's doing fine.
I think it will happen tonight.
I sure hope so...
Is something wrong?
No, it's just that these
are all my favorites.
All of your likes and
dislikes are inputted.
Inputted?
I mean, I studied them all.
You're so...
Oh, nothing.
This looks great!
Please, eat lots!
This is good!
Poor Kenichi.
I heard that your parents are always busy,
so you've been alone since you were little.
I guess...
Kenichi...
Poor Kenichi.
It's fine, I'm used to it.
So don't cry.
I'm sorry, I'm such a crybaby.
It's okay, thanks for worrying about me.
Besides, now that you're
here, I'm not lonely at all.
I'm glad.
Aki...
I'm sorry...
I can't hold it anymore.
Kenichi...
Please wait.
No!
Please, wait.
Like a child clinging onto his mother...
...he buries his face deep in my breasts.
And he fondles my
breast through my clothes.
I can feel that my
nipples are getting hard.
His rough breathing is
stimulating my belly.
He is so cute.
No...
No more...
Why not?
I get up and straddle him...
And I begin to please him.
I take his penis out of his pants...
...and stroke his penis slowly.
What a cute penis...
Kenichi's penis...
As I stick my butt in the air...
...I look at his penis...
Penis...
Dick...
Good morning!
Good morning...
What are you...
Kenichi, you like looking at these?
I want to see yours.
Please masturbate.
Look at me...
...and stroke your penis hard.
Please masturbate.
Look at me...
...and stroke your penis hard.
Aki!
Touch me.
Touch my breasts.
My breasts...
My nipples...
My pussy...
They are all yours.
That hurts.
Sorry.
I like you.
I like you very much.
I like your penis, too.
I will do anything for you, Master.
Kenichi, does it feel good?
This is how my life with Aki began.
She let me have my
way whenever I wanted.
But Aki would never let
me cross the final line.
I want you to get bigger in my mouth...
...and give me your yummy come.
Semen.
Aki...
Did you swallow my...
Aki!
Aki.
Huh?
I love you, Aki.
Kenichi...
So please let me do it!
No!
I want to have sex with you.
No...
Anything but that.
Please.
Kenichi!
I'm sorry...
...but I don't want to leave you...
Oh my, what is going on?
What is going on?
It' been a week!
I'm sorry.
You're taking too long.
It always goes wrong at the end...
He comes too fast?
Y-Yes.
Don't make me tell you again...
Your job is to collect and
store his fresh superior sperm...
...in your manmade uterus.
You have the technique
programmed for that.
Yes...
Then suck it out before the kid spills it.
Y-Yes.
What's the matter, you
don't think you can do it?
What will happen once
I have fulfilled my duty?
We will collect you
and go to the next job.
We're backed up.
What will happen to Kenichi?
Nothing.
His old maid will come back, that's all.
Can't I stay with him?
I'm afraid we can't let you do that.
Just focus on completing your duty.
Got it?
Yes...
She wants to stay?
There is definitely a bug in her system.
Can you believe it?
Interesting...
Hey, Amamiya.
Now we know why you've
had so much energy lately.
What?
I saw her, the gracious beauty!
Even you'd prefer a young
girl to an old hag, huh?
But it looked like you were
having a spat with her today.
She's just a substitute for our maid.
Maybe we can study
together at your home.
What are you saying?
I thought we were friends.
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry, I wish I had
cake or something...
Don't worry about us.
That's right.
We've come to study with Amamiya.
That's right Aki, they're
not here to hang out
So don't worry.
But it's almost dinner time.
Aren't they staying?
Don't worry about it.
Don't be so cold.
Of course, we'd love to stay.
Great, I will make my best dish!
Stay as long as you like.
Thanks!
I'm sorry, but will you guys leave?
Why all of a sudden?
I want to study fellatio with her!
You said you'd introduce us to her.
I changed my mind.
Oh come on, my dick is ready to erupt!
That's not my problem.
Now go home!
Wait, she made us tea.
Let us finish our tea.
Have tea at your home!
I want to have tea that she made.
Hurry up.
Delicious...
It really is.
Amamiya, drink your
tea, it's getting cold.
Okay, but go home
when you finish your tea.
Oh?
Raining again?
Quiet!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
It's study time.
Kenichi!
Don't worry, he's out
cold on some pills.
His dad is a doctor.
It's a sedative, he'll be up in two hours
Stop it!
Don't be like that.
Just let us do what
Amamiya gets to do.
My relationship with
Kenichi isn't like that.
Liar.
It's true.
I like Kenichi, so...
So what?
I don't want to leave him,
so I won't have sex with him...
You don't want to leave him,
so you won't have sex?
That's weird.
Then why don't you show
us what you do with him?
Come on, put it in your mouth.
Use your tongue more.
Here's another one for you.
Hmm, Aki's pretty butt...
Good...
This is great.
She's great.
Aki's pussy...
Don't use your teeth.
Anything as long as it's not sex, right?
You feel great, Aki.
It's better than Kenichi's, isn't it?
Aki...
What, you're awake already?
A-Aki...
Look, Amamiya.
She loves sucking my dick.
And her pussy is mine!
I'm gonna come soon.
You better not spill it.
Aki...
Amamiya, thanks for
the great study session.
Did they hurt you?
After what they did to you,
you're worried about me?
Yes, because...
...I love you, Kenichi.
You love me?
Me?
Yes.
Why?
Then why won't you let me do it?
If you did, then I would...
I can't hold it!
I'm going to do it!
Your semen is special.
Kenichi!
Order from headquarters.
Your duty will be terminated tonight.
But I haven't...
Whether or not you procure the sperm,
we will come pick you up tomorrow.
But...
You've fallen in love with
your subject, haven't you?
You are defective.
Properly functioning Andromaids
do not love their subjects.
But I...
Tonight is your last night.
Aki!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Kenichi...
Make love to me.
Let's just go to sleep together.
Yes.
Aki...
Aki?
Aki!
Aki...
Aki, Aki...
Aki
Aki!