Who...is someone there?
W, well?
Nadesico?
What happened here?
It' alright...you can tell me, what happened?
Dark Future
Scene 2: Dark Present...of the Sacrificed.
(Sign: Photo Club)
E, excuse me, is anyone here...?
Well well...
Welcome, we've been waiting.
Here...drink this to relax.
U, um, what do you want...
It's an herbal tea.
A herbal tea!
Also, please get in a uniform you like.
Please dress in here.
Once you are dressed, please let me know.
I will gather everyone.
By the way...
Don't wear your underwear.
So, she chose the nurse outfit.
Well, it does hide the most skin.
She's taking off the skirt!
Next is the top!
Look, she's going for the bra!
They're bigger and firmer than I've imagined!
L, I, look, now the panties!
Can you please look this way?
(Random talking)
What's wrong with me...
It's very embarrassing...
Yet, I'm excited.
Spread your legs more.
Eh, I'm...
Not wearing anything under...
Please...hold your legs and turn your face this way.
Smile, smile, smile, smile!
Wow, that innocent Shion seems to be getting wet!
This...this far?
This can't, this can't...
Huh, what?
Lets have you put this on.
Now, the real photo shoot...
Begins!
Drink every last drop of my holy water.
Don't you dare miss a drop!
You guys do it too!
Shion, the school hotie, is drinking my piss!
I'm so excited, I can't aim!
Still more to go.
Wonderful expression.
It's not the end yet.
Wow...
The third shot!
And still going!
P, please Chayamachi...restroom...
Oh, so you know what it is.
Then...beg for...it.
Beg for it!
No, it won't stop, it won't stop...no!
Please Chayamach, let me go to the restroom!
You rejected me over him!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please, stop!
Only if you were this obedient from the beginning.
That trash had your virginity!
S, stop...it's coming out...out....
You gave it to him!
Look, just look at you!
Cuming...going to bust a nut!
Not inside!
Don't!
I don't think so, I'm cuming inside!
Not inside!
Don't please!
E, even he hasn't came...inside.
No...no...
I can't...
My stomach...it's...so warm....
It's...it's...
Hold it!
He went in here.
Those guys...
Relaxation Club?
This wasn't here when I was here before.
Ms. Takebe, you came to this school before?
Yes, as a student-teacher.
Anyhow...those guys....
Lets go in.
OK.
What a creepy club.
Smells nice though.
Hey, I know you're there!
Come out!
What is it?
Are you the president?
How rude, take off that mask!
I think you girls are the rude ones.
You came in here without permission.
What!?
I saw one of your club members run into here!
What's happening...
They were trying to voyeur her!
You're part of this too, right!?
You're coming to the office with me!
Ms. Hinoki!
Wha....wro....
This...what....
Welcome to the club...
Ms. Hinoki!
T, Teacher, oh.
Ms. Hinoki, Ms. Hinoki!
W, what is this?
I can't...
What a whorish teacher.
Who, who are you!?
I didn't...give you permission...to speak!
I like your scream.
It turns me on.
I don't think you should be worrying...about others!
Lets see...lets start of with Ms. Hinoki
the bitch who's sniffing us out.
It appears that she misunderstands us.
It'll be a bit rough, but I have confidence
that you'll soon convert to our club.
Do a better job at jerking!
Feels wonderful!
M, me next!
Cuming...cuming!
Lots...lots of cum...
Well...no more doubts left I assume?
Y, yes...no more doubts....
That's wonderful.
Great, it's great, more, give me more!
I'm cuming, cuming!
Give me, give me all the cum, I want it!
Cuming!
Alright, next up...the one who's been very rude to me...
It is your turn, Teacher.
No, no no no no!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Time to be punished!
It feels great.
That's it, keep up the good work.
Put your feelings into it when you suck it.
Looks like you enjoy the vibrator.
It's turning me on.
Well, here's the next step.
Feels good!
I can't take this, I want to torture you more.
But...time to get to business!
Not my butt.
I'll fuck you til you drop.
Great, it's great!
More, I want more!
I like it, I like it up my ass!
Cuming, cuming, it's making me cum!
The only thing I want is for you to understand...
More, please give me more!
(sign: Publications)
The photo club should be open...
But no identification of the
home page being...renewed.
On top of that, a complicated
coding with layers of filtering...
Well, then how about this!
There!
Uh...
I guess it isn't...easy.
A bunch of expensive machines...
No way can the school fund all this.
I need to at-least find the financial statement...
Without a doubt that this site brings in the money...
I will prove it...
Their bad intentions...
I will not...forgive them!
We've been waiting...
Let me in.
Scene 2 -The End-