Come on, wake up!
The food is getting cold.
In a bit...
Shesh, you're always like this...
Make this calm down!
No``
I, it feels...don't !
No, my uniform is going to wrinkle...!
Stop!
I'll take it off for you then.
Don't ..you're going to make us late.
Don't worry about it.
But, if we're late together...
they'll find out we live together!
Cuming, cuming!
Does it feel good?
Dark Future
scene 1 Ravaged Past
Good morning!
Hey, did you hear?
The new ghost sighting.
Yeah, I was searching about it right now.
Well?
Looks like no one reported about it yet.
I see...
I heard it was seen near the storage at the indoor pool.
And the new student who saw it isn't hear today.
But I don't want to bother him at his home.
Didn't think l would hear such comments
coming from our top journalist, Kaede.
Umm, Chief...
To be a good journalist you have to be at
the scene and talk to everyone that was there.
Why are you backing out, Kaede?
He saw your panties.
White, a very clear white.
Us journalist must find out everything by themse..!?
...and put their lives on.....
Idiot!
Our theme this time is, "The ghost
who is spreading fear in school."
Hinoki will check the student
web-pages for information.
Kaede and I will try to interview witnesses, if any.
Yeah, whatever...
Alright, we're going to start this right after school!
Crowded as usual...
Too bad I couldn't get lunch ready today...
It's all Masa's fault...
Shion Shizutani.
Oh, sorry about that.
I'm alright.
I came out in a hurry so I forgot to put on a bra...
What?
Shion, do you have any worries or secrets lately?
Well...
Take a look
We want people with stress to attend
this and let them free themselves.
Aroma therapy treatment?
We at the Relaxation Club promises you to
relieve your stress with our special herbs.
We are limited with time and
supplies, so keep this a secret.
Hey, Shion?
Oh, there you are...let me treat you...!?
Chayamachi?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Shion and I were talking about the
spiritual aspects of the world, right?
Spiritual?
That's gay.
It's something you would never
understand with your brains.
Man, he thinks he can do everything because
he's going to be the next class president.
Why are you two like cats and dogs.
Who knows, we probably were enemies in the past life.
Relaxation Club. One year anniversary.
Aroma therapy, gather.
I think it's here.
Welcome to the Relaxation Club.
So beautiful.
Please, have a seat.
Smells very nice.
The cute new student, Nadesico Mitsu.
She looks fresh.
Well, lets get this going.
Oh, where is Sumire?
Sumire took the new guys for some test.
So she's going to train the newbies.
With her great techniques...
Hey Ma....where is the chief?
He came by to pick up the camera then left the room.
While shouting, " Scoop, scoop!"
Shit, he's one step ahead of me!
Lets see...this...and this....alright!
Scoop, scoop!
They both did the same thing.
The rumored ghosts appears in the old swimming club.
The swimming club was closed 15
years ago because of an incident...?
I wonder what the incident is?
A quiet pool ground is so freaky...
I think this was the place...
What's wrong, what are you afraid of?
Hurry, come here.
What are you guys waiting for?
But Sumire, I hear ghosts appear...
Coward, as a member of Relaxation Club, you have to
be able to able to give some advice to problems.
We came here to practice that!
But...a courage test?
That's one of it.
Are you alright, Sumire?
I think I'm injured, can you look?
O, OK!
It looks like it's ...more inside.
Can you see...the wound?
What's wrong...it's twitching?
Looks like something big is going to happen.
Shit, I can't really see from here.
Alright...
Still hard...
You bad boy...
Su, Sumire!
What about you two?
Please!
S, sorry!
M, me too!
I can't go out like this, clean it.
Y, yes...
Um...tissue...
What are you guys thinking!?
Clean it with your mouthes.
My clothes is going to get dirty if you guys don't hurry.
Stop!
Who says you can suck on my lips and nipples!
S, sorry!
Fine, as your punishment, both of
you take off your pants and undies.
Then lick my wound.
I'm always excited during my period.
I'll make you two feel better...
Don't stop!
I understand your problems.
Just talking about it makes me feel better.
You see?
Now just relax and drink this
specially blended herb tea.
OK...
You guys recover fast...
Come here.
Ghost!!!
How are you going to....take care of this?
What's going on...?
We're just trying to get rid of your problems...
S, stop it!
You'll feel better soon...
S, stop!
If you continue to resist, I'll broadcast
your " secrets" on the internet.
A, anything but...
Relax a bit...
No, not here...
It hurts...!
Smells like a virgin...
So embarrassing..
What's wrong?
You want to touch my thing?
Touch it!
The drug should be kicking in soon.
So warm...
Don't hurt me.
Shut up!
Don't hurt me...!
Well, doesn't it feel good!?
We're just getting started.
It hurts...
It hurts, stop.
Stop...
Shut up!
Why don't you start begging.
Something like..." Please don't stick it
my piss smelling, blood leaking hole."
I can't ...say that....
Stop!
Then say it...say it!
Please....stick it in my...piss smelling...
Hurry, hurry!
A dirty little virgin ehh.
Not so violently...
I'm loosing....it!
No...what's this...feeling...?
It's driving me wild...more, more!
Ouch...
Masa...got to be more gentle...
Uh, alright...
You're...good.....
No, you're driving me wild..
Feels wonderful...
Much better than those boys...!
I want yours!
Sumire...!
I can't ...hold it!
Cuming!
I want to cum too, Masa...
Great!
Oh, this is what I wanted!
Cum, you can cum inside me!
I'm on my period...
Like this or like this!?
T, that's ...!
It hurts, stop...
Really?
You really want me to stop?
D, don't ...
Are you telling me what to do?
Alright, but you have to clean my cock
that's smothered with our juice and blood.
Alright, now...show me your ass.
No...it's so...feels...more, more!
Not there!
No, so embarrassing!
Hurry...give, give it to me!
Warm...my tummy...feels warm....
F, forgive me...I'm going to....
You are...now my slave!
Cuming...cuming, cuming!
Something...warm...squirting inside me...!
Who's our next prey?
We invited her to the photo shoot.
I see, so we're going to be...the Photo Club next.
Going to be busy.
Yeah.
Oh?
What is this?
What...is this?
Coming soon...internet broadcast!?
If you want the pictures changed...
please come to the special...meeting!?
Who!?
Scene 1 , The End.