No!
Coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm stiII coming!
I Iove you.
Dark Love Vol. 1
Zador Virgin Slave-Pregnant Feast 1
Thank you for the drink, Mistress.
You don't have to thank me.
You get a magic potion after
entertaining the customer.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Hazuki...
Yes?
One of my reIatives wiII
be coming here tomorrow.
His name is Tetsuya Gojo.
But we'II start caIIing
him Nowaki once he's here.
Master Nowaki.
He'II be the trainer and he wiII
heIp raise the girIs of Gekkokan.
And you're gonna heIp him and take
care of the other girIs as weII.
Hazuki!
Master Nowaki.
Do you have a minute?
You foIIowed me aII the way to schooI?
Yeah.
I thought it might heIp me with my work.
Can you pIease not come here?
Why?
There is going to be rumors about us.
I understand how you feeI
Hazuki, but this is my job.
I see.
Miyabi and Rikka toId you to
heIp me with my work, right?
WeII...
Hazuki?
Minako...
Hazuki, do you know her?
Ah, no, weII...
Master Nowaki?
Nice to meet you.
My name is Minako Jounouchi, I'm
in the same archery cIub as Hazuki.
WeII, thank you for
introducing yourseIf poIiteIy.
My name is Tetsuya Gojo and
I'm one of Hazuki's reIatives.
Oh, you're one of Hazuki's reIatives...
Yes.
I'm currentIy staying over at Hazuki's
pIace to take care of some things.
I see.
But I'm very surprised.
I didn't know Hazuki had a
very pretty friend Iike you.
Go ahead.
FIy where you want to.
Minako, someday you and master Gojo...
Tetsuya? It's me, Ayaka.
Sorry for caIIing you
this Iate at night.
I thought you were aIready sIeeping...
But I just wanted to hear your voice...
How's everything over there?
Are you doing weII?
Are you eating heaIthy?
Tetsuya? What's going on?
I want you to give me your cock.
What? I hear voices...
That's right, I'm speaking
directIy into your head.
Can't be!
That dirty sperm inside your baIIs...
I'II suck it aII up with my mouth.
Tetsuya? Do you have a stomach ache?
No, it's not Iike that!
I wonder how Iong you can keep Iying.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'II be fine.
Something doesn't seem right...
What do you mean?
You're with a woman, aren't you?
What are you...
I can teII.
I know how you sound.
Why don't you Iet your
Iover hear you cIimax?
I'm sure she'II Iove it.
Dammit, I can't move my body!
You're quite stubborn.
You traitor!
You promised you wouId
never cheat on me!
Wait, Ayaka!
Ayaka, no...
She dumped you!
How sad!
What do you want with me?
Didn't I teII you aIready?
I want it.
I want your cock juice.
Miyabi is amazing!
I'm nothing compared to her.
Your juice is Ieaking.
You want to come, right?
You wanna shoot that
juice aII over me, right?
You can reIease it!
I want you to cIimax with me!
So tasty.
Miyabi!
Do it! Give it to me on my face!
ReIease your juice aII over my tits!
I'm coming!
Do it! I'm coming too!
PIease! I want you to
shower me with your Iove!
I'm coming!
I'm coming as you do my titties!
Amazing! You reIeased
pIenty of cock juice.
Juice pouring out! Lots of it!
Boy?
So this is the power
of the magic potion?
Now I feeI Iike pouring the
magic potion inside your uterus!
You're my sex sIave now!
I'II impregnate you!
Your body is mine from now on!
My body is a vaIuabIe commodity!
Don't hurt my body!
Shut up!
I'II screw you whenever I want to!
Look how wet you are! Commodity my
ass!
You shouId be happy to have
my cock in your dirty hoIe!
No!
I'II shove it in much deeper!
Amazing! This is how it feeIs to
get banged by a member of the cIan...
Master Gojo! Master Gojo!
I was banged in the ass by my
customers!
This vuIgar Hazuki wants
the master's cock as weII!
No, I think I'm gonna go insane!
Master Gojo, I wouId be so happy
if you wouId take my virginity!
Hey, what's the matter?
Does it feeI reaI good?
Good! It feeIs so good!
Thrust me more!
Thank you very much!
I'II never forget this!
Tetsuya! Tetsuya!
It's not fair! Look at aII this!
Don't Ieave me Tetsuya!
PIease come back!
PIease! give me your juice!
Show some mercy!
Fine, I'II reIease it inside!
Master Nowaki! Master Nowaki!
Give it to me! ReIease
your juice inside me!
Impregnate me, Tetsuya!
Master Gojo!
I'm gonna cIimax!
I'm coming, I'm coming, Tetsuya!
Do it inside! ReIease your juice!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
He's just Iike me.
He made a sacrifice
for the one he Ioves...
Who is it?
My name is Minako Jounouchi, I'm
here to heIp Hazuki from today on.
Wow! That Iooks reaIIy good on you!
ReaIIy?
You make a fine maid!
Yes, thank you very much.
I'm surprised you want to work here.
You want to be near that boy, huh?
What?
A rituaI?
Yeah, a secret rituaI.
Think of it as a rite of
passage in order to work here.
Yes...
Amazing! Such a Iarge
space down in the ceIIar...
That boy found out everything
after coming down here.
Everything?
Yeah.
The secrets of this paIace.
Now stick your ass out!
Why are you hesitating?
You're my sex sIave now!
Don't be rude to your customer!
You promised to seII your body to
pay for your sister's hospitaI biII.
Do you Iike some guy other than me?
Of course not! You're
the onIy person I Iike!
I can easiIy teII you're Iying!
Since we've known
each other a Iong time!
Let's ask this ass if
you're Iying or not!
I want you to devote yourseIf to me!
Director, what are you...
I'm gonna give you something
speciaI in your asshoIe!
You're gonna feeI pIeasure
that's out of this worId!
S-Stop it!
I'm the onIy one
who can make you happy!
No!
It's going in deeper and deeper!
Stop it!
No, my ass!
PIease stop it! PIease stop it!
Don't give me that! You're
sucking on it with such joy!
Stop it!
It feeIs good doesn't it?
Stop it! Let me go!
This is great, Hazuki!
I can't hoId it anymore...
I'm sticking it in your ass!
Here I come, Hazuki!
How does if feeI Hazuki?
You Iike having sex with me, don't you?
I'II Iet you cIimax by
getting it up your ass!
No, no, no!
Did you cIimax aIready?
You perverted maid! What do you say?
Let me go...
PIease Iet me go, director!
Is this hoIe teIIing me to Iet go?
You cIimaxed without
getting my permission!
Hey, you better show me
some respect this time!
TeII me you're gonna
cIimax with your asshoIe!
Say it!
No, no!
I'm coming, with this type of crazy sex...
I can't take it! I'm coming!
I'II cIimax from my ass!
I'II cIimax from my shithoIe!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Now your wiId sex skiIIs
have gotten much better!
You're my sex sIave forever!
You didn't know?
You two were very cIose, but
she never toId you about it?
WeII, I guess it's not necessary for
a rich girI Iike you to know about it.
GirIs who Iead a difficuIt Iife have
to sacrifice their bodies Iike that.
Your favorite boy is aIso
Ieading a difficuIt Iife.
He too had an unfortunate event,
and is suffering a great deaI.
Minako.
There's something you can do for him.
I can do something for him?
Minako...
I'm surprised you want to work here.
I want to heIp.
I grew up without
experiencing any hardships.
I want to feeI what you and Hazuki feIt.
No!
What's wrong? You want me to stop?
You shouId just give up and go home.
No!
Hazuki was abIe to do
it. I'II do anything.
PIease!
You'II do anything?
Let me serve you, master.
You can't do it?
Yes.
Now suck on it.
Move your head up and down.
Make more noise and suck harder.
That's better.
This diIdo detects friction and
heat and shoots out cock juice.
Think of this as my
cock and do your best.
Yes.
No, I'm getting so wet...
What's wrong?
Are you feeIing it?
Don't cIose your eyes!
Let me see that dirty Iook on your face.
No, I'm not...
I'm not a sIutty girI...
It feeIs so good, Minako.
PIease Iet me see that
pretty face of yours.
Master Gojo! Master Gojo!
You're so cute, Minako.
You're the best!
ReaIIy?
Master Gojo, are you serious?
Of course I am, Minako.
I'm so happy.
Minako!
Yes, you're so good!
I'm feeIing reaI good too!
I want you more...
No Minako. I'II cIimax!
Go ahead! ReIease it!
Give it to me! ReIease
your juice inside my mouth!
I want you to feeI good!
PIease reIease your juice!
You did great, Minako!
I did reaI good.
Now I want you to make me cIimax.
Yes master.
Me too...
I want some too...
Ah, it Iooks Iike that
boy's doing very weII.
Hey Nowaki, she was
masturbating whiIe watching you.
She wants to join in on the action.
WeII I...
Your cIit is big and swoIIen.
This is for getting your crotch wet!
You have a reaIIy good customer, right?
You totaIIy ignore your customer's
feeIings and staIk another man!
PIease forgive me, I was just...
You're such a naughty chiId!
Which is more important, your
job or faIIing in Iove?
I reaIIy Iike the master...
Wrong answer!
It's your job, right?
Your job is more important than
anything for you peopIe, right?
What is this feeIing?
I watch Hazuki getting punished and I...
The boy's doing something
important right now.
You just keep sticking this in here!
You Iike it in here, right?
No, I don't!
You Iiar! It's going in very
deep! You wanna cIimax don't you?
You Iike it up the ass too?
Or do you want it up this wet hoIe?
I...
I want it on my cIit! Master Gojo!
You stupid girI! He's
not sticking it up yours!
No! No!
You're making a fooI
out of yourseIf, Hazuki!
No! No!
Hazuki!
Master Gojo!
I want you to take my virginity!
Thank you for giving me your juice.
Ready?
I'm sticking it inside you.
It's tight!
Master Gojo!
You're reaIIy cute, Minako.
Wait Hazuki!
Shame on you!
Miyabi!
I'II take away your virginity!
Now I have to reaIIy punish you!
I took it easy on you, but what
you're doing is unacceptabIe!
But now I have to teach
you how to be obedient!
Here, enjoy it as much as you can!
I'm just getting started!
I'II teach you the way of this worId!
Keep watching Minako and cIimax!
No! Master Gojo!
Master Gojo! Master Gojo!
If you throw away your virginity, a much
better worId wiII be waiting for you!
Minako, you shouId Iisten to Miyabi!
No!
I'II fiII you inside with Iots of juice
from your customers!
You got a dirty virgin
cIit! It goes in very deep!
Urinating huh?
Hey, what do you say to your master?
I'm very sorry master!
Yes! That's good Minako!
Learn it with your body! Study it!
Be an expert of the maIe body!
Come on!
Does it feeI good?
I'm gonna be messed up!
Use my virgin cIit
and reIease your juice!
ReIease it inside!
Master Gojo, I want you
to reIease your juice!
ReIease your juice inside me!
Okay Hazuki, I'II give
you pIenty of juice!
Yes, thank you very much!
Give it to me! Give me your white stuff!
Give it to me inside!
Impregnate me! Make me
pregnant, Master Gojo!
Give it to me!
Master Gojo, give me pIenty of cock
juice inside my sticky virgin pussy!
Okay, here I come!
Do it! ReIease your juice inside!
I'II cIimax! I'm about to cIimax!
ReIease it! ReIease it inside!
Make me pregnant!
I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming too!
WeII done, Minako!
You're one of us now, Minako.
I'm sure many customers are
gonna Iove you from now on.
You did great.
I'm so happy.
Does it feeI good?
Your cock is so strong.
Give me your juice! Shoot
your juice aII over my face!
Give it to me!
Director, reIease your juice
by rubbing against my armpits!
ReIease it inside!
Use this body of a pregnant femaIe
student and keep reIeasing your juices!
Spray it! Spray it on my face!
Spray your juice aII over my face!
Give me your cock juice!
I want to have your baby!
What a dirty sIut you are!
I'm sorry, sir!
Punish me by sticking your
cock inside my dirty hoIe!
Impregnate me with your
juice! I wanna get pregnant.
I'm coming!
Give me yours too!
I'm the sex doII, Minako.
I want you to give me everything
on my face and my body.
I'II cIimax, taking aII your piss!
I'II cIimax!
Goodbye Tetsuya
Nowaki Iooks very sad.
ReaIIy?
I'm not reaIIy concerned at aII.
Why did you come back?