You and your hard dirty cock.
Are you excited because I'm reaIIy good?
You're reaIIy perverted.
Did you know I'm aII wet?
That's why I can have sex with big
cocks, even though I'm short.
If you want more magic
potion, get more women.
If you have sex with a femaIe virgin...
Heaven wiII give you a magic potion.
Damn it!
Dark Love Vol. 2
Zador Virgin Slave-Pregnant Feast 2
Yes, thank you so much.
I'II give it to you this month.
Yes, I'm reaIIy sorry.
Thank you for understanding.
Yes, goodbye.
Hey sister, I brought a customer.
HeIIo...
Honoka...
This is Hazuki, one of
my students from cIass.
And this is her reIative Tetsuya.
You have a reaIIy nice shop.
WeIcome!
Hazuki is a very good student, I'm
very proud to have her as a student.
Oh pIease...
Man, I feeI Iike I'm getting
praised, I'm a bit embarrassed.
Kaori.
Yes?
Can I order something?
Sorry about that.
Can I get some miIk?
Sister, what are you so excited about?
I'm not excited at aII!
She's Iying, Tetsuya.
My eyes may be bad, but
I can hear it in your voice.
Enough!
Anyway, what do you want to drink?
I wiII have...
But you said over the phone today
that you'II wait for 2 more days...
How Iong are you gonna make me wait?
I'm sorry. But...
No buts!
Understand? You have untiI noon!
l'm sorry.
Who is it?
It's me.
Tetsuya?
TaIk to me, I can be of heIp.
You want a hot drink, Tetsuya?
Don't mind if I do.
Get me some miIk.
MiIk?
Yes, thick Iike breastmiIk.
Wait one minute pIease.
Wow!
It's exactIy what I
ordered, a very thick miIk!
It Iooks Iike cock juice.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry Tetsuya.
I'm reaIIy sorry, I was being careIess...
Your important spot...
Kaori.
Yes?
That hand toweI is soaking wet and coId.
CIean it with your mouth.
You're right! It won't be
coId if I do it with my mouth!
That's right Kaori, cIean it
up with that mouth of yours.
Yes!
Tetsuya...
Your mouth is so warm.
Kaori, it feeIs so good.
Who taught you how to do this?
Who did yu offer yur body and soul to?
I'II find out your secret Iife...
Stop it!
PIease stop it!
You're the best.
More! Go in deeper!
I'II never Iet you go
Kaori! You're aII mine!
I'm about to cIimax!
Take in aII my juice, Kaori!
Sister? Are you here?
What's that smeII?
Sister, you're here right?
Where are you?
Your sister soId her body in
order to pay off her debts.
I'm sorry, Honoka.
She soId you off as weII.
Sister, you didn't...
WeIcome to Gekkokan.
PIease enjoy the show for tonight!
No!
It's in there, aII right!
This is great! It's
Iike screwing a sex doII!
What's up with her? She
enjoys sucking on it!
You crazy sIut!
You feeIing it in your mouth?
It feeIs so good!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Do it inside!
It's reaIIy coming inside!
It feeIs good doing a
married woman in the ass!
My cock is feeIing your uvuIa.
Cry! Cry for me, you sIut!
I'm about to cIimax!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Here, have some on your face!
You're so mean.
I'II take away that virginity
of yours! Take some of my juice!
Amazing! Her tits are
Iike a masturbating toy!
It feeIs so good that I'II cIimax soon.
Keep on Iicking it! Here I come!
I'm gonna cIimax too!
It's coming!
Scream some more! You fine piece of
ass!
I'm gonna Iet you have it on your face!
I'm gonna reIease it inside!
Here, take this!
Make more noise whiIe sucking it!
I'II stab you to death with my cock!
Your virginity beIongs
to us! Give us everything!
WeII? What do you think
of my grind technique?
I'II punish that dirty face of yours!
There we go.
I'm gonna cIimax.
I'm gonna cIimax again!
You give up aIready? You sIuts!
I'm stiII not satisfied! Cry some more!
What's wrong? You can't even taIk?
Give me more of your dirty cock juice!
She's reaIIy nice and quiet!
I Iike this one better.
Shake your ass some more!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Look at her. This is great!
AII right! This is my 5th time!
Take this!
Here I come!
I feeI sick.
I'II throw up!
UnbeIievabIe! I'm gonna cIimax again!
You're so cute, Honoka!
I'm gonna cIimax again!
I'm gonna cIimax!
Go ahead and cIimax!
After this is done, I'II
Iet you drink my piss!
Thank you very much!
Give it to me! Let me
drink some piss too!
Piss aII over my face!
I'm coming!
Open your mouth.
Here.
I'm reaIIy gonna die!
Thanks to the magic potion, I
gained powers beyond my imagination.
Hey, Iet's decide who the
reaI master of this pIace is.
Master of this pIace?
What's wrong?
You don't Iike the way things are?
I don't Iike your attitude, the Iook
in your eye, and the way you taIk!
I've just about had it with you!
You're just a spoiIed brat.
Be with me, Rikka!
Offer me your body and souI!
You? Take my body?
You don't seem to know
the situation you're in.
Of course I know.
That's why I prepared
something speciaI for today.
The magic potion!
Where did you get that?
I did just what you toId me to, master.
But the keys to the basement...
I'm sorry, Rikka.
If I didn't do what he toId me to...
He said he wouId never Iet
me drink his cock juice again.
I'm sorry mistress.
You peopIe...
You said that if a woman gives up her
body, she gives up her souI too, right?
So if I vioIate you right here...
Then you wiII be mine.
That's wonderfuI, your skin is so white.
PIus it's so smooth.
Now Iet's remove those panties, shaII
we?
Oh, did you wet yourseIf?
No! PIease stop!
Somebody heIp me!
PIease!
HeIp me!
Master Nowaki!
It's amazing!
Stop it! Stop it!
Do me! Do me more! Make me aII sticky!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Stop it!
I'm coming!
Master Nowaki, I'm coming!
No, no!
No!
I'm coming!
There's no turning back now.
Prepare yourseIf.
Amazing! You're so good!
Does it feeI good inside me?
Do me! Do me harder!
Yes! Tease me more!
Harder! I want you to hurt me!
I'm the master of this pIace.
Nowaki.
Rikka...
You're awake.
I'm no Ionger human?
I'm sorry.
I gave you too much of that magic
potion, and now you're aII miserabIe.
Magic potion...
Why is my body Iike this?
That potion...
The magic potion is created
by a God named Abaramach...
And it's considered
to be a potion of Iife.
For a Iong time, our cIan has
protected this secret potion.
PowerfuI potion of Iife...
Yes.
The potion gave you so much power.
Nowaki, pIease.
Protect this potion aIong with me.
I don't care if you keep
on doing shameIess acts.
I can never go back to my human form?
GirIs are gonna hate me.
No.
You don't Iook scary at aII.
I think you Iook powerfuI.
You're not worried?
You're stiII the same to me.
Thanks to the magic potion,
I can maintain my youth.
Rikka, you're beautifuI.
I don't care if I'm not a human anymore.
As Iong as I have you...
I can't eat anymore.
Tetsuya...
Let's go.
Okay.