It's okay, I want to be with you.
Waking up, my princess?
Ryosuke. I'm really sorry!
It's okay. I'm ready to pass out
when we get to our room.
I was nervous last night.
Me too.
Newlyweds! Have a happy honeymoon!
What were you dreaming about?
Well...
About our wedding night?
No.
Well, no.
Ryosuke!
Sorry! I'm tired too.
No wedding night until we get to Hawaii!
We'll both have to dream about it for now.
Aska, I'll promise to make
this a special trip.
I can't wait.
Here you go.
I feel a bit like a princess.
How embarrassing.
After we check in I'll call room service.
What?
Room service to go!
Stop! No!
Screaming isn't going to help you now.
No! No!
Come on, give up!
I said Stop!
Spread them sweetie.
Your legs are in the way.
Does she always wear lingerie!
Or is this for the wedding?
No! No!
Give up, stupid bitch!
Hey, can't be rough with our product.
Don't abuse our woman.
You don't want to be hurt.
You'll regret being passed out
on your special wedding night.
"Our product." "Wedding night?"
No! Stop!
You mean "don't stop!"
Take a look at this body!
Ouch!
Why, you...
Open the door!
Someone, please open the door!
We haven't even stuffed you yet,
stop crying! You're ruining the fun!
Shit! This isn't the best place for this.
All right.
We'll make this a wedding night
you'll never forget.
We sure will.
Sweetie, you're pussy's all wet.
Smell that sweet pussy.
I can smell the hot juices.
Let's sample.
Go ahead and take your bath first.
I said Dad will drive me home in his car!
Now my new dress is all wet!
Your dad had to go back home.
He shouldn't have taken a job so far
away! Mom!
You're such a baby!
You think Aska is having fun
on her honeymoon?
Aska's being a baby
with her new husband.
One of these days you'll be married, too.
But hopefully not until you're much older!
I hope not until you are bigger than me.
I'm not my sister!
I didn't know you had a cute girdle!
Hello! Welcome to the
Caruun's Burger Shoppe! Aska!
How are you, Miku!
Your uniform looks good!
I wasn't expecting you guys!
I was expecting real customers.
Table for 3? Would you like
smoking or non-smoking?
Non-smoking, please.
I'll seat you now.
Aren't you going to seat us?
We're real customers.
I can't believe it! You're getting married,
and you're the shy one!
Surprised?
Aya.
Really.
Well, Ryosuke told me he couldn't wait
until we graduate.
How disgusting.
You're just jealous.
You're right, Tamami.
Ryosuke was my tutor.
Even Miku wasn't able to win over these.
Tamami, stop!
So have you guys done it?
So has he fondled your breasts like this?
Stop it! That hurts!
Hi, Ryosuke!
Everyone seems to be having fun!
Am I early?
Were you two planning to meet here?
He wanted to come by and pick me up.
Already acting like a hubby.
Tamami, you'll find someone good, too.
Yeah, we both will.
Are you almost done here?
Is it okay if I come along?
Of course!
Okay, it'll be just a second!
What a brat! Problem maker.
They didn't want me to come.
Soon.
Yeah.
Ryosuke! Look! Watch me slide!
Come Over! Hurry up!
All right.
What a little brat!
What a problem maker.
Be careful, Miku.
It's okay! I'll be fine!
Sorry.
God, Miku.
You should be more careful,
you should avoid the slide.
But it's so fun! Why? It's so fun.
But still...
You're weird.
I'm home!
Hi Mrs. Akiyama.
Where's mom?
That's strange.
How is everybody?
Welcome, Ryosuke.
Hi! Good evening.
Mom! Go get dressed!
For crying out loud!
Besides, I'm old...
nothing to look at anymore,
right, Ryosuke?
Go!
I'll get dressed. Please stay and relax.
Mom! You're embarrassing me!
He's going to be my brother-in-law.
Take care.
See you.
Leaving already Ryosuke?
Yeah.
Well then, no need for this lingerie!
Miku!
Ryosuke! Please! Don't look!
Stop it, now!
Let's take this off! I'm doing you a favor.
Miku!
I'm going to walk him out!
I'll get you back!
Miku, It's late. No need.
Only for you, you know,
for my brother.
Well...
I usually wear bloomers,
but Mom washed my spares...
and it's not like I go around
showing off to everyone...
I just want you to see. Just you.
I wish you'd teach me, you know.
I can't.
You tease.
I thought you were a real man.
Usually. I thought you were an adult.
What? Miku?
I 'm old enough for lingerie, too.
When you come over to tutor me.
Stop it! That's not something you
go showing off to everyone!
You're special. If you're worried
in case I forget...
my bloomers you can buy me a girdle.
Honeymoon should be fun.
I'm going to ask him to buy me...
cute panties next time when he comes
back I'll make him pay attention.
She's a virgin!
No shit!
See?
Ouch!
You're pussy's so tight.
Waking up? Ready for more?
Do you like the taste of your pussy?
Waking up? Is it tasting just right?
You're not full yet, are you my young bride.
We know you want more
you're still hungry, aren't you?
Where are you? Ryosuke! Help!
This is great! I'm about to come!
No, stop!
You little punks, you have no manners.
Don't look!
How dare you! You bitch, I'm not kidding.
No!
You're fucking up my car!
You're getting crap all over my car.
I'm sorry!
But I'd say I've got a gift for the boss.
I'm a woman now, too.
Mom! Phone's ringing!
I'm Cooking. Please, Miku!
Hi! This is Miku Speaking.
Hello?
Wrong number maybe?
Are you Miku Akiyama?
Yes? This is she.
I'm watching you.
What?
Who?
Rather than pink, you look better
in white underwear...
especially the sweaty, cotton ones.
Hello?
Good pictures?
Who are you? Who did this?
I've got videos too you know, when you're
trying to seduce your brother-in-law.
That's not true.
When you're kissing him
and showing your panties...
you know what you're doing,
you know better than to play dumb!
Letting a man fondle and kiss you,
know what results from those kind...
of unhealthy sexual action
from what you've learned in health class.
That's not true!
You want me to keep quiet?
Blackmail! How much?
Do you understand you situation, honey?
I'm not going to repeat myself, I said "no!"
You still don't understand, do you?
It's just not your head
that's come to its senses.
Bastard! Traitor!
Yumiko, stop sucking.
Ms. Reika Tatsuoka, you're no longer the
wealthy debutante you think you are...
you're not even a person anymore.
You belong to us!
Your parents gave you up
in exchange for clearing...
their massive debt, so now we own you
as a sex slave!
I'm not a lowlife whore like you!
I'm not like your kind.
You only need to open that mouth
to suck cock!
Do you need to pee? Beg to be excused.
Beg?
This will make some cash!
A film of the wealthy debutante
pissing in her pants!
No!
Stop! Forgive me! I'll do what you want!
If you'll let me do what I want I'm
going to come in you.
No, not that! Stop!
Still haven't learned...
I'm coming!
Please, not inside!
This isn't porn, why should he
come externally?
Good girl. You learned quick.
I'm about to come.
Yeah, I'm coming.
We're done for now.
Where's the boss?
In the back, yeah. Hey, can I have that?
This is for the boss.
I can't hold it!
Can't hold what, exactly?
Don't push there, please!
Tell me what you want,
you don't want to go here.
Pee.
Can't hear you.
I need to pee, I really need to pee!
That's my girl. In that case,
I'll let you really go to the bathroom.
No! No! Absolutely not that!
Check that out. You're next, by the way!
You are all fucking crazy! No!
No, we'll drive you crazy, in perfect style!
Stop!
Not to worry Reika.
I'll keep you around for a while.
We're going to concentrate
on making videos.
No!
Stop complaining!
There are lots of girls...
that are forced to shit and piss
in front of crowds.
Fuck up and you'll end up there!
What?
Right now I have other plans for you,
but fuck up and you'll end up there, quick.
That'll make her shut up.
I'll teach you to respect me
through your ass!
No!
Just like the man on the phone said,
is this really Mom's?
She's never had anyone come inside her?
I can guarantee that.
She was a virgin,
her hymen has been torn.
I could care less about that,
the hymen can go to the moles.
When you set up the camcorder
get out of the way.
Your name is Aska?
Both this magnum and my magnum...
are about to burst,
which would you prefer?
Bang!
She'll never forget this.
This will become a treasured memory.
Please don't tape this!
I can't have anyone see.
It's not like this kind of honor
happens every day!
Idiot! This is a once in a lifetime memory.
No one's going to interrupt this time.
Enjoy fucking a real man!
No need to worry
about the tape running out.
I'm going to take my time. I can't wait
to be the first to come inside you.
My cock is going to fill you...
with precious gifts!
I prefer ass, but this is looking...
No!
Didn't expect your pussy
to feel this good.
I can't believe how good you feel.
I'm also enjoying your screams!
Still bleeding just a bit.
More treats are coming your way, baby.
Yeah! I can come again!
I still got plenty of juice.
I'm going to pump you full, have you heard
about a man coming?
Three times in a row without pulling out?
Wow! You're still studying?
I have a test coming up.
I know you're studying hard,
but put some clothes on.
I know you're studying hard
but with such loosed behavior...
you're never going to
find a decent husband.
You sleep naked all the time.
That's different, where did you find these
old underwear?
They might be cute but they are too small.
Change those and get dressed!
Okay.
I can't take it!
I did what you wanted, the photos
and videos back...
can I please take this off?
My panties are getting wet.
This is my favorite panty.
You're going to go to school like that.
I'll call you later.
Wait a minute!
This is crazy! Help! Ryosuke!
I've been asleep?
Aska, is that you?
Go away!
No, I'm just embarrassed.
Okay.
By the time I'm done, you're going to
be a living tank full of my jizz.
More like you're going to be a storage tank
for my jizz.
Don't forget, sex slavery
is a one-way ticket.
No cancellations.