I can't.
Ryosuke, I'm ready to go.
What is that costume?
Why, I thought you would like it,
don't you think she looks good?
Looks good?
I don't...
What?
Are you saying you don't like
the costume my wife picked out?
What are you doing in here?
Blackmail II "second over the Il"
another tomorrow: The animation
3rd stage: Chain Bride Aska
I hope you don't mind...
sharing your lovely bride
with others tonight.
Aska!
We need to go to the party.
We'll have a lot of fun tonight.
All right, I'm going to check out the pussy
of this dirty little girl to see if it's wet.
No!
Looks like she's all shaved!
Nice and smooth!
I can't believe this wet pussy here
belongs to a virgin!
Hey, are you sure we can really fuck her?
He said we could, so I'm going to.
Ryosuke!
I'd fuck her anyway.
Shit, she's really tight.
You guys don't look
completely satisfied yet.
I see you have someone more
mature for our enjoyment!
This one looks good, too.
She's had all her holes filled.
I'll take my turn.
If you're going to blame someone,
blame your sister.
My sister?
Your new bride is awfully popular
at this casino!
I suppose the opportunity
to fuck the new bride...
first in front of the groom before he does.
Gets everybody excited.
Yumiko, please stop this!
I was the one that left you!
Don't take it out on Aska.
Don't worry, I have something
good planned for you, too.
Well, it looks like the first contestant
has been decided!
Aska! I think you're getting turned on...
by watching your bride get fucked
like that.
What kind of a husband are you?
I'd like to see the expression on your face.
You want to open your eyes
right about now.
Don't you think it's strange?
For a virgin, she seems to be
enjoying things...
a little too much.
Especially since didn't let you come
near her at the hotel.
Yumiko, how do you know?
You'll know soon enough
just look into her eyes...
as she gets fucked hard
like that by another man.
But!
My, your bride has already
been with 40 men.
You haven't wanted a single girl!
This has to stop, Yumiko!
I would come quickly if I were you.
I think there's at least
50 guys left for Aska.
Yes!
Stop this madness!
Just let Aska go.
Do you love her that much?
We'll see about that!
I have a special guest for you.
Hi, nice to meet you, Ryo-suke.
This is awfully convenient.
She looks a lot like your sister-in-law.
Yumiko, how did you know?
I'm glad you like her.
We'll show Aska how much you like here.
Stop doing this, please!
I really don't see why not.
You're awfully selfish, aren't you.
I just want you to now fuck her...
or she'll see the same fate as Aska.
What?
The poor girl knows nothing about that.
Her fate is in your hands.
Mr. Ryosuke.
Hey!
I didn't say stop.
Yes.
Do you want to be gangbanged
like that again?
I'll do what you want, Mr. Miyake.
If I didn't agree to help her,
I would have never been caught...
by Miyake and forced into this blackmail.
You see, I want to do something so Miku
will stay away from Ryosuke.
Something like...
Isn't that a crime?
I'm just teaching her a lesson.
Are you filming all this?
Yes, I am.
Tell me what you're doing.
I am filming my best friend Aska's
mother and sister get raped.
I can't Yumiko.
Not with this girl.
You like her that much?
At least you're not related to her!
Yes!
Ryosuke, just like that,
fuck me harder with your cock!
More, more!
Miku!
I want you to come hard,
I want your big load inside me!
I am your Miku.
I want you to come inside me!
Come on, fuck me!
I want you to release
a big load inside me, Ryosuke!
Coming, I'm going to come!
Now hurry, come inside me!
I want to come with you,
I want you to come with me.
I'm sorry Ryosuke, I don't want you
to come inside me just yet!
I'm sorry.
I promise I'll do anything you
want me to, Ryosuke.
Just forgive me.
I'm going to come!
Please, don't tell anyone.
I promise not to tell anyone.
I'll give you my virginity so just swear
you won't tell anyone.
Promise, promise me!
Yeah!
Come inside.
Inside me!
You didn't think I was going
to let you come so easily?
You said...
you were in love with Aska.
Ryosuke?
Ryosuke!
I like that.
Ryosuke...
Yes.
I'm coming!
You're not Miku.
Where is Miku? I want Miku.
I want Miku.
I want to come...
inside Miku!
What's going on Ryosuke!
See, Ryosuke...
it's like Miku's right here with you!
I make a decent substitute.
Ryosuke!
It's time for you to release your husband!
You just need to pull this.
That is, if you love him.
Although, for him, you're
only a substitute for your own sister.
The sooner the better, I think.
Otherwise, he might suffer
serious damage.
I love it Ryosuke!
Miku! Miku!
That was good.
You wanted him to come inside you, right?
Even after we came home, Ryosuke
showed absolutely no interest in me.
He didn't want my body at all,
he wanted Miku instead.
I need to do something
so I wouldn't lose him.
But Miku was also suffering
at the hands of Mr. Miyake.
My heart.
Mr. Miyake?
No, my god, no!
Let go of me, now!
Don't come inside me, please!
I can feel him still coming inside me!
I should have never asked Aya to do that.
I'm going to make it up to you Miku.
Who is it?
Miku, I'll share him with you.
Breaking news. There was a large explosion
at this downtown office building that...
was occupied by the Yakuza.
Everyone that was in the building
perished including the following.
The police are working on establishing
the identity of other people.
Is this what you wanted, Reika?
I hope I didn't ask for too much.
Don't worry.
It was no trouble for me to arrange at all.
You are my very favorite, personal pet.
I'll do what it takes to keep my pet happy.
Thank you very much, my master.
I need to get going now.
Aska, Ryosuke, what are...
No, stop Ryosuke!
No!
Don't resist, Miku.
I know you learned some new habits
from this whole experience.
Don't worry.
Ryosuke will take care
of your needs from now.
Aska!
I'm going to give you something special.
We both have a matching wedding collar.
Aska!
Congratulations!
Congratulations Miku!
You look beautiful Miku!
Everyone!
Everyone...
Thank you!