Please, don't tape this!
I can't have anyone see! No! Stop!
I'll wait until you absorb the water,
this is your last chance.
I'm sorry, we're out of time!
I can feel a good load coming.
Should we edit his voice?
These bitches sound horrible!
Dub over it. This is the scene!
Can we slow it down?
It's noisy.
On top of the computers.
The angle sucks.
Nowadays they're picky about angles, too.
Here!
Slave! You're supposed
to do the work here!
Take a good look at her.
She knows what she's doing!
Your body remembers.
Good girls are easy to handle,
they aim to please.
If you can't return a compliment,
maybe this will...
teach you this amount
should be perfect.
Thank You! I said "thank you!" Stop!
You enjoy that, don't you?
Was I given a choice?
You're moving a bit slow,
maybe an enema will speed you up!
No! I'll do what you want, just not that!
I said, "thank you!"
Where's the please?
Thank you, please!
No need to be shy! Give her a full load!
No!
I still have some left!
No! Stop!
Aska, you must be an enema virgin.
Reika, you do it.
Teach her the pleasure!
What a good girl! Takes orders well!
No! Don't put it in!
What's taking so long?
My god, it's cold! Stop, please!
Reika, you have nothing left
in you, but Aska probably...
has some nice solid presents to show us.
A home cooked meal by the new bride!
Nice touch.
In addition to her cooking,
you got to taste her everywhere...
and fuck her every hole first,
instead of her new husband...
on their precious wedding night!
Here's an additional treat,
come here, Aska!
Serve your master.
Very nice!
I'll let you go home soon, for now.
Just remember that your pretty body
is now our property!
Yes, sir.
Can you face your husband after all this?
All shaved. So cute!
You had a good lesson in fucking tonight.
Thank you, sir.
I'm sure your husband will agree.
Thank you, master.
What a body! I'm regretting letting
the boss have you first.
Well, I'll just take my time
and make up for it now.
Yes, thank you master.
This feels good.
I can't believe I'm enjoying getting raped.
I just cleaned you up.
You know the smell of come
suits you better than any cologne.
Yes. I have had my fill. Thank you.
Are you okay?
Aska?
Yes!
I'm okay, really!
On your honeymoon?
Yes!
He seems nice.
Thank you for the compliment.
It's true, I don't deserve him.
You sure you're okay?
You've been asleep the whole time.
I'm just tired,
I hope I'm not boring you.
I'm just tired, I'm sorry
I haven't stayed up to talk.
I shouldn't be talking.
I don't even remember our wedding night!
Ryosuke, well...
We'll make up for it in Hawaii.
You're not looking happy!
That's not true!
Already bored with your honeymoon?
Lt'll be a long trip, why don't we chat a bit?
Let's review last night's lessons,
practice makes perfect.
No.
I am the 17th sex slave to my master.
This sick bitch loves to have
my master watch me piss!
I am the 18th sex slave to my master.
This horny bitch likes to suck on come
more than anything else.
What if my husband comes back?
Don't worry, or would he you rather know
about what happened last night?
That will be one quick divorce.
We'll enjoy this honeymoon.
Together.
Your pretty wife left her seat
right after you.
Yumiko?
Ryosuke?
What the hell are you doing here?
Do you have something to say to my wife?
No.
Picking up on my wife
during his honeymoon...
what a worthless loser!
We are reviewing Japanese history today...
please open up your textbook
to the last chapter.
I can't take this! How can I make it stop!
Miku! Read from the text,
starting at the top.
Miku Akiyama!
Yes!
You need to be paying attention?
We're waiting!
I'm sorry!
What's wrong? Hurry!
Yes.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm sorry, where were we?
Which chapter? Which page are we on?
You're taking this well!
Make it stop! Please!
I'm about to go crazy!
This is just the beginning!
This is punishment,
to make sure you'll stay a good girl.
No! Stop!
Stupid bitch! At least pretend to like it!
Unlike you, Aya, young girls
don't want to learn to please their man.
No matter how much they get fucked,
they keep insisting I'm hurting them!
No, please! Stop.
Hey, Kaoru!
Yes!
This one's no good.
Find me a new one for next time,
something cute, with bigger tits, nice body.
Do you have any suggestions?
Shiomi in my class has big breasts,
she's always complaining...
that she can't find bras.
Bring her here tomorrow.
Aya, have you made your preparations?
Should be ready tonight.
All right. We'll carry out the plan tonight.
I'm sorry Miku. Aska is the one to blame.
She's the one that betrayed us.
I've have all three, soon!
No, not inside!
Tastes good?
Yes.
You're getting more.
Smell of come suits you
better than any perfume.
Yumiko. Yumiko Miyazaki, right?
Wrong person.
Yumiko!
Ryosuke.
Ryosuke!
Where did you disappear to?
I'm sorry.
Where were you?
I just wanted to walk around.
I was really worried about you!
I'm sorry!
I'm not mad just well as long as you're okay.
Get out!
I know Miku
is having constipation...
and hAS seen the school nurse
twice about it.
You must be worried.
Being a health teacher...
medical companies
give me special pricing.
Though this might be useful.
Stop leaving these strange
things every day!
And! You only come here
when Miku's not home!
I'm the problem.
I'm calling the police!
Apparently you like what I leave behind!
I'm sure you'll enjoy what I brought today.
This is turning out to be so easy.
What about the youngest girl?
Tamami's on it.
Friendships are so fragile.
I was impressed
when you and Tamami promised...
to be my slave to protect the Akiyamas...
but now you're actively helping me!
No more tonight.
All right. Whatever. Enjoy your evening!
Thanks for waiting? Enjoy your meal.
Tamami?
I can't just leave, I'm working!
Lt'll be quick.
But...
Do you like Ryosuke, Miku?
Why are you asking?
He's not worth it.
He used to be such a player.
He hurt lots of people.
What?
If you're that good looking,
I guess it's almost natural.
Why are you telling me this?
He hurt both Aya and me, as well.
What?
But since he met Aska, he changed!
And we were hoping
he'd break her heart, too.
What are you looking at?
This isn't a free show!
Fucking bums!
Tamami!
Insolent bitch!
Grab her!
Shit, she's getting away!
What a cunt!
There's her friend!
We'll catch her!
We'll teach her.
Drag her over there!
What the hell?
Come on. Hurry up!
Now sit! Don't look so frightened.
This is just foreplay.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Yes.
You just wait. You'll have a plum role
in your daughter's debut.
It's all Aska's fault!
No! Stop! No!
She's all dressed up!
Idiot! This is her work uniform!
Don't take it all off! I like this!
What the hell is this?
They're horny around this age.
So much for looking innocent!
Let's turn this up!
A toy can't really satisfy you.
No! Stop!
We'll show you what
the real thing feels like.
Drag her to the bed over there!
No! Please! Stop!
Her pussy's so wet!
No longer have to wait!
Don't take it all off!
I got it!
No! No! Tamami, help!
Smell this, little girl!
This is what a real man smells like.
Stinks! Help Tamami!
Nothing like a good pussy.
No! Help! No! Stop!
A masquerade party?
I'm sure you and your wife will enjoy it.
Please, come.
We met for reason.
We would like both of you to attend.
Sure.
Not interested?
No! Sounds good.
We'll both be there.