Here you go.
Thank you, Mom.
You look really good, Asuka.
Isn't it a little revealing?
You only get married once,
show off your beautiful figure.
Hey, look!
Voilà!
I borrowed one.
You need to find someone good soon.
I will get you a cute wedding dress
as a gift.
It's not been such a long time
since that day.
It's as if everything was but a dream.
Not a trace is left.
Even those who I thought were my friends.
It's time.
Okay.
I've come for you, Asuka.
No more daydreaming.
Was that Aya?
Aya?
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Aya?
You're big now.
Hey.
You're leaving me behind and growing up.
What're you saying?
We'll always be together.
We're friends.
I got their clothes.
Miku, don't spill it.
No more. Help me, Mom.
Sakura, Miku's talking to you.
Help.
Why don't you say something to her?
Because I'm sucking you off.
How can a mother talk like that?
Don' be so mean.
You made me swear
I'd be just another woman to serve you.
Don't do it rough anymore.
How many times do I have to tell you?
A pampered kid like this one
likes it a little rough.
She's my slave. I make the rules.
Yumiko.
We can play your games,
but know your place.
I'm sorry.
Behave like a slave.
Please, stop, Asuka.
No!
I want to run away somewhere far away.
I'm home.
Sis?
Asuka?
Mom. Miku.
Aya, if you keep on crying, I can't help you.
If you tell me, maybe I can help.
It's too late. Because of me, Asuka is...
It's all my fault.
What happened to Asuka?
No!
You liked it in the asshole.
Don't!
Sakura made love here
every night and you two were born.
I'm going to do the same thing to you.
Please, don't.
Don't just cry.
Watch your sister become a woman.
Help me, Sis.
Miku...
No!
It hurts!
Miku.
Who are you?
What're you doing?
Are you all right?
You.
Ryosuke.
Yumiko!
What's the commotion downstairs?
I'll go take a look.
Miku.
Yumiko, why?
Watch out!
Ryosuke!
I didn't know.
Now I see why Asuka was acting like that.
It's all my fault.
Let's go.
Where?
We have to save Asuka!
No.
I have no face to show her.
You're scum.
Sis?
You have learned to enjoy men.
Enough, already!
I like tough bitches.
But maybe I'm not just bluffing.
You mustn't. No!
I know. You want more.
Please stop!
We're both women. Don't be embarrassed.
Don't just stare.
No!
- Give me your ass.
- No.
I'll push it into your precious hole,
while your boyfriend is watching.
Asuka.
Yumiko, tell them to stop.
It's not clean there.
Don't look. Please.
Someone help me.
It's all my fault.
It feels good.
I'm surprised how you let yourself go.
No wonder your sister is twisted.
You've been her mother.
She sent her friend a threatening letter.
Don't say that.
Asuka is making the same noise now.
Swaying her big boobs.
One day I'll have you all side by side.
Tamami.
You're late.
You have to show up as soon as I call you.
I had to go to practice.
Shit, get naked and join these two.
What, do it now.
Tamami?
Tamami, you killed...
I wanted my brother
to see me run in the race.
You know
he doesn't have much more to live.
I wanted to encourage him anyway I could.
I thought I'd do anything for that.
But I was wrong.
When I saw you,
I thought I was seeing myself.
It made me sick.
I knew I was doing something disgusting.
Tamami...
Aya.
I don't care what happened
between you and Asuka.
But...
Don't do anything you'll be sorry for!
Let's be responsible for
what we each have done.
Stop.
No!
Don't.
Please. Don't move.
No.
A gift from our Master.
Miku and I have sworn to serve them.
You must, too.
Don't be ridiculous.
We'll make sure you will.
You saw me, so this'll make us even.
No, please don't!
It's cold.
No!
It's inside me.
I'm not done with you yet.
No more.
No more. Please. For the love of God!
I can't take it anymore!
Don't move.
I want to go away. I want to run away.
But I have nowhere left...
... to run.
It's so good.
Good old days.
The history of Yumiko growing up.
It sure is.
More! Give me more!
No more. Let me go to the bathroom.
I can't hold it anymore.
You can do it here.
I will wash you thoroughly.
I found your weak spot.
It's about time.
You like to pee, don't you?
I can't hold it.
Look, back here, too.
I can't hold it. Don't look.
Mom, Miku, no more!
What is it?
Yumiko!
I'm sorry.
Your mother's masters.
They're all dead.
But how fragile motherhood is.
We gang-raped her
and gave her an enema and...
...she readily swore
to give up her husband and her family.
She had her husband
and daughters to protect.
The more you have to protect,
the more fragile you become.
I have nothing. So I'm strong.
You're wrong.
What?
I just realized something.
You can be strong
because you have something to protect.
I've always wanted to run...
...but when I realized
there was nowhere to run...
...when I realized I had to protect
my mother and Miku...
...then I had courage. And maybe that's...
Do you know
why I did not rob you of your virginity?
I didn't want you to discover
the pleasure of a woman.
Before I killed you!
Aya?
Aya. You.
Yumiko.
Let's end it.
No! I have to die.
I have to die.
Revenge is not going to bring you back.
Give me back everything I have lost.
Don't worry. Let's go look for it.
This time I'm coming with you.
We'll be together forever.
I'm sorry, Asuka. I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing, Aya?
I don't understand.
I'm really sorry.
Aya!
That was the last time I talked with Aya.
Before everything became public
and the people showed up.
Aya and others disappeared and
nobody could find them.
Tamami had to leave school
after her murder of Mr. Miyake.
But Reika's father used his influence...
... to cover up the whole thing.
My life went back to the way it was.
I dated Ryosuke for a while, but...
... I married someone else.
I thought it was all over.
I wanted it to be all over.
She was not in the dressing room.
Where has she gone to?
Asuka, I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Aya.
I promised Tamami I would be responsible.
Asuka.
Long time no see.
What are you doing?
Stop.
No!
I did make you a woman here.
Once you taste it, you'll never forget.
You haven't changed.
Size is the only thing
you've got working for you.
Don't say that.
Aya.
I will love you, Asuka. Forever and ever.
Have a nice day.
Time for your walk.
Yes, Ma'am.