No.
No, no, no!
Aya! Help me, Aya!
No!
Don't!
No. Don't!
You two girls looked bored.
We're just trying to entertain you.
Leave me alone. I don't want to.
No.
No!
You had enough. My turn.
No.
You've got cute underwear.
I wonder what's underneath.
What?
No!
Aya, Aya!
Yumiko, I can't...
Hey, Camera Girl. Film it right.
If you don't want to get gang-raped,
film it right.
I will. I'm sorry, Yumiko.
You're kidding, Aya.
Aya!
Let your friend hear your screams!
No more. Take it out!
What's wrong?
I can't. No more...
Then we'll rape you.
What're you doing?
No! Stop! No!
Look at these cute boobies.
They're too small.
I want them as big as these.
No more.
Play with them well
and they'll grow big fast.
Stop! I'll do as you say.
Aya.
I'm sorry, Yumiko.
Well, Aya, nice, isn't it?
You shot my first time really well.
I shot yours very nicely.
Let's watch it with your sister later.
You got to her, too?
Or, maybe like the last time,
we can show it to him.
To Ryosuke, I mean.
No. Not him.
I shall make you suffer,
both you and Asuka.
All the girls involved with Ryosuke.
You'll all be sorry you were born women.
Are you finished?
Let her go to school today.
If she stays away too long,
they might get suspicious.
Maybe.
Give me your tongue.
Don't do it so much.
If you enjoy it too much,
you may have to pay for it.
I can't, not while you're watching.
A woman's body is defenseless
against another woman.
No.
You have no manners.
Ask before you let it go.
Wet. Clean them.
No, they're dirty.
Dirty? It's yours.
Do it right or I'll punish you later.
Good girl.
I'll give you a reward.
Come on out, Miku!
You'll be late for school.
I want to take shower, too.
Asuka! Don't you want breakfast?
She's a little strange since last night.
I'm not going to school today.
Are you sick?
Wait!
What's going on?
Aya? Asuka's already gone...
I'm sorry, Asuka.
Good morning.
I'm sorry, I'm not used to trains.
They usually give me a ride to school.
How's your sister?
Don't worry, it's nothing.
Be quiet! You don't want people
to find out about the photo, do you?
Be quiet and nobody will see
the photo of you masturbating.
You took it?
Anything wrong, Asuka?
No. Nothing.
- A pervert?
- He's not.
Pervert!
I saw with my own eyes!
She's denying it herself.
Asuka, you hated
this man touching your butt, didn't you?
No. I didn't.
Asuka!
No, really.
He didn't do anything.
Asuka.
You called me a pervert
in front of so many people.
You have to pay for it.
What do you want? Money? How much?
I don't want money.
Do a striptease for me.
Take your clothes off.
You want me to be naked here?
You're her friend, tell her.
Please, Miss Takatsukasa. Do as he says.
Asuka!
I'm sorry.
Hurry! Before more people come in!
I know.
You need a hand?
No thank you.
Is that it?
You don't get it, do you?
Hold her.
Do you want that to go public?
Asuka, what're you doing?
No! Stop!
No!
Hold her tight.
Help me, Asuka.
Spread her legs.
Move.
Don't.
Please, Asuka.
No!
A real lady has high-class skin.
Smells really nice.
Enough! I'm going to scream.
Then your friend will be my accessory.
No.
No!
You're so careless.
Three women living alone
and you're so quick to open the door.
There was no need for this bait.
Who are you people?
A married woman knows
how to entice a man.
She's not wearing a bra.
You're wrong. I was going to take shower.
No!
A married woman smells good, too.
Let me go.
Asuka?
What did you do to my daughter?
We did nothing.
She went there on her own to get laid.
No!
Don't worry. Seems she's still a virgin.
She got raped in the ass.
She couldn't.
You. I saw you yesterday.
Miku, run.
You're not running, are you?
Doesn't it feel good to have revenge?
Don't touch Miku.
What about you?
I'm a married woman.
No.
You don't want the neighbors
to see your daughter's photo.
Bastards! Is this blackmail?
Who wouldn't want to probe
such a slutty body?
Since your husband's away...
No! Let me go!
I don't want to!
I'm sorry.
If you resist too much,
I'll do your ass again.
No! Please don't!
Sakura, lift your ass.
Your ass just won't quit.
I'm going to take you from behind
and you'll be screaming.
Please. Not like that!
You like it, too, don't you?
You smell nasty.
You're wrong.
You're breathing hard.
Stop talking nonsense.
No.
Don't!
No. Mom will be angry.
Please. Forgive me.
I'm not being mean.
What is this? You're trembling.
I was like you, once. Innocent.
I fell in love. But it didn't work out.
No!
Maybe that's why. I see you and...
You make me sick!
I'll put you on the best stage.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Instead of apologizing...
...tell me what's going on
between you and him?
Nothing. I don't know him.
Let's go somewhere to clean ourselves up.
- We need to buy undies, too.
- Don't worry about me.
My father owns a hotel nearby.
What's she doing here?
You'll come with me, won't you?
No. No!
Please. Stop!
You mean, "Please don't stop," right?
Smells like women.
Are you done with her already?
Asuka is too obedient...
...she's not fun.
My sister?
Can I put it in her?
Only her back entrance.
Not the front entrance.
I'm saving it for the show.
Not again.
No, no, please!
No, take it out!
Can you feel your sister's heat?
It was inside her a few minutes ago.
Take it out!
Is this it?
And the funny part was...
What's this? Clothes?
Stand over your friend
and put your hands against the wall.
Your hands against the wall!
- It's creepy.
- Let's go.
Asuka?
If you make too much noise,
those girls might come back to take a look.
Please. Take it out!
No!
Stop, already!
Shut up or I'll stick it in your ass!
Pull it out.
Forgive me. It hurts.
Your sister said the same thing
while she was enjoying it.
No!
This is horrible.
If you don't watch it...
...he'll do the same thing to you.
No.
Stop.
Why don't you come, already?
I'm waiting, and I'm bored.
Don't boss me around.
Would you wait for me outside?
We have to talk.
I don't want to accuse you of anything...
...but I have the right to know.
I'm sorry.
This really is it, right?
Stop complaining and start sucking.
You lick like a lady, too.
I told you to use your boobs.
How does your friend's asshole taste?
Idiot, too late now!
I'm coming. Swallow it all.
Swallow it to the last drop.
Asuka?
Not so hard.
You're mean.
I can't say that.
No.
No!
Miku.
Help.
I'm sorry, Miku.
Miku.
Miku is enjoying.
Miku has...
...your fat one...
...enjoying it!
Forgive me.
I will be your slave.
Are you running away?
Welcome back. You got them?
Go wherever you want to.
Just don't forget we have these.
Aya.