Ryoka University Hospital is...
aside from the hospital director
and the head nurse...
made up of graduate students
of Ryoka University.
Ryoka University Hospital
It has some of the most prestigious
records in the country.
Every year, several students
from the university and high school...
come to study here first-hand.
She is the daughter of the owner
and chairman...
of this hospital
and university, Ryoka Kisaragi.
Her father is currently overseas,
so she is essentially the owner.
The director, Shinobu Hazuki. Single.
She rose to the number 2 spot
by becoming the chairman's mistress.
My stomach is also clean
thanks to the enema.
The smell of semen covering my body
won't go away.
I, Minako, will serve alongside you
for the rest of my life as a nurse...
reeking of come.
Does your stomach hurt?
Show me it come out. Make it come out.
It's coming! It's coming out!
I'm being called.
Lesbian Ward: Night of Discipline
Volume 2
Record 6: Lesson #1
Yuka?
Today I'm going to steal
your other virginity, got that?
- Minako.
- Yes?
Now pour it all over, please.
There's no need to be scared.
Let's get this started.
That's it. Nice and easy.
Use your tongue all the way down,
like if it was a patient's dick.
You know the way they like it.
It's going to be your turn soon.
Yuka, does all that semen taste good?
Yuka.
Record 7: Walking the Dog
Come on, move faster!
The patients are all waiting.
It looks like someone's getting hungry.
Yes!
Harder! Harder!
My, aren't you lucky.
Getting a treat like that.
You better say thanks.
Now, let's go.
You can keep on begging forever, got that?
Now, go to the bathroom right here.
My, that doesn't look like
the position to pee.
That's more like the position to poop.
No pooping now, okay?
It's coming! It's coming!
It's so embarrassing.
Record 8: Fellatio Talk
Now let's begin with the usual service.
You need makeup.
Sexual Slave
Cosksucker Pussy Bitch
You're all set.
Allow me to clean your body!
My, it's full of smegma!
If you keep building up all this scum...
you'll get sick.
Now it's squeaky clean!
It's so big and wonderful!
I'll collect your sperm while I'm at it.
It's so hot.
It's delicious.
Does it feel good?
Does your dick feel good?
I absolutely love that dark, vein popping.
Dirty dick with big round glands.
I want to do this until I die.
Record 9: Titty Play
Don't bite. You naughty boy!
What a naughty little dick you are.
Dicks, dicks, such naughty dicks!
Become big and squirt milk out!
Record 10: Lesson #2
Get on all fours and show me your ass.
I want to see it.
I'm so embarrassed.
They're staring at my asshole.
How embarrassing!
Yuka, suck this dildo while saying,
"Please fuck me up my dirty ass."
Now say it!
Please fuck me up my dirty ass.
Your asshole, it's beautiful.
Please punish my dirty asshole.
I'll do it!
Yuka, you're beautiful.
Do I look pretty having my ass raped,
covered in come?
Am I cute?
Don't come yet. It's only just begun.
Okay.
Here I come, Yuka! We'll come together!
Record 11: Stained Glass Moon
I'm coming!
Right now, yes!