Ryoka University Hospital...
aside from the hospital director
and the head nurse...
is made up of graduate students
of Ryoka University.
It has some of the most prestigious
records in the country.
Every year, several students
from the university and high school...
come to study first-hand.
She is the daughter of the owner
and chairman of this hospital...
and university, Ryoka Kisaragi.
Her father is currently overseas,
so she is essentially the owner.
The director, Shinobu Hazuki. Single.
She rose to the number 2 spot
by becoming the chairman's mistress.
And...
when all the patients are put to sleep,
another face of the hospital appears.
A nocturnal service using the young
students and nurses as a sacrifice.
A festival for the VIP patients begins.
And today, again the beautiful students
are called in...
by the head nurse.
Lesbian Ward
Ryoka University Hospital
Starting with the hospital director,
the vice director...
the chief of the surgical department...
and the head of the internal department.
The entire staff is made up
of graduates of this university...
and this is the only hospital
in the country with an all-female staff.
And the chairman's daughter,
Ryoka Kisaragi...
being named after this hospital...
was destined to become its owner
from the day she was born.
- Yuka?
- Yes.
Maeda.
From today on, you are to save people
from disease with your service.
Yes.
Under the name of Our Lady
and the mother of nursing...
I hereby pronounce you
a full-fledged nurse of the order.
Father, Mother.
Your Yuka is becoming a nurse.
- Shiori Koike.
- Yes.
- Minako Kurokawa.
Kyoko Mitsuya.
Yes.
From that night on, my fate was sealed.
When the politician suddenly
began writhing in pain...
that night, when the head nurse
saved me.
That's right! From that night on.
Record 1 Semen Bath
Minako.
What's wrong?
Shall we take a bath? Come on.
Okay.
This is a bath made up of warm come.
Come collected over many days
from the patients.
Tonight, the patients are fetishists
that want us to become lesbians...
living a life covered with come.
The patients are watching us
through a camera.
Next to them are full-time nurses...
who help them masturbate.
And have them come.
Ejaculate over and over again.
The soap, the shampoo,
and the conditioner...
there is come in everything.
We are continually given
all the patients' semen...
until the balls containing the come
are have been sucked dry.
This hospital has a late night treatment
for VIPs with sexual worries.
A treatment where their every
sexual desire is realized.
The nurses selected
by the head nurse...
must do as she says
and serve this treatment.
Using everything, mind and body.
- Minako.
- Yes?
You seem to be getting off on this bath.
Does it feel good? Does it?
I know it does. Your pussy's all wet.
Go ahead and say it.
Yes?
Minako?
Come on, Minako.
You absolutely love semen, right?
Yes.
I absolutely love semen.
I do, I love it.
Thank you.
For making...
all of my wildest fantasies
become a reality tonight.
All of my wildest fantasies
Minako is a semen-eating slutty whore.
Good girl.
But see? You can't rest now.
Repeat it! Keep repeating it, come on!
Minako!
Minako is, Minako is a
semen-eating slutty whore.
Good girl, keep on going.
Minako is a semen-eating slutty whore.
That girl in there.
She doesn't sound so bad.
Yuka, you mean?
Of course, I trained her.
She's a good girl.
It's good you found her.
What was it again?
Minako is a semen-eating...
The politician, Kimura, in room 504,
was going to die...
so I had them put in charge of him.
Them? There were more than one?
Yes, it saved me the trouble.
I assume that you switched
the intravenous fluid?
During the night shift, at that.
All nurses put responsibility first,
after all.
Then, as a showing of appreciation...
and in return for your keeping
of their secret...
they are to work at your late night ward.
You understand exactly
what I mean, don't you?
It's all downhill from there.
But...
thanks to that, they are guaranteed
to become nurses.
And also...
to have a job for the rest of there
lives, isn't that a form of happiness?
Record 2: Love Gun
Minako.
Lick it.
Yes.
Okay.
Now, get on your hands and knees.
Look that way and raise your ass high up.
Show my your asshole, Minako.
What do you want me to do?
Give me it to me now.
I can't hear you?
Give it to me!
Give you what?
Penis!
You won't become a good nurse
if you can't beg correctly.
You have to tell me where you want what.
My ass, in my ass.
Please jam that dick up my ass.
You are such a good girl.
Here you go.
Please stop it!
Please stop!
Please, stop it, not again.
- Why?
- It'll leak out.
The come will leak out of my ass.
Please don't do it again.
Does your stomach hurt?
Yes.
Show me your come.
Make it come out.
Right now.
You're mean, Yuka.
It's coming! It's coming out!
It's coming out!
Was that okay?
Yes.
Record 3: Shave
My, you take care of yourself.
You won't be able to become
a cute nurse with all this thick hair.
No way.
It can't be helped.
If you don't spread them far
enough, I'll cut your pretty pussy.
Okay, I'm going to shave all this bush, then.
See, it's now clean. It's like a baby.
Now where's your greeting to everyone?
I am Minako Kurokawa, a student nurse.
My skin is nice and shiny
thanks to the semen bath.
My stomach is also clean
thanks to the enema.
The smell of semen covering
my body won't go away.
I, Minako, will serve alongside you...
for the rest of my life
as a nurse reeking of come.
Please make me your one
and only semen nurse.
Record 4: Red Thread
Let's get to know each other.
I did it.
It's my turn now.
Here, too.
Record 5: Nurse Cap
And...
the girls who the VIPs like are hired
as that person's personal nurse.
With a devoted heart,
we give our entire life to that patient...
as a nurse of sex.
That's right.
"Our entire life."