Have you heard?
It looks like another
murder happened last night.
I'm so scared!
They say every
victim is a beautiful woman.
You should be careful.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who
should be careful, Azusa.
Especially when you go out at night...
Excuse me?
I don't go out a lot at night.
I just haven't the time lately.
Why?
Actually...
I have this new private teacher.
And you know what?
He's so good-looking.
Again?
What do you mean by that?
Anyway, he's tall, handsome, and cool.
Hey, hey.
Are you listening?
Miho!
What's wrong?
Can you see him?
Next stop is the private school.
The private school.
Who?
A strange man holding a cat.
Please be careful as you step down.
Thank you very much.
Let's go.
Good morning.
Great!
You're always so good.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Are you okay?
Azusa, what's this?
You're talking about this stone?
Remember when we
went to Karuizawa last time?
I picked it up then.
Pretty, isn't it?
Yes...
Miho?
Hey, Miho!
What's wrong?
Everybody's gone already.
Well, can you give me this stone?
What?
Why not?
It's just something I found.
But why do you want it?
I'm just kind of interested in it.
It's not just an ornament, there's
something mysterious about it.
I always feel relaxed when
I look into a beautiful stone...
Oh, I have a pretty stone, too.
All right, all right.
Whatever.
I have to go.
W-Wait a moment, Azusa!
Hey, Azusa!
Sorry, I have to go somewhere.
Okay, take care of yourself.
See you.
My goodness!
I didn't expect it to take this long.
It was that cat again.
I was so scared.
I was asked a lot of
questions by the police.
And?
Of course, I told them everything I saw.
But they said the
cat didn't kill anyone...
I think that man did it.
Remember, yesterday he
was in the bus watching us...
The cat he held was the
same cat I saw last night.
I'm positive...
Are you listening to me?
What?
O-Of course.
Are you thinking about a guy again?
I told you yesterday.
My private teacher is coming.
I'm thinking about seducing him.
You're kidding me.
You come here to pick me up?
Miho, this is my
private teacher, Mr. Inoue.
This is my friend, Miho Murakami.
H-Hello.
See you tomorrow.
The bus is too late.
Jeez, aren't I attractive enough?
Azusa.
Y-Yes?
I have something to ask you.
About what?
You picked up a beautiful
stone at Karuizawa, didn't you?
What?
It's very important.
Please think about it seriously.
A stone...
A pretty stone at Karuizawa.
Yes.
A pretty stone that shines blue.
Come to think of it, I
remember something like that.
Where is it now?
Let me see...
Where could it be...
Azusa!
Take it easy.
I don't have it right now.
Then where is it?
Let's sit on the sofa and talk about It.
Well, Mr. Inoue...
about the stone, don't you?
You want to know
I can tell you about it.
In return...
...﻿would you do what I want?
Well...
...﻿Mr. Inoue.
Mr. Inoue.
Hey, you're so hard already.
It's wonderful!
Mr. inoue, please lick me.
So good...
The stone...
I-I gave it...
I gave it to Miho!
More, more!
I-I'm coming.
Mr. Inoue...
Hello?
Azusa...
He's...
He's the sex beast.
He killed Azusa.
Wait!
Open the door!
Please, open the door!
Mr. Inoue!
Wait!
Mr. Inoue, please help me!
That man...
Stay away from him!
Stop...
Miho.
He is looking for the Dark Stone.
The Dark Stone?
The Stone you got from Azusa.
He approached Azusa
and tried to take the stone.
And, he killed her.
You have the Dark Stone, don't you?
I need it now.
Finally...
Finally, I have the Dark Stone.
You...
You killed...
You killed Azusa!
You'll pay for that!
Please, listen to me.
I didn't kill her.
You're the sex beast.
That's obvious.
Yes. I'm a sex beast,
but I didn't kill anybody.
You saw, didn't you?
Inoue's true nature.
He's a sex beast, too.
I was chasing him.
I came here to kill him.
It wasn't you who killed Azusa, was it?
You aren't the serial killer.
No, he is the criminal.
Then why was that
cat always at the scene?
Because I have been chasing him.
Sex beasts have taken human
energy to survive for a long time...
But we never kill human beings...
...because we would die
if our food source died out.
We have co-existed with you always...
However, now there is a special
sex beast, whose aim is to kill humans.
I have to kill him for our race.
I have to take back the stone, too.
What is the stone?
That stone is the Dark Stone,
handed down for a long, long time.
The Dark Stone?
The Dark Stone
gives us unlimited power.
He tried to get the
stone when it was sealed.
I got in his way, and we began to fight.
I tried to take back the Dark Stone.
We couldn't approach because it
was protected by a mysterious power.
It was the power of the Bright Stone.
The Bright Stone is
dangerous, because it can kill us.
So, he couldn't approach Azusa
easily because he was afraid of the stone.
But, she was killed.
She didn't have the Bright Stone.
The person who has the stone is...
...you.
At that time, only you were near Azusa.
It can't be...
The Bright Stone.
I'm positive.
You must have it.
There is a stone in my charm.
Where is it?
In my pouch.
Shit, now he has it.
That's right!
It's in my locker from yesterday!
You left it there?
Yes.
Let's go!
Found it!
We can get rid of him with this.
Yeah.
I can avenge Azusa, can't I?
That's right.
Let's go.
I have to hurry...
Wait!
I'll fight with you.
Here.
Finally, I have unlimited power!
Now!
Hurry up!
Shoot!
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I could
take revenge for Azusa.
You...
I've reached the end of my life.
Don't say that
What can I do for you?
I know!
If you take my energy...
I can't do that
You're a sex beast...
...﻿but you fought for us.
This is the one thing I can do for you.