Best Beauty Body Incorporated.
Abbreviated BBB.
This is where I'll be working
from now on.
A mid-sized woman's lingerie maker.
Incidentally, about 80 percent
of the employees here are women.
And they're all better looking than average.
That's what people say.
So, the President's group doesn't have
any idea of our plans?
No need to worry,
we're in the clear, sir.
Good. I'm counting on you, Zaitu.
Thank you. Excuse me, will you?
Right.
Lingerie Club Office 1
Come on, spread your legs!
How can I tell if the products fit?
You hear me? Don't piss me off,
spread those legs!
Yes, sir.
How's this, Mr. Yamakura?
Yes, that's better.
That's not, what are you...
It's okay. I have to check the Fabric,
it's so soft.
No, not there!
Now you're getting the idea.
All right, pull your panties up.
All the way up inside you.
No! I can't.
Are you saying you don't want my
company's business anymore?
Please don't say that!
Then get on with it! Silly girl.
Yes, sir. Like this?
Yes, higher. Get it all the way in!
Lift your ass up so I can really see!
Like this, Mr. Yamakura?
That's perfect. Keep on going.
Very good.
Yes, I especially like how your wet slit
sucks the panties' crotch.
It's my pleasure, sir.
That's what this is all about.
Sir! What are you doing there?
This area is for authorized personnel only.
This one is the super hot!
Thirty-six, 26-36, and blazing.
I'm sorry. Actually,
today is my first day...
I was looking for the Personnel Office.
Would you...
Personnel? That must make you
the new Section Chief...
- for the number 2 planning department.
- That's right.
My name's Yusuke Nakanishi.
And you are?
Rena Asaoka
from the advertising department.
I heard that we're getting
the temp agency's best.
It's an honor to meet you.
Let me show you the way.
Would you like to follow me around here?
Are you coming or not?
- Can I ask something, are product...
- Excuse me, but...
for your own sake, you should mind
your own business here.
That has nothing to do with you.
Here, this way.
Temp Careers temp agency
is famous for its high quality staff...
meeting all client demands.
Even if those demands are
rather delicate.
I know your reputation,
and I'm counting on you.
Thank you.
However, I didn't know the Personnel
Manager was the President's son.
What was it you wanted me to do?
An easy job.
Eliminate the Vice President's faction.
The Vice President's faction?
Yes, I think you're right.
Vice President Horida rose to his position
from within Engineering...
For the last few years there's been
friction between him and the President.
Especially recently.
The Vice President's closest crony...
the head of the planning department...
Miki and Zaitu, Chief
of the planning department's first division...
are particularly suspicious.
I see.
This is just a hunch,
but I think Vice President Horida...
is planning to take over the company
but then there's no actual evidence, either.
We have to keep this quiet
amongst ourselves.
So, you want me to collect evidence
and get rid of them...
before the executive meeting
in three months, correct?
Right. Like I said, you will be the planning
department's second division chief.
You have three months
until the board meeting...
how you take care of it is up to you.
Don't forget. Never betray me.
Do you understand?
These guys are total losers.
Well, what to start with?
The planning department head, Miki...
and section one's chief, Zaitu...
getting rid of them will be
the best way to cripple the VP's faction.
Boss!
You're Miss Mayumi, right?
Yes, that's right!
Chief Nakanishi, please take a look
at my new design!
I've been dreaming about it for so long!
I wanted to debut a killer new line
for our new manager!
I just knew you could do it,
from the second I saw you!
Mayumi's at it again.
If she want's to be a go-getter, fine.
But leave me the hell out it.
Not going to happen.
No way our designs will get approved.
Nobody even thinks
were even part of the company.
Let's do it! Come on, Boss!
You certainly seem motivated.
Yes, Sir!
First of all, could you
bring me a hot cup of tea?
Tea? Yes, Sir!
Right away, dear sir!
At least someone around here
will do something.
Here's the data
Fijiyama said he'd send.
Apparently, the girls in this file
are the key to this whole business.
Rena Asaoka, advertising.
That chick from the hall.
And, next we have...
Chisa Sakurai, research and development
supervisor. A real star in that department.
And that leaves...
Alice Nonoyama?
Wasn't she the one
at the product demo?
Here's your coffee, Mr. Nakanishi!
This is coffee? I asked you
specifically to bring me tea!
What? I blew it!
I'll go make some right now!
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry about it. This is fine.
Please forgive me!
I'm so sorry, sir! I'm sorry!
There something I wanted to
ask you about.
Yes?
The Product Demonstrations?
I think they're part
of the planning division...
section 1 is in charge of them, section 2
never has anything to do with the demos.
I don't really ever hear anything
good about them.
I guess she's out.
Maybe I'll try later.
Hey there!
Can I help you with anything
in our department?
Hi! I'm Nakanishi, the new...
I already know.
You're the head of section 2, right?
I'm Alice Nonoyama,
the supervisor of the department.
It's nice to meet you! You're a lot better
looking than I imagined!
Welcome.
I can't wait to give you the tour
and show you all the sites around here.
Why, thank you.
And I heard you were
this blonde beauty...
but it looks like
that was quite an understatement.
And not merely beautiful, but...
Holy shit.
You're sweet, but...
isn't that what we call
"sexual harassment?"
Too bad.
That's just how I am, I guess.
That's okay.
I certainly don't hate it.
Was there anything else
I can do for you or help you with?
What about those
we were talking about?
Yes.
I can certainly start work
on anything you like.
You sure can.
What about those product demos?
Miss Nonoyama?
Planning manager Miki wants you to see
him in his office after 3 o'clock.
Shall I confirm it?
Yes. I'll see him there.
Wait a minute, Alice!
It looks like Miki's got her tied-up
pretty much constantly.
But why the hell does Alice let them...
Here it is. R & D department.
All right, where is she?
Right there.
That's the one, Chisa Sakurai.
One of the best minds in the company.
I can tell from her demeanor
she only cares about work.
But nothing could hide
those amazing tits!
Huge, double D's at least.
But they look perfect!
No one's ever laid a finger on them.
But I think I'll deal with Alice first.
Boy, I'm really looking forward
to doing that.
Tomorrow?
Yes. Someone from Itsukoshi
made the request.
He requested you specifically.
And their chief of sales will be there as well.
What?
I can't.
They said they wanted to spend some
real quality time with you.
Not there, please! No!
You always get wet way too fast!
That's good.
Anyone in there, it's Zaitu.
Please come in!
Excuse me.
I've reserved a conference room
for the product demonstration.
Excellent!
I don't want to do this anymore.
- Please forgive me!
- All right, then.
I'll call the U.S. And cancel our contract
with you. Is that what you want?
No! Anything but that! Please!
Well, in that case...
just do what he wants then.
You know it's a good deal for you.
Now, I think you need
some practice!
That's the way, you slut!
Just like that.
Make sure you squeal as much tomorrow,
you little cunt!
I'm the first one here!
Good morning.
Boss? Good morning!
How come you're here so early?
Just trying to get used
to the new office.
What's a great boss!
By the way, I went through
all the plan reports from section 2...
and your designs were very interesting,
to say the least.
Especially the seamless lingerie.
Some points need a few minor changes,
but on the whole...
it really looks rather good.
Will you look it over and see
what improvements you can make?
Maybe you could ask some
of the others to help, too.
Are you serious?
Sure.
If we work this out, it'll be a hit.
We can really surprise
the shit out of everyone!
You'll be into this, won't you, baby?
"The shit out of them?"
That's right,
we'll surprise the whole department.
Going to the product demo?
Mr. Nakanishi?
What is it?
- What do you want?
- To help you, that's all.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't even try that.
I know what's going on
at these product demos.
You've got no real choice
in the matter, do you?
That's not true. I want the clients
to realize the quality of our lingerie...
it's not what you think.
Listen...
I'm sorry, but I looked into your file.
You're working here
for your grandmother...
who lives all by herself in the U.S.
Isn't that right?
In fact, she's in a hospital
with a serious medical condition.
You're paying for that as well.
Am I right?
- Stop it!
- Just quit this crap!
Thanks, really.
But this is my own problem.
Just forget about it, okay?
Goodbye, I have to go.
Can I Have your attention?
Let's begin the meeting!
This is a huge chance for us.
We've got to get together
and make this happen, or else!
We've got to crush those other sections!
Are you with me?
No!
You know that's not gonna happen.
- That's for sure.
- Are you two with me?
Yeah, got it.
All right, we're with you, then.
Well, well. I've been dreaming of
face-fucking a blonde like this.
We're going to fuck you for hours.
What do you think of that, bitch?
Suck it! Suck it!
She's just about ready for me.
Keep sucking!
Here you go, bitch!
All the way in.
This is why I love product demos!
You can't go in there!
Mr. Nakanishi!
Please, stop!
What do you think you are doing?
You have to leave!
Mr. Nakanishi!
Who the hell are you!
You can't just walk in here!
Yusuke.
Alice, put your clothes on and go.
Here.
What's going on? I have to do this.
Don't worry about your grandma.
She's fine now.
What the fuck is going on here,
and who the hell are you?
Gentlemen, Please excuse the intrusion.
I'm Nakanishi, the new head of section 2.
It more than a pleasure to meet both of you.
I'll be taking over for the rest of the
product demonstration from here.
What the fuck you say?
That's it! We're out of here!
Wait! Mr. Yamakura!
I'm so terribly sorry about all this,
allow us to make it up to you later!
Screw you!
You'll rue this day, I swear it!
But Mr. Yamakura...
Are you insane?
Have you any idea what you've done?
But, then again, thank you, really.
You were so gallant! I loved it!
And my grandma?
How did you do it? Just who are you?
Just your average temp, that's all.
I happen to have a friend who runs
a hospital in the U.S. No big deal.
It's a good place,
and he'll set it up...
so you can take care of her
with your regular salary.
You'll never have to worry about it again.
Everything will be taken care of.
You're so sweet.
Whatever!
I'm only here to try my hand
at a bit of sexual harassment.
What?
This place is Nirvana!
I get to screw pretty girls
and then they work for me.
What do you think of that?
Would you be into something like that?
You really are insane!
But that's almost kind of hot.
And by the way, I never let anyone fuck
around with a girl I'm into.
Wait a minute.
Are you hitting on me?
I told you, that's what I'm here for.
Pervert!
Why? You want me to stop?
No.
What a tight ass, really smooth.
Hey, wait! We can't do this here!
Anyone could just walk in!
I didn't know you were this kind of guy.
Can't believe it.
You have no idea.
This is just the beginning
of a mutually beneficial partnership.
Beginning of what kind of partnership?
You know, that nasty, kinky, freaky shit.
Like what?
So round and plump.
No!
Damn, already wet?
Your gash is soaking.
You must have been getting off before.
Don't be mean.
Hey, no fair!
I think it's my turn to show
what teasing really is!
Your cock, it's just incredible to me.
Son of a bitch!
You really are good, Alice!
No wonder everyone wants
to get in you.
Yeah, suck that. Good girl.
Hey, boss. Do you like my clit?
It's perfect, hot and dripping.
I can't wait to stick my cock in you.
It's begging for a stiff fuck.
I think I'll stop and admire this
cute little asshole.
Stop teasing and nail me! Do it now.
"Nail"? I'm not sure
I understand what you mean.
Please, I want it right here.
Your throbbing, hard cock
in my tight, hot cunt. Please! Please!
I want it now!
I'm not sure
you really want it that badly.
I do, please! I'm begging you!
Okay, if you want it that much, I hope
you can handle me.
I love it! Harder, harder!
Yes! Right there! More!
Yes! Yes!
Fuck me hard! More!
Rip me in half, baby!
Please, please harder!
Yes!
More!
Fuck me! Fuck me hard!
I want it. More!
It's so deep!
I want it all the way in!
Yusuke, you're amazing!
I never knew it could be like this!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
Mr. Yamakura from Itsukishi
Department Stores told me...
he wanted to reduce
the terms of our deal.
Just what in the hell is going on, Zaitu?
I smoothed it over this time...
I'm sorry, but listen, some new guy...
Nakanishi from over in section 2...
he fucked up the product demo.
Nakanishi?
You mean the guy
the President's son hired?
That's him.
I think we should take
some extra precautions and...
I think he needs to be eliminated.
And I can count on you to deal
with him yourself?
Of Course!
You know where my loyalties are.
All right, then. You take care of it.
So, do you like it inside me?
Believe me, it's unreal, baby.
Are you coming?
You're close, aren't you? Me too!
Please come inside me.
I want to feel your hot jizz in me.
Please come.
Just blow your load as deep as you can!
Come with me, it's okay, now!
Yes!
NEXT TARGET