No!
I know you fuck them in here.
I've been watching you.
Just look at yourself. You're loving this!
They're stealing company secrets
to sell to the highest bidder, aren't they?
I'll take your silence as a "yes."
Stop it!
I thought you said you didn't like this.
But you're sopping wet
just from a bit of fingering.
No!
Best Beauty Body Inc.'s stocks
are fluctuating in an odd pattern lately.
And when these fluctuations
are peaking...
even though the stocks are being offered
at an inflated price...
other companies are grabbing them up!
Do they have anything to do with that?
I don't know anything!
Please stop! Someone might
see us from outside!
Why? Let them watch.
Why are you...
Why are you doing this to me?
Please stop!
No!
I can't believe we went to so many
lingerie boutiques!
I'd never even been
to one before today!
So you didn't enjoy yourself?
Well, no.
I'm amazed how serious you take this.
You mean my work?
I want to do every thing I can...
to make sure our products
are presented the way they deserve to be.
Every weekend?
Just about. I guess so.
You really love your work.
I guess I do.
I guess I was hoping
for a more romantic date.
Rain?
Shit, I didn't bring an umbrella.
My apartment's close by here.
I'll lend you one.
This is a nice place you have.
Let me get that umbrella for you.
Must be expensive living in such luxury.
How do you do it on your salary?
This Zaitsu from section one.
So is he your boyfriend?
How long have you been going out?
My privacy is none of your business.
Sorry.
Zaitsu? I can't really picture
that fanatic as your lover. I don't get it.
Not any more...
but he used to be so different.
Sweet, gentle, and he truly loved me.
But you're also seeing Miki, aren't you?
I found out that Miki owns this building.
You're such a bastard!
I'm that kind of girl, I guess. Disappointed?
Did you think I was different
from everyone else?
No, I just what to know something.
What are you... Stop! Stop it!
Let me go!
You can't do this!
Stop or I'll scream!
Now, tell me about that hacking
into R&D's network.
You still haven't answered my question.
Just what the hell are those swine up to?
Wait, no, not there!
No! Please!
I get it. Quite a nice little rosebud
you've got here.
So, it looks like you're a bit
of a back door slut.
No, not there. Please stop!
Damn! I'm barely rimming you,
and you're already soaked!
You're even drenching the floor!
You need a plug for this little hole.
Slides right in with ease.
You're, huge!
You horny little slut!
You're tighter than I thought.
You make a great ass fuck!
Look at that guy over there
checking you out.
He's staring at your dripping wet pussy
and cock-stuffed ass.
Don't say that kind of dirty stuff.
Give him a nice little show to jerk-off to.
Now, answer me.
What are they trying to do?
I don't know anything about it.
Don't even try lying.
No!
Stop, it's too much!
What's too much?
Grind your ass!
You know you want me to!
I can't take this! I'm so hot!
Fuck me in the ass!
More! Harder!
You like to ass-fucked that much, do you?
I love it! It feels so good!
Give me more!
Your dick feels amazing!
Why did you stop?
Tell me everything those bastards are up to.
I can't.
If you tell me, I'll finish fucking you.
But...
Just tell about their dirty little plans.
Just say it!
M and A.
M and A?
That's right.
I don't know anything beyond that.
I promise.
There. That's a good girl.
Did you still want that ass fucking?
My God!
You're pulling my asshole inside out!
God! I'm coming!
Alice, that looks incredible on you!
Even though I'm a girl,
I can't stop staring at you body!
Why, thank you!
But it's not me...
it's this seamless lingerie
that looks so good!
I've never worn anything more comfortable!
So, we choose Alice
as our spokes model then!
Just leave it to me!
Great! Thanks a lot!
It's time for the presentation.
I've sent invitations
to every single department store...
and lingerie boutique in the city.
This has to be a success!
All right then! Let's do it!
How is it? Anything suspicious?
Nothing. There's been no movement at all
in the past couple of weeks.
I'm afraid they may have discovered
that we're watching them.
There's no clear evidence
linking the hacking...
with the stock fluctuations.
I see.
I'm sorry, I can't help you anymore.
No, you've done a great job.
Mr. Nakanishi.
Wet already?
You are a horny little bitch, aren't you?
Stop!
So juicy.
Wait, there's an e-mail coming.
- Mr. Nakanishi?
- What is it?
Fuck!
It's been copied anonymously
to the entire company.
Nakanishi.
Did you see the e-mail?
I totally did! Mr. Nakanishi, right?
And the girl looked like Rena
from marketing!
I know! That girl was Rena for sure!
But do you think it's true...
that he was taking advantage
and raping her?
That fucking son of a bitch!
Stop it!
That picture is total bullshit!
Someone's trying to screw with him.
Besides, we've got the
presentation tomorrow.
Come on girls, let's go!
All right!
Chief.
Spreading around dirty pictures of yourself
is some pretty perverted shit.
You did a really fine job selling me out.
I'm quite impressed, actually.
No! It wasn't me!
Hey there, love birds.
This is a business,
not a bower for some lovers' spat.
You two should really get a room.
Well. I didn't realize it was the
infamous Mr. Nakanishi.
Zaitsu. So it was you, then.
What are you up to here, anyway?
I'd have though you'd have a more
urgent matter to deal with at present.
About the section chief you replaced.
He quit due to some sort of sex scandal.
Be a pity if the same thing happened to you.
Let's go, Rena. I wouldn't hang around
him if I were you.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
welcome to Best Beauty Body!
So many people.
Mayumi's done a great job.
Exciting and innovative designs.
Seamless lingerie!
It's Karma, you know?
We hope you'll enjoy the show!
That's what you get for fooling
around on me!
You're right.
But with this many people here...
I hope my last project here
will be a success.
I think I can help you out with that.
Hold this for me.
What the hell's this?
So, without further ado...
I present the innovative 3D weave
technology of Seamless Lingerie!
Take a good look.
I'd like you all to examine my panty-line.
What do you see?
Notice how the lingerie
perfectly forms...
to my body no matter what
movements I make...
I get it.
Moreover, this...
...product is never binding
even with exaggerated activity...
making it both stylish and sporty.
So, she slipped a vibrator
in her cunt beforehand.
Wow, she's like a bitch in heat.
So, even in a pose like this,
a woman will never...
need to worry about the fit of her lingerie!
Thank you very much!
Yes, you'd like to place an order
for the entire line?
If you'd sign here at the bottom,
we'll be all set. Thank you.
A contract to carry the Seamless Lingerie?
Nice work, Mayumi!
Alice! Thank you so much!
You were awesome!
You looked totally beautiful
and gorgeous...
and really sexy, too!
Thanks, but that's because Chisa
designed it so perfectly!
But it was Mayumi's idea in the first place.
I made what she requested.
- It wasn't really all me.
- Everyone did great.
Mr. Nakanishi!
You all really did an excellent job.
Thanks for everything.
Hey, Rena!
The presentation was a great success.
They can't dissolve section 2 now, at least.
I guess not.
They'll get rid of me for sure
at the next board meeting.
But, I did my best. No regrets.
See you.
I'm quite disappointed.
I really though that I could count
on you to be discreet, Nakanishi.
Nakanishi?
Hey Mayumi. What's with the sad face?
That's not like you at all.
Is it really true that you're leaving
the company?
Yeah.
Why? The product demo was such
a great success, and all because of you!
I have to deal with the scandal.
I don't really have a choice.
But that bullshit was all a set-up!
I just know it!
Thanks Mayumi, for believing in me
to the very end.
Mayumi?
Nakanishi...
I think I'm in love with you.
You really are beautiful, Mayumi.
Now move your hands away
and show me your tight little body.
I don't know, I'm so nervous.
Go on.
Naka...
Beautiful tits.
They fit perfectly in my hands.
You don't mind that
my tits aren't very big at all?
Not at all. Yours really turn me on.
It all pretty and pink you know.
I love it.
Don't state at me like that!
I'm getting embarrassed.
Mayumi.
Well, then. Do you think you're ready?
Nakanishi.
Yeah?
It's my first time doing this.
What?
But I want you to be my first.
Be gentle, please.
Just relax. Here I go.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm okay now. You can keep going.
Are you ready?
More please, more!
Nakanishi!
I can feel you so deep inside me!
Am I doing everything okay?
Your tight little cunt feels incredible.
Nakanishi! I think I'm coming!
Me, too! It feels so good inside your cunt!
I'm going to come!
Come inside me, please! I want it!
I can feel your jizz inside me. It's still hot.
Hey, Mayumi!
I'm fine. I just can't help crying.
Did I hurt you?
No it's not that. I'm just so terribly
happy that you were my first.
Thank you. Thank you for everything.
Rena, I appreciate you
coming to say goodbye. I'm touched.
Take this.
What is it?
This is the log data containing the record
of Zaitsu's hacks into the network...
and evidence showing his plan
to manipulate company stocks...
for a hostile takeover
by the M and A company.
I also found Miki's bank statement...
with payments showing
his involvement, too.
Why are you...
It should be more than enough
to prove their corruption.
Are you sure you want to do this?
You'll be implicating yourself, too.
I've thought about this for a long time.
My mind's made up.
All right, if you're sure.
Thank you, Rena. Really.
There's one thing that I really regret
about all this.
What's that?
That I couldn't star
in your new commercials myself!
Well then, shall we face the music?
With Rena's help, I was finally able...
to depose the Vice President's faction.
And due to the tremendous success
of Seamless Lingerie...
I was even asked to take over Miki's position
as overall planning department manager.
Could you be more gentle?
Sorry!
Rena's hard at work as my new secretary.
Mayumi! Keep it down!
Everyone can hear you!
I'm coming!
Right there! Yes!
You're getting hornier everyday!
Just look at the size of this dildo!
Yes, right there!
It's your fault, you know!
Right there, yes! Fuck me!
No. You can't.
You really want me to stop?
No. Don't stop!
You're really confusing me, Chisa.
I want it! Harder! Please!
My daily grind is not
all that bad, considering.
- Again?
- Yeah, right.
I know you still want to show off.
But...
I can't believe your stamina.
How many times a day is enough for you?
Enough for me? You've got to be joking!
No!
I need this! Fuck me again already!
God, this feels good! More, more!
Harder!
You're amazing!
But I won't be here forever.
I'm ready to go global
I'll use this company to get me...
to the top, and then I'll take on the world.
And all of the women too, of course.