It came out pretty good.
I can't believe you're making me do
this, you pervert!
Call me an artist.
Besides, it makes a great souvenir.
Whatever you say.
Hey, behave yourself!
So, the girl I asked you about...
so what can you tell me about her?
Chisa Sakurai from Research
and Development, right?
Are you going to hit on her like this, too?
Don't jump to conclusions.
I wanted to ask for her help with this
new line we're designing.
Liar.
I know you already.
But, it's okay.
Let me tell you something else.
She looks really demure,
but she's got a real...
nympho side-once you get her going.
- What is that, women's intuition?
- Something like that.
Thanks, that's good information to have.
Yes!
- Yusuke, I want...
- Already?
You want something in return
for your advice?
Is this what you had in mind, Alice?
LINGERIE CLUB VOL 2
Zaitu?
You're here late. Working overtime?
Yes.
So, do you have time
free for me sometime?
You and me?
Yeah, we're working
on a new design at section 2...
so I wanted some help
from the advertising department.
I think you'll need to make
a sample to...
show me first before
I can do anything for you.
The best brain in the advertisement
department, Rena Masaoka...
together with Miki's trusted,
Zaitu from planning section 1...
it would appear she's part
of the Vice President's faction.
How do you like it?
You are wet like a fountain,
you must be loving it.
Yes! I love it! I love it! More!
Look at you!
So many people at work admire you
for your business sense...
but in reality you're a dumb slut, aren't you?
Admit it.
You fucking whore.
I want more! Harder, deeper!
I like it!
I think this design is perfect!
Really? Thank you so much!
No thank you. Great job guys!
Thank you! I'm so happy.
I knew seamless lingerie would work.
You always give good advice.
Usually, a bra leaves marks
on the skin right here.
And panties are always a problem...
binding and marking here and here,
and right where the garter belt lays. See?
Hey, Mayumi!
My gosh! What am I doing?
I'll get some tea!
Mr. Nakanishi!
You scared me! What are you doing here?
My bad. I didn't mean to scare you.
- I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't be so jumpy.
I wasn't expecting anyone else to be here.
I though I'd finish my work.
About the new designs section 2 came up
with. Will you make a sample of them?
What? I told you I couldn't help you!
I'm too busy for any of that.
I've got my own work to finish.
Come on, don't be like that.
Relax, working in the dark like this,
all by your self...
you need a break...
is there a reason
why you need the lights off?
Well?
If I remember it correctly,
we need to get permission...
to use the office after business hours.
I'm sure such an honest person like you
wouldn't forget something like that.
So, what about the sample?
You'll take of it, won't you?
My beautiful baby.
Like I said.
Mr. Nakanishi! Stop that,
or I'll call security.
Come on! Just say yes.
Please stop!
Hey, is someone in there?
It's me, Nakanishi
from the planning department!
The new chief of section 2!
Everything okay?
I'm looking for some data for our new
design. I heard it's somewhere in here.
I'm still a rookie here,
so I've got a lot to learn.
Stop.
I see. It's easy to work hard when you're
looking at panties all day.
You got that right! I'm almost done, though.
Sorry to bother you!
Don't worry about that!
You can stay as long as you need to.
Just make sure you
lock the door when you leave.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Thanks!
Why are you hiding under there?
You rotten bastard!
Be quiet! That guard might come back.
You've got to keep your mouth shut!
These are some of biggest I've ever
seen. Amazing.
No!
No, stop!
Please stop!
Don't look at me!
This is interesting.
What do you call this right here,
Miss Sakurai?
I don't know.
Hey, what's going on down there?
How come you're so wet?
Please stop, please!
I can't take it anymore, please stop.
Mr. Nakanishi, Please let me go.
I can't take this humiliation anymore!
- No!
- You can come out now.
This is how you get people
to do your work?
Fine, then.
I'll work on the sample for you.
But I need something in return.
In return from me?
Recently, the engineering department's
network server was hacked by someone.
What?
Hey, you're not trying to trick me
or anything, are you?
I'm very serious.
But, it's clear the hacking was an internal
job someone within the company...
and I'll find out who it was!
In order to do so...
I need a completely independent
network server...
that's fully separated from our company.
But it's too much to deal with on my own.
That's where I need your help.
What kind of money are we talking about?
That's what you need from me, right?
About $30,000.
$30,000!
That won't come out of my pocket.
I don't want an outsider coming in
and messing with our technology!
Even if that person is from our company!
I've got my pride.
Okay, I understand, just relax.
Do you think you can help me?
I think I can do something about it.
Just, don't forget
about the samples, okay? 'Bye.
Mr. Nakanishi.
Hacking into R& D interesting.
Alice wasn't kidding, that Chisa Sakurai
does have a nympho side.
So, R&D is his next target?
Yes, it would appear so,
as far as I can tell.
- He is getting in our way.
- I agree.
Morning everyone!
I can't believe it.
Did you know Mr. Nakanishi...
convinced R&D to make our samples?
That's our Boss, you know!
He could really save our section.
But people on above him must really
hate him, though.
It's so obvious.
Why?
Because, Fujiyama at personnel was the
one who headhunted Mr. Nakanishi.
And Mr. Fujiyama is in league
with the President's faction.
So there.
Nakanishi has become quite a nuisance
for the Vice President's faction.
I hope he'll come out
of this alright, through.
Hi there.
How long have you been standing
there looking up my dress?
As long as seemed appropriate.
So, what do you want?
Can I help you?
I think we are almost done with making
the samples for our new design...
I thought you could help me
with that advertising now.
- So you didn't hear about it, then?
- What?
Chisa Sakurai from R&D was dismissed
as the R&D supervisor today.
Every project she was working on...
and all her previous responsibilities
were taken away from her.
It's really too bad, don't you think?
It's really too bad.
Fuck! This is no good.
Mr. Nakanishi.
Sorry about what happened.
No. I'm sorry.
I couldn't finish the sample for you.
It's my fault. They told me I was
disturbing the workplace...
because my work here
has been entirely self-gratifying.
They said I'm a cancer in the department!
I've slaved so hard for this company.
All I've really done
is make trouble for everyone.
Especially you, Mr. Nakanishi. I'm sorry.
I feel terrible about this,
but I really needed that money.
I have bills to pay, I really trusted
what you were doing.
I know. I'm terribly sorry.
I'm not saying you have to pay back
the money right away or anything...
but at least don't ruin
the new designs for our section.
I even had to lie to security,
that was difficult for me to do.
I'll do anything to make it up to you.
Don't move.
See, the sample needs
to fit your body just right. Beautiful.
Look, this part right here especially
needs to be more relaxed.
With our new design,
getting into a position like this...
will be so much more comfortable.
This seam right here.
Do you know what I mean?
I can't do this.
Look how tightly the seam is pulling
from the thigh to your buttocks.
Don't move!
And this is the most important point,
right here?
Are you getting wet over this?
Well are you?
No! It's not like that! Please stop!
Please stop!
I said don't' move!
Damn, you really are getting wet.
Not just wet, but drenched!
Scream!
I can't believe people
think you're so innocent.
Stop already, please let me go!
Yeah!
I guess I'll let you go, then.
For the day.
What, you mean I'm not forgiven yet?
Of course not. I need another favor.
What?
Keep working on you hacking investigation.
You want to know who responsible
for this, don't you?
Well, yeah. Of course.
Then find out who did this, okay?
Yes, Sir!
- Take care of it, okay?
- All right.
- Mr. Nakanishi?
- Hey, there.
Tell me, how are those designs coming?
- Well, things are certainly interesting.
- Interesting?
Yeah, extremely.
By the way, I'll need you help with
some advertising like we discussed.
I'll need it soon.
But...
But what?
Nothing.
And if it's all right, let's meet alone.
There are some things
I need to talk to you about.
Sure.
In that case, how's you next day off?
Next day off? That should be fine.
I'll leave the time and place up to you.
Well, see you then.
I can hardly wait.
Good night, boss!
See you tomorrow!
Okay, guys. See you!
Boss?
Hey, Mayumi, It's time to go home!
I heard this rumor,
that R&D dismissed Miss Sakurai.
Am I right?
What about it?
So, what's going to happen to our
seamless lingerie designs?
Don't even worry about that!
- Well, I sort of am.
- Just trust me.
I was worried because
everyone's saying different things.
What do you mean "different things?"
Well, I heard some people saying that
recent movement in the company's share...
performance looks like there's some kind
of stock manipulation going on.
But I'm sure it 's all silly rumors!
You shouldn't pay too much attention
to what people say.
- Of course. See you tomorrow, then!
- All right, then, Mayumi!
So, the stock market?
Sorry to interrupt
such a precious moment.
How's it going?
I've almost got it.
Here it is!
- But this ID is...
- Who is it?
This is section 1 chief
Mr. Zaitu's ID number.
That's what it is!
Wait! The ID number is Mr. Zaitu's,
but the pass code belongs to...
What's wrong?
No! It can't be!
There must be some
kind of mistake. Why!
No, it can't be Mr. Miki!
So, the hacker was Mr. Miki then.
He used to work as engineer, like me.
How I respected him!
I wanted to be like him!
How could he betray us?
Are you okay now?
Yes, thank you.
Well, Mr. Nakanishi?
Yes, Chisa?
I have something I want to show you.
I think you'll be pleased.
Chisa, you're...
I finished your sample.
Do you like it?
You finished it?
Yes.
It's amazing!
You've really saved section 2!
Chisa, you're wonderful.
I did it not because I promised you
I would...
but I also really liked the design
when I first saw it.
Really? Thank you.
I think it came out pretty close
to how I imagined.
I think this is way more
than I imagined!
It's just amazing.
I was thinking of you
when I first saw this design.
I knew it would fit your incredible
body perfectly.
Such a beautiful cock!
How are my breasts, Mr. Nakanishi?
Unreal! I could tit-fuck you all night!
Thank you!
I love your hot prick between my tits!
Chisa, I'm about to...
Come on me, please! Come!
Your nipples are so hard and tight!
Do you like it rough like this?
I guess you love it like this.
No! I'm not that kind of girl!
I'm afraid these nipples
make it look like you're lying.
But I'm not a slut! No!
How does this work for you, Chisa?
I don't know.
It's so fucking good!
No!
No? What do you mean, "no?"
You're almost there, aren't you?
You need to ask permission to come,
or I don't think I'll let you.
Don't you have something to ask?
Okay. That's it, then.
No. Don't stop.
Then beg for it!
Say, "please make me come all the way."
Please, I'm so close!
I need your...
Come on.
You need my what?
I want your cock inside me!
Please! Make me come! Fuck me!
Good girl.
Yes! Yes! Please let me come!
I'm coming, yes!
I'm coming!
Mr. Nakanishi?
Do you hate slutty girls?
No. I love them.
Good.