Give a synopsis of the last episode, please!
Eh...
I have returned to my hometown, Little Monica, after being away for a long time.
The changes I saw were staggering.
Everyone used to love the arts. Everyone used to be generous and happy in this city.
But now, Kajo rules the city, and it is overrun with evil.
How can I restore Little Monica back to the cheerful city that it used to be?
No... I have to think of the city now.
But it's so hard to concentrate...
Mei, you shouldn't be doing this. You're going to get in trouble again.
It's okay. Sis went shopping.
But Mei...
You're the one who said I could do whatever I wanted.
Hi Mei. I'm researching some things about the city.
You can do whatever you want as long as you don't distract me.
Okay.
I said as long as you didn't distract me...
Am I distracting you?
Hi Tina... I didn't know you were there.
Will, I...
Tina.
Tina, lick this! It tastes just like your cakes!
Huh? Does that mean it's sweet? That can't be good!
Well?
You're right. It's salty.
Salty?!
You always put in too much salt.
Oh, now I get it.
Nothing.
Have another lick. You might grow to like it.
Sure.
Okay.
What obedient girls...
You two really like it, huh?
I don't want to stop.
I can't stop.
You make it sound like it's a shrimp chip.
What is a shrimp chip?
It's a snack. They are eaten in Asian countries.
You know so much.
You're so amazing.
But there are things that I can't figure out.
Really?
Like what?
Kajo wanted to see all of you naked the other day. What was that all about?
Maybe if I saw you naked again, I might be able to figure it out.
Will you take your clothes off?
Okay! Sure!
I can't tell by just looking. I should take a closer look.
Can both of you get on the bed?
I want to check a certain part of your body very well.
A certain part?
That is...
Here!
The temperature and wetness are different. Does this mean something?
Will, I...
You're so amazing, Will.
Really?
Let me see how you taste.
Spread your legs and lie down.
I'm home!
The Little Monica Story - Part 2
Huh?
Tina? Mei?
They taste slightly different.
The amount and the consistency is also different.
The size of their breasts and their texture...
They suck differently too.
Tina! Mei! Is anyone home?
Will...
Will, it feels so good.
They're both really feeling it.
Jeez, those two...
I'm going to stick it in.
Will, give it to me.
I want your cock inside me.
Okay.
Hi Celia. Did you need something?
I was looking for Tina and Mei but...
Excuse me. I'm going to go downstairs and prepare the store.
Wait!
Sorry!
Mei!
You two need to stop slacking off! Jeez...
Will! I need you to supervise those two when I'm gone!
I'm sorry. I was just trying to learn more about the city and I kept holding them up.
Jeez...
Men's rooms smell so bad. Open the windows for a change.
S...Sure. I'll do that from now on.
By the way...
Is there something else?
Do you want to go out to see the city later?
It's hard for you to come up with ideas if you don't see it for yourself.
Good idea. Let's do that. That is great.
There are a lot of thugs...
Some of them are dressed up, but...
They're either here for the prostitutes or the gambling.
It's pretty quiet during the day, but it gets much worse at night.
I didn't think it was so corrupt.
I just realized that I don't hear any music. No one is even humming.
Kajo banned music.
The strip show you went to is one of the few places where it's allowed.
We can only play our instruments because we're not in the center of the city, but...
...we have to be careful. If we get caught, we'll be sent to prison.
This is all because of Kajo...
The first thing we need to do is figure out how to get rid of him.
Kajo has enough money from his shady businesses...
...to bribe both the army and the police.
Everyone is too scared to speak up.
Isn't that Mom?
It looks like her.
I was too young when Mom left, so I don't really remember her.
Let's ask her!
Will!
Excuse me!
Yes?
Are you Ingrid?
Are you? This is Celia, Tina, and Mei. Do you remember?
They're your daughters.
I don't have any children. I've given myself to God.
I'm sure that you can tell I'm a nun by just looking at me. Are you making fun of me?
Will. Let's go. It's not her.
No, I'm the oldest, so my memory is the best. She's definitely Ingrid.
Please stop!
You're bothering me.
Will.
Celia, I'm sorry I've taken over a corner of your store.
It's just that I can concentrate the best here.
That is fine. Thanks to Kajo we barely get any customers.
Him again... We have to do something quick.
Where are Tina and Mei?
They're cleaning the kitchen. It's their punishment for slacking off the other day.
Then I'd better work hard to rebuild this city.
Will, I had a lot of fun yesterday. Thank you.
About our mother... You did your best for us, so...
Oh, that... I was raised by foster parents, and some things were hard...
I was lonely at times, but... you guys didn't even have that.
When I thought about how hard that must have been, I...
Thank you, Will. It's the thought that counts.
It might not have been her, but we'll have you from now on, so...
You're right. I'll take good care of all of you.
But, I'm really sure that woman is your mother, Ingrid.
It was strange the way that she kept denying it.
That is because she lost her memory.
What is wrong, Will?
Welcome. I didn't even notice you come in.
Oh? Are you friends with Will?
No, I don't know her.
She just surprised me because she said that suddenly.
Oh, really?
I'm a traveling fortune-teller. I heard that the coffee here is great, so I stopped by.
When I overheard your interesting conversation, I listened in.
Anyway, is what you just said true?
It's true. I met her at the port. I thought she was acting strangely, so I asked her...
She told me that she lost her memory, but she also said...
...that there is something familiar about this place...
...and there is someone out there that is precious to her.
Will! Does that mean...
It must be you girls! That woman is Ingrid!
I'm going to go look for Mother!
Wait! I'll go with you!
She also said there is someone out there who wants to harm her.
As far as I can tell, this harm will also affect Little Monica.
I want you to listen, because this has to do with the fate of Little Monica.
You'll still have time to look for your mother afterwards.
Okay, I'll listen. I'll get my sisters.
These are my sisters, Tina and Mei. We're all here now.
I see. I'm Chateau, a fortune-teller.
First, there is something I want to ask you.
Do you know where the town's name, Little Monica, comes from?
Everyone knows that.
Little Monica was the heir of the family that took care of the theater for generations.
She is the one who supported the city.
But one day, she disappeared...
...and I took over the city!
About Little Monica's whereabouts...
...do you know where she is?
Yes, according to a reliable source, Little Monica...
...should have died by my hands, but...
...instead she disappeared in front of his eyes.
Little Monica and her family have the ability to...
...possess other people's bodies. That is probably how she hid herself.
That happened thirteen years ago...
About the same time that Ingrid disappeared!
So Little Monica's spirit is hiding inside Mom's body!
Yes, but Little Monica can only remain there...
...until the night of the full moon of the thirteenth year.
If she doesn't leave by then, she'll end up killing her host...
Little Monica won't do that. She'll definitely leave.
There is no point in killing the host.
My opportunity will come when she leaves the body in spirit form.
That is when the manuscript and birdcage come into play.
If I chant the spell from the manuscript, she'll return to her true self.
Then I'll trap her inside the birdcage, and Little Monica will be finished.
All I need to do is find the woman who is her host.
I see... I read somewhere...
...that when a spirit enters a body, marks will appear on the host's body.
That is why Kajo is checking the women in the city.
He is looking for the scars from when he stabbed her!
Wait... But isn't the full moon...?
Tonight.
Yes, it's tonight.
They don't get it, do they...
The reason why I stopped to tell you is because I want you to be prepared.
When Little Monica leaves your mother's body...
...if you can't stop Kajo, someone must be willing to take in Little Monica.
The same person can't be possessed twice.
If you love this city, I want you to be prepared to make this sacrifice.
It's okay. We'll just have to do something about Kajo before that.
But how?
I'll figure something out. You girls go find your mother.
Chateau and I will head to Kajo's mansion.
Okay, Celia...
Sis...
Sis!
What is wrong, Sis? You're spacing out.
Look! That carriage!
Carriage!
Mei said she saw Mom in that carriage!
Really? But that is Kajo's carriage!
I know! We have to go after it!
What did you find?
It's empty. The carriage is gone, so he is gone too.
Damn it! I thought he would be here.
He is probably at the outdoor theater.
This isn't good. We need to meet up with Celia.
What is it, Meow? We have to go.
I can't forget the last time we had sex. I want to fuck you again.
Now? This isn't the time!
But this may be the last time. I might not see you again.
Meow...
You're going to...?
You can't do that! You're not from this city!
That is why. So...
So please, Will?
Meow...
Will, it feels so good...
The grass is so prickly, it's turning me on.
Meow, this isn't like that. It's not that...
When I learned that you had decided to become Little Monica's next host...
...I was really moved.
Huh? I never said that!
I said that I might never see you again after this is over...
...because I'm leaving this city. That is all.
Then this is just sex.
Wouldn't you feel guilty if it wasn't just sex? Especially towards Celia?
Plus, I doubt you want to stop.
Will, touch mine too.
Okay.
Will, that feels so nice... I can tell you're starting to get into it.
You're terrible. You're just taking advantage of me.
You're terrible for making me so wet.
I didn't think we would do this again.
Will, it tastes so good.
You too, Meow.
You're so wet.
I can't wait any longer. Fuck me.
It feels so good. Make me feel good.
Okay. Here I come.
Will, your cock is so big. You're filling me up.
It feels so good! I'm going to cum!
I...I can't take anymore!
Me too... I'm gonna cum!
Cum with me!
This is where he must be checking the women.
Does that mean he is in here?
Probably. Let's go in.
We'll get caught if it's just us. We should wait until Will comes.
We don't have time. The moon is almost out.
What is wrong, Tina?
Hi Missy. Long time no see.
No wonder I couldn't find you at the store.
Don't look so depressed. We just had sex.
Sex or no sex, I shouldn't have done that. Now I feel so guilty when I think about Celia.
You can't help it. You're a playboy.
Hi, kitty. What is wrong?
That is how I always pictured myself up to now, but when I'm with Celia...
...I don't want to be like that anymore. After talking to her...
What? That isn't good!
What?
They saw their mother taken away in a carriage and followed it.
To where?
Probably the outdoor theater. Let's go!
I knew we shouldn't have been having sex! They might have been caught by now!
By the way... Did you think of a way to defeat Kajo?
You promised them you would take care of him.
You're right. We shouldn't move without a plan...
But I haven't thought of one.
No way! I thought you already had a plan. I thought you were ready...
...because it didn't take much to distract you!
I did my homework, but there wasn't any information about his businesses.
There wasn't anything about Kajo, either.
All I know is that he has bad taste.
Have you ever met him?
Once, when he came to the store.
When he came in...
...he was especially sensitive to Ajo playing the violin, and ran out.
On top of that, music is banned in this city.
His weakness is music!
That can't be. They can use music at the strip show. He must hear it.
No, he doesn't hear it.
Really?
Yes, the strip show announcer told me.
I'm the one who made Kajo agree to let music be played during the strip show.
If I'm announcing, the show must be perfect. It would be stupid without music!
How did you make him agree?
I gave Kajo earplugs. I asked him to use them during the show.
Go ahead. Tell me I'm great.
Hell no.
Then I'm right!
Master Kajo. The nun and the sisters are the last ones.
I see. Good work. Oh...
That is the woman who rudely threw me... And her sisters too!
I don't know who the nun is, but...
Why don't we take this opportunity to throw them around?
Great idea. Let's do it!
Idiots! Don't take me seriously. I would never do something so violent!
You're our Mom, right?
Tina! Shh!
Idiots! Don't take me seriously. I would never do something so violent!
She has to be! She is our Mom!
Really?
Yes! There should be a more elegant way of doing it. Let me think.
Mei, you too! Who knows what they'll do if we don't stay quiet!
What are they doing over there! Don't they know they're hostages?
Oh forget it. Let's get it over with. Take their clothes off.
Sis!
No, don't come near me!
D...Don't worry. Calm down. Will is going save us.
Everyone stand back!
What is this? Why are we caging them in?
What is this? What is going on?
It's okay. It's a stage prop. I've cut your ropes.
Chateau, thank you.
It's too bad I'm not Will, huh?
You're the woman from the port.
It's good to see you again. You're going to escape with me.
You three go behind the stage and wait for us in the orchestra pit.
There is an orchestra pit in the back?
No time to chat. Hurry!
Forget the stage prop. Open the curtains! Hurry!
How long are you guys going to sit there?
Hurry up and do something!
Y...Yes Master Kajo!
Where is Will?
He went back to get Ajo. He should be back at any minute.
Ajo?
Hurry and get in.
We're going to run straight ahead. It's the fastest way out of this tent.
Don't worry. Just hold my hand and run.
I see! I see! I seeee! You're the one Little Monica possessed.
Finally, the time has come. The night of the full moon of the thirteenth year is here.
Come out Little Monica, or else the nun is going to die.
Once you come out, you're going turn into a canary and live in this cage.
This city will belong to me! I'm going to change its name to Kajo!
Wait! I won't let that happen!
You again! Are you going to stop me?
Not stop you, finish you off!
What?
Go, Ajo!
I discovered your weakness! But that is just the beginning!
The curtain is going up.
Are we supposed to play now?
It's fine. Let's trust Will and play.
How do you like that, Kajo?
Huh? What happened to me?
I see. Ajo was the embodiment of Kajo's love of music. It must have escaped.
But I didn't know that he was possessed by a rat.
Mom!
The scar on your back... Does that mean that you really are our mother?
Mom, don't you remember us?
I'm glad it worked out, Will. Bye!
Really?
Mei... Tina... and Celia...
Yes, Mom...
I'm so surprised. You're all grown up.
I'm sorry to surprise you.
It's fine.
Mom!
My dear daughters...
Mom.
Thank you.
Thanks to everyone, the evil Kajo is no more.
Little Monica.
I'm sure that with your hard work...
...peace will return to Little Monica...
I believe that day will come, and I will be watching from afar.
The show is going to start, but they're not back yet.
Did they say where they were going? It's about to start.
The main reason I came back here was to see you again.
I love you. I always have. I only have eyes for you.
Me too, Will.
Will, make love to me...
Not yet, Celia. Go down on me.
Good, Celia. Can you do it with your mouth?
That is good. It feels really good.
It feels really good... I'm going to cum soon.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Are you all right, Celia?
I'm okay. It feels really good.
Celia.
I'm so happy. We've become one. I'm so happy...
Me too...
It feels so good.
More. Fuck me harder.
Your hard cock is thrusting in and out...
You're the best, Celia. I love you.
I love you too.
I'm going to cum...
Go ahead... cum.
What's that you bastard?
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
I love you sekai de hitotsu
What's that you bastard?
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
I trust my heart...
itoshii kokoro kaze ni nosete
...and voice will reach you.
omoi mo koe mo kitto todoku kara
Say my heart.
say my heart
Holiday in Sepia...
sepia iro no horidei
Velvet never changes...
kawaranai berube
I'll rip off your skirt!
hazu atsu no koi wo
Passionate love -
omoi nobun so sogune
- I'll put my heart into it.
Mei-chan, you're so cute,\Naren't you? Shall we\Ngo on a date to get\Nto know each other?
I'll trust you all the way.
zutto anata wo shinjite
Let's be more courageous.
moto yuuki wo de sou
You'll smile and think everything is good...
kitto ii ne to omoeru egao
...I can give you that.
kimi ni ageru yo
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
I love you sekai de hitotsu
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
My heart and thoughts will definitely reach you...
itoshii kokoro utabi nosete
...because I put my heart to the wind.
mirai mo yume mo kitto kara utara
Say you love me.
say you love me
I love you sekai de hitotsu
I love you! You're the only one in the world!
deatta kiseki saikou no present
Our miracle encounter was the best present!
itoshii kokoro kaze ni nosete
I trust my heart...
omoi mo koe mo kitto todoku kara
...and voice will reach you.
say my heart
Say my heart.
sepia iro no horidei
Holiday in Sepia...
kawaranai berube
Velvet never changes...
hazu atsu no koi wo
Passionate love -
omoi nobun so sogune
- I'll put my heart into it.
zutto anata wo shinjite
I'll trust you all the way.