Nikkatsu Video proudly presents
Uchiyama Aki's
Sick Aki-chan
Waii!!
EEK!
Oh no...
Is it time to go home already?
What are you laughing?
Where am i?
Inside your home, didn't you know that?
Really?
Who is this?
I am Aki
I'm Aki too
We are of same blood
Aki-chan, you shouldn't be here
Ohh..
If I stay here my mom will punish me?
Is that what you mean?
Children shouldn't worry about things like that
This way leads out?
Good, Aki-chan
You never should go up there though
That way leads to nowhere?
That's true
Death awaits us up there, probably
But I'm not sure
I didn't study these things enough before our journey
Aki-chan doesn't like this!
Don't be too concerned, this should be easy...
Whatever can happen, but being good should ensure our survival
That's not all though..
I won't protect you if you're afraid
Okay! Aki will be good!
EEK!
You're so cute...
Aki-chan...
Don't do that!
It hurts!
Mommyy!!!!
Why are you naked?
How can I get out of here?
I have lost my way and wouldn't want to be here...
You mockery of a girl will stay here!
My mom would scould you..
...thanks for the meal!
I'm sorry!
Okay! I will be good!
Your sobbing makes me angry...
How's this?
Thanks for the meal!
Scary!
You're lucky...
Stop that!
Young meat doesn't sell well,
so I won't butcher you
You can take the place of that woman instead!
My humble greetings
I should be starting now, I hope you enjoy yourself
This is your future..
You should use your life for better things...
Anyobody here?
I think they will see me here...
Open the door, please!
Aki!
My little Aki...
We don't have much time...
Sounds really bad...
This is not the way it should be...
Don't worry
I will reveal myself little by little...
I loved listening your childish nonsense,
but everything will come to end
Aki-chan really tries to understand!
Good girl
Then it won't matter
Aki-chan promises!
Now I'm ready
Be good and say "Aaa"
You're good... Suck it more...
I'm coming...!
So, Aki-chan likes soft ice-cream?
You probably want more of it...
Don't open your eyes...
I'm awaiting for you!
Faster! The power of my ancestors is hatching inside me.
See for yourself! My end is near...
Don't complain about it! You promised!
Somebody help me!
What we have here?
I pee from there...
Where can you find flowers like this?
I think I will borrow your hole a bit
Will I find an answer for
my problems in there?
I hope it will be tasty atleast
Bit dry, much like pie..
Now we are both dirty!
I will do some nice things for you...
I'm scared...
I'll stick it in for good...
Be still now, I'm already cumming!
Hey, girl...
What's your name?
Try someone else!
The End
Translated (badly) from Japanese by:
PeTA