This subtitle made by hentaiguess.com
Not for sale, rent or ebay.
Shari may think of herself
as more the masochist type...
but that's not where
her true nature lies.
You think she's a sadist?
I'd say that she's a natural actor.
I think that she can become
the type that Mr. Beat Me desires.
The only problem is time.
Reliability is number one
in this business.
We can't make
the clients wait forever.
Can you feel it?
I don't know.
It's like something...
something else is inside me.
You have to look
deep into yourself.
The answer as to who you
really are will be found there.
Who gave you permission
to go there?
That's right. Two weeks.
We'll get him what he wants.
No. Tell him we can deliver one
that's beyond his expectation.
I understand.
I'll tell him right away.
Good-bye.
Hello. Takeda Enterprises.
Well, well. It's the trainer.
There's a favor I want to ask you.
Right.
All right.
I'm sure you remember
that guy Hiroshi.
I'll use him.
Don't worry about it.
There're lots of guys under him.
But I'm surprised that
you'd suggest such a thing.
This training job
might've been your calling.
What about Okinawa?
Sounds great! Azure seas,
blue skies, good-looking guys...!
Can you make it, Natsumi?
I don't really know.
You guys can go without me.
We can't leave you behind.
It wouldn't be any fun
without you.
Hey, maybe we can all chip in
for Natsumi's ticket.
No, no. You can't do that.
We can just split it three ways.
Yeah, yeah. No problem.
Good evening.
Would you women like to join us?
There's also four of us.
Well, I wonder
what we should do?
Come on.
We can all have a lot of fun.
Don't worry about it.
Well, I'll take this one
back to her home.
Don't do anything I wouldn't do!
That drug Takamori gave me
sure did its job.
Damn. She sure has a great bod.
And don't you lay a hand on her.
Got that?
See ya.
Hey, it's me. Anytime.
Wake up!
Are you Natsumi Sakurazuki?
Is this bag yours?
Uh, um...
It's yours, isn't it?
Natsumi Sakurazuki.
You are under arrest for
contravening the prostitution law.
I...
I told you what you have to say.
May I cum?
Sure.
L-I'm cumming...!
I'm cumming!
Uh, my phone...
Hello?
Sana.
Right, right.
All right. Don't worry.
I'll be there right away.
Just take it easy.
What's the matter?
Um...
I think I told you
about her before, but...
it's about my sister.
You told me about her.
She's been arrested
because of some misunderstanding.
Arrested?
I have to go and get her.
No. I'll go instead.
I've got friends in the police,
so I can sort it out faster.
But...
She's your precious sister, right?
That means she's
precious to me too.
Precious to me too, huh?
The show's over.
Looks like it went well.
I'll get the money
from the office later.
Um, where's Sana?
She's working right now.
She'll be here soon.
Have something to eat
while you wait.
But, this seems extravagant.
Don't you worry about it.
Oh, is it this late already?
I still have some work left to do.
Sorry, but I'm going to
have to get back to it.
You can just relax here.
Well, I want to go home.
I'll end up
getting an earful from Sana.
Sana should be coming here.
So, you just wait.
B-But...
The food's getting cold. I know
it's a bit lonely eating alone, but...
- See you later.
- Uh, um...
What's the matter?
Say it.
What's happening to you now?
Y-Yes. Your foot is...
rubbing against my tender spot.
And? How does it feel?
Uh, yes. It feels good.
It's total bliss.
Miss Shari,
please show me a little more.
Miss Shari, show me that
beautiful place of yours.
So you want to see it, huh?
All right, take a look
with those pathetic eyes.
Take a good look.
Miss Shari...!
Looks like she's ready.
I'll let her finish for today.
We can send her
to the client tomorrow.
Sure. That sounds good.
Well, you should go
deal with Natsumi.
I know.
Sana?
I've come to get you, Natsumi.
Let's go and see Sana.
Today we'll do
the reverse of the usual.
I want you to pleasure me.
Can you do that?
Sure.
Think of me
as the boy-next-door.
You're going to teach me about sex.
Take charge this time.
Make me as horny as you can.
Does that feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Would you like me to touch it now?
Yeah, I sure do.
But, I don't know.
All right. I'll touch you there.
You sure are nice and big.
This is where Sana is.
Now, come with me.
Um, where's Sana?
S-Sana.
Take a good look.
Don't avert your eyes.
Sana is in training right now.
T-Training?
That's right.
Training to become
more desirable to our clients.
The training will help
improve her value.
Sana is trying to regain her past.
Her father, her mother, you...
To go back to the past
when you had a happy family.
The debt that your father carries...
is not a sum that can be paid back
through ordinary work.
However...
it can be paid off if clients are
willing to buy her services.
That's why Sana is working
as hard as she can...
so that she can command
a high price.
That's not all.
Through this training,
Sana was able to discover her new self.
Take a good look.
Look at her thighs.
I'm sure you know what that is.
Giving pleasure to another has
also become pleasurable to her.
Hey, I really want it now.
Do you want me to put it in?
Yeah. Please do.
Sure.
It's going right in.
Can you feel it?
Can you feel it going in?
Of course.
Ohhh...
That feels so good.
But even like that,
the client will not want to buy Sana.
The client's desire is
to be loved by two women.
It seems that he was never
able to forget the affection...
he received from two
neighborhood sisters long ago.
You seem to understand.
But we're not going to force you.
Unlike you, Sana came here
out of her own choice.
However, it's up to you...
whether all the work
Sana's put in will go to waste.
No! I'm going to cum!
Once you've made your decision...
you can go to the room
at the end of the hall.
That's where they are.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, cumming...!
In three...
or four hours?
I'll bring the money to you
as soon as I get it.
All right.
But why do you need all that time?
I've got some things to deal with.
He'll do it another time...
but who knows for how long.
Yes. I'll see you later.
My goodness.
Look at the stiffy you've got already.
You're not really sick, are you?
You just got admitted...
so you can see me
under here, right?
My, my.
You've gotten all big again.
Here. Payment
for your first assignment.
You did well with Shari.
I'm looking forward to
more of that on the next one.
Seems like you got some cash.
I'm taking out
this month's payment.
Keep up the good work.
For me too.
Um...
I want you to...
I want you to do to me
what you did to Sana.
Are you sure?
Yes.
You know that you won't be
able to quit part way.
I understand.
- Then, take your clothes off.
- Huh?
- Take your clothes off.
- Uh, right.
Underwear, too. Everything.
Yes.
Move your hands out of the way.
Sit on the bed.
What's your experience?
What?
Do you have experience with men?
No. None.
You were watching me with Sana
on the monitor, weren't you?
Yes.
Did it turn you on?
Wh-What?
Say the truth.
I think it's normal
for any man or woman...
to get turned on
after seeing something like that.
Raise your knees up.
So I can see you well.
There. You're all hot and horny.
You're all wet.
You must've masturbated before?
Let's see.
What...?!
I want to see.
You know the way.
Your nipples are
nice and hard already.
Natsumi.
Sana.
I want you two to talk things over.
I'll be out on deck.
Come see me when you've decided.
We've decided.
Please train the both of us together.
Let's work hard together.
No matter how big the debt,
one day you'll be able to pay it off.