This subtitle made by hentaiguess.com
Not for sale, rent or ebay.
Bastard!
You're long overdue!
You know how much that's
going to cost you in interest?!
Asshole!
If you can't pay us back,
you'll have to pay with your body.
Huh? Maybe with your kidney
and your corneas?
We'll settle it at our office.
What're you doing, Hiroshi?
This one ain't
taking care of his debt.
Oh, it's you.
Leave this one to me, Hiroshi.
Can't you live
a more legitimate life?
If you want to change your life,
how about joining up with me?
There's an interesting business
I'm involved in.
Don't worry.
No blood and guts here.
The yakuza these days are
no different from any other business.
The first objective is, of course,
to earn a profit from our businesses.
I want you to lend me a hand
in one of those businesses.
It's my little operation.
You can be sure that
I wouldn't pick just anyone.
Getting involved with this guy
always leads to trouble.
And he's the one to blame
for all my debt.
I don't want anyone else to
ever hear what I'm about to say.
If all goes well,
you can work off your debt.
And you'll even make a little extra.
Sound good?
Ever since college, he's been
coming to me to do his dirty work.
I'll take your silence as a yes.
Let me explain.
I run a business where I introduce
certain quality women...
to a "gentleman's club."
But this is a club like no other.
We match suitable women
to clients with special demands.
Our clients are prominent figures
in society. They are all quite wealthy.
The better we're able to
satisfy those clients,
the more they spend.
I want you to be a trainer.
He sure thinks he's a big shot.
I've been left in charge
with running the club.
There's someone who's in charge of
bringing the clients to us.
You'll meet her at Odaiba.
You can get the details
about your job from her.
She'll be here soon.
There.
We've been waiting.
You're exactly on time, as usual.
So, is he the one?
Yes. He's my man.
Uh, hello.
I'm Sakura Matsunai.
You're it, huh? Did Takamori
tell you what's involved?
Uh, yes.
This chick must be
some kind of big shot.
She's higher in rank than Takamori.
I'm going to refer to you
as the "trainer."
I'll come right out and
tell you what we're about.
The purpose of this club is
to attract members.
This is made possible by providing
clients with the women they desire.
Do you follow?
We have to tailor our women to fit
the specific desires of our clients.
In other words, we must train
the women. That will be your job.
Are you clear?
Yes.
I could just walk away from this
if I wanted to.
Of course, we will pay you
an appropriate sum.
But if you're not able to give us
a satisfactory result...
you'll have to settle
all outstanding matters.
You too, Takamori.
Yes, I know.
Hey, answer her. Mr. Trainer.
Huh?
Sakura Matsunai, huh?
Seems like a pretty tough bitch,
but she sure is a babe.
If you give us a result that
exceeds clients' expectations...
you will receive
additional compensation.
Sounds like a pretty good deal,
doesn't it?
Will you accept this job?
What is your answer?
Yes or no?
It's understandable that
you can't give me an answer right away.
I want you to come to Takeshiba Pier
at exactly noon tomorrow.
But, you'll end up scaring
the women away looking so sloppy.
Here's 300,000 yen. I want you
to look your best tomorrow.
Here.
Hey, take the money.
Uh, thank you.
There're all kinds of people
in this world.
People can do anything they want
if they're willing to pay.
Human desire can never be
completely satisfied.
That's what creates
new opportunities for business.
We train women to
better satisfy the clients' desires.
We create them and
provide them to the clients.
That in turn grows
into a large business.
Well, it's really nothing more
than prostitution.
But new people with new skills
will become necessary.
That's the job of the sex trainer.
Should I take that on?
Right now I'm unemployed.
And I've got a debt to pay off.
I haven't taken the job yet...
but I'm already getting interested
in this Sakura Matsunai woman.
So you came.
I was a bit worried.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let me start by explaining to you
who our clients are.
Member 1121.
Code name, "The Licker."
He's got erectile problems,
so he's an oral connoisseur.
He prefers novice Lolita types,
who are shy and react coy.
He'll chew on any hole
'til the cows come home...
and he likes to hear
different responses for each hole.
Of course, he likes to
play with toys as well.
We leave it up to him
what he uses.
He'll wait until we're able to
train the best possible candidate.
He'll pay anything
if he can get satisfaction.
I'll give you copies of this later.
Right.
Let's go to the next one.
This member 1145. Code name,
"Mr. Beat Me."
He's a masochist.
In other words,
he desires a dominatrix.
As one option,
he likes to get rough foreplay.
He's also a high-heel fetishist.
His preferred climax is to
see the dominatrix get beat.
He'll masturbate to that.
Likes fantasy scenarios
and play-acting.
Her training will require
aspects besides the physical.
The training will last 30 days.
Yes.
Next we have member 0058.
Code name, "Madame Pleasure."
She's been a big fan of the all-female
Takarazuka Theater since she was young.
She desires a lesbian partner
of a cat-like quality.
And she likes foreplay.
She doesn't want a gentle cat.
She wants a mischievous partner.
After a lot of lesbian play,
she likes to
finish off with a threesome.
She desires to be treated rough.
Two months to train her partner.
Maybe I should take her on.
Next we have member 1188.
Code name, "Twin Lover."
He was treated affectionately by his
two older sisters when he was young.
He's never been able to forget this,
and he desires to have sex with
two sisters at the same time.
He likes the typical
girl-next-door type.
But the sisters have to be particularly
affectionate towards him.
Apparently, he recently
received test results...
saying that
he might have cancer.
He's become more fussy
about his desires ever since.
I bet he'll be willing to
pay quite a bit.
You could say so.
He certainly has the means.
Mr. Trainer, I'm assuming that
you'll be accepting this job?
If I'm able to pay off
all of my debts...
I can quit anytime I want, right?
Sure.
Then I will accept.
We have an agreement.
You will be responsible
for four candidates.
I'll introduce the first of those
to you right away.
I leave it to you to decide
which clients to match the women to.
I understand.
This could be just the right thing
for you. Do what you've got to.
I'll be leaving here.
I've got other matters
to take care of.
This is your room.
Details about each of the women
are on the table.
Look it over.
This one, huh?
You can start training her today
if you'd like.
The rest depends on your ability.
This is the trainer who will be
working with you from today.
Nice to meet you.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Sana Sakurazuki.
Have a seat.
I'll get the crew
to bring you dinner.
And the two of you can have
a nice, long chat.
You'll have to excuse me
as I have to take a rest.
Yes.
Sana Sakurazuki, 22 years old.
Her father failed in business
and has since disappeared.
Her family's suffering
financial difficulties.
She has a sister
who's four years younger.
A virgin? I thought so.
I was thinking of having
a quick shower before dinner.
How about you?
I'm fine.
Well, you'll have to excuse me.
It looks like dinner's here.
Now, that was refreshing.
You should've had a shower too.
Red wine, huh?
You can drink, right?
I don't drink.
A little bit of wine will relax you.
Here. Take it.
Come on.
Let's drink to our success.
Wow, this looks delicious.
What's the matter?
You'll feel better if you eat a little.
What do you mean by
"to our success"?
We're fated to work together.
Fated?
To work together?
That's right.
We were both brought here
because we have debts to pay off.
I'm here to teach you about sex.
In other words,
I'm your sex trainer.
Sex trainer?
My job is to turn you into the ultimate
object of desire for the clients.
And then what?
The better I'm able to offer
the client satisfaction...
the better they pay us.
I'll be able to earn more money,
and pay off my debts more quickly.
What?! I didn't know
anything about that!
They gave me a tough one
to start off with.
Maybe I'll try the rough approach.
- Well, let's start your training.
- What?!
Open the door! No!
I don't want to get rough on you.
No! No! Let me go!
I'm sure you understand
why it is that we have to do this.
No! I don't want to!
Now that I've accepted this job,
I can't just walk away from it.
No! I said no!
Knock it off!
No!
Stop!
If that's how you want
to play, then...!
Don't!
This is terrible!
Just settle down. If you'd just
settle down, I won't be rough on you.
This is so we can both
pay off our debts. Right?
Don't you see?
It's not like
I really want to do this.
Now, remove your hands.
No! Don't!
You sure have it rough.
Your dad went bankrupt
and has disappeared.
Your mom's in the hospital
with mental problems.
Your sister's trying to
get into university...
so that leaves only you
to make ends meet.
You're aware of
what kind of organization this is.
If you're not inclined to
work and pay back your debt...
you should get off this boat.
But I bet your sister will be
brought here to work instead.
P-Please do it quickly.
You're beautiful.
No!
Your pussy has a nice color.
A light pink, and soft as velvet.
A beautiful shape, too.
I'm embarrassed.
Please do it quickly.
I mustn't rush this.
This is her first time, after all.
I'll penetrate her
after I suck on her pussy again.
I'm coming in.
Can you feel that, Sana?
Looks like she came.
Should I cum too?
Sana definitely has a special quality.
With training, she'll become
quite a valuable commodity.
Can I come in?
Please.
How did the training go?
I'd say she passed the first stage.
I see.
By the way, did you cum too?
Yes, I did.
That's unfortunate.
The trainer mustn't cum.
And he mustn't get excited.
You have to calmly search out
the woman's weaknesses.
And then work that
pleasure point ceaselessly.
That way, you'll discover
the other hidden weaknesses.
For example, it's wrong to think
of the anus simply as a hole in the ass.
After training,
the ass can become wetter
and more sensitive than the pussy.
Also, there's a difference
between sex with love...
and sex play
for the pure pleasure of it.
I understand.
Well? Would you like
some sex play with me?
Yes.
Are you getting in the mood yet?
Try to find my weakness.
You bet I'm up to the challenge.
Sakura's weakness
seems to be her asshole.
I'm going work her ass
a little more.
Now, I'll try to find your weakness.
Lie down on the bed.
Did you feel that.
Let me ride you until I cum.
L-I'm cumming...!
Me too...!
Just hold off a bit.
I want to go under you.
Fuck me again.
Harder! Harder!
Wait.
I want you to cum in my ass.
What the? Sakura's asshole is
wetter than her pussy.
I can't get enough of this sensation.
It's so tight.
I'm cumming!
I want to train Sana
for the "Twin Lover," member 1188.
But there's one condition.
I want her sister Natsumi to
take part in the training as well.
Think you can pull it off?
Are you sure you have enough time
to train both Sana and Natsumi?
A woman's body is deep.
I want to get to know
Sakura some more...
and teach Sana, who I just
deflowered, more about sex.
For someone with
nowhere else to go...
the decision seems
pretty clear to me.
I am broke, after all.
I might as well work
as a trainer for a while.