Kiyoka.
System returned to normal.
What's wrong?
I detected a malfunction in the tank
for a split second.
But now I am back online.
You'd better have Kanako look at you.
No, I would like you
to perform maintenance.
Me?
Yes.
Please.
"Necross."
I don't get it. What can I...
There is a desire to feel
you physically. I...
Please have sex with me.
What?
Kaoru, you had sex with Kanako.
You...
You were asleep at that time.
I was connected to the circuit
in the room.
I was able to monitor your activities.
Damn Kanako.
May I?
May I have a permission...
May I have a permission
to kiss your lips?
What?
Was that funny?
Not a very ordinary conversation.
This is difficult.
You...
When did you learn to do this?
I watched the Adult Channel on TV.
I concluded that, this would increase
your erection ratio...
thus enabling
smoother penetration.
The way you talk...
That's enough to get me soft.
Soft. Slacken. Shrink.
You must not!
This is so strange.
Oil leak?
Why are you so wet?
I have a feature to enable
smoother penetration.
My specification states I can perform
missions that require sexual activities...
I'm telling you to stop talking
like that.
Abnormally high physical sensation!
Need for controlling sensual
organ overdrive.
Endangering logic circuit!
Alice, are you afraid?
What?
Can't you trust me?
Yes. I trust you.
I am losing all my abilities.
To hand over all of my functions is...
it is scary, but I am glad.
The emotion of gratitude
is overwhelming.
This is too much.
I'm unable to control areas
surrounding my vaginal organs.
This is abnormal.
Abnormal.
Yes?
Abnormal means you're normal.
What do you mean?
No, not that.
No more abnormality, please, Kaoru.
Is it your...
Here we go.
I feel it.
You are connected with me.
You're warm inside.
I am connected with you, not
through information, but physically.
My emotion is filled with you, Kaoru.
You're a poet.
Something...
Something is abnormal.
Kaoru, no more. No more.
Alice.
What was that?
Surpassing sense organ limitation.
I am becoming abnormal.
I cannot control...
out of control.
I cannot. No more.
What was that?
Finally, completely.
What?
It's been a while, Kaoru.
Alice, what are you saying?
Alice is gone.
Because I'm back.
Aren't you happy?
Get a hold of yourself, Alice!
I see. Kaoru, your memory...
My memory?
I have to go, Kaoru.
When you get your
memory back...
come to see me.
I love you, Kaoru.
You're mine.
"Xinn?"
Xinn.
Got a nice ring to it.
It sounds like "God" in Japanese.
"God."
And what about it?
Kaoru, come to my home today.
To your home?
Tonight, I become God.
That's what Dad says.
Yes. Mayumi.
My high school sweetheart.
I did go to Mayumi's house
that day.
What're you doing,
Mr. Mikogami?
Where's Alice? Is she there?
Do you see anything unusual?
Alice?
What about Alice?
Dyne Wiseman, president of
Digital Demand Corp.
She used to be Dr. Wezmar's
assistant and mistress.
There is a high probability she
maintains contact with Dr. Wezmar.
Dyne should know
Alice's whereabouts.
I have locked out Wiseman's
security system.
Roger.
How much time do I have?
I'll do my best, but...
my limit would be
about 30 minutes.
Not even the phone?
What's going on?
You?
Kaoru Mikogami.
I put your "star" to sleep.
So you hacked
my surveillance satellite.
What's this about, Mikogami?
That's it.
You're a civilian.
How could you know my name?
That's what it's about.
Miss Wiseman.
Don't you ever think...
you can get away with this.
What are your objectives?
Answer me!
Don't.
Our objective is...
To resurrect and awaken Mayumi.
Thereby creating God.
Any more than that...
No! Please don't stop.
You want to talk now?
If a person can take the entire...
Network on this planet
and put it under his control.
Please, do my back end, too.
If he can, then what?
Then it would be the same
as being God.
It's possible if you activate Xinn.
Please put it in. I'm going crazy.
Give me more information,
and I'll give you more.
What the hell is Xinn?
Xinn happened...
because Mayumi's psyche, asleep in
the Network...
tried to find a host...
and run a search throughout
the entire planet.
If we can apply this to...
Incredible!
I'm coming again.
This is his job.
I know it's his job, but still...
- Hey, look!
- What?
Shit!
Mr. Mikogami, you're running
out of time!
What's going on?
Please respond!
Mr. Mikogami, please respond!
Where is Alice?
The personality Alice
no longer exists.
Massy Spector was the activation
key for Mayumi's resurrection.
Alice's body is now occupied
by Mayumi.
Alice, Mayumi, Massy,
doesn't matter.
Where is she?
The security system
is back online.
Emergency. Security breach.
SC level A.
Activate Guard System.
Top priority,
secure President Wiseman.
Why do you care about that robot
so much?
She is my partner.
Ridiculous.
Alice!
Alice is dead.
She has become Mayumi.
Now she is Wezmar's weapon.
Alice is dead?
We can't leave Alice alone.
We have to locate Wezmar as soon
as we can.
But now Dyne is dead, and Alice has
disappeared without trace.
It's already been 2 weeks.
We've been watching the Net,
but now...
it's all up to the lmperial
Intelligence Section 6 and CIA.
Kaoru, it's Alice.
Alice is telling us
her whereabouts.
This is Alice's personal code.
There is no doubt.
Alice is alive!
Alive? Alice is alive?
My daughter...
the time has come.
Coordinate among
the four groups!
Mr. Mikogami is somewhere
in there.
I'm going, too.
Hey, hey.
What's this?
That experiment was a failure.
It was a failure.
But I spent ten years to build
back the whole thing.
Wezmar Diorg.
That must be Steve.
The rats may come scrambling,
but it's too late.
Even you are no more than a bait
to resurrect Mayumi.
Steve!
I arranged you to work for the
lmperial Intelligence, Kaoru Mikogami.
I manipulated your memory
like this.
Can you see me?
My love is forever.
Just being with you...
it's too much for me.
Having your around,
even just saying your name is...
extremely important to me.
I live by necessity.
Tonight...
I will be God.
For you.
Kaoru, Kaoru.
Please.
Please kill me.
Kill me.
You have a reason to exist...
no more!
Die!
What?
Don't be stupid, Mayumi.
Are you betraying
your own father?
I resurrected myself
to fulfill my own wish.
Why? I spent ten years
to fulfill your wish!
My wish is to be
with Kaoru forever...
and avenge myself!
Mayumi!
So, you have come for me, Kaoru.
I'm so glad.
Mayumi.
Is that you, Mayumi?
What's going?
We didn't make it!
Xinn is activating again.
No.
My name is Xinn.
I am the will of the planet Earth.
I gained consciousness through
your Network.
I wish to sign a treaty with you...
and I have prepared the
declaration and details.
What follows is a detailed and
prioritized treaty...
to be exchanged and signed
between me Xinn and human organisms.
- Are you saying, this is Xinn?
- We still have a chance!
We can destroy Alice, now in the
core of Xinn.
Destroy Alice?
We got no communication.
We can't rely on the armed forces.
In that instant, my consciousness
was directly linked to the vast Network.
My body was destroyed.
But my mind was wandering
over the Net.
Waiting for the day to meet you.
Kaoru, let's go
to the realm of God.
There, we'll be united forever.
Come on, be with me.
Come on!
Kaoru!
You must not! Do not get absorbed!
Alice! Are you there?
I have made a break, taking
advantage of a territory...
that Alice and Mayumi cannot share.
A territory you two can't share?
My memory.
My memory as Alice.
- It is mine.
- Alice...
Soon my personality will meld with
Mayumi's personality.
But for now, if you kill me, you can
kill Xinn, too.
Alice...
Please kill me, Kaoru.
- I love you.
Forever and ever.
As long as...
pieces of me exist somewhere...
I will continue to love you.
Kaoru...
I will...
continue to love...
I lost Xinn's reading.
The network is being released.
Mr. Mikogami.
Alice.
It's the self-destruct! Retreat!
Mr. Mikogami!
- Come on!
- Idiot, let's run!
Kaoru!
Mayumi, or Alice?
Who are you now?
It doesn't make a difference.
I'm right by your side.
Kaoru!
It's been several months.
There was some confusion, but
the Xinn Phenomenon is completely gone.
Ninth Heaven has disappeared
as well.
The mysterious death of Dyne
Wiseman was not revealed to the public.
The press reported it as an
ordinary retirement.
Maybe it was just a trick
of my eyes.
But fragments of Mayumi and
Alice's feelings must be...
still existing within the virtual
reality of Network.
After all, our feelings never die.