What happened to Brooks?
He involved Security Police,
but as we planned...
he was killed.
And Massy's fallen into the trap?
Yes.
Well done, Dyne.
Enjoy.
Good, so good.
Shadow is watched by the Security Police.
Be careful.
Yes.
Dr. Wezmar...
You said you hurt your arm.
Is it okay now?
Yes, I only had a minor damage
to my neuron system.
I see.
Were you worried about me?
You're under my care, after all.
I don't want to use you too harshly and
end up writing a damage report.
You have your maintenance
machines in the kitchen.
Yes?
Move them into the living room.
It clutters the kitchen too much.
Inconvenient.
Yes, sir!
Please, don't let me go home tonight.
But, you...
I love you. Please sleep with me.
But I have to...
I know, when the sun comes up,
you have to go away.
That's why I want to imprint
your memory inside me.
Approaching. A female.
Armed, confirmed!
You?
Metropolitan Police Department,
Security Task Force.
Lieutenant Mamoru Mikogami.
Confirmed.
Kaoru, your sister is here.
What's going on?
Who's this girl?
What are you doing here?
Right. I came to complain.
No! I came to ask
foran official explanation!
About the other day?
That was within my jurisdiction.
You're the one who breached
our operation...
based on a false information.
I've received no explanation!
You work for the Security Police.
You understand there are certain things
we just can't talk about.
You're always like that, Bro.
You suddenly left home.
Who knows when you started
this dangerous work.
Just like you, I'm a public servant.
But why did you have to disappear without
telling anybody? Why?
Couldn't you tell us why?
Yes. There was a reason...
why I joined the Imperial Intelligence.
That was...
Hey, Bro!
What? What did you say?
See, you aren't listening to me!
Ninth Heaven!
That's what I'm investigating.
Ninth Heaven?
It's a cyber drug popular
in the Subcultures.
The same one as we found in Brooks' room?
Yes. My analysis reveals it
was made of pure neuron units.
The same material used for Alice's brain.
It appears to be a system to send some data
directly into human brains.
Maintenance complete.
There's no abnormality
that will pose a problem.
What do you mean?
There are abnormalities,
but they aren't a problem?
Of course there are.
Girls are very complicated.
Mikogami, come in right now.
I'm wanted. See you later.
Alice, listen.
Yes?
Since the Brooks incident,
I see your emotions are not steady.
Yes, I am self-aware.
Is the unsteadiness caused
by Mr. Mikogami?
Well...
Strange.
I cannot control myself.
Really, you're just like a human.
Is this the way humans are? What can I do?
Be true to your heart.
Throw yourself at him.
Throw myself?
You mean, I have to attack Kaoru?
I cannot do such a thing!
Machine or human,
we have the same feelings.
Right?
Hey!
This is Steven Mayhew.
He was in charge of Alice, in the States.
In charge of Alice?
Are you CIA?
Massy Spector was...
the first guinea pig for MJP.
MJP?
A technology to directly connect
human brains and computers.
Was it all right?
You told the top secret to Mikogami.
We applied Alice Technology
to develop MJP.
I don't think Massy is aware
of this yet himself, but...
he's carrying the dormant
memories of Mayumi.
Mayumi...
For Mikogami's sake as well,
I was hoping nothing would happen.
Mikogami so far has no clue
to lead him to Massy.
I'm worried about Dyne Wiseman's
activities, too.
The question is...
why Digital Demand requested
Brooks' assassination.
This is interesting. But I do not like these.
I like...
What's wrong?
Behavioral malfunction now?
- Even for a joke...
- I like you, Kaoru.
I am happy that I got to meet you.
That I got to meet you is...
the best thing that's ever happened to me.
Again!
Red and purple.
Where's your money?
I caught them red-handed.
Mimura, come in now!
Mimura, what's wrong?
Do you copy?
That you came over here means...
You got something pretty heavy.
Ninth Heaven.
Know anything about it?
It's a chip with a stimulus program
to activate a human brain.
They are color-coded in nine colors,
and each has its own effect.
If you use one color too many times.
Or if you use it wrong...
it can cause the user's brain
to go into overdrive.
If you use the 9 colors in a certain
sequence in a certain time period...
it is said that you will gain
an absolute power.
Who says?
Nobody knows the said sequence
or the time period.
There are rumors, all wrong.
An urban legend, sort of.
I want to know the distribution route.
It's not the lmperial Intelligence work, is it?
It's sort of a dangerous investigation...
It's personal.
Whatever.
So long as you pay the fee.
How much?
You know.
With you only.
It's a barter.
Great, Kaoru. You're the best.
More. Give me more.
No, I'm coming.
They all come from a group
called the Shadows.
You can find their small fish easily.
Two dogs. Stupid.
But one of them is a girl.
We killed the guy.
The girl, we're keeping.
Not even a scratch.
Not even a scratch? Nice.
She's not talking much,
but she'll be a fun toy.
Who the hell are you?
You're a Shadow, aren't you?
Do you feel like telling me
where the girl is?
I'm not listening to you.
Then you don't need ears.
What else don't you need?
Eyes? Nose?
No!
Stop!
Let me go! Do you think you
can get away with this?
We can get away with anything.
You're a dog.
Now whimper. Cute.
Too bad, such a body is wasted
on the Security Police.
No, don't touch me!
Let's tame her, and make her our pet.
A pet without manners needs
harsh discipline.
What are you doing?
No!
Let me go, you perverted bastard!
Stop it!
Ouch.
What a pathetic bitch.
Twinkling around everywhere.
Only a dog would do that.
Bro.
No!
What else do you want?
Any discipline requires both
honey and thorns.
No.
Even Security Police girls have nice racks.
No, let me go.
It's disgusting.
Do you want it?
Who would want to be your...
I take it you're still a virgin.
No.
No!
No, no, no!
Didn't I tell you?
You're about to enjoy some sweet dreams.
No, no, don't look at me.
No, let me go.
Please.
No. Don't suck me there.
No.
You're driving me crazy.
I can't any more.
Something's happening.
First a leak, now a shower.
You really don't have any plugs,
don't you?
You need harsher discipline.
What? It's cold!
Don't put it in! No! Pull it out!
Pull it out! No!
It's coming in. It's coming in!
You're ripping my tummy!
You're ripping me!
The fun's just started.
You.
No.
It hurts. Hurts!
You're killing me.
Just kill me! Kill me!
I'll release it now.
No, don't pull it out.
I've joined the Security Police Attack Force.
You won't be the only one
making the world safe!
Mamoru...
Aren't you going under maintenance
at the Headquarters today?
I have confirmed multiple firearms
under your jacket.
- I order you to go back.
- I refuse.
What?
It's against the rules to act
on your own judgment.
Right, Mr. Mikogami?
Kanako!
I see you took the date from Alice.
But I have a personal business
to attend today.
Don't try to stop me.
I can pull the trigger faster than you
by 0.1003 second.
Why don't all three of us
break the rules together?
Thanks.
A Security Police bitch.
Who cares if she breaks?
Red and black. How about five each?
She won't be coming back anymore.
Help me, Bro!
What is it? Who is it?
Good evening.
Let's make it easy for Mr. Mikogami
to sneak in.
We have to make as big
a mess as possible.
Are you ready, Alice?
Here we go!
What?
This is a very expensive stuff. Enjoy it.
Finally, she's become an obedient pet.
Who the hell are you?
Alice!
This is it, girlie.
No, this is my favorite skirt!
You made it all dirty!
You'll pay for this!
Alice!
Are you all right?
I am fine. What about Kaoru?
Mamoru! Get a hold of yourself!
It's me. It's all right!
Mamoru.
Bro, help me.
Bro...
Mamoru!
Multiple bruises, abrasions, grazes...
perineum laceration, vaginal damage,
cervix injury.
But worst of all
her psyche is compromised by something.
Probably Ninth Heaven,
the new cyber drug going around...
I hear its real name is MJP.
MJP?
You have a new voice mail.
The Sender is Ayn.
Kiyoka, then.
Kaoru, I've got news related to the Shadows.
Bro.
Help me, Bro.
Help me, Bro...
Where is Alice?
It's Massy!
I finally figured out where he's gone to!
When Brooks died, he jumped to a nearby
neuron-type brain and possessed it.
Which is, Alice!
Massy is hiding inside Alice!
No way!
The Shadows are backed
by Dyne Wiseman...
the president of Digital Demand
Corporation.
I'll give you the details in person.
Kiyoka.
System error?
No.
Break in the current task.
Unable to control.
The other personality hiding inside Alice.
It turns out to be the final process
to create a new God.
Alice disappears,
and in order to bring her back...
Kaoru charges into the center
of the whole mystery.
"Necross."
Something is waking up quietly.