The target is a weapons technician.
He called in several prostitutes...
and impulsively started
to slaughter them.
It seems he is compulsively committing
crime, due to LMJP.
Good. It feels good. Good.
Use your hands more.
Make me come hard, or I'll snuff you, too.
Don't stop!
All in position!
- Okay, let's go.
- Yes, sir!
One-o-three, report!
What happened, 103?
I can't feel anything. You suck!
No! Help!
Bastard! He's killed two!
We can't muscle our way in.
Give me A's ETA.
Who's next?
No!
Okay, where are you coming from?
Mission accomplished.
The target is dead.
It seems the perpetrator has been killed.
Storm in right away
and rescue the hostages.
Roger. Waiting for next command.
What is it? Someone's jamming it?
Xinn.
September 1st, 2039.
All the computers connected
to the Network froze.
All the computers repeated four letters...
X-I-N-N for 1 second...
and the phenomenon was over.
This one second blink by the Network,
an immense virtual organism...
caused immeasurable damage
to the human race.
A terror literally akin
to a frozen moment in time....
sent a shockwave throughout the world,
"Connect"
It's so good, Kaoru. Give me more.
If you keep up like this, I'll come.
I can't hold back anymore.
So good.
Go ahead, Kaoru. Come inside me.
I can't.
There is only one conclusion, Kaoru.
The question is, who am I?
What?
To me, Kaoru,
it's like we are a part of each other.
I love...
That dream again.
- Hello?
- Sorry to wake you up,
A request placed through
the American Embassy?
Sounds complicated.
You don't need to
bother with reasons why.
It's none of my business.
The main passage to the city's
upper Level will be crowded,
Use our special elevator,
One more thing,
As soon as you arrive at the scene,
retrieve the supply,
Supply?
The target is Massy Spector, 18 years old,
Requesting a refugee status,
He's hoping we'll assist him,
"Hoping we'll assist him..."
Too bad.
I'm Massy Spector.
I'm Ishikawa, from the Intelligence Division.
Have a seat.
Let's talk about your request for refugee
status in our nation.
Let's try not to read between the lines.
Or shall I say,
let's not play a three-penny opera.
You know, Japan and the States have been
in the same bed so a long time.
You!
I taught that sofa a little trick.
It's 8-G now. Shall I make you heavier?
I don't have such poor taste,
as to watch as your body is...
squashed like a tomato.
Imperial National Security
Investigation Agency.
Special Intelligence Force,
Kaoru Mikogami.
What?
So you're an assassin
from the Imperial Intelligence.
How do you know?
I don't know how.
I just know, that's all.
Good bye.
What?
I shut off the Artificial Gravitational Field.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Who are you?
Alice. Call me Alice.
I have been supplied for you, as of today.
Supplied?
Are you a robot?
Yes, Mr. Kaoru Mikogami.
No way. It's just an illusion.
Leaked?
Massy's assassination plan
had been leaked?
Yes. He knew about it.
Also he...
knew me.
I am a little suspicious of the client,
as a matter of fact.
So it was good idea that I send out Alice.
So, what is this?
It's a weapon developed
by the Untied States Army.
They loaned us one, and that's that.
And I remembered you wanted
help before, so here it is.
I wanted human help.
Not a sex toy. It's in a poor taste.
Sex toy. That'd be another way to use it.
Chief!
This has killed more people...
than you have.
That can't be.
Please use me like a firearm.
I was created for that purpose.
Mr. Mikogami.
Kanako, working late again?
I've been analyzing the XINN phenomenon.
The progress is so slow, it drives me crazy.
XINN. I remember that.
It happened only a month ago.
Why don't you leave that to the old man,
slouching in the chair next door?
You fought with Chief?
Because of that girl?
She is a very good girl.
There's no good or bad.
It's a machine, either it works or not.
How did a US Army toy come
to us in the first place?
It's not just for us.
Before she was sent over here,
Alice was stationed at...
the Marines Corp,
a SWAT team and many other places.
I think they want it
to accumulate experiential data...
so they can use it as a basis
for mass production.
It's invincible.
Pedophiles will fall for it at once.
Like Chief says, when it is not in need...
it can help out our men's desire.
I'm tired today.
I'm going home to bed.
Chief instructed me to await
your instructions here.
That old man, what's he thinking?
May I set up my maintenance
supplies over here?
Wait.
I don't like to clutter up my living room.
I understand.
Please instruct me where would be
the optimal location.
The open space right now
would be the kitchen.
I understand.
You have one mail,
Bro, been a while!
Mamoru.
Are you alive and well?
You haven't called me in a while,
What, you got a girlfriend?
No way,
Good morning.
How long have you been there?
For about 15 seconds.
And I didn't notice?
Is breakfast ready?
What? Breakfast?
I did not receive that order.
I was joking.
How can I expect company property
to do that?
Joking?
Yes. I do not understand Kaoru very well.
He was probably being shy
about what he'd said.
Shy. Blush. Embarrass.
I still do not understand.
Maybe it's still too difficult for you.
Yes, it is difficult.
J. H. Brooks. 36 years old.
An Al Software researcher
at Digital Demand Corp.
Digital Demand?
Their technician is our target?
For security purposes.
I see.
Who's the girl?
She's the key to this operation.
Brooks is extremely cautious.
His security system is perfect,
and he rarely goes out.
But he seems to have a bad habit.
You're kidding.
A perfect operation for Alice.
Are you okay with this?
I have nothing against it.
Mr. Mikogami.
I researched various recipes.
This appeared to be the most
generic combination.
When did I order you to prepare
a breakfast?
This is my self-judgment.
Your what?
I judged this was within
the operative parameters...
that defines my non-operational
hour activities.
I don't intend to have a live-in maid.
Kaoru.
I'll eat. Let me wash my face first.
The Headquarters has contacted.
Commence the operation
today at 2300 hours.
A perfect Ninth Heaven.
I finally got it.
It's working!
So this is MJP.
One hour until full charge.
Why are you upset?
Alice has completed her missions...
but her emotional side is undeveloped.
In the States, they probably cared only
about her mission success rate...
and didn't concern themselves
with her emotions.
It's still the same.
It is not!
Take breakfast, for instance.
Alice is trying to get close to you.
I just can't stand this.
You're overreacting.
But, I know. My intuition tells me.
For someone working in this field,
you're surprisingly irrational.
Because I'm just like Alice.
Kanako?
You know what happened to me before...
Being raped, by the agents...
Sort of.
All I can say is that it was unfortunate.
Call us agents and it makes
us sound important...
but we're just murderers.
Something's wrong with us. Including me.
Kanako?
I love you, Kaoru.
I want to be with you, Mr. Mikogami.
You can rape me. Please.
Right there.
No.
Silly.
We don't call this rape.
Kaoru.
No.
- Does it hurt?
- A little.
It's been a while.
Then I'll go slow.
Okay now?
Yes, okay.
Wonderful, Kaoru.
Something's weird with my body.
I can't. No more.
I can't, Kaoru!
You're new. Come in.
I can't stand your doll-like face.
Enemy System Check.
Multiple operatives confirmed.
Five operatives confirmed, all armed.
Armed? It's a trap!
Don't worry about me.
Complete the mission.
Roger.
Brooks is aware of the operation.
Danger. Please retreat immediately.
Alice!
Mamoru?
Bro?
Freeze! Security Police!
Security Police?
What's going on? Why are you here?
We got an information that armed
terrorists are hiding here.
Why are you here?
Armed terrorists?
Shit, they tricked us!
You guys wait here, okay?
On whose authority?
They played you guys.
- There's no terrorist around here.
- What?
Listen, don't move.
Hey, wait!
Bro...
Alice!
Mr. Mikogami.
Please, retreat. This room is...
Game over.
A detonator? A bomb?
I've staged a scenario for you and the
Security Police to kill each other.
You manipulated information, didn't you?
That's very easy for me, Mr. Mikogami.
This brainwave belongs to...
I never die.
Massy.
Even if this body dies,
I will come to see you again.
Spector.
No way.
That is, if you don't die now.
Raise your hands!
Alice!
Led by something mysterious...
Kaoru and Alice begin to share
their feelings,
Meanwhile, Kaoru's sister Mamoru
follows a lead on...
Ninth Heaven, only to fall into the clutch
of an Underground Organization,
Luv Wave, the 2nd Process, "Protocol."
Someone is sleeping there.