THE NIGHT WHEN EVIL FALLS, VOLUME 3
Everybody, let's punish
the demon that destroyed your city.
Alright!
Yeah!
Congratulations, this is your first gangbang.
Look at that.
She's so wet!
My pussy is so wet.
Repent in front of everyone.
I can't move.
This is great.
No kidding.
All their dicks are so hard.
This spell magnifies the opposite
of what you are feeling...
and makes you a puppet to it.
I'm not simulating the lust you are feeling.
It is the raw lust of the gangbangers.
Those humans want to fuck me?
Just being looked at turns on this girl.
How nasty can this horny demon get?
You shot so much cum inside Akane
and you're still not satisfied.
You're about to be gangbanged by all these people.
Your pussy is dripping wet and ready.
Oh, yeah!
You're still dripping juices...
from when Gilva took your virginity.
Gilva...
Now, Sheliss Elleness,
the coup de grace.
First I'll turn that cock back into a clit.
It's no fun if you don't cry.
Stop playing around and just kill me.
Otherwise... Oh!
Take it, baby.
You'll never feel one that's this big!
Pain and pleasure.
Submission and joy.
Let's hear you love it.
God, your cock is so hot.
Just wait.
I'm going to get back at you.
This slut loves dripping her pussy juice
in front of all these people.
This chick is such a masochist.
Her pussy is drooling.
Look at her hard nipples.
Look!
Akane, you must be humiliated
to repent the destruction of this city.
No. I didn't do anything.
But I like this!
Now, service all these people.
Do what you want to me.
I love cock.
Roll your tongue around the head.
It feels so hot.
Fuck my ass.
Yeah, that's nice.
Look at my cock in her pussy!
Her ass is so tight!
Fuck me, fuck me harder!
I want to do that too.
There's no need to gawk.
No need to be jealous.
What's in store for you
is much more elaborate.
Everybody, look.
Look at me spread my legs.
You may be a demon girl,
but being watched turns you on just like humans.
Let's start the show!
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Watch me stroke my pussy.
Whoa, she's so nasty!
She's rubbing her clit so hard.
Doesn't it hurt?
I can't stop masturbating.
This demon is a hardcore pervert.
Watch this.
Just stroking her tail turns her on.
Now watch this.
Stick the tip in my ass.
Do you all understand?
She's a masochistic slut...
that sticks her ass out
and loves to take it up the ass
when you stroke her tail and turn her on.
That's right. I love it up my ass.
Now watch me stroke my pussy until I squirt.
Wow,
her pink pussy is dripping all that nasty hot honey!
I'm getting wet just looking at it.
You were once fucked in the ass
by a water monster and you came.
This is the same.
This would've never happened
if I hadn't let Gilva escape...
An intruder has penetrated the castle gate!
What are these filthy creatures?
Those are my servants!
This is horrible.
Sheliss Elleness,
have you stopped mourning?
Who are you?
You'll meet a pathetic death
and I'll carve that fact on your tombstone!
My name is Gilva.
I have abandoned the human world.
I'm a demon that has descended to Hell.
Gilva, you intentionally chose a time
when most of my subordinates are gone.
I have no intention...
of wasting my energy on your minions.
I have no idea what business
a dog like you has in my castle.
But I will not accept your insult.
Stop acting so important.
You're just an insignificant sentry.
An incidental servant.
A rebellious storm that rises to the heavens
is my secret strength.
I only aimed for you periphery.
Next, I will tear off your limbs.
Try it if you can, little girl.
Not bad, Sheliss Elleness!
Did you actually think...
you could strike me
by charging at me like an idiot?
Fine.
This is, at the least, an appropriate welcome...
for a demon like me.
This is a fake!
Good. Don't rely on your human form.
Come out!
Damn.
You have seen through me!
You are so ugly
compared to your human form.
Sheliss Elleness,
how dare you!
Did you think of me
as any less than my father?
How mistaken of you.
My nails can slice demon souls.
They can slice the soul of your real form.
Now, for the finishing blow!
I have handed your soul to the Death God.
Sheliss Elleness!
Huh?
Damn, that body was a decoy!
The gate to the underworld that Gilva used
is open.
For damaging my castle,
he will regret this in a place deeper than Hell.
...never have happened.
Look at me.
Look at my nasty pose.
Whoa, check it out.
Awesome.
You're such an exhibitionist.
You get so wet just by showing off.
You were just a virgin.
But you follow your nasty cunt.
Your box is so tight it almost hurts my fingers.
That's right.
I'm a nasty slutwith a tight pussy.
Whoa, it looks so tight.
I want to stick my cock in it.
Stick it in both holes!
I'm so hard.
You want those hard cocks...
squirting hot cum all over you,
don't you?
Say it.
Beg to be showered in hot cum.
Please.
I want your cocks.
You want our cocks?
What a nymphomaniac.
You like it up your ass?
I bet it's tight.
Yeah, my ass.
Hurry up and stick it up my ass.
Admit you're a slut and I'll stick it in.
I'm a slut, a slut, a slut.
I want your thick cock.
Take this!
Let me stick it in this hole too.
Hey slut, you really like it rough, don't you?
More, more.
More, more, more...
I love it.
I love it rough in my...
ass and pussy.
I love your big hot dicks!
Alright. We're going to give you a cum bath!
Huh?
Whoa!
Oh, yeah. Let's go another round.
Awesome. I've never been this hard before.
Here I go.
I'll stick it in as many times as you want.
Spread your ass toward me.
Grip my tail.
Whoa, look how big my cock is!
Awesome.
Stick that big fat dick in my ass.
Fuck my ass now!
Yeah!
It hurts so good!
It's so thick!
She's begging for it in her mouth.
You're so tight.
Let's try your tail.
Awesome.
This is awesome.
This is so awesome!
This is awesome! I'm going to fuck her pussy.
Yeah, fuck all my gaping holes.
Cum in my mouth, cum on my face!
I'm going to pee.
Fuck me harder.
Fuck me as deep as you can.
I'm going to pee again!
Mix my pee with your hot cum!
I'm going to cum. I'm cumming!
Good job, my demon princess.
But that's not to say it's over.
You can't give in yet.
There's a lot more I want to do to you...
Sheliss Elleness.