It must be my imagination.
No!
Eek!
My hole.
A vulgar sacrifice to help heal Master Gilva
who was wounded in the magic world.
How effective will it be?
There is no need to worry.
The plan was for Gilva to defeat
Sheliss Elleness and capture her.
But it failed and he was wounded.
Sheliss Elleness, one of the children
of Zurbach, King of Evil,
was stronger than anticipated.
Caught with his pants down.
Master Gilva's alternative plan
is to gradually heal his wounds in this way...
until he can fight on favorable terms.
He will not waste his energy
until he heals his wounds.
Hmmm.
The time for the attack is near.
Shall we go back?
Yes.
I came to see
what this nauseating smell was.
It's a horrific goblin.
Dealing with this kind of small fry
won't get me anywhere.
Huh?
What?
This one is in a higher class
than the last one.
There is no need to fear.
I just need you to serve as a guide.
You think I'm scared?
Who do you think I am?
You should mind your manners.
You're only alive because I have use for you.
Look who's talking.
What's your name?
My name is
Sheliss Elleness Zurbach.
And yours?
Akane Kido, Demon Killer.
Introductions are over.
Where is Gilva?
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
You reek of evil spirits.
You must know Gilva.
Now...
Listen to what I have to say.
Take this.
You asked for it.
That wasn’t just a grenade.
It was customized and full of anti-goblin matter.
You were just an over-the-hill goblin.
I wanted to ask the whereabouts of Gilva.
That's too bad.
Your hatred is very good.
Your parents were industrial researchers
beaten to death by Gilva.
They were left to hang
from the side of a building.
You will not forgive him...
until you find him
and exact revenge with your own hands.
How did you know?
You must be his partner.
This misunderstanding must be resolved.
Kelderos!
Let go!
For a tomboy, you're curvy with a girlish body.
But your tits are small.
Damn it. Let go!
I'll show you the sorcery of the King of Evil.
I'm getting hot.
I'm so horny.
Kiss my nipples.
Pinch my clit.
I'm so wet.
Let me lick your pussy.
Please, baby.
Stick your finger in my box.
I'm gushing!
Doesn't it feel good?
Let me lick and suck your clit.
You lost your parents and had a hard life.
You fell for a loser of a man
and lost your virginity.
Stop looking into my past!
You're a vulgar girl who loses control
to a swollen clit.
I'll teach you the discipline of Kelderos.
This pain turns me on.
You're so cute.
Such a horny skank.
I will take you to a world you'll love.
Now stick your ass up in the air.
I'll do anything for you.
And you will love it.
I love gangbangs.
Oh, yes.
Enjoy, you horny skank.
I'll take care of you.
Stick it in deeper.
This is a magical contract with a spell...
that will let us get along.
Just sign it.
I'm cumming!
Fuck me!
Sheliss Elleness Zurbach has appeared
in this dreary land.
One of your few remaining mercenaries
was defeated sooner than expected.
Huh?
Did I say something to upset you?
Miti, do you really expect that trash
to be food for me?
You should watch what you eat.
Before I forget...
Master Gilva.
May I have fun with Sheliss Elleness
before you eat her?
I'm not in a hurry to eat her.
Meduna, you will have plenty of time
to go down on her.
I can't believe I'll get to molest such cute girls!
I am so happy to have been born under you.
I, Slave Meduna,
will follow you to the ends of this earth!
It has been many days
since I was defeated by young Zurbach.
But the days of humiliation and disgrace
will end!
We will devour people and magicians.
Our powers will rise and once again,
we will rule this world.
First, we must exact revenge against
Zurbach, King of Evil.
We attack his daughter, Sheliss Elleness.
Then we beat Zurbach to death.
Sheliss is traveling
with a demon killer named Akane Kida.
Let us entrap them.
Meduna, Miti, don't let me down.
- Yes, sire.
MUSEUM
Is this really Gilva's stronghold?
That's what I heard.
There is a path that leads to his caverns.
The snitch said the information is accurate.
Don't you sense anything?
I'm still not used to his world.
I would like to depend on your sixth sense.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Innumerable deeds of hell.
Innumerable deeds of good.
This evening, these powers
will be unleashed in battle.
The challenger to Devil King Gilva is...
a kind hearted, yet ferocious
privileged princess of darkness
whose spirit has been tormented.
And a girl whose parents
were killed and lost all hope.
A brave, wild, and hardened
demon killer.
Please give a round of applause!
Huh?
I wanted to deal with the small fry first.
Small fry?
But you should be terminated first,
Sheliss Elleness.
Are you Miti?
I am honored that you know my name.
Akane, hold back.
I will abandon you if you take the lead.
Alright. Go ahead.
Good.
I'm sorry to let you down...
but Akane and Miti must leave the arena.
What is going on?
You even removed one of your own.
Miti is scary.
She steals the show.
And, upon your capture,
she would immediately present you to Gilva.
I wouldn't have any fun with you.
I see.
Aren't you worried?
Akane is in trouble.
No. Akane is a demon killer.
She can take care of herself.
That's so cool!
The image of two cool girlfriends
meeting horrific endings.
I get horny just thinking about it.
You can imagine all you want.
Right, Meduna?
Oh, no!
This water...
It's too late to realize now.
Sheliss, you're so quick tempered.
Aren't you scared?
No. You have power,
but no experience in fighting.
What?
Take this!
This water that clings to you
and restrains your body...
is harmless now.
But...
once it comes into contact
with our pussy juices,
it becomes an oily slime,
and becomes an intoxicating body massager.
Do you actually think I am so unsophisticated
as to surrender to something like that?
That feels good.
Finger me.
More.
You do all sorts of things to Akane,
but you get embarrassed
just getting your pussy rubbed.
Don't talk as if you know.
But I do know.
I've always been observing you
through reflections in water.
You pervert.
You think so?
Whenever you stroke your pussy,
you rub your ears on a pillow.
You even watched that?
I bet you wanted somebody to lick it.
Yes, my pussy is gushing.
That feels so good.
Do it more.
I've wanted to do this from the day...
I first laid my eyes upon you.
It looks like the water is ready.
Your pussy juice is transforming the water
into a total body massager.
Oh, yes!
I'll try to use this water against you.
This is going to make me cum!
The water is absorbing
the magic in your pussy juice.
My! You're so sensitive
where your wings are connected.
Stroke my tail.
Oh, yes, yes!
Sheliss, we're just getting started.