THE NIGHT WHEN EVIL FALLS, VOL. 2
That feels nice. Keep doing it.
From the first time I saw you,
I wanted to have sex with you.
You look about ready.
This sex slime,
created to mix with your pussy juice,
will make you cum and cum.
Oooh.
Do you really think
this water trick is going to work?
This won't work!
It will.
Because it has absorbed your power
from your pussy juice.
You're so sensitive where your wings connect.
Yeah. Rub my pussy.
We're just getting started, Sheliss.
It's going up my ass.
Do you know what this is?
You don't mean it's a...
You got it.
A super enema!
Oh, yeah!
Hold it in.
It's the ritual for you to become my plaything.
Not so easy.
I love that humiliated agonizing expression!
I can't hold it in.
How much longer do I have to take this?
Strengthen your abdomen
and hold it in.
Do you want to let it all out?
Then let's see you take this!
God, it's going to spurt out.
What's going to spurt out?
Please, I have to let it out.
I can't hear you.
You have to plead louder.
Please!
I have to pooh!
All right...
No, I changed my mind.
Not until all of the enema is deep inside you.
It's going to leak out of my ass.
I can't hold it in.
I can't hold it.
It's coming out!
Go ahead.
It'll make you all clean.
I can't hold it.
Here it comes.
Sheliss, you're in ecstasy.
God, it feels good.
Now, let's really clean you out.
You're going to blow out everything.
My butt is so hot.
Fill me up.
I want to do it again.
Yeah! Let's see you let it all out.
I can't hold it.
It's going to spurt out!
Sheliss, we're finished.
My ass is still burning.
You're so sensitive inside.
See? Look how wet you are.
Oh, my pussy is dripping.
I bet you want a big thick cock
up your ass.
If you were so turned on with
just a liquid enema,
I'd like to see what a big hard dick
would do to you.
And now, may I introduce
our special attraction.
What... what is that?
My pet, the water monster.
Save a little for Master Gilva, all right?
Now, let's see some water monster
anal penetration.
I don't know if I can take anything too big.
You think I can't take it up my ass?
I dare you.
You'll cum so hard that you'll never recover.
Awesome. The head is going in.
So do you like it?
Do you like that big head in your ass?
It's so big and thick. I love it.
Cumming?
No. I won't.
You don't have to lie.
You can't make me cum.
Oh god. I'm losing it.
I'm going to squirt.
It looks like I win this round.
It's so deep up my ass.
My gaping ass feels so good!
It hurts so good!
It's going to be even better in a moment.
Fuck my ass harder.
You're not playing fair.
I think I'm going to squirt and gush!
You were fucked in the ass
by a water monster.
Aren't you embarrassed
at how you let yourself go?
Sheliss is a nasty girl.
You squirmed and screamed in delight
as you did anal with the water monster.
And you squirted out of your pussy
and gushed out of your ass.
A nasty girl indeed.
Before I present you to Gilva,
I'll drink your pussy juice
to gain magical powers.
Then tonight's show is over.
No. Your pussy juice is too strong!
I feel sick.
Meduna.
You run away.
Let me go...
...or finish me off.
This is what you get
for what happened to Meduna.
This is Sheliss' pussy juice in my mouth.
By now, she's recovered
and in a blinding rage.
All you have done is awakened a giant.
That amount of magical pussy juice
isn't enough for Master Gilva.
If you didn't get in the way, we could've
captured Sheliss at the aquarium.
I'd sure like to put a bullet in your head
right now.
You lost your fight to me, tentacles restrain you,
and you still resist.
I'm impressed.
Why don't you just finish me off?
You don't even have the courage to do that.
If you didn't have any value,
I would've killed you a long time ago.
Value?
Don't expect Sheliss to come save me.
But Akane, you're extremely valuable.
I read your mind when I captured you.
You two have a mutual abstinence contract.
What about it?
Sheliss is alive.
She'll beat the crap out of all of you.
Just wait and see.
You don't get it.
Are you stupid?
Just finish me off.
I don't care... huh?
Damn you.
Gilva, Sheliss will come.
I wouldn't play around.
I'm putting her in her place.
We can't have her causing problems
after we subjugate her.
Subjugate me?
Gilva, what are you doing?
Contractually, you're immune to her sexual attacks.
You're perfect bait.
If I control your body,
she'll fall under my domination.
My box is all wet.
You failed miserably at avenging your parents.
Akane, you're quite a loser.
Damn you.
Go subjugate your soul in my netherworld!
The energy of the water magician
is in this direction.
Meduna, I have to thank you.
You reawakened my desire for revenge.
Akane, you've been subjugated.
Gilva did it.
Sheliss, get away!
Sheliss...!
Do you really think you can abuse
my contract with Akane?
I guess I can't fool you.
It doesn't hold water in the demon world.
Do you know how I deal with such fools?
I attack until you crumble.
You are already in our trap.
Take this, baby!
I wanted to warn you from the beginning.
My name is Sheliss, not baby.
You're too rude.
You embarrassed me you wench!
No!
You're nothing but a skank.
My black magic can crush diamonds.
It's a dagger that pierces monsters...
and brings upon inevitable destruction.
There!
Black Javelin!
Let the true Darkness appear before me.
Ferociously and thunderously
appear before me!
My true Darkness,
go raise hell!
Akane, move aside!
Oh, no!
You're finally depleted.
I can still fight.
You may have the will,
but your body and magic is depleted.
Sheliss, I'm sorry.
Sheliss Elleness, I will now brand you
with the victor's mark.
No. Stop.
Don't subjugate me!
Come here on your knees.
Lift that leg!
I can't see your face like that.
What's happening to me?
I'm creating something
from your subjugated clit.
You can't control it.
When a woman grows a cock for the first time,
even the holy ones scream like animals
and splatter cum everywhere.
How about you?
This will be the first ejaculation ever
for the demon princess.
Let us welcome it.
Then I will suck it.
Sheliss Elleness, this is my sweet revenge.
Let me suck this girl's cock.
Miti, do your thing.
Sure.
Don't shoot your wad with this little trick.
You won't be able to do the real nasty stuff.
Even a child can hold it longer.
I don't know how to hold it.
I'm going to shoot cum!
Shall we let her shoot her thick hot cum?
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to cum!
I don't believe it.
Look how wet Akane is.
Let's see you two fuck.
It's so thick!
Akane, stick that big fat cock up your cunt.
Oh, Sheliss.
Akane.
Oh, yeah.
It's so hot. I'm going to shoot!
Fuck me harder.
You like my fat cock in your box, baby?
Yeah, I can feel the head
all the way in.
Cum, Akane.
I'm going to cum!
I can't stop fucking you.
Please, don't stop.
Your cock feels so good!
Fuck me. Fuck me harder!
I love fucking your tight pussy!
I can feel that throbbing cock head
deep inside.
Let me make you cum...
with my big long dick!
Yeah, baby.
I'm going to make you cum.
I'm going to cum.
Come on, baby.
Cum on my cock, baby.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to shoot!
So how do you like
the pleasures of a man?
Are you sad?
Are you resentful?
I didn't know demons had such feelings.
Now, Sheliss Elleness,
the coup de grace.
First I'll turn that cock back into a clit.
It's no fun if you don't cry.
Stop playing around and just kill me.
Otherwise... Oh!
It's too big!
Take it, baby.
You'll never feel one that's this big!
Pain and pleasure.
Submission and joy.
Let's hear you love it.
God, your cock is so hot.
Just wait.
I'm going to get back at you.
What... humans?
The citizens of the destroyed city
are approaching.
Master Gilva, may I have some fun
with those humans?
Look...
She's just lying there...
We can do what we want to her...
She's irresistible.
Everybody. Let's punish the devil
that destroyed your city.
Yeah! Hurrah!
You're going to be gang banged.
Oh, no!