Magical Twilight
This is impossible!
Who'd have thought such a hot
little number would come on to me!
I can't take it!
Please pass your papers
to the student behind you.
All those who have turned in your papers may leave.
Those having to take the practical exam, it will begin in one hour.
You will all be notified of the results of your test.
We'll take a break until then.
So, teacher, how about doing something
about my written exam scores?
Are you crazy? I cant't do anyone a favor like that!
It would have helped if you had taken the damn test!
Besides, you seduced me!
Quit whining! Even human school girls have a price.
And you're smart enough to know, nothing's free!
So don't go thinking your're getting
off with any freebies from me!
Come on. I'm sure you could do something.
It would be so sad if I had
to tell the Great Principal.
Expulsion from the Magical World
is so extreme!
You had this whole thing planned!
What a bitch!
Thanks for everything, teacher.
I'll be counting on you!
Chipple! How'd it go?
Your third Graduation Exam?
It'll be a major miracle if I pass!
Chipple... Wait!
Have you seen Irene?
She was supposed to take her exam today
too, but we haven't seen her all morning...
I wonder what could have happened to her?
I don't see how she could have forgotten...
I really don't care!
How can you say that? Hasn't she been
your best friend since you were little?
No, she wasn't, not ever! Our houses
were just close together that's all!
Why are you so angry?
Because I
HATE IRENE!
But why? Irene is such a nice girl!
That's right and she's so sweet and generous!
Right!
Boy, has she got you fooled! She's as sweet
and innocent as the cat who ate the canary!
You wouldn't belive the things she's
tried to do with me when we were alone!
Just because she's stronger and more powerful,
she thinks she can get away with murder!
She's a two-faced pussy!
Meow.
Hi, Chipple!
What's that about a pussy?
Irene!
My stomach...
Are you alright, Chipple?
I'm okay. It's okay. Don't worry.
I'll just go see the nurse...
Take me out of the path of danger...
The Great Principal bids
the next examinee to enter.
Yes sir!
Student number 15,103.
Ellington, Chipple.
Yes sir.
You have failed to achieve a passing
grade on your written examination.
Yes sir.
Do you want to give up now?
Or will you take the practical exam?
Of course I'll take it!
This is the third time I've
taken that exam this year...
I really, really want to graduate this time.
My only dream is of becoming a good witch!
Yes, you've certainly been among
our most willing students...
You may not be aware that I personally grade
all performances on the practical exams
even if you failed the written portion
on my grading curve it's still
possible for you to graduate.
Simply do the best you're capable of.
Yes sir!
Now, about the exam. First, you must
go down to the surface.
To the surface?
To the Human world?
To the surface!
Alright! I'm going to do everything
I can to pass the test!
At last, I'm here!
Beautiful!
Chipple!
Chipple, you were flying like a
runaway express train!
Irene! What are you doing here?
I've got the same assignment for my
practical exam as you do, Chipple.
He said that we had to do it together.
Just how can you be taking the practical
exam without taking the written exam first?
Oh, I took it orally.
My written essays were
in body language.
I should have known.
Oh, by the way, could you tell me
the details of our assignment?
What? You mean nobody told you?
I thought I could get
what I needed from you.
I can't belive how pathetic you are!
Alright, I'll tell you just once.
We've been assigned to move
into a human household.
We must strive to make a good
impression on our test subject.
if the subject's impression is
favorable enough, we pass the exam.
And who's our human target?
Tachibana Tsukasa
He's a 19 year old student,
currently preparing for college.
That's all the information I have.
I hope he's not too ugly.
Why must you be like this?
He's the only test subject we've got!
Well, these are the details! Bye!
Hey! Wait for me!
Please... stop...!
Another dream about being killed...
Excuse me, please?
Yes?
Good morning!
Hello, we're two apprentice witches
from the world of White Magic.
Witches?
That's right.
I'm not interested!
Crap! He's got some nerve, brushing
me off from behind a door like that!
Uh, Irene...
You're just a lousy human!
I won't forgive you!
You idiot!
I think you went too far, doing that.
He asked for it.
Well, I guess we've lost a few points.
This is all your fault!
What's going on?
Is it still morning? What happened?
Hey dude, what are you doing here so early?
You look like shit.
This crazy girl forced her way into my house
and wouldn't let me go back to sleep.
Oh yeah? And since when have you
been going out with this chick?
It's not like that.
These two girls just showed up this morning.
What? Two girls? You lucky son of a bitch!
You don't understand, they're both witches!
Huh?
Pretty funny! That's a good one, Tachibana!
I've been thinking...
these awful dreams I've been having.
Maybe they're connected somehow to those two.
Hmm, you're pretty sharp!
Huh? What the hell?
You've got to be jokeing...
Jokes aren't my style
Where the hell did she come from?
What is it?
That's her! The girl who
comes to me in my dreams.
You're not here to kill me, are you?
Bingo! I sent those dreams to psych
you up for your impending death!
Yo! Yo! Babe, Where are you from?
What's your name?
My name is Liv, a witch from
the Black Magic World.
Another witch!
Of course, I'm not really a full fledged
witch. I still have to pass one last test.
That's right. Those other two were
saying something about that.
I see, so that makes this chick
witch number three, right?
Number three?
In any case...
Why are you so set on killing me?
Because killing you is the practical
portion of my final exam, of course.
Noway!
Well, I'm going to let you go this time.
Besides, it looks like I've got something
else to take care of.
Tachibane, I don't know what's going
on, but I'll bet it gets pretty interesting!
I'm going to die!
This is no time to make jokes!
She's cute.
No, no. This is the old "a girl looks
best working in the kitchen" trick.
What's wrong?
What the hell is going on here?
A witch is trying to kill me, and you idiots
show up in my apartment and ask what's wrong?
Kill you?
Your friend showed up at school
and told me all about it!
She said that killing me
was part of her final exam!
Damnit! I've got my own test to take
and if I fail it'll be my third time!
Get out of here! Both of you!
This is my house!
There's no need to be so rude
about it, you know!
What?
I've got an exam to pass, too!
Stop thinking of no one but yourself!
You brainless bimbo! Why should I
give a damn about your problems?
That does it, I've had it with you!
What the hell are you doing?!
So, there are White Magic students
taking exams here too.
You really did have a rough night, didn't you?
So, how did you get rid of those two?
Oh, that was the easy part.
If I don't have any favorable impressions
of them, they'll fail their final exams.
Scaring them away was as easy as
telling them what kind of grade
they'd get if they didn't leave!
I see, but don't you miss them?
It's not healthy for you to eat
the same thing everyday.
Please, try this. I made it just for you.
Leave me alone!
Tsukasa-kun, please listen to me.
Shut up! I told you not to come here!
Tsukasa-kun, I... I've failed
this exam three times already.
That might not be the only reason but I feel
I do understand how you're feeling right now.
I just wanted to see if I could
cheer you up a little... that's all.
That's all I wanted to say, please eat well.
Bye!
Wait up!
You're... Chipple, right?
You can call me Chipple. And...?
That food of yours...
Yes?
Since you already brought it...
Let's eat it together!
This one and that one.
That one is really good.
This one?
Yes, it's very good.
Let's see...
And...?
Yes! Delicious!
I knew you'd like it!
That's great!
What did you want to talk about?
That you're a little sneak!
I can't believe you pulled that sorry
"Home Cooking" stunt on me!
That was never my intention!
Forget it! But remember this!
From now on I'm going
to do things my way!
You mean you're going to stoop
to your usual dirty tricks!
You got it!
And if I don't work quickly, that Black
Magic witch is likely to kill Tachibana.
I mean to have my way with him
before she finishes him off!
That's your karma, I guess.
Why's she so set on
killing Tsukasa, anyway?
You really don't know?
In order to receive a Black Magic License...
...a student has to kill a human
to pass the practical exam.
I see. They're a little more extreme
than us White Magic users, aren't they?
Ah! But that means we can't
ever leave him alone!
Not with that Black Magic
student out to get him.
You mean that one?
That's her!
Shes's heading towards his apartment!
I'm not letting her get away with this!
Hey, I'm not going to
let you sneak off again!
Oh... Chipple... I...
Your happy dream ends right here!
I'm here to turn your worst
nightmare into reality, as promised!
You again!!!
I won't hold you to that promise!
You really didn't have to get up so
early to ruin my Sunday, did you?
"Good deeds should be done
quickly, without hesitation!"
Good deed? You're trying to kill me!
Which is a very good thing, from
a Black Magic point of view.
Now, prepare to die...
No! Stop!
Die!
Don't get too far ahead of yourself!
Chipple!
You must be one of those children
from the White Magic World.
If you make any attempt
to harm Tsukasa-kun
you'll have to answer to me!
Chipple.
Alright, if that's the way things are,
I'll eliminate you as well.
I might even accure bonus points
on the exam for taking you out!
What'll I do? My magic's
not even as powerful as Irene's...
Here!
Chipple!
I'll make you forget about Chipple.
How is it? Are you cuming?
Chipple!
Tsukasa-kun!
Hmm! Should I kill you both at once?
Get out of here! Chipple! Hurry!
Tsukasa-kun!
What can I do?
I don't have the power to beat her!
Go on! Get out of here now!
I'm going to hurt you, slowly but surely.
Chipple! Hurry!
Tsukasa-kun!
This is quite unexpected!
I never would have believed that such a powerful
witch could exist in the White Magic World.
But, the next time we meet,
it will be I who prevail!
Prepare yourself!
That means she's going to try
and kill me again, doesn't it?
Hey you!
Hey, you're that witch chick, aren't you?
Decided to give me your phone number yet?
Are you crazy? Is your friend
Tachibana here today?
Well now, I don't think
I've seen him around...
Is he out someplace with
that White Witch bitch?
So, I can't do anything about him yet.
Yo! Yo!
You can do something
with me, though!
I don't have any business with you.
Hey! It's Tachibana!
Where?
I've got a lot of business
to do with you, witch!
What's going on???
Don't worry, this is the school nurse's office,
and I made sure no one else can get in.
You bastard! Do you really think you can
get away with doing this to a witch?!
Strangely enough, it's not against
the law to do anything to a witch.
That's not my point!
What point would you like to make?
Stop it! Don't touch me!
Sorry, I've got to teach you something
that's a lot more fun than killing people!
Stop...
What's so urgent all of the sudden?
I've made up my mind!
About what?
Just stay here, and make sure
you lock the door!
Now I understand! Chipple's going to...
Chipple!
I'll make you forget all about that
goody-two-shoes Chipple!
Shall we pick up where we left off?
I can't move!
I can feel her presence. Somewhere nearby,
is a Witch of the Black Magic World.
She's in there.
The witch is in there!
If I can't take out this Black
Magic user, Tsukasa-kun will die!
I may not survive, but this is for him.
I will protect Tsukasa-kun!
Hey, babe! What's shakin'?
I've decided not to kill Tachibana.
In fact, I've quit being a witch. I don't
want to be parted from this man of mine!
So, you must be Chipple, right?
You heard what the lady said,
tell Tachibana that everything's cool.
Magical powers are one thing, but they
can't stand up to my magic wand!
This will definitely bring me up for graduation, yes!
Irene.
What the hell have you been doing?!
Chipple!
You used your magic to force him
to do this, didn't you?
Perhaps, but his body certainly
hasn't voiced any complaints!
I'm going to make
you very, very sorry!
Chipple, you don't really
think you can beat me?
That's unimportant! This is for Tsukasa-kun!
Don't be stupid! You know that falling
for a human's only a waste of time!
If I do this for Tsukasa-kun, it won't be a waste!
You're out of your mind!
I'll make you understand!
Come on!
Stop it!
Don't you lay a hand on Chipple!
If you're going to do
something, do it to me!
If you're going to do it, do it to me.
Tsukasa-kun!
Chipple...
I'm here.
What a bunch of crap!
I can't take anymore of this!
So... I won't be able to see you again?
We may not live in the same world, but...
I guess there are things no one can control.
This one time, it was real.
Our first time, our last time, together.
Good-bye, Tsukasa-kun!
That stuff's not very good for you...
It's unhealthy, eating that stuff everyday.
What?!
Here!
How is this possible?
I flunked.
You must go back to Tachibane's place
once more, and retrain yourself!
I'll phrase it like that anyway!
That's what he said!
That means...
I guess I'm going to be
a student forever!
Chipple!
From now on, I'm not going anywhere!