This place is huge.
Please keep an eye out for your
children to avoid any injuries.
I can't wait!
We will now lower the safety bar, be careful.
Please enjoy the show.
It's been days since Kagano said her goodbye.
There hasn't been any rapes since then.
And everyone forgot about her existence...
I thought I would never see her again.
I also felt that something of me was missing...
See, he's right here!
We were looking for you!
What are you doing, Onii-chan?
Here, I bought you lunch.
Let's eat together.
Onii-chan, here. Fried noodle bread and milk.
Thanks.
Huh, where is Chie-chan?
Chie got the cold since yesterday.
I see, too bad.
Yeah, she sounded sick on the phone.
Let's go visit her.
Yeah, but Chie's mom said
we should leave her alone.
I see.
Onii-chan, today is minimum day so
let's all go out somewhere after school.
OK, Miahiro-senpai?
Akitoshi, I want to ask you something later.
Kagano!?
Hey, Onii-chan!
Okajima-kun?
Kagano!
Uh... wrong person...
What's this!?
I'm so happy you asked me out!
That voice, is it Chie-chan?
What did you want to talk about?
What is this!?
What's wrong!?
No, no, something is crawling up!
No, it's so sick!
It's coming inside my panties!
Chie-chan, what's wrong!?
No, don't come. Please stop!
What's going on!?
Chie, Chie-chan!
What is this!? What's going on!
It hasn't finished yet...
Hasn't finished?
Kagano?
Yes...
It hasn't finished... beware of the ones dear to you.
Okajima-kun?
Onii-chan?
Akitoshi!
Kagano...
Okajima-kun, are you ok?
Onii-chan, what just happened?
Miahiro and Touru?
Chie-chan! Is Chie-chan alright!?
What are you saying, I told you
she's been sick since yesterday.
What...?
Don't you remember Yua-chan said she has a cold?
What's wrong, Akitoshi?
Onii-chan, what's wrong?
Oh, food!
Was that Kagano?
No, something was different.
Akitoshi, Akitoshi!
About that question, may I please ask Yua-chan...
out on a date?
Hmm, yeah...
She said it wasn't finished yet...
Is it about the rapes?
More monsters!?
...beware of the ones dear to you.
So it's OK with you if I ask Yua-chan?
Uh... yeah...
Yes, alright!
Not... finished?
Coming.
Hello, Okajima residence.
Akitoshi-chan, dinner is ready.
Please tell Yua to come home.
Huh, Yua?
Oh, Yua isn't there?
It's 8 o'clock, where could she be?
Did she tell you anything?
Out on a date?
I'll go look for her.
Oh, thank you.
Wassup Akitoshi?
Touru, you know where Yua is?
Oh, Yua-chan and I separated at the park.
The park?
Hey, you said I can ask her out on a date.
Oh yeah... but where is Yua?
She said she forgot something
inside the park and went back inside.
Yua isn't back yet?
Yeah, not yet.
Want to go look for her at the park?
Yeah!
Alright, I'll wait for you at the park entrance.
I overslept! Where is this?
This is the park...
Chie, don't scare me!
What are you doing here, Yua?
Huh, didn't you have a cold, Chie?
I do, but I was worried about
you so I came looking for you.
Really? But what about you?
Anything for Yua.
Yua, I always thought you were so cute!
Chie, you're acting weird.
Chie, you're scaring me.
I love you.
Yua...
Crap!
What is Yua doing!
Akitoshi, over here!
No, Chie, what's wrong!?
Don't run, Yua.
Chie, what happened, what's going on!
I'll be gentle...
Yua...
Chie is a monster!
So cute...
My first kiss... taken by Chie.
So happy...
No!
Wait up, Yua.
So mean, thought we are friends.
No, stop it!
No, no, Chie stop!
Not like this, no!
Quiet down, Yua.
Good girl.
Looks delicious.
Cute breast.
No Chie, stop!
Yua, so cute.
Chi...!
No!!
No, No! Chie, let go!
I loved you since we met.
I want to have you every way possible!
Not there!
No, not the butt!!
Touru, you sure she's here?
It's locked.
I'll go from behind, you stay here.
Hey, Touru!
Is someone there!
Who is it!!
Yua!
Hey, what are you doing!?
Oh, Okajima-senpai. You here to pick up Yua?
Too bad, she doesn't want to go home.
Onii-chan...
Yua!
Now it's Chie-chan? It didn't finish!?
Senpai, let's have fun together.
Onii-chan... come...
Yua, wake up!
Chie, realize what you're doing!
What? I can't hear you from over there.
Senpai, what is it?
Senpai, you love Yua too, right?
You can touch her breast
and lick her womanhood all you want.
Oh, you have never seen it before?
Here, let's show him closely.
So cute, look at him Yua. He's flushing red.
Onii-chan, look at me and make me feel good...
Stop it! Stop it, Yua!
You're so stubborn.
Yua, let's team up to make him feel better.
Huh?
Yua, stop it!
Stop it, Yua!
Senapi, you were quick.
Was Yua's mouth that great?
But it's only the beginning.
What are you...
But... there's one thing I want you to tell me.
Who is Kagano Ai?
Who is Kagano?
Oh, I think you know her very well.
No one named Ai is in my class.
I never said your class...
See, you know.
It's her, right?
Who is she... what is she to you?
I told you, I don't know!
I see... if you don't tell me, Yua will be...
Chie-chan, stop! What are you doing!?
If you don't tell me, Yua's pussy will get penetrated!
Stop! I really don't know!!
Senpai, Yua is still a clean virgin.
See, it's tight.
But, if you don't tell me...
Feel like talking?
Senpai?
Chie-chan, I beg you. Please stop!
No! It hurts!
Really, I really don't know anything!
Stop lying!
Onii-chan, it hurts!
She told me not to ask anything!
You think I will believe that?
Stop it, stop it!
It hurts, it hurts! Onii-chan!
Stop it, please stop it!
You are stubborn...
Yua, I'm sorry but blame your brother.
Yua, sorry... l'm sorry...
Who is it!
I'll tell you...
Right there!
I am Ai.
Kagano!
Ai...
No worries, I cut off the tentacles controlling her.
Kagano, you came back!
I just have unfinished business...
Oh, Akitoshi!
Touru...
Yua-chan! Chie-chan!
Why are they naked?
What happened?
Wha!? Touru!
Forgive me, Akitoshi.
You finally show yourself.
Touru?
I've been waiting for this.
I thought you've gotten away
after that fight with Harumi-sensei.
Stop it Touru!
This is the end of the magical warrior...
Touru, why are you doing this?
This is revenge... to all humans.
What do you mean!?
Akitoshi, I've been attending
the school before you have.
It was when I barely started the school...
An older schoolmate asked me out...
That's nothing to hold hatred against.
What if it was... a man?
Let me tell you I don't swing that way.
When I declined his offer...
He called me out and...
And raped me with 3 others...
The insult of being sprayed with their cum...
People came and looked...
But no one came to the rescue...
Despair...
Akitoshi, do you know?
How I cursed being called cute!
But...
I came to a conclusion, to have revenge!
With powers that no one can come close too!
Touru. I know how you feel, but stop this!
You know how I feel?
How is that possible, you didn't experience it!
But...
Fine, Akitoshi. You think you
can stand the pain I experienced?
Well, do you think you can!?
S... op... Sto... p, Touru...
My pain is not even close!
How do you like my power, Akitoshi?
If I wanted to, I can snap you half.
...op, st... p, Touru...
You are...
pathetic.
You can't do much with those powers!
What!?
You are pathetic.
Your powers are not yours.
You are being controlled.
The real you is a puny bastard!
Is that all you have to say?
Fine, let me show you your so called weak powers!
Wait, you won't be able to use this rod.
If you want to use the rod, split Akitoshi with it.
Shit!
Do you have anything else to say?
I get excited when people rebel against me.
Wildly, that is!
Hah, do you like the pain!?
I hope you understand my pain at least a little.
I see, so you want to play tough... alright!
I will never surrender to you.
Touru, aren't you satisfied?
Stop it!
Your blood is delicious.
I'll suck your insides from down there!
Touru, Stop! I beg you!!
Akitoshi, you're annoying.
Shut up!
Peace and quiet at last.
I see...
So you don't want to open your legs.
However...
There is no blind spot for a woman's body.
This is what you get...
for insulting me!
You can not get away from me...
I will keep violating you!
Until you die!
The liquid being released is a deadly poison...
When absorbed during climax
you will keep climaxing until you die!
Until you die...
I will never forgive you!