How did I come... home?
I can't remember...
Why am I here?
My head is throbbing...
I think something terrible happened...
How long has it been?
I'm starting to remember, slowly...
My name is Akitoshi Okajima.
And this is... my room!
I'm sure I...!
A, are you Ai?
Is it really you!?
I told you not to get involved with me.
Why are you following me?
I could've left you alone.
But you would've died.
There will be no next.
So, don't come near me.
Alright... how's...
Mikage?
She was being controlled by the Yuragi.
She has accepted them into herself.
Yuragi?
I told you not to get involved...!
It is up to her for survival...
What...?
Sexy Magical Girl Vol. 2
- Fall of Magical Girl-
Mikage, where is Mikage!?
Mikage... was not at the scene.
Not a single trace of what happened last night...
Thinking back to the incident that took place last night...
I was not in the mood to be waken up by Yua.
As expected, the front gates are not open this early.
I go in from the back and walk pass the chairman's office.
I wasn't expecting anyone to be here this early.
Teacher Harumi!?
I'm cumming!!
Who is it!?
Ai did not come to school today.
Mikage came to school, but she went
to the nurses office because she felt ill.
I was relieved.
I didn't know how to react if I saw either of them.
Class Call.
Stand... bow... sit
Terrible news again.
Another murder took place last night.
I've already said this many times, but
don't wander around, especially at night.
This goes to both you males and females.
Alright, homeroom is finished.
Study well you guys.
And Mr. Okajima.
Come to my office after school.
Understood?
Y, yes!
What did you do, Akitoshi?
None of your business.
Come to think about it, I didn't
have anything to eat since last night.
This is harsh...
I'm so hungry...
Today was such a tiring day.
I think I'll hurry home.
(Brother didn't come home for dinner...
Shit, it's Yua
and he wasn't home for breakfast either,
Brother, lets go home!
Strange, Brother isn't here...
If his bag is here, that means he should still be around.
What now?
We are going home together today!
I'm mad at him for ditching me in the morning.
Well, I'll go home by myself.
I'm not going to forgive him!
Crap, now I'm stuck here.
I better wait until Yua leaves.
I'm so sleepy...
Hmm, this voice...
Sex in the classroom!?
Somebody from class?
Please stop...
It hurts... Teacher, please be more gentle.
What are you talking about? Look at your nipples!
You are such a slut!
Teacher, down... there too!
Mi... Mika... ge?
You mean right here?
More... Lower.
Right here?
You are so wet.
Let me punish you for being so horny!
Hurry, please punish me!
Look at this, I...
Got ready!
I'm so happy, please poke me with them!
What's going on?
Why is Mikage... with that pervert?
Look at the juices flowing out.
It's great, more... more!
No, don't pull out!
No!!
Shut up, lets go!
No, Teacher!
Mikage...!
Teacher... Teacher, please!
I'm so wet...
Who... is someone there!?
Who is there!?
Who?
Me...
Akitoshi... it's Akitoshi!
Akitoshi, did you watch? Did you look at me?
Let's do it. I'm so wet, I need it now!
Wait up, Mikage...
Please say yes, I will do anything.
Hold up, Mikage!
No!
Please Akitoshi, don't make me loose my mind.
What has happen to you, I'm so lost.
Please do me, Akitoshi.
I can't hold it... so please... please, Akitoshi!
If I don't have sex, my urges go wild.
If I am like this during the day I won't
be able to come to school anymore.
So please...
Akitoshi, you're getting bigger.
Mi... Mikage...
Mikage... are you sure?
Yes, please... I can't hold out much longer...
Hey, can I stick it in?
It's inside...
So big.
It's hitting deep in me... do you like it?
Feels good... It feels good.
Mikage, you're warm inside and it's gripping my thing.
I'm so happy, I feel good too!
Wow, it's getting bigger!
Akitoshi, your penis is making me feel good!
Mikage!
Please, do me as you wish!
Mikage, it feels really good!
More, more, give me more!
Push it in me deeper!
Stick it in my butt, too!
Use that vibrator!
Are you sure?
Please, please make me cum!
Please have me as you wish, Akitoshi!
I won't remember a thing anyway.
Please!!
Here I go.
Yes!! Both my holes are filled!
More, give me more!
It's wonderful, hitting my g-spot!
I'm going to cum...
Me... too!
Please, cum with me!
I'm cumming!
Cum... please cum inside me, Akitoshi!
Mikage!!
Cumming... cumming... I'm cumming!!
Thank you...
I should be fine for a while...
Mikage...
Mr. Okajima!
I told you to come to my office, yesterday!
Why didn't you come!?
Yes!
Give me your reason!
Well, I fell asleep and...
What? I can't hear you!
Yes...
Never mind, but you better come today. Understood?
Alright, lets start class.
Page 78, Ms. Takeuchi, please read.
Yes.
The bells of...
That day, Ai came to school.
Although she was ignoring me, I was
afraid to look straight into her face.
However, I found myself attracted to her.
Ai, about the day before yesterday...
You remember!?
Yeah, for the most part...
So your memories aren't erased...
There are people like you at times.
Huh?
You remember I told you not to get near me?
Yeah...
Then please!
Why though, I don't understand?
You don't need too.
Please don't... it's for your own good.
But...
Want to die? I told you there is no second.
What's up?
I remember I had to do something important.
But you have to go to her office today.
Sorry, please cover for me.
Wait up!
I don't like Teacher Harumi either!
I wonder where she went.
Don't tell me...
She is here.
So she can smile.
This one again?
So, she likes this doll...
Damn, I lost her.
W, what!?
What are you doing!?
I was looking for you and... uh...
Why do you come near me?
Didn't you understand my warning?
If you get in my way, I will kill you.
I get it...
She got away...
Got away?
Leave this place.
Alright, I will, but here...
What?
Well, you were always looking at it... here.
W, why...?
Well, you did save me last time...
It a... well... a token of appreciation.
I don't want it!
I have no use for it!
Why, you were always looking at it?
Why do you do this!?
Because, I really like... err...
What do you mean...
Well, it's hard to explain, but...
My dad told me that a guy would
do anything for the girl he likes.
A girl?
I'm a warrior!
Are you here to mock me!?
Go home, now!
Awaken!
Wild Fangs, cometh!
Dragon Wings, cometh!
Where am I?
Where? Where are you at?!?
I don't know.
Inside me...!?
Mr. Okajima!
I told you to come to my office!!
Teacher Harumi!? Why?
My body...
Why?
Mr. Okajima, I told you to come to my office, today!
Te, Teacher Harumi!
Why you...?
Oh my, Ms. Kagano too?
What strange clothes... you are cute.
I'll be sure to take care of you.
What is happening!?
What's wrong?
You, don't move!
If you try to move, I can't move!
Easier said than done!
No, stop!
Such luscious lips.
I can't move...
My body is confused because you're trying to move.
It' so delicious... let me taste inside your stomach.
Lets see how this tastes.
No... my powers...
Please, no!
So pink and delicious.
Amazing, you're already so wet right here.
Your lips are warm against my fingers.
Does it feel good?
You can moan louder.
You are so cute, let me love you more.
Here I go...!
Your inside feels good.
Ai... Ai!!
Now make me feel good.
C'mon, do it.
That's right, deeper!
I'll stick one in your butt too.
Ai!
Ai, no! Hang in there!!
Ai!!
Ai!!!
Move... move... move!!
My body, please move!
Ai!
You, don't try to move. Let me take care of the rest.
Alright.
You won't get away!
Hold it, girlie!
That should be the end of the Yuragi.
Yuragi...?
My job here is done.
Are you going?
Ai, you...
Forget me.
For your own good.
But!
This has no effect on you...
I'll... take this...
Ai...
Ai was no where to be found the next day.
No one remembers her.
But the empty seat next to the window
Is the proof she did exist.
Yua Attack!!
Good to go!
How dare you when I'm thinking seriously!
What, what? About what?
None of your business!
Come on, tell me!
Don't pull on me.
The normal days are back.
I felt relieved, but depressed at the same time.
Ai Kagano came for a short time and left without a trace.
Disappeared with my heart...