Looks like you haven't had enough.
Don't worry, the real fun is just about to start.
Kagano Ai, I've always wanted to...
make you my personal toy!
You can no longer escape from my clutch.
But don't worry, I'll make sure you'll die in pleasure!
C'mon, have some fun.
How's it, Ai-kun?
How does it feel to be violated in every single hole while being stirred deep inside your body!?
See this big thing inside of you?
Well, it's inside your womb!
I'll make sure to fill you everywhere!
You feel it? You feel it inside your ass?
Doesn't it feel good to be violated by my tentacles while you're bound, Ai-kun?
Almost, Ai-kun.
See, it went through your ass to your mouth!
Looks like there's no spot on you that is left untouched!
If you want, I can make you my personal pet!
Did you just have an orgasm, Ai-kun?
She's unconscious... oh well.
Akitoshi, time to wake up.
You awake, Akitoshi?
Touru, what did you do to Ai!?
I didn't do anything but give her the time of her life.
She's unconscious because of it, though...
Touru!?
It was a great show.
But I want to share this with someone else.
That's why I woke you.
What!?
You should thank me, it's a one of a kind show!
Touru!
I think you'll thank me.
I bet you never seen anyone die.
Stop it, please stop!!
Just sit back and relax, and enjoy the show.
What do you think is going to happen?
The death of the magical warrior!
Stop Touru! If you kill Ai, I will never forgive you!
That's just what I want!
Hatred, Jealousy, Lust... these are the sources of our power!
That's right, your negative energy is flowing in me.
Hate me, put your anger on me so I can be more powerful!
What!?
Ai!
Finally awake.
You're still tight after all that!
Well that bar is big.
But don't worry, I'll make it fit.
Ai!
So, how does it feel to be penetrated by this big thing?
Doesn't the thickness feel good?
Stop...
Stop! If you don't stop, Touru...
That's it, throw your anger at me!
No!
Delicious, it's delicious!
Ai, Ai, Ai!
Already finished?
I was hoping to have more fun.
Stop it, Touru!
If you don't shut up, I'll make you shut up.
Touru... you...
That's right, I'm no longer human.
For revenge...
I won't go easy on you either, Akitoshi.
Won't forgive...
Ai?
So, you're still alive.
I won't forgive you!
I'll finish you off then.
Shit!
Take this!
Ai!
Shit!
Stop, please stop, Ai!
Ai!
I'll get you next time!
She is no different from us!
Yes, she fell asleep while we were studying.
Yes, first thing tomorrow morning. OK... Sorry.
I had to call Yua and Chie-chan's home...
I couldn't let them go home like that.
Oh, are you alright?
Thank you.
I'm not good at it, but... I casted a heal spell on myself.
Sorry about the clothes.
It's fine.
But I'm glad, I thought I would never see you again...
I regretted that day.
I regretted that I didn't tell you this.
I...
Yuragis were never this strong.
They were weak creatures feeding off emotions.
But we found out that it was more than that...
Look at you!
You set a trap, but it backfired.
Shut up, who knew she had such powers hidden!
I will kill her next time!
You talk, but look at you now.
This body...
It'll heal in 2-3 days.
You are... Yabe Natsumi-kun from class 1-3.
The same thing was supposed to happen to Kagano Ai!
You're next.
You are going to become my mother.
I'm going inside you to be re-born.
You're hurting me!
C'mon, don't cry just yet.
I'll be full grown when I'm out.
No, stop!
This is great, it'll only take me a day!
In search for more energy, the Yuragis began to parasite on humans and began controlling them.
Touru as well?
Correct, and there's also a bait to lure other humans...
Don't tell me, Miyahiro?
Miyahiro Mikage... she is the bait to lure others.
Miyahiro...
And sometimes... their ambitions lead to death.
Ai, who are you?
I can't tell you.
But I've been fighting for a long time.
Ever since civilization...
Are you going to disappear again?
Yes, when this is over... but it doesn't look so easy this time.
It seems that they are planning something.
I have a feeling that there's a greater Yuragi hiding somewhere.
Somewhere...
We have to find him and find out what he's up to.
Or else, this will never end...
They're here!
Ai!
They're gone!
They took them.
Huh, why them?
It's from Miyahiro...
Yes?
Miyahiro?
Okajima-kun, I'm at school right now.
Why at this time?
Naito-sensei told me to come here.
He's harassing you again?
Not yet.
I'm at the grounds.
On top of the stand.
I've been thinking...
During morning calls.
I get called to the front and Naito-sensei orders me...
To take off my clothes and masturbate in front of everyone.
Miyahiro, what are you talking about?
I don't feel comfortable but I slowly take off my clothes.
Then everyone looks at me as I spread my legs open.
Then they spread my pink and look inside me.
Then I start to masturbate and my clit begins to throb.
It feels good... see look at this juice.
You listening, Okajima-kun?
Miyahiro, what are you...
Then one by one, they greet me.
They all greet me with their hard cocks in my pussy.
But they are too quick...
They all cum under 10 seconds.
But they come one after another.
I start to feel good, but...
There's a lot of boys and one hole isn't enough.
I then use both hands.
Honestly, I'm happy about it.
Then I start to lick cause I want more.
Soon my ass gets filled.
All my holes are filled!
It hurts, but it feels good!
Cuming, cuming, cumiiiiing!
Miyahiro?
I came...
Miyahiro...
Okajima-kun, looks like Yua-chan and Chie-chan are here, too.
I saw them go inside the school.
Yua and Chie-chan?
Okajima-kun, you're coming right?
I'll be at the dean's office.
Miyahiro, wait!
She hung up...
It's a trap.
A trap?
They don't want us to rest.
Does that mean the boss is at school?
I don't know, but...
We have to go.
But you're still wounded...
I'll go myself and bring them back.
You think they'll let you out alive?
But this trap is to get you, Ai.
There is one way for me to sneak in unnoticed.
But I would need your help.
I would do anything to save those three!
Take off your clothes.
Always keep calm and believe in me, OK?
Relax and don't think...
Imagine yourself in space.
You are an egg, a big white egg.
I am inside of that.
You inside me...
Concentrate, you and I are one.
We are one...
One...
What's this strange feeling... I'm healing?
Ai, you sure they won't find out?
Nobody will if I hide my presence...
They won't find me inside you.
The dean's office.
There's lights, but no one is inside.
Be careful.
There's a stair under the desk.
Looks like they're expecting us.
What now?
Lets go.
Lets walk into their trap.
Hey, the path continues.
They'll be surprised when they see you alone, that's what we want.
This place looks very old.
Looks like they've been here for a while.
What the...?
What is this?
Looks like the Yuragis are feeding off of them.
Man...
Give us... come... please...
Stay calm.
No, calm down!
You alright?
What is this place?
Looks like it's their nest.
You're late, Okajima.
Harumi-sensei?
You're... alone.
Where is Kagano Ai?
I'm by myself.
Damn, only the food came.
Okajima-kun.
You came.
I'm so happy... let's do it, let's feel good together.
Miyahiro?
No need to run, Okajima.
Harumi-sensei?
Listen to Miyahiro, let's have fun until Kagano comes.
Let's do it a lot, Okajima-kun.
Ai!
Do what they say, they're just puppets.
Hold it until the boss arrives.
Beautiful, it's beautiful, Okajima-kun. It's so big!
Delicious, yours tastes the best...
Stop it, Miyahiro.
Don't forget about this!
C'mon, lick my important spot.
Ai!
Not yet, still hold!
If you don't listen, I'll rip this!
I will, I will!
Let me lick it!
Okajima-kun, me too...
So thick...
Ai, I...
Hold it... No, I can feel it, too...
It's rubbing my clitoris... This is how it feels like for a man?
Ai?
Endure it! I'll do my best, too.
Ai!
Yes! Okajima-kun!
Give it to me!
Okajima, push in harder!
Oh no, I'm cuming, cuming, cuming!
Wonderful!
Harumi-sensei, why?
Why?
Because it feels good, what else.
And that's it?
I'll make you feel good too.
I can't, I'm going to cum!
Please stop this!
Why don't you just give up, Okajima.
Yua!
Chie-chan?
Sensei!
Onii-chan...
Looks like he's the one.
Ai!