Maids in Dream
Episode 2: Maids In The Scene
Good morning, master!
Master, you're still in bed again!
You have to get up.
It's time for us to pick herbs.
Let's go pick herbs, master.
Get up, okay?
Please let me sleep in.
Come on!
I shouldn't...
if I rush him like yesterday...
Please don't! Don't!
Come on!
It's not a good time.
It is!
What's that supposed to mean?
His thing was really big.
My jaw was very tired afterwards.
Master, this position is embarrassing!
Shut up!
You do what your master tells you.
Did I really do that to the girls?
Am I punishing them every time
they make some mistake?
No, that's just a dream.
It can't be real. But, it is.
I'm not in a normal world.
Anything can happen here.
I unconsciously did that dirty thing
to the girls which I wouldn't...
normally do, although, in secret...
I wanted to do I did
that horrible thing to them.
What should I do?
Master, good morning.
Lovely morning, isn't it, master?
Morning.
As soon as breakfast is ready,
we'll call you.
So, please wait.
Yeah.
Please don't make any mistakes.
It's not good... lt's suffocating.
Master, good morning.
- Oopsie daisy.
- Watch out!
Don't worry.
I carry this many every day.
I'm ready now.
Master, please try this tea
I made for you.
Did you taste it first?
I'm glad I didn't drink it.
I'm glad it didn't fall on you, Master.
That would have been terrible.
Tsubaki, you'd better practice
when no one's around.
Yes, master.
Will you find this book for me?
Yes!
Let me see.
This is the one. Thanks.
You girls, now, listen up:
Is it going to be like this every day?
It's tough. It'll drive me crazy.
No, I can't sleep!
Maybe taking a hot bath will help.
Master!
Master! Master, are you okay?
Are you hurt? Master?
Did you fall? Answer me, please!
Does it hurt?
As you can see,
I'm perfectly okay, really.
Are you sure you're okay?
It's just a small bump
on the back of my head.
A bump's nothing.
Like a goblin in the story,
I can tear it off if you want.
Just say the word.
I think I can see something
like horns on your head, Ichigo.
Is that true?
This isn't a laughing matter!
Our master's head got injured.
We must monitor him
for a while to make sure he's okay.
Got it, girls?
What's the matter, Karin?
Why are you acting so uptight?
I'm not acting uptight at all.
Sakura, what happened?
I forgot to place the plate
notifying you that I was bathing...
and I caused your injury.
I'm so sorry.
That's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It's not a big deal.
These things happen.
Thank you.
Master, you're so soft-hearted.
Sakura, you know what this is about?
Yes.
Well.
What a problematic maid you are.
It's about time you get punished.
Listen, my orders are absolute.
You must obey no matter what.
All right?
Yes, Master, I'll do anything you tell me to.
Good. Then take off your panties.
Yes, master.
Now, wash me clean.
Touch it gently.
If you hurt me,
you'll be punished more.
Yes. I understand.
Open up your legs wider,
so that your master can see you better.
- Yes, master.
- Good. That's right.
What a nice color you've got!
Does this feel good?
Yes. It makes me feel strange.
Master, you're getting quite hard.
I can see inside you clearly.
You'll see, later on,
I'll let mine enjoy yours.
It feels good.
It's making me feel so strange.
Hurry up.
Are you aware of the gravity
of the mistake you've made?
Yes, master. But what am I
supposed to do?
I don't know.
This time, you're to clean mine
with your mouth.
Put it in your mouth!
Start licking gently.
- Is this the way?
- All right. Good!
It's good.
Do it faster! Faster.
Don't spit it out. Drink it all.
- It feels strange. It feels restless.
- Feels good?
I don't know. But you might be right.
Are you a slut?
Finding my punishment enjoyable?
It feels good!
It feels as if my body's melting.
It feels so good.
That's incredible, more please!
Harder, master. Please harder!
It feels good!
More! More!
It's not working as a punishment!
All right, let me get you
more excited, then.
Not there.
Shut up! Do you mean to disobey
your master?
No, I didn't mean that.
Looks like it'll work.
Now, I'll insert a lot thicker
and hotter one inside, all right?
No, it hurts.
Of course it does.
This is your punishment, after all.
It hurts! No!
It's tight!
It feels strange.
Some strange sensation is bursting out
from deep within me.
What do I do?
Good! Incredibly good... it's fabulous!
My behind is coming.
Yes!
Sakura, I'm coming.
Master, please come.
I think I'm coming too!
Yes!
Master, what's wrong?
It's already lunch time.
Aren't you hungry?
I don't want to eat.
You go ahead without me.
Are you feeling well?
If not, you should take some medicine.
Please, just leave me alone.
I don't want to see anyone today.
That's not good.
Shutting yourself up in your room
all day long will make you sick.
I'm begging you.
Please leave me alone!
What am I supposed to do?
If I don't want to witness their mistakes,
I can't even walk around the house.
Hey, there's an idea.
I wonder what's wrong with our master.
Could he be homesick?
What do you think?
With his amnesia, that's impossible.
If he's not sick, could it be that
we've done something wrong?
Something's happening inside
our master's head. That's for sure.
Let's get our master to tell us the truth.
So, first of all, we must get
our master out of his room...
whatever it takes.
Do you understand?
Everyone, please enjoy the meal.
Yummy! It's so yummy.
I've never had a lunch
this yummy before.
I must say Nadeshiko, your food tastes
like the best in the world.
I wish our master could taste some.
Darn it! That looks so good.
I'm absolutely starving.
Should've eaten earlier.
Is it true, Karin? I can't believe it!
Don't say this to anyone else.
Let's keep it our secret, okay?
I certainly will keep it
our little secret...
but boy, when she does it...
she goes all the way.
She's either bold or shameless.
All it says is
is that we can never guess...
what is going on
in other people's heads.
Master's watching us.
So, there is more to the story.
Do you want to hear it?
I do! I do! Hurry up
and tell us everything.
Tell us everything.
It didn't work.
No.
All right, it's time for extreme measures.
What?
That'll be so embarrassing!
For the sake of our master...
we should all get ready right away.
Okay, girls?
How is it, Sakura?
Yes, it's fully visible.
I'm all sweaty.
What?
Hi, Tsubaki.
What? What's going on with you all?
Your panties are showing!
No don't!
Someone!
Someone help me,
please help me!
Karin, this strategy isn't working.
Let's go back.
You're right, it's not working at all,
even after we put on the miniskirts.
I can't bear it. I just don't know
what to do. Help me.
Master...
What happened between us?
I want to see her
I don't know who she is...
but I really want to see her.
Master.
I got it! It's her!
I should tell her everything!
Then I might... who's there?
- It's me, Suzuran.
- What's wrong?
What can I do for you at this hour?
I'm sorry, but there's something
that bothers me.
All right.
I had something I wanted to tell you anyway.
She looks like me?
The moment I saw you...
I had a feeling that I'd met you
somewhere before.
If I could only remember who she is.
I think I might be able to
remember who I am and go back...
where I came from.
And get rid of all this
crazy stuff in my head.
I don't know if I can be of any help,
but I'll do anything I can.
I'm at your service.
But, what happened to you today?
Everyone's worried about you.
Of course I'm sorry. Well, I...
You despise me now, don't you?
What I've done is nothing
but sexual harassment.
The punishment you gave
is what they deserved.
The fact that it manifests itself
in a sexual form only reflects...
how comfortable we feel
with you, Master.
It didn't happen just because
you're sexually frustrated.
We care about you.
This is just their punishment.
They had to go
along with it, that's all.
Let's have some tea.
And don't worry about it.
Of course, they're not making mistakes
on purpose...
but they're receiving your punishment
with pleasure.
Master, you cannot think
about this anymore.
You have to relax and enjoy.
Is that really so?
Then, you too?
I guess you're so perfect
that you probably won't...
make any mistakes.
I can't believe it.
I'm not perfect, either.
When the time comes, I'll be there
to accept my punishment.
I thought I was a horrible pervert,
sexually harassing everyone.
It was bothering me.
It's a relief to know I'm not like that.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
It tastes good.
What's the matter?
I think something like this
happened in the past.
But I can't remember!
Master, if there's anything
I can do, I will.
No matter what it is.
You can count on me.
Thank you Suzuran.
I can feel your passion, Suzuran.
It feels really good.
- Let's go to my bed.
- Okay.
You have such beautiful skin.
Suzuran, yours is a beautiful pink.
It's also a beautiful pink inside you.
It's an embarrasment. It feels so good.
It's wonderful, Master!
It's incredible. An endless stream
of your fluid is coming out!
Your body is unexpectedly sensual.
Master it's good.
Let me lick you now, master.
I can't take this anymore.
Please let me lick you.
It's good, Suzuran.
It feels incredibly good.
No, I can't take this anymore.
Please I want you!
Give it to me, give it to me!
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
It's hot! It feels like
my body's on fire, master!
I love you.
Me too, master.
It's not right He's my master.
A maid isn't permitted to love her
master as a man.
Absolutely not.
It's incredible. It's making me feel wild
I can't anymore. I'm coming!
- Me too! Ready?
- Yes.
All I could remember was
her face in tears, after all.
I can't. I'm just a maid.
I must not fall in love
with my master.
No, never!
Good morning.
Master, you're back!
Let's eat!
The soup looks delicious.
And the salad too.
I'm starving, I just can't wait to eat.
Good morning, Suzuran.
- It's a nice day today, isn't it?
- Good morning.
I bet Suzuran got our
master's problem resolved.
I'm jealous, but I know I tried.
Regardless, my affection towards
our master is stronger...
than anyone else's,
and it always will be.
Master! Let's go and pick the herbs
right after the breakfast, shall we?
That sounds great.
Now, let's enjoy a delicious breakfast
and have a great day together.
Let the feast begin!
Yes, let it begin!
Healing of our master's injured soul...
means the day of his departure
is getting close.
Until that day arrives,
it's my responsibility to serve him...
as his maid the best I can.
That's all I can do.