No!
ORIGINAL STORY BY MAID CLUB
ORIGINAL CHARACTERS
BY TSUKINAGA IGUL
What do you think you're doing?
I want this to stop. I'm working here
as a maid. I'm not here for this.
MUSIC BY YOSHI AND OTHERS
Are you going to defy your master?
A maid is supposed to do
whatever we tell them to do!
TOMOMI MIKAMI
MAID SERVICE
CHAPTER OF DESPAIR
PART I
Please... stop...
Your tits are better than I thought.
I'll be able to get good footage with these...
A camera? Why are you doing this?
Isn't this fun? Wanna watch it together later?
No!
Cut the crap!
If you don't listen, who knows
what'll happen to your ring!
My ring? Are you talking about...
I'll hold onto it as a contract between us.
B-but...! Give it back!
Whoops. No can do!
Are you going to listen, or would
you rather lose everything?
No!
Let me get a taste of your pussy.
Come on. Act like an adult for a change...
I'll do anything else.
You can't do jack shit!
No!
Move your hand!
Ow... It won't go in...
You better get wet quick if
you don't want it to hurt.
Yeah... This feels good!
What's wrong? Where'd all that energy go?
It's no fun if you're quiet.
Yeah, that's more like it.
You might not like this,
but your body can't lie.
Look at how wet you are! Moan louder
so the whole house can hear you!
Make sure you clean up the
stain on the carpet later.
You're the one who soiled it.
Was that a yes?
Or does it feel that good?
You're feeling it and you know you
like it, but this is getting boring...
I'll try it up the ass.
What are you doing?
Great asshole. It's nice and tight.
I wonder if my dick would've
gone in without your cum.
What is this? You call this
"serving your master?"
It's too late if I have to point it out.
This is weak!
How did it come to this?
I never would have dreamt
this would happen...
...when my parents were alive.
My father's sudden death... My
mother didn't want me to worry, and...
...worked hard to afford my expensive
tuition, but it killed her in the end...
My mother's death meant I
had to leave the school...
...unless I sold my mother's
ring, her keepsake.
That's when he came up to talk to me.
Momoko... I don't know what
to say about your mother...
Thanks Takaaki...
By the way, this might be rude to ask but...
...are you okay financially?
Well...
I was wondering if you want
to work as a live-in helper.
You can keep going to school. My
family will even pay for your tuition.
Wow! That's a wonderful offer, Momoko!
But I can't let you do that for me...
I don't mean to trouble you, but I'd
be happy if you came to my house.
Jeez, this is embarrassing...
I accepted his gracious offer
without even thinking about...
...the terrible consequences
that awaited me...
We cannot keep making
demands to the school.
She's so amazing.
The student government
must think responsibly...
...five, even ten years ahead for the
future students and face the reality.
She's beautiful, smart and a born leader.
Mana is so perfect in every way.
And that is why we must overcome these
hardships with a healthy mind and body.
I wonder if there's anyone
who doesn't look up to her?
Don't you agree, Momoko?
Momoko!
Why are you so spaced out?
It's nothing...
Are you exhausted from work and school?
You have to keep up the good work
if we want to graduate together.
Yeah.
Momoko.
Hang out with Yurika for a change.
Just come back before six.
Really? He said it was
okay. Let's go Momoko.
Takaaki made it a point to give
you some time off. Let's go.
Okay...
Thanks Takaaki!
You're welcome!
Are you wearing it?
Bye! Sorry to keep you.
Hey, I wonder if Takaaki has a thing for you?
He has to!
Or why would he be so kind to
you? What do you think about him?
I think he's pretty awesome.
Are you feeling alright?
I'm fine. It's nothing...
But...
You guys! Stop talking! Be quiet!
Sorry.
If I stand up, people will think I peed
in my pants. What should I do?
Please... Takaaki stop...
I wonder why the door was left open?
Mr. Okamura?
Sorry for the intrusion.
I had no idea what this room looked like...
Is that...?
A photo album...
Is this picture...
Takaaki's mother?
Who is this person...?
What are you doing?
Mr. Okamura. I... the door was open so...
I don't remember giving you
permission to enter this room.
What do you have to say
for yourself, Momoko?
I'm sorry.
Come to think of it...
Do you understand the rules of the house?
Yes... By the way about
Takaaki... I mean, Master...
Where are his parents?
Only Master Takaaki lives here.
He lives alone?
Topics such as his parents and
family are taboo in this house.
Understand? Please remember this rule.
Yes sir.
Is there a secret in this house? What is it?
I'm going to pour my cum into your mouth.
Come on. Why are you barfing it up?
Why are you doing this to me?
You piss me off, that's why.
What do you mean?
You're commuting from Takaaki's house right?
But I'm working at his house as a maid!
Shut up! Lulu and Takaaki grew up together;
she's in love with him!
Meaning, you're a nuisance!
She wants to get rid of you.
Lulu, you've got it all wrong.
I'm not in love with Takaaki...
Shut up!
What are you doing in there?
Open up! I said open this door!
Hey! I'll kick the door down!
Momoko are you okay?
Thank you so much...
That crew seems to be ruling this place.
Everyone ignores what's going
on and walks past them.
You've made enemies with them...
You only just transferred here...
I'm sorry.
It's fine. I'd rather deal
with them than stay silent.
We should get going.
Okay.
Master you called for me?
Let me introduce you. They're
my new maids, Mana and Chika.
Mana! Chika from the next classroom over.
Momoko...
Make sure you teach them
what they have to do.
Why are they here?
Miss President has a bad habit...
I just happened to catch her in the act.
A bad habit?
Miss President...
...must have been stressed out.
Everyone expects her to be perfect.
I bet you didn't even want that.
You just wanted the thrill... Right?
You promised that you'll give me the
negatives after I work for three days.
You promised me!
Sure I will.
Because I don't have
anything to hide, unlike you.
And Chika came to work because
she's in a similar position to Momoko.
She's here to save her parents'
company, so she'll be here for a while.
So that's the story.
Everyone get along, okay?
Momoko, who's going to
be my partner tonight?
Choose between the two.
Me?
Yes. I'll respect your decision.
Wait a minute! What do you mean, "partner"?
There's something I want to try.
I've always wanted to use whips and candles.
I want to try S&M.
Enough of your crap! I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
You're not here because you
need the money like they do.
A shoplifting scandal won't hurt you one bit.
Th... that's...
Momoko, who will it be? Who's
going to satisfy me tonight?
Um...
Make up your mind!
Mana...
Okay.
You're a good student but you're a woman.
I'll make sure to play with your nipples too.
Are you feeling it? Your nipples are hard.
Are you sure you're not feeling it?
Momoko... you made the right choice.
She's dripping wet.
Don't lie! You slut!
Is the vibrator not enough?
What a masochistic bitch.
Everyone's going to be surprised...
...when they find out what a pervert you are.
No, I'm not like that.
Oh, then that's it for the whips and candles.
You're going to stay here until we
have to go to school tomorrow.
N... no.
Which one will it be? You want it or not?
Hurt me more... Make it hurt.
Then satisfy me first!
Nice view. You want to become a politician?
A beautiful politician and her past scandals.
Shoplifting and S&M. This will pay so well.
What? That's not what you promised!
If you do as I say, then that won't happen.
It's not like I need the money.
I'd like someone like you
to run our government.
She's really enjoying it.
The Mana we knew was an act.
That's the real Mana that no one knew!
Are you worried?
Yeah.
But we have no choice.
We just have to persevere.
Chika, are you still a virgin?
I see... But it'll be okay.
Look at me. I'm doing fine.
I wonder how long we have to live like this?
Help!
Chika?
I'm having trouble falling asleep.
I'm going to do a little exercise.
Please leave her alone until she
gets used to this place. Please.
Are you trying to order me around?
Shut up and stay there or
else you'll be penniless!
Chika. You too.
It's a lot prettier than I thought.
No...
No? I'll be nice.
Nice flavor. It's a virgin's flavor.
You didn't want it, but you're dripping wet.
Good girl. Let me give you a reward.
I knew you were a virgin.
It'll be a good memory. Your first
fuck was with a gigantic vibrator.
It hurts... Stop!
Nice view...
Women have breasts so
that men can suck on 'em!
Stop...
The more you resist, the
more it turns me on. Yeah...
You're turning me on. Look at my cock.
If you want to look away, fine.
All I need are your big tits.
They're great. Just as I thought...
Here's a facial mask for you.
It suits you Chika. You'll have smooth skin.
The first time is the most important session.
I have to make sure you know your place.
Suck it. Aren't you gonna
listen to me? I said suck it!
Yes, just like that. You're pretty
good. Are you sure you're a virgin?
Are you feeling it? What a slut. Do
two vibrators make you that happy?
I feel so strange...
Jeez! You pissed! Do
something about the smell!
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Okay, lick it clean. You're the
one who pissed everywhere.
Then I'll forgive you.
But...
This is your punishment.
How long will we have to live like this?
Until graduation? Until I get my ring back?
It's too late after I say it!
Momoko, are you okay?
Are you going to defy your master?
Maids are supposed to
do whatever they're told!
You piss me off, that's why.
I'd rather deal with them than stay silent.
I don't mean to trouble you, but I'd
be happy if you came to my house.
Jeez, this is embarrassing...
Is obeying his orders the only way I can live?
Please tell me. Mother!
TO BE CONTINUED