Maids in Dream
Episode One:
Welcome Master
I'm so glad.
I'm really happy.
Who are you?
I'm Sazuron,
a servant of this house.
Glad to be of service to you.
How are you feeling, Master?
Where am I?
Master, are you all right?
We were so worried.
That Master you're addressing, is it me?
Yes!
So, if you need anything
or want to eat something...
please let me know.
I'll be happy to bring you...
anything you ask me to.
Same here.
Please ask me anything,
and I'll do my best to accommodate.
Me too! In the name of my sword!
Master, I see that you're awake.
- How do you do, I'm...
- It's not good.
You're supposed to be present
when our new Master wakes up.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes, I understand.
I was worried about
our Master's health...
and that's why I was making
a special drink for him.
A drink?
How did you know I was thirsty?
Master!
- Karin!
- What?
Did you taste the drink yourself?
Why? I'm healthy,
so I don't need to drink it myself.
I must stop him right away.
What's wrong with her?
Master!
What do we do?
Nadeshiko, fill up the kettle with water!
Ichigo, get the orange juice from the fridge!
Sakura, get the ice!
Tsubaki, fetch the towel!
Yes!
We'll help stop the pain right away.
What's wrong?
Is that because of...
Yes, that's right.
Don't they say,
good medicine tastes bitter?
I didn't say that the drink
was delicious, did I?
It's not my fault.
Master should've tested it
before he drank it.
And, it's your fault for not stopping him!
I shouldn't take any of the blame.
I understand!
I understand,
but can't you do something about it?
Master, you'll be okay.
Good. He's better now.
I finally feel better.
I'm glad, master.
- You might be glad, but...
- What's the matter, Master?
I don't remember
anything about myself.
I think it's amnesia.
That might be it.
I guess your name is Akio.
Before you arrived...
I asked my crystal ball
who'd be our next Master.
It said it was Akio.
Reading your crystal ball again?
We can't really count on
that being his name then.
Nadeshiko, your fortune telling
has never proved to be true.
You're right, but...
That's fine. Akio's going to be fine now.
I believe you've temporarily
lost your memory.
I'm sure you'll gradually
remember everything, Master.
Somehow, I know this isn't the place.
Please tell me, what is this
place I'm at, anyway?
I'm really confused about everything.
I suppose you want to know, Master...
the geological location of this place.
Unfortunately, we don't have
the answer for you.
This place is everywhere
and nowhere at the same time.
That's all we can tell you.
A parallel world,
what does that mean?
You can analyze it
however way you want.
But, everyone who comes here has a reason.
And our existence does, too.
As soon as all your unresolved,
personal problems are fixed...
you can go back to your own world.
To assist you with that process,
we maids are here for you.
Even if it kills me, I'll help you, Master,
to go back to your own world.
I promise.
Why don't you take your time
and think about it, Master.
That's how I began to live
in this house with the strange maids.
A dream. I wonder who it was.
- Come in.
- Good morning!
Master, I brought you a perfect
blend of herbal tea to wake you up.
This one is made from the freshest herbs,
soaked in cold water from the well...
and steeped under the morning sun.
Today, I mixed chamomile,
lemon balm, spearmint and rose.
Please have some.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
You don't need to worry, Master.
It's not like the one from yesterday.
I'm pretty good with herbs, you know.
Delicious!
I'm so glad you like it.
More, please.
There's this spot behind the woods where
you can find a lot of fresh herbs.
Would you like to come
with me to pick some before breakfast?
It's my secret spot
which no one else knows about.
Master, you're special, so I'll show you.
We can have a tea
with the fresh herbs we pick.
Since that morning,
it became my daily routine...
to go out and pick the herbs
with Karin every morning.
It was refreshing and a lot of fun.
For me, without my memory...
this has become a very special time.
Fully relaxing.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing. I'm fine.
Yes!
Why don't you eat with me?
We're just your maids, Master.
We have ours in a separate room,
aft you're done with your dinner.
That's right.
So, you're just going to watch
me eat like that?
Does that bother you?
It would be really nice
if you'd sit down and eat with me.
It would make it more fun for all of us.
You've got to be kidding.
We can eat with you?
Please don't joke like that.
But, we're meant to serve you, Master.
How could we dare eat with you?
Nadeshiko, you're so uptight.
Our Master's telling us to do it.
Aren't we supposed to obey
our Master's orders no matter what?
Right, Suzuran?
Yes, that's true.
I suppose we can share
the dinner table with him.
All right!
Thanks, Suzuran.
She's really sensitive to my needs.
Nadeshiko, fill up the kettle with water!
Ichigo, get the orange juice from the fridge!
Sakura, get the ice!
Tsubaki, fetch the towel!
Suzuran, could she
be in love with our master?
Why do I care about that?
It doesn't matter.
I shouldn't care about the feelings of others.
- You okay?
- Yes.
Watch your step.
Master! This is where I come in handy!
The power of the sword!
That was very good.
How could you,
after I told you to watch your step.
And Tsubaki, there was
no need for the sword.
I'm sorry.
That was bad, I know.
You know the punishment.
Yes.
No need to punish them.
These two meant well.
If we start punishing
for small mistakes like that...
They'll be no end.
Master?
The case is closed.
Let me go and continue with my book.
You two, you know why you're here.
Yes Master.
Then hurry up and come over here.
Please punish us for our mistake today.
We're ready to accept
the consequences of our actions.
You two, I expect you to obey
the words of your Master.
Yes.
Without reservation.
It feels so good!
- Feels so good!
- It's fantastic.
It's a punishment.
I made a yummy-looking cake.
Master please. Please punish me more!
Are you ready?
I can't take it!
Insert your stiff part into me!
- Me too!
- All right, I will.
Master, you're so incredible!
I can't take it anymore.
Not yet. You must come when I do.
I'm coming!
Don't even imagine that
your punishment is over.
I just got going.
Understood.
What was that? Was it a dream?
Good morning.
Good morning, Master.
Master, you're up early this morning.
I hope you slept well.
Yeah.
Is anything the matter?
No, nothing.
Master, good morning.
What a nice morning it is.
Don't you think so?
- I think it is.
- Yes, indeed.
That was a dream after all.
But I wonder when I'll get my memory back.
I don't remember a thing
about the world I've come from.
But I want to return anyway.
I think it'll be better if I do.
This is a very comfortable
place to live in, but...
All I remember is that girl.
She's probably someone
I cared about before I came here.
Damn it!
Can't sleep now after
thinking about it so intensely.
Master. He's late.
What's wrong, Karin?
It's nothing. Let me try this.
Karin?
As I thought, you're still in bed!
Master, please get up!
It's time for us to go
and pick some herbs.
Please let me sleep in.
No, you shouldn't.
It's not good to sleep in.
Keeping the regular routine
is good for your health!
Let me, just ten minutes!
Or five.
Come on, let's go.
You've promised that you'd go
and pick herbs with me every morning.
Even though you're our Master,
you can't break a promise.
If you want, I'll resort to force!
Please don't, don't!
- It's not a good time.
- It is!
That's why I told you not to.
Karin, you're rather quiet this morning.
- Is there something wrong?
- Nothing.
To think of it, you didn't go
to pick herbs with our Master.
Really? Karin, did you get into
a fight with our Master or something?
Please tell me everything.
No, we didn't get into a fight.
She's right. We really didn't.
How dare you embarrass me.
Didn't I tell you not to do that?
I'm sorry. I just...
I didn't expect that you would...
I'm sick of your excuses.
You've made a big mistake.
One that's going to be
very hard for me to forget.
As your Master,
I must punish you now.
Understand?
Yes.
Then, suck my dick. All right?
I can't believe you'd leave my dick
alone after seeing how excited it is.
But, it was unexpected.
Don't bite with your teeth!
I'm sorry.
It's good.
Master's penis is incredible.
It's getting so big and hard.
I'm coming.
Master, what are you doing?
Here, touch me.
Incredible! It's already hard again.
It feels good. Master, please punish me.
Please, more, punish me!
Master, you're touching me,
very deep inside me!
The deepest part of me!
It feels it feels incredibly good.
Master!
It's numbing me, it feels like...
as if I'm melting from the inside,
it feels so good!
Master, this position is embarrassing!
- I can't...
- Shut up!
You'll do what your Master tells you.
It's good.
It's good! It's so good!
I'm sorry, it's so good!
It's incredible!
Not yet. If you thought your punishment
ends so quickly, you're mistaken.
No, I'm dying!
I can't take it anymore!
I can't, anymore.
Now, it's time to lick it clean.
Yes.
All right, I'll do you the favor as well.
Let me clean you up.
It's time to resume the punishment.
Master, it feels good!
It feels good master!
Don't stop!
Another weird dream again.
It feels strangely real,
and I am exhausted by it, too.
It's so good.
I've got to sleep some more.
Master's late again.
Good morning, Master.
You're still in bed again!
Master, please get up.
It's time for our daily routine
to pick the herbs.
You have to get up now.
Let me sleep in.
I'll have to wake him up. Master!
I shouldn't do this in such a rush.
If I force him like I did yesterday,
I'll get punished again.
What's that supposed to mean?
His thing was really big.
My jaw was very tired afterwards.
Did I really do that to the girls?
Am I punishing them every time
they make some mistake?
No, that's a dream. It can't be real.
But, it is real.
I'm not in a normal world.
Anything can happen here.
I unconsciously did that dirty thing
to the girls which I wouldn't normally do.
Although, in secret, I wanted to.
I did that horrible thing to them.
What should I do?
If this is left alone...
every time I witness them
making a mistake...
my true desires will take hold of me,
and I'll end up forcing them to have sex.
What should I do? What should I do?