What is this?
It feels like my breasts are filled.
It's painful...
Let go of me!
Let go! Let go of me!
Just because you said ''let go''
doesn't mean the worm will.
Rococo, why you...
D-don't touch!
Your breasts... Doesn't it feel good?
N-no.
You can't lie to me.
Your breasts are filled
and are sensitive now.
H-how do you know?
N-not there!
It starts feeling good, so don't!
Oh, so Jiburiru is turned on
by her nipples, huh?
No, it's not like that!
Why you are so stubborn?
For you being like that...
...here!
My breasts should be hurting...
But why? Why does it feel so good?
I-if you suck on it that hard...
Worm, suck on it harder and harder!
It's coming. It's gonna come...
N-no, it's going to come out!
It's coming out!
It's coming out... W-why?
Milk is coming out...
I used a trick on your meal.
It's the famous milk tank,
known all over.
The best demon world beef for you!
Next, I will put this in you.
N-no!
It's in there.
The worm is hitting my uterus!
Don't play with my nipples!
It's gonna come out again!
The milk is gonna come out!
Oh, you know it feels good
when the milk comes out.
It keeps on coming, coming in, a lot...
It's full inside!
I-it feels so good...
N-Naoto, I can't...
I-I'm gonna come!
My breasts feel good...
What an angel you are!
Come on! Come as you wish!
You huge pervert!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna...
I'm coming!
It's coming out again...
The milk is spewing out...
It looks like
everything is going smoothly.
It's you, Misty May.
If we stay at this pace and
release the sexual energy out...
...the demon power inside Jiburiru
will wake up in no time.
Then the holy battle angel
will become a demon angel.
By the way, did you find out
where that girI is?
Of course. I was just
thinking of going to say hello.
Okay.
It's better to have no nuisances around.
Jiburiru
Second Coming
Innocence! Distressed Love
What's going on? Hikari...
You're in a good mood.
Because I became a fine woman.
And my first time was
with Brother, so...
I'm happy.
Then tonight we'll celebrate
by cooking rice with red beans.
Yeah!
Come on, you guys...
To tell the truth,
it's stinging a little bit still.
Brother, please take care of it for me.
Really? It was that rough?
If his girlfriend Rika finds out,
it would be bad.
S-stupid!
We had to do that because
we need to rescue Rika.
It's not because of
some ulterior motive...
What's wrong, Hikari?
W-what do you mean by
Rika being your girlfriend?
What?
Hikari, I didn't tell you?
Rika and I have been dating
since summer vacation.
I-I never heard about that!
I heard that you and Rika were
having sex, but I thought...
...that was for the
purpose of gaining amore!
I didn't hear that
you two were a couple!
W-why are you getting mad?
Because I...
I...
Hikari?
I'm done.
I'm going to head to school now.
Question 3.
What is it that crawls...
...on 4 legs in the morning...
...on 2 legs at noon...
...and on 3 legs in the evening?
Do you understand?
I will repeat it again.
From: Hikari
Sub: Lunch
Let's eat lunch on the rooftop.
Thank you for the food.
You are welcome.
Hey, Hikari...
It's about this morning...
Huh?
Oh, I'm fine. I'm not worried about it.
O-okay.
I just felt that you were getting
further away from me, so...
...I was getting a little sad.
By the way, Brother...
To gather amore and
to learn secret techniques...
...we need to do perverted stuff
at school, right?
Yeah, that's true, but...
Why the heck did Loveriel tell
those things to Hikari too?
So... So...
H-Hikari?
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Hey, it's okay, right, Brother?
Hikari, you're okay with it?
In a place like this...
Yeah.
If it's with you, I'm fine doing
a lot of perverted things.
Wow, it's hot already.
And it's really hard too.
How is it, Brother?
I-it's so good, Hikari.
Really?
Wow, it just keeps on getting bigger.
Huh?
Brother, something came out of the tip.
That's called Cowper's fluid, and
it comes out when it feels good.
So, Brother, you are
feeling good with me?
I'm happy.
Then how would this be?
Hikari, what are you doing?
With my underwear
that I just took off...
If I do this with it...
Wow, it's lukewarm.
Heave-ho,
heave-ho, heave-ho...
Brother, does my underwear feel good?
Yeah, if I think that it was
just covering your pussy...
...it excites me so much.
Gosh, Brother.
Brother, are you about to come?
Yeah, it's gonna come out...
My semen is about to come out, Hikari!
You can. Just come
right on to my underwear.
Here I go, Hikari!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Wow, Brother, you came a lot.
Yeah, it felt really good...
your hand and your underwear.
I'm glad.
Hey, it's a flood inside you, Hikari.
Brother's fingers are moving inside me.
It's squeezing so tight.
You saw my ejaculation
and got really excited, huh?
No!
I'm not that much of a perv!
Don't rub so hard...
You can't rub inside!
Let's stop teasing you
with my fingers about here.
Okay, here I go.
Yeah...
Please come, Brother.
I-it's coming in!
Brother is...
My pussy and my breasts...
If you do something like that...
...I'm gonna come a lot!
Inside my dirty pussy...
...Brother's big fat one is rioting!
I... I can't...
I-it's fine.
Please, just like this, Brother.
Just like this and inside me!
Come... Inside me...
In my pussy, pour all your semen!
Come!
Hikari!
It's still coming out...
Warm...
Brother's is so warm...
I'm sorry, Hikari.
I came inside you again.
It's okay.
'Cause it feels good
when you come inside me, right?
Um, ah... yeah.
Brother, you perv.
General Hospital
So, Brother...
This is the hospital that your friend
named Meimi is hospitalized in?
Yeah, according to Loveriel's story...
...she was found unconscious in
the park and was brought here.
Miss Meimi Otonashi
Ah, it's right here.
We're coming in.
Otonashi, we came to visit you.
Is she asleep?
This is... What can I say... well...
S-so big...
What? Brother, you can't look!
Is it already time for the check up?
My bad. Did I wake you up?
Huh?
Naoto!
Well, we came to visit you...
I-I'm sorry I look like this...
What?
Um, well...
As usual... It's big.
In any case, I'm glad you look fine.
Yeah, thank you for
being worried about me.
Um... she is...
Ah, this is Hikari, and
she's my sister-in-law...
What?
Ouch!
Are you okay, Hikari?
Yeah, I just cut my finger a little.
It's nothing serious.
Nothing serious...
You are such a klutz, Hikari.
Hold on, Hikari.
There should be a bandage
in that drawer over there.
Otonashi!
N-Naoto.
You are a patient,
so please take it easy.
I-I'm sorry...
What's wrong, Hikari?
You've been acting weird.
After all, my breasts
aren't as big as Meimi's!
What are you getting mad about?
Brother! Hikari!
Loveriel?
Brother, Hikari! It's awful!
Awful, mean trouble! It's trouble!
Why are you coming out of a garbage
can?
Stop doing disgusting things!
Forget about that! There's trouble!
What happened all of a sudden?
I was informed by the
Heaven Information Bureau, and...
...apparently Misty May
is going after Meimi!
What?
Otonashi!
Naoto...
Well, well, seems as
you were a little too late.
Naoto Jinno and Lolita angel.
Misty May, you...
If you don't rescue her soon,
Meimi Otonashi is going to die.
Hang in there, Otonashi!
We'll save you!
Hikari, are you ready?
Y-yeah.
Okay, here I go!
Hikari!
Angel Amore!
Let me explain!
Hikari Jinno uses amore power to...
...transform into the
holy battie angel Jiburiru Aries.
The sexual act with
her beloved brother...
The happiness and
the guilt's contradiction is...
...the source of her power!
Clean, positive, and beautiful...
You lay a nurse down and
give her an erotic shot!
I won't forgive those perverse crimes!
Devil Angel Jiburiru Aries, newly born!
What?
No! What is this?
Do something, you slowpoke!
No!
It's winding up, and it's disgusting!
Don't touch my breasts!
What happened?
Are you turned on by the
tentacles touching your breasts?
I never thought they would
be making a new Jiburiru.
But after all,
they are lascivious angels.
Look! Look! The worms are
going after your private parts.
Ah, no! No!
Not there!
Stop it!
My pussy...
And don't rub my clitoris!
You can't suck on my breasts either!
Oh? Was it the worms rubbing
your pussy that totally soaked you?
N-no, it didn't!
This juice is the
tentacles' sticky substance!
Ha, say what, you thing?
Worm, make it more rough!
If you move that roughly,
it's going to come out.
I'm going to pee!
No, it's going to come out...
It's going to come out!
Everyone's watching and...
...I wet my pants.
My gosh, how could you wet
your pants at a sacred hospital?
I'm sorry...
It's okay, Hikari!
In my view, wetting your pants is okay!
That's 'cause you are
just a pervert, brother!
The dirty tentacle is
coming into my pussy...
Seems like it feels
really good, Aries...
All that moaning you're making.
Come on, worm!
Pour all your dirty semen
into the angel's pussy!
No! You can't!
No semen other than
Brother's could go into me...
Please don't!
No!
Hikari!
Meimi!
What's up?
You are at your limit already?
That's why the worms that
Roco makes don't get the job done!
Are you okay, Hikari?
Brother, I'm sorry...
I couldn't shine...
Lucky you. Because it seems
the worm's at its limit.
Aries, the next time we meet,
we'll cherish you a lot more!
So look forward to it.
She got to say what she wants to!
Losing to that black-clothes-only
impertinent woman...
...make me so mortified!
When we go home,
we are doing a reflection session!
Don't get that mad, Loveriel.
Otonashi was okay too.
Isn't that enough?
Brother, you don't understand.
If we want to rescue Rika...
...but can't beat Misty May,
there is a problem.
That's right.
Once Rika comes back...
...Brother won't need me anymore.
Brother, I came back to
confess my love to you.
But for you, there was
already a girI named Rika.
That's your girIfriend...
C-come on, Hikari.
Only Hikari's not fair!
Loveriel too, Loveriel too!
I guess I can't avoid you guys.
I'm sorry, Rika.
But just for now, is it okay
that he's my only brother?
Naoto...
I want Naoto to do it to me.
Not these tentacles, I want Naoto.
Naoto...
I want Naoto's big one.
I want him to stir it all up
inside my pussy!
Well, well, I guess the worms
didn't satisfy you enough, huh?
That's Naoto's...
What? Does Jiburiru want this?
I want it. Not a toy like this,
I want a real penis.
I guess there's no other choice.
So, how does it feel
after a long absence?
I-it's so good...
It feels so good.
Well, well, haven't you
gotten so obedient?
As a reward,
I'll tell you something good.
Something... good?
Apparently, Hikari Jinno
transformed into Jiburiru...
...and appeared in front of Misty May.
Hikari did?
So here's a question.
Who is Hikari Jinno mating with?
T-that's...
Naoto Jinno is such a cruel man.
Being raped by a devil
but still being turned on...
What an lascivious angel you are!
I'm about to come.
I'll come inside you,
so you should thank me.
Not inside!
If it's not Naoto,
you can't come inside!
Too late...
I'm coming!
I'm coming too!
It's coming out...
A lot of semen is coming out...
After all, you and Naoto Jinno
both are fragile things before sex...
That's not true...
Naoto said to me that
he loves me the most...
See you soon
La, la, la, la, la, la, la
la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la...
La, la, la, la, la, la, la. Little my star.
Little my star. Littie my star.
When the door opens,
many stories will start again.
I've been lost. But a light is illuminating.
That's my theory.
Launch your rocket into my sky!
You will be more powered up
when you are not alone!
I know.
I wondered for a long, long time.
And I finally, finally understand.
I wish I could tell you
how I really feel.
One, two, three, four. Okay!
Oh my, oh my, littie my heart.
I will gather my courage...
Fighting, fighting, littie my star.
Please wake up, angel!
Yes!