I am so late because of work...
Why did the manager have to
leave me and go home right away?
I found you, Meimi Otonashi.
No, Misty May.
But it's so quiet...
Seems as something might come out.
Ouch...
Why am I such an klutz all the time?
Since that incident ended,
I decided to change...
But this is reality.
Meimi Otonashi. Found you!
What?
No!
Eternal worm? Why in a place like this?
Ah, no!
Don't stroke me over my underwear...
I'm weak in that spot!
Those are my newly remodeled
eternal worms with...
...reproductive instincts.
It will go aiming right
for your sexual organs!
Who are you? P-please stop this.
No!
Of course not!
Don't! Not my breasts and my nipples...
I'm sensitive there...
A really hard tip like that...
Don't grind it against my hole!
If you do something like that... Don't!
What?
Perhaps the worm rubbed you,
and your pussy got soaked?
I-it's not soaked.
I won't get soaked just by being
rubbed by something like that!
My breasts too.
I'm not turned on by it...
Are you bluffing? So cute.
N-no! It's touching
my pussy and my ass!
Even though it's disgusting... No!
So let the insertion start.
We are going to dock
into your pussy and anus.
But don't lose consciousness!
N-no!
It hurts! It hurts!
Take it out! Take it out!
There is a fat one moving inside
my stomach! No, don't move it!
What, moaning?
Meimi, you're so dirty.
Who are you?
Why do you do such things?
You want to know? I guess it's okay.
I'll tell you as a maid cafe present.
I want to borrow the power of Misty May
that's sleeping inside you.
Misty May? So you are a
creature from the demon world?
Eternal worm, full-force mode...
Start grinding!
No, no, don't move!
My insides... Don't violate me!
Those tentacles have
special fluids inside them...
...and the moment you climax...
...they can separate Misty May from you.
S-stop it! My stomach...
My stomach...
Eternal worm! Pour lots of
semen into Meimi Otonashi!
N-no!
Worm babies will be made!
It's coming out... Inside my uterus...
A lot of hot stuff is coming out...
Ah! Meimi, you didn't climax, did you?
It's no use.
Once more from the beginning!
What?
No, help me...
Help me, Naoto...
Naoto!
Jiburiru
Second Coming
Born! New Jiburiru
Huh?
Why did I wake up?
I felt like I heard Otonashi's voice.
Oh well... Whatever.
Right now, there was a sound, right?
Is someone there? There's no way!
This is my sister's room, and
she's studying abroad right now.
Could it be...
...an underwear thief
who likes them young?
I won't forgive those perverse crimes!
What?
Um...
This is...
Striped underwear, huh?
No!
Brother, you perv!
And why are you here, Hikari?
Why?
That's because...
Um...
Well...
Brother, your face is scary.
Don't change subjects. Aren't you
supposed to be studying abroad?
Yeah.
I took a leave of absence
because a few things happened.
A few things?
Well...
So...
I can't tell you in a place like this...
Okay, that's fine.
The next problem is that uniform!
That's my school's uniform, right?
Yup!
''Yup''? Wait, you didn't!
Please look after me, Brother.
Good morning.
Hey, Take, I borrowed this...
Thank you!
Morning, Naoto.
Oh, Rika?
Naoto, what's wrong?
You have been sighing a lot.
Um, nothing...
Ah, Naoto, maybe you are curious
about that transfer student.
Transfer student?
Apparently, there is a really cute girl
that transferred into 1st year.
All the guys have been talking
about her since morning.
She's so cute.
You think she has a boyfriend?
I have a bad feeling...
Naoto, you have an interest too?
I'm not interested. I have you, Rika.
What?
Naoto...
Excuse me!
Oh no! Hikari!
She's so cute!
Ah, Brother!
Brother? Brother?
H-hey...
That transfer student was you, Hikari?
Yes!
Long time no see, Rika.
So, you are already
an academy student too.
Yes.
You, Naoto!
Rika!
We are running off for now!
Infirmary
Naoto, you were pulling me
all of a sudden.
Sorry, Rika.
Hikari's come back, huh?
Y-yeah. I wasn't trying to
hide it or anything though.
Naoto, do you love me?
O-of course. I was the one
who confessed my love.
I love Rika the most in the whole world.
I believe you, Naoto.
Rika...
Can we do it, Rika?
Yeah.
Naoto's touching my breasts...
Does it feel good?
Yes, Naoto. Touch it more.
You can touch it any way
you want, Naoto.
Rika, if you are that loud,
everyone's going to catch on.
Because you touch my breasts
in a naughty way, I'm feeling...
...really weird
even though we are at school!
This is so hard now.
Yeah, I'm turned on so much
my nipples are getting hard.
N-no, don't suck on my nipples...
I'm not lactating yet,
so don't suck on it...
Naoto, please.
I can't wait any longer...
I'm taking your underwear off.
Okay.
Rika, your pussy is so pretty.
P-please don't stare at it so much.
Rika, your pussy is sweet and delicious.
A lot of perverted juice is coming out.
It tastes like you.
It's your fault, Naoto.
You're making me be
in this perverted mood.
I'm sorry, Rika...
Naoto, I want to become one.
Yeah. Let's become one, Rika.
It's big...
Inside you, it's warm and feels good.
I feel like I'm going to melt.
Naoto's... Naoto's big one is...
...moving inside me!
Naoto's fat one is moving
a lot deep inside me!
I'm going to go crazy!
Rika! Rika!
Naoto! Naoto! I love you, Naoto!
Rika, I love you too.
Rika!
Naoto, come deeper inside me.
Please come in deeper inside!
It's amazing. Naoto's hard one
is hitting the back...
Naoto's hard one is hitting
all the way in the back of me!
Rika, it's such good squeezing.
It feels so good to me too.
Naoto, I can't...
I can't anymore. I'm about to come!
Wait, Rika.
Just a little bit longer for me.
No... Come... I'm going to come...
No, no!
I'm going to come too. Together, Rika!
Come, come. I'm going to come!
It's amazing. Naoto's hot stuff...
It's all pouring right into me.
Rika...
Naoto, I love you.
You guys are unchangingly flourishing,
huh? You erotic students!
Man, where did they go?
W-who is it? Where are you?
This sense... It's been around before.
This is...
Misty May!
That's right, Jiburiru.
Wait, right now
you are still Rika Manabe.
Long time no see,
Naoto Jinno, Rika Manabe.
Why is Misty May here?
Don't tell me Otonashi is again...
Rika Manabe. Today I came to take you!
Listen to what I say.
It's not going to go that way!
Angel...
Wait, Rika! Loveriel isn't here!
If you can't transform, then
you know what the outcome will be.
So be well-behaved and come with me.
Wait a sec!
W-who is it?
Heaven knows.
The land knows. Loveriel knows.
The tea you drink is oolong!
The tea Loveriel drinks is angel juice!
Show yourself!
The idol of Akihabara
and Lolita complex!
Blah blah angel...
Loveriel de Dotplanche is here!
I don't like narrow places...
Where are you coming out of?
Don't ask small details to an angel.
Loveriel!
You were peeping in on my and
Rika's lovemaking, weren't you?
W-what are you talking about?
None of that now, brother...
The halo!
Y-yeah, that's right!
Rika!
Angel Amore!
It's been a while.
So let me explain!
Rika Manabe, who can't
forgive perverted things, transforms...
...into the holy battle angel
Jiburiru with amore power!
By the way, amore power is
gathered by having sex.
That contradiction is
the source of her power!
Long time no see! It's Jiburiru!
If evil turns west,
then the tail is to the north.
Holding video in one hand
and erotica in skirt...
I won't forgive those perverse crimes!
Here we go! We don't forgive!
Ah, Brother, I finally found you.
Hikari!
Brother, what are you...
Huh?
Hikari, you can't come in!
What? Rika? W-what is going on?
Eternal worm!
Rika!
What? So that person really is Rika?
I got my catch.
I have no business here anymore.
Let go of Rika!
Goodbye, Naoto Jinno!
Wait!
Rika...
Rika!
Brother! If it comes down to this,
we need to make a new Jiburiru.
That's the only way to rescue Rika!
Hikari. You must have sex with Brother!
What?
You erotic water imp angel!
Are those the only things
that come up in your mind?
To gather amore...
...that process is the fastest
and most certain way.
Well, Brother.
The truth is, I've heard
everything from Loveriel.
About the incidents from before,
the transformation, and amore...
Hikari, that's...
Brother, if you are okay with it,
I will...
...h-have sex with you.
What?
H-Hikari?
If it's decided, please get
to the mating right away!
Loveriel will be outside listening in!
Is it this mouth?
Is it this mouth that
is saying those things?
Brother is so bashful.
W-well, are you really sure?
Yeah.
It's for you and Rika, so...
Has anyone ever touched
your breasts like this?
No...
You are the first one to touch
my breasts like this, Brother.
What am I going to do?
Perverted voices are coming out...
That's the sign of being turned on.
All girls become like that.
Brother, please don't
touch me like that.
My breasts... Amazing...
It's being rubbed by Brother,
and it feels so good.
My pussy is starting to tingle
and feel weird.
Amazing...
Hikari, your pussy is soaking wet.
Brother is touching my perverted
parts with his fingers...
He's messing with the
entrance to my pussy so much.
Hikari, can I lick your pussy directly?
Yeah. My pussy is wanting it so bad.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Brother, does it feel good?
Yeah, you are really good, Hikari.
I want yours...
I want to become one with you, Brother.
Hikari...
Please put it in me, Brother.
Something is coming in me!
A fat one is coming inside me!
Hikari, are you okay?
I am fine.
You can move in the way that
makes you feel good too, Brother.
Brother...
It's so big...
It's so tight, Hikari.
If I'm like this, I can feel you
inside me, Brother...
It hits my uterus, and it feels
like electricity going through.
More...
I want to feel you more, Brother.
Brother! Brother!
I'm sorry. I can't hold it in anymore!
It's gonna come out!
That's fine, Brother.
It's more than enough for me,
so you can come!
Come inside me!
I'm gonna come, Hikari!
Brother! Brother!
Please come a lot! Brother!
Hikari!
No, don't!
Don't... Don't come!
It hurts!
As rumored, you are such
a lascivious angel, Jiburiru.
W-who are you?
Jiburiru, from now on,
call me Madam Rococo, okay?
Jiburiru's saliva...
It's sweet and delicious.
Hey, the worms are raping you,
and you're turned on?
N-no.
I wouldn't...
It's fatter than Naoto Jinno's penis,
so isn't it better?
Naoto...
Oh, Jiburiru.
Instead of Naoto Jinno, the worms
are going to make you come.
S-stop it...
I'm going to come... Coming...
C-coming!
If we stay at this pace, we should
be able to make her fall easily.
Naoto...
Help me.
Help me, Naoto...
See you soon
La, la, la, la, la, la, la
la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la...
La, la, la, la, la, la, la. Little my star.
Little my star. Littie my star.
When the door opens,
many stories will start again.
I've been lost. But a light is illuminating.
That's my theory.
Launch your rocket into my sky!
You will be more powered up
when you are not alone!
I know.
I wondered for a long, long time.
And I finally, finally understand.
I wish I could tell you
how I really feel.
One, two, three, four. Okay!
Oh my, oh my, littie my heart.
I will gather my courage...
Fighting, fighting, littie my star.
Please wake up, angel!
Yes!