My mom was very sweet, and
she loved me more than anybody.
Her real son died
soon after he was born...
and dad brought me here
from the orphanage.
Mom loved me
as if I were her real son.
But, on that day--
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I've put all the responsibility on you
to take care of mom.
Please don't worry. I felt very
bad about what happened to him...
but I am glad to take care
of you and madam.
I'm glad you are here too.
If I was alone--
I was here ever since my mother
was a maid of this mansion.
I will never leave here.
Thank you, Rika.
My dear.
The daisies we planted together
bloomed so beautifully.
Mom...
Why do you still remember dad,
but you can't remember me, Mom?
Is it because
I'm not your real son?
Yuichi, it's because you
look very much like your father.
But it will be all right.
She will remember you soon.
I hope so.
The doctor said so, didn't he?
She is just confused right now
because of the shock from the accident.
Yeah.
All right then, I'll see you later.
See you later.
I'll see you soon, my dear.
See you, Rika, Mom.
Yuichi.
Madam...please remember
Yuichi as soon as possible.
I feel sorry for him
if this continues.
You are not the only one
who feels lonely.
Both Yuichi and I are also--
Madam...
Rika and mom...why?
Thank you for giving me a day off.
I'll go out for a while.
Uh, yeah.
I will be back for dinner time.
Don't worry.
You can take your time.
Thank you.
I'm just going to visit my mother's
grave to give her flowers.
It's the anniversary of
the day she passed away.
Besides, I have to help
madam to take a bath.
Something's wrong?
Nothing.
Yuichi, sorry for
inconveniencing you.
Then I will go.
Mom!?
Mom!
Please be careful.
Mom, are you all right?
Mom?
Mom, can you take your
clothes off by yourself?
I will check the shower.
It's ready.
Oh...hey...this way.
Are you ready?
I will wash off the soap.
Wow! M-mom, stop it!
Stop it! Mom!
Mom.
Master.
Master? What are you
talking about, mom?
Mom.
Here we go, mom.
Mom!!
- Master...
- N-no, mom.
Here, put your clothes on.
T-this is--
Mom!!
Please make love to me, master.
N-no, mom. I am Yuichi.
Why don't you remember me?
What do you mean by master?
Mom!
Madam!
R-Rika!
Madam, what happened to you?
W-well, she messed up
her clothes and--
R-Rika, why did you come back?
I forgot to
take something with me.
I-it was good timing.
Please help her change her clothes.
Yuichi...
Don't catch a cold, madam.
Master was--
Master?
Good night, madam.
I'm...I'm--
Mom, why don't you
remember me?
Please don't be so sad, Yuichi.
Rika.
If you don't mind,
can I console you?
C-console me?
Please come.
R-Rika!
Here, master.
I-is that?
This also looks just like the master's.
But yours is bigger and harder.
What? W-well...
Here, master. Please fuck me.
R-Rika...
Rika!
I'm happy...master.
D-don't you mind? Rika...
My mother also served
the master just like this.
My...dad?
Mom...
Rika.
You shouldn't look in the room.
Well, Rika...don't you think
your mother looks so beautiful?
Rika, can you still live here
after you grow up?
Didn't you feel anything at all that...
my dad and your mother were
sleeping together?
- I was also born here.
- What?
Then, are you my dad's
daughter and my sister?
No, I am your servant.
Yuichi, you are my only master.
Here, master.
Master...
I'm so happy.
Please don't leave me alone anymore.
You have to kill me
when you dump me!
Master!
Master.
Madam wants you too.
Here, please come with me.
C-can't be...
You are the new master.
You can have everything after this.
I-I can't do such a thing.
- Madam is waiting for you.
- What?
Here.
Master.
Mom.
Now, please become
madam's real master.
Mom.
Master.
Mom...mom.
Mom.
No! You are the master now.
You are the head of this mansion.
Master, please give it to me too.
After this, I became the
new master of this mansion.
Morning, afternoon, and night...
I kept having sex with mom and Rika.
And whenever I desired to.
Master...
Master, forgive me...
Rika and I are drawn to the
illusion which mom created.
Mom is sweet and still loves me
more than anybody.
Even after I became
master of this mansion.