It's already been one week
since my father passed away.
My mother had already died
a long time ago.
It was just my dad and I
living together.
But he told me
about my stepmother.
Yuichi, if something happens to me,
go see Yukiko, my ex-wife.
- Yukiko?
- Yes.
But you divorced her
a long time ago.
Her phone number is
in my address book.
Yukiko also knows about you.
Father! Father!!
Shortly after my dad died...
I found this videotape
when I was cleaning up his stuff.
Was he watching this tape
to relieve his loneliness...
after my mother died?
Hello!
I'm from the moving company.
Y-yes.
I'll be there right away.
Now I'll be living
with my stepmother.
She's now living with
her adopted daughter.
She'll take care of you
just like your mother did.
But, if it's possible, I wanted to
avoid sending you to Yukiko's.
Yukiko-- no,
my stepmother lives here.
- Who are you?
- What?
You must be my brother, right?
Brother?
I'm Mika Shito.
Mom told me that my brother
would be coming today.
My...sister?
Mom is waiting for you too.
Come on in.
Mom, Mom.
My brother is here!
Mom!
Hello.
I'm very glad that
you came here, Yuichi.
You've grown up to be very big.
Yuichi.
Doesn't she smell good?
A Mom's smell.
W-well...
Let's go.
I'll show you to your room.
Were you surprised
because she's so beautiful?
Oh, well...yes, she is.
This is your room.
And my room is just next door.
Don't peep into the room!
I wouldn't do
something like that!
Do you want me to
help you open your boxes?
- It's all right.
- I'm very happy.
About what?
Because my brother is
very good looking.
Good looking?
I-I was also surprised because
I didn't know I had a sister.
Besides I didn't even think
my sister could be this hot.
- Really?
- Yes.
That's nice!
H-hey.
Please call me Mika, brother.
Mika.
Look at my face
and say my name.
Mika.
Yes, brother.
Sorry, but I have to clean up some more,
so can you leave me alone?
I'm sorry.
D-did you see it?
Did you see who was in this video?
No.
My friend brought over
this video...
because he couldn't watch it
at his home and left it by accident.
He's always trouble.
Whatever.
Dinner will be ready soon, but
let me know if you need anything.
I'll be in my room.
O-OK.
- Oh, I'll get it.
- It's OK. I'll get it.
Hello, Shito residence.
Mom.
Is that a dirty phone call again?
- A dirty phone call?
- Yuichi, can you take care of it?
Do you want dinner, a bath, or--
Who is it?
Don't call here again!
Cool! Brother.
Does this happen often?
Mika is very popular with men and
she also gets lots of love letters.
Brother, it's not only the phone calls.
- They've stolen my panties.
- Panties?
Mom's too.
And...
sometimes a stalker follows me
on the way back from college.
Sometimes there's somebody
looking inside the house.
But Yuichi is with us now,
so he'll make a good bodyguard.
- Right, Mika?
- Yeah.
OK, let's eat now. We'll celebrate
our newest family member.
Brother.
Yuichi, until you came here, it was
just Mika and me living together.
There may be some things we don't know
about you, so tell us anything you'd like.
Y-yes.
Oh, yes. I have to buy you
some underwear and clothes...
so let me know your size too.
Y...yes.
Then, I can measure
your body size later.
Is anything wrong, Yuichi?
What? Oh, nothing.
Oh! Shameful Mika! It's not just
the two of us living here anymore.
That's okay. We are brother
and sister, aren't we, brother?
You are still young.
Yuichi, why don't you
take a bath too?
Y-yes.
Yuichi, how is the bath?
Oh, yes, it's very nice.
Do you want me to
wash your back?
N-no, that's not necessary.
I wanted to see you for a long time.
Goodnight, my brother.
Mom?
Brother.
M-mother.
Feeling good? Brother?
Do you want to
have sex with mom?
Don't turn it off!!!
Mom looks so beautiful
when she is having sex, doesn't she?
Mika!
Brother, come to me.
Are you crazy?
I've been in love with you
ever since I saw your photo.
Mika.
- Please, brother.
- N-no we can't, Mika.
- Why?
- Because...
But it's OK with mom?
I--it's not that.
You're such an idiot!
Mika.
If you want to do it with mom
so much, why don't you?
Is this all?
Father.
Mother!
There's nothing to be
afraid of, Yuichi.
Oh, yes,
it feels really good, mom.
I wasn't sure
if this was real or a dream.
Now, Yuichi, come inside.
Come to me.
Mother.
Mother, mother, mother.
I'm sorry that
you have such a bad mother.
Let's all three of us
play next, brother.
Mika...
I've been making love with mom
to ease her loneliness.
Hoping that her sexual
perversions would be cured.
I was also surprised when
I first found mom's videos.
I didn't want to see her sleeping
with those men anymore.
Please do it to her too.
Can you make love to me next,
brother?
Mika.
Come on, brother.
Brother.
Brother, I've been in love with you
for a long time.
See you later.
See you guys.
Come back soon.
Э	See you guys.