Somebody...
It hurts...
It feels just as if...
somebody's inside my head.
Let me out.
Let me out, it's saying.
Manami and Nami
Sprite
It's sweltering!
A guy like me from the
boondocks in the north...
can't put up with this heat!
I'm sure it's around here.
Oh, there it is.
My name's Toru Takamura.
My mom's in the hospital
for an extended stay...
so I ended up coming to
stay with relatives in Tokyo.
Unreal, huh?
But I think I might even
be a bit excited about it.
Huh?
Oh, it looks like nobody's home.
Maybe I should've called
from the station.
Let's see...
Huh?
What?
Oh! Gee whiz!
Huh?
Um... er...
Boy, it sure is hot out!
Hey, look! I'm not
a pervert or anything!
Mom! Mom!
There's a weirdo here!
Somebody help me!!
I'm Toru Taka...
Honestly, Toru!
I would've picked you up
at the station if you'd called.
I'm sorry, I've been
a real pain.
Well, it sounds like you've
got your troubles.
Your mom's all right?
Yeah, she had her operation,
so she's feeling better.
Manami went upstairs
without even apologizing.
I don't mind her being quiet.
But she's a poor talker,
and timid.
Well, it's my fault for letting
myself into the yard.
Manami, I explained to you that
Toru would be coming, right?
Yeah.
Um... Toru...
Sorry I was so rude to
you earlier!
No problem.
You couldn't help mistake
me for a weirdo.
It's partly my fault, too, for
letting myself into the yard.
Manami, I'm going to make
dinner, so help me out, okay?
Sure thing!
Man, I was blown away to see
what a babe Manami'd become.
Look, Toru.
I'll squeeze you between these!
Look...
It hurts...
My head hurts...
What's wrong?
Don't like your uniform?
My last uniform had
a standup collar.
So this one's kind of drafty.
Man, college uniforms in
Tokyo sure have short skirts.
Summer time; a short skirt
blows in the breeze
Morning!
Hey, Chiaki.
Come here a sec.
That Manami chick has come
to college with a stranger!
Ooh, he's kinda cute.
But what's Manami doing
stuck to him like that?
I don't like the looks of this.
No kidding!
Things would've gone
so well with Masaya...
if it hadn't been for Manami!
What?
Was Chiaki jilted because
of Manami?
Probably because Manami
put on a real cutesy act.
Which isn't to say that
you're not cute, Chiaki.
Exactly!
Manami's not just cute,
she's got a great figure.
Uh-huh.
When we got changed in gym
she had quite the body!
Cheeky broad!
So that's how she
seduced Masaya!
That's disgusting!
I can't take it!
Um... Chiaki?
Cute or not...
you're wrong if you think
I'll let you get away with this!
I'll have to teach you a lesson;
that's all there is to it!
- Right!
- Yeah, good idea.
Women are such loose-lipped
beavers.
You're mixing your
metaphors, there.
Well?
How's your first day here going?
Well, let's see...
It's a typical city college with
lots of cute babes, so it's fun!
Huh?
I didn't think I'd run into
you at lunch, Manami...
and here, you were eating
with this guy.
Sorry, were you looking for me?
Oh, she's gone out of her
way to hang out with me.
Watch out, or you'll make
Masaya jealous!
No, wait!
He's my relative's son.
Give Masaya an excuse, too.
Come on...
Bye!
See ya later!
Uh, so is Masaya your
boyfriend, then?
No, it's really not like that.
I wonder about that.
But I'm not really in a position
to be making any judgments.
Physical Education
So, women have their
periods every month.
And I'm not talking about
punctuation, here.
You listening?
Hey, I'm on to you, Manami.
You've spent the whole day
with a new transfer student?
You're gonna make me jealous.
It's not what it sounds like...
Yo, Masaya!
Better hurry to our club
or we'll be crushed again!
Right!
Wait for me in the cafeteria
till my club's over.
Uh-huh...
See ya!
Geez, sure is tough transferring
part way through college!
Hurry and get over here!
Why don't you say something?
Just what I didn't need...
a cat fight.
Manami, didn't you know Chiaki
was going out with Masaya?
You went and seduced him,
and they'd been getting along!
No way!
Man, just because you're
not bad looking!
Then today, a transfer
student's after you.
You're unreal!
That's right!
Y-You're wrong!
He's just my...
What're we wrong about?
How about explaining yourself?
Oh, boy. This is trouble!
Hey! What're you're doing?
- Leave her alone!
- Huh?
What a lame ass!
Better rescue yourself first!
Aha! He's that transfer student!
Toru!
Toru! Are you okay?
You slag!
That's how you trapped Masaya!
No, I didn't trap him!
He's the one who started
talking to me.
If you weren't around, I'd
be with him right now!
Tell me the truth!
You did it with Masaya here,
didn't you?
No!
You won't need those when
you meet with him today, right?
Hold her arms, Tomoko!
NOOO!
Ooh, look at those cute pubes!
Maybe I'll do something nasty.
No!
Somebody help me!
It feels like my head's
splitting in two again!
Manami...
Manami!
Let me go, fool.
Huh?
I told you, let go!
Maybe I'm being too
easy on you...
in paying back your tricks.
That's the same, quiet Manami?
I don't believe it!
Now you've gone too far!
Quit gawking and help
me out, you two!
What?
I'll get you!
Smash!!
Attack!!
Yay!
Yeah, right.
N-No way!
What're you gawking at,
bonehead?
M-Manami?
Don't call me that dumb name.
Just call me Nami.
Nami?
Man, that was quite the
grueling first day, yesterday.
Good morning.
Hey, where's your mom
and dad?
Dad's golfing, and mom's
at her culture class.
They just left.
Well, dig in!
Whoah! Unreal!
Yesterday was an incredible
day, huh?
Uh... um... Toru?
Yeah?
Did I do anything strange
yesterday?
D-Don't you remember
what happened?
No...
I vaguely remember Chiaki
and the others...
calling me outside yesterday.
But I can't even remember
how I got home after that.
Give me a break!
You can't tease me like that.
I'm not lying.
But you totally outmaneuvered
Chiaki and the others!
You took their panties and
put them on their heads!
There's no way I can believe
that you can't remember!
I really, really can't remember!
Something... something must
be wrong with my head!
You don't need to worry
about it, really!
Nami, you're so pretty
and strong, and cool.
It really knocked me out!
"Nami"? You mean me?
Yeah, that's what you
told me to call you.
Nami.
Man, if you can't remember
all that wild stuff you did...
it's like a split
personality!
Precisely!
Huh?
I'm Manami's other
personality; Nami.
It's a pleasure.
Get lost!
The gentle beauty, Manami.
I realized that hidden inside,
she had a split personality.
The diametrically opposed
personality, called Nami.
But neither her mom or dad...
not to mention Manami
herself knew about it.
Sometimes she merely suffers
from memory loss...
but that alone seems to
have really shocked her.
There's no way I can tell
her the whole truth.
So what does that mean?
Only I know this Nami person?
That's...
This is not amusing!!!
Manami and Nami
Sprite
Let's see... Huh?
That's strange.
What's the matter?
Nothing. No problem.
What'll I do? My bra and
panties are missing!
You don't seem very chipper,
Manami, what's wrong?
Oh, it's just that we have
swimming in gym tomorrow.
What, can't you swim or
something?
I can so!
Then what's the problem?
Well, you know...
I've gotta wear a swim
suit, right?
Huh?
Yeah, not many people go into
the pool in their uniforms.
That's not what I meant.
It's just...
You mean you're shy, right?
Mm-hm.
You don't have anything
to feel shy about, Manami.
You've got a great body!
You should be proud of it!
But still...
That's strange.
If this were Nami...
she'd have way more fun
in the pool than in a class.
Come off it, Toru!
What are you smiling about?
Oh, it's just that I'm a pretty
good swimmer myself!
She scared me, her eyes
look just like Nami's.
Well, they're one and
the same person, after all.
The shy Manami, and the
outgoing Nami.
They're both actually Manami.
She'd be the ideal woman if she
were a perfect blend of the two.
Or else if she could choose her
personality anytime she wanted...
Transform!
Yeah, right.
Nami's here!
Then she wouldn't have any
problems in the pool, either.
Hey, wait a second.
The other day...
Was it when I called her Nami?
N-N-No way!
Seeing her like that,
Sakumoto's pretty hot, huh?
She's got a childlike face.
But her hooters are
surprisingly big!
And she's got a tiny waist!
You're so lucky, living with
a cute babe like her, Toru!
Well, it's not all fun and
games, you know.
You lame brain! You're
really pissing me off!
Strip!
No! Stop it!
Let's see your butt hole!
Cut it out!
Those guys are such
loudmouths!
Huh?
That's strange.
What's the matter?
Nothing. No problem.
What'll I do? My bra and
panties are missing!
What a drag.
And I just took my gym
clothes home, too.
I hope I make it through last
class without anyone noticing.
Oh, Miss Sakumoto!
Something the matter?
Your chest seems a bit chilly.
Going bra-less, even
with those big tits?
You like feeling liberated, huh?
How does she know?
Did she take my bra
and panties?
Hey, you got something
to say?
Well, Miss Lib.
Maybe you're liberated under
that skirt of yours, huh?
No, you couldn't have...
What?
Got something to say?
Well?
No, forget it.
Oh, I sure wish I could've
gone swimming, too.
But I've got my period,
so I was out of luck.
And now, I'll give her
a real taste of revenge!
No...
Why's this happening
to me?
I wish I could just disappear!
No, you mustn't run away!
Aren't you upset about what
happened to you?
Now, do exactly as I say!
Lift up Manami's skirt
in front of everybody!
B-But...
If you don't, I'll throw out
these panties you stole!
- Give them back!
- See...
Okay, how about this?
If you do as I say, I'll
give these back to you.
And I'll also give you
my panties.
- Okay?
- I don't want yours...
If you don't want everyone
to know you're the panty thief...
then do it and don't
give me any lip!
Right...
Hey, did you hear?
Hear what?
About Sakumoto, in the
next class.
She's going bra-less and
panty-less today!!
What? Seriously?
With her body?
You!
Quit being ridiculous!
What're you talking about?
Well, Chiaki told everybody.
What?
Chiaki did?
That hag!
Wait, Takamura!
Class is gonna start!
I'm skipping out today!
Figures. He's gotta get
a peek for himself!
Crap!
Chiaki skipped swimming
class...
to get even for
the other day!
If Manami can't stop
Chiaki by herself...
and I show up all
nonchalant...
If there's one thing
I can do!
That triangle... that square...
Square means tofu...
Tofu is white...
White means panties...
If everyone finds out
you're the panty thief...
you'll be kicked out
of college!
Kicked out!
What do you think you're
trying to pull?
OWWWW!!!!
Your class is over there!!
Quit whispering in the
shadows!
If you wanna check, like him,
then get over here and check!
C-Cool!
That's right!
If she can stand up
there and say that...
then it's gotta be a lie!
Yeah!
I won't let anyone say such
bad things about Manami!
You sure had a different
opinion of her a minute ago!
I honestly didn't go because
I had my period!
Let's see about that.
Toru, pin her down!
Who, me?
Just shut up and do it!
Let me see!
No! What're you doing, idiot?
It does look like you've
got your period.
Then you've gotta believe me!
I just happened to see old Flatfish
stealing your underwear!
Hey, get out of my bag!
Then tell me just how these
got into your bag, Chiaki.
Well, uh...
I made him give them to me!
Then explain why you didn't
say anything about it.
I, uh...
I couldn't help it!
He threatened to steal mine
unless I kept quiet about it!
You liar!
Lie!
Ah, that feels better!
Come on, how about cutting
back on the violence?
You'll get Manami in trouble.
Then you should've called
me out sooner.
Yeah, but I didn't think things
would turn out that well.
They did because you skipped
class today and came to help.
Yeah, I guess.
We're home!
Oh, mom and dad aren't
home yet.
By the way, how do I get
Nami to turn back into Manami?
I usually just turn back
by the morning.
I get it!
Are you thinking of being
naughty with me...
while I'm Nami?
D-Don't be ridiculous!
I'm just honestly worried,
that's all!
Geez, all I did was ask!
Huh?
Manami wouldn't do it
even if you asked her!
Quit teasing me!
You'll get Manami in trouble!
This is just my way
of saying thanks.
It'll be our little secret.
S-secret?
Wh-Wh-What are you doing
with a bare butt?
Chiaki gave them back,
right?
Yeah, but this way feels
a lot freer!
When Manami returned
to her self...
she couldn't remember this,
luckily.
That Nami!
Quit acting, when you're
obviously thrilled!
Manami and Nami
Sprite
M-Manami!
What, isn't this what you
always do with Masaya?
It's not like that, Manami!
Toru...
You idiot!
Nami! Nami!
Come out! I'm begging you!
What's with all the groping?
You couldn't handle dealing
with Manami, so you called me.
B-Bingo.
Hate to disappoint you, but
you're not getting your way.
Because I'm pissed.
Huh?
How come you're mad, too?
Shut up!
Show some remorse!
You double-crosser!
Wait... Nami!
Hello, Miss Imai?
This is Toru Takamura.
Know where Manami is?
She's not back yet...
Well, she did come back
for a bit, but she's out again.
Yeah.
Let me know if you
hear from her.
Where could Nami have
gone to, anyway?
Nami!
What's gotten into you?
You're soaked!
I... I...
I'm disappearing...
What?
Nami! Nami!
NAMI!!!!