Ah...
Narutaki...
I shouldn't be doing such a
thing in the middle of the day...
But I can't stop my hands...
Narutaki!
It's Narutaki's fault
that I have to do this...
Because you stomped on my feelings...
I'm going to come...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! Narutaki!
I'm coming!
I feel so miserable...
Why does an attractive woman like me
have to masturbate alone in her bed?
There's no justice in this world...
This is all because
Narutaki turned me down!
Narutaki, I will make you mine someday.
Even if it's against your will...
Please show me the
future in a hologram.
I'm in love with you more than ever.
Marine A Go Go!
When I get close to you,
I get goosebumps.
Because you are my destiny.
When I touch the rainbow,
my heart beats faster.
Because you are so real to me.
Miracle, Miracle!
I know things you don't know.
Maybe because I was born in this
world, or maybe because I'm an angel.
I'm filled with love.
Maybe because I just want to
kiss you right here, right now.
Please kiss me for
a brighter tomorrow!
Project 3: Final Battle! Love
and Serve VS Love and Force
And that is why a hundred
of you are here today.
A jerk-off contest?
What is that?
Who the hell is that man?
Also, today's battle is approved
by the government, so enjoy it...
...to your heart's content!
It's going as planned...
Yes. We've given them a very
special kind of anesthetic.
The drug will erase the next
six hours from their memories.
They will not remember
a thing about this event.
Excellent.
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's a jerk-off grand prix!
Let me explain the
rules of this contest.
It's very much like an
all-you-can-eat system.
Two selected women will attend to
your manhoods one after another...
...and compete for how many men they
can make ejaculate in 20 minutes.
Men are divided in two teams, and
the winning team will be granted the...
...chance to have sex with the
losing girl as much as they want.
I will stop Doctor Marilyn's
revenge plan no matter what!
And I'm going to beat South Pole
One with my love and service!
That's the spirit!
Pon...
Don't worry.
I'm with you!
Okay! I will do my best!
Why did you add the last
rule, Doctor Marilyn?
Why not?
The loser deserves the humiliation.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I see...
That's how this is going to be, huh?
Then I'm going to use the Flute
of Naru to change Marine's costumes!
Go ahead.
Without that trick, Marine
would have absolutely no chance.
I can give you a handicap
if you want, Narutaki.
The Flute is enough.
Marine won't lose!
Fine! We will surely destroy the girl
you've trained to "love and serve"!
Let's begin!
Here is the representative
of Doctor Marilyn's team...
South Pole One!
Her technique can make an impotent
man's penis hard as rock in 10 seconds!
Blow job, tit job, and
anal play, anything goes.
Her suction is like a velvet vacuum!
She will take you to
heaven in ecstasy.
I give you the ultimate sexy weapon...
South Pole One!
Hi! I'm South Pole
One! Nice to meet you!
I want you to stick your big rod inside
me, and screw me as hard as you can!
And the next contestant is from
the Narutaki Laboratory team...
Marine Nonohara!
She attends St. Maria university. She
is just an innocent lovely young woman.
Her favorite food is
mille-feuille and ginger tea...
...her hobby is collecting stuffed
animals, her dream is to marry a
gentleman.
She looks so innocent I can't
believe I get to do it with her.
I'm already about to explode...
She's a girl who is
born to love and serve...
Come on out!
Marine!
Hello, I'm Marine.
I'm going to do my best to
make you feel really good.
I hope I can get a lot
of semen from you today!
Well, now we will begin
the jerk-off grand prix!
Ready...
Go!
Both girls got a wonderful start!
Both girls are giving
the first men deep throat!
It's all about rhythm...
One two, one, two...
I've learned this by loving and serving...
Both are getting into mounted position!
How is it?
Do you feel good?
Harder! Harder!
Come already!
I don't want to come yet,
but I can't hold it anymore!
So much come...
Another one!
...please!
Both girls are ready for...
...another one!
Look at them! This is amazing...
I wish I could join them too...
Even if it's your request...
At least, not until we find
out who's pulling the strings...
I know that!
How could this be?
How is Marine keeping up with South?
Is it the power of cosplay
that's making the men so excited?
Doctor Marilyn...
I don't think you understand why
I make Marine wear those costumes.
What do you mean?
You don't just wear
costumes, but you have to...
...become the character in the costume.
Marine isn't just changing costumes.
She cares about men and is trying
to become the women they love.
Her devotion is the key
to making them reach orgasm.
I'm coming!
If you don't believe, just look at them!
The men who did with South Pole One...
...seem exhausted, as if
their lives were sucked out.
On the other hand, the
men on Marine's side...
...got their orgasm
with big smiles on their faces.
I see...
South Pole One is equipped with neither
restriction ability nor a limiter.
It is true that the strain
on her men is much greater...
But Narutaki, I will remind you that...
...one of the important qualities you
need to win this battle is stamina!
All you need is to make them come!
Attention, everyone! It's
a group battle from here on!
No need to wait for your turn!
Vagina, mouth, breasts, and anus,
please fuck and come wherever you
please!
No! Run Marine!
W-What are you doing?
Come on! I'll take all of you!
I see.
That's why you allowed me
to use the Flute of Naru...
The Flute of Naru won't work against
multiple targets at the same time.
Now the silly theory of cosplay
you've studied is nothing but nonsense.
What are you going to
do, Professor Narutaki?
Marine is in danger!
Why isn't he stopping them?
If he doesn't stop them,
our project will fail!
No!
Please, not there!
Please, not my butt!
Two penises are rubbing
against each other inside...
You're going to break me!
Not my butt!
Look at that, Narutaki.
Is your Marine ready to retire?
After all, there is only
so much a human can do.
It doesn't matter how superior
that SM-01 inside of her is.
A human cannot make full use of it.
Now is your chance!
South Pole One! Jerk off
as many dicks as you can now!
Okay!
Doctor Marilyn!
Yay!
Come on...
I have to grab another
penis and keep jerking!
But...
But I can't get up...
What should I do?
Am I going to lose?
I can't beat South Pole One after all?
Help...
Professor Narutaki...
Stop whining and snap out of it, Marine!
Where am I?
Pon?
Stand up, Marine!
Narutaki Professor chose you to love
and serve, because he knows you can.
There is no doubt that South
Pole One is very powerful...
...but Professor Narutaki sees something
in you, something only a human has!
Just remember what you've learned.
Marine!
You're right...
I served those gentlemen
with all my love...
...and they were filled with
satisfaction when they came.
Not only physical satisfaction,
but also from the bottom of their
hearts...
It's not only to collect supreme
semen, but for a brighter future!
To give them the energy for tomorrow...
To love and serve is my duty!
What? That's impossible!
You still don't get it, do you, Marilyn?
South Pole One is truly
an amazing machine...
...but it lacks
something very important.
Something very important?
That is the unlimited
power only a human possesses...
It's power of love!
Good bye, Marilyn.
Professor...
Go Marine!
For the brighter future of Japan!
Yes!
I, Marine, am here to love and serve!
I'm back!
I can't believe you're back...
That's the great spirit of
a true Japanese woman.
Let's settle this once and for all.
You may have the skills and power...
...but you've got no caring
and love in your service!
I will beat you...
...with a loving heart!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes! Come on!
I'm coming I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Harder! Harder!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Come on! Come on!
I'm coming!
Winner! Marine Nonohara!
Did I win?
Yes. You did an excellent job, Marine.
Marine!
Everyone...
I will not accept it!
Doctor Marilyn!
Is your South Pole One...
It looks like you finally realized
it, didn't you, Narutaki?
South Pole One isn't an
ordinary blow-up doll!
She is a military Sexaroid!
I see...
But those missiles use an
American Laser Beam Riding system...
Is the Pentagon behind you?
You're sharp as usual.
I'll tell you something else...
This project wasn't only
to test South Pole One.
As a matter of fact...
South Pole!
Okay!
I shall see you again soon, Narutaki!
I can't believe the Pentagon
was pulling the strings...
Me neither...
Now I have hurry up and
finish that invention...
Penta?
What invention?
So Prime Minister, what do you say?
I don't think he can hear you.
Right.
I risk my life to save the future.
I'm alone, praying
to the stars above again.
I care about you so much.
Why can't you see my love for you?
My love will never be true...
Time just passes...
...if I deny the future.
...as I cling to the past.
But that is not why we live.
Always, sacrifice your feelings...
Turn sorrow into strength...
People may have doubts, but still...
They live for tomorrow...
They live for their hopes...
...because they have
love inside themselves.
Everything is for love.
And the threat was
gone, or so they thought.
They didn't know a new menace
awaits them in the near future.
Fight! Marine!
The future of Japan depends on you!
I'm Marine! I'm here to love and serve!
For the bright future of
Japan, I shall take your semen!