Please show me the
future in a hologram.
I'm in love with you more than ever.
Marine A Go Go!
When I get close to you,
I get goosebumps.
Because you are my destiny.
When I touch the rainbow,
my heart beats faster.
Because you are so real to me.
Miracle, Miracle!
I know things you don't know.
Maybe because I was born in this
world, or maybe because I'm an angel.
I'm filled with love.
Maybe because I just want to
kiss you right here, right now.
Please kiss me for
a brighter tomorrow!
Project 2: A New Enemy! South Pole One
I have seven pearls in me...
Pearls of the North Star!
Women always swarm around me.
One thrust can make countless
women wet their crotch.
These dumb women come here,
screaming their lungs out...
...and hoping to get
their hands on my tool.
He's so sexy!
He looked at me!
Heh, piece of cake.
I am the number one dancer
at this club, City Boy.
I rule this city of neon
lights! I'm the king!
He made a woman come by just
winking at her. Very impressive...
He is number 77 on the "Men
to Collect Semen from" list.
Why is he dancing naked? Isn't he cold?
Let's go, Marine!
Yes?
That's the end of today's show.
Please carefully exit the hall.
Um, but...
Quit mumbling and just go!
Please move out of my way!
Oh my! How embarrassing!
I must apologize. I
didn't mean to land on you.
Who the hell are you?
Oh, where are my manners.
I am Marine! I'm here to love and serve!
For the brighter future of
Japan, I shall take your semen!
Um, can I get some help in here?
A stripper from next door
has gotten into my room.
No, I'm not!
I'm here to collect your semen, and...
This is why I hate obsessed fans.
They'll do anything to get my attention...
Why would I want a
dumb-looking girl like you?
I thought she was just another
dumb fan, but she's super cute!
What's going on, Number One?
What are you yelling about?
Oh, you let one of your
fans into your room again?
I don't care what you do with your
fans, but don't party too much, playboy!
It's an unavoidable hazard
for a sexy man like me.
What do you say?
You want to party with me all
night until the sun comes up?
Sure. That's why I'm here.
Well, it's settled then.
An all-nighter sounds perfect!
I accept your invitation
to an all-night challenge...
...of Marine's stamina!
W-When did he...
But this is getting interesting.
It's bringing back memories...
Climb into the ring with
Marine, King of the Night!
Or are you going to run away
with your tail between your legs?
What? Who said I'm running away?
Calm down. Don't let them get to you.
But...
Could he be sent by my
competitors to destroy my club?
Or is he jealous of Number One
and came to take revenge on him?
Whoever he is, he's good...
Owner! I will take the
challenge, whoever they are!
You...
I have to defend my honor as the
number one dancer of City Boy!
I'm not going to let
them disgrace my name!
Okay, let me just...
Oh no!
I'll explain the rules.
There will be three rounds,
just like a boxing match.
Each of you strikes a sexy pose...
...and if he can make Marine
come first, Marine loses.
And if Marine makes him
get an erection, he loses.
She may be cute, but I
will not lose to this dummy!
Okay, Marine!
Change into the target's
favorite costume!
Oh no!
What? Why the costume?
Round one!
Fight!
Damn. I didn't think she'd
be in a school bathing suit...
I still remember to this day...
When I was in school, I had
a crush on my classmate, Emiru.
She looked so sexy in her bathing
suit that I couldn't talk to her...
...let alone confess
my feelings to her.
Every day I would picture Emiru
in her bathing suit, and I would...
Oh shoot!
I must do something...
Idiot!
Don't lose yourself in the past!
Your duty is to excite women,
not let a woman excite you!
Got that, Number One?
I'm sorry, Owner.
I let my guard down for a second.
It's my turn now!
The owner used his experience as
a club owner to break the memory.
Be careful, Marine!
Here he comes!
Too slow!
Take this!
I-it's amazing! My
body is getting so hot...
Now I understand why those girls
were so excited seeing you dance.
This is what was happening to them...
She's down!
First round, Dancer!
Keep that up.
Be more aggressive in
the second round, okay?
I want to finish this stupid game.
Then I'm going to take
her to my hotel room...
...and make love with her in
that bathing suit all night...
Hmmm, bathing suit...
I guess we have to use our secret plan.
Listen...
What is it?
This is for the men of Japan.
We have to stimulate
him and make him explode.
Go, Marine!
Second out!
Round two!
Fight!
Oh no!
What the...
What's happening to your costume?
The bathing suit is shrinking!
What a radical strategy!
This is so embarrassing! I
can't get married anymore...
It's getting tighter and tighter!
But I have to do this...
Please look at me in this
super tight bathing suit!
Dammit! I cannot lose this fight!
I must win, even if that means
I have to pull out all the stops.
Behold! These are the
Pearls of the North Star!
I've won...
My sexy power is at its maximum!
Now she's mine.
My goodness. What a horrible
thing has happened to you!
Huh?
It must be some kind of serious
disease...
Because you have such a heinous
thing...
...you're so ashamed of it...
...and your torturing yourself by
dancing in a place like this.
N-No...
I put these in myself...
You don't have to lie.
I understand...
It must've been tough...
Listen, I'm telling you that...
Okay, fine. You win.
I'll do whatever you want.
If you want me to strip in the
middle of the street, I'll do it.
You just want me to lose
my popularity, don't you?
Well, can I have your semen?
You're an amazing girl.
I feel like I'm really going
to fall in love with you.
If my semen can make you happy,
I'll give you as much as you want.
I've never had a blow job like this!
Her tongue's wrapping
around my dick so gently...
...yet sucking it hard at the same time...
The girls I've had were always
so excited to suck my dick that...
...their blow jobs had no feeling...
This is great!
I can't believe I'm
so excited like this...
I can't hold it any longer...
It feels amazing!
I can't believe it...
This was his wake up call.
We'll have a fresh start
tomorrow, right? Number One?
A new step to tomorrow...
I'm going to come soon!
I'm coming! I'm coming! Marine!
I'm going to come too!
I'm almost...
I'm coming!
Thank you.
Will you come to see me dance
sometimes?
Yes.
As expected from a great
playboy, his semen was primo!
Okay, let's keep going, Marine!
Yes, Professor Narutaki!
We have two more targets tonight.
Don't worry, I called your house.
Your mother thinks you're studying
at your friend's house tonight.
Using my ability to change my voice...
...I left three messages as different
friends on the answering machine.
What a super cover, Professor!
That's right, I'm the chosen one
who's destined to love and serve...
I am Marine! I'm here to love and serve.
For the brighter future of
Japan, I shall take your semen!
I'm starting to get the hang of it.
Hmm?
W-What's this?
Professor, looks like our
target has become a mummy.
Damn it.
He's been squeezed
down to his last drop.
I have a bad feeling...
This target is a hard-core otaku
and has had no contact with...
...women whatsoever for
the past couple of years...
Could it be...
It must be!
Someone has the list, and that someone
is getting to the targets before we do.
I'm pretty sure...
Professor, what do you mean?
There's only one person in this
world who knows about our schedule...
And probably...
It came from the next room!
Hurry! Our second and third
targets are twin brothers!
That's amazing...
Yes! Yes!
Come on!
She isn't Japanese...
A blonde American girl...
Come on! Come on!
Oh my goodness...
How can she...
We've got an audience!
Okay! I'm getting turned on!
It's a dream come true!
I've watched many
American porn videos, but...
...I never thought I would be
doing such a pretty blonde girl!
Wait! That's...
It's so tight!
It's squeezing you tight, isn't it?
W-What is going on?
Why he is inside her rear
end? And he's going in so deep!
How is that possible?
Her anus...
Maybe it's a strange
thing for me to say...
...but it's like a snapping
turtle in its prime...
Incredible ability!
That suction! That contraction!
It's way beyond a human's capability!
It seems like my hunch was right.
She isn't a human girl, probably she is...
What took you so long, Narutaki?
I knew it was you, Doctor Marilyn.
What's going on?
Why is Doctor Marilyn here?
That girl...
You created the Sexaroid, didn't you?
That's right!
I created the Sexaroid
to take revenge on you!
Her name is South Pole One!
South Pole One?
Just as you guessed.
She may look different, but she
is like a sister to that SM-01 POM...
Her ability is the same
as his, or perhaps better...
Doctor Marilyn, why did you do this?
I'd like to know why you had to do this.
I told you, this is
my revenge against you!
This is becoming rather intense!
Yeah, dead serious...
We were both still
attending Varhard then...
How could I be so careless?
I'm coming down with a cold?
Um...
Narutaki...
This...
Oh, thanks.
Cruel...
You're cruel!
Revenge...
I'll get my revenge on you someday!
I've changed since that day.
I swore to myself that I would make you
bow down before my inventions
someday!
But since you were so far ahead
of me, I had to steal your work.
So I swallowed my pride,
and became your assistant...
...hoping only to pay you
back for what you did to me.
That was a love letter?
I'm going to stand in your way!
I won't let you collect any more semen!
I will crush your
Preservation of Japan project!
Harder! Harder!
This is awesome!
You can't come yet!
More! Harder!
So great!
Move your hips, that's right.
One two, one two...
This is the power of a Sexaroid...
How am I supposed to...
I'm very sorry, but it looks like your
love and service are no longer needed.
It isn't effective to have a human
woman serve a man to begin with.
A Sexaroid is better in every way.
I don't think so.
Why can't you admit it?
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm coming in your ass!
In your ass!
You're finished!
Ass!
Hi, my name is South Pole One.
Nice to meet you!
Even a dummy like you
should realize the...
...big difference between
a human and a Sexaroid.
I advise you to give up your
"love and serve" business.
Or do you have the
guts to challenge South Pole One?
How cruel...
I won't forgive you...
Is she...
I won't forgive you!
You have no right to do this
to this man for your revenge!
Even if God forgives you, I will not!
For those who became wrinkled
mummies...
...I will take you on, South Pole One!
And let's decide who is
suited to love and serve!
I, Marine, will challenge you!
Okay, Marine!
I will take that challenge!
To be continued...
Definitely.
I risk my life to save the future.
I'm alone, praying
to the stars above again.
I care about you so much.
Why can't you see my love for you?
My love will never be true...
Time just passes...
...if I deny the future.
...as I cling to the past.
But that is not why we live.
Always, sacrifice your feelings...
Turn sorrow into strength...
People may have doubts, but still...
They live for tomorrow...
They live for their hopes...
...because they have
love inside themselves.
Everything is for love.