Please show me the
future in a hologram.
I'm in love with you more than ever.
Marine A Go Go!
When I get close to you,
I get goosebumps.
Because you are my destiny.
When I touch the rainbow,
my heart beats faster.
Because you are so real to me.
Miracle, Miracle!
I know things you don't know.
Maybe because I was born in this
world, or maybe because I'm an angel.
I'm filled with love.
Maybe because I just want to
kiss you right here, right now.
Please kiss me for
a brighter tomorrow!
Location: 30 degrees right at 12
o'clock, vertical angle: Minus 14.
Roger!
Distance, 350.
Target locked on!
Start auto scan!
Are you sure she is the one?
No need to worry, Pon...
Look!
Her manner is so lady-like,
it almost seems unnecessary.
She is completely sheltered from
all the burdens of the world.
I am certain that her
brain was developed under...
...very pure circumstances, created with
"naive and not-so-bright brain cells."
And to prove my theory...
...look at those well-developed,
stress-free, gigantic boobs!
And those curvy hips, which
mercilessly stab at a man's heart!
She is the perfect candidate!
Born to please men!
Hmm, you might be onto something...
That's right, and capturing
her would take us...
...one step closer to
success in our project!
Collecting frozen semen?
Yes.
We will collect prime
semen from men with...
...strong sexual energy
from all over Japan.
To prepare for our brighter future!
I see. And you want me
to approve of this plan?
Yes. And if you could...
...we'd like to keep it secret.
I-I understand...
I will take care of the ministers.
Thank you very much.
If we collect prime semen and
freeze it to preserve it...
...we can later use the
semen to procreate.
Also, we will enhance the genitals
of the semen's owners...
...so that they can go
spread their semen all over Japan!
I've been planning
this for a long time...
I call it the "Preservation of Japan!"
The time of young and healthy
Japanese men will return...
And just how do you plan to do it?
I, Narumi Narutaki, have
everything planed out.
We have already selected a
candidate for this project.
She is a woman of exceptional talent!
Marine! It's your turn to take
care of the school bunny tomorrow.
Don't forget, okay?
Of course I won't.
I learned a valuable
lesson from the last time.
I will do whatever it takes to
take care of the bunny this time!
You don't have to do anything special.
Just use your common sense, okay?
Common sense?
Well, don't feed it a piece of
cake like you did last time.
But when I saw that cute little
bunny, I just couldn't help it...
You couldn't help it?
But you should know that
cake can make a bunny sick.
That's common sense.
I love cake, so I thought
the bunny would love it too...
I mean, who wouldn't
love such delicious cake?
Everybody doesn't think like you.
You're such a dummy.
Yes? Did you say something?
Um, nothing.
Well, my car is waiting for me.
I'll see you tomorrow, Marine!
See you tomorrow!
She's dumber than I expected...
Okay, let us carry out our plan.
Roger!
My goodness!
Um, hello?
Water... I want some water...
Oh my! This pink turtle is speaking!
But how? How can a turtle speak?
It's not that surprising.
The turtle from Grimm's
Fairy Tales spoke too, didn't he?
Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry, Mr. Turtle.
I've never met a turtle
who could speak before.
I'm sorry if I've offended you.
W-Water...
There you go.
Well I was afraid water would
be bland, so I made you some tea.
Please, enjoy.
How is it?
You seemed exhausted, so I
added a secret ingredient...
I used extract of snapping turtle.
Oh my goodness!
Let me bring you a new cup.
No, that's all right!
I want to thank you
for the delicious tea...
I want to give you this...
Oh my...
But I cannot accept
such an expensive gift.
My mother told me not to accept gifts
from strangers nor eat food off the
street.
Uh-uh.
That's not how this works...
See, you helped me, so now you're
obligated to accept this gift from me.
It's been said since ancient times...
..."he who rejects gifts will
be kicked to death by a horse."
Never heard that?
No, I've never heard that before.
Cut the crap!
Dying from being kicked by a horse
is a common fate in human history.
It must be true if you say so. After
all, turtles have such a long life span...
All right.
I will accept the ring.
But this ring is a little small...
gotcha.
The ring is...
The ring is moving on its own!
W-What's going on?
Who are you?
I am the greatest scientific
genius of the 20th century.
He's that creepy mad scientist
from the mansion next to the school!
I am Professor Narumi Narutaki!
W-What am I going to do?
The teachers told us to always
stay at least 10 meters away...
...but he's already 3 meters away...
I'm a lot closer than you think...
As a matter of fact, you've
already fallen into my hands!
I'll tell you why, Marine Nonohara!
The ring you put on is my
newest and greatest invention...
I call it "the Cursed Ring"
What do you mean, it's cursed?
It's a very pretty ring.
My goodness!
W-What's going on?
The "Flute of Naru"!
By playing this flute, I can turn the
owner of the ring into a "servant of
men."
I'm a genius, aren't I?
But...
Wait, this costume...
I can't take it off!
The costume can only
be taken off by men.
You should be honored.
It's made with the best materials...
...and designed to capture men's hearts.
We had the best cosplay
store make this costume.
I am a pure genius!
I beg of you. Please take this ring off.
No can do!
Even I cannot take the ring off...
But there's one way to take it off...
Oh please! You must tell me how!
Fine, I will tell you...
You must sexually serve men
and collect semen from 100 men!
Why?
Why do I deserve this?
Now you've got no choice...
I'd say that victory is already ours.
How long are you going
to sit there like that?
If you don't do anything, you'll
stay in that naughty costume forever.
I bet people will talk about you.
All I need is play this flute...
Then whether you're in a train...
...or in a bathroom...
...or even when you're
bathing in a hot spring...
...you will become a sex
slave in an instant!
How horrible!
I pity you, Marine.
Soon, the only place you'll
be welcome on Earth will be...
...anime cons
full of uncirc\umcised nerds...
...or shady lounges
in the red light district.
What have I done to deserve this?
Is this because I made the bunny
sick? Is that why God is punishing me?
But still this is just too cruel!
I even saved that pink turtle earlier...
Who are you calling a turtle?
You!
Ow!
Just open your eyes and
look closely, you dummy!
I hate when someone calls me a turtle!
But you used the anecdote about the
turtle from Grimm's Fairy Tales...
Shut up!
I never said that I was a turtle.
I'm no turtle.
I am a snapping turtle!
So you lied to me?
You're one dumb girl.
Let me introduce you!
He is my great assistant,
and also my best invention...
Model Number: Bio-animaloid SM 01...
...Snapping Turtle Semen
Collecting Robot, "P-O-N"...
I call him "Pon"!
That's right!
B-But...
Maybe it's beginning to dawn on you,
but...
Everything was...
...an act just to trick you!
So, what do you say now?
Are you going to collect semen for us?
You want to take the
ring off, don't you?
Huh? What's gonna be?
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
No!
Akira Fuse!
Number 29 on Narutaki's "Men
to Collect Semen from" list...
Age 21, blood type: RH+A, hobby:
Collecting photos of cosplayers...
Times you were turned
down by girls: 14.
87% of them gave you
"Let's just be friends."
What?
You failed the college entrance exams...
...and you've been going to a
cram school for three years.
W-Who the hell are you?
Do you have any hope for the future?
Don't you want the energy to go forth?
I could take you to heaven for no charge
during this special promotional period!
What do you say?
Is this some kind of solicitation
for illegal sexual activities?
Just leave me alone...
Because I have to study...
I don't have time to talk to you.
Besides, I'm a...
I'm a...
Listen Marine...
You need training first.
I've arranged an easy target for
you since this is your first time...
Don't worry, he's just a meek student.
But don't let your guard down.
He's been studying day and night,
his stress level is very high...
You cannot predict what
he'll do when he snaps.
But we have no time to worry.
You have to master many
different techniques to...
...endure the trials that await you!
What took you so long, Narutaki?
We're all ready.
So, that's the girl...
Let me introduce you,
Doctor Marilyn!
This is an exceptionally talented girl...
...l've picked from many
other candidates... Marine Nonohara!
C-Cute...
I see, she does appear
to have some potential...
Well, okay then. Let's
see what she's got.
All right. This is your
first assignment, Marine!
Use that sexy body of yours to
brighten this sad man's dark future!
Go Marine! Suck out young
and healthy semen from him!
No!
I cannot do such a
thing! Please, have mercy!
My Flute of Naru can read
the mind of the target...
...and change your costume to
the one the target most desires.
Do I have to change the costume again?
Oh no!
What's happening?
It's changing again?
W-What's going on?
Again?
Oh no!
What the hell is this? Her costume
keeps changing and changing...
Oh! I got it!
He has a cosplay fetish!
So his mind cannot
decide on one costume!
So his desire to make her
dress in different costumes is...
...causing this phenomenon...
That's right!
Please, someone stop this!
Are you going to stop it?
Well, it is pretty entertaining, but...
...we have to move on...
Let me choose the costume then.
F-Finally it's stopped...
We've got no time to waste!
What are you doing?
Come one, move your hips more!
Please stop it!
This is so embarrassing!
Panties!
Please don't take them off!
If you want me stop, then you
better serve this man on your own.
Yes! I'll do whatever you say!
I will serve him!
All right!
Doctor Marilyn, shall we
prepare for the lecture?
Th-This is the manhood itself?
I never thought it would be so big...
First, use your hands to please him.
Oh my goodness, it's throbbing.
And it's hard, and twitching too.
So this is what a man is...
Ew!
What's this?
Something sticky is coming
out from the tip of it!
Don't get so excited,
it's just pre-come.
And now, give him a blow job.
Um, excuse me, but what is a blow job?
You put it into your mouth and suck it.
What? Into my mouth?
But...
Oh no! Why me!
Please help me Mother!
Just give it up and do it already!
This isn't too bad either...
Please forgive me!
Stop whining, Marine!
You'll never collect the semen of a
hundred men if you keep acting like that!
You'll never be a woman
of love and service.
It's showtime!
Now Marine...
Doctor Marilyn and I will show
you everything you need to learn!
Just watch very closely!
Lesson one!
I want you to shoot a load of come...
Th-that's naughty!
That's naughty!
Lesson two!
Please, give it to me...
I want you to come on my face.
I want your thick love juice...
Shoot it all over my face!
Narutaki!
I want it...
Cover me with your come.
So much milk comes out of a man...
Is that...
Is that "ejaculation"?
Thick as usual...
Hmm... yummy.
Lesson Three!
Yes!
I can feel it deep inside me!
It's going in deep!
I'm going crazy!
Harder! Harder!
Don't tease me!
Please give it to me!
That's filthy!
I'm coming!
This is the end of the lecture!
Well then Marine...
We wish you the best!
No!
No! Don't put it in there!
I'll never get married!
I can't believe it!
My first time shouldn't be like this...
This Chinese dress reminds me
of Miss Mirei, who I had a crush on...
Miss Mirei!
Hey, Narutaki.
You wanna go for one more round?
I'm sure you still have
plenty of energy left...
Please, not now!
Japan's future depends on this training!
Idiot!
If he keeps doing this, my
body won't last too long...
I'm sorry.
We don't have to do this.
It's sad. Really.
It takes forever for me to come...
That's why all my girlfriends dumped
me...
Maybe I'll never be
able to come having sex...
Damn it!
What a poor man...
You must've gone through a lot...
Don't worry!
I promise I will make you come!
We can do this together,
okay? Mr. Student!
Good job, Marine!
I've been waiting for you to say that!
Professor!
"Love and Serve" mode, activated!
Now is the time to achieve your mission!
My mission?
Destined to live a cursed fate...
The goal is one hundred ejaculations!
I'm Marine! I'm here to love and serve!
For the bright future of
Japan, I shall take your semen!
You're so great, Marine!
He's already naked.
You're better than any cosplay gals!
This is the best blow job I've ever had!
Oh, Marine...
I can't believe this is your first time.
Marine, are you sure?
My virginity may have
been taken away earlier...
...but now I will give
you my true virginity.
I'll put it in, Marine.
Yes...
Oh Marine!
I'm going to come...
I'm really going to come, Marine!
Thank you so much, Marine.
I'm glad that you finally came.
Congratulations!
I came, because of you.
Mission accomplished!
No way...
Congratulations on your first
successful mission, Marine.
But I cannot get married anymore...
No need to worry! Pon has
a semen collection function.
By shrinking myself to microscopic
size...
...I can become one
with your you-know-what.
What?
So as long as Pon is inside
you, your virginity is protected.
Then I'm still...
You don't have to worry
about your wedding night.
Professor...
You are one step closer
to taking that ring off.
There are only 99 men left to have sex
with!
It seems like a hopelessly long way...
Life is tough. You just
have to work harder!
You're right. I have to work harder.
That's the only way for me...
That's right! Atta girl!
A bright future awaits you!
Yes! I'll do my best!
I risk my life to save the future.
I'm alone, praying
to the stars above again.
I care about you so much.
Why can't you see my love for you?
My love will never be true...
Time just passes...
...if I deny the future.
...as I cling to the past.
But that is not why we live.
Always, sacrifice your feelings...
Turn sorrow into strength...
People may have doubts, but still...
They live for tomorrow...
They live for their hopes...
...because they have
love inside themselves.
Everything is for love.