It's been a while, Cain.
How have you been?.
Fine, thank you. I'm pleased to see...
...you have returned safely.
Thank you.
Charlotte, you're now more
beautiful than ever.
Cain, how has your time as a Lord been?.
I haven't been very sucessful
in my role as Lord.
Is that so?.
I'll go and prepare some tea.
It will just be a moment.
Thank you. But I simply came by
to tell you that I've returned.
Money means nothing to us.
These woods are all we live for.
What a stubborn race you are!.
By joining us you would profit
beyond your wildest imaginations.
I understand though. Unfortunately,
you leave me no other choice.
Stop!. You are in Norland now.
I won't allow this.
You...You're...
Tsubaki Ohouin.
Whoa there!. OK. It's only a matter
of time now anyway.
When I become King, I'll burn you
and your woods to the ground.
Then your buried treasure will be mine.
What did he mean by
"buried treasure"?.
The dwarves won't admit it, but there's
definitely buried treasure in those woods
If we had that treasure, we could
strengthen our forces.
..and most likely turn the tide
of this war in our favor.
Ann, what do you think?. Are they
really hiding treasure?.
Um...Well...
I have read several old texts that
mention hidden treasures.
But there's no way to tell if
they're true or not.
Who cares if it's true or not?.!.
Have a look for yourself
what we'll be facing!
How are we going to defend
ourselves against huge tanks?.!
This could be the last straw.
If the dwarves have hidden treasure,
they should help us out.
Isn't it the Lord's job to convince them?.
Hey, I haven't seen Tia around.
What happened to her?.
She's been gone for the last three days,
for personal reasons.
Personal!?.
Yes. And she might
not be coming back.
She's not the issue here!
You have to make a decision!
Yeah...Buried treasure...
Boss!
Charlotte. So you're in here.
Father...
You look bored. Do you want to go hunting...
...Iike we used to?.
Definitely! But father...
What do you think of the war
between Norland and Tedmond?.
Just thinking about it gives me a headache.
Either Francis or Cain will succeed me as King.
For that reason, I must remain neutral.
That is why I cannot get
involved in that matter.
That's true.
But that will all be over soon
enough, Charlotte.
Your twentieth birthday is approaching.
Yes.
Cain has exceeded every expectation
in his role as Lord.
But Norland is the underdog in this war.
At this rate, it looks like Francis will win.
Charlotte, you do not have
a problem with that?.
As per the arrangement, I will marry whoever
has been the better Lord of his land.
This not a personal matter. It is
for the best of the country.
Really?.
I'm home!
Tia, what happened to you?.
You're all covered in dirt.
Where have you been
in this time of crisis?.
Don't pick on me! You don't know
what I've been doing!
I was trying to lend a helping hand
by spying on the Tedmond.
What!?.
Look at this.
I see. They're deploying their troops
along the Eastern valley front.
This is great! Now we know all
about their military installations.
Now we know where to strike. It will
be quick and less dangerous.
They belive they've already won the war.
They spend their nights drinking and
having sex, so their security is very lax.
Tia, I really appreciate this.
It's nothing compared to the kindness
you've shown me.
Let me handle this now.
I'll create a strategy that will win this for us.
I trust you, Tsubaki!
Yes.
First, we have to rescue the
prisoners from the jails.
Than we'll attack the armory
and take as many weapons
as we can. We'll burn the rest.
Our primary targets will be their tanks.
Quickly, everyone. We're
here to rescue you!
You! Sandra...
Well look who's here. The young
Lord from next door.
We've got to stop meeting like this.
Bring her too, Tsubaki.
Tsubaki, there are no tanks here.
There's nothing more we can do then. Let's
get out of here before they notice anything.
What?. Norland's army?.
Yes.
Those peasants?.! They're still trying to resist?.
We'll put an end to that soon enough.
Oh, you're finally awake?.
You've been asleep for three days.
But please get some more rest.
You were hurt pretty badly.
Most people would have died
from wounds like yours.
Why did you save me?.
My Lord will not alow anyone to suffer,
no matter what the circumstances.
It's natural to want help people.
Well, eat up and get some more
sleep. You need to heal.
Hey, I heard you'd woken up.
I didn't ask you to save me, so
don't expect me to thank you.
As a prisoner, I have a right to
food and proper care.
You're right. Good. Since
you feel that way I guess
you'll be leaving soon.
The truth is that I really don't
have the time to punish you.
Normally we'd put you on trial but...
...if you promise to never loot another town...
I will use my authority to simply banish you.
Are you trying to show me mercy?.
How sweet!
I may be a woman but I'm a bandit leader!
I have my pride!
I'm not afraid to die.
You should end this now.
Justice will be served.
Otherwise you'll come to regret
it someday, Sir Lord!
If you want to kill me, do it now.
W...what?.
You fool! What the hell are you doing?.!
Listen to me! You bandit bitch!
You just spoke of your pride...as a bandit leader.
I may be young but I am
the Lord here.
I have my pride
as well...as leader of these people.
You don't know what justice is.
Humans don't live for justice.
Justice exists FOR humans.
It's not just an ideal. Everyone
can live peacefully.
There is such a thing as true justice.
As a Lord, I truly believe that!
If you die, do you think
people will be happy?.
Are you only happy by making
other people unhappy?.
That's not true, is it?.
There's just no way!
Damn! Damn you! There's no
other Lord quite like you.
No. There was one before.
You're the second.
Second?.
You're just like my father.
Your...father?.!
My father was a great Lord,
who was loved by his people.
But he was too kind and trusting of others.
He was betrayed by his closest
and most trusted aide.
My father was made a prisoner by
his own people and died in jail.
My family was split up and we
were banished from the land.
I was very young and sold to slavery.
I bounced from place to place and
ended up in this business.
But I loved my father.
As a Lord, he was too honest.
But he put his people, his family...
me... ahead of himself.
I don't know a human being alive
who's greater than he was.
Sandra...
You poor thing...
That feels weird. My whole body's tingling...
Awesome! You taste so good!
Don't worry! Relax and enjoy this!
Wow! This is great! I'm so hot!
I'm coming!
How's this?. Feel good?.
Fantastic!
This feels amazing!
Not yet...
If you keep that up I'm going to...
Damn! You came a lot!
How's this, Sandra?. Feel good?.
You're awesome!
For me too! This is the best!
So deep... In me! Rubbing my... back walls!
More! More!
So hot! My body is...burning up!
That's it! I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come!
Good. Let's come together!
I'm coming!!
Shortly thereafter...The day of the final battle arrived.
We had taken our prisoners
back and stolen their weapons...
So that boosted our military strength, but...
...we were still overpowered by the enemy forces.
Norland's back was to the wall.
So it ends with a bang!
Aim for the dwarves' woods.
Fire!
I'm truly sorry about everything.
But we'll still have Francis' head for this.
Let me try my magic.
I haven't used it in years, so
I'm not sure if it will help or not, but...
Why now, Chiffon?.
I'll do whatever I can for the
good people who fight beside me.
Chiffon...Thank you.
We'll split up and attack, just like we planned!
Chiffon, cover us!
Yes.
What's going on?.
Shit! But this changes nothing!
Onward! Get them!
I'm sorry, My Lord. I...
It's alright, Chiffon. You did your best!
So this it?.
Elise?.
What?.!
Hey, everybody!
Are those the dwarves?.!
The dwarf army has come to our aid!
And don't forget about us!
Sandra!
It's them!
Damn you all!
That day, a miracle happened!
Norland was on the verge
of defeat, but...
...with their help we turned the tables and won!
This long war has finally come to an end.
Yes. So many people have been
waiting for this day.
I'm finally able to repay the Boss
for all his kindness.
What?.
Nothing.
The victory made me the
most powerful Lord.
And I was given Charlotte's
hand in marriage.
The dwarves promised me their
hidden treasure to mark the occasion.
It is wealth enough to end poverty
and hunger in the entire country.
Chiffon will end her role as my advisor
and she'll return to the church.
Tsubaki realizes just how many people
I can help when I become King.
So she put feelings for me behind her.
But she will become the head of the palace guard.
Tia will continue her work on my staff.
But we now have a professional chef
so she doesn't cook anymore.
That means I can finally enjoy a decent meal.
Due to their help in the battle
against Tedmond...
Sandra and
her bandits got a full pardon.
The Emerald left the country to
pursue a new, honest living.
You may kiss the bride.
That feels strange...All tickly...
No.
It's alright. Trust me.
OK.
Charlotte, your pussy tastes great!
Your getting really fucking wet!
Please don't say that.
I'm coming!
I learned about this in bridal class,
but have never done it for real.
It's really hard and pretty warm.
You've gotta learn how to do it
or we'll have problems.
Move your hand slowly...
Like this?.
Yes. That's good.
That's really good. You're doing great.
That's fucking fantastic!
If you keep that up, I'll...
You don't have to hold it. I'm fine with it.
Are you sure, Charlotte?.!
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
It's alright. I'm glad you enjoyed it.
It's not poisonous, right?.
Charlotte, I love you.
I love you too.
I'm gonna put it in.
O...OK.
It hurts!
Sorry. But it always hurts the first time.
It'll feel good soon enough.
Al..Alright.
I feel strange.
I'm burning up inside!
Yeah! It feels wonderful!
Awesome! More! More!
That's it, Charlotte. Keep going!
I'm going to...
Charlotte, I love you.
I love you too, Cain.
More than anyone else!
Charlotte?.!
Oops! I'm sorry. Did I wake you?.
Well... I was curious...
It was getting big while you slept.
Umm...I was hoping we could do it again.
You got it! Let's go, Princess.
Our country grew and prospered. And we
were soon with an heir to the throne.
Although we are kept busy,
we live a wonderful life.
And then, someday...