Time has passed quickly. Cain has
become a great Lord, loved by the people here.
However, it is not all good news.
Norland was viciously attacked
by the armies of Tedmond.
We're losing the war and they're stealing our land.
The resolve of our people is
being pushed to the limits.
Our Lord is having a hard time
dealing with everything.
It is our duty to comfort him
and take his mind off things.
That is how I spend my nights,
doing the best I can to him.
Boss, you're so good! You're amazing.
I'm going to die in ecstasy!
Are you alright, Sir?.
Yeah. That was great, Tia. You're awesome!
Thank you. I'm so happy you enjoyed it.
Charlotte will return from her
studies at the monastery in months.
Then she'll celebrate her twentieth birthday.
It's also the day we'll find out who
the Princess' husband will be.
If Francis is chosen as her husband...
What happens to us as we're at war?.
We'll either be killed...or become slaves.
No! I couldn't...
I could never go back to being a slave!
That's the reality of it.
We have no choice but to
accept whatever happens.
Please don't say things like that, Chiffon!
Ann, what are the dwarves'
feelings about the future?.
Ah...Yes..Well...
Our position will never change. We remain neutral.
But we will protect our woods at all costs.
Why?.! You live here in Norland just like us.
Why won't you fight with us?.
I...I don't know what to say...
Tia! Stop it! Ann is the dwarven ambassador!
You should not speak to her like that!
I'm sorry. I just got upset.
Tia, please don't cry!
If only Tsubaki were here.
She could kick Tedmond's army ass!
In these difficult times, she is
nowhere to be found...
...Ieaving us no means to
even contact her.
Where do her loyalties lie?.
Tsubaki left to continue her training...
to help protect Norland.
Stop it! Both of you! Even if
Tsubaki were here...
...she couldn't defeat Tedmond all by herself.
We have to stand together these days!
This is no time for arguing!
It's been years since I became the Lord here.
Chiffon has been my advisor from day one.
But still I feel she distances herself from us.
Our target tonight is a
Tedmond warehouse, boys.
Francis is making money hand over fist in this war.
Don't feel bad to take whatever
you get your hands on!
Yes, Sis!
Stupid! I told you to call me Leader!
S...Sorry!
Tedmond is winning and keeping
all their spoils of war in one location.
That makes it easier for us to do our jobs.
Norland doesn't even have
a pot to piss in anymore.
I don't care about their war.
We just steal from whoever has the money.
Let's go!
Yeah!
What's wrong, Leader?.
This is too easy.
I can't possibly ask anymore of our people.
We have no military power.
I'm too tired to even think.
I should just get to bed and
worry about it tomorrow.
Why does this happen to me?.
Aren't you done yet?.
Don't rush me, please!
Just a little more...
It's the end of the line for you, bandit!
Shit! It's a trap!
Thay're gonna kill us if they catch us.
Do whatever you have to to escape!
Yeah!
Arrest them!
You!
Stop them!
Get out of our way!
Leader!
Leader...
Time to tell us what you know. Out with it!
I've endured harder whippings from slave traders.
Stubborn bitch! Where's the rest of your
gang hiding?. Where's your loot?.
You have to have a hideout somewhere. Tell us!
Hit her!
I've never seen anyone withstand
such pain. Even a man.
I'm impressed.
You've got a pretty nice pussy for a bandit!
What's up?. You're getting wet.
Are we not having fun yet?.
We aim to please all our visitors here.
The Tedmond police know how to
take care of our guests.
Wh..What are you doing?.
It's a special service we offer.
If you don't like it, just tell us
where your hideout is.
I'll never tell!
Is this all you've got?.!
Anything yet?.
She is much more stubborn than I expected.
Interesting woman. Let me handle this!
Woman. Put this in your mouth.
Francis, that's very dangerous.
If she bites you...
If that happens, we'll kill them all.
Do it, bandit!
Never!
Leader. Don't worry about us!
Damn you!
Good. Keep going!
Get me off and you get time
off for good behavior.
Good. Here we go...
Swallow it!
You whore.
Leader...I'm sorry...
So what do you do about the dwarves?.
They show no sign of leaving.
Just leave them be!
When this country is mine,
they'll be forced to obey me.
Yes, sir!
Tia!
I'm sorry!
Tia, your cooking has really improved.
It's a vast improvement over
when you started here.
Th...Thank you so much.
But I've had trouble with the menus
as there's not enough food anymore.
The farmers have been injured in
battle and the fields are destroyed.
But we should appreciate how
good these mountain vegtables taste.
Y..Yes. These mushrooms and
sweet potatoes are quite good.
But it's hard for growing kids to
eat such things everyday.
T..That's true...
Chiffon! Please don't make this
conversation so serious.
Let's at least have some fun at dinner.
There are so many people suffering
out there right now.
Is that fun?.
B..But..
It's OK, Tia.
Boss...
As Lord, this is all my fault.
I'm so ashamed that I can't provide
for you or my people.
Oh, right there, My Lord.
I love having beautiful creatures like you around.
You're like living art that responds to my touch.
Charlotte, my bride to be, must surely
have grown into a beautiful woman by now.
Soon, she will wallow in pleasure as my wife.
Charlotte, I've tried my best to
become your future husband.
But my land is in ruins and my people are suffering.
Elise!
It's been a while. What's happened?.
You don't look good.
Surely you know.
You see everything that happens
in this land, right?.
I can't do this anymore. I should
have stayed a simple shepherd.
You can't give up just yet.
Give up?. Why would you say
something so stupid?.
How can I turn this situation in my favor?.
Ask Chiffon. Have her use her wizardry.
Wizardry?.
She's half human, half Dark Elf.
Dark Elves have strong magic powers.
I've never seen Chiffon use any magic.
And she doesn't even try to be
friendly with any of us.
It's like she doesn't even care
that Norland is losing.
Have you ever asked her why?.
The reason?.
I never asked her why.
It was pretty rough again today...
but at least we can appreciate
having dinner together like this.
This is so good.
Is something wrong, My Lord?.
Tonight, you're my partner.
Chiffon...
Yes.
As you're well aware, Norland is
in serious trouble.
You're an elven wizard, sent by the church.
But I've never seen you use any magic.
Can you really use magic?.
I been so long since I've used it... I don't know anymore.
Can you use your power to help our people?.
I don't concern myself with the wars of humans.
I was born half human, half Elf.
But I soon found that there was no
place for me in either world.
I was an outcast from the time I was a child.
And I was considered different and unique...
I was raped and abused by human men.
I was taken in by the church and became a wizard.
But I still have a deep rooted mistrust of humans.
I came here simply as a favor for
the church after all they'd done for me.
That's the only reason.
My Lord?.!
I'm so sorry. Sorry to stir
such painful memories.
As a human,
please accept my apologies.
Here I've been having sex with you,
thinking nothing of it. I'm just as guilty.
I've been blind to the pain you've
kept bottled up inside.
I am a horrible person. How can I call myself a Lord?.
My Lord, you're not...
You're not like that.
Chiffon, your body is warm.
I am...warm.
My Lord!
I've never seen you get like this, Chiffon.
That feels wonderful!
I'm on fire!
Could this be...?.
My Lord, don't worry about that now.
OK.
This...This is unreal, Chiffon.
I've never felt like this before.
That's good to hear.
Keep enjoying it.
My Lord, don't hold back.
Chiffon!
It's inside me! Deep inside me!
What's inside you?.
My Lord's...
Say it or I'll take it out!
Your cock! Your big cock!!
My Lord, you're different.
You taught me how warm a
human's heart can be.
I will light up my life for you.
I smell blood.
If these Norlanders had just left,
they wouldn't have to go through this.
You sound happy.
Of course, you can enjoy war
when you're winning.
That's true. We can have their
money and their women.
Hey, you! What did you just say?.
Have you attacked Norland?.
Whoa. We can't see your face but...
You'll soon be ours.
I'm not in a forgiving mood!
What?.! You little bitch!
She's...She's the woman who...
She beat Bagwell!
Do you want to try your luck too?.
The smell of blood does not wash out easily.
What...What the..?.!
Boss...What happen to Norland?.