This is great, Charlotte. You're so beautiful.
I'm sorry to wake you up so late.
I couldn't wait to tell you how I feel, Cain.
I'm in love with you.
Ever since I met you...
...it's like you've become a part of me.
And with each passing day...
...your hold over me continues to grow.
The reason I've become so ladylike...
...is because I was scared that you would hate me.
You're the only person who treats
me not as your queen...
...but like a real woman.
I really enjoy that.
I've been watching you.
I've been thinking about you all the time.
Ah...I can trust you, can't l?.
Yes, you can, Charlotte. I love you.
Hold me tight. Don't leave. Please!.
I want you to be with me forever.
Yes. I'll be by your side forever.
Ah... I can't... I'm losing it...Ah...Ah...
Daddy...
Cain, you have to be the
most powerful...
Lord of a I l the
lands w i th i n the next five years.
Become someone loved and respected by the people.
Yes, Princess Charlotte!.
Chiffon, I want you to stay and help Cain.
Yes. Anything her Majesty desires.
Alright. I'll come back and check
on you before too long.
Please, Princess. Come anytime.
Princess, It's time for us to be going.
I know.
So long.
Excuse me, Princess.
But do you really think that young man, Cain...
...is capable of becoming a powerful Lord?.
I don't know...
But I believe in him.
I have a feeling that the spirit of
Mother Earth will look down on him.
What makes you say that?.
I can smell it in the air.
I'm Cain Asbell, a shepherd.
One day, I followed some sheep
that had strayed off...
...into a cave, where I found a strange vase.
From inside the vase came Elise.
A fairy who'd been trapped
for over a hundred years.
She thanked me for setting her free.
She told me to go and check
out an abandoned cabin.
There I found a Princess, Charlotte of Franberge...
...who had been kidnapped by bandits.
I saved her life.
I was invited to the royal palace and
rewarded with the Lordship of Norland.
I was also chosen as one of the candidates
to become the princess' husband.
However, if I am unable to make my land the
most prosperous in the country in five years
I will lose not only my title of Lord...
But my chance at the princess' hand in marriage.
I still don't know if I should be happy or not.
But I have no choice but to do my best.
I give up!.
What's the matter, boys?. Finished already?.
I'll give 100 flange to anyone who can beat me.
Nobody else wants to take a shot?.
My challenge fee is only 2 flange!.
That look. She must be from the
Eastern lsland of Yapan
Hello!. Nobody wants to try?.
Hey, you there!. I see you
have a pretty nice sword.
Wanna test your skills?.
What are you doing here?.
I am Cain Asbell, Lord of this land.
You do not have permission to do this.
You won't get away with this if you keep it up.
Is that so?. Well, excuse me.
I didn't know you were the Lord.
But what do you mean that
I won't get away with it?.
This is great! Go, Sir Lord!
Show us your strength!
You're not thinking of running
away from a woman, are you?.
No. I just don't fight with women.
I wouldn't want to hurt her if I fought for real.
You should just hurry up and leave this place.
If you have such superior skills,
I would like to have the chance to fight you.
You don't need to worry about me.
AH...well. You see... I haven't... Umm...
practiced recently so...
I'm...kind of...Well, my sword
is...deadly.
My skills...Umm...
passed down in the family.
And...There are a lot of...rules involved so...
You know...that kind of stuff...you know...well...
I'm telling you that I'll be fine!
Ah...well...
If you won't start this, I'll go first!
What?.! Wa...Wait a...
AH...AH...No! Listen!
I won't fight a woman...
MEN!
You! You'll get hurt,
if you don't fight back.
C'mon!! Stand up!
Or could it be...?.
Is that all you've got?.
Princess!
Princess...
It's too dangerous!
You'll fall!
Love Escalation!
Princess Charlotte! What are you doing!
You'll die if you fall from there.
Shut up! I'm not Charlotte!
I am the mysterious Masked Knight!
Nooo!
Princess!
You, there! Ms.Tsubaki!
I won't let you pick on the weak!
If you're still looking for a fight...
Why don't you try your luck with me?.!
How fun!
Come on then, little girl!
Show me what you've got!
What?.! If you underestimate me
just because I'm young...
you're in for a world of pain!
People like you who disregard the law...
will fall in seconds thanks to my special skills.
Come on then, little girl! Let's fight!!
Stop it, Charlotte! It's too dangerous!
Listen, everyone! Open your
eyes and watch what happens.
Here I come! YEAH!
Huh?.! She's fast, Well...
YEAH!
Take this!
DEADLY
LOVE
ESCALATlON
Charlotte!!
Is that all?.
Are you alright?.
She couldn't even be my sparring partner.
Just by looking at you sorry bunch of losers...
I can tell how weak the army here is.
You're not worthy opponents.
Do you understand?. Get out of my sight!
In this era, strength is the law of the land!
Cain...
Charlotte! Are you Alright?.
Cain...The Law has nothing...
to do with strength.
The person here who can save
the people here from poverty
Someone with a generous heart like yours...
The power born from kindness and hope...
That is the law of this land!
Cain, have more confidence...
... in yourself.
I truly...
... believe in...
...in you!
What a tearjerker that was!
I feel sorry for the people here...
...stuck with a Lord like you.
Come on! Show me what you're gonna do now!
What?.
Cain!
I...I give up.
Ah... Umm...
Everyone, this is how strong the
power of love truly is.
AH...
You did great!
It's been a while since I slept that well.
She almost forced them to join her.
I wonder if they can become a
proper army like this?.
I heard a rumor from some of
the people training here...
...that The Emerald, a bandit group,
is hiding somewhere in our lands.
You made the right decision hiring her.
She said she'll work for free.
Why not let her work a while and see how it goes?.
I guess so.
What did you say?.
That female bandit and her
men are hiding here!?.
Boss, please allow me to organize
the troops and go after them.
No. We haven't found out where their camp is yet.
And I can't send untrained men into danger just yet.
Then why don't you and I go?.
What!?. Just the two of us?.!
We'd be able to handle these
bandits without any problems.
No matter how many there are!
Don't be ridiculous!
What's wrong?. You look tired.
Hi, Elise.
It's about Tsubaki, right?.
Yeah. We have to be careful of
her aggressive personality.
I think Tsubaki just really wants
to help you out.
You know she's a very righteous person.
You're right.
I'll talk to her again tonight.
It'll be alright?.
Yeah, it'll be fine.
We just have slightly different
opinions, that's all.
She'll understand if I talk to her.
But I'm a little worried. She's very stubborn and...
Don't look so concerned.
Have a little faith in me...
Just let me handle this.
Why don't you go on night patrol?.
Alright, I'll do that, if you say so.
But don't upset her.
Don't worry.
We'll both be smiling and hugging
by tomorrow morning.
Alright then. Good luck.
Yes?. Is that you, Tsubaki?. Come on in.
Welcome.
What's wrong?. Don't just stand
there. Please have a seat.
What's this about?.
Huh?. Don't shout! You'll wake everyone up!
What do you want?.
What's wrong?. Are you upset?.
Of course.
I...I trusted you.
But after all I've done, you call me here for...
What?. What is it?.
...for SEX!
What!?.
You called me here for sex.
Don't make light of it.
I... It's not like that...
Then why would you ask a woman
to your room this late at night?.
Or did you call me just so you
could look at my face?.
It's not like that at all.
That was dumb of me.
I didn't think she would
misunderstand me inviting her like this.
Won't she just believe me and relax?.
I won't accept this, even if you are my boss.
Hey, Tsubaki. Why are you so nervous?.
Why...What?. I am not nervous!
If you don't need me, I'd like
to excuse myself.
What?. Hey...Wait a minute!
Why are you trying to avoid me?.
I...I'm not avoiding you.
You're lying! You're definitely avoiding me!
Why?. Tell me if I did something wrong.
You may work for me but I also
consider you a good friend.
I can't continue being your Lord if this continues.
I'm worried rumors will spread about
my coming here late at night like this.
If that happened, I don't know
what I'd do. After all you've done for me
I...
I...I'm sorry, l...
What's wrong?.
They're here.
Who is?.
Those bandits...The Emerald.
What?.!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Fighting is fun! Nice to meet you!
If you don't want to get hurt,
just give us your money!
Once we've finished here, we move west!
OK, Sis!
Idiot! I told you to call me Leader!
I...I'm sorry.
You there!
Huh?.
Leader, that's the new Lord here.
I see.
You're the bandit group,
The Emerald, aren't you?.
Stop this now and leave our lands!
So you're a comedian too?.
You should be more fun than the
Lord of that last town.
By the way, I am Sandra,
The Emerald's Leader.
Also, I don't like you referring
to us as bandits.
We prefer chivalrous thieves.
Chivalrous thieves?.
They just pretended to be noble.
They devastated our neighbors to the south.
It's rare to see a woman leader.
If you clean up this mess and leave us alone...
I will allow you to stay here.
You don't need to keep acting
like animals and committing these crimes!
Such thoughtful words. I'm so
happy I'm about to cry.
Yeah, right...
Listen up, Sir Lord. We eat when
we want and we sleep when we want.
We won't take orders from you.
Your words are only falling on deaf ears.
C'mon, Boss, why don't we...
No, Tsubaki. We need to size
them up more first.
Leave this one to me!
Hey, Sandra! You'll only end up
getting hurt if you underestimate us.
How about you and I settle
this, one on one?.
And if I win, you promise never
to set foot in this town again!
Leader, we should shut them up...
Well...wait a minute.
No need to get all hot and bothered!
We really just came to check
out the new Lord today.
But don't worry, you'll be
hearing from us again soon enough.
You're running away?. You cowards!
Don't be silly! I just don't feel like fighting today.
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Yes, Leader!
I won't let you get away!
Stop, Tsubaki! Don't!
Tsubaki!
I'll teach you to turn your back on us!
Are you alright?.
It hurts!
I think you need a little more training
if you fall for something like that.
We'll see you again soon, Sir Lord!
This area's been pretty badly damaged too.
If only we'd found them earlier,
this never would have happened.
By the way, where did Tsubaki go?.
I don't know.
I'm worried about her.
Hey! I finally found you.
Boss...
It's only been a day. You shouldn't
work so hard just yet.
I'm sorry, Boss...
Boss... I'm not fit to lead your army.
Tsubaki...
It's really too much for me to handle.
I'm sorry but... I...I...
B...Boss...
It's alright. Let me see it.
It's pretty bad. The bleeding won't stop.
You shouldn't blame yourself
for this, Tsubaki.
You always call me Boss.
But when we're not working,
we're both just normal people.
I might even be able to cheer you up a little.
Listen, Tsubaki. I want you
to promise me one thing.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I get sad when I see you look like that.
Boss...
Well, let's get back and ask
Chiffon for some medicines.
Tsubaki...
I'm sorry. I know how bad it is...
...to fall in love with the Lord you serve.
But...when I'm alone...
I can't stop thinking about you!
I can't stand being apart from you.
I can't take this anymore. I can't lie to myself.
Tsubaki...
I'm so sorry you've suffered.
You're so beautiful, Tsubaki.
You're shaking. Are you scared?.
I'm not shaking.
You're so cute, Tsubaki. Just relax.
Does that feel good?.
I'll make you feel even better.
No...There?.!
It smells so good. And it's very soft.
No... Not down there.
Do you usually wear underwear
under your kimono?.
I know girls wear cute underwear.
I don't need that stuff in battle.
You'll catch a cold if you don't
wear anything down here.
Don't say such nasty things...
Huh?. Tsubaki... Her body reacts when I talk dirty.
Well...Let me try this.
You're great, Tsubaki. Look how
wet you're getting.
No... Please...Don't say that.
If you keep saying that... I'll...
You'll drive me crazy!
Did you come already?.
Y.. Yes.
Boss...
How does that feel, Boss?.
Tsubaki...That's great!
Don't, Tsubaki! That will make me...
Boss, I want to return the
pleasure you gave me.
Tsubaki. I can't hold it...
I'm sorry, Tsubaki.
I don't mind. I love every part of you.
I love you, Tsubaki.
Are you sure?.
I want to...With you...
I'll put it in...
Boss...
Oh, my god! It's in me!
You're inside me!
You're amazing!
No! don't say that. I get embarrassed.
Tsubaki, I can't stand it! I'm gonna come!
Boss, you're so deep inside me!
How is it for you?.
Fucking awesome!
Me too, Boss. Me too!
Tsubaki...
Boss... I feel so hot! Hot!
No... I'm going to come!
I... I...I can't hold it anymore!
I'm gonna come too! Just a little more...
Oh, God! Oh, yes!
Oh, Boss! Boss, I love you!
Tsubaki!
Are you sure this is the place?.
Yep!
Good.
The idiots here have no idea about
the treasure buried right under their noses.