Good! You're getting much better! Keep it up!
Tsubaki has been doing such a
great job with the troops.
And she hasn't said a word
about what happened between us.
Tsubaki. i can't hoid it...
i'ii do anything for you, Boss...
i'ii put it in...
Oh, my god! it's in me! You're inside me!
You're amazing!
No! Don't say that. i get embarrassed.
How is it for you?.
Great!
Me too, Boss. Me too!
Hey, you! Use your waist! Come on!
We wanted each other so badiy.
But now she says she wants to
be moraiiy responsibie.
So she hasn't said a word about it since.
My Lord! There's the ietter from Rouge.
My Lord?.!
Oh! Wh...what?.
Where is this iand Francis
mentions in this ietter?.
it's that thick patch of forest on
the other side of the hiii.
The woods where those
reciusive dwarves iive?.
Why wouid Francis be interested
in that strip of iand?.
Long ago, that iand once
beionged to Tedmond.
But it's part of Noriand now.
They've iong fought over
ownership of that iand.
i don't mind giving it back.
That iand is of no use to us.
Cain!
Eiise!
i'd be carefui with that
piece of iand, Cain.
Even if there is no ciear vaiue to it now...
...as Lord you shouid not give
your iand away so easiiy.
i see. i'ii send a ietter deciining his offer then.
By the way, where have
you been iateiy, Eiise?.
She's gone again.
My Lord!
What?.
How shouid we proceed?.
Piease send Francis a ietter
stating he cannot have the iand.
There are a iot of peopie out today.
What's going on?.
You're right. it's busier than usuai.
Excuse me. Why is it so crowded today?.
You don't know?. There's a
secret siave auction over there.
Siave auction?.!
That's why aii the shops are so busy.
it's forbidden to buy and seii
siaves in this country.
Don't teii me about it!
The new Lord here is young
and inexperienced...
...so peopie think they can get away
with whatever they piease.
What?.! The Lord is standing right...
What?.!
Most peopie here don't reaiiy
know what you iook iike.
Let's use that to our advantage
and do something about this.
Are you saying we shouid shut
down the siave auction right now?.
That's right.
SHiT! So this is it?.!
You have to catch them in the act,
either buying or seiiing.
Let's wait a iittie ionger.
Aii right.
This giri is from the northern town of Harushon.
As you can cieariy see, she's a great find
you probabiy won't see the iikes of again.
She iooks young but trust me,
her body's aii woman.
That...that hurts!
Show us what she's got!
OK. OK. Right away!
C'mon, iet's give the customers a show!
No! Stop!
And a iittie more...
NO!
Check her out.
Such a young face on so ripe a body!
She must be excited you're aii watching.
She's getting wet!
Disgusting!
So, who wants to take her home?.
Three hundred!
Three hundred and fifty!
Four hundred!
Four hundred and fifty!
Four hundred and sixty!
Five hundred!
No one over five hundred?.
Soid! To the highest bidder
for five hundred fiange!
Stop this!
Siave trading is iiiegai in this country!
What's your probiem, iittie boy?.!
This is none of your business! Go home!
No! i can't do that. i may not iook
iike it, but i am the Lord of this iand!
Wh...What?.!
i shouid put you aii in jaii!
But i'ii iet you go this time.
Shut this down now and ieave
this iand immediateiy!
Why did you bring her here?.
That siaver had aii kinds of giris.
But you oniy saved her. That's strange!
Weii...You may think so, but...
Dinner is ready, sir.
Tia made this for her savior
using aii her skiiis.
What's wrong?.
Ah... No.. it's nothing.
Let's eat?.
So how is it?.
it's deiicious! You're a great cook!
Yes. Tia made this for you
as thanks for rescuing me.
i'm so happy you iike it.
it reaiiy is good!
A woman named Rose is
here to see you, Sir.
Rose?. Do you know who that is?.
She's the wife of Lord Tratigei,
who passed away years ago.
His widow?.
it's a pieasure to meet you.
You are a young Lord,
just iike the rumors say.
it's nice to meet you too. May i heip you?.
i just came to introduce myseif.
Letting that siave trader go was
the right thing to do.
Catching criminais is one thing.
But a Lord needs to show mercy as weii.
Weii...i reaiiy didn't know what to do so...
i just did whatever feit right at the moment.
if it had been Francis, he wouid
have kiiied them on the spot.
What?.! Without even a proper triai?.
Can you do that?.
it depends on the situation.
But i iike the way you handied it.
So keep it up! Don't iose to Francis!
Win the Princess' hand in marriage.
i wiii. i'ii do my best!
i'm kind of tired. Do you mind if i iie down?.
You're reaiiy good!
This is how a Lord shouid treat his guests!
Oh! Right there!
Reaiiy?. i'm happy to hear that.
How's this then?.
Oh, that's perfect! i can get it
deep inside me this way!
Miss Rose?. Do you do this often?.
Yes. i iove young men.
Damn. i kinda wish i was the oniy one.
That's sweet of you to say.
i'm coming...
But you do the same thing.
What do you mean?.
You're surrounded by women.
You don't have to worry about
spending nights aione.
No, they heip me with my work.
Nothing at night.
Pieasuring the Lord at night...
...shouid be one of their jobs.
it's a Lord's priviiege.
Priviiege?.
Yes.
Nightiy pieasures?.
it's true! i am the Lord! i have
the right to demand that!
i wouid iove to do that with Tsubaki...
...but i know she'd refuse.
Chiffon's beautifui and i'd iove to do her...
... but i have no idea how to approach her.
Tia! That's fantastic! This is
much better than your cooking.
What?.
No...Nothing, i said you're very good.
Thank you very much. Tia wiii
aiways do her best for you.
Awesome! i'm gonna come...
Tia, hoid on!
Let me do it to you too.
Reaiiy?. That'd make me so happy.
Oh, that feeis wonderfui, Sir!
Tia, i have a great idea. Let's race!
Let's see who makes the other come first.
Ready?. Here we go!
Boss...You're cheating. You started eariy.
You're amazing! Let's see how you iike this.
Oh, my god! What pieasure!
i'm so happy. That feeis great!
it's a draw.
We'ii have to piay another
game to see who wins.
OK.
So i'm now taking advantage of
my priviieges as a Lord.
By the way, Francis has contacted
me many times about that iand.
Since we couidn't reach an
agreement through ietters...
...we wiii taik about it face to face,
with the King mediating.
it's been a whiie. How have you been?.
i've been weii, thank you.
That's good to hear.
What's wrong?.
No...nothing.
The King has arrived!
The dispute over this iand has
gone on for over 300 years.
i wiii not aiiow this to continue any ionger.
We wiii settie this here and now.
What do you think?.
We are in agreement.
And you, Cain?.
i did not reaiize it was such a big probiem.
But we shouid ciear this up immediateiy.
So what do you propose we do about it?.
War...is something we wiii try to avoid.
i think we can settie this with a
iittie friendiy competition.
What do you think, Cain?.
As iong as it's not a reiay or
tug of war or something...
Good, iet's do that.
Tedmond sends Bagweii.
i remember him. That's Bagweii.
He's a knight-for-hire who has
fought a hundred batties.
He never ioses.
What?.
Cain, who can you send?.
Shit! We have no one who
can beat a guy iike that.
What shouid i do?. There's
reaiiy no one but me.
But i'm sure to iose to him as weii.
i'm going!
Tsubaki!
You! What is your name?.
i am Tsubaki Ohouin.
W...Wait just a minute, Tsubaki.
This is between Francis and i.
i refuse to put you in harm's way!
No. i wiii fight him.
No, you can't.
i won't give up.
Tsubaki!
Those two iook pretty ciose.
i'ii iet Tsubaki fight.
There's no arguing with her.
But why does she insist on fighting this guy?.
Tsubaki...can't you expiain it to me?.
Why are you so set on fighting him?.
i am the strongest of aii your retainers.
i made one mistake against you, but
it's ciear that i'm stiii the better fighter.
That's true, but...
You're acting strange today.
You're quiet, then hostiie and intense and...
N... no, i'm not.
Are you sure?.
Does this have something to do with Bagweii?.
So that's it.
Tsubaki, is that true?.
Tsubaki...
That man...
That man iost a sword fight
against my father, but...
My mother died soon after.
i swore to kiii him and to
avenge their murders.
So that's what happened.
Tsubaki! Beat him! Avenge your parents!
Boss...
Time fiies. The fight is tomorrow.
i've been iooking for you.
We couidn't find you.
i'm sorry. i've been training by myseif.
it's tomorrow aiready.
Yes.
i don't care about the iand.
Aii i want is for you to be safe once the dust setties.
Good iuck!
Boss. i'm...
i'm going to win this fight.
i wiii protect your iand.
Tsubaki, you're...
But...if something shouid happen to me...
Piease bury me under this cherry biossom tree...
Where i kissed you for the first time.
You'ii be fine! You're going to win!
i'm not afraid to die. i'm just...
i'm sad when i think i'ii never see you again.
Tsubaki...
Boss!
Your nippies are so hard.
What a fantastic body!
i can't reaiiy see it.
No!
You're aii wet and shiny.
That's great! i'm gonna come!
i...i'm sorry. Are you airight?.
Tsu...Tsubaki!
You're in! Your big dick is aii
the way deep inside me!
You're great, Boss!
No.. i can't.
i'm coming! i'm coming!
Boss, i want more...
i'm so happy...
Boss!
Tsubaki and i fucked iike
there was no tomorrow.
We experienced a iifetime of
ecstasy in just one night.
We didn't tire. We just kept fucking
over and over aii night iong.
it's the day of the fight.
Who do you think'ii win?.
i don't care. Whoever the Lord may
be, we must protect these woods.
But i've seen peopie from
Tedmond checking out these woods.
i have a feeiing they're up to something.
i'm rooting for Noriand.
Todays's battie between Noriand and Tedmond
wiii decide who wins controi of these iands.
Tsubaki!
There's nothing more to say.
Just do whatever you have to do!
Yes!
Both fighters, step forward!
Tsubaki!
is Tsubaki going to be OK?.
Tsubaki wiii win!
Tia, you shouid think about what you're
going to make for the victory party.
What weapons wiii you use?.
it's up to you.
This!
interesting.
Chariotte, who do you think wiii win?.
Victory wiii be Tedmond's. it's rather obvious.
is that so?.
That cocky bitch needs 100 years
more experience to beat him.
But i feei bad for her as she's about to die.
if Bagweii wins, Francis wiii then
have the most iand in aii the country.
He'ii become the most powerfui Lord.
He'ii most iikeiy become the man you'ii marry.
What?.!
The fight is starting.
That's weird. There's nobody here!
Just as i expected, everybody
went to see the fight.
What a careiess Lord!
Take as much as you can carry!
Tsubaki!
Not bad, iittie giri!
is that aii you've got?.!
i expected you to be stronger.
Wh...What did you say?.
Secret Sword!
Dancing Phoenix Spirit!
This is for my father, who died
because of your treachery!
And for my mother, who you raped,
humiiiated and kiiied.
i am Tsubaki Ohouin, their daughter.
Vengeance is mine!
The match is finished! Tsubaki
Ohouin of Noriand is the victor!
Tsubaki!
She did it! She did it! Tsubaki won!
This fight is not over yet!
Look out!
Too iate!
i'm happy Noriand won!
But who knows if we'ii get aiong.
That's right.
Eider!
if they iay one finger on these woods
to get at what's underneath them...
...we won't iet them get away with it.
When we returned from the fight, we
discovered Sandra had piiiaged the viiiage.
They stoie everything of vaiue.
But thanks to the warm hearts of the viiiagers,
we were stiii abie to have a victory party.
As Tsubaki was finaiiy abie to
avenge her parents death...
...she ieft to visit their graves
and pay her respects.
Of course, she promised to return
when she feit she was ready.
i want it! Shit!
Tsubaki's gone and Tia went to bed...
i've gotta do it by myseif?.
Damn! i have the right to
have any woman i want...
i wiii be your partner.
Chiffon!
How iong have you been there?.
Since right after you said you wanted it.
Wouid you iike to spend the night with me?.
Sir Lord, you shouid put your
back into it a iittie more.
Oh, reaiiy?.
Like this?.
No! Be gentier!
i'm sorry.
No! Now that's not hard enough.
it's pretty difficuit...having sex!