The Fearful Fivesome had the helm of
this school after the principal left.
After I experienced their bullying,
I almost lost my passion for teaching.
Then Marimo, the student president,
came along and saved me.
With her support,
I made my best effort to...
...banish them from
our school one by one.
My first target was the
Japanese teacher, Miki Kannonji.
The next one was Mayumi Onijima,
the coach of the swim team.
Our strategy was successful.
They became a laughingstock among
students, and left the school.
Sextra Credits: Credit Two
If feels so good.
Professor, please, screw me hard!
Like I did to Miki and Mayumi?
They are worth nothing.
You are mine, so do it hard, please.
You are one naughty student president.
Your dick is filling me up from behind.
I feel it...
Professor! Professor!
Your big, hard thing is
moving inside of me...
Professor, I can't take it anymore...
Professor!
I'm coming!
Three more remain.
Their behavior was unusual.
Someone might have plotted this.
A plot?
Yes, someone is planning
something to entrap us.
Are you serious?
That's not impossible.
If this person ousts us,
the school will be under his control!
But who could do this?
That's what I was asking myself.
No one on the school board
is brave enough.
And nor is Professor...
Come on! Monkey?
You can't be too careful about this.
Pay attention to things
around you, okay?
Yes.
See you later.
Rui Mizuta and Kaori Aizaki...
It may not be too far-fetched
to think that they are...
A freshman?
What is he doing there?
Do you eat your lunch here every day?
Yeah, well, I feel comfortable
being by myself.
Do you think I have a problem?
Well, I don't think so.
I just thought that
you might feel Ionely.
I'd rather be here.
This place relaxes me.
He is also an outcast...
He reminds me of how I used to be.
You're unbelievable!
You were looking at
this crap during class!
Shame on you!
I would say that you lack good taste.
I can't overlook this!
Come to Chemistry lab after school!
Do you hear me?
Yes.
What will you do, Kaori Aizaki?
Take off your clothing,
your underwear too!
This art teacher is a freak!
Do you really think you can
learn about the depth of true love...
...from this porn mag?
Put away that filth!
We'll show you real love and sex.
Observe well.
You won't bother looking at
that filthy magazine after this.
What are you doing?
Don't touch yourself!
Lick me more...
Lick me harder...
You taste so good, Rui.
Please, give it to me.
So good...
That's my spot, around my clitoris.
Rui, you are so beautiful.
Your private parts are accepting me
and squeezing my fingers.
Don't say such things...
Your pussy is mine.
Yes, I am all yours.
I want more. More!
I can't hold it any longer.
I'm coming!
Damn, it's hot!
Professor Aizaki,
my dick couldn't be harder...
I can't take this any more.
Rui, suck his stinky, dirty dick!
What? No, I can't do that!
Don't worry, if you love me,
there's nothing to be afraid of.
I'll love everything about you now.
No, it stinks!
Trust me, go ahead.
Don't touch there...
Sister!
Poor student...
But I can't leave now...
I guess I have to edit him out.
Come over here.
And put that ugly thing inside her.
I'm sorry, Rui, but this stimulates
our love, doesn't it?
Sister!
Why does she do that to me?
Professor Mizuta...
Oh, Sakagami.
Are you here with a boyfriend?
Well, you see, Professor,
I'm not interested in boys.
Have you noticed that
I was always looking at you?
Do you know what I mean?
Well, I have something to tell you.
I've always admired you...
I love you, Professor!
I got her.
Marimo, you are so beautiful.
I want to be with you forever.
Shame on you, you're nothing but a
hypocrite, pretending to be a teacher.
Judgment day is approaching.
What is that noise?
Are you crying?
What are you doing over there?
Damn!
Run!
Are you okay?
Yes.
What is this?
Aizaki, they are engaging
in Illicit sexual activity.
It's not right for an instructor and
a student to be doing such a thing!
It's absurd!
I can't overlook this!
I'll help you. They deserve punishment.
Well, my guess is that Sakagami
is the one to be blamed.
She must have seduced Professor
Mizuta.
Otherwise Mizuta would
never do such a thing!
Maybe that's true.
We can't put anything past
young people these days.
Right, she needs to be put in her place.
What do you mean?
Do you think you can kidnap
Sakagami and train her?
What?
Don't worry, you aren't alone.
I know someone who would help us.
Yes, she is coming.
Are you sure I can have sex
with the student president?
Yeah, I'll let you go first.
Hold her down, and pull her in quickly.
Yes, Sir.
Here she comes.
Yes!
My dream has finally come true!
I'm gonna have sex with Marimo!
Ouch...
Now you will be sent to
prison for attempted rape.
We're here to investigate Kaori Aizaki
and Rui Mizuta for the school board.
Sister, where is Marimo?
What are you talking about?
Don't give me that!
Marimo called me, and told me
that you kidnapped her.
She called?
Monkey told me that
he and my slave got rid of her...
I've already recorded your
Illicit sexual activity on tape...
...and Aizaki's dreadful plan as well.
I'll prosecute you two for your crimes.
What...
What have you got to prove it?
The video tape is not enough?
Hey...
Now your slave has become
our key witness.
Please, don't do that...
I'll do anything.
You go first.
You don't need to hesitate.
She is a masochist.
Do whatever you want.
Please stop it!
Shut up!
Ouch!
Isn't it fun?
This one too!
Please, stop it!
How do you like being treated like this?
You hypocrite!
You shall feel the pleasures of hell!
Rui...
Look.
You feel pain first, but seems
like you're turned on by that.
That's a masochist's nature.
How about this?
Please stop it! You are
going to stretch my clitoris!
Please stop!
No!
But you are so wet down there.
You came already?
Okay, stop the vacuum and
use the special lotion next.
It'll make you feel so good
that you might just pass out.
This is a mixture of wasabi,
mustard, and Tabasco.
Please, I'll do whatever you want me to!
Your clitoris got so big.
I don't know if anyone
will marry you now.
It's starting to work!
It'll be so hot that you won't
be able to control yourself.
You'll beg me to make you feel better...
It's hot, it's hot!
Please wash it off!
It's burning! It's burning!
Okay, this is the final touch!
It's hot!
The inside of my pussy is burning!
Please, someone wash it off!
It's burning! It's burning!
Why don't you do for yourself?
My pussy is burning!
It hurts! Someone help me!
Look at that, she is
getting wet again, you slut!
Now it's your turn, you wretch!
What happened to that attitude
when you were teasing students?
I'll let you experience
something special.
Bring that bottle!
It seems like you really hate men.
So, why don't we clean all
of your holes with this now?
Let's start with disinfecting your body.
Doesn't it feel like both your
body and soul are cleansed?
Please stop it! It's making me feel hot!
Fill her mouth with your dick
and shut her up.
If you bite, there'll be
severe punishment.
Well, this reminds me of
the Beauty and the Beast.
You made fun of me!
Damn it!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Professor! I'm coming!
Already?
I'm sorry, I haven't
gotten off for a long time.
It must be so sticky then.
Why don't you try the other hole?
But save the ass for me!
Yes!
I'm going to throw up...
You're gonna take that?
You should not judge
people by their appearances.
You are not educated
enough to be a teacher.
I'll insert my dick deeper then.
Oh you are getting wet, teacher!
Your body is honest.
Can I come inside of you?
I'm coming!
No! Don't do that!
Please, don't do that!
I don't want to get pregnant!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
This is a gift from me!
My sperm to your womb!
No!
What happened to me?
It's my turn now.
What is this feeling?
You will not forget the taste of men.
This is always the tightest spot.
I feel so strange...
Why? Why do I feel like I want more?
See, your pussy is twitching.
Your students will look down on you!
That's good.
This is punishment for tricking
a student into a trap.
Why don't you be a slave for a while?
I'm coming soon!
Let's finish together!
Professor! Professor!
Go ahead, you can come in my mouth.
You are so cute,
you can come over my face.
Put yours in here.
Professor, I...
Yuma.
Professor.
You are doing great, Yuma...
Professor, I feel so good!
Kyoko, it's over now.
Is he...
Professor!
Oh did you finish yet?
Yeah, I'm done.
I don't know if I'll need to use it,
but I got the evidence anyway.
Maybe Kyoko is a victim too.
I'll have a long talk with her tomorrow.
I'll try my best even though
the fight is getting harder for me.
To return this school back
to the way it used to be!
That's my professor!
Hey!