My name is Jotaro Saruwatari,
I'm a teacher in this school.
The chair I'm sitting in right now
is called the Monkey's Chair.
Why am I sitting in this chair?
Because the "Saru" in my last name
means "monkey."
These women are powerful
figures in this school.
They find excitement in bullying me.
Other faculty and students
call them the Fearful Fivesome.
Sextra Credit: Credit One
What were you thinking,
apologizing to a student?
It's sad to see how teachers have
lost authority over their students.
Teachers like you are
a menace to education!
I've never heard of a teacher
who kneeled down on the ground...
...before their students!
You are nothing but a
monkey, just pathetic.
Shame on you!
Listen, Professor Saruwatari...
You are not to teach from now on...
Instead, you must visit our classes
to learn how a teacher behaves.
You can't do that.
I will lose the students' respect.
Think of this as punishment.
You should take this time
for self-examination!
I missed the days when
the old principal was in charge.
I wanted to be a teacher like the ones
you see in after-school dramas.
But the principal still
highly valued my passion.
Then he became sick...
...so Vice Principal Migiwa
was put in charge of school.
Everything has changed since then.
Are you listening, Mr. Saruwatari?
Yes! Of course!
Marimo Sakagami?
What is she doing here?
Did she come here to
watch me being bullied?
To watch them having
their fun at my expense...
Wait, she is always around
when something happens.
She must be the snitch.
Being student president
must have gone to your head!
They may fire me after all...
...but I'll never forgive you...
Just you wait, Marimo Sakagami!
She should be coming soon.
No!
Please! Don't do it!
Please, no!
Someone help me...
Be quiet, before I kill you!
This is punishment for what you've
done.
It's time for you to
atone for your sins.
I'm curious to see our student
president's private parts.
It seems pretty tight.
No...
How do you feel now?
I want to show my appreciation to you.
Damn, it feels good.
I'm coming inside of you!
No! Please!
I'll get pregnant!
Please, stop...
No!
How do you like the
taste of your own pussy?
Suck it hard.
I'll let you experience something
you've never experienced before.
It's called humiliation.
Damn, I'm coming again.
And to finish it off...
Oh no, it's too big for me!
Please forgive me!
You'll rip me apart.
It's Mr. Saruwatari, isn't it?
Why did you do this to me?
I know you've been ratting
me out to the Fearful Fivesome.
They've humiliated me.
But I'm leaving the school!
No...
That's not true...
I just had a crush on you...
You must be lying...
No way...
What have I done?
I'm sorry...
It's too late, isn't it?
I really like you, Professor Saruwatari.
I've been worried that you might
leave school someday because of them.
Sorry, I don't know what to say.
Then let them pay the price.
I want you to take revenge on the
Fearful Fivesome...
...drive them from school!
Please bury them with your hatred!
I'll help you!
Remember how you used to be!
You taught us to have passion for
everything we do, Professor Jo!
Professor Jo...
That's what students
used to call me back then.
Have you prepared the midterms yet?
That's how I started
planning my revenge on them.
My first target was her.
Ms. Kannonji gets intoxicated if
an airplane flies by during class.
Then she tells students to study on
their own and leaves the classroom.
Restroom?
No, Captain...
Is she masturbating?
During class?
Oh no, Captain.
Your dick is too big for me.
It's hard and tastes good, Captain...
Give it to me...
Please, put it inside me, now.
I can't hold it anymore...
It feels great, Captain!
Give me more, I want more...
Captain!
Wow...
I want you to tell her that
you want to be a flight attendant...
...and meet her at the infirmary
in the old school building for advice.
Why does she want to meet me here?
Ms. Sakagami...
That's strange...
So you've got a flight attendant fetish.
Oh that's my spot...
Do it hard, Captain...
Good...
please, co-pilot, put that
thick one in my ass...
It feels so good...
I'm coming...
I feel so good. I'm happy!
I'm flying! I'm flying!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Why are you here?
Quite a show, Ms. Kannonji.
Ms. Sakagami...
You call yourself a model teacher?
You couldn't even cut it
as a flight attendant!
How dare you say that?
How dare I?
You are nothing but a nympho!
I'll make sure the whole school finds
out!
See if you still can talk to me
like that afterwards.
Mr. Saruwatari, are you threatening me?
No. I'm just talking to myself.
I'll show people what
kind of role model you are.
A lot of the boys will want to
become pilots because of you.
Please don't tell anyone.
I'll do whatever you want me to.
I'm about to burst.
Take care of this first.
You shouldn't play
with yourself so much.
Oh no, I'm coming again...
I'm coming, I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Look at me, everyone.
After the incident, Miki Kannonji
decided to leave the school.
Four of the Fivesome remain.
The next target is Mayumi Onijima.
She is the gym teacher
and coach of the swim team.
Mayumi Onijima is in
charge of the swim team.
She is a big-sister figure
to swim team members...
...especially the boys.
I believe there's a secret behind it.
Mayumi, what is your secret?
Professor Saruwatari.
It is prohibited to watch swim practice.
You aren't even visiting
classes like you've been told.
You are the worst professor
I've ever met.
If you have time to peep
around, go clean the campus!
But, what about my class visit?
It wouldn't help the likes of you,
anyhow.
Hurry up and go clean.
Okay, I'll do it...
I'm doing it right now!
Okay, that's it for today.
You can go home, except
those on cleaning duty.
Now now, don't be so hasty.
It smells good...
If you do it like that,
I'll come too soon!
I didn't know she was
whoring around with students!
Let me taste your delicious come.
I will train you to win the
national swimming championship.
Come inside me, on my face,
all over my body!
I can't hold it anymore!
I can come inside of you today, right?
I want to come inside of you.
Yes baby, I want it all!
I'm going to come in your ass!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming too!
She may act like a passionate
coach, but she is just a slut!
Who is she to lecture me about morals?
You'll learn what
happens to hypocrites.
What does that monkey want from me?
A class president like you should
know to stay away from him.
He is just so annoying.
He was so creepy
watching swim practice...
Is he interested in me or something?
Monkey! What do you want?
Why did you bring me here?
I'm busy now!
I won't take that much time.
I found something interesting.
There are over 20 bottles, with
someone's fingerprints on them.
You can't hold that against me.
There's no evidence.
Things will get worse if you
don't cooperate with me.
Good girl...
Marimo, come over here.
Ouch! Stop it, it hurts!
No!
I got this smooth skin
from the semen of young men!
I need to disinfect you.
You are already wet.
I need to teach you
how to instruct someone.
I feel yours inside of me.
Please give it to me hard.
Professor...
Do you want this so bad?
Yes, give it to me!
Pour it over me!
Sacred semen from young men...
Please cleanse me with it, now!
Okay, but I'll give you this one first.
No, it'll rip me apart!!
You're exaggerating.
It went in smoother than I thought...
Maybe it wasn't big enough.
I feel so good!
Please give it to me!
Pour it over me!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
This is the punishment of God.
You have to apologize to the
students for being a hypocrite.
You got it?
I forgot to tell her
that this is horse semen.
Three of the Fivesome still remain...