It first began when the strange
incident occurred that day.
It was peaceful until then...
Yes, until that time...
I'm Yumi Hachiban. Pleased to meet you.
However...
Ever since the day I was led into the
world of this mysterious video tape,
inside it my long suppressed desire
for Yumi grows ever stronger.
No!
My humiliation of Yumi...
The guilt of the me that's not me doing such things,
and the yearning to see all of Yumi...
The desire seems to keep growing.
No!
How cute!
Excellent reaction!
That was just a little warm-up.
Now, I'm gonna give you a lot more!
I'm cumming!
They had begun that day,
the lewd dreams which had tarnished me.
Naively watching the mysterious
world of the video tape...
"You're a slave, Miss."
There I was, watching the humiliation
of onii-chan's girlfriend.
Stop it!
Wonderful expression, Miss Kaori!
The occurrence that has ruined me and changed me...
Wonderful expression, Miss Kaon!
No!
Stop!
I'm cumming!
These things would never have come
true if only I had endured it.
But, my feelings toward onii-chan which I kept hiding
are beginning to dominate my dreams.
Big Brother is ashamed...
I wonder why I have to come along
on your date with Nobuhiro?
Sorry.
After Nobuhiro confessed to Yumi,
Kaori and I end up accompanying
them on a double date.
But hey, going out with him might be a good thing.
After all, he's not a bad guy.
Y-yes.
Onii-chan, you really think so?
Well, he's my friend..
But, those weren't my true feelings.
There was a faint flame of jealousy within me.
The night before,
I was agitated by a conversation
with Nobuhiro over the phone.
"I've confessed to Yumi, but I have no confidence
on my first date. Can you come along?"
After agreeing to his request,
without any reasons for being mad,
I escaped into the world of the video tape.
This place is...
the school's science lab?
I'm wearing a lab coat.
Have I gone into a different world again?
Ruri, since you've come this far, just go for it!
She's right, Ruri.
You've always said that it's fine
if it's with sensei, right?
Yumi is different from her usual appearence.
Y-yes...
Even Kaori is wearing a uniform.
Don't hold back just because it's sensei.
There's nothing wrong in doing this since you like him,
right?
B-But...
She's absolutely right. Let's go inside.
Excuse us!
Excuse me.
O-oh! Pardon me...
What is it that you girls want?
I could hear your voices all the
way from here, you know?
Oh? Really?
That makes it easier, doesn't it?
Hey... Are you really sure about this?
Well, of course!
We've come this far, there's no turning back now.
They look as if they've switched personalities.
So, Sensei, please take good care of Ruri.
What?!
We'll be waiting outside.
Hey!
What is it? If there's anything
you want to say just say it.
N-no...
B-but...
It seems like you are seriously
in need of a little magic,
to make you more assertive.
Y-yes...
Then go lie on top of that desk over there.
Yes.
What am I trying to do?
Ermm.. sensei, this is...
Preparations for spellcasting.
Trust me, and do as I say.
Yes.
What a great sensation!
U-um...
You don't want me to do this?
If I don't touch your pussy, the spell can't be cast.
I'm embarassed..
If the spell works, the embarassment will disappear,
and you'll become more assertive.
Unless you want me to stop?
No. Please...
The spell is about to take effect.
Sensei, I...
can't hold it much longer!
Do you want me to insert this thing into your pussy?
I don't know.
You've done it before, haven't you?
Th-that's...
Or do you want mine?
B-but...
This is my first time.
But, judging by the conversation in the hall just now,
it sounded like you wanted this.
Erm...
Am I wrong?
No.
I think it's about time the spell took effect.
Please...
Good. That's the way to be assertive.
Alright. Go ahead and suck my dick,
and I'll lick this cute pussy of yours.
Wow! It's so big!
Delicious!
The hot pussy lips and the inner flesh feel so nice!
Your juice tastes wonderful, too!
You're doing great! Great!
Even if Ruri insists for me to do it,
how can I do this to her?
Please... Please give it to me!
Here goes...
S-sensei!
Good, Ruri! Ruri!
It feels greeeeeeat!
Thank you very much for the magic.
Yo, Yuuto! Sorry about this.
Good afternoon, Yumi-chan.
Good afternoon, Kaori-san. Sorry...
I kind of feel bad for Yumi-chan.
If I had more self-confidence, then I wouldn't
have needed you two to tag along.
That's right!
That's right.
S-sorry...
No... It's my first date, too.
I didn't know what to do either.
I'm very thankful that Kaori-san agreed to this.
Come to think of it,
going on a date in a park at
your age, this is so like you.
Is that so? But I can see a lot of couples around here.
Let me tell you, they only come here to
have a meal, or to play around,
or to take a break along the way.
Yuuto! You could have told me this earlier.
Heh! I just thought Yumi and you
are well-suited to this kind of place.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sorry, Yumi-chan...
Not at all, I think this is kinda fun.
Alright, alright. Line up, line up.
This is your date, isn't it?
You should walk closer to each other.
Don't get too close to her, Nobuhiro. That's my Yumi!
I'm only doing this just because I don't want
these feelings I have for Yumi to be known.
I'd even show you the video tape of Yumi if I could!
Yuuto!
Those two look kinda great together, don't they?
You really think so?
What's with her?
She won't even face me.
That's right. Our relationship
became strange last time.
If things go well with Yumi and Nobuhiro,
would that mean it's the end of my "affair" with Yumi?
Perhaps this is the best way to
hide my feelings for Yumi, but...
Because I don't want others to know
the feelings I have for onii-chan,
because I know that it's wrong,
I accepted the date with Nobuhiro-san.
But, my true feelings were the same as the
other me that I saw in the dream last night.
Ever since that day,
whenever I watch the video
tape before going to sleep,
the confusion I feel in my waking life clears up.
But, it s also a scary world where
I don't exist as myself.
My feelings for onii-chan always
lead to embrrassing situations.
Hmm...? Where is this?
It looks like a hallway in the school I graduated from.
Ruri and Kaori are there, too.
We're wearing the same school uniforms.
Huh?! What am I saying?
...fine if it is with sensei, right?
I see, I'm inside that dream.
There's a me that's not me.
Let's enter.
Excuse us!
Excuse me!
0-oh! Pardon me...
What is it that you girls want?
I could hear your voices all the
way from here, you know?
Oh? Really?
That makes it easier, doesn't it?
So, Sensei, please take good care of Ruri.
What?!
We'll be waiting outside.
Hey!
Oh! Leaving Run alone in there? What am I doing?
...﻿how about you, Yumi?
I'm a little worried. I'll wait here.
Is that so? Well, tell me the results later, okay?
Okay.
Sensei!
If you want me to cast the spell, then do as I say.
Okay!
Just what kind of spell is onii-chan trying to cast?
Sensei!
Who's there?!
It's me.
Right! I gotta stop them!
Yumi!
Peeping? That's some hobby you got there.
Sensei, what's is this magic you mentioned?
It's a magic to make the shy Ruri more assertive.
That kind of magic... I wish he
would cast it on me in reality!
But I don't want the onii-chan in this dream.
I can't stand him.
It seems like the mood in here is completely spoiled.
Then why don't we change places, Sensei?
Follow me.
What am I trying to do?
Yumi?
Are you done?
Why are you here?
It's like this... We re going to cast a spell on Ruri
so that she'll be forward about her feelings.
Huh?
So that's it. The toilet might be a good place.
Sensei?!
Onii-chan!
Peeing in front of everyone is magic, too.
That's... too embarassing.
This is for your own good, Run.
No!
This sounds interesting!
Onii-chan, stop it!
No!
Finally... Do your best, Ruri!
Forgive me!
Don't resist.
I'm the worst...
Kaori, could you take out the thing in my mini-pocket?
Yes.
Here sensei, what do you want me to do with this?
Use it to heat up Ruri's pussy.
No!
Start commencing the spell now!
Yes.
It's hot!
Don't worry. I'll be careful so you don't get burned.
Nooo!
It's getting wet. Ruri is such a slut!
Are you actually getting excited?
Ruri is actually a masochist!
Oh... That's surprising.
Stop it... everyone!
Wow! It's soakin wet.
It looks like we have no choice.
Shall we let her cum instead of peeing?
That also counts as magic, too.
No! I can't anymore!
Haha! It's coming out! It's coming out!
Don't look!
We can see it clearly, Ruri.
Wow!
So this is what urination looks like.
If it was myself, then I wouldn't be able to see.
Thank you, Ruri.
The spell was successful.
Sensei.
What is it?
I love you. I love you.
How disgusting!
This is unforgivable...
The me inside of me isn't human!
It suddenly rained,
and we went to a nearby rest area for shelter.
This is a disaster.
It's just an evening shower. It'll stop soon.
Hey! What are you looking at, Nobuhiro?!
Ehh? No... Uh... That...
Geez!
Yumi, put this on. You'll catch cold.
Thank you.
Sorry, Yumi-chan.
For our date to turn out like that...
Don't let it bother you.
You should take care of yourself
so you don't catch cold.
Thanks, Yumi-chan.
See ya. Bye.
Yumi-chan is such a kind girl!
I copied that mysterious video
tape from Yuuto's room.
At least, with this tape, I can satisfy
my unfullfilled lust for Yumi-chan.
I took a shower, and let my rain-soaked
body be refreshed.
But, when I gave Yumi my jacket,
I'm sure it looked suspicious...
Even though she's just my step-sister,
it would be devastating if anybody
found out my feelings for her,
especially for the innocent Yumi.
The reason I travel into this cursed video tape,
even though it's only for a short while,
is in order to experience that unattainable
relationship that I desire in the real world.
This is school's science lab.
This is the second time I've been here.
It's us.
We look like like we're having fun.
What?!
Nobuhiro is doing it with Ruri-chan.
Sense... is this also magic?
Yes. If you like me, then you should obey me.
Yes. But... this is... too cruel of you.
It is too cruel of me indeed.
How can I let them do this!? What am I thinking?
Wow!
I'm worried about Yumi who is
watching the scene calmly beside me.
It's true that these things are enticing,
but my precious Yumi is nothing like this!
Now Ruri, cum together with Nobuhiro!
Yes.
Feels so good!
Sensei!
Don't hold back and cum... together with Nobuhiro!
Yumi is getting excited too.
Sensei. I... feel weird.
It's nothing weird. That's just natural.
It's our turn now.
I'm going to do it with you.
I've been wanting to do it with you for a long time.
Hey! What the hell am I saying?
Go ahead, sensei.
I don't dislike sensei.
Yumi too?!
Is that so? Then, without reservation...
Hey!
How can I do this?
I don't require any magic.
It's ended over there.
It's our turn now.
Yes. As long as it's sensei.
Feels so good.
Yeah? Me too.
Sensei! Sensei! Give it to me!
Take a good look at it.
This is sensei's...
It's so hot and hard!
Feels good!
This boldness of Yumi, which cannot
be expected from the real her...
The complex feelings of wanting this to
happen, and at the same time not.
Sensei, I can't hold it much longer.
But this is your first time, isn't it?
Are you going to be alright?
Yes, I'll be fine.
I was actually jealous of Ruri when
you cast the magic speli on her.
Really?
Yes. So, please... fuck me hard!
Okay!
Good! Feels so good!
Sensei! Sensei!
Please give it to me... Give me your hot dick!
Sensei, you can fuck me now. I'm feeling great!
Why?
Your pussy is sacred.
So I'll fuck your ass instead.
Understand?
Sensei1
It has loosened just right.
Smells really good too.
I'm feeling hot. I can t stand it anymore!
Here goes.
Sensei!
It's so tight!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
I can't anymore!
Yumi!
Sensei!
I'm being called "sensei" by Yumi.
The amplified desire caused by this video
tape is being unleashed this moment!
Come to think of it,
just what on earth is this video tape?
It displays one's desire,
taking you into a reality of imminent danger.
This video tape will lead the demons
rampaging from the deepest part of hell,
onto the path of everlasting happiness.
That woman who's involved with
the mysterious video tape,
what will become of her?
Will I see hell or heaven?
I can't even predict.
The video tape world I see next,
what will it be?