No!
It's leaking from my ass!
Hurry.
Shove it up my ass!
My ass...
It feels great!
Yay!
Sagayama
My brother is here!
You feel excited when Toshiki
comes to visit, huh, Chiyoko?
Yeah, because he's very kind.
Hey, that means I'm...
...scary!
Very scary!
Hey! Cut it out, Toshiki!
Miyuki sensei is kind too.
R-Really?
Well good luck with
your studies, Chiyoko.
Make sure to follow this
scary woman's instructions.
Yes!
Widow
Here you go.
Thank you.
Is it alright for you to
come and visit everyday?
Don't worry about it.
I'm pretty much free from all the exams.
Chiyoko has been very anxious to
see you ever since she was a child.
Well, I feel the same way too.
Really?
My parents said they were afraid
to even go through the gates...
...of this Sagayama estate.
Maybe it's because they
were rich landowners.
It's what separates the
kids from the adults.
I still feel the same.
Exams huh?
It brings back good memories.
I miss those days.
What's wrong?
Oh, well...
It's been a month since
Satoshi passed away.
You've been wearing a
funeral dress since then.
That's just my choice.
I'll wear it until Satoshi's brother,
Kaoru, arrives to pay his respects.
Satoshi's younger
brother, Kaoru Matsumine...
Chapter 1
Kaoru is originally
from around here right?
Yes.
I believe he was living in the town
next to ours until he went to college.
His family lives there?
No, Kaoru doesn't have any family.
His parents died a long time ago.
I see.
It was just the two of them, so
they went through lots of hardships.
So they're just like you, Taeko.
Not really.
In my case, I had people helping me
out, so I didn't really have a hard time.
I wish I could've done something too.
That's all right.
I'm just happy that you take time out
of your schedule to come and visit.
I just have lots of free time.
Even when I go home, it's not
like anyone's waiting for me.
Shouldn't you go and live with Miyuki?
She...
...is just my classmate.
You two have been in the same
class for a long time right?
I don't know why...
Don't say that.
But I'm a bit relieved.
Huh?
Oh yeah...
I found an old photo
album while I was cleaning.
Huh? Photo album?
It's this picture.
Do you recognize it?
Recognize what?
We played a lot with each other.
Oh, like hide-and-seek,
jumping ropes, kicking stones...
And playing doctor.
What?
Did we?
You don't remember?
N-No.
All right then.
Wait...
So now do you remember?
You touched me like this.
While wearing your panties?
I think you touched inside my panties.
We have to do it like
we used to, don't we?
Go ahead. Put your hand inside.
Inside...
Go lower.
You touched me much lower.
More...
Much lower.
Don't scratch me with your nails okay?
Other than that, you
can do whatever you want.
I understand.
Ah, it hurts. Take it easy on me.
I'm sorry.
No, don't stop your fingers.
Keep moving them.
Okay...
More.
You want more?
Does it feel good?
Yes, very.
W-Wait...
Taeko!
Wait.
This time I will...
Taeko...
It's gotten so hard.
Didn't it hurt?
Ah, yeah...
Taeko.
I can't...
It's okay, let it rip.
Taeko...
Let's climax together this time.
Okay?
How beautiful it is!
It's pink!
Can she be a virgin?
Behind...
Play with my asshole too.
Like this?
Your asshole is very soft.
Good. Good.
My asshole feels good!
Taeko, I can't stand it.
Can I shove my cock up your ass?
Stick it in my asshole.
Please!
Are you ready, Taeko?
My cock is deep into your ass.
Hot...
It's hot!
Me too.
Bang me, bang me more!
Taeko, I'm about to...
My ass...
I'm gonna climax!
Hey! You listening to me?
I was talking all this time
but you were daydreaming...
It seems like your
heart is somewhere else.
Ah. W-well.
I was hanging out with you,
but I woke up really early.
I felt a bit disoriented.
So, what were you saying?
Ugh!
Chiyoko's uncle is
stopping by today right?
You mean Kaoru?
It looks like he's gonna
stay over for a while.
He seems to have a lot
of things to take care of.
He was overseas and didn't attend
the wedding nor the funeral.
I don't think showing up now is
gonna make up for the past, but...
...I guess he just
couldn't leave it alone.
Of course.
Taeko and Chiyoko are the only
ones left in the Sagayama family.
You don't mind if Kaoru
steals Taeko away from you?
What are you saying?
Even if they're not related by
blood, she's still his sister-in-law.
Plus it's her first
time meeting with him.
What, are you kidding?
She lost her husband and is in
mourning.
Then his brother, carrying the
same DNA as her husband shows up...
...and plans to stay under the
same roof for a long period of time.
Are you...
Kaoru Matsumine?
Yes.
I-It's very nice to meet
you, I'm Toshiki Inaba.
She's Miyuki Serikawa.
We are tutors for your niece Chiyoko.
I'm Serikawa. Please
accept my condolences.
I'm Matsumine.
I see, you two are Chiyoko's...
I have met Chiyoko before.
When I came back from overseas one
time...
...she came along with
my brother to greet me.
Chiyoko is very anxious to see you.
Uncle!
Wow! Good morning.
You're late, uncle!
Well, I tried to come early.
Chiyoko, don't be rude to Kaoru.
Good morning.
Good morning...
...or should I say, it's nice to
finally meet you, my sister-in-law Taeko.
It's nice to meet you, too.
The tea is ready.
Satoshi used this room for his studies.
You don't mind staying in such a room?
Not at all.
The room might be useful for
sorting files and paperwork.
May I?
Please.
By the way, did Mr. Suzuki,
your attorney, contact you?
Yes, he did.
He said the paperwork is ready.
I see.
I will go visit Mr. Suzuki
sometime in the afternoon.
Do you want me to come along?
No, I'm just going to
pick up the paperwork.
Plus I need to go visit
my brother's grave.
Can you tell me where it's located?
I'm heading out in just a bit.
Uncle.
Can I come in?
Ah, sure. Come in.
I brought you something good.
Something good?
What is it?
This.
It's a video.
Yep, it's the wedding video
of uncle Satoshi and Taeko.
I see.
Then both you and
Toshiki are in it as well.
Let's watch it together.
It's starting.
VIP seating!
Wait, Chiyoko.
Hey, look!
Isn't she beautiful?
Yeah, she's beautiful.
What...
Oh no, I'm in it too.
I look horrible!
That's not true, you look very cute.
Really?
Really.
But I'm kind of embarrassed.
Well, keep on watching.
It's embarrassing.
It's very touching.
You think so?
But it's somewhat uneasy.
Why am I crying that much?
Hmm...
I wonder why.
Uncle.
What's wrong, Chiyoko?
Nothing's wrong.
Kaoru, I'm coming in.
I thought you might
like some cold beverages.
Oh, Chiyoko.
See you later, uncle.
I see you were awake.
When I came by before,
you were sound asleep.
Well...
Chiyoko brought it over.
Oh, Chiyoko...
May I?
Please.
I was contacted by Mr. Suzuki.
He found some mistakes in the
paperwork...
...so he needs to extend
the meeting until tomorrow.
What is happening to me?
This thirst and irritation...
Just past the large Zelkova tree...
There it is.
That girl...
K-Kaoru!
You're hurting me!
W-What are you...
No!
Ouch!
P-Please stop it, Mr. Kaoru!
Call me Master!
N-No.
It hurts.
Please, stop it!
Call me Master! Master!
It hurts, Mr. Kaoru...
Master...
Please...
Please stop it.
Well?
How is this compared to masturbating?
What is your response?
Then how about this?
It hurts!
Stop...
Stop it!
Really?
You really want me to stop?
Don't stop.
You're telling me what to do? Huh?
Now, clean all that vaginal
juice off my cock with your mouth.
Good.
If you can do it well,
I'll give you a reward.
P-Please, Master.
Hurry.
Please.
Don't panic.
Don't climax yet, we have more to go.
My stomach.
My stomach feels hot!
I'm gonna come!
Master Satoshi!