Widow, Chapter 2
My head hurts.
It's good.
Taeko prepared it, huh?
How nice.
Master Satoshi!
For me?
The postmark for the town, as
well as the sender, is unknown.
I wonder if Uncle is awake.
He seemed very tired last night.
Uncle.
Come here, Chiyoko.
Uncle...
Your fingers are going into my pussy.
Now, I'll make you feel much better.
It's embarrassing.
Uncle...
Chiyoko, you're beautiful.
Uncle!
Uncle, it tickles.
It feels strange.
Uncle, it's embarrassing.
Your pussy's gotten very soft.
I think I can stick
something big inside.
It's okay, you can stick it in.
Chiyoko.
Spread your pussy wide open.
Like this?
Your huge thing...
Is it going to fit inside?
I'm ready, Chiyoko.
It hurts!
It hurts, stop it!
Uncle!
Uncle, please don't move!
I can't do that, Chiyoko.
It hurts, uncle!
It hurts!
Stop, Uncle.
No, not yet Chiyoko.
Now, Chiyoko, let's finish up.
Uncle, let's stop.
I'm ready to come, Chiyoko.
Chiyoko.
From now on, I'm your master.
How many times is it now?
What a sex-craving asshole you are.
It's still wide open
and wanting more.
Don't say that.
This voice and this ass...
It must be.
That's for Kaoru.
You knew I was here?
You're early today.
Ah, well...
You worry too much...
...about Taeko, don't you?
Miyuki...
You're worried about me?
Yes.
Since Satoshi's younger brother Kaoru
is going to be living with Taeko...
...under the same roof for a while.
Hey Miyuki, you better stop...
Good morning.
You're very early today too, Miyuki.
Isn't this a good opportunity
to set things straight?
I'm sure you are aware of it but...
Toshiki has always...
What do you think of Toshiki?
What?
Good morning.
Good morning Chiyoko.
Good morning, Toshiki and Miyuki.
What's wrong?
You don't look very happy.
I feel fine.
Could you go wake up Kaoru for me?
Uncle said he's going out
to search for something.
What?
Oh, I see you were up
very early this morning.
Yes, I went to my lawyer to discuss
the paperwork for the inheritance...
...and I had to run other errands as well.
Did you eat?
I already ate.
By the way...
...where are Toshiki and Miyuki?
They're both tutoring
Chiyoko at the moment.
I see.
We need to talk, but I don't want them to
hear about it.
What is it?
You are aware of the envelope
that was addressed to me, right?
Yes.
I brought it to your room
along with the ice tea.
What do you think was inside?
Well, I don't know...
It was a video.
Video?
It was a wedding video
of you and my brother.
Video huh?
I wonder who sent it.
Well, it's more like footage
taken after the wedding.
After the wedding...
Would you like to have some wine?
Wine at this time of day?
There's an antique
wine cellar on the grounds.
Wine cellar...
...that sounds great.
Which do you prefer, red or white?
Then, red.
Wait one moment, please.
Sister.
May I join you?
Sure.
What's wrong? You look sad.
Huh?
Is it because you couldn't find Taeko?
She probably went shopping.
You like Taeko, don't you?
What do you mean?
Just answer my question!
It's not like that.
Liar!
You're in love with Taeko!
Stop saying that!
I know exactly what it is!
Does it matter whether
I like her or not?
Of course it does!
What Taeko said...
Does it bother you?
You want to know how I
feel about you, Toshiki?
Miyuki...
N-No!
Wait a minute, Toshiki!
What do you mean?
Don't say "no" to me now.
It's not that, it's just...
I wanna go to the bathroom.
There's no bathroom in this park.
Wait right there.
Miyuki!
Toshiki, no peeking!
Go away!
Let me see it, Miyuki.
What?
I want to take a look
at every part of you.
Is that okay?
Everything?
That sounds a bit perverted.
Well, all right...
But you have to let me see yours too.
Are you happy now?
Toshiki.
Miyu...
Miyuki, it feels great.
But don't you have to pee?
I'm fine, I can hold it a bit longer.
I want you to come first.
But after you come,
I want you to go away.
Then I won't come.
Besides, it's not good for
you to hold it in, Miyuki.
But I can't...
Let it out, Toshiki.
Miyuki...
I can't...
Miyuki, are you alright?
I'm okay.
Anyway, I need to...
Please, go away Toshiki.
Don't look.
Now it's time to show your stuff.
It's embarrassing.
Are you satisfied?
Miyuki.
H-Hey, Toshiki...
Ouch!
Don't bite so hard, Toshiki.
Toshiki, not there.
It's dirty.
I didn't wipe myself after peeing...
It's beautiful, Miyuki.
Let me see some more.
This isn't right, Toshiki.
What if someone sees us?
Don't worry.
Besides, don't you
want others to see you?
It's wet.
The juice is flowing out.
No, don't say that!
Are you ready, Miyuki?
Tell me if it hurts.
No, I'm fine.
Miyuki.
It's embarrassing, Toshiki.
Toshiki, I'm connecting with you.
Toshiki, I'm going to...
I'm out of gas too.
It feels good, Toshiki...
Me too, Miyuki.
No, not there!
It feels so tight, Miyuki.
Toshiki, I feel it in my ass.
Do it.
Come, Toshiki.
L-I'm going to...
M-Me too.
Do you like wine?
I like it but...
...I'm more used to drinking
the cheaper wines from the store.
You're just like your brother.
I didn't really have many
opportunities to drink with my brother.
I see.
My brother and I were always busy.
Did you drink with my brother often?
Yes.
It was just...
...maybe a sip or two.
The taste is very rich, and I can
appreciate the great taste and smell.
It's certainly wonderful.
We've had these for a while.
My father loved them.
We still have a lot more.
He was a playboy who
spent all his fortune.
Your family history is very interesting.
I always knew as a kid,
that you folks were rich...
...since you lived on top of the hill.
Coming from a wealthy household
doesn't really mean much.
In fact, it's uneasy and depressing.
My brother died here.
Am I right?
I'm very suspicious
about my brother's death.
My brother was very healthy, yet
he died of acute heart failure.
Plus the video that was sent to me
clearly shows you and my brother.
The footage also showed
these walls in here.
Yes, your brother did die here.
You carried his body out by yourself?
Yes.
I couldn't reveal this
place to the public eye.
What do you mean?
I was going to tell you sooner or later.
What is this place?
Is this my brother's studio?
That's right.
Satoshi built this place just for me.
My brother built this place for you?
What did you put in the wine?
Kaoru...
Welcome to the Sagayama family.