Akiho, look over here.
Uh...
Please don't say my name.
And I don't want
my face to be on tape...
Don't worry, I'll censor your name
and blur out your face on the tape.
Okay...
Looking good, Akiho.
Stop!
What are you doing?
You really thought you'd get
paid just by masturbating?
No!
Your nipples are already hard.
You're very sensitive, aren't you?
No, it hurts...
Akiho...
A-Almost...
I-I'm coming...
Not inside!
I don't want to have a baby!
...baby!
Mom, I'm going to work.
Already?
Yep.
Can't you get an earlier shift?
I doubt it.
I don't want you to come
home late every night...
Somebody has to
work at night, you know?
I guess it's better than
you hanging out all night.
Well, Mom, I'm going now.
Take care.
Akiho?
Akiho, it's me.
We made a video together.
Good to see you again!
I have a friend who lives around here...
You've got the wrong person.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
I'm in a hurry.
Do you know your video is very popular?
Don't you want to do it again?
Hey, wait.
Damn.
Your nipples are already hard.
You're sensitive, aren't you?
Give me more...
You're very wet down here, too...
Harder, harder...
Please fuck me harder!
You are such a slut.
I'm coming...
Please, shoot inside me!
A-Akiho, I-I'm coming!
Yukari, how come you're
wearing sexy underwear?
Aren't these cute?
I know, you have a new boyfriend!
Hello.
Hi, Akiho.
Listen, Akiho.
Yukari got a new boyfriend again.
You slut!
What's wrong, doesn't having a
boyfriend make a girl sexier?
Don't you think so, Akiho?
Well, I don't know...
Don't tease my Akiho like that!
Megumi!
Akiho is too naive to
answer a dirty question like that.
Right, Akiho?
Megumi's doing it again.
Are you hitting on Akiho?
Yeah, so what?
Boys are no fun.
Love should be...
...only between girls.
Akiho, I didn't know you were so sensitive.
What a surprise.
It looks like you
feel the same way I do...
I'm happy, Akiho.
You're so dirty!
It's not like that...
Okay.
Boss, the early shift girls
and late shift girls switched.
All right.
Yes.
Akiho.
Yes?
Boss is calling you.
Thank you...
Did the two girls leave?
Yes.
It's only Megumi and me right now.
Well, let's start then...
Show it to me.
Show it to me!
You've kept it inside the
whole time like I said, right?
Yes.
The battery is dying, it won't
make you feel good much longer.
I'll take it out for you, Akiho.
You made such a mess.
You have to clean it up yourself.
Good...
Since you had the vibrator in all day,
fingers aren't going to satisfy you now.
I'll give you something
better than fingers...
How do you like it, Akiho?
Are you coming?
N-No!
Where is Akiho?
We have so many orders!
It's not my problem,
next order's coming up!
Hey Akiho!
Akiho!
Shit.
Come back and take some orders!
Where are you?
Looks like you've been spared this time.
You can go now.
I'll leave this in here for you.
Yes.
Sorry!
What were you doing?
We're very busy.
You don't look so good, what's wrong?
I'm all right.
You sure?
If you don't feel well,
you should take a break.
L-lt's really okay.
I feel fine, I can work.
L-Let me get that one...
Okay then, would you
take that to table seven?
Y-Yes.
Thank you for...
...waiting.
Hey, it's us.
We're off today.
I knew you were working tonight.
What's wrong?
You don't look good.
Did you get all your orders?
Not yet.
The entree is right here.
Wait!
We just want to know
what you're hiding in there.
If I flip up your skirt, it'll be a great
advertisement, don't you think?
Just as I thought...
Look at this.
Whoa, how can you walk around
with such a big vibrator inside?
Please...
Please, not here...
Customers will see me.
I think you like it when
people look at you, don't you?
Isn't it exciting, Akiho?
Isn't this thrill turning you on?
It was good.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Boss, don't you think
Akiho is acting strange today?
Really?
She doesn't look good.
Oh yeah?
I think you should let
her leave early today...
You just worry too much.
But...
It's kind of busy today...
Okay, she can take a break early.
I'm sure she'll feel better later.
Yes, please.
I'll go to tell her.
Can you take over?
Yes.
It was a good idea to come
here even though it's our day off.
Excellent idea!
No...
Boss, please stop it.
It's my office, nobody will come
no matter how much you scream.
No, no!
Don't act all innocent, you're
the one who was in a dirty video.
Because you like it, right?
No...
From now on...
...you're my bitch.
Understand?
Once you're in a video like
that, it will haunt you forever.
From now on, she'll be our...
...public lavatory.
Suck it!
Hey!
Hey, hey.
Come on!
You guys left me out?
Come on, you know us.
We've been good friends
since college, haven't we?
But Akiho doesn't seem herself today.
She should take a break.
Let's take her to the back room.
That's a good idea.
We'll help you.
Then, let's go.
Akiho.
Aren't you lucky?
Akiho...
Thank you very much.
Now you have...
...two more dicks to suck.
Are you happy?
Y-Yes, I'm happy.
Don't stop, stupid!
I-I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, don't forget mine!
Your clitoris...
...and your nipples,
they look very yummy...
You're really horny, aren't you, Akiho?
Look at her, I can't
tell if she likes it or not.
She tries to hide it,
but she really likes it.
Stop!
You really thought you'd get
paid just by masturbating?
Shit, I'm coming soon!
A-Akiho!
I-I'm coming...
I'll shoot inside!
No...
Please, no...
No, not inside!
I don't want to...
...have a baby!
Boss, we should
break in a new hole.
I think so too.
We all try to use her during the break...
...so some of the guys
don't get a chance.
Really, I didn't notice.
I guess I'm not good enough
at supervising the restaurant yet.
Akiho, there is one more
way you can feel good...
I'll develop you little by little.
Boss, I'm taking a break.
Me too.
Boss, I'll take a break too.
Hey, Akiho.
You just took a break.
Akiho still doesn't feel well.
Boss...
But...
She'll feel better if she takes a rest.
You said the same thing earlier...
Yes, I know a good model.
Her name is Megumi Toyama,
she works in my restaurant.
She is a little bitch
and I want to see her cry.
You should have told me when I
stopped by to give you the video earlier.
You don't trust me?
She wasn't here yet.