You've been such a bad boy!
Making love to someone other than me!
If you ever do that again, you're
really going to be in trouble!
Yes, Nanny.
Touji, I know you're a good boy.
Nanny...
That feels good!
Nanny, can I?
Come here.
Let it all out inside Nanny!
Pour it all inside me, Touji!
You're my baby, Touji.
Don't worry, I'll love
you more than anyone else.
MILK MONEY Chapter 2
I wonder if Marika's still sleeping?
Today's Saturday, so
she's probably sleeping in.
Even so...
Marika! You should get up now.
Marika!
Marika, get out of
bed, for heavers sake!
I'm going to open the door.
I know it's a Saturday,
but enough's enough...
Marika, when did she...
You're my baby, Touji.
Don't worry, I'll love
you more than anyone else.
Mom...
Touji...
Just what's going on
between you? And why?
Marika, what's up?
I have something I
want to ask you, Touji.
Hey, you're scaring me, kind of.
Last night I saw you in the basement.
You and my mom...
Want to come in?
Yes.
Why?
Why, Touji?
Tell me why...
What a terrible thing to do...
I mean, she's my mother!
I've never heard of such a thing...
What am I supposed to do?
I really liked you, Touji!
That's not all, what you did is filthy!
Did you forget that my
mom was your wet-nurse?
Maybe you're not related by blood
but it's still a filthy thing to do!
So you saw us, Marika.
I see...
You saw me and Nanny...
Is that it?
Is that all there is to it?
But then why did you have sex with me?
Why in the world did
you have sex with me?
I'm not sure what to say to you...
I don't know why myself.
But ever since I was a boy,
I've always had a crush on Kyoko...
...that is, your mother.
You might think it's ridiculous...
...but ever since I can remember,
you could say I loved her.
At the time, my own parents
were both busy with their work...
...so I had no one else
but Kyoko to turn to.
But when my mother found out,
she threw Kyoko out of the house.
It was something that
happened all of a sudden.
Ever since that day...
...I've never been able to forget
Kyoko or what she meant to me.
Strange, huh?
Not being able to forget
the woman who breast-fed you.
I'm sure there's something
wrong with me, myself.
Please stop.
Please, I want you to forget my mother.
I want you to fall in love with me!
I'll do anything for you, Touji!
Please, I want you to love me!
Marika...
Touji.
I'm sorry.
No, it's all right.
Thank you for understanding.
Marika...
Touji...
Harder!
Harder, thrust into me harder, Touji!
That's right, just like
you did to Mom last night!
I want you to screw me even
harder, like there's no tomorrow!
Feels so good!
Touji, that feels amazing!
That feels great, Marika.
Touji, your thing is so
hard and tastes so good...
I'm never going to leave your side...
Marika...
Yes!
Right there, right there!
You're hitting my spot!
Touji, I can feel the
very end of your penis!
Yes!
I can't hold it, I'm pulling out.
Touji, your penis is
getting bigger inside me!
I love you, I love you!
I want you to come
right inside me, Touji!
I'm coming!
Touji...
This is for you.
What is it?
That's my good-luck charm.
Good-luck charm?
Yes.
I want you to keep that with you, Touji.
If my mom ever tries to seduce you...
...I want you to look
at that and remember me.
Okay.
TO: TOUJI'S CELL PHONE
TRANSMISSION REPORT: Unable to
complete; unknown address
You won't be able to
contact Touji anymore.
You have no chance.
Marika! What have you done?
What did you tell Touji?
Mom, I want you to calm down
and listen to what I have to say.
What did you do, Marika?
Why did you do it, Mom?
Don't you think it's
a bizarre thing to do?
It has nothing to do with you!
It does, too!
I don't want my own
mother to do such a thing!
Just how much older are you than him?
That's not the only thing.
You're his mother figure, aren't you?
It's abnormal!
Abnormal?
Another thing, I have
feelings for Touji.
I'm in love with him.
I don't want to lose him, even to you.
So please, just don't see him anymore.
Touji's not going to
contact you anymore...
He chose me!
So please, give him up.
Even if you carry on for now,
you and Touji have no future.
It's pointless, don't you see?
You're right.
If two people can't talk
about the future together...
...then it can't
possibly be love, can it?
So you do understand now, Mom?
I won't see Touji anymore.
I'll do just as you asked.
I'm really sorry, Mom, but
I do think it's for the best.
Don't see him anymore, and please
keep that promise for me, okay?
Then maybe someday...
...you'll be able to see him again, and
it'll be like this never happened, right?
Mom, thank you for being understanding.
Well, I'm really tired
so I'm going to bed, okay?
Mom...
I won't have it...
No one will get in my
way, not even you, Marika.
Touji is mine.
I'll never let anyone
take him away from me.
Touji is in love with you?
That's not possible.
I'm the one who raised
that boy on my milk.
How could he possibly fall
in love with anyone else?
Your cell phone's ringing.
It's not mine.
I wonder if it's ringing
inside someone's house?
Oh, that's probably it.
Anyway, I wonder what that kid
Sudoh was doing in a place like this?
He must've come here to see a friend...
The last place he used his credit card
was in that convenience store over there.
Buying cigarettes with a credit card...
Student life has certainly changed.
I guess you're right.
Excuse me, we're with the police.
Would you mind answering
a few questions?
It's dark...
It's so dark.
Oh, I see, so I died.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'm Shinji Sudoh.
I was murdered by your
mother, that's why I'm here.
I'm sorry.
Well, because...
Hey, don't feel bad, it's not
like I have a grudge or anything.
Wait a minute...
Did my mother breast-feed
you too, by any chance?
Yes.
Then you're like my brother, too!
What do you mean, then
there was someone else?
Yes.
What kind of person is he?
Well, I'm not really sure, but to
me he was a wonderful big brother.
Let me guess, you were in
love with him, weren't you?
Well, yes.
Then I hope he gets here soon.
Me, too, but that's a cruel
thing to hope for, isn't it?
That's true.
Hello?
Who is this?
Touji? It's you, isn't it?
I've missed you, Touji.
Nanny, I'm sorry, okay?
That's all right.
Marika's run away from home.
She might not be coming back.
But...
Now you and I can be alone,
just the two of us, forever!
I'm sorry, Nanny!
I'll never do it again,
so please forgive me.
No, that's the second
time you used that line.
But I swear, you're the
only woman I love, Nanny.
Then why don't you prove it to me?
Nanny, you're embarrassing me.
What's the matter, Touji?
You don't seem well today.
Nanny will make you feel better.
That feels good, Nanny.
Nanny...
I've only just started punishing you.
Delicious!
But we still have a long way to go...
This time you're going
to drink me, Touji.
Touji, keep sucking...
I'm starting to get
the shivers all over!
I want you to lick me until I melt away!
My God, what's happening? I feel
something shooting right through my
body!
Now I want you to lick
me right here, Touji.
Okay. I'll do anything for you, Nanny.
Yes!
Nanny, does that feel good?
That's it, right there.
Nanny's shy there, lick me harder!
I'll go even deeper for you, Nanny.
Yes!
Go on, stick out your behind more.
I'll lick you all the way from
your anus to your clitoris.
I'm coming!
The person you are trying to reach
is unable to come to the phone.
Please leave your name and
number within the next 30 seconds.
Marika... Where did you run off to?
That's my good-luck charm.
I want you to keep that with you, Touji.
Please leave a message
within the next 30 seconds.
It's Touji. Where the heck are you?
At least give me a call,
I'm so lonely without you...
Marika...
What are you doing here?
Nanny!
I was just wondering where Marika was...
Stop worrying about that girl,
she'll be back one of these days.
Yes, you're right.
We don't need to worry
about Marika, do we?
Nanny, it hurts! Please, stop!
Please, Nanny?
Touji, you mustn't hide
things from me!
I'm going to make sure you
can never call her again!
I'm sorry, Nanny!
I'll never do it again,
so please forgive me.
I thought you said I was
the only woman you loved!
After all the love I showered
on you, how could you betray me?
You're such a bad boy, Touji!
Nanny...
I'm suffering from this!
Touji, I'm so lonely!
Hurry up and suck it away!
Feels so good!
Touji, you're mine and
mine alone, aren't you?
Right. I don't love
anyone but you, Nanny.
There's no one but you.
That makes me so happy!
Touji...
Nanny.
Nanny, what are you doing?
Stop it, you're scaring me!
This is the problem right here.
This is what made you change from
that sweet boy you used to be.
Nanny, please!
But I have to. This is
a very important thing...
I haven't started punishing you yet.
Nanny, it hurts!
Nanny, it hurts! It's
going to fall off, stop!
It's going to fall off.
Nanny! Please, you've got to untie me!
Oh, no I won't.
You stay right here and think
about how bad you've been.
Touji...
Starting today, this will be the
only food you're going to get.
I'm going to pump out
lots and lots for you!
Now then, drink up.
What a good boy, my Touji.
Such a sweet boy.
Touji, sweetie...
Come on, suck it up!
Come on, suck my milk!
I can't hold back any longer.
Nanny, no, it hurts...
Nanny, it hurts...
Help me...
I want you come right now.
Ow, it hurts.
Now then, come!
Now don't be such a wimp!
I guess I have no choice.
All right, I'm going to
let you off easy today.
Come here.
Is he here?
Yes.
Marika! So you were here all along?
Yes. I've been waiting for you, Touji.
Isn't it strange?
Even though she treated me so cruelly,
I still never hated her, not once.
I know what you mean,
it was the same for me.
Oh, stop it, both of you.
I don't want to hear about my mother.
No, it's important
that we talk about this.
Right.
No matter how cruel she was to me, there
was still that feeling of absolute love...
I knew that she loved me.
That's why, even though I ended up
dead...
...I don't have any hard
feelings toward her at all.
That makes me bitter, but maybe
that's what absolute love really is...
But still I...
Yes?
Excuse me...
We're with the police.
You two are with the police?
Has something happened?
We're looking for this person,
do you know him, by any chance?
We know that he's been
in this neighborhood...
...but we don't know what's become of
him.
No, I have no idea.
I see...
Sorry I couldn't be of any help...
Mr. Shibuya, that pendant...
Right. There's no question.
Detectives?
Ma'am?
Oh, I'm glad you're here, there's
something we want to ask you.
What could that be?