Nanny...
I suppose I have no choice...
Well?
Is it good?
That's it, bite me harder!
Yes, that's it!
Good night, my darling...
MILK MONEY Chapter 1
Didn't I tell you not
to call me anymore?
Are you eating right?
I sent you a lot of food...
Never mind the food, did you pre-order
that game for me like I asked?
Of course, I waited in line all
night and got a ticket for you.
That's all I need to know. You don't
have to call me, just e-mail me, okay?
Even if I e-mail you, you never reply...
Is it good, Touji?
I love your milk the best, Nanny!
And I'm never happier than
when you're suckling me!
So, Marika, have you gotten
used to your new college?
Yes, I guess so.
I think it's going pretty well.
I'm glad to hear that.
Come to think of it...
...I was the wet-nurse for one
of the older boys at your school.
Wet-nurse?
That's right, I used to
breast-feed him, you see.
His name is Touji Ide.
He's two years older than
you, so he must be a senior.
Is that strange?
No, it's not strange, but...
You've heard this story before,
haven't you? About your big brother...
Because he died soon
after I gave birth to him...
...I had all this breast
milk and it was very painful.
So I breast-fed a child
whose mother had no milk.
I knew you were a wet-nurse...
...but I had no idea you were
a relic from the last century...
Why do you say that?
You really should keep this in mind.
You have to use your breast
milk, it's painful otherwise.
Then that means that this Touji Ide
and I are like brother and sister.
Well, I suppose you
could look at it that way.
Can I help you?
Um, is Ide here?
Hey, Ide! Someone's here to see you.
And that's how it came to pass...
...that I went home with my
"milk brother" Touji Ide that day...
Not that I was looking for a boyfriend...
...but since I'd just
broken up with someone...
...I did want a quiet, sweet
big brother type in my life.
I think that's what it was.
Of course, he was
nothing like my dream guy...
...but Touji, who'd never had a girlfriend
all his life, was a little awkward...
...and reminded me of one of
those wimpy heroes in a cartoon...
...I thought he was pretty cute in a way.
There's something about
Touji that's so uncool!
I mean, I envy him,
having his own apartment...
But I wonder why he's
living on his own like that?
No idea...
Maybe I'll go over there
sometime and see what it's like...
Absolutely not!
A boy who lives alone...
You mustn't go to his apartment!
Oh, it'll be all right.
He's the last person
you should worry about.
Why don't you invite him here?
Tell him to come to dinner...
That's right, if I bring him here
that'll give you peace of mind.
Come to think of it, you were raised
on my mother's milk, weren't you?
I wonder if you're so into big breasts
because you were never weaned
properly?
Or is it just that all
guys like big breasts?
Well?
Why don't you shut up?
Ow...
I can't go on anymore...
Why?
Why did you have to die?
No!
Here we are.
Oh?
Why don't you spend the night?
I'll be waiting for you tonight...
Mom, Touji's here!
It's good to have you.
It's been such a long time, hasn't it?
Um, hello.
Yes, it's been a while.
I was still young back then.
Oh, but you're still
as beautiful as ever.
Hey, no need to flatter her!
She's practically your
mother, too, isn't she?
Well, I guess so, but...
The Touji I saw that night wasn't the...
...same gloomy boy I
knew who never stood out.
Could he have been that happy
to see my mom after so long?
To me, he seemed like an
entirely different person...
...someone who was far
off in the distance.
Marika?
Nanny?
Touji, have a good night, then.
Sleep tight!
Thank you, good night!
Good night...
Touji, open up, will you?
Man, I could kill him!
Where have you been all
this time? My darling...
I don't have you to suckle me...
So look, I'm bursting...
Come here, my boy.
Nanny! I've missed you so much!
I've missed you, too.
Nanny...
I don't know if I can keep quiet,
but we can't have Marika find out...
You mustn't do it so hard...
Touji...
Nanny...
Come to Mama...
Oh, I'm going to come!
More...
Can't hold on, I'm going to come!
I'm going to come!
Did you come, Nanny?
I'm not the same person I used to be.
Look at me, I have
the body of a man now.
So warm.
Not to mention it's huge and hard.
Ever since that time, I've
dreamed of this happening someday.
Really? Have you really?
Then that means that
you're mine alone, Touji!
But even if you're all
grown up physically...
...I want you to stay the same sweet
boy I remember when you're with me!
Nanny...
Are you about to come?
You mustn't yet, I want
you to come inside me.
My breasts! Please, touch my breasts.
Harder!
I want you to squeeze
me as hard as you can!
Dig your nails into them!
That's it, do it harder!
Nanny, I can't hold it in any longer!
Then come, please, come now!
Nanny, I'm gonna come!
It's so hard!
Touji's penis is getting
bigger and bigger inside of me!
Touji...
I was wondering if it would be all
right to go over to your place sometime?
But it's really a mess...
Then I'll clean it up for you.
That's my hobby, cleaning up stuff.
I don't look like the type, do I?
But I want to see your room, and...
No, I don't think so.
There's nothing exciting
about my place, I know it.
What's up with that?
Here you have a gorgeous little
sister, creating an opportunity for you...
You dummy, Touji!
E-mail?
Who's it from?
From: Nanny, Subject: None
I miss you, my breasts
are about to burst...
Please come suckle them soon...
So who's it from?
Nobody, okay? It's just my mom.
Really?
Hey, why are you so
interested all of a sudden?
I bought you that new game at
Akihabara...
...and I've sent it
to you by express mail.
Give us a call or
e-mail once in a while.
Your dad is worried about you, too.
So you never contact your parents?
Sorry. I won't do it again.
Wanna come over?
Yeah!
Wow, this is an awesome building!
No wonder you were rich
enough to hire a wet-nurse!
Have you ever cleaned this place?
Nope.
Since when?
Since I moved in, so 3 years ago?
For real?
Oh, Mom?
Where are you?
I'm at Touji's, no need to worry.
Actually, it's a good thing
I'm here to clean it up for him.
There's 3 years worth of
garbage all over the place.
In that case, why don't you bring him
here tonight? I'll make a nice dinner.
You can always do the
housecleaning over the holidays.
My mom says we should come over.
Okay.
Okay, then I guess I
won't stay long today.
There's no place to sit, anyway.
See you later.
Does that feel good?
Yeah.
You've got bigger boobs
than I thought, you know.
Ugh, what are you saying?
Hey, look at the time.
I'd better go home, or I'll
get into trouble with my Mom.
We'll pick this up later tonight!
Dinner will be ready
soon... please wait a bit!
Okay!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Have a lot, there's plenty!
SLEEPING PILLS
Let's eat!
Is it all right if I turn on the TV?
SLEEPING PILLS
Yes.
This is great!
SLEEPING PILLS
Hey, you're right, this is awesome!
A college student who
disappeared one month ago...
What's the matter, Touji?
I wonder what's up with that.
Shinji Sudoh (18)
I don't know, it's pretty scary.
I want you both to be extra careful.
Shinji Sudoh (18)
I have an idea! Touji, why
don't you commute from our house?
Huh? But...
It's quite all right with me, after all,
you're practically Marika's big brother.
As long as you get
permission from your parents...
That's right, it's going to take a
while to get your place cleaned up.
Are you sure it's okay?
Hey, cool! It's a done deal!
The neighborhood's not
as safe as it used to be...
...so it'll give me
peace of mind, as well.
Well, you're not the type
who can rest easy in her mind.
But at least you don't have
to worry about that!
Touji, licking your penis is
starting to arouse me, too.
I'm still a virgin, see.
But I don't mind giving
it up for you, Touji.
Please be gentle with me.
That feels good!
Touji, it's starting
to feel really good!
More thrusting, I want more thrusting!
You've been such a bad boy!
Making love to someone other than me!
If you ever do that again, you're
really going to be in trouble!
Yes, Nanny.
Touji, I know you're a good boy.
Now then, I want you to
comfort your Nanny this time.
That feels good!
Nanny, can I?
Come here.
That's it...
My Touji...
More...
Yes, that's right.
Can't hold it, if I keep
this up, I'll come too soon!
Then come, it's all right.
Let it all out inside Nanny!
Pour it all inside me, Touji!
I'm coming!
You're my baby, Touji.
Don't worry, I'll love
you more than anyone else.