It's very late, my father
must be waiting for me.
Heinrich, let's hurry!
Yes sir!
Dunan is still missing?
Yes.
They say Sho, the son
of the late King Bassen...
overthrew King Randis.
Furthermore, he entrusted the throne
to Teo the Nomad, and departed!
What is all this!?
King Randis's family was spared,
yet Princess Diana is missing.
Is my son Dunan with Diana!?
Well, we could not...
You are all good for nothing!
What have you been investigating!?
Dunan...
You are not good enough of
a soldier to be the Prince of Gupta.
A kingdom that's
celebrated for its valor.
However, if you rule Doria
with your superior intellect...
it will bring infinite
prosperity to our kingdom.
That was the
reason I sent you to Doria.
I was planning to marry
you to Diana. Yet...
Father, I apologize
for being so late.
Marlon!!
You've finally returned!
I'm sorry. However,
I have completed the negotiations...
with the merchants of Saas.
Good work.
We cannot manipulate
Doria by force any longer.
We must dominate
through economic power.
Yes, father.
You are quite right.
The only problem remaining
is Dunan's whereabouts!
Be assured, I will find him.
FENCER OF MINERVA
Chapter 4: The Storm
This is the city of Saas.
Now, this is a real trade center.
Splendid!
Without trade with this city...
Doria wouldn't have
prospered as it did.
Master, let's get down there.
Alright
Don't be so hasty.
But...
OK, let's go.
Right now, Teo must be living
the boring life of a King
You wouldn't
recognize this as Doria!
Really?
I am happy to see
that business is flourishing.
He is definitely King Teo.
Hanna, if by any chance I fail,
report to Prince Marlon.
Yes, brother.
I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
Yes!
Guards from the castle!
Well, well... good work.
Master, you are the King of Doria.
It cannot be helped.
Imil must have sent them.
Yes I did, Sire.
Imil!
Since you became King,
Doria has recovered its power...
and fortune of some ten years ago.
Well, if Sho had stayed, this
kingdom may have prospered even more.
Your Highness!
That is not my point.
We are surrounded by nations
scheming to rob us of our property.
Especially, Gupta from the North!
Imil, not again.
I've heard enough of that.
No, Your Highness!
It is too dangerous to come
into the city without guards!
Assassins hired
by neighboring nations...
could attack you at any time.
OK... OK. Being King
is a boring occupation.
Please understand,
I need to have a good time...
out of the castle
once in a while.
Now, leave us alone.
Yes, Sire.
Please be careful.
A clever man,
but he is too overprotective.
He's very concerned for your safety.
I hear Mr. Imil completed his studies
at the academy with top honors.
He is indispensable
as a royal adviser.
Oh, you speak so highly of him.
That's what you always say, Master.
Right, Fina?
Yes.
I guess it is.
Oh, yes, Fina.
Please attend to Imil,
starting tomorrow.
That's a very good idea.
Ulsra, I was also thinking
about making you my Queen.
What do you think?
I am happy as I'll ever be!
You don't want to be freed?
I'd much rather be riding
in the field with you, Master.
You are precious.
I'd rather be riding, too.
Hey old man!
Three kebabs, and... well, Valna wine.
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Master!
Somebody! Help!
Your Highness!!
Master!
Your Highness!
Your Highness!!
Don't move!
This is lizard poison!!
Lizard poison!?
No, Master!!
Don't leave me!!
Wow, I wonder
what kind of fruit this is?
Look at that!!
Such a beautiful necklace!
I wish I had one like that.
Diana, stay close to me.
You are the most
valuable merchandise here.
If we become separated,
a barbarian merchant can steal you.
If you're put on a ship,
even I won't be able to rescue you.
No! I don't want that!
Even a prosperous and lively
city has its share of villains.
I... I see.
Well, let's eat.
Yes.
Is it checkmate?
No one could beat Seneca.
Well, I haven't played him yet.
You never know.
Forget it, you won't have a chance.
How about it?
Are you ready to give up?
No! Not yet!
He's right.
He can still win.
Don't you think?
No, you'll lose if
you make that move!!
You!
What did you just say!?
I apologize for my
slave's bad manners!
I'm sorry.
I am very sorry!
It's not my position
to make such remarks!
Please, please forgive me!
No, I won't!
You! A lowly slave,
interrupted our game!
It's not something your
master can apologize for!
Then, what can we do
to receive your forgiveness?
Will you be satisfied if
I punish my slave right here?
No... I've made a name for
myself as the Merchant Seneca.
I do not wish to
create a scene in public.
You...
You seem to be extremely
confident about this game.
Do you think you
can win from this stage?
No, please disregard
my earlier remark!
No, you already said it.
That's right, isn't it?!
Right!
We heard it!
She said it!
So now, you will
take over this game.
Is it alright?
Ah, yeah, OK.
That's fine with me.
Naturally, I'll let you
take your bet back.
And in it's place...
you will put yourself at stake!
If you win... if you really can win...
you can have my slave.
However! If you lose,
you will become mine!!
That's exciting!
Do it! Do it!
Understood.
If that's what's required for forgiveness,
Diana will play the game.
Alright, Diana?
Y... yes. If you allow me, Master.
Good!!
Take a seat.
I am honored to be
playing this game with you, sir.
Let's begin.
Picking up from the last move.
Yes.
Oh... I didn't think of that!
Your turn, Sir.
I know, I know!
H... hey, this move is...
from that legendary game!
She knows about that game?
A slave?
There's no mistake about it.
Those are the moves of Lyan,
the Dorian master, when he...
was playing against King Bassen.
Shut up! Damn!
How about this!?
Sir, are you absolutely certain?
Yes, I am.
Then, three more
moves to check mate.
Wh... what!?
It can't be!
I give up.
Hell of a game.
Thank you for a great game.
You're a great player.
I'm overwhelmed.
Tell me, Diana...
where did you learn
to play like that?
I was taught by
Lyan of Doria, for many years.
I see. So that explains it.
You're no ordinary player.
And, you are...
Sho, from Dori... from Pieta.
Sho, you have a great slave.
Take good care of her.
Thanks for your compliments.
Oh, that's our Seneca,
a true gamester!
A deal is a deal.
Take her.
My name is Shiera.
You will not be my slave.
Diana won the game.
Alright!
I'll take her.
A slave takes a slave!!
I never heard of such a thing.
Hey, young man.
You won't be able to sleep tonight.
Nice wench!
Shiera?
Yes, Master.
That's too confusing.
Call me Diana.
Yes, Miss Diana.
You and Mr. Seneca are?
He purchased me a few days ago.
That's not what I meant.
Well, how shall I put it...
Did he cherish you?
Yes, he was a very nice Master.
Only...
It was all my fault.
I wasn't good enough to please him.
That's why he didn't...
Don't think like that.
I'm sorry things turned out this way.
No, please, Master!
I mean, Miss Diana.
I am your slave now.
I will have you, then.
Diana, you!
Please watch us, Master.
B... but...
A slave is not allowed to keep
secrets from her Master.
Take your clothes off.
Such a beautiful body.
Come, Shiera... please me.
Y... yes... Miss Diana.
Please enjoy me.
Pretty Shiera...
Master!
So good... Miss Diana!
Shiera, you want Mr. Sho
to use you, don't you?
Miss Diana... This is so nice!
You can tell me.
No...
Do you want me to ask him?
Yes...
Master, please take her.
Now hold on!
When he lost the game,
Mr. Seneca told you that...
his slave was yours.
Yes, he did... but... I can't take her.
That's all right, Miss Diana.
I... I am... so immature and
unattractive; everyone refuses me.
Wait a minute, Shiera.
That's not what I meant.
But it's true.
Mr. Seneca abandoned me
because I was too ugly.
No, you are exceptionally pretty.
Then... you would use me!
Alright.
It's so... so...
Ah, it's wonderful, Mr. Sho!
Master...
I've been thinking since
that time with Patris...
What is it?
Please take both of us at once!
You've changed so much.
Mr. Sho... Miss Diana!
What?
You want to buy back Shiera?
I am the Merchant Seneca,
one of the biggest merchants in Saas.
I won't be stingy.
I would like to buy
Shiera for 50 gold coins.
50 gold coins!
You will, Master?
Seneca, you seem to
be very attached to this woman.
Ah, well...
Shiera, do you want
to return to Seneca?
Y... yes.
If you would allow me?
Seneca, take her back.
Oh, thank you!
No. There is no
need for you to pay.
It's alright with you, Diana?
Yes, I was hoping this would happen.
I'm happy for you, Shiera.
Your Master
cares about you, after all.
Y... yes.
Go!
Master...
I'm sorry for what I did.
Even though I was
so occupied by the game...
I shouldn't have bet you.
Forgive me.
No, Master, I'm the one
who must be punished.
Last night,
those two used me.
I was drunk with pleasure
for the first time in my life.
What? You?
To the extent that I begged
for more and more.
But you were so inexperienced...
Please punish my lascivious body.
I see, I have to check how
lascivious you have become...
over the course of one night.
OK, Shiera?
Y... yes.
I thank both of you.
By the way, Diana, about the game...
where did you learn
from Lyan, the Dorian master?
When I was serving
at the court of Doria.
I see... at the court of Doria.
Speaking of Doria,
I heard a couple days ago...
that their new King
was assaulted.
Did you hear as well?
What!? Teo!?
Assaulted!?
What about Teo?
Probably dead.
I see. Alberto, I'll have someone
bring the reward to you.
I did not volunteer for a reward.
It was out of my Loyalty
to you, Prince Marlon.
I appreciate your gesture.
I will see to it that your Loyalty
will be well rewarded...
in some other way then.
Thank you for your gracious words.
Then... excuse me.
Prince Marlon.
What is it, Heinrich?
You are not going to treat
Alberto as an equal to us?
Even a man from the lower classes,
such as Alberto, can be of some use.
Don't worry about such trivial matters.
Forgive me for my thoughtless words.
I am so sorry I couldn't do anything.
No, if you hadn't sucked
the poison out from his wound...
he would have been
killed right then and there.
I thank you.
No, it wasn't enough.
And, what did the doctor say?
Don't cry. Teo is a tough man.
He will recover.
Right.
As I have repeatedly mentioned,
Prince Dunan's whereabouts...
are still under investigation.
Mr. Adviser, you have not made
even the slightest progress.
I can't tell you anything as I was
not the royal adviser back then.
Prince Dunan's visit to
the late King Randis was treated...
as a private affair.
Therefore, no official record exists.
A private visit?
How disrespectful!
You're saying a prince from another
nation dropped by to say "hello"!
Well, simply put,
that's exactly what happened.
It 's no use speaking with you!
Isn't there someone
who knows what happened?
I'm afraid not.
King Randis took his own life.
Princess Diana, to whom your
Prince Dunan was to marry...
is missing.
What about the King?
Doesn't King Teo know anything?
I hear he was involved in the whole
incident when Doria was occupied.
His Highness is ill
and has taken to bed.
But, he can speak, can he not?
The truth is, the King was attacked
while taking an incognito stroll...
through the city.
Oh, I wasn't aware of that.
And, how is he?
His life was barely saved.
Oh, that's good.
But, this is bad timing.
Have you not heard about the actions
of the Council of Saas Merchants?
Such as?
They're considering which nations
they should carry on commerce with...
for the next year.
What?
How unfortunate for your
nation that King Teo is unwell.
The representatives from the Council
could pay him a visit any day.
Who was the assassin?
It was
probably an assassin from Gupta.
As I thought.
Thanks to King Teo,
within three short months...
Doria has recovered
its past prosperity.
It wouldn't have been
possible without your support.
That is preposterous!
All I know is what I
learned from books.
The King has encouraged commerce
with the Saas Merchants.
And at the same time,
he ordered the nomads...
to trade mainly in Doria.
Oh, that was very bold of him.
Yes.
No matter how valuable
the merchandise is...
if there's no flow of buyers
and sellers, then it is worthless.
On the other hand,
unless people hear...
that there is good merchandise
and an open market...
they will not come.
Very logical.
Usually, it takes many years
for a city to prosper to this degree.
However, King Teo...
turned it around in a mere month.
The skeptical Saas
Merchants trust him.
The nomads, despite
their flamboyant nature...
gather in Doria to trade rare goods.
He is a brilliant king.
He certainly is.
There is now nothing
you can't buy in Doria.
Merchants rush to our
markets from every city.
Because of that...
Gupta cannot attack Doria ostensibly.
That's why...
Mr. Sho?
What are you thinking about?
If you have any ideas,
please tell me.
But if you do not trust me?
I trust you.
Teo himself appointed
you as the Royal Adviser.
Sooner or later, I'm going
to need your help.
Look at this.
This is!
This is just
between you and me!!
You received it from King Teo.
That means...
He has taken the Oath
of Heroes with me...
and my father before me.
Then, you are brothers, no,
the bond between you two...
is stronger than that of brothers.
Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Sho.
Now, I can tell you everything.
To tell you the truth,
Doria is facing great danger!
I beg you, Mr. Sho.
Please help me find
a plan to protect Doria!
What?
I will,
with all my power.
Thank you.
However, there is one more problem.
The Guptans are desperately
looking for Prince Dunan.
We can't just give any criminal
to them claiming that he...
was the murderer.
Diana!
That was bad.
Diana...
I will go to Gupta.
I am the one who killed Dunan.
Don't you ever mention that!!
I made you my slave
knowing what you did.
But... but, if I don't
come forward, Doria will...
Don't worry!
Nobody wants you to do such a thing.
If I can save Doria
by sacrificing my life, then...
Don't be so conceited!
How can you even think
that a mere slave's life could change...
a country's fate?
If Doria was so vain,
nobody would mind if your life...
was ended right at this moment.
Teo and Imil, and everybody else,
are not suffering for that kind...
of fragile kingdom!
I'm sorry!
It was impertinent of me.
But... it's...
Dee, as much as you do,
we all care about Doria.
The Dorians are
concerned for us, as well.
Y... yes... Master.
Listen, Diana.
If the situation becomes such
that you must die...
I will not let you die alone.
Master...
You are not alone.
Understood?
Y... yes... Thank you.
I am yours, Master.
I will always be by your side.
We will take our leave.
Yes, thank you.
I must finish this
document as soon as possible.
Who's there?
It's me.
Fina.
What are you doing up so late?
I... I thought you must be tired.
I don't drink.
You ought to know that.
But...
Hey!?
Wh... what happened?
Why are you crying?
King Teo has ordered
me to attend to you.
He did!?
But, I guess I'm no use to you.
OK. You can give me
some wine, then.
But, just a little.
Yes, sir!
I never realized that
alcohol tasted this good.
S... stop, Fina.
I could get totally intoxicated.
You don't think you'll be
able to take me if you get drunk?
What did you say?
Please take me.
No! No!! No!!
Do you dislike me, Mr. Imil?
That's not what I mean!!
But...
Wh... what's gotten into you?
Mr. Imil... I am in love with you.
Do you like me?
Well...
Mr. Imil?
Y... yes, I do.
Then, will you accept my obedience?
Tha... that's...
Master... Please take me.
Right here?
Anywhere, as long as
you are with me, Master.
Imil!!
Good luck, Fina.
Mr. Imil will soon be the
Chief Adviser for this kingdom.
Ouch!
S... sorry...
A little gentler.
O... OK.
Like this?
Yes, that's very nice!
It's my first time.
Mine, too.
But, you are the King's...
King Teo has never used me.
He said he would find
a good master for me someday.
He didn't.
But...
I am well trained by Ulsra.
So, I think you will
be able to enjoy me!
I see.
Did I say something wrong?
No, you didn't.
You are very pretty, Fina.
Master...
I am so embarrassed.
Well, it's the first time.
Fina!
Master!
Merchants of Saas!?
What's happened?
How ostentatious.
No, that's the
Council of Saas!!
The Council of Saas
has made their move.
What will happen to Doria?
What!?
The Merchants of Saas!?
Yes!
At last!
Report to Mr. Sho!
Yes!
We are representatives
of the Council of Saas.
We wish to see King Teo!!
Do you have an appointment?
No!
Then, we must schedule one first.
That's all right.
Hello, welcome to Doria.
You must be tired
from the long journey.
The Council of Saas are
very honored guests in Doria.
Please do come in.
Excuse me, but there've been rumors
that King Teo was attacked...
by an unknown assailant.
Yes, he was.
Then, how is his condition?
I will fill you in with
more details inside.
Please come in.
Mr. Imil, I heard King Teo survived.
I would like to see him now.
That was very quick, Mr. Helman.
No doubt, you were informed by
a resourceful messenger from Gupta...
so celebrated for its valor.
It seems information travels fast.
Imil, how is King Teo?
I dispatched someone
to see you regarding the matter...
a short while ago.
W... what?
You did?
I'm so sorry.
It seems that the guards
weren't informed that the King...
wishes to see you before anyone else.
What!?
He does?
Come in, come in, please!
Wha... what?
Mr. Helman,
a messenger from Gupta!!
All hail His Majesty the King,
and Her Majesty the Queen!!
Her Majesty?
When did the King wed?
No idea...
Your Majesty,
members of the Saas Council...
and Mr. Helman from Gupta.
Your Majesty, your complete
recovery gives me great happiness.
My complete recovery?
I am in good health.
It seems there's
some misunderstanding.
Imil, you did not provide sufficient
explanation to our guests!!
This is an unforgivable blunder!
I apologize, your Majesty!!
The fault lies with me.
I dispatched the document
to their room this morning, but...
please forgive me!!
Document?
I haven't received any documents.
You haven't? Oh, no!
That is enough.
The messenger from Gupta is here.
It doesn't matter now.
The order of things is all confused.
Explain the situation to him now.
Mr. Helman, I apologize
for my retainer's blunder.
It's... no matter.
I am very sorry, Mr. Helman.
Please let me introduce
you to His Majesty, King Sho...
appointed by the former
King Teo, who abdicated...
the throne as of today
due to his illness.
The King?
King Sho?
Wha... what?
As you may be aware,
the father of King Sho...
was the late King Bassen,
who once reigned over this kingdom.
That is Sho!!
And!
Imil, I will introduce
the Queen to them.
My Queen, Diana,
is also the child of a former King...
King Randis.
Pleased to meet you all.
Well, Mr. Gigil,
regarding today's main subject...
the trading arrangement with Saas.
Tha... that is...
May I speak on that subject!?
You are!!
Oh, Chairman Seneca!
Mr. Seneca!?
Your Majesty, please forgive my delay.
We, the Saas Council
would like to maintain, or rather...
expand the close
trading relationship with Doria.
The free market of Doria
is a valuable trading point...
for the Saas Merchants.
Is it not?
Yes!!
I look forward to
expanding our relationship!
As do we.
By the way, Mr. Helman,
you said you have a question...
you wanted to ask us?
Y... yes. Your Majesty.
Regarding the disappearance
of Prince Dunan.
I understand your concern.
However, I wonder if this is
an appropriate place to discuss...
such an important matter
between our two nations?
As you say, Your Majesty.
The young must honor their elders.
Why don't we visit King Gauss
to introduce ourselves...
and explain the situation?
I beg your pardon!?
I and my Queen both
have met Prince Dunan.
If we have an opportunity
to speak with King Gauss directly...
we may be able to find
some clue as to where he is.
Mr. Helman, I wish that
you would assume the role...
as an intermediary
and arrange our visit.
As you wish.
Thank you.
We are counting on you.
Please be assured, Your Majesty.
Dismissed.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty the King
and Her Majesty the Queen!!
I am about to
suffocate in these clothes.
You were excellent.
Just as I expected from you
as a former Princess.
I wouldn't have
been able to pull it off...
"Pleased to meet you all".
Ulsra, that's pretty good.
You sound just like her.
Seneca.
Mr. Seneca.
You made a great King
and Queen back there.
I was surprised.
I had no idea you were
the Chairman of the Saas Council.
We didn't know you
were in such a high position.
You saved us.
Thank you!
No, no. I owe you 50 gold coins.
No, Shiera is worth more
than 50 gold coins now.
Since Shiera is back, I am...
Well, as the nomads often say...
"There's nothing better
than a good slave," is there?
Right, that's it!
Well, I'm going to free Shiera soon.
I've had many slaves since
my wife passed away...
but Shiera is like no other.
Then?
Yes, I am going
to take her as my wife.
That's wonderful!!
Mr. Sho, Teo is coming round!!
He is!!
Master...
Get me a doctor.
I said, "Get me a doctor"!
I need to chase this stupid poison
out of my system as soon as possible!
Y, yes!!
Imil.
You clever little boy, how did you
come up with such a scheme?
Thank you.
Sho, Gupta's reaction to all of this,
that's the main issue now.
Exactly, we still have
a long way to go.
In a pair of yearning eyes,
I fall into a dream...
and again the hard
wind blows in.
Turning back the long
way I have come...
the shadows of flowers
are swaying in the wind.
In the sky, a bird cries out...
Although the pain in my
heart brings me down...
with you...
someday...
I hope that our fates will
meet on top of the hill.