Sho! Sho! Be careful, Sho!
Don't worry, Diana!
That's a beautiful knife!
Isn't it? I found it in my father's room.
What's going on, Randis?
Can't you tell, your Highness?
I see you do not agree
with my leadership.
When you promoted me to palace guard,
I did not take the position...
only for your sake.
I'm following in the footsteps you
took five years ago, your Highness!
Dee, will you become
my servant someday?
What? I want to be a princess.
I'm not going to be a servant!
My father always says to make
servants of your most valuable people.
No! I'm going to
become a princess!
I can't be killed now.
Prince, I must take your life.
I was not supposed to take this?
No! It's not his fault!
I asked him to get the fruit!
Sho, he is serious.
Get away! Hurry!
Get away? No one gets killed
just for taking some fruit.
Just go!
Prepare to die!
Sho!
No! Sho, get away!
Get away!
Sho!!
Sho!!!!
Ms. Diana
Are you alright? You sounded
very disturbed in your sleep.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Leave me alone.
I'm going to get dressed.
I'll go get...
Just leave me alone!
In the blue moonlight, I close my eyes.
to hear the voice from above
In my dream, I say my prayers
Wishing my faith will
reach and protect you
A figure in the wind
Is Diana still asleep?
She is getting dressed now.
I see. Well she'd
better dress beautifully.
If this marriage arrangement
with Prince Dunan works out...
our relationship with Gupta
will become even stronger.
Some father, using your own
daughter to secure your position.
Better than those who sell
their daughters at the bazaar.
He is prince of
the most powerful nation.
What is the difference?
That's a poor attitude, Hilda.
If you want, I can sell you...
at the bazaar as well.
Keep a watch on Diana
and don't let her escape.
Sire!
You cannot even trust
your own daughter.
Hey mister! How about this?
Hey, hey! This woman was
serving a certain noble family!
Look at this beautiful body!
Not only good manners,
she is great in bed as well.
Hey young man, you're not
planning to buy a servant, are you?
You're too young for that.
Go to a nearby town
and steal one, why don’t you?
Good for you.
60 Krest!
80!
Any other offers?
85, I say 85!
How about 100!
100, 100 Krest!
Alright, she is all yours, mister!
Take her, you lucky son of a gun!
The next one is a virgin!
Train her any way you like!
Stand up straight
and show your body.
She is a rare buy!
Very nubile and healthy!
Look at her teeth,
and this smooth tongue!
Starting from 40 Krest!
50!
I'll pay 60!
How about 70!
70, 70 Krest!!
Stop it! She doesn't deserve
that sort of treatment!
There's no need to be so cruel.
Hey pal, are you going to buy her?
I've no need to pay for a servant.
If you're not
going to buy, shove off!
I have a permit from the
royal family to run this auction.
It's perfectly legal.
Keep your hands off me!
What!
Not bad!
You little prick! Get him!
Punk! You're not even worth
drawing my sword.
Punk!
Hey! Quarrels at the
bazaar are forbidden!
You are pretty good. Hey?!
I need to borrow this!
Hey! I said, "snatch a woman,"
not my horse!
Get back here! Thief!
Well, what're we
going to do now?
The field dragons will come out,
once the sun sets.
I'm so sorry.
It's all because of me.
Don't worry about it.
They made me angry.
So what's your name?
You can call me Fina.
I'm Diana.
Diana, it's a rather feminine name.
Don't you townsfolk know anything?
They are called water lizards.
Savage carnivores.
As you saw, you'd be
reduced to bones in seconds.
Careless people like you
should stay inside the town.
We'll teach you a lesson or two.
You can pay us with that woman.
Good idea.
You scum!
Think you are big enough?
Stupid punk! We saved your
lives from the water lizards.
Now leave us that woman and beat it.
Not a chance!
Fina!!
Trying to escape?
That's it, run!
Run, you punks!
Hey, look at them go!
Go, go, go!
How spirited.
Damn you!
I'll cut the life out of you!
Damn!
Get away, Fina! Go! Go!
Diana!
Fina!
Gilman, stop playing around!
Let's go screw her.
I suppose so.
Shit!
What a surprise!
This one's female, too!
Yeah? Good deal.
Diana! Let go! Let go of me!
Get your hands off!
Diana!!
We lucked out.
Two fresh females.
They say "The Roc bird
carries an egg,".
Should we take them now?
After showing them to the Chief.
Got it.
I must apologize for
Diana's sudden illness.
It seems she's
anxious about your visit.
She's been very difficult
these days, but it will pass.
However I would like to say...
you truly are a great prince.
I'm glad the King of Gupta...
could grant my ever humble request.
No, no. Me, I am just
an encumbrance, a second son.
Without this marriage,
I am useless to my father.
I am grateful to him,
for raising me to maturity...
and to you as well for giving me
this opportunity for marriage.
My only regret is that
I will not get to meet your...
beautiful daughter in person.
It will only be a few days.
For the time being,
please take my finest servant.
By the way...
what does your father
plan to do about the nomads?
Nothing special, I presume,
he will keep our trade...
relationship cordial as
it's been in the past.
Why do you ask?
Have you heard of the
"legendary hero'?
Legendary hero?
You mean the man they call...
"the Wind-Sent Hero"?
A pagan belief of the nomads...
of one man binding hundreds
of thousands of nomads together.
It's impossible.
Nevertheless, I've heard this
legendary hero will abolish...
the Imperial rule
and rebuild a civil nation.
King Randis, you don't actually
take this rumor seriously?
Is Diana still missing!?
She's out of the palace by now.
It'll be difficult finding her.
Only a few of us guards even
knows what she looks like.
It's possible that she's
outside of Doria by now.
What!!
If that is the case,
there is a concern.
What is it?
There have been reports that
our patrol guards have spotted...
nomad carriages outside of Doria.
You've finally awakened.
Welcome to the carriage
of the nomads' slaves.
Untie me now!
And who do you think you are?
l, I am the Princess Diana of Doria.
Did you hear that?
The Princess of Doria, she says.
The Princess disguised herself
as a man and then went outgo fight?
That's good.
And stark naked on top of that.
It's too late for embarrassment now.
We saw every nook and cranny of...
your body while you were out.
Princess or not,
it does not matter anymore.
You are now a slave,
just like the rest of us.
And a newcomer at that!
You are now in the same class
as your tender friend.
Fina... Where is Fina?
Fina, your friend is looking for you.
It's so... Fina.
It's happening...
It's happening again!
I'll stop if you like.
No, don't stop!
Please... please!
I beg you, master... please!
What did you do to her?
We're training her, so her
master won't tire of her and...
feed her to a field dragon.
Look, she's ready.
Watch well, for you are next.
Yes, watch well and learn.
No!! I won't watch!!
If you want to be disobedient,
we can throw your Fina...
outside of camp this instant.
So, so cruel.
Until you are officially assigned
to a master tonight...
you're at my complete disposal.
Well, what shall it be?
I will watch.
Just don’t torture her.
Again... again!
Yes... yes... yes!
Fina's... Fina's!
Well, seems the "princess'
is just about ready herself.
So, how do you feel?
That hurts!!
Answer with master
when you are spoken to!!
Y, yes.
Well then,
are you aroused?
l, I don't know.
You're a
troublesome princess.
Come now, Princess.
Play nice, or you know...
what'll happen to Fina?
Such a beautiful body.
That good?
I don't know.
I really don't.
Oh yes you do.
Your body is aching for
a master to come inside.
Don't... Don't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
Why don't we finish her off?
We'll have fun training you.
Now tell us, "Please play with me.
Please give it to me, Master".
I... I can't.
No!
Hurry. Say it.
Give it up.
Play with me... more.
What was that? I can't hear you.
Say it louder.
Yes!
Master!!
Diana isn't ill but missing.
Isn't that right?
The King can’t teach his daughter to
behave, though he did very well...
with her servant.
Until the Princess returns,
I suppose we'll have a good time.
Take this!
Now! Tell us! Who are you?
Diana... daughter of
King Randis of Doria...
Still haven't learned!
Beautiful whip, works like a charm.
She's in pain,
and yet still so very aroused.
Come, let's see.
Come now, why don't you give up
and tell us you want to be ours.
We'll take you to a place
you've never been.
Feels so good... can't even talk.
That's enough for now.
Put the collar round her neck.
No!! Don't!! No!!
Shut up!
Alright, who wants her?
Stand up all those
who want to own her!
All of you, huh? Alright, alright.
As usual Chief,
it's up to you to decide.
I don't get to have her?
You, too?!
Why not? It's been a while
since I've had one this good.
You and your appetite.
Alright then, we take turns!
Halt!
I'm looking for
lodging for the night.
No problem.
Welcome to our camp.
What's going on?
Just a little fun.
I don’t fight without a reason.
Is that a weapon you sport,
or just a pretty decoration?
Got butterflies?
Hey, coward.
Can't draw your sword?
You won't come out of this alive.
You finally found some guts!
You!
I suppose I can forget
about the lodging.
He'll tangle with me this time.
Chief!
I've spoken!
Chief!!
Why didn’t you kill me?
I have no reason.
The insult to me has
been paid for with his life.
Let us apologize properly.
Put your sword away.
My name is Teo, chief of this tribe.
And you?
Sho...
Sho... My name is Sho.
Excuse me for not
taking my mask off.
It's no matter.
This is the "oath of heroes, '
passed along by us...
"The Children of the Wind'.
This is a token of
ever-lasting friendship.
And we'll give
you the woman too.
No objections, fellows?
Take her.
I am on a journey,
I can't keep companions...
She claims to be
Princess Diana of Doria.
Don't be shy. Take her!
We'll have a celebration!
Let's drink with Sho till sunrise!
You look very good.
Diana, you're so beautiful.
Take that sad look off your face.
Come now, your Master
will get turned off.
Sho, is that you?
If you're really my Sho, I'll...
Aren’t you going to enjoy me?
Am I so ugly?
No, you are beautiful.
I never thought I could do
things such as this.
Enough, Dee!
You are mine Sho.
Master. Please accept me
as your humble slave.
I would serve you till the end
of my life if it will sooth your pain.
I would endure
any humiliation, any pain.
Master please, do what you like.
Stop it, Diana.
My name is not Diana.
If I was your Diana, then I would
have to kill the man who...
is my father's foe,
even if it costs my life.
Why? I want to be a princess!
Not a servant!
I want to be a princess!
My name is not Diana.
Are you really content
as you are now?
Yes.
I see.
Thank you, Master.
I will serve you to the end.
Until I am no more.
I have to give you a name.
How about "Dee"?
Yes, it's a nice name.
Dee!
Sho, my Master...
Sho!
It's embarrassing!
N... no, No!!
Dee, don't you like it?
No... I'm, a lowly slave.
How do you like it, Dee?
I don't know.
Please do whatever you like.
Master... yes... more!
Please use me as you like!
How am l, Master?
Dee, don't worry.
No!
Do you want me to stop?
No, don't stop! Sho, please!
Dee!
Master... Yes!
I'm close... yes!
Can't hold it any longer!
Master, I'm so sorry
for not waking before you.
Please... forgive me!
Dee...
You are forgiven just this time.
Yes, Master.
That hurts!
Hurry up!
We'll miss breakfast.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Sho!!
Sorry I'm late.
No worries.
The day starts with
a full breakfast.
It's a custom among
nomads to eat plenty.
Impressive! One night and
she's completely broken.
And she was so gutsy.
What do you say, guys?
You!
Y... yes.
Are you happy being his slave?
Yes, sir!!
Well, not only in swordsmanship,
but he beat me in training...
a slave as well.
I owe you, Chief. Thank you.
Thank you for providing me
with such a great slave.
Don't mention it.
I can't believe it's
only been one night.
So, what does he call you?
He named me Dee.
Dee, now that's a good name.
Did he enjoy you last night?
Yes, till his heart's content.
I have to take your life, Prince!
Prepare to die!
Sho!
Get away!
Isn't it? I found it in
my father's room.
Dee, you are going to become
my servant when you're older.
Why? I want to be a princess.
I'm not going to be a servant!
My father tells me, make servants
of your most valuable people.
No! I'm going to be a princess!
What is it?
I was wondering, where
you're headed, Sho of Doria?
What!?
I don't want to repeat
last night's mistake.
Sho of Doria, and Princess Diana.
How did you know?
That crest is rather unique.
Don't get so worked up.
You're scaring the horse.
If I was going to sell
you to the King of Doria...
I would've arranged
it while you were...
in each others' arms last night.
Then... last night, you were?
No, we didn't
mean to eavesdrop.
Then how?
Well... you were so loud,
we just overheard, despite ourselves.
That's my fault. However, you didn't
come after us just to tell us that.
I once made a pact with Bassen.
You knew my father?
Yes.
Take this.
This cannot be?
The crest of
the Children of the Wind...
binding the twelve
clans of the grasslands.
This crest is proof
of the Chief's status.
Sho, you took an oath
of heroes with a great man.
Sho, take this, won't you?
Yes... I'm honored. However...
However?
I am not a child of the wind.
The Chief of your people
must be a Wind-Sent.
When my wish is fulfilled,
I will return this crest to you.
Agreed?
Agreed.
So long as you have a just cause,
a hundred thousand cavalry from...
twelve clans will die for you.
In a pair of yearning eyes,
I fall into a dream...
and again the hard
wind blows in.
Turning back the long
way I have come.
The shadows of flowers
are swaying in the wind.
In the sky, a bird cries out.
Although the pain in my
heart brings me down...
with you...
someday...
I hope our fates will
meet on top of the hill.