Is it here?
Yes, Your Highness
And?
To welcome the guests of the state,
Prince Marlon himself...
will come part of
the way to meet you.
At least they don't intend
to assassinate us on the way.
Surely, however, they
have some sort of plot.
Please be careful!
We are aware of the danger,
how about the plan of yours?
Everything is in place.
Who's next?
What?
Even though it comes
from you, my Prince...
I cannot let my
younger sister take such a...
I understand your worries,
but only Hanna is capable...
of carrying out such a mission.
B... but...
Brother.
I accept this mission.
What? You!
I will do anything to
be of help to the Prince.
You will?
Yes.
With great pleasure!
This is trouble.
He's always letting
those plebeians accompany him.
People think of him as
a kind of celibate, these days.
Daughters from all the noble
families have begun to stay away.
Yet, he doesn't seem to care,
and he isn't interested...
in taking a wife.
FENCER OF MINERVA
Chapter 5: The Beginning
Diana?
How are you doing?
Awful! It's so slow and hot.
Riding on a horse is much better.
You'll be alright.
You are visiting them as a Queen.
I know it's a little formal for you
but try and hang in there.
Yes, but the truth is...
I'm scared to death.
Had I been on my own,
I'd be crying the whole way.
You're not alone.
I only hope we make
it back to Doria safely.
I'm back!!
Mr. Sho!
He is waiting at the inn
just a little ways ahead.
Prince Marlon?
Yes.
According to the scout,
they don't seem to be planning...
anything malicious.
Alright.
We ought to not keep him waiting.
Let's go.
Yes, sir!
Quite a show!
Trying to overwhelm us
from the beginning.
Gupta's Crown Prince Marlon
has come to welcome King Sho...
and Queen Diana of Doria.
Thank you.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is all mine.
Oh, Queen Diana,
it seems the rumor is true.
I wonder what rumor that is?
Oh, nothing your Highness.
We are still in the countryside.
There isn't much we
can offer here, so rest.
We'll leave for Gupta in the morning.
Thank you.
Please make yourselves comfortable.
During your stay in Gupta, she will
attend to your needs.
M... my name is Hanna.
Oh... she is a beautiful woman.
Prince Marlon, I am obliged
to your kind consideration.
How did you guess my taste?
Did Imil let it slip out?
She suits your taste?
Precisely, she has wonderful eyes,
shining with stubborn haughtiness.
Splendid!
It should be good fun
breaking in a woman such as this.
That's the true thrill of training a slave.
Don't you agree, Prince Marlon?
Ah... well... As you say.
The bad habit of
Your Highness, again.
He's always like this.
As soon as he sees a beautiful,
brave looking woman, he loses himself.
I apologize for his rudeness towards
such a valuable slave of Gupta.
Please, it's no bother!!
It is my duty to entertain our guests.
I am delighted to know she has won
the favor of His Highness.
Attend to their every wish.
Yes, sir!
Good night.
Hanna, could you tell our orderlies
outside to bring in our luggage?
Yes, Your Highness.
Sho.
She's not a slave.
I didn't think so, either.
That body...
What were you looking at?
Don't misunderstand.
Those toned muscles
indicate she is a good fencer.
Oh? Then you think she'll...
No, she won't come
in for any rough play.
She's most likely a spy.
Did you notice the way
she looks at the Prince?
Yes.
But, I don't believe
Marlon is interested in her.
Dee, keep out of that matter.
We're not on vacation here.
But, I feel a little sorry for her.
Women...
The King is such a ladies' man.
How can the Queen take it?
That's an attractive woman?
Oh, you're not going
to take your clothes off?
What?
I wonder if the customs
are different here in Gupta?
Is it that Guptans change
clothes many times a day?
No, we don't, but...
What are you embarrassed about?
You'll get soaked.
Why don't you take them off.
A... alright...
Such a beautiful body.
No, you're the one
with the body.
Thanks for the flattery.
No, really.
Let me scrub your back.
Thank you.
Hanna, has Prince Marlon
used you yet?
I... I'm not...
To begin with, Prince Marlon doesn't
let women get too close to him.
Really?
You never know what men
are doing behind your back.
If you keep acting so innocent,
my King may take advantage of you...
even before your Prince.
Oh, don't tell me
you are still a virgin.
N... no!
I suppose not.
No man could overlook
such an attractive body.
Your Highness, what are you?
Shhhh!
King Sho will come in if he hears us.
Is that what you want?
Would you like to be taken
right before my eyes?
N... no... Please spare me...
No... Your Highness...
Cruel Queen!
It's a punishment for your lie.
My lie?
Yes... a big lie...
N, no...
Say it!
You want to be
used by Prince Marlon!!
Yes, I'll say it, please!
I... I want Prince Marlon to...
Wha... what?
You are going on horseback?
Yes, I'm tired of being in the carriage.
It's too slow and too hot.
Besides, King Gauss
is waiting for us.
B, but...
Diana is used to riding horses
since she was a child.
She wishes to see the riding
techniques of Guptan cavalrymen...
which are highly
spoken of in our land.
I would love to see them myself.
I see.
However, if she falls behind...
If that happens,
I'll wait for the carriage to get me.
Well, then!
Let them see the real worth
of the Guptan Cavalry Division!
Fine. Tell the infantry to follow.
Let's have some fun!!
Yes, sir.
Returning to Gupta!!
Double file, gallop!
Proceed!!
Alright, let's go!!
Everybody is gone
Just as we planned.
True...
Hanna, you are very good.
You too, Your Highness.
Queen Diana is keeping up with us!
I can't believe it.
Your Highness,
are you all right?
Wonderful!
Just as I would of expected
of the Guptan Cavalry Division.
Yes, it is our pride.
Prince Marlon, how much farther?
The steeple that's just
coming into our view is Gupta.
Then, should you not
have them form in file?
How shameful of them!!
Wow!
That Queen came on horseback?
Geeez!
I wish Gupta had a woman
like that for Prince Marlon.
You'd have to be a nomad
to keep up with the Gupta cavalry.
How fearless,
challenging my cavalry.
No matter what she's up to,
I won't be taken with such a bluff.
Little wench!
Hey!
Where are you going?
I didn't think you'd
made it this far, Mr. Imil.
I was too worried
for the King and Queen.
How 's it going?
No worries!
As you expected,
all the Guptan soldiers...
went chasing after the
pretty little ass of the Queen.
The what?
I got a kick... out of her being
whipped stark naked before.
H... how impudent!!
It was a long time ago.
So, there are no Guptan soldiers?
None on this road!
Just as Doria was a long time ago,
Gupta has also been spoiled by...
these ten years of peace.
Precisely, Mr. Seneca!
Now, we will await
the signal from King Sho.
Alright, everybody!
Let's get going!!
Yeah!!
We should get ready, too.
Their Highnesses,
King Sho and Queen Diana!!
How splendid!
Splendid!
Oh...
Oh, that's the shrew who lead
our cavalry by the nose?
Yes...
It's hard to believe
just by looking at her.
If you knew how to
handle women a little better...
you wouldn't have
made a fool of yourself.
I am ashamed, Sire.
The Dorian King is paying
homage to our King!
What is he thinking?
Wh... what is?
Your Highness King Gauss!!
I am Sho, the new King of Doria.
This is my Queen, Diana.
Though I am inexperienced,
I have succeeded the throne of Doria.
I come here today to humbly
Salute Your Highness...
the Conqueror of the North.
Such dignity despite his age!
I have never seen
such a gallant king before.
That is the son
of the late King Bassen.
Nonetheless, the Queen
is the daughter of the one...
who murdered his father.
How can he?
No, no, they make
a wonderful young couple.
Such a courteous greeting,
I, King Gauss, am impressed.
Let us both prosper
as good neighbors!
Forever and after!
To Gupta's prosperity!!
To Doria's prosperity!!
To the friendship
of Doria and Gupta!!
Toast!!
Who is she?
There shouldn't be any new slaves
here on an occasion such as this.
I haven't seen her before.
She belongs to the Cavalry Division.
What, that's Hanna?
Yes.
Why is the only woman
in our glorious Cavalry Division...
disguised as a slave?
To spy on the King
and Queen of Doria.
A spy?
Coming from you,
it's not a bad idea.
So beautiful, I thought
perhaps she was your lover.
F... father!!
She's practically half man.
Not at all.
Without knowledge
of her true identity...
you'd never know
it was the fierce Hanna.
Look at the feminine shyness.
Through her disguise, her
body exposed in that slave's outfit.
It brings out the woman in her.
Woman...
Oh, well I'm not cut out for this.
Neither am I.
I wish I could strangle the
man who tried to assassinate Teo!!
What's wrong?
N... no, nothing!
She must know something.
So it seems.
But, I must thank the man
who attacked King Teo.
Come now, you shouldn't say that.
He's still in bed, suffering.
But, for him, my life-long dream
to become a queen came true.
Otherwise, I would still
be your slave.
Slave...?
You are diverting
from our plan.
Leave it to me.
Hanna where's our wine?
Y... yes, coming!
Sorry to keep you waiting!?
Master...
Oh, Hanna, thank you.
I will pour some.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Why are you trembling?
I... I'm sorry.
Have some with us.
N... no, I shouldn't.
That's OK.
It's an order.
Yes...
I'll pour some for you.
Thank you.
Why don't you empty it.
Good job.
Have another.
Are the soldiers ready?
Yes, Sire.
They won't leave here alive.
Oh my!
Then, you really were a slave.
An excellent one, I was
priced for more than 100 gold coins.
100 gold coins?
So much?
But, he would never sell me.
Right?
Of course not.
Master... Master, please
enjoy your poor slave.
Am I not beautiful enough?
You are beautiful.
Then... Master, please
use me as you used to.
Excuse me...
Hey, you are overdoing it.
But, I'm so turned on...
She's listening.
All the more reason.
Master, please... Yes...
Yes!
Queen...
That's so cruel!
N... no, please spare me...
No... Diana!
Master...
Your Highness, please...
Can't help it!
I am... a proud Guptan soldier!
Such terrible behavior, it can't be...
Prince... Marlon!
What!?
They told you this?
Yes...
It doesn't make sense.
Why would they tell
something like that to a slave?
I am not a slave!
I didn't mean...
Well, at any rate, they seem
to trust you completely.
Keep up the good work.
Y... yes...
In our kingdom, the soldiers
receive training every day.
Superb, what do you think, Diana?
Yes... But...
What is it?
Please be frank.
Then I shall.
The way they are being trained
wouldn't be of any use in real battle.
What!!
What!?
That's too much!
Such slander cannot be taken
even from the Queen of Doria!
That's very harsh.
I hear you are a good fencer,
yourself, Your Highness.
At least, a little better
than your men.
But, we cannot ask the Queen
of Doria for a fencing match.
Come now, Diana.
You are no longer
a tomboyish little Princess.
Well... Prince Marlon, how about him?
Could she know my brother
is the one who attacked Teo?
What about him?
He's probably as good as myself.
It'll be good practice.
Please don't, Your Highness!!
Why?
You could get hurt.
Don't worry.
They have protective gear
for women, don't they?
What!?
Before becoming a slave,
you were trained as a fencer.
I can tell from the way you move.
What do you say we have a match?
Well... that's...
How about it, Prince Marlon?
If you insist,
Hanna, do as they wish.
Y... yes...
Hey, Hanna.
Why don't you say we make a deal.
Loser does one thing the winner
requests, whatever it may be.
Are you sure?
It works for me.
If you don't give it all you've got,
you might get hurt.
I know.
Begin!
You're pretty good.
So are you.
Right there, Hanna!
What are you doing!?
Oh, um, excuse me.
They're both very good.
It's no wonder
you've become so heated.
Sorry.
Does Hanna belong to you?
Huh?
An ordinary man would
not be able to tame her.
N... no.
That's a shame.
With a little more
experience as a woman...
Diana wouldn't compare to her.
Hanna, what's wrong?
You've never had problems,
even against men.
Why now?
I'd never imagined the petite Diana
could be such a great fighter!
Got you!
I... I give up!
Now that's what you
call a practice match!!
True!
That's how a Guptan
soldier ought to be!!
Great!
An amazing display!
Here.
Thank you.
Where did you learn
such a technique?
My King taught me.
Well, a deal's a deal.
Yes, anything you say.
OK, then...
What!?
What did she say to Hanna?
I don't know.
You were very impressive,
Your Highness!!
Hanna, you did a good job, too.
Thank you, Prince Marlon...
Prince, Hanna has
something to ask you.
Hanna!
Pr... Prince Marlon...
Tell me.
You performed superbly.
I'll grant you anything as reward.
Please make me yours...
What?
You have to articulate
exactly what you want!!
Please have me!!
What!?
Are you out of your mind!?
Dressing as a slave made
your heart a slave as well?!
I will kill you here!
Stop it!!
You are in the presence
of the King of Doria!!
I'm sorry for my
disgraceful behavior.
Forgive me, brother.
I am in love with Prince Marlon.
If I can be by his side,
I do not mind being a slave!!
Please, Prince Marlon.
Please accept me...
Prince, what are you
going to do with Hanna?
Will you execute her for
failing her mission as a spy?
No, I will not.
She already reported to you
about our circumstances.
That was true, then?
Diana discovered her true self
only when she became a slave.
Probably, it was
the same for Hanna.
Sometimes, high standing prevents you
from being honest with yourself.
I suggest you keep her
as a slave for a while.
After that, it's up to you.
Thank you for your advice.
Hanna, are you content with that?
Yes, as long as I am by your side.
Now, we have to deal
with the real problem.
You asked for a private meeting.
I can only wonder what it's about.
My, my. Since the day
you two arrived in Gupta...
our kingdom has witnessed
unprecedented incidents...
one after the other.
I apologize.
Please consider them accidents
caused by the thoughtless behavior...
of the young...
No, I won't.
Why don't we hear
your true intentions?
Under the disguise of courtesy,
you humiliated the best of my people...
took advantage of my son's schemes,
and compelled him to take a woman.
Why!?
Indeed we have our own purpose!
Oh, and what could that be?
To find the man who tried
to assassinate King Teo...
and seek out the puppet master.
Then execute both of them!!
What!!
That's funny.
And, you think we did it, don't you?
On what grounds?
Such knives are numerous.
Really?
Unlike Doria, where soldiers
procure their own weapons...
all the equipment here is provided
by the state of Gupta.
Is it not so?
And this, an official knife
of a Guptan soldier!!
Furthermore!!
According to our Swordsmith,
this crest is not a part...
of the original design.
Most likely, the owner of
this knife had it inscribed.
Someone whose family
crest was the same as this one.
I saw a soldier who had
the same crest on his armor...
at the parade ground!!
Even if there was a soldier whose
family crest was the same as this...
someone might have
stolen this knife from him.
It was stolen?
How shameful for him,
being a Guptan soldier.
However, we could let it go.
Teo has passed the crisis.
His complete recovery is not far off.
If we keep taking revenge on each
other, it will soon lead to war.
Don't you agree?
Diana.
Yes, Your Highness!!
The signal! Hurry!
The signal! All right!
The signal!
Yes!
Let's go!!
Yeah!!
There it is! Move out!
Go!
What is this?
The knife passed along
through the Dorian Royal Family.
I killed Prince Dunan
with that knife.
What!?
What did you say!?
Prince Dunan sexually assaulted me
in front of my servants and his men...
despite the fact that I was already Sho's.
I stabbed him to death.
You!!
If you're going to interfere,
I will kill you, too!!
Like father, like son!
If that's what you want, then it'll
be my pleasure to take you on!
Such impudence!!
Little bastard!!
King Gauss, you couldn't imagine how
terribly your son humiliated Diana!!
However, there is no gain in hating
each other for the things of the past!
Hate only bears more hate!
It can only cause
trouble for both nations!
What do you say, Gauss?
An enemy attack!!
We are being attacked!!
Wh... what's this!?
What!!
Help!!
Sho's doing a good job.
How?
Your Highness!!
Gupta is completely surrounded!!
What!!
There are many thousands, no,
hundreds of thousands of soldiers!!
No country has such a large military!!
Yes, we do.
A military force which
does not wish to wage war.
Unbelievable!
Where did they come from?
Ah, we can't tell!
Official Dorian soldiers, and nearly
a hundred thousand nomads.
Nomads?
I am the Chief of the chiefs,
who binds entire nomad populations.
Your Highness!!
The Chairman of the Saas Council
and a man who claims to be...
the Dorian Royal Adviser are here!!
There they are.
I am telling you,
Your Highness, King Gauss...
we do not intend to attack Gupta.
However, if you refuse to surrender,
we will continue the siege.
The Saas are
completely supporting us.
As long as you resist,
none of the goods from Saas...
not a piece of bread,
will come to Gupta.
The Chairman of the Saas Council
is here to inform you of that.
What?
Gupta loses without a fight...
a kingdom which is
revered for its valor.
Father!!
One more thing!!
We will not occupy Gupta.
What!?
If you surrender,
I guarantee the autonomy of Gupta...
as well as your status.
Why would you
guarantee such a thing?
I do not wish
to hurt innocent citizens.
Then why did you
send in such a huge force?
To protect my Queen, Diana!
Your Highness!
Thank God, you are safe.
He is a great man.
Well, the rest is up to us.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I have one more
important task as well.
Who is it?
It's Diana, Prince Marlon.
Queen Diana?
Th... this is...!?
I heard you stayed up all night
working on the new treaty...
between Doria and Gupta.
You must be tired.
Ah, well...
Hanna, comfort Prince Marlon.
Y... yes...
So long.
I give up!
I can't outdo her no matter what.
Or rather, I can't outdo those two.
King Sho told me something.
He said it was something
the late King Bassen told him once.
What did he say?
Make a slave of the
woman you love most.
Very true!
Prince Marlon...
Address me correctly.
Well?
M... Master...
And?
Would you please...
please accept my obedience?
Of course.
Please... Master, use me.
Is that what you want?
Yes, I have been waiting
for such a long time.
Master... am I not beautiful enough?
You are beautiful.
Please! Take me!
M... my body is...
aching for you, Master.
I am already so...
Hanna...
I'm embarrassed.
Yes, please...
Who did you learn this from?
Queen Diana...
M... Master...
Hanna...
Forgive me, Master...
I cannot wait any longer!
Please let me have it... please!
Ah... yeah...
Are you OK, Hanna?
Yes...
Hanna...
My... Master...
Are you happy?
Y... yes...
You have become very honest.
I shall punish you
for your past dishonesty.
As you wish.
Master... more!
Please, punish me more!
It's so good!
Then, I will leave the rest to you.
You really must go?
Yes.
My duties are complete.
Ulsra wants to ride
with me in the field.
She's sure to be upset
if I keep you here any longer.
Promise me you'll stop by
when you are near.
I will, as long as
you are in Doria.
Mr. Sho.
So, you definitely
won't take it back.
No.
You are going to need
it now more than ever.
I have my own clan and Ulsra.
That's enough for me.
I see... Well then...
Take care of Diana.
Queen Diana.
Are you really content like that?
Yes, Mr. Teo.
I see...
I should've made you
my slave when I had the chance.
I never imagined you'd make
such a great servant.
Mr. Teo, Ulsra is getting jealous.
Have a lot of children.
We will!!
On her own free will, Queen Diana
took back her status as a slave.
Diana, who chose a new way of life,
became idolized among the women...
of this world.
The legend tells us that she
came to be known as...
"Diana the Slave-Queen",
and was admired long after.
In a pair of yearning eyes
I fall into a dream
and again the hard
wind blows in.
Turning back the long
way I have come
the shadows of flowers
are swaying in the wind.
In the sky
a bird cries out
Although the pain in my
heart brings me down
with you
someday
I hope that our fates will
meet on top of the hill.