Ho-ho! I'd pay two
gold coins for her.
This valna wine is good!
We couldn’t find any
work today, again.
Don't worry.
If worse comes to worse,
I can sell you.
You will sell very easily.
You are so mean!
Just kidding.
You know I wouldn't let such
a precious treasure go.
You wouldn't?
No, I won't.
I'm happy to hear that, Master!
Hey, out of the way!!
Get lost, old man!
Them again.
Who are they?
Licentious sons of the rich,
they're always boasting around...
doing whatever they like.
Stay away from them.
Especially from her.
Unappetizing food as usual.
Master, here's the money.
Thank you.
This table is reserved
for Miss Patris! Get up!
Y... yes!!
Miss Patris, please.
Master, wine, bring us some wine!
Y, yes...
And some food,
the best food you have.
Here, there's not much difference
between the good food and the bad.
The waitresses aren't bad, though.
That's true. Well...
Get over here!
Please stop!
Please let me go!
Pour some wine!
Y, yes...
To Patris!!
This is good.
Patris has given us permission!!
To Patris!!
This is the best outfit for a slave.
Please spare me!
Wiggle your hips!
Scum!!
No, Diana, let them be.
But...
Don't forget you're a slave, too.
I'm sorry, Master... Forgive me.
What's this?
Miss Patris wants to buy your slave.
Oh, that's a lot of money.
OK, then.
Wait. I didn't say I
would sell this slave.
Want more? Then...
No matter how much you offer,
I won't sell my slave.
Let's go, Diana.
OK.
Y... you... arrogant bastard!
Let's go.
Cain!
Wait!
Yes?
Are you saying your
slave is so valuable?
Valuable? No.
Diana is everything to me.
A King's throne wouldn't
even compare with her.
She is an insignificant slave!
Miss, you probably
don't understand.
But, you can't buy
a person's heart with money!
There's nothing money can't buy!!
Well then, tell me
how much you are worth.
Oh, very beautiful.
Maybe you are worth
as much as my slave.
You!
You insulted a lady in public!
You won't get away with this!
Stop it!
Uncle!
I won't permit such
outrageous behavior!
Go!!
OK.
Patris...
Master...
I apologize for
my niece's bad behavior.
I... it's OK, Mr. Yajil.
I must apologize to you, too.
I'm sorry.
I might have overreacted,
exposing your niece's face in public.
Thank you for your forgiveness.
My niece lost her parents
when she was a child.
I took pity on her and spoiled her.
The vast fortune she inherited
made her become so...
Arrogant!
Patris' admirers are from rich families,
too, but they’re all profligate.
We must get going.
Please wait.
Incidentally, I have a favor
to ask you, if you will.
Under the blue moonlight,
I close my eyes
Straining to hear
the Voice from above
No, Uncle!
Straining to hear
the Voice from above
I don't want them
to be in this house!
Absolutely not!!
Dear lady!
Sho is to be your...
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
Sho is to be your...
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
...supervisor.
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
And, Diana will be
your personal servant.
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
I am Sho.
How do you do.
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
I am Diana.
I will be your servant.
Wishing my faith will reach
and protect you
Listen, Patris. From now on,
you are not allowed out without Sho.
A figure in the wind
I order you as your guardian!
Understood?!
A figure in the wind
Master...
Maybe we should decline this offer.
No, we already accepted it.
You might have a hard time,
but hang in there.
No, don't worry.
Ah! Kyle.
I need a favor from you.
Anything for you.
Listen.
Diana?!
Are you going to help me or not?
OK.
Why did Uncle have to do this to me?!
Who is it?
It's Diana, Miss.
Come in.
I brought you some clothes.
I can dress myself.
Clean up the room.
Yes.
This is for the laundry.
What do you think of my body?
Well?
Very beautiful...
You're lying!
My breasts are so small;
my hips are bony.
As a woman,
I think your body is very pretty.
It would be even more
attractive to a man.
Besides...
There are men who especially
like a body like yours.
Did your breasts get big
from being touched by Sho?
How does Sho take you?
I... I can't...
She does?
Yes. She asks questions
about you and I very openly.
She seems to be
extremely interested in sex.
I see.
Women her age are like that.
How do you know, Master?
You've had...
so many?
Cruel Master,
I am just a misfortunate slave.
You are going to make that pretty
Patris your slave and sell me off.
That's a good idea.
Master, please don't abandon me!
Sho...
Y, yes.
Yes.
More... give me!
Sho... give it to me... please!
Who is it?
It's me.
Speak of the devil.
Miss Patris, can I be of service?
Am I interrupting?
Did Miss Patris have a bad dream?
Diana, I need you.
Come to my room!
Y, yes.
Oh, well...
You look nice, Diana.
Oh, you want to say something?
Do you promise not to scream?
Listen!!
Even if you do scream,
I will just say I am...
punishing a servant.
Do you understand?
M, Miss Patris... Why?
I won't allow a slave
to be loved so much.
Especially, by the man
who insulted me!!
He was touching you
like this, wasn't he?
No, he wasn't.
Luscious breasts.
You are so hard.
You are excited, aren't you?
N, no.
Well, you're excited. Say it!
Stubborn woman! Kyle!
Take my place.
Please, no!
I'm punishing you for not obeying me.
I'll watch you being humiliated.
What are you waiting for? Do it!
Mr. Kyle... No... Please don't!
Miss, please. Stop Mr. Kyle!
N, no...
Oh, no, not there!
Your body says it wants more.
N, no...
I can't hold back...
Right there!
No... no!!
Sho has trained her very well.
I wish I had a slave like this.
I envy him.
Why don’t you have her?
Kyle, why are you stopping now?
Now's your chance.
Take her now. I order you!!
Even if it's from you,
I cant take such an order.
Are you afraid of breaking the law?
Don't worry.
If Sho gets upset,
I'll let him have me.
What?
Then, he can get even, right?
What's going on?
Anything wrong?
Sho!
Shit!
Diana, are you OK?
Quick!! Get out from that window!!
I'll take care of the rest.
Diana!! Answer me!
Diana!! Diana!!
Quick, Miss!!
Get on top of me!
Patris!! I command you!
Y, yes.
That's it. Leave it to me... OK?
Kiss me, Now!
Oh, Master!
What's going on?
We sort of got into this...
Um... I'm showing her
how to train a slave.
Isn't that so, Miss?
Uh, yes.
Oh, I don't think I
ever tied you down.
W... well...
It is my wish to be
tied up once in a while.
I see.
Then, to punish you for teaching
indecent things to Miss Patris...
I shall leave you
tied up until morning.
What!?
Don't, Sho!
It's all my fault.
So, don't punish Diana,
but instead... punish me.
You can tie me or whip me...
anything you like.
Please Sho. Punish me!
No, I can't.
I am a man.
If I were to punish you
after seeing you like this...
I might go overboard.
Also, you should have
the windows closed.
Someone might try to sneak in.
Diana, someday I will...
It seems that Patris likes you now.
Yes, of course.
And, who else was there?
N... nobody.
Nobody, eh?
You do need to be
punished, after all.
He's serious.
I've been spoiling you too much.
It's about time.
Scary!
Ouch! He really tortured me!
I thought I was
going to die... but...
that was so nice!
I've never been so excited!
Diana.
Miss Patris?
You're up so early.
I... I was worried about you.
Are you OK?
He didn’t torture you, did he?
He did? What did he do?
I can’t tell you.
Things even you can't describe?
Miss Patris,
Mr. Yajil is asking for you.
Uncle, are you alright?
Where's the doctor?
I will be fine in a couple of days.
I have a favor to ask you.
Deliver this to Azmal in Farada.
What's this?
An important business document.
I need someone I can trust
to deliver it.
OK.
Sho, will you go with her?
Certainly.
I'm on my way.
Kyle, if everything goes well,
I will give you Patris.
Do with her as you please.
Yes, sir.
Sho, be careful.
Bastard!
Skimming the milk without
getting his hands dirty!!
Take it easy!
Nobody's been able
to keep up with me.
Your horse will be exhausted.
Then I will ride on your horse.
Put the veil on your face.
Not necessary,
it's just you and me.
I don't want the passersby
to see you and get any ideas.
Are you trying to say I'm beautiful?
You can interpret
it any way you like.
You are really annoying.
What is it?
Patris, stay away.
Why are you attacking me?
Sho.
What!?
Patris!?
Out of my way!
Sho!
Are you OK?
Yes.
Who are you? Get lost!
You can't kill him alone.
What?
Diana.
Knock it off, Kyle!
What!?
Kyle!?
Kyle, you don't have a chance.
I know how to use a sword
as well as any man.
Kyle... Why?
Why are you doing this?
Patris!!
Get away from him!
Kyle, are you going to kill Patris?
How can you kill someone you love?
I know.
Kyle...
Kill them all!!
Die!
Stop!!
My hand!! My hand!!
I give up.
Master.
Please take me.
No, not yet.
Who is it?
It's Kyle.
Withdraw.
Yes, Master.
Come in.
You did get rid of Sho, right?
As I said, you can take Patris.
Her fortune is mine now.
I'll reward you for your work.
Take this.
You can either stay or go.
Do what you like.
I can't wait to make Diana serve me.
Shut up!
What?
You liar!
You hired hit-men behind my back
and tried to kill me.
And, you ordered them to kill Patris
to take her fortune, too.
On top of that,
you planned to put the blame...
on Sho for Patris's death.
We heard everything.
Uncle, I am disappointed.
Such a sly old man.
Kyle!? You betrayed me!
Old man, you were
captivated by Diana.
Isn't it so?
She is very attractive.
It's no wonder.
Master.
You couldn't wait
to get your hands on Diana...
so you tried to have me killed.
There are four of us
who witnessed your misconduct.
It's easy for me
to kill you right now.
Wa... wait... Don't take my life!
I'm as guilty as he is.
Kyle!
Kyle...
You want to be my slave?
Yes.
Don't be upset, Diana.
I'm not trying to steal Sho from you.
Wha... what are you doing?
I beg you, Mistress... after you...
I want to be taken by Mr. Sho.
Please take me as your slave.
Do you understand
what you are doing?
Yes, I do.
I see then.
You are pretty, Patris.
I...
Well, Patris.
Master is waiting for you.
Please make me your slave.
I'll grant your wish.
Thank you... M... Master.
Diana, don't go!
No, Patris. This is your first time.
You must be alone with your Master.
She's good.
We'll get along just fine.
Why am I so sad?
I am so terrible... Sho!
Master!
Now... Please!
You're so indecent.
So naughty...
Master... Please use me!
Right there!
Master, more!
You're an impossible slave.
Forgive me, Master...
but, I can't help it.
Please, Master. Take me!
I can't wait any longer!
I wonder which of us is the Master.
Please!
Now, Master!
Master, I'm so happy!
Incredibly sensitive for a virgin.
You told me once
I'd make a good slave.
I sure did.
Then, please...
teach your indecent slave.
Master, it feels so good... Yes!
It's too good... I'm going to die!
I'm so close... Please... I want to!
Get Kyle for me.
He's probably in that bar.
Y... yes.
Mr. Kyle.
Ah... It's you.
Came to laugh at me?
Mr. Sho is asking for you.
S... Sho!! You!
I have a proposition for you, Kyle.
I will be continuing on my journey.
But two slaves are too much
for me, so I want you to buy...
one of them.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm serious.
My family has been slave-brokers
for five generations.
Although I did not
take over the business...
my trained eyes say, "Buy Diana"!
But, my heart says otherwise.
Diana is too customized
for you, Sho.
It's too late to re-train
her as my slave.
Besides...
Besides?
Diana is too proud to be a slave.
If she was forced
to take another master...
she'd bite off her tongue
and kill herself.
I don't want that to happen.
Then?
I'll buy Patris.
Yes!! I will buy this woman!
Sho, tell me how much.
OK. She's worth...
one copper coin! How's that?
One copper coin?!
Is it too much, Kyle?
N... no!! I'll pay you right now.
Before you change your mind. Here!!
The payment has been duly received.
She is now yours.
Patris...
Do you want to be like Diana here?
Want to be a precious woman?
A woman who takes pleasure
in being taken by a man?
Mr. Kyle...
Mr. Kyle... Please take me now!
Patris!
Master!
I've been in love
with you for so long...
I did everything...
like you told me to,
so you'd like me.
I have been waiting for this day.
Mr. Kyle.
I am forever your slave.
Kyle.
A gift for her.
What's this for?
Have her keep it on her.
As long as she remembers how
much she was sold for...
she'll never be arrogant again.
That's a good idea.
I'll make her a gold necklace
with this coin embedded in it.
If Patris wishes so, I will spend
her entire fortune on the necklace.
Kyle, slaves are not
allowed to keep any assets.
Patris isn't wearing my collar.
Not yet.
You devil!
If she marries Kyle
as a free person...
she can inherit all
of her family's fortune.
So, Kyle is not going
to make her wear a collar...
even if she is treated
as a slave in private.
Right, Kyle?
Right. It'll be a
different story in bed.
When no one is watching us.
Oh, you are so sly.
Sho, thanks for everything.
Diana, I thank you, too.
Diana, Patris is busy
taking her lessons.
We shouldn't bother her.
You are the one who sold her.
Master?
What?
With whom did you practice
tying up women?
Well, it wasn't with me.
Well, it's been 12 years...
there was plenty of time to learn.
No, not for me!!
I guess not.
You were still a virgin
when you met me.
I could tell.
But you were
a very responsive virgin.
I'm sleepy.
I need to rest.
You didn't sleep at all last night.
Do you want to rest with me?
You really are going to sleep?
That would be up to you.
That's not fair, Master!
In a pair of yearning eyes,
I fall into a dream...
and again the hard
wind blows in.
Turning back the long
way I have come...
the shadows of flowers
are swaying in the wind.
In the sky, a bird cries out.
Although the pain in my
heart brings me down...
with you...
someday...
I believe that our fates will
meet on top of the hill.