Please, no!
Quiet!
Keep your mouth shut!
Quick, take off her panties.
No! Please!
- They're off!
- No!
Look!
We can see everything now!
Please, no!
You boys can take a look
at Momone's pussy too.
You can see all the way in.
Wow! Check it out!
No!
It was a dream.
I didn't want to remember that.
I must get myself up
and get to work.
Good morning, Professor!
Good morning.
Professor Momone sure has a nice body,
looking from this angle.
I'd like to see her from the front
and sink my face into her tits.
Good morning, Professor Momone.
Hino.
Hey, Oda.
Why are you always standing here?
It's none of your business.
You're so beautiful, Professor!
Good morning, Professor.
Good Morning, Oda.
Yuichi.
You were so good
in that game yesterday.
I loved that last dunk shot
that clinched the game.
We could win the championship
this year.
Wait a minute.
These are just practice games.
We still have a season to play.
Come and see us play sometime,
Professor Momone.
Take it easy, girls.
Come on...
All right, Oda.
I'll go see your game sometime.
Masaki, I've heard that
you and Oda are old friends.
Yes.
Must be tough considering...
that he's the captain
and the women swarm to him.
You like him, don't you?
I don't care anymore.
Besides, he likes you anyway.
Look at this! It's all wedged up.
I wonder if her pussy hurts.
Be quiet, you guys.
What if the prof finds out
what you've been up to?
Come on, I know you like it too,
you perverted little nerd.
What's all the fuss about?
Professor Momone!
Who brought this here?
It... it wasn't me!
Wasn't me either.
Not me.
Hey... It was me.
Why do you have to bring
such material to class?
I'm disappointed.
What did you think of it?
Wha?!
What do you mean?
- Are you wet?
- Masamichi Hino!
Anyway, I want everyone to sit down.
Let's begin class.
Hey, Hino! You were way out of line
talking to Professor Momone like that!
You're such a wuss, Oda.
What did you say?
You'll know soon enough.
What's that all about?
- Hino?!
- I'm in love with you again.
What are you talking about?
The rest of the class is warming up.
It's just the two of us right here.
Hino, you'd better stop this.
Be quiet. You make a big noise,
everyone will fiind out.
No. No...
Come on, Prof.
Hino.
It's time to play, Prof.
Hino!
Everybody by the pool!
Let me go!
What should I do about this book
I confiscated from Hino?
Is this the kind of thing
people are into? Goodness!
Oh my, I'm all wet.
Wh... who is it?
It's me,
your beloved student, Prof.
Hino?
Hang on. I'm coming.
Stop that.
What is it?
Hey.
Well, it's a pretty boring apartment
for a single woman.
Enough already.
What do you want anyway?
Isn't it a problem for a professor...
to be enjoying porno that's been
confiscated from a student?
Look.
Just leave, all right. Please.
Don't worry about it,
Professor Momone.
You're human too.
- Stop.
- Now, come on.
I'm your professor.
I can't be doing
something like this with you.
No, you mustn't!
In their minds, all the guys
want to screw your brains out.
And I'm no exception.
That hurts.
When a woman wants to do it,
what's wrong with a student?
You're always so mean to me.
I'll take good care of you
this time for sure.
Hino!
You've got great tits, Prof.
Never seen anything like this.
They're amazing.
These hard nipples;
I just want to suck on them.
You have to promise that
you'll never tell anybody about this.
Of course.
Please suck on them...
Oh, Hino!
You're panties are wet.
All wet against your pussy.
Put your hand there.
Come on. Is a Professor supposed to
say something like that?
I'm sorry.
It's about time
I get to see inside of you.
Am I right?
But...
It must hurt,
all wedged in like this.
Take it off gently.
Here we go.
Move your hands.
I can't wait to see your pussy.
Move your hands, now!
So this is the pussy
of Professor Momone.
Spread them for me, Prof.
No. I don't want to.
I said do it. Hurry up!
You're so mean to me, Hino.
How about this?
Spread them more.
Wider. I want to see more.
No... Hino, you mustn't.
It's all red and
flowing with juices.
Don't look at me like that.
I've even got two fingers in.
Stop it. Please.
It's embarrassing.
Hino, please stop.
I wonder what everyone would think
if they knew what a slut you were.
It feels good, doesn't it?
That's a nice hard clit
you've got there.
You're so terrible, Hino.
I want you to say it feels good.
I'll even lick your
cute little butthole.
Oh, Hino. Do it more...
There, right there.
Say it like you mean it, Prof.
What's that? I can't hear you.
You have to say it clearly.
Yes. There. That's right...
Please...
Look at this, Prof.
I want you to
lick it all up with your tongue.
That's good.
How is the taste
of your own pussy juice?
Next I'll have you suck on this.
Look at it.
It feels like it's about to burst.
It's your turn
to make me feel good.
Touch it!
Incredible.
It's so hot and it's throbbing.
It's your turn to perform.
You're good at this.
Where did you learn,
with your boyfriend?
I don't know.
Who would have thought that
Professor Momone loved to suck cock.
Say you like to suck cock.
It's embarrassing.
Well, then you don't get anymore.
No, please...
Then say it!
I love to suck cock.
Here I cum.
Please, Hino,
don't tease me like that.
Do you want me to put it in?
Are you serious?
I am your student.
I wonder if it's all right
to do it with the Prof.
But I need...
- So, what about it?
- Do me...
Do me?! What's that?
Ask me properly!
Or I'm not going to do it.
I'm sorry.
Please, do it to me. Please.
Come on. Say it like you mean it,
slut Professor.
Hurry up and say it!
Alright.
I beg you.
Please put your big cock...
into my pussy.
Oh, yeah...
Your pussy is so tight.
It feels so good.
Come on, louder.
Oh, Hino...
Can you see, Professor?
Look, I'm right inside of you.
Hino!
Deeper, go deeper... deeper.
I can feel you
so deep inside of me...
Can you feel that, Professor Momone?
Does it feel good?
Yes...
Tell me you're going to cum,
come on!
I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum.
Professor, be my woman.
I'll take good care of you every day.
Yes.
Really?
Yes. I'm your woman.
That's a good woman.
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, Hino...
I'm going to die...
This can't go on like this.
I'm going to have to
tell Hino straight.
Tomorrow.
It's Momone.
Last night was quite amazing,
Professor Momone.
Hino, we've got to talk.
When you come to school tomorrow,
don't wear underwear.
I'm sure you'll do what I say.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye.
Oh, Hino...? Hino?
I hate that bitch Masaki...
I don't care if she's the manager
of the basketball team or what.
How dare she keep
our Oda to herself.
I've decided, Mika.
I'm going to tell
Professor Momone how I feel.
I see.
I can't help how much I want her.
I hope it goes well.
I'll just have to tell her straight.
Let's see it, Professor.
I want to make sure you came
as you were supposed to.
Hurry up,
the noon break is almost over.
Not like that.
I want to see everything.
But, it's embarrassing.
That's good, Prof.
You didn't wear underwear.
Imagine if people found out that
you came to school without underwear.
P... please don't tell, Hino.
What's happened, Prof.
You're all wet.
Do you get off on exposing yourself,
Professor Momone?
No...
Isn't that so?
You're getting off.
You come to campus
with no underwear...
your nipples are hard,
and you're all wet.
Be honest with me.
Giving your lectures
while dripping wet.
What a sex maniac.
I don't know.
You're getting off on this,
you nymphomaniac professor.
You're terrible, Hino.
You get off from
just being exposed.
I'm not like that.
Well then, let's try an experiment.
I believe your next class is with me.
Yes.
We can prove it then...
that you're an
exhibitionist sex maniac.
Stop.
What are you doing to me?
I'm only doing what you want.
What is this?
It's an ointment
that'll bring out the real you.
What have you done?
Today, we will do some
sketching exercises.
I will act as the model.
How about a nude, then?
We might as well.
Hino?
A nude seems like an appropriate
subject for a fine arts class.
We can draw you
with your clothes on, Prof.
Keep your mouth shut.
I know you want to see her as well.
Please be quiet.
Are you all right, Professor?
Thank you.
You're hot. Maybe you should
take off your jacket.
- But...
- Here.
- Check it out!
- No bra!
Huge!
So, what would be a good pose.
Wow, Professor Momone
isn't wearing any panties!
- What?!
- No way!
What are you talking about?
But I saw it for myself.
No panties.
Stop it.
Then pull up your skirt
and show us.
Yeah, show us!
Show us!
See, I told you.
No panties!
It's true!
Coming to school
with no bra and no panties!
You can see her pussy!
- What a pervert.
- What a slut.
Her face is all red.
I think she's getting off on it.
Could she be an exhibitionist?
If you want us to see,
then take off your clothes.
Yeah! Take it off!
No...!
Stop it. You mustn't...
So this is the prof's pussy.
It's all wet and juicy!
I want to see!
Spread 'em for us, Prof.
I know you really want us to see.
But no...
We all want to see your pussy.
Wow, look at that!
Are you some kind of
nymphomaniac?
Say it, Prof,
"I am a nympho slut pervert."
I am a nympho slut pervert...
no... I'm not.
You're lying.
Aren't you getting off on us
watching you like this?
Let's see you draw back
the meat curtains.
No... I can't masturbate
in front of...
but my fingers...
I'm so hot...
I'm going to cum...!
What's going on between you two?
This'll continue
as an extracurricular activity.
Hino?
What did you put inside of me?
It's punishment for getting
all horny with those guys.
I'm going to get all weird like this.
Take it off of me.
Sure. I'll take it off
the way you really like it.
Hino...
Where am I?
You like these kinds of sex games.
You're into bondage, right?
You like things
that feel good, right?
Let's take it off.
Stop!
Wow, it really suits you.
You look great, Prof.
You don't just
belong to Hino anymore.
You're our sex slave as well.
No...
Do you want us to
take off your chastity belt?
We'll take it off, but first
you have to suck my cock.
I hear you're good at it.
Hurry up, slut professor.
Pull down my zipper,
you cock sucking maniac.
Now take it in your mouth.
Hey, hey, hey...
Oooh... That feels good.
- What about me?
- Me too!
Hurry it up!
This way...
Yeah, that's it.
Here it comes. Here it comes.
Look at it! It's all dripping wet.
Look here, Professor. I want to see
you lick up your own pussy juice.
Let's do it together.
I'm going to cum!