Please be wake up.
Bird...
What are you saying?
Bird! I have seen a bird!
Bird? What's wrong?
What's going on?
World of Dream 3
Please beware of Godi.
Many ward numens has descended
to your world with you.
Hitomi...
Is really the descending body of ward numen.
But what should I do?
to look for other ward numens?
To ask them one by one?
And...
please remember...
Your strength derives from
loving and being loved.
You are a warrior of love.
When you find your lost loves,
you will be stronger than any others.
To turn loving and being loved to strength?
Do you mean
I should make love with all my heart?
What, it is you Shido?
I admire you with so much free time.
But I have to find out
the ward numens descending to this city.
Do you know what is ward numen?
It's impossible to know.
Do you want me go with you?
Where are you going?
Futaba, no need to pretend anymore.
Don't you like him?
Yes...
What do you mean YES?
I quarreled with him every time I meet him.
And it seems he loves other girls.
Maybe I... am not as good as those girls.
But you're denying.
In fact you fear of be abandoned and hurted.
So you look for reasons to elude your feeling.
That's right, maybe it is.
Now Futaba should be braver.
Be braver?
Welcome!
Good afternoon, Kengo.
Mia!
Is this shop yours?
I am working here.
Because I like animals very much.
Staying with these animals,
I feel something close.
It seemed that long long ago,
I lived with many animals.
But, do you feel I am cunning?
Defend these animals...
and say I like animals
I have to.
This is the rules of this world.
Who made these rules?
Sorry, I am not blaming you.
I know.
I sometimes dream.
Dream?
about a beautiful forest.
In that world...
Animals and human are living freely.
And you are also in my dream.
Me?
It seems we have met before.
Before we met for the first time,
You and me...
with you...
seemed to be friends long long ago.
Me too.
Really?
Then maybe...
we have the same dream.
Dream?
Mia.
Do you know what is ward numen?
Ward numen?
What is that?
You don't know it?
No, it's OK.
About the dream you mentioned just now,
What is the dream about?
I can't remember clearly.
In the dream...
I think...
we must be...
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Then...
that is only a dream.
But I really like you.
I like you too.
Mia, is it OK?
I have decided to give you my virginity.
I have decided to give Aoterubu my virginity.
Now?
What's wrong?
No.
Nothing.
Futaba!
Why are you here?
Futaba, wait!
Mia, sorry.
Let's postpone it.
Why, why is it Mia?
Why, why is it Hitomi?
Why not me?
Neika Sensei.
Are feeling calm now?
Yes, sorry to trouble you.
No problem, don't keep it in your mind.
Here have some.
Yes, excuse me.
Is that wonderful?
Yes...
But
Sex is the love song made of blood and flesh.
The repeating wave move me to the peak of pleasure.
In the burning happy flame,
I have gained nirvana many times.
Right, it's like the phoenix in the legend.
Sex is so great.
Don't you think so?
I am not so clear.
But you want to know it, right?
Futaba, teacher know you very well.
I know you feel very lonely.
So teacher want you to forget him.
by giving you a sweet dream.
No!
Teacher, please stop!
Please stop!
Do you really want me to stop?
OK, I'll stop then.
No! Don't stop.
Then shouldn't you be begging?
Yes.
I beg you, please go on.
You'd say you'll obey all of my orders.
I'll obey all of your orders.
Good. You're so lively, Futaba.
It's really hard.
What?
What's the matter with you?
Isn't it your important member?
This is something of a man.
Why... on my body?
No need for you to fear, Futaba.
This is only a dream.
Dream?
Right, you are now in dream.
In the dream, you are a ward numen
who have two sexual characters.
Miya.
In the dream, you can spread your love freely...
with men and women you loved.
Well...
I want it.
Is it very good?
OK, open black wing.
Fly with your desire.
I'm coming.
Oh, yeah.
It's just like this, do it at your own will.
It's a compensation for the love
you didn't get from Aoterubu.
Aoterubu
Love...
I have decided...
to give Aoterubu my virginity.
It has been late before we know it.
Sorry to keep you wating.
Mia.
Kengo, what's going on?
This late.
but I care for one thing at all time.
but you can call me.
I don't have your number.
And I want to see you too.
Mia, can you tell me the dream in details
which you mentioned to me earlier?
That dream?
What's wrong with that dream?
I hope you can remember it carefully.
To me. No, to us.
that is very important.
It is so...
Wait a minute.
Kengo.
Stop, Aoterubu.
You can't bully a friend.
What are you saying?
Please look carefully.
Futaba?! Futaba, is it you?
Right.
But her looks... could it...
That woman was a ward numen in her last life too.
She can't get your love.
so she turned to be a night ghost with to much sorrow.
It also means...
the one who made her to be a night ghost...
is you, Aoterubu.
Can't get my love?
Forgive me, Futaba.
It's all because of me not noticing your love.
Mia.
No, no.
You must do it with me.
You'll enjoy the happiness, Aoterubu.
Let me go!
Does it taste good?
It is effective to both man and woman.
What?
Look.
You're so energized.
Stop!
Shido.
Stop.
Futaba!
Miya.
If it wasn't for you,
Aoterubu would have loved me.
Aoterubu is mine!
Aoterubu...
Wonderful, wonderful.
Get it?
It's time to get your love strength.
You...
I see.
You are not the real Aoterubu.
What do you mean?
I have remembered.
tyat I was the ward numen in dream world.
Lusano's forest, Miyu.
So Mia is Miyu.
Well, it's too good.
Miyu.
Futaba, Futaba.
Are you OK?
Kengo.
Mia.
Sorry, Mia.
Sorry I have done the wrong thing to you.
No problem, this is not your fault.
Yes, don't mind.
Thank you...
Kengo.
Are you willing to love me?
I'll love you.
I love you now.
Me too.
That woman said something strange.
You are not the true Aoterubu.
What did she mean?
And...
Who is that man?