It should have beautiful flesh
and bone inside of the skin.
I am beautiful
and chase after the reality.
How can't I know?
Because of the pain to twist the face,
it looked more beautiful.
The breath of sorrow.
Also the frown
with the wrinkle between the lines.
And.
So sweet blood.
Only you.
Fruit in the garden.
Let me taste it.
Let me tast your sorrow.
Your sweet blood.
With the taste of fruit.
It is the form of our love.
Come on.
Let me see the proof.
No.
Stop.
Awudalupu.
Sorry, I am late.
What you did is not love.
You ruin such a beautiful thing.
You are happy.
You are a pervert.
You want to brainwash you.
My body.
Disappear little by little.
Don't let you get away from it.
What?
Please remember this.
Next time,
I will scratch a cut on her body.
Disappear.
Being brainwashed?
No.
Before being brainwashed,
you killed yourself.
Only the soul ran away.
He must return to the nightmare world.
He will get the new body too.
Sorry, if I am here early.
No. I am happy if you want to save me.
Kalusia, this cut...
I am ok. No big deal.
This is the late apology.
I am here to tell you
about the true love.
Awudalupu.
Awudalupu...
No, I am not Awudalupu.
I am...
The Dream world 2.
Chenwu...
Chenwu.
Yes, I am Chenwu.
So weird.
Good morning.
You are...
I am Weai.
Why are you here?
I am here to thank you
for saving me before.
Thank you.
Danger.
Thank you...
If you want to say thanks,
I got the gift.
So lucky.
What a great gift.
Chenwu.
No good. It swollen so big.
No good.
With such a strenght...
Chenwu.
Wait, Sonya, this is...
Say no more.
Sorry it is my fault.
No, this is not your fault, Weai.
No. It is Sonya.
Chenwu is no good.
Because you and Weai do some
dirty things, so they got your wrong.
Someone got you wrong idea
and hit people.
It is the girl? Sonya.
Yes, why are you
different from your sister?
What?
It is always Mai...
The sister of Mai
is not to pretend being cute?
What? What is that tone?
I am telling the truth.
What?
You two don't.
Leave me alone.
Shiro.
Sonya seemed to be strange.
Chenwu, you fool...
Shiro, where are you?
Shiro.
Shiro... hurry...
Shiro... where are you?
Shiro...
I got it.
Ok, don't move. Don't move.
Awudalupu.
Awudalupu...
Here again.
Awudalupu.
No, my name is...
You are finally here.
That voice is in my dream?
Is that yours?
My name is Acemilona.
I am the fairy to keep everything
in order in this world.
And then, you are...
I am Chenwu.
That is your current name?
But in the past.
You are one of the fairy, Awudalupu.
Awudalupu.
It had the war before.
That dream world has the fight
with the nightmare world.
Those creatures from
the nightmare world come across.
One of the powerful
is called Drangon Niskarma.
Everyone called him Ilong.
The battle of Ilong is very bad.
Fairies all died.
I am the last one.
So, we lost?
No, please seal Ilong.
But.
But what?
The power of the seal
is getting weaker.
Ilong wanted to come back.
He still wanted to destroy the world.
The place we lived...
Why?
Because Ilon found somethng...
He discovered the leader being you.
Many fairy will switch to your world.
We are the fairy.
But can deftet him.
Please think about it.
You are the fairy, Awudalupu.
You switch love and being love
to the power fo fighters
When you lose love,
you can be stronger.
That is right.
It is what the warrior loves.
I am love... warrior...
Please recall it.
Please recall it...
Please...
Please hand on...
Great, you awake.
Weai, Lian. Did you save me?
If you want to thank me,
say thanks to Shiro.
It is him to tell us
you are in the pool.
It is the fault of Shiro.
Forget it. It is the same.
Thank you, Shiro.
He is a naughty cat.
Weai, hard work.
Yes, no choice.
From the beginning, it disappeared.
What?
Since I discovered
I asked bystanders to help.
I remembered that man called Whom...
Yes, that man was called whom.
Did you say whom?
You, never won over me once.
I won 48 times.
48 straight.
You skip classes up here.
You...
I remember you are the new...
I am Yuko.
You seemed down, captain.
No.
No matter what, you can't win.
You are angry at yourself,
but no choice.
Really?
What are you talking about?
Teacher, I like to tease you.
Whom, you are great.
You are strong and powerful.
But you just forgot...
Your real power.
Let teacher help you out.
Teacher, what do you want?
There, it is there. Lick there.
That is right...
You have a good skill.
It seemed to be ready.
Let's enjoy the happiness
for not seeing such a long time.
What did you say?
Fucking good... good...
Again, push it more.
Like this, push it more.
Yes, to solve your darkness.
This way, You can be more powerful.
To accpet the darkness.
When you give it to the dark power.
You can be stronger than anyone else.
You want to win, right.
You want to win over him right.
You want to win Awudalupu, right?
Hurry, come one...
Swear to the darkness.
The proof injected into my body.
Fairy...
You are falling.
The flower is beautiful.
Yes, those flower.
We need to care for it with our love.
They will return love too.
But, sorry.
If I can come early.
It won't last longer.
No, if you can help me out,
I am happy.
Weird.
I may have heard from somewhere.
About being late,
what happened to Sonya?
She will help
when Chenwu wanted to help.
Sonya...
Forget it, think about it.
Only I an Mai.
No matter what happened, no one knows.
What...
You...
Lawulubalu.
Whom, why you...
Whom, ahead of you.
Also a fairy before rebirth.
What did she say?
Ilong also found out.
It found out you are the leader.
Many fairies come to your world.
You are the nightmare.
Your memory got back.
If Whom is Lawulubalu,
why was he with nightmare?
It seemed to forget.
You seemed to forget Lawulubelu being
a nightmare after touching Ilong.
Lawulubalu became one of nightmare.
No, stop.
Open Mai.
In the mind of Lawulubalu,
he wanted to make love with a woman.
No.
Mai.
No...
You see. Check this out.
An orgasm.
Mai.
No...
You want to run away?
Chenwu...
Mai.
Mai is the rebirth of Kalusia.
This is the apology for being late.
Let me tell you what the real love is.
Awudalupu.
Mai...
Did you remember the dream world?
I always have when I was young.
I thougt it was the dream.
Beside me,
I don't want anyone else to come here.
Mai.
Awudalupu.
Please love me, Kalusia.
Just like before.
Mai.
I am Chenwu.
I am the boy next door.
Mai, your pussy is so wet.
Chenwu.
Mai, your ass hole is beautiful.
Chenwu, your dick is very big.
Mai.
Fail?
Forget it. Lalulubalu is an experiment.
What?
From the forehead of Chenwu's dick,
it came with tasty honey.
Mai, you juice is also
tasty from your pussy.
Chenwu, get in.
Find your memory from my body.
Mai...
How can it be?
Mai.
Chenwu.
I am ready to fuck, Mai.
Fuck here.
Your pussy.
So wet, so warm, so good.
Me too.
Your dick.
Keep shaking in my body.
Mai, I am moving.
Chenwu.
Yes, like that. Hurry.
No.
I can't... ready to come.
I am coming.
Mai.
Chenwu.
I got a wonderful guy this time.
You are...
Your waist shakes so well.
Your pussy is wet.
Look. The expression is good.
Look. Madam.
Have a date with your husband alone?
Don't be this way.
You don't want
your husband to see this photo?
Madam.
I am almost there.
How can you be so reasonable
when you are a bitch in heat?
So horny.
It is definitely different from
the girls in the class.
Fool, of course it is different.
No voice, sister.
It is not good to hear the voice
of female in men's room.
So wet.
Sister, you got excited so easy.
You can feel more in this place.
It is coming out, sister.