The dream world
Mr. Awudalupu.
Who is it?
Whose voice is it?
Mr. Awudalupu.
Please love me...
Awudalupu.
No. That is not my name.
I am...
Please give me more love...
Please give me love...
Again...
Love more deeply...
Awudalupu...
No...
I am not Awudalupu.
I am...
No... fool...
It is the dream.
I have this dream because keeping seeing this.
No... the fool...
But anyway, I can sleep more.
Chenwu.
When do you want to sleep until?
What are you doing, grandfather Wu...
Chenwu.
If I am the enemy, you will be dead by now.
I said...
I don't want to have the life
being attacked at sleep like grandpa.
I said.
Why did someone want to get your life,
the chairman of karate club?
Need to say anymore.
I will say this because
I want to have more alert sense.
What are you talking about?
Damn... fool...
Damn.
Chenwu.
38.
39.
40.
41.
Take a look at yourself. What?
Your wrist strenght is off.
You need to practice more.
44.
What are you jokking about?
I have some other things to do.
51.
52.
53.
54.
55...
94.
95.
96.
Good morning.
Lian, good morning.
It is about time.
Yes, sir.
I promised him to study
at school earlier today.
What?
Yes... yes...
We promised each other.
Damn.
No choice. Four more and go.
97, 98, 99, 100.
Lian, thanks for saving me.
If you don't save me.
Not sure when I have to have
this training unitl.
What are you talking about?
We do have the appointment.
Do you forget?
I forgot.
Damn... almost the test time.
Not my business if you have the bad grade.
This...
Lian.
Mr. Lian.
Lian lord.
I rely on you.
Who cared about you?
What are you talking about?
You always rely on me.
Always like that.
It is not for the sake of you, Chenwu.
What?
Weren't we born on the same hospital?
We are the friends by ten minutes apart?
Who cared?
Grandpa wanted you to take over it.
They are different.
This guy.
A cold person.
It is no good.
You two, don't fight.
As long as we fight, the war can't be stopped.
Mai.
No... not like the way you think.
This is the love we try to show.
Yes, Lian.
No comment.
You see... they both have the good relationship.
Yes...
No matter what, Lian is like a brother to me.
No comment.
Lian, you don't need this kind of
brother to take care of you.
What are you talking about?
Sonya, you.
That is what I try to say.
Hard to stand when he was born
earlier by ten minutes.
He only knew Karate but not good at study.
Sorry... tom girl...
What are you talking about?
You kept bringing up something I cared.
Ok...
Chenwu.
At elementary school,
Sonya won by one point for the race.
Did she still remember it?
That kind of thing...
How could it be?
It must be like that.
It is long time ago.
I am better now.
Of course.
You are the man.
Something like this from you.
Hard to believe you are a girl.
Learn from Mai.
So sorry.
Ok... you two, don't fight.
Mai, why did you come to school?
No, from today I have a part time at this time.
I remember you work at the tea house
called Coffee Break, right.
Sister, isn't that shop opposite from that school?
I feel it is lonely to separate from everyone.
Yes, it must be lonely.
What? Chenwu.
You like sister so you agree with her.
Anything wrong?
Damn, I like Chenwu too.
Really?
Yes. I like Lian and Sonya.
And the pet, Pote with Mike at section three.
I like the frog, Kolo the most.
Onch, you...
Fight along the river.
The old trick.
But the item that the captain
had was out of date.
So noisy.
From the past,
fighting should be along the river?
Up to you.
You never won over me up to now?
I won over you for 48 times.
So noisy.
You can't be so boast more.
I have heard for 48 times.
Wait, you two stop.
Mai, say something.
Don't you say no more fighting?
Don't stop me, Mai.
This is about men.
Damn...
Hard to stop them.
Sister.
Damn, lian.
Chenwu never stopped what he wanted to do.
Damn.
Check this out.
Come on.
A must hit trick. So good.
Whoever moves first loses the game.
No.
I hate it.
A possibility.
No good.
It hurt... hard to handle.
This is the failure in my life.
I was defeated.
But on the other hand.
Your underwear matched well
with your appearance.
And the belt.
Some attraction as an adult.
It is shocked for Sonya to wear
this woman like underwear.
It hurt...
Compared with the wound,
the flap from Sonya is more powerful.
Damn, Chenwu,
you are a fool and sicko.
I will die if
I don't go to the hospital.
White.
Danger.
What happened...
Why is it a dream?
What is this?
Didn't I go to the heaven?
This is...
No...
Forgive me.
No... I can't...
What is this?
What is going on?
I can't...
About to go.
Don't come here.
Awudalupu.
Are you ok? Awudalupu.
Did you call me?
I...
Yes, I am Awudalupu.
I am the fairy to protect
this fairy world.
Awudalupu, did you sleep?
Awudalupu, how is the battle?
No...
Because a hole on the side is open,
the nightmare keeps coming.
Everyone does his best
to hold on to it.
I handle here.
You go the the forest of ring.
The forest of ring.
He is Muna from the beast tribe?
Dalo attacked.
No way to leave you behind.
Leave me alone, hurry.
I can't see the way I am.
I may kill you by a chance.
Lawulubalu.
I know.
No, don't come here.
No.
No, stop.
Help.
Father, help.
Awudalupu.
Sorry, I am late.
No. I am happy you can save me.
Not a big deal with such a small cut.
It is no good
if infected by the virus.
So itch.
It is ok. Let me handle it.
Any feeling? I am happy.
Why did you do such a thing?
Father let me handle you?
Awudalupu.
What?
Muna's father, Winsarao.
I am dying.
Lion king, Winsarao.
Death is another ritual for rebirth.
I am not afraid of death.
But I am worried
about my daughter, Muna.
Because the borderline is weaker
and more creatures.
You have to be the leader
of beast tribe.
Don't worry.
I will take care of her.
Thank you. You let her feel happy.
What I meant was...
You will face so many enemies.
Nothing to worry about
if the couple gets together.
So I said...
That is.
You have feeling for me.
I am so happy.
Muna, about this...
I fall in love to you
at the beginning.
From the beginning,
I want to give you my first time.
The tough had sticking feeling.
Awudalupu.
I... had...
No...
Are you ok?
My body had a big...
Awudalupu has a big dick.
Shaking inside of my body.
It became so big.
That is the proof for my love.
I can feel it...
Something good is inside of my body.
I am moving.
Be gentle.
I am cumming.
Cumming.
No.
A dream again...
Yes.
I was hit by a truck.
And then...
And then what?
It seemed not to get hurt.
Where is this place?
No. This... this...
Too good.
Chenwu.
You fool...
Your waist shakes so well.
Your pussy is wet.
Look. The expression is good.
Look. Madam.
Have a date with your husband alone?
Don't be this way.
You don't want
your husband to see this photo?
Madam.
I am almost there.
How can you be so reasonable
when you are a bitch in heat?
So horny.
It is definitely different from
the girls in the class.
Fool, of course it is different.
No voice, sister.
It is not good to hear the voice
of female in men's room.
So wet.
Sister, you got excited so easy.
You can feel more in this place.
It is coming out, sister.