No... This isn't...
Don't worry. I'll love you
for the rest of your life.
No. We're related by
marriage... This can't... No...
I've always wanted to be like this with you.
Why... Why am I feeling pleasure? It's
so good... More... Fuck me more...
I'm so happy Miwa!
This isn't right, Takashi!
You can't stop me anymore. You know it too.
I know you feel my cock going crazy
inside you because I'm so happy!
You're mine Miwa...
Th... This can't be...
Miwa, I'm going to cum inside you.
N... No! Not that! Please don't! lf
you do that, I'll get pregnant...
I want you to feel my dick cum inside.
I want you to feel it with your entire body.
No... Stop... Stop!
I'm going to cum!
No!
I can feel you...
I can feel your hot cum inside me...
Thanks for the food!
Takashi, you're in an unusually good mood.
Did something good happen?
Something has to happen once in awhile.
What?
Well, about Miwa.
Look! There's butter on her nose!
Brother, my revenge has just begun.
MY BROTHER'S WIFE
PART 2
And he's safe!
What? What are you smiling at?
You're in a good mood today!
Really?
Yeah, really!
You better not have done
anything weird with my picture!
I wonder.
Why you... Pervert!
Huh? How did he... What
happened to you, Takashi?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Takashi, I need to speak to you.
Yes?
Let's just forget about
what happened yesterday.
That was just a little mistake... Right?
We both just let things
get out of hand... Right?
'Just let it get out of hand'?
Yes, it was a mistake we
made in the moment...
Then do you want me to tell him?
Miwa! Then what about this?
Why does my dick get like this?
Are you saying this is just a mistake?
Stop! Takashi. Please, don't
say such selfish things.
You're to blame for this! You're
the one who is hurting me!
Please, stop!
It's so hard and hot...
I... thInk I'm going to go crazy...
Someone... Someone heIp
me! I can't resist his penis.
Whoever has the joker gets
the upper hand, Miwa.
You won't be able to part from me anymore.
More... Harder... Why...
Why does it feel so good?
Cum... Cum Inside me. I
want your hot cum Inside...
I'm going to take this next.
I'm sure this is still a virgin...
This will belong just to me.
I think It's just the fInishing
touches left In his training...
But...
You're so popular with the
girls now. I'm happy but...
I'm getting a little jealous.
That's not true. You're my number one.
To me, you're my number one woman.
Really? Really? Then prove it to me.
Sure.
Hey, what is this?
It's a bra!
What is this doing here?
Probably one of the girls changed here.
Lucky! Finders keepers!
Stop being so mean! They'll
hear me if you do that!
But it turned you on, right?
Oh, do whatever you want!
Well... I... With Shinji yesterday...
No way! And?
It wasn't all that it's hyped up to be!
No way...
Really! Shinji was so nervous that it
totally ruined what I had imagined.
That sucks!
It was completely different
from what I wanted.
MESSAGE: TO SLAVE...
COME TO MY HOUSE 8 PM.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Guess Satoshi is coming
home early today. Damn.
No sex today...
Where's Satoshi?
I think he'll be home soon.
I see. That's too bad.
S... Sure... but...
It's okay. Misa's coming over at eight.
Are you studying together?
Something like that. Thanks for dinner.
Good evening!
Takashi is waiting for you.
Okay.
Good evening.
Yeah...
What's with that lame reply when
you're the one who told me to be here?
You're being rude to the
hottest girl at our school.
Are you sure you're allowed to
talk to your Master like that?
Plus you're five minutes late.
Five minutes? Come on, that's not that bad.
Let's see...
What should I order my slave to do today?
Is that why you told me to be here?
Hey! What are you doing? You pervert!
I said, do you think you're allowed
to talk to your Master like that?
I'm sorry Master...
Then kiss me.
I've brought you some tea.
Guys...
S... sis...
You could have knocked, you know!
Are you two dating...?
So much for the mood. Let's go for a walk.
Brother's going to be home soon anyway.
Ow!
You're sleeping alone?
l wonder what happened to Satoshi?
He left today on a business trip, didn't he?
I got a call from him on my cell earlier.
He said he had to go on a last minute
trip and wanted me to look after you.
You shouldn't lie, Miwa. Do
you hate me that much?
That's not it. This is wrong. I can't
continue to betray Satoshi...
And you have Misa.
Are you jealous Miwa?
That's not it.
If you two start dating, I'll be...
Will you be relieved?
Even while I kiss Misa and my
cock rubs up against her pussy?
Even while we have passionate
sex like we did yesterday...
...and fuck each other
like we're crazed animals?
Even while we lick each other
and she plays with my dick?
Please stop... Please...
I'm sorry, Miwa.
You won't lie anymore?
Yes.
It's so hard... So big...
Hurry... I want it...
Miwa... How many men have you been with?
Three.
Including me?
Yes.
So my brother wasn't your first. I'm glad.
T... Takashi... That's... It's embarrassing.
Don't worry. You'll be in ecstasy real soon.
My brother hasn't fucked you here, right?
Y... Yes...
That's why I'm going to make this mine.
It's embarrassing. Please, it's
too embarrassing there. Stop.
No!
My big hard cock is going
inside your asshole right now.
No... You can't... It... Feels so good!
More... Fuck me harder Takashi!
Yes?
What's wrong? It's Sunday.
I wanted to see you...
Oh, come on.
I heard rumors that you have a girlfriend now.
What's that about?
A lot of people are talking it.
I told you, Misa is related to me.
You know that she's my
brother's wife's younger sister.
I wonder. You're not related by blood.
What can I do to make you believe me?
Well, your training is pretty much over so...
...it might be best to end our relationship.
Plus, you're able to have
a normal relationship now.
But... Don't say such sad things, Professor...
You're the only one for me.
Yes. You've gotten good at seducing women.
You arouse our motherly instincts.
Damn, you can see through everything.
Jeez... What am I going to do with you.
Then, let's go on our last date.
Can I do this since it's our last time?
Well, I'm really not into
this type of stuff but... I...
You've gotten good at convincing women.
I'm starting to feel a bit strange.
Me too, Professor.
My entire body is throbbing...
This is too much...
It's okay, Professor. I won't hurt you.
Hurry... Give it to me...
Professor, do you love it that much?
I love it... I love it so much...
A Professor shouldn't be saying such things.
You need to be punished.
It hurts! It hurts! Take it off!
It hurts! S... Stop...
What is this? How could this...
Professor, do you want to cum once?
No, I want it inside me... Thrust it in!
Fine.
It feels so good!
Professor! It's all thanks to
you! I've gotten better right?
You... had talent... from the start...
You can... make woman
do... whatever you want...
It's an amazing talent...
Professor, can l?
Do it! Do whatever you want!
You can do whatever you want to me!
I'm putting it in, Professor.
It's coming in. It's coming in...
My stomach is making noises!
No! It's going to come out!
It's going to come out! Front and back!
I won't be able to part with you...
Thus, I continued my relationships
with Miwa and the Professor.
And my demands towards
Misa began to Increase.
Misa was in love wIth me.
LateIy, I've begun to wonder If
she deliberateIy lost our bet.
I decided I won't go all the way wIth her...
I'm going to hold off on that
for a very special event.
Come on, let's.
I'm tired today.
That's what you said last night.
No...
Damn it! She told me she
wouldn't fuck him anymore!
Stop.
Just watch... Tomorrow's the
last day Misa is my slave...
I'm going to go ahead wIth the final event!
Today's the last day. Misa, do you love me?
Then come upstairs when l call you. Okay?
Yes?
T... Takashi... You can't!
Satoshi will be home soon.
Plus, Misa is here, isn't she?
You said you wouldn't
fuck my brother anymore!
You lied.
There wasn't anything I could do.
Then you should have told him about us.
I can't...
Because you love him?
No... Because I feel so sorry for him...
He's been mocking me ever since I was little.
He deserves to get something like this!
I'm going to divorce Satoshi...
Then leave him today.
Please wait a little more...
I can't wait anymore.
You're just trying to manipulate me.
That's why we're going
to make this clear today.
Misa!
What? What are you planning to do?
Do you love me?
Yes.
Then come over here and take a good look.
Miwa and I don't have
an ordinary relationship.
What do you mean by 'ordinary relationship'?
I mean, this type of relationship.
Take a good look! We've been
making love like this every night.
Stop! Not in front of Misa. Stop!
Takashi and sis are...
That's why you didn't have sex with me?
You don't love me?
If you love me, fuck me! Do it to me too!
THREESOME WITH SISTERS
TakashI, your revenge is over now.
I'm going to join in too!