Miwa...
Takashi...
Takashi! You're going to be late.
Hurry up and get dressed. Breakfast is ready.
I'm TakashI Kagura. I'm sure you've already
notIced, but I'm just your average guy.
For Heaven sake, when are you going
to be able to get up on your own?
At this rate, you'll never be able to
get a decent job in the real world.
Being on time is the basic rule of society.
ThIs is my brother Satoshi.
I've been livIng with him and
his wife since our parents died.
My brother is a successful businessman
and very strict about everything.
He's perfect in every respect.
He was the top of his class; he's
great at sports; and he's handsome.
I have a complex because
everyone compares me to him.
I can't do anything better than my
brother, so I can't really blame them.
But the reason i hate my brother most is...
...because he made Miwa his own.
Miwa, the woman I'm in love with,
is my brother's wife.
MY BROTHER'S WIFE
PART 1
Good morning Takashi.
Good morning.
Owww... That hurt!
Wake up already! Jeez...
That doesn't mean you have to hit me!
I didn't hit you. I slowly
swung my bag at you.
Anybody else would have dodged it.
Stop trying to flirt with me already!
You are so conceited!
Why would I, the hottest girl at
our school, make a move on you!
Then leave me alone. This is just bullying.
Did you just realize that? You're
really something Takashi.
What? Are you angry?
You need to lighten up. You're
not like your brother at all.
I wonder why Satoshi married her?
This little demon is Miwa's
younger sister Misa.
She's been followIng me around
since elementary school.
I'm positive I'm a better than she is, but...
Hey! Don't leave me behind! You're
supposed to be my bug repellent!
We can't have a pest following around
a gorgeous girl like me! I said wait!
They're going to announce the
mid-term exam results today.
You haven't forgotten about our bet, right?
Of course I haven't!
Today's the day when you become my slave!
MEIJYO COLLEGE
MID-TERM EXAM RESULT CHART
I win.
8. TAKASHI KAGURA
9. MISA TOKIWA
I win.
8. TAKASHI KAGURA
9. MISA TOKIWA
How? You've never scored
better than me! Not even once!
You cheated, didn't you?
No, I didn't. You shouldn't
accuse people like that.
But, how... No way...
You haven't forgotten about our bet, right?
This doesn't count. There's
no way this could happen.
There's no backing out now. You promised.
Oh, fine then. I guess our
childhood friendship is over.
I don't like people who break their promises.
Fine.
I'll do whatever you want for one week.
That's more like it.
What? What do you want me to do?
I'll take my time thinking about it.
Look forward to it.
You better not make me do something weird.
What kind of weird stuff?
I... I don't know!
Takashi, why are you grinning like that for?
Oh. It's nothing.
You got a 93 on the
math test this time, right?
You made simple math
mistakes and got two wrong.
It's too bad. You could have gotten a 100.
You need to take things more
seriously and stop daydreaming.
Your brother Satoshi
would have gotten a 100.
But you're you, so you
shouldn't let that bother you.
Yes...
Hello?
Why?
But... Give me an explanation at least...
I wonder if it's her boyfriend?
But...
Then... What were we?
TEXT MESSAGE, SENDER TAKASHI.
TITLE: TO MY SLAVE.
MESSAGE: WHAT COLOR
ARE YOUR PANTIES?
MESSAGE: YOU'RE OKAY IF
OUR FRIENDSHIP IS OVER?
MESSAGE: MAYBE I'LL JACK
OFF TO THIS TONIGHT.
Damn it! How could he!
MESSAGE: MAYBE I'LL JACK
OFF TO THIS TONIGHT.
Professor Azusa, what happened?
Fuck you! Who do you think I am?
I'm Azusa. People used to
call me the idol of Meijyo!
Professor, you can't be lying around
in a place like this. Professor!
Satoshi! You're the one to blame.
This is all your fault, Satoshi!
I'm Takashi. His younger brother.
Satoshi! It's your fault!
Oh Jeez... lf people see you here
like this, you're going to get fired!
Come on. Get up, Professor!
I can't.
What to do...
Come on, Professor. Get a hold of yourself.
Well, I'm going home.
Takashi, wait.
Professor, I thought you were drunk?
I've sobered up. Thank you.
That's not cool, Professor.
I'm sorry.
I got my heart broken...
So... Cheer me up tonight.
Just for tonight.
Professor...
Your cock is so hard and
big... I can't wait anymore...
You shouldn't be doing this
with a professor... But...
I want your dick.
Professor, you're beautiful.
Come... Come Takashi.
Right there... That's where I feel it.
Yes! Yes Takashi! It feels so good. Fuck
me. I want your hard cock inside me.
Huh? I think I'm nervous.
Don't worry. I'll take control.
See? It's getting hard already.
It feels so good. Yes, Takashi. It feels great.
Professor...
Takashi... More... Fuck me
harder all the way inside!
Yes!
No, I think I'm about to cum!
Please, cum with me. More...
Your cock is getting bigger.
We're going to cum together!
You were great Takashi.
Professor.
I'm telling the truth.
Professor... Please go out with me!
I don't like people who
can't make up their mind.
I thought so...
You got your heart broken
by my brother, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
You were calling his name earlier
and you thought I was him.
I was only a replacement for
him, wasn't I? For my brother...
But I knew it was you inside the taxi.
I dated your brother, but
that was a long time ago.
You have something special.
You just have to polish it.
It's different from what
Satoshi has, but it's your own.
You need to have more confidence.
I got it! I'll make you shine!
I'll make you into the perfect
man that women can't resist!
Really?
Really. So let's go for round two!
See! You totally have it in you!
KAGURA
This is not good...
How dare you stay out all night without
calling us! Where the hell were you?
Do you have any idea how worried we were?
We kept calling your cell.
Why didn't you answer?
I didn't realize...
Honey, he's okay, so...
I'm sure Takashi is sorry.
Be quiet.
I have a responsibility to raise
him to be a decent human being.
What's that look on your face!
If there's something you want to say, say it!
Nothing.
I'll call next time. All right?
Wait! I said, wait!
I'm sorry. Can we just let it go?
Come on. Takashi apologized so...
Don't ever make us worry like that again!
I knew It was my fault, but...
I couldn't tell him where I was and
my brother's words made me angry.
I have a responsibility to raIse
him to be a decent human being.
Mind your own business!
It's me. I'm coming in, okay?
Sure.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Your brother left already. Make sure you eat.
Your brother was really worried about you.
You two are family, so make
sure you call next time.
I'm sorry.
Oh that's right. Misa was really worried too.
Give her a call, okay?
It's Sunday, so get some rest.
Okay.
First, we need to do
something about your hair.
Let's get it cut at the salon I go to.
You're not a bad looking guy, so
you'll be okay even if it's a bit flashy.
I think this might look good.
Yup! It looks great on you.
From now on, you need to
go to trendy places like this.
See! Everyone's looking at you.
I'm home.
Welcome hom- Takashi?!
What happened to you?!
Does it look strange?
Of course not! It really
suits you. You look great!
Good.
You stayed out the entire night
and now this. What's going on?
Did something happen?
There's someone I've had
on my mind lately so...
What a lucky girl... I wonder
what kind of person she is?
'It's you, Miwa.' That's what I wanted to say.
Oh no! And I'm still not done.
I should go wash my face.
S... Sorry!
I saw it...
Miwa's...
...naked body.
That night, I was too excited
and had troubIe fallng asleep.
M... Miwa! But... I...
By the way, what time is it now?
1 2:30. Were you still sleeping?
Yeah...
You better not have shown
my picture to anyone!
Are you worried?
Jeez! That's enough!
Then you need to listen to what l say.
Fine. Five more days.
Getting down to business...
l want to see your breasts.
I have to study so I'll be waiting.
Yeah, yeah. Good night.
Right there... There... If you play
with the outer side of the clit...
...most women will writhe in pleasure!
No! Stop! I...
Class time is over.
I want it from behind.
Please stick your cock all the way inside me.
Takashi... More! More!
That's... No! It's embarrassing!
I can't anymore...
l'm going to cum again!
Takashi, you were amazing. You have talent.
I don't think so...
Today, a bunch of the female
students were talking about you.
They were saying how
handsome you look now.
I got kind of jealous.
Yeah?
What?
Nothing...
I thought I might have said a
little too much the other day...
It's okay. I'm not upset about it. .
We only have each other. How do I say...
We need to be there for each other.
Yeah, I know.
Good. I'll be on my way now.
By the way, did something
happen between you and Miwa?
You guys weren't talking much during dinner.
No, it's nothing.
Good. I want you get along with Miwa.
I know you had a thing for her at one time.
See you.
He knew!
He knew I was Infatuated with
Miwa but he took her for himseIf.
I won't forgive him. I won't forgive him.
I'm going to have my revenge! I'm
going to take her away from him!
I'll be away on a business trip for three days,
but call me on my cell if anything happens.
I'll be fine. Takashi will be here too.
Okay. Off I go then.
Have a safe trip.
Good. I'm goIng to go
ahead wIth my plan tonight!
What? Did you want to go in first?
Please! Get out! No!
Do you know who's been on my mind?
Yes, it's you Miwa!
You always talked to me in the morning.
Those moments were the happiest
moments in my boring days.
I understand. I understand, so
let's talk in the living room.
But my brother... He can do
everything better than me, but...
He stole you away from me! That's
why I'm going to take you back.
This is my revenge.
I'll scream!
You know you can't!
Do you want the neighbors to find out
about such an embarrassing thing?
Fine... Then... Just with my mouth...
I've waited for this moment for so long!
Miwa, I really love you. More
than anyone else in the world.
What's happening to me?
I'm gettIng wet. I can't be... But... But...
I want It....
Miwa, l can't hold myself back
anymore. You feel the same way right?
No, l told you all I'll do is lick
you. You'll have to cum with this.
No! I can't hold it anymore! I
want to feel your everything!
I can't anymore!
No! Not that! Stop!
No! Stop! No!
No... No...