Brother.
How did it go, Mr. Suzusaki?
It wasn't good.
I got the immigration
department's help...
to investigate departure records
for the past month...
but there's no records
on Nezu and Nozomi.
Please don't give up, brother.
Thanks.
Half Acre Mansion.
Half Acre Mansion?
Don't misunderstand me!
I protected Asuka from Nezu.
What do you mean by that?
He said Satoshi disturbed a very
important ceremony in America...
six years ago.
Nezu held a big grudge
against Satoshi.
Why did he take Nozomi?
He told me that he needed Nozomi
for the "family circle."
You saw it, too.
Nezu uses strange magic.
Nezu... Family Circle...
The Night of Beltane...
The state of Maine in America...
and the Half Acre Mansion.
But, that's the place...
Yes, the place where
I lost my memory...
and where your parents
bodies were found.
The key to this incident
is in my lost memory.
Nezu and Nozomi must be there too.
Wow, this is great!
This is making me dizzy.
Why are you going to
Half Acre Mansion?
Can't we stay there?
I asked at the airport and confirmed
the place is registered as a hotel.
The owner changed
a few years ago.
Now it's a bar and lodge, but...
Is there something dangerous?
No, it's not, but...
But?
It's just not a place where
foreign tourists stay.
I stayed there a long time ago.
All right, let's go.
What's wrong, Chief?
Oh, nothing.
Hello?
Is anybody here?
What do you want?
Well, are you the manager?
No, we don't operate here
in that kind of way.
Who are you?
I'm just a freeloader.
The owner of this place is
fixing the backyard door.
Satoshi?!
Bill!
Big Bill!
Is that you?!
Satoshi! Satoshi!
I've never even dreamed that
I would ever see you again.
I... I can't breathe!
Let me go, Bill!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got so excited, I couldn't take
my hands off of you.
You haven't changed at all.
How long has it been?
Four years.
Are you the owner of this place?
Yes, I'm the owner.
What happened to your job
as a newspaper journalist?
I quit two years ago.
Six years ago, after I was involved
with that incident...
my company felt very uncomfortable
keeping me on as a journalist.
I see.
So I quit and used my retirement
bonus to buy this place.
But, why did you have
to buy this place?
I don't know.
Somehow my mind has
strong ties with this place.
I lost my memory, but something
is telling me to stay here.
Memory?
Hey, Satoshi. Why don't you
introduce me to these ladies?
This is Haruka Sakimizu...
and this is my assistant,
Asuka Kashiwagi.
Kashiwagi?
Yes.
This is one of my best sources of
information from the old days...
and also my best
friend, Bill Toargia.
Bill said that he also
lost his memory.
Bill lost his memory after the murders
that happened here six years ago.
After Nora's death.
Nora?
Let's all talk about this later.
Bill, do you have rooms for us?
Yes, plenty.
Then we'll stay here.
Let's talk at dinner.
All right.
I'll take you to your room.
I understand what you said, but I
haven't seen that man or the girl...
in the past month.
I see.
River Banks is a small town.
People would talk if a middle-age
Japanese man and a girl visited here.
I guess so.
The only Japanese person who's
in town, except for you guys, is...
Oh, new guests must be here.
Is Rumiko.
Me?
It's nothing.
But it's good timing.
I'll introduce you.
Rumiko Higuchi, she's a
student from Japan.
Nice to meet you.
And her friend, Kate.
This is my best friend Satoshi.
And this is Asuka and Haruka.
Nice to meet you.
What's going on, Bill?
You have new guests?
Let me introduce Amy
and her boyfriend Clark.
He's my best friend.
A historical site scholar?
Yes, he said there's some important
historical spot around here.
He came here from
Germany four weeks ago.
I see.
He is a very quiet man.
Is that all of your guests?
Yes, we also have old-man Louis.
He must be drinking at
the bar in the town now.
Don't get excited for that woman!
Asuka! I'm not...
Both of you don't act like
father and daughter...
or brother and sister,
but just like a couple.
N... no way! Impossible...
Impossible...?!
What's impossible?!
Well, nothing.
I guess you're very weak
in front of Asuka.
Keep out of this!
And thanks for the meal.
Bill, is the bar open?
Yes, unless I go to sleep.
Asuka... Sakimizu,
please rest well tonight.
We'll start investigating
tomorrow morning.
Yes.
Haruka, please don't be sad.
I'm sure we can find Nozomi.
I think so, too.
Oh? It's self-service?
Yes, you drink by yourself
and leave the money.
Bill is the only person who's
taking care of this lodge.
He can't manage everything.
Would you like something to drink?
Can I have the same drink as her?
Yes, sir.
Gin and tonic.
Thank you.
I don't have any change.
Then I'll treat you guys, too.
Oh, you're a very generous old man!
Old man! You look cool.
You're my type.
Don't call me "old man."
I'm only twenty-eight.
See! You are an old man.
Ms. Higuchi, what
are you studying here?
Call me Rumiko, old man!
My major is mystic studies.
It's very hard to find a place to
study that kind of thing in Japan.
Mystic studies?
Yes, I'm getting a
doctorate degree soon.
After that, I'll start working as an
instructor at Miskatonic University.
Really?
Yes it's true. Rumiko already has a
Master's Degree in mystic studies...
and just finished her
doctoral dissertation.
Well, she must be a good student.
Necronomicon.
What?
It's my dissertation's title.
Necro... nomicon...
Nozomi, let me handle this.
P... please do it to me, Nozomi.
Nozomi?
Cute girl!
Poor girl! It's swollen and very red.
It's mysterious.
Hurry! Hurry!
I'll give this to you, too.
Then we'll become one.
Mina Shizui told me the
key words to save Nozomi.
"The Night of Beltane" and the
"murders that happened six years ago."
Well, which one are you
gonna start with first?
The first thing is...
Oh, this is the worst!
Don't complain! Bill was kind
enough to lend us his car...
that he's been using
since he was a student.
Mr. Suzusaki, why are
we going to the library?
Rumiko Higuchi gave me some hints
on where to investigate last night.
So! Did you try to pick her up?
Idiot! Listen to this.
Rumiko's major is mystic studies.
M... mystic studies?
Yes.
Necronomicon.
What's wrong?
Old man, are you all right?
I... I'm all right.
By the way, since you're
studying mysticism...
Do you know anything
about the Night of Beltane?
Beltane... it's the day
before May Day.
Do you know about it?
Yes, the original meaning of
Beltane is "Fire's Shining Light."
What meaning does that day have?
According to the ancient Roman
calendar, May is the month of three.
Three interprets life,
growth and death.
Since ancient times, the Night
of Beltane is the best time...
to cast magic spells related to
life and death in all means.
It means...
It means Nezu is planning to do
something using Nozomi...
...on the Night of Beltane,
the night of April 30.
May I be of help to you?
I want to look at the back issues
of the Daily Banks.
Yes, you can take a look at the
microfilms with the computer.
Asuka, Ms. Sakimizu, can you
research about Half Acre Mansion?
Also the previous owner, and his
whereabouts, carefully.
Half Acre Mansion?
It might have some
connection to Nezu.
What about you Suzusaki?
I'll research the
incident six years ago.
The murders, Nezu, Nozomi, and I
must be connected in some way.
I understand.
This is it.
Nora.
Bizarre Murder Case
A Caucasian woman, Japanese Professor, and his
wife found murdered at Half Acre Mansion.
The suspect is the murdered woman's boyfriend!?
This must be it.
May 1, before sunrise at the
Half Acre Mansion in River Banks...
Miskatonic University Professor
Kashiwagi and his wife...
and a student, Nora Defarlane...
were found murdered.
A patrol officer found them.
They searched and found two
unconscious men close to the scene...
They're planning to investigate
Satoshi Suzusaki, a private detective...
as a possible witness
when he recovers.
They lost their memory
about the day of the murder.
A medical specialist
will investigate them.
June 30: The River Banks
County Court accepted...
Satoshi Suzusaki's claim of
amnesia and released him.
July 2: Satoshi Suzusaki was sent
to the state mental hospital.
July 15: Marshal Perkins
investigates the cemetery...
where the suspects were found.
Cemetery...?
According to Marshal Perkins, the
suspects were found one kilometer...
from the Half Acre Mansion,
where the murder took place.
Are you all right?
I feel dizzy.
I'm all right.
I'm Cindy.
What?
That's my name...
W... what...?
I was waiting for you.
Who are you?
I still haven't been paid for the
information I gave you back then.
It can't be!
I must have seen Nezu six years ago.
Ms. Sakimizu, what did you find out?
Yes, Half Acre Mansion was called
Herbert Mansion before.
Herbert West built it.
He was a professor of the medical
department in Miskatonic University.
He came here with his assistant
after he quit the university in 1940.
Are there any pictures of him?
I found only one picture.
The person in the
middle is Herbert West.
What's the matter chief?!
We almost got into an accident!
Asuka! Look at this!
That's...
Yes, Nezu.
What?
What's this all about?
This picture is 50 years old.
I don't understand.
It might be just a
coincidental resemblance...
or somebody blood related to him.
It's possible, but under
the circumstances...
this is too good
to be a coincidence.
If this is really Nezu, then
he's already over 90 years old.
What?
I told you that I saw
Nezu six years ago.
Some of my memories came back to me.
What?
Miskatonic University hired me to
investigate Professor Kashiwagi...
and his wife six years ago.
And, I remembered one other thing.
One more thing I
was asked to investigate.
Before Kashiwagi disappeared,
he told me on the telephone...
that he discovered something very
important, which can even disprove...
history and modern science.
Really?
He said he found the
Necronomicon.
Necronomicon?
I want you to find out where Kashiwagi
is and about the Necronomicon.
Necronomicon?
And I heard the same word yesterday.
What?
Rumiko Higuchi...
She said she was
studying the Necronomicon.
I may be able to solve all
the mysteries if I ask her.
Only three more days left
until the Night of Beltane.
Yes, we have very little time.
Suzusaki, it's you again.
Marshal Perkins.
What happened?
Murder.
Rumiko and Kate were killed!
What?!
But how, I can't even
begin to describe.
Don't come in!
Cut them down!
This is the same as it
was six years ago.
People die every time you show
up in this peaceful town.
You're an important witness.
I have some questions to ask you.
It can't be!
They were dead!
Their hearts had completely stopped!!
It's the same!
It's the same as last time!
This is not what a human could do!