NECRONOMICON 730 A.D.
This is the path of an evil book...
written by Abdul Alhazard
in Damascus.
This book is described as being
very complicated and mysterious...
containing the secrets of magic...
But it is also known to carry
the very essence of evil.
The greatest book ever
on the path of evil.
It's considered the king
of all books of magic.
Therefore in 1050 A.D.,
Archbishop Michael of Byzantine had
the book condemned and sealed forever.
So we believe that the book does not
exist, intact, anywhere in the world...
What's going on?
What's happened?
Th... that dream again...
Oh no, brother... I mean chief,
you still didn't change yet?
Since vacations are rare for us,
we have to enjoy it as much as we can.
I don't think we'll ever have
the opportunity again...
to stay in this kind
of a resort condo.
I really appreciate your friend who
gave us a free vacation at this place!
What's wrong, Chief?
You look pale.
It's nothing.
I just had a bad dream.
That dream again? About 6 years ago,
when you got involved with something...
that caused you to lose your memory.
You're almost right.
Almost right?
Hey!
You should go see...
a doctor.
Yes, this is Suzusaki.
Who is it?
It's Ms. Shizui.
I don't like dealing with her.
Hello?
This is he.
What's wrong Satoshi?
Your voice sounds gloomy.
No, it's nothing.
How is it?
Are you enjoying the accommodations
I arranged for you and your daughter?
Mina, she's not my daughter anymore.
I ended the adoption when
she turned 20 years old.
Oh, is that so?
That could be dangerous.
Dangerous?
Yes, because it means you guys
aren't related to each other now.
It means you're just
a man and a woman.
I thought by the way she looks
at you, you were somehow...
What do you want?!
Are you angry? How cute!
I want you to pay me the same
price for the information...
like you did the last time.
I'll be arriving there in the
afternoon, the day after tomorrow.
I see.
Let's have a nice time together.
What were you
talking about?
Work.
She said she'd come over here
the day after tomorrow.
Work?
Aren't we here for a vacation?
Well, that's true...
Stop... stop it!
Let's go!
W... wait, Chief!
Hey! We were still talking!
Chief...
I wanted to ask you this
for a long time.
What's going on between
you and Ms. Shizui?
What's going on?
As I told you before, she's an
excellent information broker.
I can say she's the
best in the business.
No, I don't mean that.
Then what?
Well, about you and Ms. Shizui's...
private life.
Weren't you the one who said we should
enjoy this vacation to the fullest?
I don't want to deal with that
kind of question right now.
You're getting better, Asuka!
Chief, I got used to it.
Don't get carried away!
Be careful!
Yes!
Nagano Prefecture Police
What happened?
What's going on?
The Sato family in
40D committed suicide.
What a mess!
What?
A family suicide?
No, the manager who found them first
said they were viciously killed.
Viciously? How?
I don't know. He was totally pale
and he couldn't tell me the details.
Oh, no.
Asuka, go back to the room.
Chief! Chief!
Oh, well.
He's always very curious.
Oh, excuse me.
Pardon me.
Hey!
Working hard?
Who are you?
This area is closed to the public.
Please excuse me.
You're from the Central Office?
Well, what happened?
A murder.
But... the cause of
death is very strange.
All four family members died
after their eyeballs were gouged out.
Are you all right, Terada?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?!
Oh, he is from the Tokyo...
I'm just a guy from Tokyo.
See you...
What?!
You lied to me!
I didn't say anything.
Mr. Hotokeu...
Something stinks about him.
Eyeballs gouged out...
Damn!
Well, I'm sorry I'm late.
It took a while to dub the tape.
Why did you make me come here?
You have a great body I just love.
That's not funny!
I'm leaving.
Wait!
You won't want to leave
after you see this.
Sit down!
Due to the approach of a
low pressure system...
there's a chance that this bad weather
will continue all day tomorrow.
As a result, since we are at the
summit, our resort will likely be...
cut off from the town at
the base of the mountain.
Those customers who wish to leave...
please come to the front lobby
as soon as possible.
I'm leaving, even if he
didn't tell us to go.
Yeah! I don't want to stay at a place
like this one more second...
after that weird murder happened.
Who would want to?
So, how many people decided to stay?
It seems that six rooms
stayed here including us.
Is that all?
Snow on the mountain comes
together during a snowstorm.
The announcement said it was
due to the snowstorm,
but the fact is that customers were
scared by the weird murder.
The only people left here are people
desperate for a vacation, like us...
or somebody with courage or...
...the murderer.
Huh?
I'm just joking.
If I was the murderer, I would've
already left here much earlier.
That's right.
Well, I'm going to swim in the indoor
heated pool for a little relaxation.
Hey Mr. Manager, this place
suddenly became lonely.
But you're staying, too?
Yeah, I haven't taken a
vacation for a long time.
If I lose this chance, I'll never
know when I could get it again.
If the murder hadn't happened...
I heard you were the first one
to find the murder.
You...
You don't have to be suspicious.
I have a private
detective office in Tokyo.
I just have a professional curiosity.
You're a private detective?
I've never seen such a
horrible thing in my life.
I already told this to the police...
At that time, I was bringing
the dry cleaning that Sato ordered.
But nobody answered, no matter
how many times I rang the doorbell.
So I gave up and was
about to leave, when...
Mr. Sato, I brought your dry cleaning.
Mr. Sato.
What's that smell?
Mr. Sato?!
I think I'll have nightmares
for quite a while.
Come in!
You promise?
If I stay one night...
Yes, if you do what I say,
I'll give you back the master tape.
Well, let's begin.
Here! Come over here and suck this.
What?
Or don't you mind if I put your
foolish behavior on the internet?
Is this the first time for you?
Hey, why don't you lick this?
Well, you're not bad.
Do it more quickly!
More!
Don't spill it.
Drink it all up!
What are you crying for?
The night has just started.
You're?
I'll return this tape to you, too.
This isn't fair!
No! Stop it! No!
What's next?
Why don't you show
me your ass and pussy?
You can't!
Open it wider!
Oh, it's wet and shiny.
It's ready to invite a man!
Here we go!
No!
Stop it!
Good!
No! No! Please stop!
No!
And now our next story...
Around 12:00 noon today,
a fire broke out at the...
M.M. Pharmaceuticals company
in Yonago City, Tottori Prefecture...
Yukimitsu Miura, the Chief of the 3rd
development division...
died in the fire.
The cause of the
fire is still unknown.
Arson has not been ruled out.
Oh, no.
A power failure?
Who can it be, this early?
Brother!
Chief!
This is no time to argue such things!
Detective, I need your help.
What happened?
A murder case.
What?
Don't look!
I have been giving him morning
wake-up calls every day at 7:30 AM.
But he didn't pick up
the phone this morning...
no matter how many times I called.
So I came here to wake him up.
Then, he was already dead...
This is the same as my dream.
What did you say?
Nothing, did you call the police?
The phone's been dead since
the power failure last night.
The snowstorm may have knocked
the cellular phone transmitter down.
Why don't you have this?
Thank you.
I feel better now.
What should I do about the body?
To maintain the crime scene, let's
leave it as is for one more day.
If we can't contact the police by
tomorrow, we'll put him on the bed.
Is this related
to yesterday's murder?
By the looks of the
way he was killed...
Was the power failure caused by the
short circuit in the bath tub?
I think so.
What should we do now?
There's only one thing to do!
Nobody could've come in and out of
this resort from last night...
until the morning,
because of the snowstorm.
Therefore, the murderer is someone
still staying at the resort.
Uh?
What's wrong, Asuka?
Oh, nothing.
Let's check all the people's
alibis in this resort right now.
What?
What do you want?
I'm not a stranger.
I was asked by the manager
of this resort...
to formally investigate
yesterday's murder case.
I don't know anything.
I told everything to
the police yesterday.
Are you trying to bother me?
There was another murder.
What?
11:30 PM was the time
the power failed.
Yes, excuse me but...
I don't have an alibi.
I stayed in this room alone.
Alone at the resort
when murder took place?
I have no place else to go.
I'm about to go bankrupt.
I just got fired because of
company restructuring!
My wife and children left me!
The only real estate I have now,
is this condo at the resort.
I wanted to sell it earlier...
but it's very difficult
because of the recession!
Then the weird
murders happened!
This will make the
value go down again!
Shit!
Stupid fool!
What can I do about it?!
Damn it!
Coming.
What can I do for you?
Is something wrong?
Did we meet each other
somewhere before?
Well, I don't remember...
Is there something
I can do for you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Well...
So, you're a private detective?
It sounds like an interesting job.
It's not interesting at all.
80% of my work is checking a
person's private life for a divorce.
It's a very plain and gloomy job.
How about you, Mr. Nezu?
I own an import-export company.
It's just a small company
with 10 employees.
Oh?
Please have some.
Thank you very much.
By the way, what were you doing
between 11:00 and 12:00 last night?
Oh, my alibi?
Yes...
It's around the time
of the power failure.
I was watching TV.
When the power failed, I was
watching the news on TV...
about a fire at the M.M. Pharmaceuticals
manufacturing company.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I see you collect
antique books.
Oh, you noticed?
I collected these books when I went
abroad on my business trips.
They must be very valuable.
They are.
For example...
This is a medical book
from ancient Egypt.
Ancient Egypt?
This book describes the
way to obtain eternal life.
Which means?
It's a technique
to create a mummy.
A mummy?
I see, so there is no such
thing as eternal life.
It's rather ominous...
Modern medical science
is much more ominous.
Medical science and chemistry were
both developed from medieval alchemy...
only in the past
few hundred years.
Modern medical science is a worthless
study with a shallow history.
Even using humans as guinea pigs.
It's no equal to the ancient
knowledge of magic...
which has existed for
thousands of years.
Have you ever heard
of the Necronomicon?
No.
It's a banned book written by
Abdul Alhazard in 730 AD.
The book describes the method to
gain eternal life, like you just said.
Eternal life?
To be more precise, it's a way to
bring the dead back to life.
It's quite different from
making a mummy.
Is something wrong?
No, I just felt dizzy.
Are you all right?
Yes, I guess I stayed here too long.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Take care.
Can I help you?
The manager said to me that two
people are staying in this room.
Yes, Nozomi is still sleeping.
Is she your sister?
No, I'm her private tutor.
Nozomi's parents and I
are very close.
Her parents went abroad
to do some research...
so I'm taking care of Nozomi
while they are away.
I see.
What were you doing around
11:30 PM last night?
Well, I was here with her.
Oh, Nozomi, I'm sorry.
Did I wake you up?
What's the matter, Nozomi?
What's wrong?
Nozomi?
Nozomi!
It must be motion aphasia.
Aphasia?
I can't explain it clearly
because I'm not a doctor...
but I've seen the
same symptoms before.
But why?
This symptom comes out
from a strong mental shock.
Mental shock?
Yes.
Did she see something unusual...
or experience anything
abnormal yesterday?
No...
Not at all.
Then I suggest you see a doctor
as soon as the snowstorm stops.
Yes.
Nozomi... don't worry.
This kind of symptom naturally
cures itself sometimes.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Take care!
I smell something between
them and Hiruta, but what?
Mina?
I finished my work
a day earlier.
My room number is 50H.
Can you carry my luggage?
How did you get here
in this snowstorm?
I got a ride on the police snowcat
at the base of the mountain.
Police?
I heard that a murder
happened here.
They first refused.
They said I shouldn't come up,
because it's dangerous.
But since they were supposed
to inspect the crime scene again...
I see.
Mina...
I have a favor to ask you.
Anything...
But it might cost you a lot.
The phones don't work
because of the snowstorm.
But I want to get photographs of the
crime scene from the police computer.
Can you do that?
I understand the situation, but
why do you say "can you do that?".
I guess you can't.
Don't be stupid!
That's not what I meant.
I'm a professional
information collector.
So I'm telling you not
to patronize me.
What is it?
Iridium.
This is a special model,
but I think you've heard of it before.
The cellular phone you can transmit
from anywhere on the Earth.
Which do you think
performs better, yours or this?
It's ready!
The address of the
National Police Agency is...
Here, I'm in.
This is...
Stop.
Can you zoom in?
Of course.
I thought so.
What?
What's wrong?
I can conclude that the murderer
of both the Sato family and Hiruta...
is the same person.
The conditions of the dead bodies
are completely the same.
No matter what the reason...
Normal people don't gouge
out human eyeballs.
And the clue to
the criminal is...
This!
This ice pick broke off
when he gouged the eyeball...
because the nasal bone blocked it.
This is stabbed from the left.
Which means?
The criminal must be left-handed.
Did I help you?
Yes, it's still only a guess
but I found a likely suspect.
Mina...
Can you call the manager's
room five minutes from now...
and have the police come to 60D.
All right.
You should pay my price
for this information, tonight.
Yeah.
I want to ask him something
before the police take him.
I think I've met him
somewhere before.
Mr. Nezu, are you here?
Mr. Nezu!
It can't be!
The most likely person is now dead.
Who will be the next suspect?
What now, Suzusaki?!
Teasing the police department!
What are you doing?!
What did you do?!
You're under arrest for murder!
I didn't do it.
I...
I didn't do it!!