It was during the war... yes...
it was in the summer of 1943.
Jack was ten years older than me...
but he was my best friend.
When he came back home,
he completely lost the will to live.
Yes, he came home to die.
One night Jack left home by himself,
and went into the forest.
Come out! Jack!
You can't get away!
Damn it!
Die!
He won't die!
You may not believe it,
but Jack was already...
not human.
Please wait a moment.
Karl, can I talk to you?
What is it?
Well, I'm a private detective.
This is just out of professional
curiosity, call it a force of habit.
Yes?
Can you tell me your alibi?
Alibi?
There was a murder here.
I'm just a historian.
I was writing some report about
a historical site around here...
up until late last night.
And I was sleeping
in the morning.
I see.
I went to the historical site
for research in the afternoon.
So, I don't have any clear alibi.
But Marshall, your assistant told me
that those two women were still alive.
And you shot and killed
them in self-defense.
That means it's not a murder.
So, I wouldn't think checking
out my alibi is so important.
Well then, excuse me.
I was very scared when I
heard about the murders.
Can you take me to my room,
Mr. Suzusaki?
Sure, I can do that.
Oh, you look so happy.
Go ahead Chief. After all, this is
the country of "ladies first."
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Stupid jerk!
I envy you, Asuka.
What?
You guys don't act like brother and
sister, but boyfriend and girlfriend.
Huh?
No, it's just like a couple who has
been married for a long time.
There's some warm feelings.
Oh, it's open.
W... what is it Clark?!
Why are you in my room?!
I'll leave you two alone.
I'm going back to my room.
Why do you have to seduce
men, one after the other?!
Why do you hit me all the time?!
I can do anything I want to!
I'm sick of you! Get out!
Why are you attracted
to such a nerdy guy?
Hey! Don't be crazy!
Amy, show me your ass.
No!
Clark, stop it!
Not there!
Shut up!
Amy! Do you feel good?
Yes! Yes!
Clark!
You!
You're the one who...!
But how old are you!?
You talked too much!
I'm thirsty.
I want some alcohol.
Why don't we get some from
the old man next door.
I'll go with you.
Satoshi, come up to the second floor!
There's been another murder.
No!
It's not working!
I can't call the police station.
The phone line is dead.
What does that mean?
Because of the storm, the phone lines
may be cut off somewhere.
What can we do, Mr. Suzusaki?
Well, let's leave the
crime scene as it is.
I'm more worried about
the other guests.
Let's split up and look around.
All right.
This is...!
Miskatonic University
Professor Herbert West.
Established a private research facility
in the River Banks city limits.
Half Acre Mansion
for sale
Ms. Amy?
Karl, are you there?
This is...
Mr. Suzusaki, Clark
wasn't in his room.
Neither was Ms. Amy.
Karl must be Nezu.
This is Nozomi's!
Are you feeling sick?
You have to be patient,
just a little more.
Everything will be over soon.
You will become part of me.
My loving child!
Nozomi, I understand.
You don't recognize
that I'm your father.
I know I don't look like your father,
but that's only on the outside.
Yes, the soul is completely the same.
Your father's soul is in my body.
I even have the memories of
when you were born.
This is the most definitive magic
book in the world, the Necronomicon.
It's also called "Kuro No Dansho",
a book of the devil.
Do you understand?
This book has the power of the devil.
This book can protect itself
with it's own power.
It erases the memory of people
who are against it.
The memories of Suzusaki and Bill have been
sealed by the power of this book.
But that ended yesterday.
And tomorrow it will be Beltane.
The power of this book will be
gone temporarily.
Suzusaki will come here to save you.
And they will all die here!
Oh no, you had an accident?
But you're my child,
so don't worry.
I'll clean you up now.
Bill!
What happened?
I... I just remembered what
happened six years ago.
It's here! We went to that
cursed place from here!
Satoshi, are you all right?
Yes! H... here!
I found it! Satoshi... Nora!
Is it here?
There's a stairway.
It was here!
I remembered that we went
to the place from here!
But why couldn't I remember
this, until today?
Well, here are the entry records from
March through April. Karl Ihiman...
This is strange...
This must be some kind of set up.
He must of cut the phone line, too.
But why?
Tomorrow is Beltane.
Whatever ceremony he performs with
Nozomi will have to be tomorrow night.
But it's dangerous.
I know.
Please save Nozomi!
Don't worry about it.
I'll save her.
Even at the cost of my life.
I won't let anybody die
around me anymore.
Brother.
You should stay here.
Only Bill and I will go downstairs
tomorrow morning.
No!
I'll go with you, no matter what!
Please take me, too!
I want to save Nozomi!
Akiko, Nozomi's mother,
asked me to take care of her.
I'm Nozomi's guardian.
I can't just wait here
and do nothing.
Are you still awake?
Yes.
I must go with you downstairs.
You can't!
Why?
I don't want to see
people die anymore.
I couldn't help Nora
six years ago, and your...
You might be the one
who killed my parents.
How do you know that?
I read the newspaper article at the
library the day before yesterday.
But I love you brother... no
I love you Satoshi Suzusaki.
Asuka.
Thank you.
But I might be the one
who killed your parents.
Don't you mind?
No.
I know Satoshi Suzusaki is not a
person who could do such a thing.
Even if you killed my parents...
it doesn't change my feelings.
Asuka.
Women can be
dangerous sometimes.
Make love to me!
I was all by myself in a strange town
after my mother and father died.
It was five years ago...
But there was a person
who came and took me.
He was a man who wasn't so good at
expressing his feelings to other people...
He was kind of a loser.
He wasn't perfect, but he
was a very nice person.
I don't care about the reason
why you took care of me.
I love you, Satoshi Suzusaki.
Asuka.
Huh?
This is the lucky charm that
you gave me on my birthday.
I wear this all the time.
Aquamarine is supposed to have
the power to protect you from evil.
But that stone is not very expensive.
It's important because
you gave it to me.
I don't understand.
There is no such thing as a human
who never ages in this world.
Marshall!
What is it?
L... Look at this!
Marshall, there are no records
of a Karl Ihiman...
but the picture that you gave to me...
...but I found an entry
record of this person.
It was one month ago.
Of course he used a fake name.
Marshall?
Satoshi.
Yes.
I'm sure about this.
It's here.
You're...
Clark!
Why are you here?
It's no good.
He's already become a zombie.
The same as Rumiko and Kate.
And Jack, who Louis mentioned.
What?
And all the mysteries about the
murders are behind this gate.
And probably Nozomi, too.
Nozomi!
Ms. Sakimizu!
It doesn't work on him.
Bill! Shoot him in the head!
Satoshi, get inside there now!
Hurry!
You two stay back!!
Damn you!
Satoshi! Let's get inside now!
All right! Let's go!
Bill!
There's no time left!
I'll take care of this.
Bill!
Please save Nozomi.
Welcome to my party.
Nozomi!
If you come any closer than you are!
Nezu!
You arrived here much earlier
than I expected Mr. Suzusaki.
What are you trying to do to Nozomi?
Nezu!
I'm just having a party.
Today is Beltane.
The best day to have a ceremony.
What?
Before you worry about this girl,
why don't you worry about yourself...
or the friend you left outside the door?
Or are you going to just let them die?
Just like you did to your
girlfriend six years ago?
Run away, Satoshi!
I wasn't the one who killed Nora!
Yes, I killed her.
I let you know this now...
because your memory will come
back to you soon anyway.
What are you talking about?
I will reenact the scene
from that time in front of you.
However, the people who
were lying on this table...
were Professor
Kashiwagi and his wife.
You're evil, not human!
Not human?
Dear lady, you will not
be human very soon.
Just like the two
people you saw outside.
And I'll combine Nozomi's
soul with mine...
and have a perfect body and soul
to complete the Family Circle.
What are you trying to do?!
Do you know this book?
The book describes the magic
to get eternal life.
The Necronomicon.
I see.
You've researched up
to that point, Mr. Suzusaki.
You killed all the people who knew
about it or were involved with it.
Then I assume you already
know my real name too.
Herbert West!
Marshall Perkins!!
You were a former professor
of the medical department...
at Miskatonic University.
Herbert West!
The university didn't approve your
research on reviving the dead.
You quit the University with your
assistant, Toshiaki Nezu...
...and opened the laboratory here.
And you killed Nezu,
and stole his body.
You are evil!
Marshall!
I don't think I invited
you to this party.
You're under arrest for mass murder!
Do you think you can hurt me
with such a crude device?
What?!
Who is this?
Akiko!
Nezu!
What did you do
to Nozomi's mother?!
Can't you see?
I gave her immortality.
Of course if I don't perform the
ceremony on the day of Beltane...
her soul will die.
Damn you!
Mr. Suzusaki!
Stop it, Akiko!
Stop it!
Akiko, don't let them bother
me until I finish the ceremony!
Help me!
Mother!
Nozomi!
Damn it!
You bastard!
Fool!
Let me scoop out your heart.
No don't!
Stop doing this!
Brother! Run!
Y... you bastard!
Run Satoshi!
Let me go!
I have to save Nora!
We should go Satoshi.
Don't waste Nora's feelings.
Boy, are you afraid of death?
Run Satoshi!
Nora!
Fire!
He was very afraid of real fire.
Su... Suzusaki!
Akiko!
Let me go!
Mother!
Nozomi.
Asuka, run!
Let me go! Akiko!
The Necronomicon...
Kill me!
Mother.
Nozomi.
Perkins, nobody will believe
what happened here today.
I know.
Everything is over now.
Yes.