Stop!
Ms. Shizui, please help!
Ms. Shizui!
My brother is...
How many times must I tell you?
I didn't do it!
Nobody's saying you're the murderer.
I want you to tell me honestly
why were you there?
I've already told you many times.
I went to Nezu's room because I
thought he was the prime suspect...
but...
He was already dead.
That's what you're claiming?
Yes.
This is a bit difficult.
If Nezu is the killer...
...then who killed him?
He can't kill himself and cut off
his own skin afterwards.
Then the suspects in
this resort-condo...
are you, Shibusawa the manager,
and Ando in 60B.
But the other two have an alibi.
Alibi?
At 1:30 PM, didn't you go to
Ando's room and ask for his alibi?
Ando called the manager after
you left his room...
and complained about the security
system of this condo for 2 hours.
We can't find out any more details
until we do a court-ordered autopsy.
But the estimated time of his death
was about 4 to 5 hours ago.
Which means, around 3 to 4 PM.
That's exactly the same time
you were talking with Nezu.
So who do you think is the
most likely suspect?
Care to guess, Mr. Detective?
Mr. Hotokeu.
The phone is re-connected.
It seems like somebody jammed the
phones and cut the outside line.
I found this in the lobby.
I guess, of course, it's not yours?
Of course!
Who knows?
You once were a suspect
in a murder case, weren't you?
I got this fax from
the central office!
Six years ago, April 30th,
in River Banks, Maine, USA...
A married Japanese couple and a
Caucasian woman were killed...
and the skin from
their faces was cut off!
You must have done that too!
Was the Caucasian
woman your girlfriend?
Wasn't she?
You're sweating a lot.
After the incident, you were sent to
the Maine State Mental Institution.
A mental institution?
He lost his memory.
Suzusaki had amnesia and lost all his
memory around the time of the murder.
He didn't have to face
charges because of that.
And he came back
to Japan with a girl.
A girl?
Yes.
Suzusaki brought back the daughter...
of the Japanese couple
who were murdered.
He adopted her.
You must've had guilty feelings?
No!
It's not because I felt guilty.
Then why did you adopt somebody
who was involved in the murder?!
It's...
I know you can't answer!
Was it true that you
lost your memory?!
Can't you even remember one thing?!
Stop!
What's wrong Suzusaki?
Brother!
Satoshi.
I'm glad, brother...
Oops...
I mean Chief...
That you got released.
I haven't been found
innocent and acquitted.
There is nothing you
can do about it.
But you have an alibi that
you were with me around...
the victim's estimated
time of death.
But it's just the estimated time.
Chief could never do such a thing.
But the police are convinced he's
the most likely suspect.
I am.
When I think calmly, I understand why
I'm their suspect in this situation.
Don't you have any clue?
Chief...
About the person
named Naomi Seo in 40A...
She might be my classmate
from high school.
What does that mean?
We checked out the people in the
condo, this morning...
using the computer at the
manager's room on the first floor.
Yes.
I was wondering
about it since then...
so I checked it over again...
and I found out the fact that
victims Sato and Hiruta...
and Naomi are all employees of
M.M. Pharmaceuticals.
M.M. Pharmaceuticals?
Naomi told me that she would start
working at M.M. after we graduated.
I'm sure of it.
Yes, can I help you?
Naomi!
Asuka!
Naomi it's you!
Long time no see!
Yes, what have you been doing?
Oh, Naomi, do you remember him?
He's my brother...
This is Satoshi Suzusaki.
Oh, I remember this!
The school festival!
And this is when
we went to the beach!
I remember that's when I met you.
It was lots of fun, wasn't it Naomi?
Yes.
What's wrong Naomi?
Is anything bothering you?
Yes... I'm afraid.
I don't blame you.
Two people from your company
were killed here.
Yes, I'm sorry.
No, not at all.
Did you know Sato and Hiruta?
I've never seen them before because
we work in different departments.
I see.
By the way, why are you
staying at this condo?
This is one of the company
facilities for our benefits program.
The company suddenly told me
to use my vacation days...
before the end of March.
Do you know about the fire at
the third laboratory yesterday?
What?
Somebody named Miura
died in the fire.
I heard it on the 11 o'clock news.
I didn't know that it happened.
I'm sorry I don't remember anything.
What?
What does that mean?
I felt very strange recently.
I often fall asleep all of sudden.
Just like a thread
broke, or I fainted.
I was planning to leave here
yesterday. I was packing, and...
I lost consciousness
in the middle of that.
Then I woke up in the morning.
Do you think something's
wrong with me?
I think you're just tired.
You must have lots of stress.
Yes.
Well, I'm very sorry to
bother you so late at night.
Oh, yeah...
if you remember something...
please call me here.
Yes.
Naomi!
Do you have a little more time?
Yes.
Chief!
I'll stay here and talk
to Naomi a little more.
Because, I haven't
seen her for a long time.
Don't take too long.
Yes.
What's wrong, Satoshi?
You don't have to worry just because
your intuition was wrong.
Let the police take care of it.
I'm sure Nezu killed Hiruta.
Huh?
The bandage on Nezu's left hand...
That must be a burn he
got when he killed Hiruta.
But Nezu is already dead, because...
Satoshi...
you must...
What?
I'm just joking.
So can we do it again?
The price for my information
is very high.
I'm sorry to bother you
so early in the morning.
No, by the way, is there anything...
that you remember?
I thought about it
again after I saw you...
And I decided to tell
you everything.
What is that?
I told you that I stayed in my
room around 11:30 last night.
However, I was...
actually in Hiruta's room.
Huh?
I didn't kill him!
Please believe me!
Can you explain any more
details about this?
If you don't mind?
The day before yesterday...
The day the Sato's were murdered...
Hiruta told me to
come down to the lobby.
The thing Hiruta brought was...
Are you sure?
Just one night...
Sure, if you listen to me,
I'll give you back the master tape.
No!
When I became conscious...
Hiruta was already
dead in the bathtub.
Didn't you see anything else
except Hiruta's body there?
Nozomi was there.
Nozomi! Nozomi!
I understand.
He blackmailed
you with this tape.
Yes.
Why didn't you call the police?
I don't think Hiruta would've
given you the tape...
even if you slept with him one night.
The picture I have in my hand is...
Nozomi.
I'm a lesbian.
I can only love a woman.
I have been Nozomi's tutor
for a long time, and...
I started to love her...
I started to love Nozomi, only her.
I don't care what happens to me!
But if people know about this...
even if Nozomi is innocent, people
may start to look coldly upon her!
I'm...! I'm...!
I see.
That's why you didn't call the police.
Nozomi became stricken with aphasia
when she went to Hiruta's room.
Uh, yes. I guess so.
What was Nozomi doing there?
Ms. Sakimizu!
Police!
Suzusaki!
Oh, you were here.
You! Stay in your own
room and don't move!
Don't disturb the investigation!
Calm down, Terada.
Yes.
Ms. Sakimizu, we found this in
Hiruta's room, the man who was killed.
Have you seen this before?
I must ask you to accompany me,
voluntarily, to the police station.
I want to ask you
about several things.
Nozomi.
Mr. Suzusaki, please
take care of Nozomi.
Please take care of her
until I come back.
Nozomi, please...
wait for me at Mr. Suzusaki's
room until I came back.
Nozomi, please promise me.
Please.
Oh, this is slippery.
Oh, be careful.
Here we go.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Here we go.
Here.
Suzusaki!
Oh, manager.
Who is that girl?
I feel sorry to leave her alone,
so I'll take her to my place.
I see.
This condo will finally have some
peace since the murderer got arrested.
Mr. Manager, Sakimizu
is not a murderer.
She went to the
police station voluntarily.
She'll be back soon.
Oh, is that so?
But if Ms. Sakimizu
is not the murderer...
I wonder where the
real murderer went?
Oh, I almost forgot to tell you...
I'm sorry to tell you
during this situation...
but I'll be going back to my
house at the mountain's base...
when the replacement manager
comes tomorrow.
Mr. Ando will be leaving
with me, too.
This might be the
last time I see you.
I see.
I hope we could see
each other, somewhere else...
next time under better circumstances.
I hope so too.
Well, excuse me.
Nozomi...
This is Asuka.
She is my assistant.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to ask her.
Nice to meet you, Nozomi.
Asuka, I will sleep
on the sofa for tonight.
I will have Nozomi use my room,
so please change the sheets for her.
Sure.
Nozomi, can you help me
change the sheets?
Yes.
I'm sorry to have you
come here suddenly.
No problem.
You told me there is something
you want to talk to me about.
Yes.
I'm scared.
People were killed
within the last 2 days.
The people who work in
the same company with me.
I understand.
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
I'm very, very scared.
Please make love to me.
I was in love with you...
since the school festival.
Ms. Seo...
I won't be able to see you anymore.
What...!
What's wrong with you, Ms. Seo?!
Ms. Seo...
What did you make me drink?
Ms. Seo.
She's dead.
Satoshi Suzusaki, you are
in the ultimate pinch!
Who are you?
Can you escape from this situation?
However, I think you can't do it
the same way as six years ago.
You won't lose your memory this time.
What happened to me six years ago?
Nezu?
It's Nezu!
Nezu became Shibusawa.
It can't be.
Asuka! Nozomi!
Asuka!
Why?
Mukuroiwa!?
This must be a trap.
But I must go.
Please be OK...
Asuka! Nozomi!
I'm here!
Come out now, Nezu!
Let the girls go!
Let them go!
Brother...
Asuka, Mina!
Don't move, Satoshi!
Nezu is not here anymore.
He's already left
somewhere with Nozomi.
Mina, were you Nezu's partner?
I sent a fax...
telling them that Nezu and I
are the murderers.
The murderers?
Although...
the person who actually
killed them is Nezu.
I just arranged for you, Hiruta and
everybody to gather at the condo.
Then I blew up the laboratory of
M.M. Pharmaceuticals company.
Shizui! Stop it!
Why did you take
that girl as a hostage?
Aren't you planning
to turn yourself in?
Don't misunderstand me.
I protected Asuka from Nezu.
What do you mean?
Nezu told me...
Nezu told me that you had disturbed
a very important ceremony...
in America six years ago.
He held a strong grudge
against Satoshi.
So he said he would kill everyone
related to Satoshi... including Asuka.
But he only needs
Nozomi at this point.
Why Nozomi?
He told me that he needs
Nozomi for a family circle.
I think you saw it too.
Nezu uses strange magic.
He cuts the skin off a human's face,
and impersonates that person.
He controls people's minds
with hypnotism.
Nezu is...
He is a devil.
Why are you working
with such a person?
This was the first time
I teamed up with him...
because we have
the same interest.
21 years ago...
I worked in the development division
of the M.M. Pharmaceuticals company...
along with Hiruta and others.
We were researching to
stop growth hormones.
The research related to
human eternal life.
Humans start the aging process
in exchange for their growth.
So, we were perfecting growth
restraints on hormones...
to give humans eternal life.
But the chief of the division was
afraid to continue the research.
N... No... Stop!
Are you still insisting to get
away from this research?
Hiruta!
This research violates
the realm of God!
Human shouldn't invade this area.
Damn you!
Are you trying to stop us
from making money?
Ando! Sato!
All right.
Traitor!
This may be the best chance to use
a human body to test the drug.
No!
Don't worry, you and
him will be together.
Miura! Make her shut up!
A... all right!
Stop!
Please leave her alone!
Shut up!
Why don't you worry about yourself?
How is it?
If everything goes well,
you will get eternal life.
He's dead.
What are we gonna do now?
Calm down.
Nobody knows unless
we talk about this.
We just have to take
care of the witness.
But before that...
No!!
S... stop it!
Stop!
No!
They raped me, one after the other,
and then injected the drug in me.
But I didn't die.
I couldn't.
The unfinished drug, which didn't
work on anybody, worked for us.
Us?
I'm pregnant.
The baby hasn't grown for 21 years
and remains as a 2 month old fetus.
It can't be.
Since then, I lived as an
underground information broker.
And I met you, Satoshi.
I have been waiting for
the day of my revenge.
Then I met Nezu through my
underground connections.
Did you have a relationship
with me for revenge?!
Brother!
Asuka.
Please save Nozomi.
Nezu told me that he would perform
the ceremony on the night of Beltane.
I really...
loved you.
No, don't, Mina!
Please forgive me... Satoshi.
Stop it!
Mina!
Good bye, Satoshi.
Mina!!!
Brother.
Nezu! Where are you?
I'll make sure to find you!
Wait for me!
Toshiaki Nezu!