I had a dream about Kozue.
I met her at Shonan Beach.
We're in the same prep school.
We just started dating but...
Definitely...
I'm gonna get some!
Aiwa-kun!
HEY!!
Ka-chan, who's this girl?
Who's she? Who are YOU?!
You have ME! I'll never forgive you
for cheating on me with this girl!
WHAT?! Aiwa! What's going on?
No...nothing. It's not true!
You dick! Goodbye!
Whoa! Wait! Kozue! Gulp Huh?
What... What are you... doing?
Don't stop.
DUTCH WIFE 28
Shiiiitt! What a mess!
Today's my first date with Kozue.
Good morning!
What am I thinking?! I'm not
supposed to look at other girls!
I'm going out with Kozue!
Well...a cool guy
like me can't help it.
I'm smart, good-looking,
cool, athletic, good at karaoke
and tough in a fight! I'm too
perfect for even the slightest flaw.
And what's more... I'm dating
Kozue! HA HA HA HA
Are you O.K., mister?
Look at all the porno magazines!!
WOW!
YIKES! No! Stop it! Don't look!
Kids these days are so damn careless.
Come on, Miki! This guy's a pervert.
Shut up, you brats!
YAAH! Pervert!
Kids these days shouldn't
hold hands like that!
Preparatory School
Summer Session
What's so fun about having
to go to summer session?
How can I study when my body
is in its sexual prime?!
All the other geeks have
no other choice though!
They're not going out on a
date like me! HEH HEH HEH
And just what will
Kozue be wearing?
Sorry I'm late!
Kozue!
Having dirty thoughts,
weren't you, Aiwa?
First off, start the date as usual.
Eat ice cream in the park.
And what am I going to do next?
I'm gonna get some
on the first date...
That was good!
I have to get going.
Thanks for the ice cream.
What?! Already?
Yeah. See you next time.
So soon?
Sorry but I really have to go.
Well... What about tomorrow?
Wanna go swimming?
Tomorrow? Well... OK. That's fine.
Alright!
I'll walk you to the station.
Thanks!
(Singing ) Pool! Pool!
Good times tomorrow!
Good times at the pool!
At the pool with Kozue!
Excuse me. Katsu Aiwa?
Umm... that's me.
Great! Can you sign for this?
For me?
OH! That order!
That was two months ago!
I have no sexual
experience so I got this.
I'm curious and can't stand waiting
any longer to get my dick wet.
I ordered a Dutch wife named
South Pole No. 5 from a catalog.
I completely forgot about
It 'til it came today.
It said ''Please enjoy her
in the costumes of your choice.''
South Pole No. 28?
That's strange. I ordered No. 5.
They screwed up the order.
Am I gonna have to send it back?
This is...
the exact same girl I
dreamt about this morning!
I have a girlfriend though.
She's of no use to me now but...
I guess I can train on her
until I finally nail Kozue.
Wow, not bad at all. They
did a really good job.
She even speaks?!
Where am I? Who are you?
She spoke?!?!
What the hell is all this?
She's a robot?!
What are you looking at?
I don't believe it!
Has technology advanced this far?!
Wait a sec! If she's a
Dutch wife robot, that means...
she's going to need
programming first.
You really don't know anything?
Alright. I'm gonna teach a few things.
This is my house.
I'm Katsu, your master.
Master?
You can call me ''Ka-chan''.
You'll do whatever I tell you.
And who am I?
You are Number Twenty....
No! Hmmm. Satomi. You're Satomi!
Satomi? I'm Satomi.
That's right. Satomi, you love me.
You'll never stop loving me.
Ka-chan, I love you!
HEH HEH. This ain't so bad!
So this is a robot!
Not much different than a human.
No, her cuteness... her beauty...
they surpass human levels.
She's a super beauty female robot!
Hey, Ka-chan! Am I cute?
Yeah. Yeah. Cute! Cute!
Satomi's happy! Super happy!
Super happy!
Ka-chan!
Sa... Satomi, you have to do
whatever I say? Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Ka-chan!
Lovers do it like this. Five times a day!
As much as I want.
As much as you want.
We do anything!
Harder. Suck harder!
It feels good!
It does, right? I studied techniques
from magazines and videos.
There! There!
Alright! Let's have you
use your mouth and lick this.
Is it good?
Yes. It tastes very good.
It does! It tastes really good!
Your doing well.
Next, put it in your mouth.
Dreams just can't
compare to the real thing.
Now you have to
really bob and suck it!
She's just like a
human down here too.
Are we finished?
No, it just gets better from here.
Ka-chan! Ka-chan...
Ohh! This feels so good!
No! This sucks!
Here it comes!
Oh, Ka-chan, more!
It feels good...
Ka-chan! Ka-chan! Get up!
Get up, Ka-chan!
I'm alright!
You scared me. You weren't
moving so I thought you were dead.
Phew! It doesn't last
as long as they say it does.
I gotta prepare for
when I'm with Kozue.
I have to work on my stamina.
WHOA! It's big again!
What're you're doing?
Well, didn't you tell me earlier...
So... four more times!
More!
Three more times!
Two more times!
Ka-chan, don't pretend to sleep!
Let me sleep.
One more time!
Ka-chan, let's do it five more times!
Delicious!
She eats food too?
Ah, Ka-chan, you don't want that?
I'll take it!
Robots sleep?!!
Ka-chan, let's do it!
But we just did it after
we got back from dinner.
FOUR MORE TIMES!!!
We did it over and
over until morning.
Ka-chan!
I wanna do it once more!
What?
Come on, Ka-chan, Let's do it!
Hurry! come on, Ka-chan!
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
What if somebody sees you?
Excuse us.
I told you to stay in the room.
Satomi was sad.
I wanted to feel good
again with you!
I have a date... I mean...
I'm going out. We can't.
Just listen to me and
do what I say. OK?
Ka-chan, do you hate me?
What?
I don't want you to hate me so
I wanna become even more pretty.
What can I do to become
more beautiful?
Well, let me see...
You should have some pee on you.
Then you'll be beautiful.
Stay at home.
Pee, right...
Kozue hasn't shown up yet.
Maybe she wasn't feeling
well and skipped class.
First we go swimming.
Then next is the amusement park.
There are steps to get her
into bed with me quickly.
Aiwa!
I'm so sorry!
Kozue!
I was worried about you.
I thought you were sick.
No, nothing like that but...
I can't make it today.
WHAT?!
I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you soon.
Well, if you really can't
go there's nothing I can do.
As long as you make it up
to me another time. HA HA HA
Kozue!
What's taking so long?
Just a minute, Masaki.
I'm coming.
Ma... Masaki?
See you later.
What are you doing, stupid?
Who's he?
It's nothing.
He's just a friend.
Huh?
She has a boyfriend?
Shit!
Now I'm pissed off!
I'm gonna fuck South Pole No. 28
Satomi till she breaks!
She's in love with me.
And she's just a toy...
So I can do whatever
I want to her. HEH HEH HEH
Satomi, I'm home.
Satomi?
Are you hiding?
Satomi, where are you?
It can't be.
The company came and took her
back because the order was wrong?
I've been dumped by that
no brain robot No. 28?
HA HA
I'm such a loser.
Hey, this is what you
wanted, right?
Her skin is so shiny.
Well, enough of this.
I'll take care of this horny, little bitch.
I'll be the first one...
to fuck her brains out.
What are you doing?
You know what I'm doing.
It'll feel good.
Stop it! Ka-chan's the only
one who can do that to me!
What's that? She's Katsu girlfriend?
So we don't have to worry. Let's do it.
Stop it! Get off me!
Stop!
Be quiet!
That stupid No. 28...
She might have just gone for a walk.
Kozue?
Let's go to the pool together.
What about your boyfriend?
It's OK.
Don't worry about him.
I didn't think
Masaki was that stubborn.
I want to go have fun.
Let's go swimming!
Let's go have some fun!
Wait a sec while I grab my things.
Have fun? Awesome!
I'll make sure you have A LOT of fun!
The tide is turning for me.
I'm gonna score with Kozue! YAHOO!
Is something in there?
HI!
Going out again, Ka-chan?
Oh, shit! If Kozue finds out about
Satomi, she'll think I'm a pervert.
Kozue, let's hurry up.
Sounds like she knows you, Aiwa.
No, she must have been mistaken.
Recently there are lots
of perverts around here.
Again?!
What?
Am I prettier now?
Kozue, I think this girl's lost.
Let me show her the way.
Wait just a minute.
Listen here, you. This is the
wrong way to Yabu Hospital
Just what do you
think you're doing?
What are you doing, Ka-chan?
I'm not asking directions.
Who's that girl, Kozue?
It's none of your business!
Ka-chan!
Go home!
Kozue, thanks for wait...
Don't sulk, you baby.
What?! I was just
talking to a friend.
It's nothing to get angry over.
You idiot! Don't you get it?
I'm in love with you.
Masaki...
Any more nonsense though
and we're finished.
Masaki...
Did you have something to do?
No, nothing.
Ka-chan? Ka-chan?
Ka-chan, are you alright?
Satomi...
Ka-chan, you were out
for while. Are you OK?
Were you... were you
here the whole time?
Feel better, Ka-chan.
You have me!
Satomi...
Why do you smell like piss?
I had these guys pee on me.
You... you took what
I said... seriously?!
Yeah. There was so much.
What have I done?!
Then they held me down
and tried to have fun with me.
What?! Did they do
something to you?
You're all scraped up.
But I didn't do it with them.
I knew you'd get mad.
Satomi...
I got away from them.
Satomi!
Ka-chan!
You... I didn't think
about your feelings at all.
I'm... I'm... such a dick!
No, you're not, Ka-chan.
You're wonderful!
Satomi!
Ka-chan! Let's do it!
Yeah, let's do it!
Katsu, you're doing well, I see.
Ka-chan, it was these guys...
What?
We were looking for you, honey.
You ran away right in the middle of things.
How were we supposed to finish?
I'm scared.
Why so defensive?
Ka-chan!
That's just like him.
Alright, you horny bitch,
let's finish what we started.
Sneak Attack!
Satomi, run!
Why, you...
Katsu, you asshole!
I'll never forgive anyone
who hurts my girlfriend.
Don't fuck with us!
Keep your hands off my girlfriend!
What was he trying
to do back there?
He never fought back before.
Ka-chan, stay with me now.
Satomi...
What?
If you're OK with me...
won't you stay...
by my side... forever?
Ka-chan!
Ka-chan! Ka-chan!
Tear me apart! You're a
real animal today, Ka-chan!
I'm just paying you back... for
taking care of me with all your heart.
I'm on fire today!
Until morning... until my
back breaks... I'm gonna do you!
Ka-chan!
Summer ended. Then autumn came.
Now winter has arrived.
It's been over 6 months
but it doesn't look like the company is
coming to take my South Pole No. 28 back.
Ka-chan, I'll be finished
with this scarf soon.
No, not South Pole No. 28...
Satomi! In my mind...
She's not a robot.
She's become human.
Ka-chan