Shit, a nightmare!
I'll never forgive them!
LIVING SEX TOY
Nanami is our next target.
I need you to get the usual information.
Yes.
Wow, where does she get all that money?
Couldn't get much today.
Likes her designers.
Yuka, keep following her,
I know we'll get something eventually.
Yes.
All right, bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Hi, it's me.
Yes, I got it.
Yes, I'm leaving now.
Hi Nanami!
Hi Maria!
Where are you heading to, Nanami?
That woman...
was at the sex party!
My secret!
Heading to work?
Wow, good guess!
A job?
Bye-bye!
Maria, you'll let me know
what's going on, right?
Yes, I'll be sure to call you.
What's going on? About the sex party?
Thank you!
That was wonderful!
I'm glad.
Good night!
Well, I'll see you again, okay.
I'll ask for you again.
Thank you, I'd love that!
Is she a call girl?
She's an escort!
She's an escort.
Not enough.
No?
These pictures aren't good enough.
We need something a lot more explicit.
Something more explicit!
You are the best, Nanami.
Yes, I love fucking all of you!
I love getting gangbanged.
Don't talk so much.
Focus on giving me head, Nanami.
So good!
You're all so hard and big!
God!
I'm so horny!
Let me fuck her pussy!
Yeah, me too!
We'll take turns!
So good!
Yes, pound my pussy!
Yes, this feels delicious!
More, more!
I'm coming!
Baby!
Much faster!
I want you to come,
come all over my body!
Wait!
I'm coming!
I've got jizz all over me!
Good pictures! Yuka, well done.
Yes, she's a slut like the rest of them.
We're ready for the next step!
Yes!
Delivery!
Hi there!
Wait, what is this?
I have something to tell you, Ms. Nanami.
I have this picture of you here.
This one's very explicit.
I think your friends and family might
really enjoy these photographs.
No, don't do that!
Please, you can't do that!
In that case, you're going to have
to come with me.
But where?
Somewhere more private.
I'll get rid of the pictures.
I won't tell your parents.
I understand, I'll go.
All right.
Will you get inside this box?
What!
You want me to destroy the photographs?
All right, but trash those pictures!
Where?
This is a special place
for all the whores at the sex party....
to pay for what they've done!
You are....
You remember now.
You fucking tried to kill me!
What the hell are you talking about?
Is this some kind of a sick joke?
Don't lie!
It's true, I only attended
because Maria invited me!
Maria?
Who the hell is she?
Maria works for
Tokudaiji Pharmaceuticals.
I may have participated at the party....
but I know nothing about
murdering anyone, I swear!
I believe you.
But that doesn't mean
you're getting away with this!
You're still gonna pay!
You'll experience the fear and humiliation
I went through!
No, stop!
Please don't!
I can see the inside of your pussy.
You're a dirty hooker hungry for cock!
How many poor bastards
have fucked you by now?
I don't count anymore.
You're a used-up slut!
I'll show you what hell is about. Suck!
This bitch deserves a good whipping.
No!
Stop, stop!
This is not for your pleasure!
Let's see how hot wax feels
on your tender skin.
You deserve this!
I'm going to rape your precious
merchandise now!
Yes, it's big!
So good!
Faster, much faster!
You don't give me orders!
I'm sorry, will you please...
put it back inside, please?
Put what?
I want it, your hard, meaty penis!
In where?
Inside the pussy.
Whose?
My pussy!
Can't hear you.
Inside my pussy!
And what is my cock going to do?
I want your cock to ravage my pussy!
Good!
Just like that!
Faster, harder!
No!
I'm going to come!
My god!
What's this?
Who put it here?
Open it up!
I hear something.
It's moving!
No, Nanami!
It's Nanami!
Nanami Kirijima,
I enjoyed shattering your sanity.
Our next target is Maria Akitsuki.
Maria Akitsuki.
An executive assistant.
She looks like the corporate type.
See, you're already so big and hard!
I'm going to give you a treat!
I want you to touch me!
Like that.
Yes, right here!
I want your penis!
You feel so good!
Yes, I love it!
This is great!
Come on, come for me!
My god!
A monster load!
Thank you. Later!
I love sucking cock!
Fuck me, hammer my pussy!
I love younger men's cocks!
Jesus!
Thank you. I enjoyed it!
That's what you were doing!
We'll go together again.
Sure.
More younger men.
But big sis.
That's her brother?
Hi there Maria!
Hi Satsuki!
Jyun, this is Ms. Saijyo.
She is a college professor.
Hi Jyun!
This is my dear brother-in-law, Jyun.
Would you like to join us for lunch today?
Hello.
Brother-in-law?
He's not her blood brother.
I saw that woman...
at the sex party!
Perfect timing, Maria!
Can we speak in private?
Sure. I'll be right back, Jyun.
What is it?
I received a call from the chairman.
Horrible things have happened
to Miku, Kay and Nanami.
Really?
It's true.
They were raped and stuffed in boxes...
and dumped at a busy location.
What! What's this about?
I'm not sure.
The prey's death is unconfirmed!
The prey?
We were both there!
It can't be!
It's just all speculation for right now.
The chairman told us to be very careful.
I have to go.
So this is Satsuki Saijyo?
Yes, she's a professor at the university.
Interesting.
Maria comes first.
She seems to really enjoy using condoms.
Yes, and she apparently
only chooses younger men.
Let's get started.
Coming!
Delivery!
Thank you, what is it?
It's condoms!
It's the newer, textured type!
Jyun, shall we test it?
I can't wait any longer!
Yes!
Baby!
You're the best fuck, Jyun.
I love you, Jyun!
Me too, Maria!
I love you, you're all mine, Jyun!
This little bastard will be useful in our plan!
Yes, Maria really seemed to love him.
Good, let's go!
Delivery!
Coming!
About the package earlier today...
it was meant for a different address.
I didn't get any packages.
No need to lie, they were condoms.
What?
And I even have proof that you used it!
How did you!
What should I do
with these pictures, ma'am?
Don't come near me!
You dumb bitch!
You want out of the fucking box?
You made me suffer much more!
Don't you remember your prey?
Of course you do.
You wanna talk?
You are!
Yes, I am indeed alive!
But how?
You're going to die!
Enjoy the last day of your life!
Please forgive me, don't kill me!
I wasn't given a choice.
I swear I was only a participant in the sex!
Lying to my face!
I heard your conversation with Satsuki.
What?
That's okay, her turn's coming up
soon enough.
No, don't kill me, please don't!
You really want to live?
I will give you a chance.
Please give me a chance, please!
I'll be nice.
Open up that box, Maria.
It's Jyun!
He has nothing to do with the party!
He's here for a reason.
What is it?
He's the only chance you have to live, Maria.
Okay, I'll do anything
to get Jyun out of this.
I'll do anything!
You're awfully generous.
Like I said before...
What do you want?
It's really simple,
I just want to watch you two fuck!
One catch-you can't use condoms.
Otherwise, you will both be rotting
corpses in the cold ground.
Maria...
I'll do anything to save you, too.
Okay?
All right, but you have to promise...
to let him go!
All right!
I'm sorry, Jyun.
Maria!
This is so goddamned touching!
We don't have all day!
I love you, Jyun!
Coming!
Yes, come in my mouth!
Yes, it's still hard!
You'd better not be done fucking yet.
The twerp's cock is ready for more!
Jyun, eat my pussy like always.
Yes!
Yes, keep going Jyun!
I'm going to bury your tool inside me now!
Yes, yes!
I'm going to join you two.
No, not my ass!
This is different!
Fuck, I'm coming!
Maria, yes!
I'm coming!
Yes, come baby!
Come inside me!
Yeah!
It seems like you like being covered in jizz.
Is it our turn now?
Yes, make her airtight!
Cool!
I love it.
So many cocks!
So good...
to be filled up!
I love being gangbanged!
I want everyone's load!
I'm coming!
Yes, yes!
Don't think I'm done with you yet!
Maria, you will wish I had killed you!
Look at this box!
Who's is it?
Get rid of it, trash it!
I'll check first.
Careful!
Let's see....
Maria?
It's Maria!
No!
I want it.
Give it to me.
Fuck every hole!
Yuka, our next target
is going to be Satsuki Saijyo.
Get me the info I need.
Yes!
They're on to us,
so you need to be more discreet.
Be careful.
I'll do anything to help
you get your revenge!
I'll reward you with plenty
of insane fucking!