This cock is so great,
I love the way it feels!
The veins are raised like it's angry!
What is this? I can't move!
His come tastes so good!
So thick, so sweet,
and a bit bitter.
It's my turn now!
I feel it, the thick cock inside me!
Why can't I move my body?
I can feel him coming!
So warm.
It's still so hard!
You try it, too!
No, that's okay.
That voice....
Right, I was invited to a party by Yuka!
We get to enjoy him now.
This is the best penis we've had so far!
If it's that good,
make sure to suck him dry!
Don't waste a single drop!
Yes.
It's getting even bigger!
God, that's great!
Look at the amount!
Yeah, he can ejaculate so much!
Can he come any more?
Three more?
Just take what you can,
and we'll finish as usual.
Yes!
What do they mean?
He's finished.
All right, take your final nap.
Don't you think it's such a waste?
But we have to do this.
Okay, let's go!
My head hurts.
What's going on? Shit, I can't move.
I didn't write a suicide note!
Why do they want to kill me?
Why rape me, and kill me?
They will all pay for this!
Yes!
Delivery.
Thank you.
It's heavy, do you need me
to carry it inside?
I'd like that.
Just leave it here.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Somebody, help me!
Get out!
Do you know why you are here?
Do you remember that party?
Party?
The sex party?
It's called a sex party.
That's what they called it.
Do you recognize me?
You are....
Now you remember!
You tried to kill me the other day!
I don't know
what you're talking about, Shouji!
You fucking bitch!
Don't hurt me!
Your perverted friends
tried to kill me after the party!
What? I don't know anything.
Lying cunt!
I'm telling the truth, I swear!
Why pick me?
You had to bring a date to attend the party.
I wasn't dating anyone...
so when I hired a moving company
and you came over...
I thought you were just really nice.
Tell the truth!
I swear, it's all true!
Shut up!
No!
You can't be a fucking virgin!
Yes, I'm a virgin!
Yeah, you are bleeding.
I told you, I really am a virgin!
Well, I don't really give a damn.
This is your pay back
for what happened to me at the party!
I said I don't know anything!
Fuck you!
You do have a nice, large clit.
No!
A virgin shouldn't get wet so quickly!
All right, it won't hurt much now.
Yes, it feels good!
No don't stop!
You might be a virgin, but you're a slut!
Yes, you feel so big!
Yes, I never knew sex would feel so good!
No, don't pull out!
So you like the cock that much.
Yes, so please put it back in!
Will you do whatever I ask you to?
Yes, I'll do anything, so hurry!
Promise me!
I promise!
Good!
God!
I can't believe how good sex can feel.
Coming!
It's still so hard!
You really like this.
You can have my cock
as long as you do what I say, all right?
Yes, I'll do anything for you, Shouji!
Don't forget what you just said!
My penis is all yours.
Thank you!
Yuka, tell me the names
of the party's members.
I know Miku Shizuki.
I'm a tutor, and she's my student.
Miku Shizuki?
You're her freaking tutor?
What kind of a sick tutor are you?
No, actually she's the one that invited me.
Don't lie!
It is true, that was the first time
I ever went to a sex party!
There were 4 or 5 others, I think.
I didn't know what I could say or do!
You'd better not be lying!
I'm not!
All right, I believe you.
You said you would do anything I say.
Yes.
I'm going to make them all pay!
You're going to help me get my revenge.
That way, you'll get your erect,
meat hammer.
Yes, I'll help you.
Leave that for later.
Listen to me!
Yes.
Well, we'll start with Miku
and get more information from her.
I'll find out what they like
and exploit...
their weaknesses to my advantage.
But how?
Sluts that attend a sex party...
should have some
very intense sexual fetishes.
I work as a delivery man.
I'll send them a gift they can't refuse
and use that to benefit my cause.
My role?
Your role is to find out
about their sexual fetishes.
How are you Miku?
Hi Kay, what's going on?
I'm on my way to a fitness competition.
Did you win again?
You are the shining star
in the fitness competition circuit!
I'm running late, I have to go!
I hope you win!
Kay....
She was also at the sex party.
Hi Yuka, come in!
So, how is schoolwork?
Okay, I guess.
Say Miku....
about the sex party last week....
I told you we can't talk about that!
Yeah, that's right.
Miku, I know you'd really like this.
No.
It's all for you.
We should get started!
Yes.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
Miku, just relax and enjoy
your new book today.
I'll go now.
Well, but....
Don't worry about it!
I'm getting wet!
My ass needs a cock.
Yes, yes right there, I love it!
I want someone to fuck my ass hard!
I'm coming!
Yes, I'm coming!
Coming!
This is for you.
Thank you!
Later.
What is it?
This is an anal toy!
It looks so weird!
This is good, I can shove it in my ass.
My god, I can feel it.
I can feel it in my ass.
Yes, it's better than my fingers!
My god!
I love this toy!
I'm coming!
Job well done.
She seems to prefer ass-fucking.
She's enjoying herself.
You like it in the ass?
I've never...
I'll show you one day.
Yes.
So muscular!
I want more muscles.
I want to be more masculine.
God, I love the cock.
So hard.
Come on me,
I want you to unload on my face.
It's warm!
I'd love to be a man.
She seems to want a man's body.
Yes, she wants to be a man!
So that's why she works out so hard!
She can't grow a certain type
of muscle, though!
What's that?
It's your favorite muscle
that gets hard a lot.
A penis!
Yes, I think that's her weakness.
Hello!
I have a package!
You are Miku Shizuki?
Yes.
About the last delivery we made here,
I'm afraid it was a mistake!
What delivery?
I'm afraid it was an anal sex toy.
What, an anal toy?
You didn't open it, did you?
No, I don't know where it is!
I do have proof.
What is?
You don't want me posting this
around your home?
God no, what do you want?
I need you to get inside this box.
What?
Don't worry about it.
It's just a simple game, so....
You don't want the picture getting out.
I understand.
This is cramped.
It's a short drive, miss.
You can get out now.
That was uncomfortable!
Where am I?
This is where I'll punish you!
Punish, what do you mean?
You had fun at the last sex party!
Who are you?
My hair turned gray, but....
It's you!
Now you remember.
You fucking tried to kill me, right!
What, kill you?
You lying-ass slut!
Please don't hurt me!
I'll fucking kill you now!
Don't kill me, please,
I'll do anything, I swear I'll do it!
You'll do anything?
Yes, I'll do anything you want me to,
I swear to god!
Strip!
Strip now!
I'll do it.
Yeah!
A good view of your pussy and ass!
Don't look at me.
Yeah!
You really like this?
No...
not my ass!
So you're an anal slut like I thought!
So, you like this?
You like it in the ass?
Yes, it feels much better in my asshole!
Well, we'll try something new, then.
What the--
No, I feel it!
No!
My stomach.
Let me go to the bathroom!
I suffered much more than you did, miss.
No!
You can't hold it in!
Well, now that your ass is clean....
You wanted a cock, right?
A hard, ass-fucking?
My god, you feel too big...
inside my ass!
Coming!
Yes, yes!
I'm coming!
I won, but you have one more
surprise coming.
Hey, what is this?
Who left it here?
What's in it?
Let's open it!
Who is it?
Is that Miku?
No!
Hold on!
I've a package.
Thanks, man.
Night.
What is it?
A strap-on!
A penis! I have a penis!
I want a hard, dark, thick, long penis!
I want a cock just like this!
Yes!
I want one, I want to have a hard cock!
My nipples are getting hard,
just like my strap-on!
Yes!
My pussy's getting wet!
I love it!
Yes!
Yes, yes, Jesus!
I wish the dildo would ejaculate.
Coming!
Delivery service.
Another one?
I'm sorry about the rude content
inside the package.
We do need it back,
I apologize for the mistake.
But, you can't take it back.
Did you used it?
You really want your own penis?
This look familiar?
How did you?
We need to talk, so come along with me.
You want to tarnish
your fitness champion status?
But....
I'll do it.
Then please get inside this box.
I really don't want to be spotted with you.
But, I'm not dressed!
I get it.
Where did you take me?
Who are you?
Remember my face?
You are!
Now you remember.
What is this?
I'm here to make you pay
for what happened!
I swear, I don't know!
No!
Do you like the electric pulse?
Tell me about this sex party.
I swear I don't know!
I'm not lying!
I'm being truthful!
I was invited by Nanami!
I just tagged along!
Who's this Nanami?
A model!
Nanami Kirijima, please, no more!
You don't look like you're lying.
Don't you want this, see,
a big, meaty penis?
Yes, I like big ones.
Yes, thick, big meat!
The kind I want for myself!
No, give me more cock!
No, it's my turn!
Another virgin?
You're too big, you're tearing me!
A virgin that likes sucking!
You're crazy!
Don't move!
Yes, yes!
It's starting to feel real good!
I'm coming.
Take this!
I've got come inside me!
There's more surprises coming.
What's this?
Who put this here?
What's inside this thing?
Open it!
It's Kay!
Kay Yuzuiri, I'm done with you.
Nanami Kirijima is next!
Got it, Yuka?