Yes, that feels good.
Shouji.
If I didn't invite him....
Yes, that party.
Ouch!
Shouji!
You're going to continue?
Yes.
We shouldn't continue.
We've come too far.
I'll get my revenge.
But....
Scared?
Baby!
Go away, if you're scared.
No, I'll do anything for you.
Satsuki Saijyo is our next target.
Yes, Shouji.
It'll be over soon.
I'm coming!
Yes!
Living Sex Toy Delivery
Volume 3
Satsuki is a genius that graduated
medical school in the U.S. at 1 4.
She's worked as a professor since then.
A young elite.
She receives a private grant from Tokudaiji
Pharmaceuticals for her research.
Tokudaiji? Maria's company.
Hold on.
They were collecting a lot of sperm.
Yes, I've noticed.
There has to be a reason.
Start your investigation.
Yes.
Is that her sister?
I have a present for you today, Satsuki!
I'm honored, Ms. Ayame.
It looks good, Satsuki.
Now, on your hands and knees
like a good dog.
Shake!
You're my slave bitch.
Listen to your master like a dog.
Answer me!
Yes.
No, bark! You're a dog, right!
Arf!
Now, lick this!
I see, she's a masochist.
An elite, like Satsuki?
Powerful people sometimes need
to feel submissive.
Find anything about this other girl?
I don't know yet.
We'll know soon enough.
Who is it?
I'm an outcall esthetician.
You have the wrong house.
We're doing a introductory special
free of charge right now.
I'm a skilled massage therapist.
Massage?
Sure, I'll try that, then.
Thank you very much.
Come in.
Sure.
That feels good.
Yes!
You're very good.
If you don't mind.
More pressure, just like that.
That's great.
Please pinch me, please pinch my ass!
You want me to pinch you?
Yes, hurry!
Like that!
Grab a whip from my drawer over there.
Is this it?
Yes, I want you to whip me with it, hard!
Stronger!
Yes, whip me!
Yes, harder!
More!
Harder, whip me hard!
Yes, keep going just like that!
Yes!
I love it!
Master Ayame, you're the best!
I'm coming!
Did you enjoy your massage?
You were very good.
That was wonderful.
So she's a true masochist.
She cried out "Master Ayame."
I think that might be
the name of that girl.
You might be right.
Any pictures?
Not today.
Nothing?
Yes, I'm sorry.
That's fine, we'll find a way.
Who is it?
Delivery.
Thank you.
What is it?
It's nice and rough.
You won't graduate with your grades.
Please, I absolutely have to graduate.
Will you do absolutely anything
I ask you to?
Yes!
Then tie me up.
What?
You don't have to.
You just won't graduate this year.
I'll do it.
Yes!
I love the roughness of the rope!
Isn't it painful?
This feels absolutely divine.
I can feel it in my pussy and nipples!
Now.
Insert this.
Stuff this into my pussy.
Like that, move the dildo in and out.
Keep fucking me like that.
Ms. Saijyo.
Put the other end inside you.
Ms. Saijyo!
Move your hips for me.
Keep going, that feels wonderful!
Ms. Saijyo, I can't.
I'm going to....
Keep moving, harder!
Yes, very nice!
My god!
Ms. Saijyo!
These are good shots.
I'll get her now!
Delivery!
Coming!
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, your package yesterday
was supposed to go to a different address.
The package contained ropes.
You didn't open it, did you?
But....
I thought so.
However, this is for you.
How did--
You're going to have to come with me.
Come with you?
Hold it!
Try that again and I'll post this
all over your work.
Please don't!
Then you're going to follow my orders
without resistance.
Where am I?
Want to know?
Yes?
Welcome to the Gates of Hell.
No, stop!
Let me go, please don't hurt me!
What did I do?
Don't play stupid, you bitch!
Don't tell me you don't remember!
Take a good look at me!
You're the--
You thought you got rid of me!
No, I was just following Ayame's...
Ayame? Who the hell is she?
I can't say.
Tell me, who the fuck is Ayame?
You won't talk?
After this, maybe you'll want to
open up a bit.
After this?
Feel like talking now?
Like that?
Remember, you and your friends tortured
me and turned my life into a living hell!
You're cruel!
Now, answer me, damn it!
Who the fuck is Ayame?
Answer me!
Tokudaiji.
Pharmaceuticals.
President.
That's all l--
That's fine, I can find out the rest.
I still need to make you pay
for what you did!
You're going to get punished
with this whip!
You're wet already, you whore!
Yes, I want a thick cock in my pussy!
I didn't expect a intellectual like you
to beg for a hard cock!
I want it!
-I want a thick, hard one!
-Shut up, damn it!
I didn't bring you here
to make you feel good.
You noisy, stupid cunt!
Take this, you whore!
That hurts!
You'll never enjoy sex again!
Please stop it!
I thought you're
a goddamned masochist, right?
That's too much!
You're tearing my pussy!
Who put this box here?
What is it?
Let's look inside.
Be careful!
Professor Saijyo!
Satsuki Saijyo.
Your life is ruined now!
That girl!
It's her. Why is she here?
Good night, President.
President?
That girl's the president?
Ayame Tokudaiji.
Yes, she is the president.
I can't believe it,
she still looks like a child!
That's strange.
I want a thorough investigation of her.
Yes!
This looks like the place.
I remember, this was where
the sex party was held!
Terrific!
The thickness, the texture.
I'm so horny right now.
I feel like I'm on fire!
Yes, I feel it.
Yes, I'm dripping wet now.
I want a slave.
I want my slave to eat my pussy.
It's dripping!
I'm so wet it's flowing out.
My pussy juice.
Tell me I'm the master,
tell me I'm the queen!
I want it!
I want my slave!
I want a slutty, masochist,
female sex slave.
Yes!
Jesus!
Ayame is a sadist.
Yes, I'm sure of it.
So, you're sure that this was where
the sex party was held?
Yes.
Yuka, it's your turn.
What?
You're going to be Ayame's partner.
Partner?
You mind?
No, I'll do it.
I'm your slave, Shouji.
I'll do whatever you want.
That's right, you're my bitch.
Delivery!
Thank you.
She's behind all this.
What is it?
Nothing. Good night.
A video?
Does your life need some excitement?
Maybe a sex slave from the Lily M.
Club is your answer.
I'm sure you will be very satisfied
with your decision!
Good morning, my queen!
I'm a whore,
and I want to be your slave!
I've been bad, and I need to be punished
by the queen!
Call the Lily M Club to fulfill
your deepest desires!
That looks like a lot of fun!
I'm from the Lily M. Club,
and my name is Riho.
I was waiting, come in.
Sure.
Doesn't it make your body feel hot?
Yes, I'm glad to be punished
by a beautiful, young master like you.
Thank you.
You'll get a special treat from me.
Here, you may drink my piss.
Thank you.
Don't waste any!
Drink all of it!
Guzzle it down.
I've been saving it all day for you.
So, was it delicious?
I'm so honored to be allowed to drink
your delicious piss, my queen.
Lick it, clean my pussy
with your tongue.
Very good, Riho.
Yes, keep licking me there.
Play with my clit with your tongue,
just like that.
Now, on your hands and knees!
You're going to be my horse.
You can go faster.
Come on horse-girl.
Faster, much faster.
Riho, you are a very good slave.
I'm honored, my queen.
You're adorable.
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
Let's see what's inside this CD.
Ayame was drinking this.
Riho, I'll be out in a minute.
Sure.
What's in here?
Shouji Ikenaga,
test subject number 1969.
Test subject?
Sperm Production Ability Grade A.
Subject disposal complete.
Disposal complete?
Dear god!
Misayuki Miyama, test Subject.
That's enough!
Now, copy the data.
Yes, but what is this all about?
Eternal youth.
Ayame is drinking sperm from different men
to regain and maintain her youth.
So the beverage in the refrigerator....
Satsuki collected the sperm.
The men were later disposed,
like lab animals.
I'm going to get that fucking cunt
back for this, damn it!
Coming!
Delivery.
You must be Ms. Ayame.
Yes, I am.
Who are you?
Untie these ropes, and let me go right now!
Do you know where we are?
This is my basement.
Your collection room.
I was your test subject in this room.
You're.. but that's impossible!
Now you remember.
I was one of your disposable test subjects.
You recognize this CD, right?
That's my--
You're finished, bitch.
You're going to lose everything you have,
once I go public with this information.
I just wanted to stay young, that's all.
I hired Satsuki to do research,
and became a test subject myself.
I don't think I did anything wrong at all.
And it worked, right?
That's right, I've been able to reverse
the effects of aging.
How many men died for this?
You dirty come whore!
You deserve to die.
No, stop!
I can give you lots of money!
Stupid bitch!
You're going to suffer.
Can you tolerate not being in control?
That hurts!
Please stop!
I suffered more than this, you cunt!
No, stop!
Take this, you whore!
It burns!
No, stop!
I'm sorry, I was wrong!
No more, please stop!
I'm just getting started.
You slut, you like being fucked
with a candle?
No, stop it!
You're wet enough now.
Extinguish that.
No, please, pull it out!
Pull it out right now!
No, it burns!
Stop!
I'm not done with you just yet.
Forgive me!
That hurts!
It's tearing apart, please!
No more, stop!
What is it, you want your pussy stuffed?
Wait, that feels really different.
I kind of like it.
God, yes!
More!
Yes, faster!
I want you to come inside me!
No, please don't stop!
Fuck me, fuck me!
You piece of shit!
You took enough jizz from me!
You're on your own.
Yes, this feels so good!
Step away from the box.
What jerk put this box here?
Please, step away!
I want more cock!
Yes!
How gross!
What the fuck!
President, what happened!
President?
What's wrong with her!
Please, I want a big cock right now!
-I'm calling an ambulance right now.
-I'm done.
I'm finished with my revenge.
Please step back and look away!
But why am I feeling so empty?
What is the purpose of my life from now on?
Now we're finished.
Will you please fuck me tonight?
That's right, I still have her.
I'm coming!
If I keep drinking his come,
it will prevent me from getting old forever!
I'm not going to let you go!
My Shouji!
I want more come!