In the 22nd century, due to
the population explosion...
...and diminishing natural resources...
...humanity spread out in all directions.
Underground, on the
oceans, and out into space.
Aiding this expansion was the
development of a virtual computer system...
...the creation of new materials by
bio-tech firms, and the development of...
...advanced robot technology that
made the creation of Silhouettes possible.
But...
Stop!
If you don't stop within five
seconds, under law 104, chapter 7...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
They destroyed the Silhouette.
The suspect is armed with missiles.
But the Silhouettes have become
widely used in many dangerous fields...
...and are now being used in
serious crimes, such as murder and rape.
W-What?
Let me taste a little.
You'll hurt yourself if you move.
What's happening?
Our research department was right...
You're useful.
Rika, good job!
You've mastered the block chop!
Now, if you break this stone, the
power will sync with the Silhouette.
Mimi the Silhouette
will create an electric wave.
It's a required skill for
surviving dangerous situations.
Ouch, that hurts!
Not good enough, Rika.
Your fighting skills are improving.
It will take time for you to
master them, but you can do it.
What are you going to do now?
I was just clumsy.
Are you done?
I'll have to be your
bodyguard for a while.
Yes, coach.
Can you get out?
If you don't move fast...
I'm going to do things like this!
Stop, Sandy!
Oh, your breasts are pretty big.
S-Sandy!
Try and escape now, Rika!
But...
Stop, Sandy!
If I were a pervert,
do you think I'd stop?
I won't stop!
How do you feel?
Feeling hot?
Because you're doing that!
L-I was asked to get you...
I'm on my way.
How long have you been there?
For a while.
Good morning.
How's everything?
After this experiment, the latest
model, Silhouette Mimi, will be completed.
It's different from a security or
service robot with virtual control.
It'll share all the human senses,
from consciousness to touch.
It's much more advanced
than an ordinary Silhouette.
That's our Rika.
Not just because of Rika.
It's also because of our staff.
Well, let's detach
Mimi and connect it to Rika.
Brain wave and pulse, normal.
Her ability as a manipulator is excellent.
Is that so?
We don't know why the most qualified
candidates are around 19 years old...
...but Rika is especially endowed
with intelligence, health, and stamina.
I guess old people like
me aren't qualified then.
Oh, no, that's not what I mean...
It's too much for Masa.
She's even sexier when she moves.
It's even more feminine than Rika is.
She feels as if she's really naked.
Masatoshi, check her skin sense.
Touch her body.
L-I got it.
Is this okay?
Okay, now check her lower body.
Lower body?
But I've never done
anything with Rika before...
Are you okay?
O-Ouch!
I guess so.
Rika, be careful.
Mimi's power is far
beyond human strength.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for waiting.
So, you slapped Masatoshi with Mimi?
You didn't hurt him, did you?
I just knocked him around a little.
That's how strong Mimi can be.
Cheer up.
This isn't like you.
Let's go home.
Hello, it's me.
They just left the office.
Get her when she's alone.
So, did he go home?
No, he's still in the lab.
I see.
He's really a hard worker.
So, how long have
you guys been dating?
Did you do it yet?
Stop it.
We're not like that.
Are you crazy?
You're so old fashioned.
So, I'll pick you up tomorrow morning.
Okay.
We'll practice real hard tomorrow.
Stop it, Sandy!
What driving!
Flawless victory!
Is this the suspect in
the kidnapping cases?
Marvelous.
You son of a...
Ms. Rika!
Sandy didn't pick you up this morning?
It looks like she's missing.
Missing?
Her Countash is also missing,
so she might've had an accident.
She would have called, otherwise.
I wonder what happened after
she dropped me off last night?
We don't know.
But she's not easy to kidnap.
Even a male
bodyguard couldn't beat her.
That's right.
You be careful, too.
We'll get you another
bodyguard right away.
I'll be your chauffeur.
You?
Well, I guess it's better than nothing.
Father!
Don't worry about me.
I know the self-defense
techniques Sandy taught me.
You want Ms. Rika to protect you?
No, um...
I'll protect her!
Sandy...
Are you awake?
Who's there?
It's quite a sight, little Sandy Moore.
Let me go!
Sure.
If you'll be a Silhouette
manipulator for our organization.
Silhouette manipulator?
You know, it's something
your company working on.
Are you an industry spy?
Unfortunately, I know nothing about it.
No, a spy is already in your firm.
We really liked your work as a
fighter and a computer technician.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Can you promise?
To become one of us?
No way!
Let me go!
I guess we need the ceremony.
Ceremony?
What's going on?
What's...
What's this?
This is the ceremony that
will make you faithful to us.
Ceremony?
No, don't come near me!
No need to be scared.
They are controlled by
well-trained manipulators.
You are our...
Sandy, we are going to have fun.
This music will sound
soothing to you soon.
Subliminal stimulation.
You know a great deal.
Stop it!
You must want to know.
The real you...
Now relax.
Sandy, open your mind and
your body, and be one of us.
Be one of us.
We will take you to a
world you've never been to.
To the world of pleasure...
Sandy, your body wants a man.
A man's finger.
A man's tongue.
A man's body.
You'll be our Silhouette manipulator.
Silhouette manipulator...
More, more!
More!
This unit was designed to control the
feedback system for the Silhouette.
It will detach the excitement
patterns from the nervous system...
...so in case the Silhouette has a
breakdown, there won't be any feedback.
After attaching it, virtual
Mimi would be complete.
What?
To tell you the truth, it's lost.
Lost?
It was stolen?
Do you have any doubts about Sandy?
If she doesn't show up...
I don't believe it!
Now, you can be the Silhouette
manipulator for our underground fighting.
Thank you for going out with me.
Sorry about yesterday.
Did I hurt you?
A little.
So, can you stay with me tonight?
Okay, Rika?
So, you also think Sandy did it?
Oh, I don't know.
So, some stranger?
No, that's impossible.
Our lab's security can't be broken.
Then it's somebody from the inside?
But it's weird.
When you and Sandy
left, it was still in the vault.
So, who was the last
person in the lab last night?
Tell me who it was!
Well, our security
department is still investigating.
Maybe she has
nothing to do with this case.
Oh, my god!
Would you pick it up?
Ouch!
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Hey, I really want to know.
If you tell me, maybe I'll
stay with you until morning.
Oh, I see!
Okay then.
It was me and Jessica.
Jessica?
The new technician?
Rika?
I'm sorry, I just remembered something.
Oh, Rika, won't you
come home with me?
I know it's not her...
Well, I'll ask Jessica.
But what if Jessica is the spy?
Is Jessica here?
Yes, you must be Rika.
I knew you'd come here.
What?
Hold it, come on in!
Jessica wants to talk to
you about Silhouette Mimi.
Mimi is right here!
Oh, I pushed too hard again!
Where is Jessica?
By the way you showed up,
you must think I'm the spy.
I knew you'd react that way.
Take a look.
Shit!
I won't let you go.
Let me go!
Don't touch me!
Oh, Mimi!
Iron Ox wins!
Now Iron Ox has won his tenth game!
We will pay your share
based on your percentage.
You may negotiate
that last game's rights with Iron Ox.
Our next match is...
Our audience is very lucky tonight.
This match is a Rape Match.
Also, our guest fighter is the
daughter of a corporate bigwig.
Of course, she's a
very talented manipulator.
And her Silhouette is a prototype!
A state of the art, girl-model Silhouette!
Of course, our Silhouette
is more advanced than hers.
It's about time for her to wake up.
Where am I?
Mimi?
Jessica!
It's time, Rika.
No!
If you want to survive, you'll
have to fight with the Silhouette.
Who are you?
Don't waste your time.
Whose voice is that?
Oh, you found me.
That's my Mimi.
Who could it be?
Sounds familiar...
I told you.
If you want to survive, you have
to beat him with your Silhouette.
Or would you rather be raped and have
the data fed back to your own body?
Shit!
Go to hell!
Hey, Sandy's
self-defense technique saved me!
Oh, no, I'm naked!
Ouch!
Leave me alone!
Stop!
It's a woman's sweet spot...
It was good that we
stole that safety mechanism.
You must be feeling
everything perfectly.
What?
What are you touching?
No!
That's against the rules!
There are no rules in this match.
You're so cute, Rika.
God, it's really a woman.
Please, stop it.
So, being a woman is your weak point!
Oh, no!
Being so sensitive is your weak point!
No, stop!
What are you doing?
No!
This is great!
She even moans like a real woman!
No!
It's great!
It's too great.
What a Silhouette!
It's better than a human woman!
Now, I will take you from behind.
What the hell?
Take this!
I did it!
Good job!
But, he'll never be able
to use his thing again!
His thing?
It's okay.
We have somebody that's
a little better than him for you.
Now, for our main event!
We have our Lee
Corporation prototype.
Our top Silhouette!
I had it made
specially for such an occasion.
I am glad I'm able
to use it for this match.
Sandy?
Don't you think it looks like her?
What's wrong, Sandy?
It's me, Rika!
Don't bother!
She's just a
Silhouette manipulator now!
No, stop it, Sandy!
What's going on, Sandy?
Wake up!
This Silhouette looks like Mimi.
Technically, it's the same type.
Do they have the same power?
This is a pit fight!
I have to win to get Sandy back!
Wake up, Sandy!
No, I can't beat her after all...
It's getting near the end.
Here, Sandy.
I'm so jealous, Rika, your friend
Sandy is going to treat you so well...
What the hell is that?
Sandy, what are you...
Stop!
Sandy, why?
Please, Sandy, stop!
You did it, Jessica!
Now, Rika and Mimi belong to us.
We will get other Silhouettes from...
It's so good, so good!
I've always wanted you, Rika!
I love you, Rika!
I can't beat her with
my normal techniques.
I'll try this!
Damn!
Boss!
Oh, Dad!
Now what?
Was that Mimi?
Sandy!
Sandy, it's me, Rika!
Hang on!
Sandy!
Mimi!
No, Rika...
It was beautiful!
Oh, Sandy!
You're back to normal.
I guess...
But, you finally mastered that skill.
You really beat me.
Thank you, Rika.
Thank God!
Oh, we should name that
technique the Thunder Break.
Okay.
Oh, we have no time to chat.
Rika, fight with Mimi.
It's okay, you can beat them with Mimi.
I'll take your body.
Thanks!
Mimi, go for it!
You think you can get away with this?
Shit!
I can't let you go this time!
Get out of my way!
Don't come any closer!
How dare you
destroy my cute Silhouette!
I'll get you for this!
Now!
Wait!
Rika, what happened?
What's wrong with Mimi?
What is this?
Oh, Iron Cow.
Miss, why?
Mimi!
Rika!
Rika?
Did Mimi...
Oh, my god!
Rika, I'll take it off.
Rika!