One: A Glorious Season, Episode 3
Kohei!
You sleepyhead! Wake up now!
What the...
Kohei, where are you?
Your bag and uniform are
here, so you must be here.
You'll be late for class for sure!
Where are you?
I got you!
Come out!
Good morning...
Why are you sleeping under the bed?
I thought that you'd be surprised, so...
My goodness, I was surprised!
Are you happy now?
I guess.
Why didn't you prepare
for school last night?
You have to learn to do this everyday!
We have Math class, Japanese
Literature and gym class!
Kohei...
What?
Are you sure that you were lying
under the bed just to surprise me?
Can you think of any other reason?
You surprise me all the time,
you didn't need to do that.
You couldn't be comfortable
sleeping like that.
You know I'm the type of
person who can sleep anywhere.
There are other things you can
do to surprise me, you know.
For instance?
Well, you know...
Like, you could appreciate me
for waking you up every morning.
Okay, then how about
going out on a date?
What?
It's perfect since today is Saturday.
I don't think that's
such a great idea...
Why?
Well, you know...
Some girls might get upset
if they saw us together...
Nah, I don't think so.
There're girls who like you, you know?
No way.
Yes.
Who?
I don't know who those girls are.
Okay then, let's go out on a date.
Kohei?
Were you sleeping under the bed,
so we'd have this conversation?
W-Well, that's quite
a stretch, isn't it?
Kohei, I know you are lying
because you looked away from me.
Let's go! We're gonna be late!
Oh wait!
My home is this way.
Okay.
Good night.
What's wrong?
It's just that you were
really nice to me today...
You're not going to go
way or anything, are you?
What are you talking about?
Just a thought.
Well, good night...
Sometimes I just want to cry...
Where should I go to cry?
What I should cry for?
A feeling of emptiness never
brings happiness to us...
Floating in the ocean,
what should I cry for?
Happiness? Why would
I want such a thing?
I feel as if I have a hole in my heart,
and there is nothing left to lose.
Can I call it a perfect environment?
If I have nothing to lose in this
world, what am I still afraid of?
It is like the dead
end I am heading for.
It is like the end of a story...
I felt the same emptiness
before I knew all of this.
Emptiness...
I couldn't do anything, but wait.
After he left, I started
to forget about him.
Misaki...
Who are you?
Have we met?
Hello, young man!
She made me feel so uncomfortable...
Are you looking for a
gift for your girlfriend?
Yeah...
What are you looking for?
If I'd known, I would have gotten it!
Excuse me?
Oh, I want something that
can make a girl smile...
Well, how about these stuffed dolls?
They are popular items in this store.
These are so popular that
sometimes we sell them out in a day!
Um, could I have this one?
Hello?
Mizuka? It's me.
Hey, what's up?
Do you wanna go out with me next
Sunday?
What?
What's wrong?
We just had a date last week!
Is anything wrong with having
dates two weeks in a row?
I'm not saying it's wrong...
Okay, then I'll meet you
at 3:00 pm at the park then.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it!
I have to make up to her
for the Christmas party!
I can't believe that I overslept today!
Good, she isn't here yet...
Well, who does she think
she is... keeping me waiting?
What is she doing?
Is she still picking up her clothing?
I can't believe this! The forecast
said precipitation percentage is 20%!
Does that mean that it
rains 20 percent of a day?
It's not funny...
But Mizuka would wait for
me, she's that kind of girl...
What is she doing?
Are you all right, Kohei?
Mizuka...
Your aunt told me that you didn't
come back after you went to the park.
I was so surprised when I
found you lying on the ground!
What were you doing there?
Don't you remember our promise?
What?
Nothing...
Mizuka?
You are pretty...
What are you saying all of sudden?
No, Kohei...
Your kiss tastes like milk.
I remember you like milk...
Stupid...
Kohei, you'd better stay in bed!
No!
What are you doing, Kohei?
You smell good, Mizuka...
Kohei...
No, we'd better stop...
I mean, we can do this another
day, after you're all better...
No! Don't look!
I want to see!
Kohei?
I want to see it closer.
Kohei, you're too close...
You must be kidding...
Mizuka, let me put it in.
You look exhausted, Kohei...
I can do this because I like you...
Kohei...
Did I hurt you?
No...
Here we go...
You're going to break me!
It feels amazing!
Kohei! It feels great!
Kohei!
I can't hold it any longer!
I feel so hot inside!
Come, Kohei! Come inside of me!
Aw, it's so cute!
I wish I could've
seen Kohei buying this!
You are mean!
Thank you very much, Kohei.
I'll cherish this.
All right.
I'll stop by tomorrow.
Okay.
It's the way to home...
Hmm?
I feel like I'm on my way home.
Is that so?
I went somewhere far away that day.
Yeah?
That day, the sky looked so
much different from usual...
It seemed as if the sky led me to
a different direction in my life...
But I couldn't go home because
I went too far that day.
I ended up crossing the ocean and
living in a city I didn't know.
After I grew up, I remembered there
was a city where I spent my childhood.
It was such a lonesome feeling...
Because the real affection and
warmth should have been there.
Maybe you are talking
about yourself now...
Did I sound like that?
Yes...
I tried my best until the very end.
I wished to stay in my old town forever.
I didn't mean to deny this world...
Rather, I thought if
I accepted this world...
...I would be allowed
to stay in my old place.
But it didn't work.
I don't want you to tell
me a story like that.
I wonder if I would have worked harder,
could I have stayed where I was?
Why?
I'm not saying that I
don't want to come here...
I just regret that the bonds
I had with other people...
...were not worthy enough
to tie me to that world.
What do you think?
I don't think you could...
Because this world
starts inside of you...
I see...
Yes...
Or maybe I could put an
end to this world being...
Yeah, maybe I still can...
This world would not end,
because it's already over...
Hey, Kohei!
Good morning.
Good morning...
What are you doing?
I've been waiting for you, of course.
Waiting for me?
Yes, waiting for you.
This is your first time, isn't it?
I guess so.
Does this bother you?
Not at all.
I like it!
Okay, good.
Yes, I am happy.
You don't have to repeat yourself!
Embarrassed?
No way!
Are you sure?
Well, let's go!
Yes!
Kohei, where were you yesterday?
What?
Your aunt told me that you didn't
come home after you went to the park.
Well, I was at a coffee
shop, then I fell asleep.
Unbelievable!
Eternity...
There is a place that exists
forever beyond this world.
The new world was born on that day,
passed, and now is about to disappear.
And now I'm heading for that world...
Oh, Mizuka...
I guess we are strangers now, huh?
Good bye, my lover for life...
I got you!
I finally got you!
I was pretending to be a stranger
because I thought you'd disappear...
I wanted to run to you and hold
you tight, but I held myself back...
I was about to burst into
tears but I tried not to.
It hurts...
You are holding me too tight, Mizuka...
I'm not letting you go!
You'll leave me alone and disappear.
I am not going anywhere.
Really?
Really.
I just...
I just want to hold you.
We were around their age...
I met Kohei...
In front of that swing...
Why are you crying?
Because I'm lonely...
What made you so sad?
I thought that my happy
days would never end...
But I learned that nothing
would last forever...
There is eternity...
Eternity is here...
I'll be with you forever.
That girl was you, Mizuka...
What happened, Mizuka?
Am I smiling now?
Yeah, you are smiling...
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'll choke you if you lie.
Are you trying to kill me?
I've been living a normal life.
I've been trying to lead
my life like I used to.
It was not easy for me, but I was always
trying to have a positive attitude.
But what made me feel sad like this?
The season changes so
slowly, but it's for sure.
I can't stay in the same season.
Time still passes.
Little by little, I'm getting
further away from that day.
What I was looking for and what
I am looking for are not the same.
The view is also different.
Everything changes.
The only things that can
stay the same are memories.
The brightest memories...
Things wouldn't change in this world.
Even a boy disappears from this
world, and from everyone's memory...
But he would never
disappear from my memory.
Because I know Kohei
will be back someday.
Hey Mizuka, I'm Mr. Rabbit!
You look a little down!
Whose fault is that?
Listen Mizuka.
Do you have a stupid
and senseless friend?
Well, he actually likes you a lot.
Why are you telling me that now?
So please smile for him.
Because your smile makes him happy.
You should talk!
And even though he's not around,
please don't forget to smile, Mizuka.
Even if it's hard for you,
smile as much as possible
You never know when he'll come back.
Well, that's all now. I hope
I cheered you up. Good-bye!
So Kohei, please come back soon...
This is a lonely place,
and I'm standing here.
No...
I'm feeling sad because
I know something now...
Are you sad?
Yes. I didn't need any prize.
Even though it gives you pleasure?
I realized that I didn't need them.
Why?
It's about growing up.
I don't understand.
You don't know yet.
Because you are still a child.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Do you know that you
can't come back, right?
Yes. I know.
So you chose this.
Yeah.
Kohei
I have to go now.
Okay. Good-bye.
Thank you. Bye.
Then he suddenly came upon me!
And then?
So I threw his ass so bad.
It's funny.
It's too soon, and I wasn't ready!
Hey man, I haven't
seen you in a long time!
What happened to you? Did you get
sick?
Hey, Mizuka...
Well...
I'm back.
Let's stay together
forever from now on...