Why is everywhere I
go such a lonely place?
It all looks beautiful to me...
...but if it looks sad to you, it
must be something I don't understand.
People don't exist in these places.
You're right.
I wonder why I am trying to exist
in the world where no one exists.
I want to be in places like crowded
streets or places where everyone
smiles.
I don't know why...
...but these places are brought
into reality from your heart.
You mean, these lonely
places are reflecting my mind?
It's sad, isn't it?
I don't know.
But I think I'm attracted to these
places because of their sorrow...
Where should I go next?
Don't worry. I'll go wherever you go.
You're right, so I should
keep on going forward, right?
Yeah. Keep on going...
One: A Glorious Season, Episode Two
Have we met before?
Hello?
Hello, this is Nagamori.
Um, well...
Hello? Kohei?
Is it you, Kohei?
Hey Nagamori, what's up?
What do you mean "what's up?",
you're the one who called me!
Oh yeah?
Are you okay?
You've been acting strange
since the end of last semester.
Nothing is wrong with me.
You should talk to me if you
have something on your mind.
It's not like that...
I just wanted to hear your voice.
Don't tease me like that.
I'm not lying.
What are you up to?
I told you, I really wanted
to listen to your voice...
Nagamori?
Is it true?
About what you just said...
You don't trust me?
I'm sorry.
It just made me happy...
Are you eating well?
Yeah, Ms. Yuki's vacation
is coming up soon, so...
Call me when you need me, okay?
I know!
You sound like my mom or something.
I'm just worried about you!
Okay, okay!
Having such a trivial
conversation with Nagamori...
...I could feel my
frozen heart melt away.
But I knew that it
wasn't just a premonition.
I knew that something
horrible was about to happen...
Are you still waiting?
You aren't gonna ask me
who I am again, are you?
What do you want?
Do you think I came here to hit on you?
This may not be my business...
...but you'll catch a cold if you
stand out in this cold weather...
First of all, who are you waiting for?
You look so sad...
Sorry. I didn't need to say that...
But I couldn't help it
because you look sad.
This is not my business, so I'll go...
My childhood friend.
I've been waiting for
my childhood friend.
Your childhood friend?
This is the place we said goodbye...
I liked him a lot...
That's why I'm here, waiting for him...
Did you make a promise with him
that you would see each other again?
So, there is no point
to wait for him here.
That might be true...
But you'll still wait for him here?
Satomura...
Hello.
Hey, it's me.
Do you know what's tomorrow?
What?
I knew that you had forgotten...
School starts tomorrow!
Today is the last day
of our winter break.
You have to wake up
early tomorrow morning!
Nagamori...
Hm?
What would you do if
I suddenly disappeared?
Well, I'll talk to your aunt and get
the money back that you owe me!
I'm serious!
Well, why can't you be
serious about your future then?
We have to take the
entrance exams next year.
Forget it, it was a waste
of time to talk to you!
I would probably regret...
I would regret it a lot...
Nagamori...
Well, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Don't stay up too late.
Good night.
Regrets...
I was really surprised!
Hey, tell me what you
know about Satomura.
Well, she is kinda cute...
I'm not asking about that...
Oh, I see...
I didn't know that
Satomura was your type.
Huh?
It's not going to be easy.
She is very popular, you know?
What do you mean?
Just what I said...
You mean she is popular among guys?
I don't know about her
personality but she looks gorgeous.
I wasn't...
But from what I heard, she
doesn't like men at all.
A lot of men were heart-broken by
her icy attitude and cruel words...
Damn it!
So you've been dumped
by her before too, huh?
What's up, Satomura?
Do you mind if I join you?
I'm done.
Wait a minute! You still had food left!
I'm full.
It's not good to leave your food.
It is said that a lot of
spirits live within rice...
...and they will cast spells
on you if you disgrace the rice.
My lunch was sandwiches.
I'm sure sandwiches
have their own spirits!
No, they don't.
That's cold.
Hey, are you going home now?
Me too.
So what?
What a coincidence to see you
here, so I thought I would say hi.
And?
Well, that's all I wanted to do...
Do you want to tell me anything else?
Um, no, I don't...
Me, neither.
Let's see which one is more stubborn!
You look like I'm bothering you.
You are bothering me.
Well I don't mind if you ignore me.
Oh, this waffle with red
bean sauce is spectacular!
That's black bean sauce.
Why you are covering your ears?
My brain will leak
from my ears if I don't.
My friend eats rice and wheat
noodles at the same time!
Not funny, huh?
Not at all.
Damn!
Hey Akane!
It's been a while!
You haven't called me in
ages, I was worried about you.
I'm glad that you look good!
Yeah.
I'll call you soon.
Let's go shopping
together sometime, okay?
Sure...
See ya!
Is she your friend?
Not really.
She is not my friend.
Your lunchbox looks cute.
This doesn't suit me, right?
I never said that.
Satomura, don't you think
it's a little cold out here?
No.
I'm freezing my butt here.
Then why don't you go
back to the classroom then?
You're cold too, aren't you?
Not really.
I don't think you're being honest.
You are wrong.
You look like you're shivering, though.
No, I'm not.
If you say so...
Aren't you cold?
No.
Has anybody seen Satomura?
No, I haven't seen her today...
That's strange, her family told me
that she's already left her house.
Is she...
Satomura, you'll catch a cold.
You should listen to
my advice sometimes.
You really don't need to
wait for someone like this...
This is my everything.
This is all I can do.
I was happy.
My days were simple and
nothing was exciting...
...but I was satisfied with
such an ordinary life...
...because I had my
childhood friends by my side.
Shiiko, him, and myself.
I thought that he was happy too.
I thought that it would
last forever, but...
Shiiko was the first
one to forget about him.
Then other classmates started
forgetting about him...
It was a rainy day like
today, he suddenly disappeared.
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting for
my childhood friend.
I couldn't do anything but wait.
After he disappeared, the memory of
him inside me started fading away...
But I just couldn't...
But I didn't want to
let these memories go.
So I tried to think
about him all the time.
I thought that he might come
back if I don't forget about him.
But...
Satomura!
Satomura, are you all right?
Akane!
I'm glad that you came back.
Please don't leave me...
Don't leave me alone again...
Orihara...
Call me Kohei.
Where am I now?
My aunt made phone calls
to school and your parents.
Don't worry.
She told them that you didn't feel well.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
When I changed your clothes...
Oh, don't worry, my
aunt changed you, so...
I didn't see anything.
It would be nicer if you fainted near
my house on a sunny day next time!
Okay.
I'll bring something hot to drink.
Uh...
Well, Kohei...
Thank you.
No problem.
It's nice and hot...
You'd better have a sleep
again after you drink that.
Hey, wait a minute!
Why are you giving me a look like that?
My aunt is downstairs.
Do you want me to call her up here?
I was just kidding.
You look cuter when you're smiling.
Don't tease me!
You're blushing.
It's because I'm having this hot drink!
Whatever.
When someone gives you a
compliment, just say thank you.
Come on, say it.
Thank you.
Well, I'll go downstairs and watch TV.
Oh, one more thing, Akane.
You were dumped.
You should forget about him.
Okay.
Wait, Akane!
Yes?
It's Saturday today.
Do you wanna go on a date with me?
I don't.
Come on, we once slept
in the same bed...
Don't say it like that,
there are other people around.
Besides, I just took a nap in your bed!
Let's meet at the park at 3:00 p.m.
I told you, no.
Are you sure that you
don't wanna go out with me?
Good bye.
Well, I'll be waiting for you anyway!
Don't worry.
If you don't show up, I'll just take
a walk around the park by myself.
What a beautiful day...
Can we still do things like lying down
on the grass and feeling the breeze?
Of course, you can.
I like looking at big clouds in the sky.
Then do it.
This is your journey, you
can do whatever you want.
But how can I do that?
I'm always outside of the world...
It may still be difficult for you...
...but I can feel the
breeze and smell the grass...
Teach me how to do it.
Okay, I'll teach you...
She goes behind my back, and
holds me with both arms.
Can you see the clouds?
Yes, I can.
They're moving slowly, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Do you know what's moving those
clouds?
Wind.
Yes, wind.
The wind blows and moves
clouds to the end of this world.
I noticed the smell of grass.
The smell is carried by wind.
I can feel the breeze now.
Good.
Would you hold me for a little longer?
Sure.
I wanted to know her real feelings...
Akane, you came!
You wanted me to come, didn't you?
You wanted to come, didn't you?
I just brought you an umbrella.
It's a beautiful, sunny day, though.
My aunt is out now.
Really?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you think I brought you
here to do something to you?
I didn't say anything...
Where did my aunt go?
I know.
What?
I know that you are not a bad person.
If you say it like that,
it makes me want to do it.
What?
I want to kiss you.
No...
I'm kidding!
What?
Kohei, you're so mean!
I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to hurt your feelings...
That was not a joke.
Are you okay, Akane?
I wouldn't do it if I didn't want to do.
Akane, do you feel embarrassed?
Yes, I do...
...I can't even think...
Oh no, don't touch it...
But you're already wet like this...
Oh no...
Turn around.
No, Kohei...
I feel so strange...
I feel so hot down there...
You look so beautiful, Akane...
Are you ready?
Yes...
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Please be gentle...
No, Kohei...
It hurts.
Akane!
Kohei!
I feel you, I feel you inside of me.
Kohei, I feel so good!
Kohei! It feels good!
Akane!
Kohei!
I'm coming...
Kohei...
I'm going to come with you!
What's wrong?
Nothing...
You looked so scared just now.
I had a nightmare...
I'm fine, as long as Akane is with me...
As long as you stay with me...
It rained a lot this year...
Kohei, are you listening?
What? Yeah...
How can you be so
absent-minded in the morning...
Sorry, Nagamori...
Would you go ahead by yourself?
Wait! Kohei!
It's the same...
Kohei...
What's gotten into you?
Why did you start running suddenly?
Hey, Mizuka...
Is something wrong, Kohei?
You never called me by my first name...
Mizuka, will you remember
me until the last moment?
What?
No, just forget it...
Kohei...
To be continued...