My name is Reiko Kure.
I'm a detective for the
Tokyo police department.
One day, I rescued a girl at
the scene of a ghastly murder.
She closed her mind obstinately, but...
...I saw my dark past in her eyes.
At the time, I still didn't know
how fateful that meeting would be...
Ema Nozomi...
Soon after, I started to see
suspicious shadows around her.
A nurse and my best
friend were attacked.
Each time, she was
scared by something...
...yet still blaming herself somehow.
What was she scared of?
Why would she do such a thing?
While I was at a loss because I could
neither understand nor help her...
...a mysterious man tried to end her life.
But...
...he was not the real danger
that has been haunting Nozomi.
Nozomi': real fear...
...and her real pain come from
the ogre, the tattoo on her back...
...which is able to come to life.
That's right...
The ogre exists...
The ogre on her back really exists.
I know it's hard to believe.
But I was raped by the ogre.
Please, sit down here.
Are you ready?
Yes...
Does it hurt?
I' m okay.
You have some lacerations...
I'll treat it for now.
We'll have to wait for
the result of the blood test.
How about semen?
Huh?
Is there any left?
I took care of it.
Do you think...
---"m Pregnant'?
Doctors can never be one
hundred percent sure.
That's true...
Thank you.
All I'm saying is that we
have to wait for the result.
Please let me know if something
happens, I'll be glad to help you.
I appreciate your concern, Mr. Makabe.
Would you mind sending the
semen sample to the crime lab?
Who was it?
Did you know him?
An ogre...
I haven't told anyone
about that night yet.
I thought no one would believe it.
I was raped by...
...the tattoo of an ogre.
There you are.
Mr. Tagami.
How are things?
Okay-
She's not awake yet, but
she's passed the critical stage.
Not about Yasuko...
About you.
Huh?
The knife that the suspect left behind...
...matched the weapon
from the skinning case.
Really?
Yes .
It's not an ordinary knife.
It's been designed for skinning.
Psychotic criminal...
Where is Nozomi Ema now?
She should be back at the church.
She is in danger.
He was after the tattoo on
her back from the beginning.
She's not here.
What's the matter?
Nozomi...
I know now that it was the only way
she felt she could show her appreciation.
She didn't want to
hurt anybody anymore.
No, please...
Flo!
Don't come out.
Please, don't come out...
I'll give myself to you, so...
Don't come out, please...
Please...
Don't come out!
Don't stop now!
Flo!
What are you doing, no!
Shut up!
If you scream, you'll get hurt.
Be quiet.
Don't come any closer.
Leave me alone!
What are you talking about?
You like touching yourself, don't you?
No!
Move your damn hands!
Good...
You want me to do this, don't you?
See, you're wet...
Don't you feel good?
Don't...
Please...
Don't you like it?
No...
Please...
Leave me alone.
Are you sure, you're
loving this, aren't you?
I'll make you feel much better!
Take your clothes off!
W-What the...
W-Why do you have a tattoo like that?
For your own sake...
Run away now.
I like it.
What a great view.
We're gonna have fun!
No, stop it!
Are you ready?
There...
No, stop it!
Hey, he!!!
W-What?
Come on, who did this to you?
Not now, he's in a very bad condition.
Ask him later.
Come on, please...
Who did this to you?
O-O...
What?
What are you doing, officer?
I feel sick.
After the skinning case,
it's a stabbing case.
SQ?
It's an ogre.
He said an ogre did it...
He probably saw an ogre
when he crossed the River Styx.
Let's go.
We'll lose face if we don't
solve these crimes soon...
Yes...
Nozomi...
Was that you?
Get out!
You can't run away naked, can you?
I' m sorry.
It's not your fault.
The doctor says if I continue physical
therapy, I will be able to walk again.
Good...
Are you all right?
I can't take a break until I find her.
You still can't forget about
what happened ten years ago?
Of course not.
If it didn't happen...
...I wouldn't have become...
...a detective.
Is this about revenge?
I wonder if an unwanted
life is still important...
Excuse me.
Huh?
May I ask you some questions?
Wait, open the door!
Open the door!
Shit...
O-Ouch...
All right!
I'm just holding it for my friend.
What are you talking about?
M-Marijuana, marijuana!
Marijuana?
We just wanted to ask you some
questions, why did you try to run?
You're so stupid.
Do you know this girl?
She has a tattoo of
an ogre on her back.
She's got some balls, huh?
She looks young too.
By the way, how about you?
I bet a fairy would look
beautiful on your back.
Flo!
Tattoos are only for lowlifes like you.
I'm not asking you.
I have one more question.
Do you know a tattoo
artist who can give life to a tattoo?
Life?
Kure?
His tattoos comes out from the
skin and moving as if they are alive...
...as if the have souls, and the person
with the tattoo has no control over it.
What are you talking about?
Tell me.
It's "Garyo Tensei."
What?
It's a story about a painted dragon.
I know that story, so?
Long ago, a famous painter drew a
dragon, and when he painted eyes on it...
...the dragon came to life
and went up into the sky.
I've heard that there is a tattoo
artist who gives life to his tattoos.
Nonsense.
It's just a myth.
Tell me...
...the name of the tattoo artist.
I think it was...
...Horioni.
If you want to kill me, do it now,
I have a splitting headache.
I won't kill you.
You are mine.
It's so beautiful.
It's so delicate and realistic...
It is living art...
This tattoo of Horioni's...
Horioni?
Horioni': tattoos are the best.
He's the only one in the world
who can draw a living tattoo.
Do you know him?
Do I know him?
I'm a student of Horioni.
This place used to be Horioni': studio.
Now, I'm renting here.
Where is he?
Let me see him!
The drugs should be working by now...
You took a tranquilizer
they use to mate horses.
If things go wrong, you might go mad.
Let yourself enjoy the
pleasant sensations...
...and show me the ogre.
You'll never make me...
...feel good.
What?
I'd rather die that let you
keep touching me like that.
Bitch!
I can kill you...
...whenever I want!
Look!
Aren't these beautiful?
This is my collection.
I'll add yours to these eventually.
You won't be able to scream,
and you'll live in my studio forever.
If you like tattoos so much,
why don't you get one?
Isn't it beautiful?
This is also by Horioni.
It's incomplete...
My body refused.
The swelling from the
needle lasted for three months.
Then Horioni left me.
But, I couldn't give up.
If I can't have a tattoo on my body,
I'll draw a better tattoo than Horioni's.
And this is what you came up with?
Examining the real ones is the
best way to study on my own.
I'll ask you again...
Show me the ogre, for my art.
An?
You don't know...
I lost my parents
because of this ogre...
I won't show it to you...
I'd rather die than show you my ogre!
You bitch!
It's awful...
It's inhuman...
That's...
Nozomi!
Are you okay?
Mr. Tagami?
Mr. Tagami!
Don't move.
Oh, it's you.
You are...
He'll live if he gets help right now.
Don't...
Don't do it!
I'll tell you what to do.
Good, next, your underwear.
What's wrong, take it off.
Yes...
Kneel down and put it on.
You want to help her, right?
Your partner needs to be
treated soon or he'll die.
Well?
Yes .
Please...
Please help her and Mr. Tagami.
Help them...
Please...
Oh no!
You awake?
Hey!
Why are you here?
Look, she's going
to get fucked for you.
Lick it.
What's wrong?
Beg for forgiveness.
Apologize for disturbing my art.
Look at me and say you're sorry!
Stupid...
That's why I left you,
why did you come here?
You have nothing to do with me!
Yes, I do...
Hey, raise your hips higher.
It's not only your problem anymore...
No, stop it!
Please, stop it.
Shut up!
Flo!
It's all inside.
Look, she's your scapegoat.
Don't look away or I'll kill her!
Okay, that's good.
Please, don't...
No...
I said not to look away!
Some detective, isn't she?
She's thrusting her hips by herself.
Do you like your gun so much, huh?
Stop it, please!
Take it out, please...
Take it out!
Stop it, she's gonna die!
She gives her life for you...
I'll do whatever I want.
Good...
The most beautiful
moment is when people die.
Show me the moment!
No, stop it!
Show me...
Show me the moment of death!
Flo!
I've taken the bullets out.
She passed out...
...or did she come?
L-Is this...
T-This is the ogre!
It's coming alive!
Wonderful!
It's Horioni's...
Show me the...
Show me the moment!
I told you to leave me alone.
I'm sorry but I can't stay with you.
I have to go look for someone.
Let go.
My period is late...
It's your baby...
It can't be!
I'll go with you and find the man
who drew the ogre on your back.
It's not only your problem anymore...
May I help you?
Are you looking for Horioni?
W-Who are you?
Leave Horioni alone.