A student like you is a
disgrace to the name of Horioni.
You will never draw another tattoo.
N-No!
Please don't!
Flo!
Dear!
Wake up!
Oh Dear, no, please...
To tell the truth,
I didn't know why but...
...I was very calm.
When I heard that detective
Enokido had been attacked...
...I wasn't surprised, but I thought
it had been only a matter of time...
And my thoughts were confirmed...
...when I heard that the
weapon was a needle for...
...carving tattoos.
I'm home.
We are now...
...becoming involved with something...
...something extremely horrifying.
Something hidden from the public eye...
Nozomi!
Help me...
The secret of the living tattoo...
Slop!
Please don't hurt her anymore!
No...
No, don't...
Flo!
Wait.
If you want it so bad, you can have me.
So...
Please leave Nozomi alone.
I'm coming...
I' m sorry.
It's okay.
It's my duty to protect you.
And...
...I don't mind being with you.
Look, I'm not...
Um, I'm not a lesbian, okay?
I'm kidding.
Forget it.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yes .
Is that morning sickness?
It's nothing.
Have you gone to the hospital yet?
Why?
I want you to get rid of it!
That's a mean thing to say,
it's your baby, after all.
No, it's not!
It's the ogre's!
I don't care...
If the baby has the will to be born...
...I'll give birth to it.
But...
I don't care if
something happens to me.
Come over here.
Look at that.
There.
Over there.
That's him.
He's probably in some kind of shock.
He's completely shut away.
He cannot kill people anymore,
much less draw tattoos.
His left arm was severed...
...and the nerves in his right
arm are severely damaged.
You know, like your boss...
This is the same case
as detective Enokido's...
There is a puncture wound
from a needle on his arm.
It's a warning...
Someone wants us
to stop searching...
I'm worried about you.
Why haven't you come for a checkup?
It's better to take care of this soon.
She said the same thing.
Who?
I would like to start...
Are you ready?
Scared?
I' m okay.
This is the only way I can help you.
Look over here!
This is Horioni':
tattoo, the one you wanted!
You wanted to have this, right?
What's wrong, Kure?
Are you okay?
We're okay.
Don't worry.
Take a good look!
And try to remember!
Who did this to you?
Who took your tattoo from you?
It's Horioni, isn't it?
D-Damn you...
I don't care if you're Horioni': woman.
I'll make you pay for this!
Jun Ando!
I'll make you pay...
I'll make you pay for my arm!
Jun!
Jun Ando...
Clumsy bitch!
How many times do I have to
tell you not to use your teeth?
Mm sorry, rm Sorry
I don't need a slow learner like you.
BYE bye.
Please forgive me, please!
Detective?
Bring him here.
Let's all have some fun.
Jun Ando'?
I don't know.
I've heard she is the lover of
a tattoo artist called Horioni...
No girls have a tattoos in my place.
Girls like that are usually
hanging around the harbor.
Thank you.
Hey, you!
You're cute, female
customers are welcome, too.
Wanna come in?
Maybe next time.
Why didn't that bother you?
I'm used to it.
So, it is true...
Huh?
You said that you don't dislike
girls the other day, remember?
You have experience, right?
I was raped.
Just ten years ago...
It was awful.
I trusted no one for a while.
I was scared to be in
public, so I shut myself away.
Then somebody extended
a helping hand to me...
She was my best friend.
She taught me...
...the joy of being loved by someone.
I was happy-
I'm not the like you.
I can't get over it yet.
I can't love people yet.
I'm dirty now...
I don't have the right
to be loved by anybody.
That's not true.
I'll interview a few more people, so...
...just wait here.
Okay...
Oh no!
Damn...
You bitch...
What do you want?
Shut up!
You're under arrest for
interfering with a police investigation!
Not bad...
...Miss Detective.
My boss wants to see you.
Would you come with us?
Welcome, Miss Detective.
You are...
You are the boss?
I'm pretty surprised myself.
I've heard that a detective was
snooping around about Horioni, so...
...I thought it would be some old man.
But, who knew it was
a beautiful woman?
You know about Horioni.
Why won't people leave us alone?
He has done nothing wrong.
Tell me!
Where is Horioni?
Are you Jun Ando?
Are you?
Be quiet!
Lick it.
If you lick my foot, I'll tell you.
Don't make me laugh!
Don't use your teeth.
Slowly, and use your tongue...
Not satisfied with my toe, huh?
Someone, make her feel better.
Flo!
I've warned you...
...not to look for Horioni.
You people are like ants...
...following the scent of food.
I have to punish you.
Right?
What's that?
Who the hell are you?
L-it can't be...
Is this...
What the fuck is that?
N-Nozomi...
Please, go now!
Why...
Why is that here?
Why?
Horioni': work...
I won't forgive you!
I will never forgive you!
Hey...
What's wrong, Kure?
What happened?
Jun Ando.
She's Horioni': lover.
What?
She attacked detective Enokido.
Please go arrest her immediately!
Where's the investigative section?
What is this in regard to?
H-Hey!
Who are you?
What's that?
I'll go.
Wait, hey!
Slop!
Wait!
S-S-Stop!
W-What the...
H-Hey!
You!
What are you doing here?
Don't worry, I'm here...
Mr. Tagami?
No more hide-and-seek.
Now, it's my turn to play.
Jun Ando...
Yes...
I'm Jun Ando.
Oh no, you too...
That's right.
I have one of Horioni':
tattoos, just like you.
I was chosen to be
the canvas for Horioni...
My skin is one in a million.
I'm Horioni': masterpiece!
Nozomi!
No...
Let go of me!
Yes, it's Horioni': work.
Call your ogre, and
show it to me again!
What's wrong, show it to me.
Or is it not worth showing to me?
He's coming.
Who could compare me
to this puny creature?
Don't make me laugh!
Flo!
Slop it!
Don't hurt her, please!
Shut up!
Look at her...
You can't have your ogre
come out and help her anymore.
You useless piece of shit.
Besides...
...no matter what happens to you,
the ogre can't save you either.
Flo!
Slop it!
Are you a virgin?
I see...
Don't worry, I'll teach you.
No!
Yes !
Please stop it!
I'll do it...
I'll do anything you want.
So, please don't hurt her!
Okay then.
Yes...
Put both in by yourself.
What's wrong?
Do it now!
She's thrusting her hips by herself!
Whore!
Feels good, huh?
Say you feel good!
Y-Yes, I feel good...
Oh?
I guess you're not
interested in foreplay.
Well then...
Let's do something really fun!
N-No!
Don't, please, stop it!
Please, don't!
Flo!
Why are you doing this?
It's quite a show, isn't it?
Please make them stop.
She's pregnant!
Oh really?
Well then...
Thrust harder!
Don't!
My baby...
You'll kill my baby!
How awful...
You're evil, you're not a human being!
You're a demon wearing
the skin of human!
Don't talk fresh!
You're the monster who
carries that pitiful ogre on your back!
But, you're still my friend, we
both wear the art of Horioni.
We should get along well.
Are you ready?
That hurts!
No...
Let's have some fun together!
Flo!
No...
Please don't...
How is it?
Don't you feel good?
Come if you want to.
It hurts...
Stop it, please...
My baby...
My baby!
Yes...
Oh yes!
Both of you...
Come!
I can tell, you both are enjoying
getting fucked like this, aren't you?
Yes, yes...
Come on, let's come together!
Oh, I'm coming...
...coming...
Come with me...
Oh yes, I'm coming...
Yes !
Nozomi?
Oh God...
N-No...
Flo!
That moment, I lost
something very precious.