Oh, that's good...
You're getting turned on
by being raped, aren't you?
You can come if you want...
Feel it.
Oh yes!
Flo!
Do you have any leads?
How do you feel about this incident?
Twenty-two police officers were
found brutally murdered last night.
The suspect is still at large...
The crime scene is very chaotic...
...with all the police vehicles.
Many believe that some large
underground organization is involved...
The case seems to be a direct
challenge to law enforcement...
The Tokyo Police Department is
putting every available man on this case.
Flo!
Since that day, the ogre on
Nozomi': back never rose again.
He didn't seek blood...
...nor put her in the pain
of shameful pleasure.
Nozomi's mind was
locked in the darkness...
...with the evil mind of the ogre.
The Nozomi I once knew
would not come back to me.
The suspect is an 18 year-old girl.
Are you saying that the girl
killed 22 policemen by herself?
Yes, she did!
But, there are no witnesses...
I saw it!
I see...
Okay then.
Well, you take a rest.
Doctor, please take care of her.
Y-Yes...
She still seems to be
in some sort of shock.
Well, she just had a
miscarriage, I wouldn't blame her.
The police have pride.
Including you, the
victims are all policemen.
They won't rest until
the case is closed.
So don't worry, and
get some rest for a while.
It's doctor's orders, now.
They raped me...
...and took my baby away.
How can I rest?
What are you talking about,
were you going to have the baby?
You don't even know who the father was!
I'm sorry, I said too much.
But...
I know the father.
Nozomi Ema.
What?
I was raped by the ogre on her back.
And I became pregnant...
Wait...
Are you talking about
the tattoo on her back?
It's the truth.
The tattoo would come to life and
come out of her back, running rampant.
And Nozomi is not the only
one who has a living tattoo.
But just like the other cases,
the police will never catch the suspect...
...because everybody believes
that it is some yakuza gang.
What are you talking about,
have you gone mad?
Stop the car!
H-Hey, calm down!
Do you really expect
me to believe that?
Nobody will believe you!
Hey, you!
Excuse me.
When did she come here?
I guess it was about two
o'clock, but you were asleep.
She came to the reception
desk and left those for you...
As I just returned from hell...
I guess you still can't
put it out of your mind.
It's been ten years...
Kure...
Flo!
Hey, lick it!
I'm telling you to lick it all up!
Hey, hey...
What the fuck did you do to him?
They were hospitalized for three months.
Without Mr. Enokido's intervention, it
wouldn't have been a simple self-defense case.
After all that, you're just going to
quit and go back to being a murderer?
I'm sorry...
...but I've already decided.
Nozomi?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Water...
Give me water...
Be careful.
Water...
Give me some water.
Yes, more, lick me more...
Oh good...
Stir harder!
Good, good!
Shimon, give me your dick, please?
Stick it into me as hard as you can.
Please, hurry and fuck me.
Here, yes, until it won't go further...
She's the detective from the other day.
What should we do?
Let's kill her.
Don't disturb me now,
I'm coming soon...
Oh good...
Yes, I'm coming!
Yes !
W-What?
Long time no see.
Did you come here to
catch me by yourself?
Or...
...is it that you can't
forget about my taste...
Stupid bitch!
The police, no, even
the army can't catch me!
I have a guardian
angel that Horioni gave me.
You mean that
disgusting tattoo of yours?
I'm gonna kill you!
I'll give a slow and painful death to
anyone who makes fun of my tattoo!
I'll cover you with shit and dump
you in front of the police station!
No, that's not good enough...
I'll make you suffer before I kill you.
Where is the girl who was
with you the other day?
What are you going to do to her?
Answer me.
Where is she?
I'll never tell you!
I'll make you tell me...
Where should I start?
Take a look at this.
It was inside of her pocket.
It's a church in
Nakano, I know where it is.
You seem very happy here.
Is she your bitch?
That's not your business!
So it's true!
You are the worst!
Maybe we should all go pray.
Please, forgive us sinful souls...
Mr. Enokido...
Thank you for coming.
What are you doing,
you haven't recovered yet.
Please, help me look for Kure.
She is going to kill the suspect.
What?
She left her resignation,
but she still has a gun.
I have to stop her before
she does something stupid...
I came to talk about the case.
What about it?
I did autopsies on the bodies.
The policemen were not attacked.
They killed each other.
What?
The bullets from the policemen':
bodies were New Nanbu .38 caliber.
One policeman': skin was stuck
under another policeman': fingertip.
It's a sign of a struggle.
Are you sure?
Not only that...
The semen sample I took
after Ms. Kure was raped...
The test results show it's from several
different policemen at the scene.
Kure didn't say anything about that.
She was probably tricked too.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Good evening, sister.
Reiko?
Yasuko, run away!
Can a person who serves God
forsake her friend and run away?
I'll be enjoying you...
...all night!
Mass hypnotism?
Yes, are you familiar with
the running water effect?
It's often used for copperplate prints.
When you stare at a striped
pattern, you get dizzy, right?
If those patterns are combined,
it will look like a moving picture.
Doctor, please get to the point.
Ms. Kure said that the tattoo on the
suspect': back jumped out and raped her.
Of course, that can't happen.
If she saw some kind of
hallucination, then it all makes sense.
Doesn't it?
The tattoo artist who
gives life to his tattoos...
Horioni!
Yasuko, run away!
Hurry!
Please, run!
Don't worry about me, just go!
Yasuko!
No, don't!
No...
slop it!
It effects not only vision...
...but also hearing and smell,
as well as the other senses...
And it made her see the tattoo
come to life from the girl's back.
The policemen were
probably hallucinating too...
And they thought they
were killing the criminals.
Please, stop!
That's terrible...
You may be right.
It makes sense, but...
...there's no proof.
There is.
What?
That case with the gangsters...
it was the same situation as this case.
And that girl was the
only the person alive.
Nozomi Ema!
She's probably at the church right now.
Please stop it!
Let her go!
I'm begging you, please let Yasuko go!
Please leave me alone...
I can't...
No way.
We're gonna fuck you until
your pussy becomes useless.
If you wanna blame
somebody, blame her.
Water...
Give me water.
Nozomi, don't come!
Flo!
Look at the poor girl,
what happened to you?
I fucked you so hard
that you went mad, huh?
But a more horrible
tragedy is about to happen!
Stop it, leave Nozomi alone!
Do you think you are in a
position to ask for anything?
Nozomi...
Shut up!
What is that?
Don't you feel anything?
That's no fun.
You did this to her.
Nozomi...
Are you really a human being?
If I can have fun, I don't
care about anything else.
The whole universe
revolves around me!
I'll kill you!
Are those a detective': words?
I guess I'll have to keep
fucking her until she feels good.
Nozomi...
Not yet, I'll do it more and more!
You really don't feel anything...
I wish you could enjoy this pleasure too.
Well it's time to say goodbye...
No, what are you doing?
Don't kill her!
Nozomi!
Goodbye, Nozomi...
Don't...
Please stop it!
Nozomi!
N-Nozomi?
Don't just stand there, kill her now!
Ogre...
It's the ogre!
No, it can't be...
No, what are you doing?
Flo!
Slop it!
NO, stop!
Stop it, please!
You're a detective, stop her!
I'm sorry, but...
...I'm not a detective anymore.
I guess the universe
doesn't revolve around you!
N-No, help me!
No, don't!
Feels good?
W-What?
You don't need to hide.
You're already so wet...
That hurts!
No, it won't go in any deeper!
Slop!
Flo!
Hear this?
Dirty sound...
I won't forgive you...
But...
...I'll let you come one
last time before you die.
Come!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Goodbye...
Let us through!
This way!
Excuse us.
I'll go check the back door,
please take care of things here.
Let's go.
Reiko kept her promise with me.
The promise that
she'd never try to kill anyone...
...and that she'd take care of herself...
Then she disappeared with Nozomi Ema.
Aren't you going to look for her?
I'm not that insensitive.
Go look for her if you want.
I'm not saying that...
I just want to know the
truth behind the tattoo.
Everybody has a demon inside.
We all try to control it
with the power of reason, don't we?
That's true...
it's likely that the girl's
suppressed emotions...
...erupted because of that tattoo.
Probably...
You would make a good psychiatrist.
Stop it, I'm just a
run-of-the-mill detective...
Please, give it me...
I know it's just a momentary pleasure.
I know this ogre's horn that connects
our relationship may be only an illusion.
I love you, Nozomi.
I'm coming!
But even so...
Please fill me up with your come!
...we'll still look for Horioni.
I'm coming!
I have no regrets.
We finally have our freedom.
Now that we're complete,
we could fly up into the sky...
...just like the painted dragon when it
came to life with the last stroke of the brush.