Just as I thought...
This is what I've been seeking.
Wonderful!
How awful...
Hey, don't step over the dead bodies!
S-Sorry.
Come to think of it, that
was the beginning of it all.
If I didn't work on that case...
...I'd never have quit...
...being a detective.
There are 13 victims.
They're from the same yakuza group.
It's probably a gang war.
Any witnesses?
None.
The restaurant's owner
downstairs reported it.
He discovered blood
dripping from the ceiling.
Were they high or something?
Why?
It's strange that
there are no witnesses.
And a simple fight
wouldn't be so terrible...
How can you be so calm?
I'm not.
Is Kure here?
Yes .
Come here.
A girl?
Yes, we found her at
the scene before you two came.
Can you take care of her?
Yes .
I'm Reiko Kure, from the Shinjuku precinct.
Thank you very much.
You are safe now.
We're going to the hospital.
Do you feel all right?
I'll get you some new clothes.
Tell me anything.
I'll help you as much as I can.
Don't touch me!
I'm sorry, but...
Leave me alone.
Okay, I see...
So, what's her name?
Nozomi Ema...
Mei how private school?
Yes .
A private school in Kyoto.
I remember the uniform.
Yes...
She's about to see a doctor now.
Can you change by yourself?
A female doctor is coming.
Just a moment.
Flo!
What's wrong?
W-What are you, no...
Flo!
She might've been kept
there for a long time...
I'll keep my eye on her for a while.
Please, someone help!
N-No...
No...
What happened?
Get yourself together!
Where is she?
Where is the girl?
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Hey...
Stop.
Slop it!
Hey!
Don't disturb me!
Leave me alone!
T-That is...
Hey, stop m
slop it!
Let go!
Flo!
Let go of me!
Are you okay?
Yes...
Please leave me alone!
Let go of me!
At the time...
...I was really angry.
Hey!
Let's go!
But not at Nozomi Ema...
...at whoever had
done this awful thing to her.
That tattoo of an ogre...
I got some information.
Nozomi Ema has been
missing for three months.
So have her parents...
She's been held captive...
...by those yakuza.
Why do you think that?
She has...
She has the same eyes that I have.
That's why you care so much.
I' m sorry.
Nozomi Ema was...
"hospitalized because
she might hurt others.
What's your opinion?
Do you think she's dangerous?
Could you talk to her?
Anyway, we're in trouble because she's
the only witness and we can't use her.
Cancel her hospitalization!
I think she was nervous
because she had just been rescued.
You want to take responsibility for her?
Yes !
Okay-
We'll start over from
the tattoo and the yakuza.
Yes .
Come on.
I've decided that I'll take
care of you for a while.
You don't want to stay
in a cold room, do you?
I want to help you.
It's not just my job.
I want to know about you...
...as a friend.
You' ll regret it.
No, I won't.
Long time no see, Reiko.
I'm sorry, I'm asking for your help again.
No problem.
Are you Nozomi?
Let me introduce you.
She is the head sister, Yasuko Kurisu.
Nice to meet you.
She'll take good care of you.
How are you?
It's a 20 year-old man who
lived nearby, he was unemployed.
His roommate identified him.
Two days in a row, this is too much...
The skin on his back...
Yes, actually...
I've heard he had a tattoo of
a Japanese demon on his back.
Tattoo?
Coincidence?
Oh no...
Blackout?
What's wrong?
I'm okay, just leave.
Do you feel all right?
Please, leave me alone!
Don't come close!
Don't be scared.
It's just a blackout.
Flo!
W-What?
N-Nozomi...
Stop it...
Oh no!
No...
N-No!
I'm coming!
Die!
Who are you?
I came to take...
...your Ogre!
R-Run!
Flo!
Get off me!
Nozomi, run!
Run!
Get in!
Hold on!
No, stop it!
Don't move!
Shinjuku No. 8 to headquarters...
It's Kure.
I need backup.
We're in South Oui, Shinagawa.
We' re safe now.
Did you get hurt?
I'm fine...
Show me.
What happened?
That man tried to kill you, didn't he?
Do you know why?
Is that...
...the same man?
No...
What?
What's wrong?
No...
No, don't come out...
Don't!
No...
Flo!
No, stop it!
It's your fault.
He always whispers
in my ear from my back...
"More, I want more."
I usually try to keep him
quiet by touching myself...
But...
It's him!
...he gets out of my
body and hurts people.
Yes...
The nurse...
...and those yakuza...
They were attacked by my ogre...
Please...
Don't...
Please, stop it!
Flo!
Don't look at me!
It's your fault.
It's your...
N-No, please don't...
Don't look...
No...
That's why I told you...
...to leave me alone.
I couldn't believe it.
Is it possible?
Can a tattoo be alive?
However...
...my body remembers...
...that the ogre pierced me.
When I think about
her life with the ogre...
...my heart feels...
...such deep sympathy.