So it's been ten years now.
Miyamoto-sama?
My master awaits you.
Please come this way.
Seimei!
So you knew I was coming?
To reunions.
Back in the city, very mysterious
things are still happening.
You mean the body without organs?
How could...
That hasn't been released to the public yet!
Calm yourself.
You intended to tell me about it anyway.
But let's put that aside for now.
I want to deal with a different
sort of issue first.
S-Seimei! Who are these women?
Your work must keep you too busy to
have time for making love to women.
Consider it a little break.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
I didn't come here to...
So, Miyamoto-sama.
My, how amazing.
You're very well endowed, sir.
Seimei...
I didn't come here to mess around!
Right now, the mystery
I'm working on comes...
Don't hold yourself back, Miyamoto-sama.
You're already so firm down here.
Hey, you, can you please stop that.
Oh, Miyamoto-sama,
Hey, you, can you please stop that
I feel so tight down here.
Could you please pet it for me?
Mi-Miyamoto-sama?
Will you please tell me what is
happening to me down there?
You... You're very wet.
More!
Pet me more inside!
Well! Eiko-sama, you're having too much fun.
I want him to pet me as well!
Come, Miyamoto-sama.
Me too.
Miyamoto-sama. Over here, too!
Miyamoto-sama! More! Pet me harder, please!
Miyamoto-sama!
.
Don't give all the attention to Bisho.
Be sure to pet me as well!
Miyamoto-sama!
Miyamoto-sama...
Dammit, Seimei.
Oh! Y-You're so amazing, Miyamoto-sama!
My body's so hot I can't contain myself!
Miyamoto-sama!
I feel as though my insides
are going to burst!
Me too!
Miyamoto-sama!
My old friend Seimei is an onmyouji.
(Onmyouji - a specialist in magic and divination)
Those women were mere shikigami
created by her spiritual powers.
Since they're made from paper
they disappear when wet.
These days, very few people in this
world believe in that sort of thing.
However, one cannot deny...
that some things in this world cannot
be explained by mere science.
(Matsukura Hideko Murder Case)
A murder, huh?
That's right It happened half a year ago.
Matsukura Hideko was the mistress
of the mansion we're about to visit.
She was a widow in her thirties.
Ah, yes. I wouldn't recommend looking
at the picture of her body.
Too late. I'm looking at it.
Oh, sorry.
Her organs had been cleanly
removed from her body.
Then they were hung artistically
from the faucets in her house.
And the water from the faucets
washed away all her blood?
Yup. There were no traces of it.
I see.
See what?
Be careful.
Of what?
A-Are you okay, Seimei?
I'm all right
It appears that the other
person is also all right.
I apologize. I accelerated too suddenly.
Are you all right?
Yes, we're fine.
But why would a sober man
like you drive so recklessly?
That's hard for a police officer
like me to swallow.
What are you saying, buddy?
I wouldn't drive while intoxicated,
I swear it! See?
Chuujo Shinnosuke.
He's a common drunk now,
but he used to be a general.
He knew the victim before she was married.
It's possible that he held a grudge
against her for rejecting him.
He's definitely a valid suspect.
One piece, eh?
What?
Is something wrong?
No.
It's nothing.
Pierre Francois.
He's a Frenchman.
He loves Japanese aesthetics,
so he moved into Hideko's mansion.
However, he did nothing but use Hideko
as a model for his paintings.
He was obsessed.
He seemed disturbed about
his own lack of talent.
Inoue Hiroshi.
He wanted to be a writer
but according to those who
have read his manuscripts
he doesn't have a shred of talent
Hideko apparently pitied him for
his difficulties and took him in.
If her sponsorship made him feel pressured to
succeed he might have wanted her to disappear.
Those are the three lovers Hideko took in.
Each of them have their
own motive to kill her.
But I have no proof that any of them did it.
I see.
So?
Who do you think killed her?
Good question.
If I take into consideration the
strange way she was killed,
Pierre makes sense, because
ne sees himself as an artist.
But Inoue's suppressed screams could
have driven him to madness.
Those "suppressed screams" of which you
speak seem to be nothing but noise.
So you think he shouldn't be a suspect?
But then, how do you even know this?
Don't tell me,
Seimei, you already know who...
Hey, tell me.
Looking at the evidence, it seems likely
that her killer is the thrill-seeking type.
It's highly probable that a man like
that would repeat his crime!
Hey, Seimei, I'm begging you!
Please help me!
S-Sorry, Seimei!
Don't be deceived by what's on the surface.
Some things can be seen,
and then there are shadows.
Some are possessed by parasites
and controlled.
The shadows are where those
dangerous beings dwell.
Let me uncover the killers identity.
You must do it this way.
Okay? You understand, right?
Preparations complete!
A young woman's cooch-sake.
This is what men love!
Stop. You're embarrassing me, sir.
Wow, what great breasts! They're so perky!
Wow, what smooth, clear skin!
You're perfect!
Am I really?
Even more so than your late wife?
Of course you are.
Even the most beautiful woman can't
compare to a twenty-year-old.
I'm so glad.
This is directly above Chuujo's room.
And the other two are Pierre and Inoue.
The roof and ceiling are one
continuous piece.
We can see everything from above.
Take a card.
We will place a card over each room.
I thought I could listen in with this.
Do as you wish.
What's wrong?
Just think of me as a toilet.
Let it out fast!
Can't ya give a man a little excitement?
Aw, so you were holding it in.
You had a lot in there.
A young woman's water is sweeter
than any liquor in the world!
Hey! Take a look at this!
Amazing!
Well? Smelly, ain't it!?
That's 'cause I haven't
taken a bath in a while.
What's wrong? You can't take it?
Come on!
How's that?
Hey, now.
Take it all in.
Yeah, good girl.
Try a little harder.
That's good.
Suck it dry.
Oh, amazing. You've got great technique.
I can't hold back anymore!
How's that? Ya like me?
Now I'm gonna push my
balls into your mouth too!
Good! I'm coming now!
That was good.
You're the ideal woman.
I'm bet you said the same
thing to your mistress.
Of course I did.
That was my job.
A man's gotta say that
even if he doesn't mean it.
So you mean to say you tolerated
her but didn't love her?
I'guess so. After all, I'm all
about younger women.
So perhaps you were happy when she died?
Because this mansion...
and her money... became yours?
And did you kill her for those things?
Why you sayin' that?
Nothin' good's happened since she died.
If she'd lived, she'd still be
here to take care of me.
I'm not even sure if I can
stay here much longer.
All the other freeloaders could
be plotting to kick me out.
Beautiful...
A beautiful flower has
bloomed on your breast!
And desiring the sweet nectar of your body,
a butterfly comes to you!
And this is your nectar.
No!
Ah! It's almost as if
a real butterfly is here!
My art has caused your body to metamorphose!
This is what I have truly desired.
How grand!
Real nectar is flowing forth!
My art...
has done this unbelievable thing to you.
Oui, my love.
It pleases me!
You see that art must be understood
not with the mind but with the body!
Please, my love, put more
and more art into my body!
Very well.
W-Wow! Unbelievable...
Believe it.
With this instrument I will enable you
to feel all the art that flows within me.
Its throbbing! Art is throbbing within me!
Exactly.
You will... become a part...
of my art collection.
Then have you ever thought of me the
way you thought of your mistress?
You say the same things as the police!
I do not see any artistry in death.
Art takes life only in the living!
I feel the beauty of myself in her.
So why would I steal that beauty from
her and display it around the house?
I could never do that!
I feel the same way about you.
Pardon me, my love. I mistrusted you.
I'd be honored to join your art collection!
Oui, Mademoiselle.
The only one left is Inoue.
So it seems.
Amazing!
I-I've never felt anything
like this before.
I'm already finished.
This is the fourth time.
I-I wonder why you feel so much?
I haven't come yet.
Put it back in.
You are welcome to everything in my body.
I know everything.
I know where you want to be touched,
and how you want to be moved.
I know.
How is that possible?
I'm both male and female.
That's why I know how to
give you what you want.
A hermaphrodite!
Hermaphrodite?
What's a hermaphrodite?
Half and-half.
He has both male and female sexual organs.
And the devil has already
begun to move inside of him.
Don't keep it all to yourself.
Stick it in me too.
O-Okay!
Move it.
And keep it in.
Okay.
At last I feel it.
Don't come yet. Hideko wasn't like that.
What happened?
She got too wet.
She almost returned to paper
form before his eyes.
So we failed?
He is the most suspicious of them all.
But I still need solid proof.
Then we have no choice.
I only use this as a last resort.
Did she get scared...
and run away?
I'm waiting for you at the
fountain in the back garden.
Love, Gozonji.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm counting on you.
Your mistress was sliced up and
hanged from this fountain?
Who the hell are you? Who sent you?
Your late mistress used to employ me.
Two weeks ago, I received
a letter from her. She said,
"I can't forget you, and
I want you to come back."
But then she was murdered.
Well, isn't that a shame?
She also wrote about you.
"There's a demon seed here
so be careful."
So Hideko sent you to investigate, huh?
Good girl.
First off, how about we taste each other?
Sounds great.
That's right.
Down there too.
Did Hideko tell you?
Don't get too worked up from this.
I haven't felt much pleasure yet on my end.
I understand. Allow me to rectify that.
That's the way Hideko would behave.
S-Seimei!
I think it's about time I had some fun, too.
Miyamoto...
Leave now!
You must leave now!
S-Sorry!
I didn't intend to spy on you during
such an intimate moment.
Not that! Go to the fountain!
The demon is coming out!
Good. It's about time now...
Time for me to bury my
evil seed inside of you.
Here I come!
Wh-What the hell is this?
That won't work on him! Move it!
Seimen!
Wh-What's going on, Seimei? Are you okay?
Seimei!
Wake up, Seimei!