Date General Hospital
The victim is Date Sojiro, age 52.
He is the Chief of Medicine
at this hospital.
The head nurse found him.
She has a spare key to this room.
Because the windows
have latches and curtains,
we can think of this as a locked room.
And the cause of death was... heart failure?
Apparently so.
Though the records indicate he
didn't have a heart condition,
and his hair was still pitch-black.
Something wrong?
No. Itis nothing.
For now we're guessing that he saw or experienced
something so shocking, that he had a heart attack.
Yes. We believe so.
Still, he could have been poisoned.
We won't know until after the autopsy.
Good point.
And where are the two nurses?
In the morgue.
There's just one.
What's that about?
Take off the shroud.
Pact 2
S-Seimei?
Hey there!
So you're the detective guy? Such fun!
Wh-Who are you?
Me-ya? My name's Byakko. Nice to meet'cha.
Just for the record! I wasnt'spying on her.
I have some information
that I want to give her.
So don't jump to conclusions.
It's a light beer! Want some?
It's really popular these days.
No, thanks.
Really? But it's so yummy.
I'm on duty. I'd be crazy to drink alcohol.
Never mind that. Will you
fetch Seimei for me?
Well, let's forget about that for
now and continue spying.
What?
Hey! What's the big id
They can't hear ya down there.
Just shut up and watch.
I don't get it
Why are two women doing that to each other?
They're just having a little
fun in their spare time.
But damn, that Suzaku is such a slut.
Your eyes are staring in disapproval,
but your body sure likes it.
Hey, what are you doing? Cut it out!
Stop fighting it.
What you want is right before
your eyes. Just watch it.
Don't worry, I wont tell Seimei.
Damn, you're big.
It looks like cream, but it
tastes completely different.
What cha doin' there?
Seimei will be out soon. We're leavin'.
What the hell is going on?
Have they been autopsied?
Why are you avoiding my eye?
I'm feeling odd. Don't mind me.
So what do you think about this case?
Good question.
If you asked me here to see if demons
were involved, you must not know.
Yeah.
This case is too bizarre to
be the work of a human.
The Chief of Medicine was
alone in a locked room.
He received a shock that
turned his hair white and died.
Both nurses were sliced in
half and then sewn together.
The other halves haven't been found yet.
And I can't forget what you told me.
Demons are everywhere,
wriggling around like worms.
For starters, I've interviewed
everyone at the hospital.
Seimei...
I've called you here to help me,
because I believe that only
you can solve this mystery.
I know that this will put
you in danger again.
To be honest I almost don't want
you to help because of that.
Demons like that are not my enemies.
So don't worry.
What the hell are you saying?
You almost fainted that day,
and you could've died
if I hadn't been there!
Is that how you remember it?
Why do you keep saying things
that are easily misinterpreted?
I don't understand you.
Miyamoto.
What is it?
Actually, that was...
Yo! Whassup?
Jeez, what's with the long, secretive faces?
What'cha think of my nurse's outfit?
I made sure to hide my ears and tail.
This should work just fine, right?
You have some nerve showing your
ugly face to me again, you worm.
Because of your clumsy work I got
stuck in this boring place for hours!
What a sickening worm.
Funai-san! Leave him alone!
Let him go!
Funai Taibo.
He's the new CEO of Funai Co.
Several of his trade rivals have died
mysteriously making him my prime suspect.
He's a very disreputable man.
As a result of a train accident yesterday
he's currently a patient at this hospital.
Funai-san!
He's under observation
in the psychiatric ward.
He won't bother you here anymore.
So calm down already! Be still!
Anzai Makoto.
He was the driver in the
aforementioned train accident.
The accident happened because he
suddenly jumped out of his seat.
He was brought in with a
severe case of dementia.
Just as I thought. You're insane!
Go get locked up and don't come out again.
Taki-san.
Its about time to return to your room.
Taki Mariko.
She tried to commit suicide many times with
her husband, but she always survived.
This has put her family deeply in debt.
Others have nicknamed her
"Mrs. Double Suicide",
but we think the whole
suicide bit was a fake.
After the fourth suicide
failed, she was admitted here.
So you're saying...
that many people capable of committing these
murders happen to be here simultaneously.
Exactly.
And the one I find most suspicious is Funai.
In the train accident everyone
near him died instantly,
but he mysteriously survived
with just light injuries.
That could mean there's a demon inside him.
That would explain everything.
While that might be true...
What?
You sound unconvinced.
No. Its just that...
I am still unclear as to why you are
suddenly so interested in demons.
I feel I'm in danger.
I sometimes wonder if a demon
might be trying to control me.
Or perhaps you are controlling me?
You could say that.
These are the only things I can control.
You want to use them, don't you?
Yeah.
So, Funai-san!
Here's your water.
Take your time, stay still,
and have a nice drink.
Wh-What are you doing?
What am I doing? I think
you know what I'm doing.
No! Please stop this! I'm calling for help.
Don't go!
Gotcha!
No!
Mop it! Let me go!
Now, now, that makes me
not want to stop even more.
She's really putting up a fight.
I wonder if she's okay.
She's a shikigami programmed
to act out his fantasy.
Of course she's okay.
Why are you here?
Because Seimei is busy meditating.
Ignore what doesn't concern you.
Concentrate on your own job.
You're so soft. I love young women for that.
I'll bet my son would like to have you
after I'm done, don't you think?
Okay.
Come on. Open your mouth.
Take it in deep, or you'll be sorry.
Good. Good girl.
That's good. Keep it up.
Get it all the way in.
Good.
Oh, your juices are so thick.
Your pussy is crying tears of joy over this.
That hurts. Please stop.
Shut up!
If you scream, I'll stick this
all the way up to your throat.
Got it?
Come on, face me.
Come closer to me.
There you go. Go on.
This money is for you.
There. You like it don't you?
What do you think?
Yes, I like it
Oh, that's very good.
Don't!
Shut up!
No!
Hang in there until it burns!
Too bad about yesterday.
You didn't get a lead.
I had no choice.
If I hadn't intervened, the shikigami would
have turned to paper and burned up.
Maybe we took things a
little too far with that one.
Horrible news!
Funai was murdered!
I thought I smelled blood so I went in.
The door was locked.
The nurse's body disappeared!?
This might be a bit dangerous,
but I'm glad you're helping.
Thanks.
I'm sure Miyamoto had a reason
for asking Seimei to do this.
Please tell me. Why do you
keep trying to kill yoursel?
The police don't trust you.
But if you just tell them the truth,
they might help you.
Yes. Stick your tongue out more.
I understand you.
Even though you're ill,
you're still a good person.
You just like to be here because it's safe.
Let the doctors and nurses...
take care of you.
Wow.
You're already so hard.
See? That is a normal healthy reaction.
But... you seem to be in pain,
like someone has taken over your mind.
I will release you from that now.
I cant stand it!
Wow!
I can't go on!
Don't you want to touch them?
You may touch them.
If you want to touch them...
I... I saw it. I saw it. I saw the demon.
But no one believes me!
It was standing on the
tracks and glaring at me!
That's why I...
I believe you! I do
believe you! So please...
I-I mustn't.
Why are you doing this?
Because I want to get to know you.
This is the best way to
get to know each other.
See? I'm making you wet.
I can tell you don't mind.
Aren't you lonely?
I-I don't know what you mean.
You can't lie to me.
All the men you loved so dearly are dead.
Then, why don't we see what
it's like to love a woman?
Our lips are soft.
Our skin is beautiful.
Come.
Suck mine, too.
It's a beauty that no man has.
Good.
Let's do even better things.
Next is this.
You're so wet! It tickles!
I cant.. Stop it, please!
We can't stop. We've come this far.
We both need to be satisfied.
Wh-What's this?
Mariko-san?
What is this? What's going on?
Nurse, this is how I show my love.
I'm showing my love to you,
just like I showed my love to the others!
Let's all go into the water together!
Darling! I want to go with you!
But I... But I...
If only... If only I didn't
have this cursed body!
I could have stayed with him. Why me?
Why?
Are you going to sleep all night?
I know you've been exchanged. Show yourself.
Aw, shit. Ya got me.
It's the sort of plan that
a woman would create,
though I had hoped she would do it herself.
Apparently I underestimated her.
You think you're tough?
Well you ain't fought the likes of me yet.
You hid my prey.
As punishment I will feast
on you in her place.
But before that..
Seimei!
I think I'm ready to cum.
Just a little more.
Stay still. Otherwise,
your head will fall off.
I have no other way to relax!
Seimei!
Wait! Seimei!
Resistance is futile.
You cannot escape my shrine.
I shall now deliver the final blow!
I'm amazed that there was
a shrine to her in this city.
Thanks to that Byakkos powers
were increased tenfold.
Yeah.
What is it?
What do you mean?
You keep stopping yourself
from saying something.
No.
It's just that I wanted to hear what
you started to tell me yesterday.
If you don't want to tell me, that's okay.
As part of being a sorceress,
you must suppress all five senses in order
to link your spirit with a shikigami.
You know what I'm implying.
So..
Your body still can't merge with a man?
Exactly.
So that's why...
Don't you want to change?
But I really like it.
It makes me all brave and strong!
Really?
If you hate it that much, I'll change
back when we get home.
But I can wear it until then, right?
No. That's not it!
That's not the demon I saw!
That wasn't the demon I saw!
What's wrong
Nothing. I'm just hearing things.
It's an airplane!
This world is full of machines now.