Alllllllright!
I present you the Maid team!
Have you finished all the preparations?
Everything is ready, Master!
These new clothes are quite amusing.
Although I prefer my black clothes.
How do they look..? Master...
Well this isn't the first time you've seen me in these clothes.
So it might look a bit plain in my case.
I think you look fine.
Anyways we should be heading out to the beach soon.
Um...
The beach?
Yes.
The beach.
Beach.
The beach, huh.
Come here all of you.
Yes~
Welcome!
Please come this way.
Here's your Iced Coffee, I'm sorry for the wait.
Sorry for making you wait!
Thank you very much.
The Yakisoba is ready!
Yes!
It took a bit.
Thank you for waiting.
Yunis...
You came to the beach as well?
I just decided to go somewhere and ended up here.
Are you working here now?
Yes..
Inis' Yakisoba is very good here.
I didn't come here to eat!
Yunis...
That was an amazing stomach sound.
It wasn't me.
It was.. It was this..
Oh, it was Mochi.
However we both,
That's because coming to the beach and eating Yakisoba.
Wait a second!
That's not what we came here to do!
Oh..?
Yunis.. Welcome...
Onee-sama! There you are!
You're here as well?
Churi...
My name is..
Nakata, Churi.
I wasn't asking for your name.
Well, Shiraha likes to act that way.
That's not the point.
Yunis...
Today your breast's somehow seem bigger.
Did you do something..?
You shouldn't touch me like that.
That's right.
Is my food ready yet?
Yes...
Here's your Ramen.
Come get it before it gets cold.
Yes!
This is bad!
Why did even bring them here...
I thought it would be a good thing to bring them here to do some work.
I... am their master after all.
Master!~
What is it?
Do you need something?
Yes!
Can I ask something of you, Master?
I guess.
As long as it's nothing too bad.
Master..
May I sit beside you?
Yeah.
You sure seem happy.
I'm still getting used to being here, but after today I think it will be fine.
I see.
However, I don't look great in a swimsuit.
Onee-chan has a lot more 'Boin Boin's  to show off.
However my chest is still like this.
It's not like those things matter when you're a maid.
What do you mean by that?
Maid's are...
Us maids.. we have to serve the master.
Even when it comes to this, right?
Akari!
Akari is ready to help the master with this too.
Wait Akari, you shouldn't do that so fast.
Yes, you're right I shouldn't start there.
I should use this method instead.
That's not what I mean.
You're going too fast.
Why?
You still have a lot of things to do before you do anything like that.
Even so I still want to do it.
I've seen you doing this with Shiraha as well as the others though.
Akari wants to do it too!
You...
Why do you mention Shiraha?
Shiraha was able to do it with you.
So I thought that I could as well.
No, no.
These aren't things you have to be doing yet.
Besides...
That isn't one of the things you're here to train for.
Master...
Why not?
It doesn't matter.
That's the end of this conversation.
Master...
This job is really tiring.
Good work.
And how did things go?
It seems things well?
I'm certain that we all gave it our best here, including the pans.
Um.. I just got back.
Is that so?
When you're a maid you have to keep working.
Well then.
You're done now though?
Yes.
Well it's good that at least a lot of people went and we became known.
Even though this was the first day for us.
We did have plenty of customers.
I didn't think we would have had so many customers.
Well I hope it's not too hard for you.
No way, don't say that.
If you say it's fine then I understand.
Well all of you are maids after all.
You especially are pretty amazing.
Master...
Ah.. No...
I m-mean..
It's just that you always do your best.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Now your clothes get all wet because I made you come with me.
If we go this way we can probably find someplace to pass the rain.
Let's go!
Yes!
It's raining pretty hard isn't it?
Master...
Yeah.
If I recall correctly I should have something here...
I was sure I left my other clothes here.
I'm sorry, Master...
Oh well it doesn't matter.
Master... I didn't mean to look away.
Geez, You sure are a ditz sometimes.
Master...
However you are beautiful and I'm sure many men would like to be with you.
I realize this even more now.
Do you really think of me that way, Master?
Look at me.
Master, please take me then.
Philine.
As long as it's the Master.
You can look at me always.
I'm grateful you look at me that way.
Master...
No..
You're already wet down here.
Th-that ...
This..?
Master, please don't look at me there.
You are very cute when you're like this, Philine.
Any man would say the same about you.
I like you this way.
No..
I'm glad you didn't say no to me.
It's getting really hot here.
Philine, please go ahead.
If the master says so.
Philine.
Let me use those.
Is this okay?
Move them while you're like that.
Like that, keep going.
Are you sure you're ready, Philine?
You are very beautiful.
Philine.
I'm sure you can see that already though.
You did that very well.
But I understand if you don't want to.
No, it's not like that.
I am here to serve you in any way you need.
Master...
Do you like it like this?
Philine.
I'm going in.
This might hurt, Philine.
You can move inside of me as much as you want.
Yeah, I like it like that, well then..
What is it?
Don't look at me please.
Master...
No more..
This is the masters...
We're back!
Welcome back!
You two weren't doing anything strange were you?
What? Did something happen?
Philine..
Yes?
Nothing happened, Laila.
Welcome back, Master!
Hurry up so you can eat dinner, Master..
What's wrong, Akari?
She's hiding something.
I can't tell if she is in fact hiding something.
But something is going on here, I can tell.
Ah! I understand now!
Both of you went to the beach and ate already!
You two are too sneaky!
Akari, found out what you did!
Master, your tea..
Lalai, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
He's resting on my lap.
Th-That's not what I mean.
Isn't it obvious?
We're all here to do what he wants.
Master...
Don't start fighting over this now.
Geez.
Akito..
Master!
Your tea.
Thank you, Shiraha.
No problem!
Shiraha.. You too?!
I guess I am not need-..
Philine!
Nice Assist!
Now Akito, come to me!
Yeah.
Master.. come to me!
I see.
Don't leave me here.
You're going to end up destroying him like that.
Who's there?
Akari?
What are you doing?
I wanted to make sure you were fine.
You came all the way here late at night to come check on me?
Well that's..
You should head back and go to sleep soon.
But..
But, Akari came here..
It was hard to escape from Shiraha..
I can't believe this..
Master, please, train Akari in that as well!
Akari is the only one that doesn't know about that.
Please..!
I guess it can't be helped.
I will train you.
Yes!~
Well, before anything are you sure you're ready?
Yes? Master..?
Don't you want to train Akari as well?
Then start by making this hard..
What do I do with that?
That's right, here is where you start.
Yes..
Stroke.. stroke..
Stroke... stroke?
That's the first thing..
Yes..! the first thing..
Stroking..
Like this?
Yes, like that.
Ah! It's getting bigger now!
The master's thing doesn't scare me anymore.
It looks kind of cute now.
Is that so?
Is it okay if I keep doing this?
Another thing you could do is fellatio.
Fell...atio?
You have to lick it.
I have to lick it?
Yes.
Fellatio.. fellatio.. I have to do..
It's a bit scary..
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
No, I have to! The master wants Akari to do this for him.
There's a bit of something coming out.. from here...
You don't just have to lick it, you can also put it in your mouth.
Yes!
You can also use your tongue while it's in your mouth and stroke it.
Yes..!
Yes, like that.. you're doing good for a first time.
Like this?
The master's penis got really big inside of my mouth when I did that!
Do you want to learn something else?
Are you going to teach Akari something else?
Yes, does Akari want to?
Does Akari want to?
Akari doesn't know what else to do with your penis.
I guess it can't be helped then.
Take off your panties and let me see.
You want me to take off my panties?
There..
Move your hands, so I can see.
And life your skirt.
Yes...
The master's fingers inside of me feel really good..
You're really wet here.
Do you see it?
Yes.
It feels like I'm going to pee..
No, that's because of how you're feeling.
I'm going to put it in.
Master...
It..it hurts!
It..It Hurts, Master!
Should I stop?
No, don't stop! Akari wants to do this..
I want to be just like Onee-chan!
Well then.
It hurts.. it hurts..
Are you sure you're going to be fine?
I'm fine.. Akari is fine.. so please keep going!
The master's...
Akari is feeling really good inside, Master..
Akari, I'm cumming.
Akari too, Akari is...
It's coming out.. It's coming out..!
Master...
I left a little mess in your bed..
Geez.
And it had to be right here..
I'm sorry...
Master hurry up, I am next.
Yeah, just wait.. in line..
Shiraha?
You were here?
Yes, I overheard.
No..
I don't really care..
Hey, what are all of you doing here?
Master..
Akari..was here!
What do you think you are doing?
What do you mean by that?
I am the master here.
I understand that already.
That's why you have to treat us all the same..
Geez, you have to be like that with all of us.
Ah.. me too!
Hey, all of you, wait a second..
I was the next in line..
Shiraha..
Lick it.
Master..
Shiraha! It's not about what you want..
Master...
Could it be that you really like doing that?
Master..
It feels great..
Akari wants to as well!
What's is it Akito? You don't like it with everyone here?
Master, you like it when I do it like this right?
Master.. that feels so good..
Master's.. chest..
Or they look like it...
Master~
Master!
Akari! Be careful..
No way!
Master!
Akito!
Master...
Why does this happen every time?
Don't mind.
These are my maids, and this is what I go through every day.
It's completely out of my hands...
Master!
akutsu