Akari.
Yes!
Master..!
Today's dessert is this cake with a special ice cream icing.
I see. Today you picked another sweet dessert.
What..?
Akari!
Are you okay?
Master, be careful!
It seems I cut the wrong thing again.
No, I don't quite think that's the problem.
Whatever..
Don't say that.
The master's cake..
Don't worry about that.
Don't you say anything either.
It's obvious though, isn't it?
Philine.
Allow me.
Shiraha, clean up at once.
Akito, at least help us a bit.
Don't do that!
This is what I have to go through everyday, with my maids.
Please stop doing that!
Lesson 1
Maid
Oshiete
akutsujin.wordpress.com
akutsu ~
My name is Ayabe Yukari.
My job is to teach and to raise girls to be maids.
Well, and about all this...
What does it have to do with me?
I will be the one to inform you of that.
I'm the headmaster of the school for maids.
Your job will be...
You have to be their master.
What is this?
That's Mochi.
Mochi?
She has a cute voice.
When they say I'm cute, I get embarassed.
It just spoke.
Calm down please.
The person who just spoke is the headmaster.
What?!
This strange thing is the headmaster?
No, you're mistaken.
This is Mo-chan.
Well then..
Doesn't that mean you're Mochi?
Wow, you are really flexible.
You're going to break me...
I see, so Mochi uses this as a method to communicate.
That's right.
The headmaster is a very busy person.
That is why I have to send people like Yukari-chan and others to speak about the maids for me.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
And? What is it I have to do? Yukari-san?
Please, call me Wistoru.
This is what you are getting.
These are the four maids that you have to take care of.
Back then I never thought they would cause so much trouble.
Come in.
I have brought you some tea, Master.
Bring it over here.
Yes!
Don't run with that.
And don't forget to close the door after you come in.
I'm sorry!
Master...
Jeez, even though it's something so simple.
Don't move around like that!
Akari?
Hey Akito!
Just what were you doing? Akari was crying.
I think it was more of something that was done to me.
A..Akari did it again I guess.
You should really go change those clothes.
All of you are maids, you should at least do a few things for me..
Since I am your master after all.
Well, Akito is like this after all right?
My old master was just as useless, he didn't know how to do or use anything.
Ah you...
The way you act, would sure make them think bad things about you.
Well then...
I've told Philine to take your clothes.
What do you mean?
It should all be in this closet.
It's not in there.
It's real nice outside today, so it's been set out there to dry.
Philine.
Mas...
Why are you walking around like that, Master..?
Well, all my clothes is out here.
Ah.. well it doesn't matter which one, just please put some clothes on.
Incredible.
I'm sorry.
It seems all of your clothes has gotten wet again.
This weather is quite strange.
It sure is, isn't it?
Hey, Shiraha.
Why can't you get down here like normal people.
What do you need? Master...
Whose life must I take?
No.
Who do I have to kidnap then?
Then...
What?
Help wash all these clothes.
That's a job for a maid.
Aren't you a maid?
So that's what it's about.
I'm no longer a bodyguard..
Well then, please help me with this, Shiraha-chan.
Understood.
What's wrong Shiraha?
Master, please run away!
Calm down, Shiraha!
DIE! I'm going to kill you, I'm going to kill you!
Be careful, Shiraha.
DIE! DIE! DIE!
Either way...
That's how it's been so far.
I understand.
By the way...
Why are you dressed like that?
Because of that girl who thinks she's a soldier.
I see.
It seems like your maids haven't really done what they are supposed to be doing for you.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about what they are supposed to be doing at night.
It's a bit too early for them to be doing anything.
They can't even do regular work during the day.
I don't think you understood what I just said.
The type of work they're supposed to do at night is...
I'll show you how it should be done.
How would that be?
Wait, Wistoru...
All you have to do is stay there, Master.
It seems it woke up...
It seems to like this too...
Well of course, you have to let the maids do their jobs at night.
Be it one of them, or all of them.
Because if the master wishes for this...
His maids must heed the call and come to his side.
Wistoru...
Because being alone with their master...
They can feel his chest and be loyal to him.
That is the joy of being a maid.
This is what they must do.
With your permission, Master.
Wistoru...
It's so warm inside of Wistoru...
This is the first time I've felt it like this...
Your penis is so warm, Master.
And so big.
Right now you are the owner of this body, Master.
So do whatever you want with it.
The clothes is finally dry, I must hurry and take it to the master.
Akari, remember to not run.
It hurts...
You are so mean Shiraha-san!
It's my turn to take the clothes to the master!
Onee-chan...
It feels so good, Master.
Cumming!
Master..!
Please give me all your cum, Master.
Give it to me please.
Wistoru...
Master...
Akari...
That is also part of our job.
To think that my sister and the master do those things...
Akari is also a maid, and the master...
and the master...
What have you been doing? Servant.
Yonis-chan...
Could it be that if you screw this up again, they'll be mad?
You are the younger one, right?
And your sister is Wistoru, right?
You.. You're mistaken!
Akari.. well the master...
What about the master?
Well, the work we have to do at night...
No way! Don't tell me that guy has done perverted things with my sister...
No, it's not that.
Onee-sama!
Ah.. Yonis-chan...
Miko-chan...Mako-chan...
Onee-sama!
Wa..wait Yonis-chan.
Just like I thought, even though my sister dresses like a maid, she hasn't changed one bit.
What are you doing wearing that uniform outside of the school, Yonis?
Wistoru...
This place is used for training.
If you're just here to cause trouble, leave.
It wasn't my intention to cause any trouble.
I was just visiting.
Well then, excuse me please.
Ah! Yonis-chan, wait!
Wistoru.. are you going to be going home now?
Yes...
I had to do a few things and lost track of time.
What's wrong?
Akari...
No, everything is fine. It's nothing, Onee-ch.. Wistoru.
Is that so?
I hope you get along with your Master.
He was fun.
Yes!
Well then, I'll be leaving everything in your hands now.
Akari-chan.
Come and help me.
Night training is it?
Come in!
What is it Shiraha? It's late.
I came here to provide the night service.
I see.
Hey! Shiraha.. Do you even understand what you're saying?
I understand.
Shiraha..
What are you doing?
Maid's must satisfy their masters in all of their wishes.
You're wrong about that.
What.. are you doing?
Is this what you want to do?
It has only just begun.
Just leave everything to me.
I studied a bit to do this type of work.
Hey, wait a bit, I haven't taught you anything yet.
It's okay.
I've seen erotic books and Eroge games on the computer, to have some input.
It's okay!
It won't be okay.
First of all, I must make my master's penis get big.
To do this I'm going to use the fellatio technique.
It's getting bigger...
She's pretty good at it, even though it's her first time.
Let's start...
Shiraha, stop for a bit, okay?
A maid must not only clean her master's soul, but his body as well.
You can do that in another way.
This night time service, is the time for my master and I to become one.
Don't interrupt me.
This is not a game with your master.
Be quiet!
I can feel the master's penis, breaking through my hymen.
It hurts more than what I thought.
It's fine, you don't have to.
No, it's my duty as a maid, to please the master.
In those games, do they do this with their masters?
Until the master cums, my duty won't be fulfilled.
Shiraha...
How is it master? Do you like how my pussy feels?
If the master doesn't feel good...
But...
I just want to make you feel good...
It's really warm inside of Shiraha...
It's also incredibly tight...
What is it master?
Give all of your cum to your maid, master...
If you do that...
It's all inside... you came so much inside of me, master..
This is.. semen...
This.. is the master's semen...
Mission accomplished.
Hey...
Shiraha...
Take this off...
Take this off of me, before you get all dressed up.
Shiraha! Wait...
Don't just turn off the lights..
Shiraha..!
What is this?
Laila-san! Help me!
Philine!
What are you doing.. Yonis?!
What do you mean? It's obvious that I'm molesting her.
I have to feel her up before that disgusting master of yours has his way with my sister.
Yonis-san, you should go back to the school..
You know I can't do that, Onee-sama!
Please give me your virginity, Onee-sama..
No..!
What? What? A gun? How can this be?
First..
The trash...
Wait a minute, I'm.. Yonis!
I can see that.
What's going on? What's with all the noise?
What just happened?
Why was she here this late at night?
Akit..
Philine.
Philine.. Are you alright?
Master!
Calm down.
Everything is fine now.
Akito..
Akito.. you IDIOT!
What's wrong with her all of a sudden?
Please go after her, master.
But..
I'm sure Laila-san is waiting for you to go get her.
I understand.
Laila..
Are you in here?
S..So..Sorry!
Once again, I'm always giving Laila-san a bad impression.
Akito.. you can come in now.
Are you sure?
I said it's fine, didn't I?
Yes..
I'm coming in.
Laila! Those clothes..
I thought wearing this today would be nice.
That's the outfit all of us made together..
Yes, even though it's still not finished..
Look at me!
You're not mad anymore?
Of course I am mad..
But, to be honest, there isn't really a reason to be mad.
I guess..
Yes, because I am a maid after all..
And you are my master.
And even so, you came looking for me.
How rude.
Laila..
That is why.. I..
I don't mind this relationship, me being the maid and you being the master.
That I have..
They aren't as big as Philine's, but they're still big.
Don't compare me to Philine.
They are bigger than Akari and Shiraha's though.
Not that..
Don't talk about anyone else right now..
Idiot..
You don't ever change, do you?
Akito.. that place..
Don't worry, I'll treat you nicely..
Yes, but..
Akito's hands are all over my breasts...
I never thought I would actually get to do this to you, Laila..
Me too, I didn't think I would be doing these types of things with you, Akito...
You're already wet..
If it would always be this way, it would be very cute..
Well I'm sorry it's not always like this!
A..Akito..don't.. I'm going to.. cum if you do that...
If you keep doing that, I'm going to cum..!
Now then..
Here I go.
Laila! This your first time?
Of course it is!
What are you going to do now?
It's your fault that I've lost my virginity..
And we've already started, so don't you think about stopping now.
Then turn around..
Be gentle with me..
Now..
Start moving.
Then, here I go.
Akito!
This..
Feels amazing..
How do you feel, Akito?
I'm happy, because knowing this is your first time..
and that I am your first.
Well of course, because Akito..
Akito..
Akito!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...!
That felt really good..
I still can't believe that was your first time.
If you keep this up, you will definitely be more interesting to me, than any of the other maids.
You might even end up being the best one at the night service.
Akito...!
IDIOT..!
Wh..why..?
I wonder if I can make great maids out of them, in under a year.
Hey! Don't turn off the lights!
If you enjoyed this release, please consider purchasing the original DVD, support Hentai!
akutsu fansubs
www.akutsujin.wordpress.com ~ Future releases, comments, etc.