After racing
through a cheerful season...
...what will happen to the
footprints in the sand of my memory?
Tears are rolling down
to the beach of my heart...
Wind wipes them away.
The sky is reflected in my heart.
You always change like a whirlwind.
Why don't you come over
to my apartment at midnight?
Both of you.
Saki...
Kindness pushes back clouds...
But rain like tears falls from them.
Sometimes, indigo girl...
...sadness is just like a
quick rain before you grow up.
Start to run, now...
Dream in the future.
Let's finish the fight
that started three years ago.
I wonder what happened between them.
Kaori...
Yes.
Sorry I got you into trouble.
It's okay.
Well...
Here we are.
This is Saki's apartment.
It's open.
Come in, Kaoru.
Like I said, I'm using
my real name, Yuko Imai.
You're so punctual...
...as always.
Don't be shy, come in.
This room looks the
same as it did three years ago.
Unbelievable. She always...
What happened?
Nothing...
All right.
Let's start the game right now.
If you win, I keep your secret.
But if we win, I will take Kaori.
We?
The game won't be interesting if it's
just between you and me, Big Sister.
Because we have a pretty guest...
I added a special twist.
Sayaka.
Yes, Big Sister.
Ms. Tamura, Saki definitely...
Do you know her?
She is Sayaka Tamura and she
debuted in the same year you did!
Ouch!
You two competed for the
Best New Singer Award, remember?
I'm sorry.
You guys lost the mood.
Anyway...
Oh!
She is one of my collection.
My cute pet.
How's this?
We will swap partners and if
you make her come first, you win.
What?
What? That could be fun.
Moron.
This is a problem between you and me.
It's not good to get them involved.
Kaoru.
You have no choice.
Yuko.
Ms. Saki!
I will do it.
No, Kaori.
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
I want to help you.
Kaori...
Sayaka...
She's a good girl.
Needless to say...
...it's lots of fun to
make such a pretty girl come.
That's right.
Feel it.
You are already hard enough...
No...
Such a cute voice.
What happened?
Is that it?
You're no match for me.
No.
I won't lose.
I don't know what
happened three years ago.
But, I trust Yuko.
Trust...
Can you trust Yuko?
Yes, I can.
What the hell do you know?
Three years ago...
Yuko disappeared
without saying a word.
She said she loved me.
She said she would be my side.
She betrayed me!
I have waited for her.
But she picked you up.
Ms. Saki...
How can you trust her?
Saki...
Shit.
I have to...
Seems like she is enjoying it...
But her reaction is so-so...
I have to, otherwise...
I will lose.
What?
You're kidding me!
As I guessed, Saki
trained you to enjoy anal sex.
In that case...
No...
I will go wild for a while.
Looks like you found out.
But...
It's too late.
I will win.
Okay, Kaori.
I will make you come inside me soon.
I have to win.
Are you coming?
You want to come, right?
I'm coming.
Please, hurry up.
I won!
Kaori!
What!
Sayaka.
Yuko.
Saki, you are the one
who taught her about it.
And I am the one
who taught you about it.
It was easy to figure out her fetish.
That means I lost.
Saki, listen.
I feel bad that I disappeared three
years ago without saying anything.
But...
Saki...
You think I didn't know anything?
I knew what happened three years ago.
Why?
What I can't forgive is...
Yuko.
You feel jealous of Kaori.
That's why you challenged us to this...
Don't flatter yourself.
Why should I feel jealous of
the girl you abandoned me for?
Saki...
I played the game just
because I wanted Kaori.
The game is over.
I'll keep her secret.
Go.
Ms. Saki...
I'm sorry, Saki.
But trust me.
It wasn't that I didn't like you.
Go away right now.
Saki.
Idiot...
Four years ago...
Saki and I debuted in the same year.
We competed against each other for
most of the Best New Singer awards.
We were very good rivals.
But, once we left the stage, we had
to deal with a lot of different people.
Yuko...
It's locked.
You've gotta be kidding.
Boss! Open the door!
I know you're there.
Please open. Can you hear me?
Open! Boss! Boss!
Please open!
Why?
Don't come near me!
Liar!
You told me we were
going to just drink together.
Why are you giving me trouble?
Your agency
already said this was okay.
You've gotta be kidding me.
When I said it is necessary
for you, they gladly said okay.
Unbelievable...
We will give you a lot of opportunities.
Of course, it's not free.
You should decide.
You want to sing as
a star in the spot light...
...or return to being a regular woman?
How can I...
Looks like you understand.
No...
Let's start!
Here...
Don't be selfish.
No! Please stop!
Here, keep using your mouth.
I'm coming!
No!
What's that?
You're giving up already?
I wonder if you can survive in
this tough entertainment business.
Next is...
No, let me go!
What are you talking about?
Your friend just showed up.
Why don't you play together?
No!
Saki...
Are you okay?
That wasn't so bad, was it?
Let's go Saki!
Yes...
Wait.
It's your job.
You have no choice.
I'll get over it...
I can't stand it any more.
I became a singer
because I want to sing.
Why do I have to do these things?
This isn't the
reason I became a singer...
Saki...
I will quit sing--
Don't say any more.
But I can't handle it...
You don't suddenly
dislike singing, do you?
I like to sing, too.
I am sure that there are
people who are waiting for my songs.
If I believe that, I can keep singing.
No matter what...
Let's be together.
Kaoru.
I will be always on your side.
But, one year later I got...
...an infection...
...damaging my vocal cords.
I didn't want her to notice
that I couldn't sing any more.
Because I liked her, I really liked her.
I didn't want to be seen as
such a miserable figure by her.
So, I disappeared silently.
But, I didn't imagine I hurt her so much.
Yuko, I think she
definitely understands your feelings.
How bitter and sad you were...
...she definitely understands.
I am sorry, I made you feel bad.
That's not true.
Because...
My life has been
better since I met Yuko.
Good morning.
What?
Hey guys!
Saki!
Ms. Saki?
Why are you at our office?
Boss, what is this?
Well, actually...
You moved to our office?
Yes, I hope you will
treat me kindly from now on.
What the hell are you thinking?
As I promised, I'll keep Kaori's secret.
But...
I never said I'd give up.
Excuse me...
Hey Saki!
You know what...
I won't give you up, either.
Ouch!
Why did you do that?
Don't say anything strange in here.
Don't be so violent.
You should talk.
You are always so...
Don't nag me.
What did you say?
Thank you very much.
Today is the last
day of my concert tour.
Without your support, I
couldn't have made it through.
I would like to introduce a wonderful
guest who will join me for the encore.
It is Ms. Saki Midorisawa,
who just joined our team.
Good evening! I am Saki.
Please support me as you do Kaori.
Ms. Saki.
Oh!
What are you doing?
Never mind. Just wave, okay?
After racing
through a cheerful season...
...what will happen to the
footprints in the sand of my memory?
Tears are rolling down
to the beach of my heart...
Wind wipes them away.
The sky is reflected in my heart.
You always change like a whirlwind.
Kindness pushes back clouds...
But rain like tears falls from them.
Sometimes, indigo girl...
...sadness is just like a
quick rain before you grow up.
Start to run, now...
Dream in the future.
My heart beating engraves my past.
My memory fades and drifts away.
Keep knocking at your heart...
I push my cheek against the solid door.
The sky is reflected in my heart...
...doesn't change even now.
Romantic feeling falls down like snow...
My passion comes
out, on and on and on...
Sometimes, indigo girl...
...a romantic moment can
be a head wind keeping me back.
Let's step out, now...
Dream in the future.
Kindness pushes back clouds...
But rain like tears falls from them.
Sometimes, indigo girl...
...sadness is just like a
quick rain before you grow up.
Start to run, now...
Dream in the future.
ЯQ