Good. Did you do everything
like we told you to?
Y... Yes. But why...
You tried to snitch on her, didn't you!
Huh? But how? It was just moments ago...
She knows everything that's going on!
You're lying! You guys are
thinking about doing it anyway...
Us? With you? Voluntarily?
You've got to be kidding me.
Stop... Please don't do this... It hurts.
Look! She's in pain from one kick
in the stomach. You ugly bitch!
Stop looking down!
Her face is swollen. What a disgusting face.
Look, you're on camera. Smile.
PERVERSE INVESTIGATIONS
Part II
This was in your bag?
A tape?
Did you watch it?
I thought so. It must have creeped you out.
Okay. Leave it to your big brother
to watch it and take care of it.
I didn't say anything...
I was going to, but I didn't.
You guys are the ones who stopped
me... Why are you doing this... ?
We're still taping, Nozomi.
No, stop. Please, no more.
We're not stopping yet.
It's just finally getting good.
You know you want to cum too.
Come on. You're not sucking on it right!
You're done already?
Please make them stop...
We've done enough. Let's stop.
Please don't...
Is this a warning to us?
Probably. But who took this video?
This was in Kizuna's bag...
If we don't stop prying...
They'll most likely do the
same thing to Kizuna.
Okay.
Let's decide who we're
going to punish tomorrow.
How?
Let's do "Follow the Line".
Kizuna.
Masayoshi.
What's wrong? Why are you standing outside?
Kizuna...
Thank goodness...
M... Masayoshi?
What's wrong?
What's the meaning of this?
Isn't it obvious?
We want to talk to you.
Hurry up and get out of the pool.
You used Hikaru Nagihara, made
the coach your accomplice...
...and became the top athlete of
the swim team, Ms. Sae Ichijyo.
What do you want? Money?
You ignorant, greedy pigs.
You have no right to call us that.
You're the one who's ignorant.
Winning the meet will also be
good financially for the school.
Ms. Sae Ichijyo thought she had the
coach in the palm of her hands...
Shut up!
Be quiet!
Professor Yuko knew about it!
Are you talking about the
professor who fell off the roof?
I don't know anything about it.
It has nothing to do with us.
Your name was in the
professor's schedule book.
Nami Sudou.
Kiyoka Enjyoji.
Shiori Sakura.
Nozomi ltou.
Hikaru Nagihara.
And you.
You know something.
No, I don't. Even if I did, I wouldn't tell you.
Don't you guys know when you
should mind your own business?
What?
So that means you do know. Let's punish her.
Punish me?
What is this?
Sae, come out if you're ready.
I knew you'd have an angry face,
but that's what's so hot about you.
Don't just stand there. Pose for us.
Pose?
Like this?
Nice toes!
Next you're going to pose like you're
picking something up without kneeling.
Picky bastards.
It's great! What an amazing body.
Hey, those pictures better look nice
or else I'm gonna give you a fat shot.
Stop talking like that,
you're ruining the mood.
Just so you know, you're the one
who's gonna get a fat one. Not us.
And I'm not talking about a shot.
I'm talking about a big fat cock.
Right, Masayoshi?
That's enough.
Stop. Hey! I said stop!
Stop... No...
You act tough, but you break down easily.
You're wrong... This isn't...
That's because you've
never felt like this before.
It's because you've never
done this with a man.
It's because you're a virgin.
So what?
I'll take your virginity, so that you'll never
think about pulling dirty tricks again.
It's your punishment.
What? You...
Punishment, yeah right! All you want is this!
Well? Well? Well? Well?
What's wrong? Why don't
you fuck me yourself?
Rape me! Are you scared?
You're only a filthy animal!
My real father was a criminal.
Rape, burglary... In the end, he
took his own kid as hostage.
The detective who saved
me was Kizuna's father.
You're the son of an animal.
That's right. I'm...
I'm using Nami Sudou, and having
the girls who are in my way raped?
What are you basing this assumption on?
You have no right to
accuse me of such things.
I have proof. I have pictures and video.
You probably made them yourself.
First of all, why would I do such
a thing? It's reckless and childish.
There's no need for me to do that.
You had a motive and a
need. That's why you did it.
Humans are greedy. You were in a situation
where you couldn't satisfy your needs...
...so you became more and more selfish.
You decided to take drastic
measures to fill that gap.
Anybody can see that you're that type of...
You talk like you know me.
I do know you.
I'm impressed that you were
able to enter the premises...
I have guards to keep animals
like you from getting in.
I wonder what they're doing?
Someone helped me in.
I'll introduce you. Come with me.
Thank you for coming to our store.
You're Samejima's...
What are you planning to do?
I won't forgive you if you're...
It's a punishment.
A punishment?
Mistress Kiyoka.
Mistress Kiyoka didn't look too
comfortable in her clothes today.
It's probably because of the body suit
that she ordered through our store.
I'm glad you liked it.
You liked it so much you wore it to school...
You made my father submit to you...
Ever since I saw you for the first time
at the party, all I wanted to do...
...was to see your beauty and grace
get dragged down with sinful pleasures.
My wish will come true today.
Please show us.
Mistress Kiyoka, how beautiful...
Your outfit, knee high socks
and loafers... It clashes, but...
No...
What's wrong, Mistress Kiyoka?
I don't want to do it dressed like this.
Please, let me go to my room. I'll
come back wearing my leather boots.
You mustn't. The outfit
brings out your true beauty.
The knee high socks and loafers
can be compared to my love...
And now you will be humiliated.
I'm going to call you my slave.
Turn around and put your
hands on the bench.
What are you doing? Spread your legs.
No!
At least get me wet please.
What are you talking about?
Do you think the women who were
raped had their wishes granted?
No!
Stop! No!
There you are.
Hey.
One of the girls told me...
...that Sae Ichijyo and Kiyoka Enjyoji are
in a lesbian relationship with another girl.
Guess who?
I don't know.
Shiori Sakura.
And apparently she's after your sister Kizuna.
My sister?
Yeah, your sister.
Am I wrong?
I had no idea we had a sister
school in Brazil. Is this essay okay?
Kizuna. I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Could you show me your
brother's birth certificate?
Masayoshi's birth certificate?
Yes, please.
Masayoshi!
Brother!
Shiori... Shiori...
I want you to stop.
Brother?
I want you to stop calling me that.
Masayoshi.
It's not what you think. This...
Kizuna is precious to me, and
that feeling just took over, so...
I don't care.
Kizuna!
Please don't forget my favor!
Why are you running away?
What about you? Why are you
following me? If it's not about Kizuna...
Stop acting dumb!
You're the one who got Nozomi ltou raped.
What? Nozomi was raped?
You're the one who gave
Sae Ichijyo the idea...
...about how to get
promoted on the swim team.
Sae is an amazing athlete.
You're also the one who made
Kiyoka Enjyoji and Nami Sudou...
...rape the other students.
They were jealous of me.
Was this all to keep your position
as the student president?
Do you honestly think I'm
stuck on something like that?
You're the son of a detective.
Your reasoning is pathetic.
You're wrong!
I'm not the son of a detective!
Then why are you after me?
To punish you!
Are you surprised? It's ugly, isn't it?
I can't get naked in front of other
people because of this ugly scar.
My body is so ugly... Are you
going to be able to punish me?
You know you want him to.
Poor Shiori...
I made that scar, and because of it you
became someone completely different.
You kept blaming me, saying
that you couldn't date men.
That's why you kept girls around
you that you could manipulate.
But Masayoshi is willing to fuck you.
Aren't you happy?
Stop. Please...
I yelled that too, but nobody listened...
They even did this... and that to me!
Here you go, Masayoshi.
It should be easier now.
Please go ahead and
punish her with your cock...
Go on...
No, not that... Please. Help me.
No!
How dare you try to get
away after doing it to me!
You saw the video, right?
I'll do the same thing to you. Masayoshi
is going to fuck you over and over!
Every time he does you're
going to cry for help!
You're going to keep getting
raped even after you faint!
Do it!
Ow... It hurts... No...
There's blood mixed in with the cum.
Your cherry's been popped! Aren't you happy?
No!
Don't look at me. No... Please... I beg you...
You're doing it wrong, Shiori.
I can't see your pussy when
you're positioned like that.
Masayoshi. Please fuck
her so I can see her chest.
I can see it! I can see your ugly parts so well!
Masayoshi, please cum in her.
Please desecrate Shiori as much as you can.
No!
N... No! No! No!
Oh, it's dripping out. What a waste.
Come on. Drink it.
Drink it! Drink it! Drink it!
You deceived me, Shiori.
You had plastic surgery!
You always were slow.
You're no fun. Go away.
I wonder if you are?
Nami, let's have fun today too.
Nami, you're the best!
What are you talking
about? Kiyoka's the best.
Masayoshi.
Fuck me.
What a borlng chick.
Let's get it on.
Masayoshi... It feels so good...
No... Stop, Masayoshi. Masayoshi.
Masayoshi!!
Stop... Masayoshi...
Why are you doing this?
To have fun.
Were we all manipulated? But why us?
It was... by chance.
By chance? That's it?
I had my reasons.
Time goes by so slow.
That's why I have to keep
entertaining myself with little things.
I can't just have one ultimate experience.
Go on, you still have things to do.
Go.
MASAYOSHI NEGISHI KIZUNA NEGISHI
I wonder why Masayoshi
said that? And Shiori...
MASAYOSHI NEGISHI KIZUNA NEGISHI
I'm home.
Brother! You're home!
What's wrong?
Oh... it's nothing.
I see.
Sorry. I wasn't thinking straight.
I think Professor Yuko's death
really had an effect on me.
I'm sorry, too.
The more I cried, the
more you had to hold it in.
I'm sure that was hard on you, too.
I'm fine now.
Okay.