Shinya, you start.
Okay...
My family is in the love hotel business.
Because of that, I could never
bring myself to trust women.
Professor Yuko taught me the
importance of trusting someone.
Daisuke and I secretly taped people
fucking. I was going to sell the tapes...
...at my family's video store,
but Professor Yuko found out.
Professor Yuko scolded us
from the bottom of her heart.
Even our parents had given up on
us, but she was so determined...
Professor Yuko was always
worried about Kizuna and I...
...because our parents
died, and we were alone.
She always looked after Kizuna.
Kizuna has been depressed ever
since dad was killed on the job...
...and she didn't want to go to school.
Hey, that's enough.
Shut it off.
Huh? But... We still haven't taped Kizuna.
No... She still hasn't fully recovered from
the shock. I want to leave her alone.
Oh... Sorry. You're right.
PERVERSE INVESTIGATIONS
Part 1
Masayoshi! You'd better hurry,
or you're going to be late!
I'm coming down.
You're such a sleepyhead!
This is more like a feast than a breakfast.
Pretty impressive, right?
Professor Yuko taught me.
I want her to have some too.
I wonder when she's coming?
Hello? Shiori?
This is Kizuna.
Yes...
I just got a call that school's cancelled today.
Kizuna.
You have to mix it so air gets in. Like this.
I see.
Try it.
Like this?
Yup. You're doing a good job.
Mix it a little faster.
Okay!
Sorry, that was really rude of me.
It's okay. Thanks for coming guys.
Hope I didn't get in the way.
Of course you didn't. Right Masayoshi?
Yeah.
Professor Yuko fell from the roof...
but no one was allowed on the roof.
Yeah, but the lock was broken,
and people used to hang out there.
I used to take girls and fuck them
up there, but I heard rumors that...
...people were starting to deal up
there, so I haven't gone up there lately.
Maybe she saw something, and
her death wasn't an accident.
Don't you think that's possible?
Why would she go to the roof
by herself, for no reason?
Yeah, she was so square. Maybe
she lectured the wrong guys?
I can't believe it.
Yuko always put herself in
danger to protect her students...
...but she wasn't reckless.
And now she's de...
She's dead!
She was such a wonderful
person, and she died alone!
She laid there until she was
found the next morning.
She didn't... She didn't
deserve to die like that...
Hey Masayoshi... Let's
get to the bottom of it.
Let's investigate why she was on
the roof and who she saw last.
Yeah. Let's do that.
Hey wait.
What are we investigating? If she
didn't die from an accident...
What's that?
My dad's keepsake.
My dad was an officer who would
never let a suspect get away...
...even if it meant his own death.
I swear on his handcuffs.
I'm going to punish the ones
who left Professor Yuko to die.
Hey Nagihara!
Hurry up and come upstairs.
Okay.
You're nice and wet.
I'll stick my cock up your pussy
after you're done sucking it.
Your mouth isn't that bad.
Looks like you're ready.
Your pussy is gonna feel so
much better than your mouth.
Little bitch!
Don't think you can manipulate me
because you spread your legs.
You'll make Sae the anchor
again at the next meet, right?
I said you can't manipulate me.
Plus I'm not done with your ass.
Come on. Get up and get on all fours.
Wow! That's so amazing.
You guys are making your dicks hard for me?
Here you go Nami. Will you suck it?
Looks so yummy!
Nami, mine too. Mine too.
Sure.
Then I'll take her pussy.
Then I'll fuck her up the ass.
Nami. Go ahead and lower your ass.
Okay!
Here comes another one. There!
Yes. Your ass is so nice.
I'm going to cum.
I can feel your hot cum inside.
Nami, I'm cumming in you next.
Nami, you can't pay attention
to just one cock. Here.
Suck mine Nami.
Nami, I'm going to cum.
Who's going to cum next?
You're so dirty Nami.
We shouldn't be doing this during a funeral.
I don't care. It has nothing to do with
me. She's dead, she won't mind.
So hurry. Cum in me...
Okay.
Here I come!
Wow. Nami, you're such a pervert.
This is so amazing.
I'm going to cum again!
Nami!
This is the best.
It's so amazing... It's so amazing...
More... Fuck me more...
We're paying our last respects
in order of class year.
We'll meet up here after it's over.
Professor Yuko! Professor Yuko!
Kizuna.
Kizuna, pull yourself together.
Sorry... Kizuna!
Masayoshi.
She suddenly broke down in tears.
Kizuna, are you all right?
Masayoshi... Professor Yuko is...
Yeah...
Come on. Let's go home.
Sorry about the commotion.
Not at all... Oh, Masayoshi.
Yes?
I wanted to give this to you guys...
Masayoshi... Masayoshi... Masayoshi.
Um... Would it be okay if we join you?
I'm really worried about Kizuna,
so I want to be with her.
Oh, that paper bag looks
heavy. Let me hold it for you.
No thanks.
I'll take Kizuna home by myself...
Okay, I understand. Bye Kizuna.
I'll see you tomorrow at school.
Masayoshi, please excuse me.
Nozomi, we should help
Professor Yuko's mother.
Okay.
Let's go.
Masayoshi, what's in that bag?
Oh this? It's Professor Yuko's
keepsake. Her mother gave it to us.
Professor Yuko's...?
Yeah, her mother knew she
always looked after us.
So she wanted us to have this.
Professor Yuko's schedule book?
Yeah, it was mixed in with
the stuff her family gave me.
Kizuna...
Here.
Professor Yuko's handkerchief.
If this came back from the police, they
must have determined it was an accident.
I'm sure that's how the
school wants it to be, too.
It smells like Professor Yuko.
Masayoshi, let's read it.
Sure.
Her schedule's packed. There
are so many students written in.
And I thought she had
her hands full with us...
What was scheduled on the day she died?
MATTERS ON THE ROOF
Matters on the roof.
She knew something was
happening on the roof!
There are names on the next page.
SAE ICHIJYO
NAMI SUDOU
Sae Ichijyo, Nami Sudou.
HIKARU NAGIHARA
Hikaru Nagihara.
KIYOKA ENJYOJI
Kiyoka Enjyoji
SHIORI SAKURA
NOZOMI ITOU
Shiori Sakura and Nozomi ltou.
SHIORI SAKURA
NOZOMI ITOU
All of them are well known,
and have a reputation.
Yeah, but who's Sae Ichijyo?
You don't know who she is? She's
the top athlete on the swim team.
Everyone knows her on campus.
Hikaru Nagihara, whose name is written
next to Sae's, is also on the swim team...
...and she's attached at the hip with Sae.
I've heard rumors that she can't swim.
Nami Sudou is the school slut, and a bitch.
Kiyoka Enjyoji is a super rich
girl who has her own groupie...
...but her popularity is second,
compared to Shiori Sakura...
...the School Chancellor's daughter.
Nozomi ltou is Shiori's shadow... she
follows her around everywhere.
Was Professor Yuko
meeting them on the roof?
We don't know that...
We set up cameras everywhere, so
if something happens we'll know.
We promised Professor Yuko we'd
never do this, so I feel really guilty.
What we're about to do goes
against Professor Yuko's wishes...
...but I want to find out who killed her...
...and I want them to suffer
for what they've done.
A punishment?
Yeah...
Let's set the table.
Okay.
That paper bag looks heavy.
I'll go get your brother.
Good morning, Masayoshi.
Breakfast is ready.
I was just about to come get you.
What are you doing here?
I was worried about Kizuna... Professor
Yuko used to come everyday, right?
Yeah... Thanks for coming.
There's no need to thank
me. I wanted to help.
What are you two doing?
Breakfast is getting cold.
We're coming, Kizuna.
Sorry to worry you, Shiori.
I was thinking about it last night. I used
to rely so much on Professor Yuko.
I'm happy that I was able to
see her every morning, but...
...she came to our house because
she was worried about us.
I'm going to be strong, so she
doesn't have to worry anymore.
I want to tell her she can rest
in peace, because I'm fine.
That's very inspiring, Kizuna.
I want to be able to tell Masayoshi, too.
Then I fell in the bathroom, and...
First is... the phys-ed coaches' office.
They're going at it! It's the swim
team coach, and the woman is...
It's Hikaru Nagihara.
The one written in the schedule book?
Didn't take much to dig up some dirt.
I wonder if they talked about something?
Yeah, let me rewind it.
You'll make Sae the anchor
agaln at the next meet, rlght?
I sald you can't manlpulate me.
Plus I'm not done wlth your ass.
Come on. Get up and get on all fours.
And you won't say anythlng about lt, rlght?
It wouldn't be good for the school, elther...
Hey, hey, hey. You guys are the
ones who declded to do that.
You know damn well that If It
gets out, I can just act dumb.
But don't worry. As long
as I stay qulet lt'll be flne.
Come on, show me your ass!
Stop the tape.
Yeah.
I wonder what they were talking about?
It must be that rumor. So it was true.
What rumor?
Remember the swimmer from
Nankai Academy that was raped...
...and didn't show up for the meet?
That was the only reason we won.
She must have plotted that rape, and
the bastard coach is keeping quiet.
But Hikaru's a first year. I
doubt she planned all of it.
So someone else was behind it?
Someone written in the schedule book...
Yeah, let's look at the other footage.
Okay.
Naml, let's have fun today too.
Naml, you're the best!
What are you talklng
about? Klyoka Is the best.
But I'm the only one who
can have sex wlth her.
You're only her mlnlons
who follow her orders.
It's Nami Sudou.
You're only her mlnlons
who follow her orders.
A fivesome? I knew she was a
whore, but I wasn't expecting this.
I'm so jealous of you, Naml.
A fivesome? I knew she was a
whore, but I wasn't expecting this.
I'm so jealous of you, Naml.
What can we use on you today?
By the way, who's the next target?
Huh? Don't you thlnk It's a llttle
too soon? We should walt a llttle.
It's flne. Nobody's golng to stop us.
The ugly troll from the school
newspaper Is keeplng qulet...
...and the annoylng professor Is dead.
Oh, that's rlght.
Did they do something to the
leader of the newspaper club?
Oh, that's rlght. Could you
keep an eye on that ugly troll?
Did they do something to the
leader of the newspaper club?
Oh, that's rlght. Could you
keep an eye on that ugly troll?
So Kiyoka Enjyoji is the mastermind.
Huh? Why?
She's klnda down. It's because you
guys dldn't take It easy on her.
I'm sure she's the one
who's also manipulating...
She's klnda down. It's because you
guys dldn't take It easy on her.
...Sae Ichijyo and Hikaru Nagihara.
Whoops. Sorry.
So who's the next target?
We haven't declded yet, but If
someone's snooplng on us...
...you guys need to act fast. Untll then,
you can do whatever you want to me.
Professor Yuko died because of them.
...you guys need to act fast. Untll then,
you can do whatever you want to me.
They need to be punished.
Let's get ready to punish Sae
Ichijyo and Kiyoka Enjyoji...
...so they'll never think of using
sex to manipulate people again.
Kizuna is at the student government office.
She's helping Shiori...
I see...
Thanks.
Masayoshi.
What?
You'd better not get involved any further,
or else you... Not just you, but...
Masayoshi.
Are you here to get Kizuna?
Yeah.
Then let's walk downstairs together.
She's waiting for us at the shoe storage area.
Are you coming with us?
I...
I still have things to do, so I
can't walk home with you guys.
Let's go. Kizuna's waiting for us.
Stop... Please don't do this... It hurts.
Look! She's in pain from one kick
in the stomach. You ugly bitch!
Stop looking down!
Her face is swollen. What a disgusting face.
Look, you're on camera. Smile.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
What a boring chick.
Let's get it on.
But she really doesn't turn us on, so...
How about this? This is better than before.
Yeah, a little. Her breasts are so small.
Let's fondle them so they'll get big.
All right.
No! It hurts!
Stop! No!
Shut up!
No! No! It hurts! Stop!
You should be happy we're helping
you make your breasts bigger. Right?
No! No! It hurts! Stop!
You should be happy we're helping
you make your breasts bigger. Right?
That's right. Lame girls like you are
useless unless you have some breasts.
That's right.
I bet nobody's ever messed with your pussy.
Hey, she's wet.
Stop... No...
You're right.
Gross.
We're not ready yet. Don't get wet without us.
Come on, jerk me off.
Mine too.
Whoever gets hard gets to fuck her first.
Please... Please let me
go... I beg you... Please...
We need to fuck her. That's our orders.
Please... Please let me
go... I beg you... Please...
We need to fuck her. That's our orders.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm hard!
Already?
You're a pervert.
Shut up!
Situations like this turn me on.
Please... Please stop...
Shut up already!
It's more fun when she's squirming.
Who cares. Hurry up.
All right then.
It's tight...
No! Stop! No! No!
She's a virgin!
Of course she is. She's
busted. It's not surprising.
I've never fucked a virgin,
so I'm having a moment.
You're an idiot.
It hasn't been used, so it's so tight.
Take a good look. There's
a cock in your pussy!
It feels so good.
How about this? This should
give you a better view.
I can't hold it anymore, I'm going to cum!
No! That's dangerous! Not
inside... Please don't cum in me!
I can't hold it anymore, I'm going to cum!
No! That's dangerous! Not
inside... Please don't cum in me!
Make sure you watch him cum inside you.
I'm going to cum... I'm going to cum...
Stop! Stop!
Nice load.
Me next!
Hurry up and fuck her. It feels really good.
You're right. It feels so good.
I'm gonna get a blowjob.
You'd better not bite. If you bite, I'll
put your pussy out of commission.
Damn, it feels good. If she was
Kiyoka this would be awesome.
Then close your eyes and imagine it.
Why... Stop... I'm going to get pregnant.
The metal piece is in the
way. It won't go in anymore.
This is great. I'm going to cum. Hey,
make sure you take good footage.
No more... No more... It
hurts... Stop... Please...
This is great. I'm going to cum. Hey,
make sure you take good footage.
No more... No more... It
hurts... Stop... Please...
I know, Mr. Director.
And lastly... A little bonus...
That was pretty fun.
Yeah.
The tape's going to end. Get a close up.
Okay.
Okay, pull out slowly.
And cut!