Welcome to Pia Carrot.
This way, please.
Let me clear that.
What are your plans for summer vacation?
Going to Okinawa, of course!
Yusuke!
You scared me, Satomi.
I thought it was Shiho.
No more dilly-dallying, back to work.
Yusuke, let me help you.
Shoko is so kind. Satomi is so mean.
No, Shoko.
Show no pity to this good-for-nothing.
- But...
- Both of you.
Don't just stand there,
you have work to do.
I'm sorry, Shiho.
Shoko, it's cooler inside anyway.
Yusuke, I'll help you some other time.
- Yusuke.
- Yes.
When you're done here,
please clean the storage area.
Sure.
What a way to spend a summer vacation.
Damn you, Dad!
You tricked me!
Dad, that's not what you said.
I promised to work for you in July only.
I'm planning on going to
the beach in August.
You were planning on picking up girls,
which you would fail to do anyway.
If only you'd failed fewer of your classes...
Bro, give it up. You promised.
Stay out of this. Shut up, Milk.
I'm not a kid anymore.
No more nicknames, call me Rumi.
Okay. Yusuke.
You will work at Pia Carrot
for the whole summer.
What?
And I'll ask Kiyomi to tutor you.
No.
My precious summer holidays...
Ladies' Dressing Room
Lucky.
Ouch.
Satomi, you're a bad girl.
No, no, Shoko...
Yusuke, you pervert!
Yusuke, are you all right?
This must be a mistake. Forgive him.
Shoko...
What's the commotion?
What did you do, Yusuke?
I'm sorry.
I saw a cockroach and screamed and...
It's true.
The three of us came to take a look.
All right.
Everyone, your break is almost over.
Reika.
What are you doing? This is my room.
This is the only room with a big mirror.
Don't get so mad.
Hey, Bro, let's go to the Summer Festival.
With you?
I've invited Satomi and Shoko, too.
Well. It might be not
a bad idea to go out with you.
Really? Great.
I'm not that bad, am I?
Yeah, you look good in that yukata.
We haven't been to
the Festival in a long time.
Yeah.
- Here we are.
- Shoko, we've been waiting for you.
Can't refuse Rumi.
Wow.
Hey, isn't that your father?
Dad.
Surprise. We underestimated Dad.
- Didn't we, Rumi?
- Well, yeah.
Yusuke, take the trash on your way out.
- Do it yourself.
- Hey, hey, do it.
Shit. Satomi's a bitch.
Anyone there?
Reika.
- Don't worry, it's nothing.
- Nothing?
- You like me, don't you?
- Well...
That's too bad.
I have weakness for kind boys.
Yusuke, do you have a girlfriend?
No. Nobody special.
What about me?
Please. You're toying with me.
Reika.
What are you going to do, Yusuke?
You might not graduate high school.
I study everyday.
You're a mess.
I'm embarrassed to face your father.
Maybe I need to stick to your side
and watch after you.
I'd be glad if you'd watch after me for life.
Kiyomi, marry me.
Too bad, I will only marry a worthy man.
- Miss Kitagawa, don't be so mean.
- Bro's bothering Kiyomi again.
Yusuke, why are you so wishy-washy?
What are you girls doing here?
You have to go to work this afternoon.
Go on. Move.
This is heaven.
What are you staring at?
- Stop, please, stop.
- Die, die!
What a day.
Hey, Yusuke.
Have you thought about it?
Don't toy with me, Reika.
I don't mean to.
Watch out.
Don't let go of me. I'm falling!
Are you all right?
Reika.
Thank you for saving me.
Oh. I can't...
Ever felt a breast before?
No, no.
Be gentle.
Yusuke.
Where are you? Are you in there?
There you are.
I've been looking for you.
Let's go to lunch together.
Yusuke, wait up.
Kiyomi.
- Let's have tea.
- Thanks.
Yusuke, finish that quiz, then come down.
Okay.
Reika.
What if Shoko hadn't barged in...
- It's about time for Yusuke.
- I see.
We can't keep him the way it is.
Okay, let's do that.
Yusuke.
- What're you doing?
- Nothing.
Yusuke, speak of the devil.
We've been talking about you.
About me?
Shiho and I have decided...
...it's about time you waited tables.
- Good for you, Yusuke.
- I don't want it.
I know you got something up
your sleeve, Dad.
Shiho will notify you tomorrow.
This is an order from your employer.
Yusuke, do you need a hand?
Thanks.
But I'm almost done. Don't worry.
- Can I call you tonight?
- Yeah, sure.
Then I'll talk to you tonight. Good night.
Reika.
Shoko's cute. I'm getting jealous.
It's not like that.
I like-
No, you can't talk to a girl like that.
Maybe I should wait for you in the park.
But maybe you won't come.
So you came for me after all.
I didn't think you would.
Why not?
Well...
You're not busy?
No.
I like you, Yusuke.
You don't want to go out with me?
But why me?
You're toying with me.
I see. That's how it seems.
Tell the truth.
You don't want to go out with me.
That's not true. You're beautiful, and...
- Reika.
- Yusuke. I...
I...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're surprisingly manly.
Am I?
Stay like this.
It keeps me calm.
I've always wanted manly men.
Reika, that is...
You're getting manly down there.
Hello? Hi, Shoko.
Bro? He's not back yet.
Okay, bye.
Reika.
No. I can't hold back.
I want you inside me.
Reika. I love you, Reika.
Wait.
Yusuke. You're crushing me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. But be gentle with a girl.
Okay.
Good. Go on.
Are you all right, Reika?
Yes. It was wonderful.
Now let's use your tool.
Okay.
Oops.
That's strange.
Don't worry,
everyone's like that the first time.
Right here. Here.
You're so warm.
Reika.
Breathe deep.
Good, go slow.
Good. Harder.
Reika, I can't...
Good, go ahead. Come inside me.
Good morning.
Good morning, Yusuke.
Wait up, Yusuke. I called you last night.
Sorry, I ran into a friend on my way home.
Good morning, Reika.
Good morning.
She's getting busy with her school work.
This will be her last week.
No way.
Yusuke?
Good morning.
Yusuke, what're you daydreaming about?
Preview
Everybody is acting strange lately.
Besides, Shiho is leaving us, too!
Hey, Bro! What are you doing to Shoko?
I won't forgive you if you make her cry.
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
Our next episode is:
Would You Like An Adult Romance?
We'll see you next time!