Yusuke.
Hi, Reika.
My fault.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm so glad you're okay, Shoko.
But you have to be careful.
I broke so many plates.
No more crying. You have work to do.
Okay?
- Yusuke.
- Yes?
I'd like Shoko to change her clothes.
I'm sorry.
How's Shoko?
She's in good hands.
Reika.
KINOSHITA
What do you think, Yusuke, Rumi?
The new Pia Carrot uniform.
Not bad.
Would you move?
If you don't understand fashion,
no girl will fall for you.
Dad, if that's all you do,
no woman will fall for you.
That's my affair, stay out of it.
Always trying to sound so strong.
Don't make fun of your father.
- Michiko.
- Yoshio.
Michiko.
Reika.
What's with you, Reika?
Our boss is not a bad designer after all.
Let's get to work, Shoko.
Right, Shoko?
- Shoko?
- Satomi.
I see. It's Yusuke, isn't it?
I've got it. Let me handle it.
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
Hey, Yusuke. I'm talking to you.
What are you staring at?
Nothing. What do you want?
Yeah. Are you busy tonight?
I've got nothing to do.
Then come to karaoke
with Shoko and me.
Well. Why not? Just this once.
It's a date. Happy, Shoko?
I'm excited.
Getting there.
I guess Satomi can be
surprisingly feminine.
Hey!
Cute. Hey, Kitty.
Good timing.
Too much spice, maybe?
Weird. What if I toss in this...
Oops!
I just remembered.
I'm busy tonight, I gotta go.
What? Some other time, then.
You don't want to go with me?
Okay, okay. Just for an hour, okay?
- Yeah!
- That's my Yusuke.
- Good night.
Reika...
Good night!
Go on, go on.
About time now.
She's doing good.
Huh?
What?
Here.
Shoko. This is not a Karaoke place.
Come on, Yusuke.
This is a hotel.
See you tomorrow.
I made up my mind.
I want you tonight.
Shoko.
No way.
They must be kidding.
Shoko.
Shoko, Shoko.
You can't do that.
My palm bra.
No, Yusuke, this wasn't in the books.
I'm sorry.
This is my first time, so please be gentle.
Men.
I hate men!
Yusuke, I'm so happy.
I've been waiting for this.
Are you sure, Shoko?
Shoko?
Shoko. Shoko.
I love you, Yusuke.
Oh, well.
Yusuke, I was so happy last night.
I'll see you at the restaurant.
See you later.
You can't flirt with other girls.
No. I've had enough.
That sounds like...
- Lovers' fight.
- So early in the morning.
Shiho.
I'm tired. Let me think about it.
This is heavy.
Why are you depressed, Mr. Casanova?
- It's nothing.
- Oh, good.
There you are. Let's go home.
You don't have to cling to me so much.
Don't be shy.
We've been skin to skin, haven't we?
Help.
You're too much.
I'm home.
- I'm exhausted.
- No. Don't say that.
Please don't leave.
What, Rumi, too?
I'm sorry. Talk to you later.
Bro, don't sneak up on me.
What, you just weren't paying attention.
Someone dump you? No wonder.
Huh, I'm not like you.
Is Dad home?
Don't go in there now.
Wrong. Wrong.
Wrong, wrong.
What's going on?
You're working hard.
Yusuke.
It's about Shiho.
She's leaving us.
I'm sorry. Family emergency.
What's wrong with everybody?
There's something weird
going on at Pia Carrot these days.
Reika.
Stay away!
Stay away, and listen.
I was dating someone.
He dumped me.
I was so lonely.
Then I saw you.
I tried to fall in love with you.
Reika.
I'm sorry. But I couldn't.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
We're getting wet.
Yusuke?
What're you doing out at this hour?
You're soaked. You'll catch cold.
Come on.
I see. Today was Reika's last day.
Did you forgive her, Yusuke?
It's beyond that.
There was nothing I could do.
Poor girl. Well.
I'm in the same boat.
Cheer up. Tears don't become you.
You're leaving us, too.
Yes.
I have to. I'm not getting any younger.
- Things are happening with my family, too.
- No.
Yusuke.
Please, Shiho. Don't quit Pia Carrot.
Reika is gone,
Dad and Satomi are acting weird...
...now you're leaving.
Shiho.
Don't go. Please. Stay.
Shiho, Shiho.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
Good, Yusuke, you're good.
Wait. No, not there.
No. Don't look. Please.
- You're embarrassing me.
- You're beautiful, Shiho.
Yusuke. It's so nice, Yusuke.
Shiho, I...
Hold on. Come with me.
Yusuke.
Bro.
Satomi and Shoko are here.
Why?
I invited them. It's a big lunch party.
Party?
- Hey, Yusuke.
- I'm here, Yusuke.
Go have fun. I'm busy.
We'll cook our best.
Please come join us later.
I'll bring him down when you're ready.
Go cook.
I'll ask you to join us later.
I'll help you, Shoko.
- Thank you, Rumi.
- Let's go.
They're so feisty.
Shoko practiced cooking for you.
She's so earnest.
You have to be nice to her.
Aren't you joining them?
- Do you want me to cook for you?
- Kind of scary.
- What do you mean?
- You're choking me!
- What is this?
- I don't believe it.
- What're we going to do?
- What is this?
- Help.
Satomi's feast. Great.
Looks so yummy.
What's wrong? You're not eating?
I...
- It's so good.
- Isn't it?
Really. Satomi, it's so delicious.
It is, isn't it?
It can't be.
Delicious. It's seriously good.
It is, isn't it?
I was pretty sure.
It's so good.
Preview
Bright sunshine and beautiful ocean!
We're looking forward to our Okinawa trip!
But what is happening to everybody?
Shoko, Satomi, what's going on?
Can't we stay like this forever?
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
Our next episode is:
Would You Like Her Just The Way She Is?
We'll see you next time!