Seiji!
Yuna!
Thanks for the dinner.
It was delicious.
Yet another boring day
with nothing to do.
The city is peaceful and
bustling with people.
But two-thirds of the population
are robots now.
The new millennium saw a decline
in the sperm count of humans.
Maybe it's nature's way of
limiting population growth.
This has resulted in
a serious decrease...
...in the birth rates
of advanced nations.
It led to a world depression.
Large numbers in weaker
countries were wiped out.
Humanity was quietly
and steadily...
...beginning to eliminate
its members.
Robots were quickly developed
in response to the situation.
And mass production began
in order to...
...address labor shortages
and for domestic service.
Both my parents were pianists...
...and I followed in their footsteps.
But three years ago...
I injured my right hand.
Since then...
I have not performed in public
as a concert pianist.
At the hospital, a nurse helped me
through my difficulties.
She was a DX-V999 android.
Afterwards, I bought the same
model to be my maid.
Her name is Yuna.
Does it still hurt, Seiji?
You shouldn't push it.
I guess so. Sorry.
I hope you recover soon.
You look so happy
when you're playing.
It's the one thing I do really well.
Hey, why don't you try playing?
I don't have the necessary data
to play piano.
I guess not.
How about the data
from my performances?
We could download it.
I have a sequencer, too.
Come over here, Yuna.
Sure.
This should do it.
Now, sit in front of the piano.
All right.
That's amazing!
Wow! It's perfect,
with no mistakes!
Really? I'm glad.
All right. I'm going
to teach you piano.
I'm sure you'll be able
to play like a pro.
If you're going to teach me...
I'll be sure to do my best.
You're really cute.
Oh, Seiji!
This feels really good.
Release yourself.
Make all the noise you
want when you cum.
Seiji!
It really feels so good.
Me, too!
I... I...
How was I?
Needs a little more nuance.
All right, I'm taking you
to a real concert...
...since I can't play well enough
for you to be inspired.
A concert?
I've never been to a concert.
Get ready then. I'll book
the tickets on-line.
All right!
What did you think?
It was a great learning experience.
Good. I have high hopes for you.
Takeo, maybe we should
just go home.
How dare a machine like
you tell me what to do!?
Just shut up and follow me!
I can have you replaced
just like that.
You talk back to me and
I'll have you taken away!
Yes. I'm sorry, master.
I'll never--
Just shut up and come!
Let's get a drink!
I'm scared.
People who treat robots
like animals are scum.
Seiji treats me really well.
Like a human.
What's wrong?
A little shaken after
going out tonight?
Well, no... You are a kind man,
aren't you?
What do you mean?
Thank you.
I don't think of you as less
than human. That's all.
Seiji...
It feels so good.
Yes... Yes...!
Well, you've gotten much better.
Thanks to you.
We can do it if you're this good.
Right. I'm going to arrange
your professional debut.
Go get ready.
Let's go there directly.
Sure, but...
Hurry up.
Yes.
Well, Mr. Kurosaki!
It's been a while.
I was wondering if you could
arrange a recording.
Your wrist is healed then?
It's not for me.
It's for this lady here.
She's a student of yours?
That's right. I guarantee her talent.
Please arrange the session.
Mr. Kurosaki,
isn't this woman a robot?
What does it matter
if she's a robot?
I've never heard of
a robot debuting.
Her talent nearly matches mine.
I have full confidence in her.
But, I can't...
The Goldberg variations!
I want her to start big!
Wait a minute.
However good she is...
...it's no different than a concert
by a player piano.
How dare you!?
It wouldn't be received
by the public very well.
It's all right, Seiji.
It's okay. Let it go.
This isn't the only record
company. There are others.
Let's go, Yuna.
If you just listen to her,
you'll understand.
Please give her an audition.
Mr. Kurosaki...
I have a reputation to uphold.
There's no way I'm going to
record a robot performance.
What's the difference between
robots and humans?
How dare you. We owe a debt
of gratitude to robots.
It's all right, Seiji.
Let's just go home.
I'm not giving up.
You're going to have your debut.
Yuna?
You sure have strange interests,
Mr. Kurosaki. A robot?
Yuna!
Where are you? Yuna!
Where are you?!
Yuna... What's happened?
Is this the warranty company?
My robot has gone missing.
Please find her right away.
Yes. She's a model DX-V999.
A replacement?
No, that's not what I want.
I want my robot back!
She's the one I want!
Yuna, where have you gone?
Where did she go?
What have I done?
I've treated her so well.
Better than any human.
Give me the strongest
drink you've got.
One more.
You've gotta move
your ass properly.
You're lousy. When are you
going to learn, anyway?
That's it.
Yeah... That's the way.
See, you can do it if you try.
Stop!
Yuna.
This music...
Seiji.
I cleaned it up properly.
Yuna.
- Yuna.
- Seiji.
I'm sorry to have worried you.
This is really the only place for me.
- Will you take me back?
- Of course.
Don't worry about my debut anymore.
There's nothing we can do.
I'm happy just playing piano here.
But...
You seemed so happy
teaching me how to play.
But you mustn't live
your dreams through me.
My only wish is that...
...your hand will completely recover.
That you will play again...
...and return to the concert stage.
Yuna.
Seiji.