Put out that fire! The rest of you,
find Professor Nalerof!
Terminal force is sanctioned!
Have you found him?
Excellency Guizel, it will
be any minute now!
Have you found him?
Excellency Guizel, it will
be any minute now!
Make it soon.
Yes, Sir!
We've got him! Block 13!
Elysse, take this escape pod
up to the city levels!
Papa, what about you?
I'll be right behind. There's
not much time.
Go on. Get inside.
Elysse, live a long life. Thwart
Guizel's evil ambitions.
You've been a very foolish man,
Professor Nalerof.
Kill him.
Papa!
I want to go to the beach!
Oh yeah...
We're staying here 'cause the Cha
Cha Maru is in port for repairs.
What? Where is everyone?
Who cares?
Oh, nuts!
I've overslept!
Boing!
Mei! Nichol!
Mikhail! Balboa? Roger?
Hey, Nichol?
Jeez, they went and took
off without me again!
Hey, Tita, you lazy bum!
The rest of us are already
back at the ship!
Right!
The rest of us are already
back at the ship!
Of course, even if you were here, you
wouldn't be doing anything!
That's why we left you behind!
And one more thing. If, as usual,
you're getting up about noon,
you might as well stop and pick
up our lunch on the way in.
We'll be seeing you!
This message was brought to you
by Nichol, your brilliant pilot.
Here I go!
This message was brought to you
by Nichol, your brilliant pilot.
Whoa!
Thanks!
Whee!
Mikhail! Mikhail!
How's it coming over there?
Almost finished. And you?
Well, maybe another day or two.
By the way, where is that idiot Roger?
I don't know.
Nichol, I'm dying from hunger.
No kidding, it's way past lunchtime.
I'm going to waste away, right here.
Even you can't starve that fast!
Oh, jeez!
Guess I bought a little too much.
Come on, get in there!
Finally, everything's loaded!
What in the world?
I'm sorry!
Oh, don't worry about it. I'm all right.
I'm so sorry.
What's her hurry?
Move it!
Who were they?
Today's just not going to be my day.
Abandoned, and now my tiny
little breasts get flattened...
Let go!
Bastards!
Hop on, quickly!
But...
You're on the run, right? Come on!
Damn! Stop them!
Hang on!
Right!
A-Unit! We have failed to
apprehend the subject.
B-Unit, where the hell is C-Unit?
Use your vehicles to block number 12!
Persistent!
Hold on tight!
Damn!
Call in the divers!
I'm sorry. There was an
unexpected complication,
and we couldn't risk more assertive
action here in the city, and...
All right. But I want them found
within twenty-four hours.
Otherwise, it'll be your body they
find floating in the river.
Yes, Sir!
Something must have happened to her!
There's no way she could be this late!
The hotel said she left before noon!
It's a guy, that's what it is.
She's out doing the old "in and out"
with some good looking stud...
Roger!
That's a dirty lie!
How do you know? What makes
you so sure, Nichol?
Well, because...
In any case, it's because of
her that we're starving!
She is rather late.
All right, all right! She's always
giving us grief,
but today I'll teach her a lesson!
Tita?!
Sorry about lunch. I lost it.
What?!
Nichol! Get her some water!
Yes!
No more for me, thanks.
I've swallowed enough.
Yes!
No more for me, thanks.
I've swallowed enough.
What happened?
Who's this girl, Tita?
It's a long story.
Don't worry, this is the crew
of the Cha Cha Maru.
They're all friends.
Tita, what happened to you?
Mei! I'm fine, but can you
take a look at her?
I think she took a hit.
Here, let me see you.
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
I just want to clean your wound.
Pretty girls shouldn't have
to carry scars. Right?
From the look of things,
I'd say you've had a rather
rough day, Tita.
Okay, you're all set.
I'm glad it was nothing serious.
Thank you.
Now, can you tell us why you
were being chased?
It's possible that Tita and the rest
of us might become involved.
Is there some reason you
can't talk about it?
By the way, what is your
name anyway?
I can't keep calling you
"Hey you!", right?
C'mon, please tell me.
If you don't, I'll just have
to give you a name.
All right, Tita, take your friend
down to the bathing area
before the both of you catch
your death of cold.
Yeah, great idea!
Let's get out of our wet things and to
the Ladies Sun-Bathing Facility.
By the way, you won't believe
the bathtub we've got here!
Come on! Let's go!
C'mon, c'mon! Hurry!
But...
Did you see Tita?
Nude?
So, where's your house?
Don't you live on the island?
What are you doing?
Here.
Come on, let's go.
Well...
Just how old are you?
You could tell me your age, at least?
I'm sixteen.
Sixteen?
I'm a whole year older, but...
This is terrible!
I'm depressed. I'll never be
able to face the world.
Aw, what the hell! Let's go! Hurry up!
Yee Haw!
Boy, that was fun.
Wasn't that great?
We used up a whole containment
facility making this bathhouse!
Why did you rescue me? Who are you?
Oh, sorry, I guess I never told you.
My name's Tita Mu Koshigaya.
This ship's a pet shop hunter
and I'm its captain.
As for why I rescued you,
well, that's hard to say.
Is "I couldn't not do it," a
good enough answer?
There were a lot of soldiers
chasing me.
That's why I couldn't help myself.
I said to myself, she doesn't
look like a criminal.
Come on. Let's not do this, Roger.
This is a really bad idea.
Are you kidding? I thought you liked
Tita. Don't you want to see her?
Yeah! See!
Okay, here.
What's this? A high-pressure
sea scope!
And with it, we can see everything, no
matter how thick the steam gets.
Use it.
What are you doing?
Excuse me...
What?
Just what does a pet shop hunter do?
Well, we capture the creatures that
live in the sea of clouds,
then sell them as pets to collectors
on other planets.
It's just animals, though.
See, there're some right above us.
You...
DIE!
I'm sorry about that.
Everything's fine now.
Those people are strange.
Really? Nah, just perverted and stupid.
I'm sorry.
I'm too quick to jump to conclusions.
My name is Elysse.
Elysse Aldo Mordish.
Elysse... That's a nice name.
Did you find anything?
Take a look at this.
What?
What happened?
It's about that big accident
five days ago.
Look at the one underneath.
"Military sources confirmed that
lab supervisor Professor Nalerof
Aldo Mordish and his daughter,
Elysse Aldo Mordish, perished
as a result of the accident."
What's that picture?!
That's a girl who's supposed
to be dead,
and the military's involved as well.
Am I the only one who smells
something nasty?
There's something going on.
Does Tita know?
I don't think so.
Great! We made it in time!
Look.
Gorgeous! I've never seen a
more beautiful sunrise.
That's cool!
Let's have breakfast now. I'm famished!
Yeah!
Balboa, your hunch was right.
The military are sniffing their
way across the harbor,
like they can scent Tita and Elysse.
That's not good. What if
they're already there?
Balboa, Tita's at Windmill Hill. Hurry!
Got it!
What's going on?
I don't know.
That was good.
I'm very glad.
I haven't enjoyed myself this
much in quite a while.
Not being out at sea was
starting to get me blue.
You like the sea more than the land?
Of course I do! I'm a pet
shop hunter after all!
Chasing cloud whales across
the sea of clouds is my life!
...and then Nichol got himself stung
by the cloud jelly snake!
He touched it with his bare hand
and was numb for two hours!
But why do the job at all,
Tita? I mean...
Chalk it up to my father's influence.
He was a pet shop hunter too.
With this same crew.
Was?
He went out one day when I was
about six. He never came back.
They said it was an accident.
There was a major malfunction
in the engine section.
He saved everyone by jettisoning it,
with himself inside.
He vanished into the sea of clouds.
We searched for about a year, but
under those circumstances...
But you don't believe
he's dead, do you?
What? I'm not sure, but...
Sometimes I get the feeling part of him
is still out there, somewhere.
I guess that's why I do what I do.
I hope I can learn to feel that way.
I think I like you, Tita.
What the? That's...
An armored assault craft!
Look out!
Get me there in time!
Too late!
Tita! Where are you? Tita!
Damn! They're in the city!
I'm sorry, Tita.
What?
I'm sorry I got an innocent bystander
caught up in this.
I'm not a bystander!
Don't worry about it!
Lousy bastards!
Tita, listen to me.
One week ago, there was an accident
in a laboratory section
at the base of the colony.
In actuality, a terrible weapon
attached to the gravity belts
was activated.
Tell me about this later.
I've got to tell you now!
That accident was caused by my
father, Nalerof Aldo Mordish.
This colony is kept afloat
in the sea of clouds
by gravity belts supplied by the I.D.P.
For the last ten years,
the military has been developing
new uses for those belts,
while keeping the information from
the civilian government.
My father, a scientist, was
employed by the military.
He'd already completed his research
when he realized the truth.
His dream of making a better
life for everyone
had been twisted into a monstrous
weapon by Guizel.
Then my father...
Destroyed the weapon and helped
you escape. Right, Elysse?
Then, where's your father now?
He's dead. The military killed him.
I'm sorry, Tita. We couldn't bring
your father back with us.
I understand.
Tita, let me off now!
I can't let you do this!
Tita, you're the first friend
I've ever had!
And you're my friend.
Because you're my friend, I'm not
going to let you give up!
Elysse, I'll protect you!
Tita...
Was that...
You've led me on quite a chase.
Now, give me the password.
I don't know anything
about a password!
All right then. Let me
jog your memory.
Elysse, tell me now or else...
Stop! I really don't know!
Stop it!
Tita! Tita!
Her hunter-suit's a good one.
Even more bulletproof than
the military versions,
but what about her internal organs?
Stop, please!
Now do you remember the password?
I really don't know the password!
I have to do an analysis first.
If I could go back to the lab...
And in return, you expect
me to spare her?
All right, but I want to know
the procedure now.
Don't tell him.
Tita!
You're dead as soon as you talk.
I'm sorry.
Land the assault craft.
The password for reactivating the
gravity destruction weapon
is the last twelve digits produced
by an analysis of my DNA
using the BRG exchange method.
Tita!
Liar! You said you'd spare her!
So sorry.
Tita! Tita!
TITA!
What?
Tita!
A smoke screen?
Tita! Elysse!
A pet shop hunter?
Balboa, a bomb just went
off at the hotel.
This'll be the next place to get
torched. How's Tita?
Old man, we can't stay any longer,
the ceiling will go any second!
Mikhail, go on, get out of there!
I'll bring these two!
Got it!
It's all right.
None of her internal organs were
ruptured, fortunately.
It's all my fault. All mine...
Don't worry yourself over it.
Tita is going to be all right.
Don't die. Don't die, Tita!
Mei, is Tita... Is Tita okay?
She'll be all right, but
she's sleeping now.
Go ahead, keep an eye on Tita for me.
Thank you!
Call me if anything happens.
Tita...
How's Tita?
She's doing fine.
I see. That's good.
And now, Miss Elysse, I think it's
time you tell us everything.
Yes!
You can wake up now, Elysse.
How'd it go? Did you find anything?
Yes, but it will take a little time.
I see.
Where are you going?
I need some air.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mikhail.
I was just staring at the clouds.
So, what's the story?
What do you think?
About what?
About Tita.
She's like her father.
That's not what I'm talking about!
What are you asking?
This whole thing. What happened
to Tita and the rest of us...
It's all just too much.
Our job is hunting animals.
We're not professional soldiers.
Tita just hasn't figured it out yet.
You used to be in the military,
didn't you?
If you're getting cold feet,
why are you still here?
Why'd you bother coming back at all?
Old man...
Listen to this!
Now, if you can't believe
in the captain,
get the hell off this ship!
Hold it! That's not what I said!
But we're up against military
professionals.
There's no second chance, and if
Tita is killed, it's all over.
I won't let that happen.
Even if the cost is our lives,
I'll never let Tita die.
Ouch!
Twice in one day!
You bastard!
Tita... Don't die, Tita...
Nichol... He stood watch,
all through the night.
Thank you.
Tita! You shouldn't be up yet!
It's okay. I feel fine!
Tita!
Tita?
Miss?
Sorry I had you all worried.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah! Top of the world! I feel
like I can do anything!
Tita, what's our next
move going to be?
Mei's already clued me in.
We're going to take these bastards on,
and pay them back with interest!
One hundred times!
Yeah! Let's do it, Tita!
Tita...
Come on, Elysse!
Let's do it for your father!
Tita...
If my dad were alive, he'd
have done the same.
Right! Everyone take your positions!
Aye aye, Sir!
Come on!
Ready to jump ship, Balboa?
Everybody on this tub is
out of their mind.
What?
Myself included.
Looks like I've fallen under
Tita's spell as well.
You won't die alone.
When we break into Heaven,
I'll take the point.
Thanks.
What? Tita? Where is she?
Hey! Tita!
You're getting slow, Nichol!
Tita!
Prepare to submerge!
What? We're diving?
Just a duel with the military.
Say what?!
Sonar response! Target vessel
cruising in at point 0-6522.
It must be the Cha Cha Maru, Sir.
All ships, go to cruising depth.
Standard pursuit formation.
Going to cruising depth.
Block 8, partition C-2, partition D-1,
Block 2, partition B-2 closed!
It looks bad, Tita. The ship
can't take any more.
Right!
Come on, Elysse!
What?!
You're committing yourself
to certain death, Tita!
What?!
You're committing yourself
to certain death, Tita!
But the Cha Cha Maru
can't get any closer,
our best bet for stopping that thing
is through the upper levels!
We'll go, then!
Wait! The Cha Cha Maru can't
function without you, Balboa,
and right now I'm about as useful
as a fifth wheel! So...
But...
Please, let me do this! I've got
to take care of it myself.
But...
Please, let me do this! I've got
to take care of it myself.
Do you swear you'll come back?
Really come back?
All right, go!
Until you get back, we'll defend
this ship with our lives!
Thanks!
Tita, be careful.
Nichol, let's kick some military butt!
You must be joking!
Hurry, hurry!
Prepare the low-pressure pulse net,
Nichol! Maximum output!
Starboard side, simultaneous operation:
eject floater gyro,
and launch a thermal limpet from
the lower tyrail hatch!
All right, fire!
Showtime!
This isn't good. We can't
get any nearer
to the control room with
all this security.
Oh yeah, in the gravity-reactor section
there should be emergency sub-panels
every 150 feet or so.
We should be able to disengage
the device from there.
How do we get there?
Through the ventilation ducts.
Okay, let's go.
Commander, we're about to finish
inputting the password.
Good. As soon as it's ready, set the
parameters to the city levels.
Yes, Sir!
What's the status on those
damned intruders?
Yes, Sir!
What's the status on those
damned intruders?
We lost track of them ten minutes ago.
We're making every attempt
to find them, Sir.
Ten minutes? Is it possible?
Where are we?
This is the colony's core,
where the reactor that feeds the
gravity belts is housed.
We're on the underside of
a giant spinning top,
whose axis extends over 25 kilometers
from top to bottom.
From this emergency sub-panel,
which leads to the main panel
in the control room,
we should be able to access the
gravity destruction weapon.
Password input accepted.
Diffusion attract to be activated at
target point plus 100 meters.
All workers are to complete their
assignments and leave the area.
I can't do it from this terminal.
What do we try now?
Wait a second!
Got it!
There's a terminal 200 meters below us
that should accept the emergency
disengage password.
Look out, Elysse!
Bastard!
I guess we don't have time
to debate the issue.
Commander, we have an
activation on laser 252!
It could be the intruders!
Now we have them!
Redirect the troops in blocks 3 and 4
to the gravity reactor area.
I'm going too.
Wow! It won't stop!
Please stop... stop!
Stop! Oh, please!
That was cutting it close,
don't you think?
Oh well... Hold on tight, Elysse!
Hurry!
Hold it right there, little mice.
Damn! Just one more step...
You brats have caused us a great
deal of inconvenience,
especially for a pet shop hunter.
I just wanted to make sure you
got what's coming to you!
How stupid can you be?
You'll live just long enough
to regret defying me.
Balboa, the gravity belt!
You didn't make it, Tita?
What are we going to do, Balboa?
The ship's falling apart!
We can only wait.
In just a few minutes,
the people in the city levels
will begin to die.
And, knowing so much about it,
you'll have to die as well.
Shoot the intruders!
Elysse, get down!
We're saved!
Elysse!
You were hit?
It's nothing. How about you, Tita?
I'm all right.
Now you brats have really
gone and done it.
I'll take care of Guizel.
In the meantime, you input
the password, Elysse.
Okay.
Don't move, Guizel!
I'm not letting you get away
with this, you bastard!
How very humorous!
How could you have hoped
to overcome me?
Tita!
Password...
Hurry, Elysse!
You go first!
Three!
Two!
One!
ZERO!
Tita!
You can do it, Tita!
Thanks, Elysse.
I thought you were dead!
Diffusion attract password
has been inputted.
Tita...
To disengage, depress the G-button
within three hundred seconds,
Go ahead and push the button.
To disengage, depress the G-button
within three hundred seconds,
But this is...
To disengage, depress the G-button
within three hundred seconds,
Tita, this is happening because of you.
To disengage, depress the G-button
within three hundred seconds,
Tita, this is happening because of you.
as described in the guidelines.
I'm here because of you, Tita, so...
But... No way!
Please, do it with your own hand, Tita!
Dad, it's over. It's all over now.
Thank you, Tita.
Okay! Let's get back to the ship!
Right!
It's over, right?
Yeah, it's over.
Okay! Let's leave the
military in the dust!
Let's run away!
Roger!
What?! His excellency,
Guizel, is dead?
We'll be up to our hips in it if the
Government finds out!
This could be trouble.
All ships! Battle stations!
Target that hunting ship
directly ahead!
Don't let them get out of here alive!
Begin firing!
Tita, they're shooting at us.
1,205 homing lasers, 3,852 torpedoes!
Okay! Engage the main engines!
Forward full power to coordinate 125!
Let's go right through them!
Balboa! I'll be needing a simultaneous
launch of the number 4 pulsenet!
Let's rock!
Did we get them?
Shoot! Shoot!
But, Sir...
I don't give a damn! Destroy
that ship no matter what!
150 meters to fleet.
Take her in, full throttle!
This is insane! Dodging bullets
in the middle of a fleet!
I won't let you live!
Old man!
Are you all right?
Idiot! Never leave your position.
Are you mad?
Tita, the engines will blow
if you keep this up!
But...
Tita, the distance between them and
us is getting pretty small!
What can I do?
It's a one in a million chance, but...
Roger, in one minute... No, in thirty
seconds, give me full power!
I can't!
Go ahead, Tita!
Mikhail!
Let us take care of it.
Okay! Nichol!
I know!
You want me to set a course
for that whirlpool, right?
Go in from point 102, riding
the current to the center.
Balboa, I want all the ship's energy
focused through the main forward
radar assembly!
We're inducing a temporary shutdown
of the main engine limiters!
Hang on to your seats!
What are you doing? After them!
Stop the engine!
Let the current take her to the
center of the whirlpool!
Balboa, on my signal,
release all the energy through
the pulse radar assembly!
What?! The ship will...
Oh, I get it! There is a way...
Got it!
We're lined up on axis!
Countdown, five seconds!
Got it!
We're lined up on axis!
Countdown, five seconds!
FIRE!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Fire!
Mei, could you take a look
at my wounds too?
Can't you wait just a moment, Mikhail?
There, all done.
Thank you, Mei.
You and Tita ought to be more
careful with your bodies.
That scar may not fade completely.
That's all right. I'd like to keep it.
It's sort of like a medal of honor.
Whatever! I give up!
Tita...
Elysse?
It's beautiful.
Yeah, a gorgeous sunset.
Can I ask you something, Tita?
What?
Why? Why did you do all this for me?
Guizel and the gravity belts weren't
the most important part.
There was something I liked about
you the first time we met.
I just wanted to be your friend, Elysse.
When I looked at you,
I saw the same look I saw in my eyes,
five years ago.
The look of a girl who's just
lost her father.
I guess that's it.
I didn't want you to end up
like me, Elysse,
never quite able to get over it.
Hey, Elysse...
Would you like to stay on this ship?
You could join the crew, we could
be together. Well?
No, I think I'll go back to the island.
Like you, Tita, I've inherited
something from my father.
I want to build a gravity belt that
will really benefit civilization.
So...
Yeah, you're right.
Man, does that mean someday
I'm going to have to deal with this
whole stupid business again?
All right! If that's how it's
going to be, Elysse,
let's have a going away party!
The time is 20:46. The period of
emergency has passed...
The one who's closest to my heart
I chose in my young innocence
I love to see your soft face beside me
I'm so happy and I'm so glad
That I have lived this life of mine
It's been enough just
to have known you
I'm on top of the world
I feel I could do anything
I set my heart upon
If you asked, I could ride on the wind
You are everything
There's no other person like you
You're totally irreplaceable to me
Pull me against the firmness
of your sweet breast
I want to be the one
Who's the only one for you
I'm on top of the world
I feel I could do anything
I set my heart upon
If you asked, I could ride on the wind
You are everything
If we believe in ourselves
And the sweet bonds
that tie us invisibly
We can make it all work if we just try
You are everything
There's no other person like you
You're totally irreplaceable to me
Pull me against the firmness
of your sweet breast
I want to be the one
Who's the only one for you
You are everything
If we believe in ourselves
And the sweet bonds
that tie us invisibly
We can make it all work if we just try
You are everything
There's no other person like you
You're totally irreplaceable to me
Pull me against the firmness
of your sweet breast
This may be my ocean
But I'll share it with you