You must be the
leader of the Demon Clan...
...who is destroying
the Laan Continent.
Indeed.
How dare you attack me during the
30th anniversary celebration of my reign!
It's my pleasure to attack your
kingdom on such a memorable day.
I won't allow you to
invade my beloved land!
Prepare to die!
Father!
Mother!
I will not take your life.
Yes, sir.
All right?
Report to the princess in Asronia.
I'll run as though my life depended on it!
I'm counting on you.
No need for that.
W-Who are you?
Now that we're here, you
don't need to send anybody.
Send?
Where is Yonus?
I found him.
I see the land owned by
our Demon King is expanding.
What a great view.
The continent called Laan has
been peaceful for over a hundred years.
Ever since many small independent
countries formed a united confederation.
However, the peace was broken...
...by a mysterious army consisting
of dragons, swordsmen, and sorcerers.
Especially a group called the Shadow
Clan, known for its fast movement...
Those countries that could not
defend themselves against air attacks...
...were gradually
invaded and taken over.
The leader, known as the Demon
Dragon, dresses in all black armor...
...and has become
known as the King of Horror.
Step back.
Yes, ma'am.
Princess Yurie, be
careful of the dew on the grass.
You always talk as
if you're my older sister.
I apologize.
It's all right.
We've grown up
together just like sisters.
Princess, you're so
thin, yet so feminine.
What are you doing?
We're attending the 30th anniversary
cerebration for the king of Gostaria.
It's a very special occasion.
You should dress accordingly, right?
See, you look nice like this.
I'm just a bodyguard.
Don't you like to dress up nicely?
I know you do, every girl does.
Yes.
I want everybody to celebrate.
The citizen's happiness
is my own happiness.
Yes.
I have an idea.
Let's put these flowers on
the other guard's costumes, too.
No, it's time to go.
I'm sure Prince Elias is
looking forward to seeing you.
Prince Elias...
You two will bring Asronia and
Gostaria together and rule them happily.
All the citizens of our countries,
including me, are waiting for that day.
You're mean.
Dragons!
A flock of Dragons!
Be careful.
Get into a fighting formation.
Yes!
Why are they here?
Princess, the carriage...
Someone is riding it.
I didn't know that was possible!
There was a tribe once called the Shutaam
and they used to have power to do that.
Shutaam?
Your highness, lower your head!
The Shutaam were
extinguished a long time ago.
Who are they?
Your Highness!
I'm all right.
How's everyone else?
Princess, please stay here.
That's the emblem of
the Demon Dragon King.
Don't come any closer, you bastards!
Maya, behind you!
I see it!
How many are there?
Princess!
A ninja, huh?
Very interesting.
Who are you?
How dare you attack
Princess Yurie of Asronia!
She's the princess...
Not really my type, but I'll take her.
I won't let you!
Damn you!
Oh, this is your technique.
What?
Cute.
I like that in a woman.
Maya!
Unfortunately, I don't
have much time now.
Maya!
What did you do to Maya?
Princess Yurie, come with us.
Take your hands off of me!
How dare you!
The Demon Dragon King is
waiting for you at Castle Esten.
Castle Esten?
Has Gostaria fallen to the
Demon Dragon King's hand?
The Demon Dragon King!
I knew it.
Let me go!
I can't let the princess go with them.
Maya!
P-Princess Yurie!
Leave me alone!
Let me go!
Traveling in the sky can
be dangerous, so be quiet.
We are going back!
Castle Esten.
Are you awake?
It's awful.
Oh, no.
I feel a dirty gaze from somewhere.
I have brought Princess
Yurie of Asronia Kingdom.
Princess Yurie, welcome to my castle.
He's the Demon Dragon King.
What?
The princess has been kidnapped
by the Demon Dragon King?
Oh, my God.
Hang on, Roletta.
Maya, did you actually
see the Flying Dragon clan?
Yes, I saw the Rose and
Skull emblem with my own eyes.
I should not have let
you take care of the princess.
What are you going to do about this?
Do with my body as you wish.
I'm very impressed.
Make up for your failure with your life!
Hold it, Gooseman.
Maya's death will not
bring the princess back.
But, Your Majesty...
Yurie's guard had to be Maya.
When Yurie was a
little girl, she was very shy...
...and didn't trust anyone except Maya.
I am your new bodyguard.
My name is Maya.
I'm at your disposal.
Really?
Then be my big sister.
Promise me, Maya.
Excuse me, sir.
What is it?
The Flying Dragon Clan has
allegedly invaded the Hita Village.
What!
The Demon Dragon King is a ruthless
conqueror who's invaded many lands.
Gooseman, I'm counting on you.
Yes sir, I'll leave right away.
Maya, you must bring our
princess back no matter what.
Don't come back alive without the princess.
Yes, I swear on my soul.
Please be patient, Princess Yurie.
I swear to save you.
I swear!
Beautiful...
Is this man really
the Demon Dragon King?
Are you surprised, Princess?
I haven't revealed
myself for a long time.
Please, take a seat.
Oh, that hides my aura from my
enemies so they won't find my true identity.
Are you really the Demon Dragon King?
When we're alone,
please call me Andreas.
Andreas?
Right.
No, Demon Dragon King...
I would like to ask you something.
About the royal family
of the Gostaria kingdom?
Yes, I killed them.
We demanded their surrender
but they chose death to obedience.
Both the King and Queen.
What happened to the other people?
Oh yes, of course, their two children...
...Princess Denise and Prince Elias.
Of course they are alive.
I don't like meaningless killing.
Where are they now?
Would you like some hot soup?
No thank you.
So how are they?
Lady Denise!
Princess Yurie!
You idiot!
You spilled the soup!
Please forgive my rudeness.
Lick it up.
Yes, Mistress Karla, my pleasure.
Lady Denise...
She decided to
become my pleasure slave.
Pleasure slave?
Yes.
She's not allowed to
speak when you talk to her.
I'm so sorry.
Don't move so slow!
You're dismissed when you're done.
Prince Elias...
Where is Prince Elias?
Don't worry, he's fine.
Oh, you were
engaged to him, weren't you?
Please let me see him.
It's up to you.
But first, you'll have to accept my offer.
Your offer?
Yes.
I've taken a great risk to kidnap
you to aid my conquering Asronia.
Therefore, you are now my property.
Don't come any closer.
I'll not be your hostage.
If I am to be your property,
I'd rather bite my tongue and die!
I see.
That's up to you, but
take a look at this first.
This is one of the
villages in Asronia, called Hita.
Die, all those who disgrace my Asronia!
Gooseman!
Oh, is he the famous
spear fighter, Sir Gooseman?
But he's not our enemy.
Now, Princess, this is the highlight.
Do you see those girls
who are about your age?
No!
Shut up!
Stop it!
What are you going to do them?
Maybe you don't know, but that
is made from the dried Maldo tree.
That induces sexual stimulation.
Are you humiliating
those girls because of me?
Aren't you going to watch it, princess?
You can hear their voices of joy.
No, stop it!
Please, stop it...
Stop, please stop it!
Don't worry, they're not suffering.
It's about time for the
Maldo to start working.
My body is getting paralyzed.
What's wrong, Princess Yurie?
Are you envious of them?
Please turn it off.
They will be
enjoying it until the morning.
This is just the beginning.
What will happen to them afterwards?
After being humiliated
by your barbarous soldiers?
The flying dragons
get hungry, you know.
That's terrible, just terrible!
Then...
...you'll agree to be mine?
No...
What is this strange feeling?
You can't do this...
Well, until you say yes, I will take
each village in your country, one by one.
Oh, my body is getting hot!
L-I don't care what happens to me.
So please let those girls go.
All right, so show me some proof.
Impressive, Master Andreas.
He's taking her body already.
I wonder if that's the
woman the master told us about.
I know how you're feeling inside.
Look how wet your underwear is.
P-Please don't say that.
No!
I want you to take off the rest.
That's enough!
I beg you.
I can't do it anymore.
That's fine, you don't
care about your people.
That's...
Then, take it off.
No, I can't.
You're giving me a hard time.
What?
No!
You asked for it.
This is so humiliating.
You just need to obey me.
Accept me.
You are the only one
who can save your country...
...and Prince Elias.
Lord Elias...
Yes, it's all up to you.
If you obey me, I will let you see him.
Don't be afraid.
Now...
It feels warm...
His lips, his body.
Why, why do I feel so warm all over?
No!
You have such a beautiful breasts.
I'm so aroused.
D-Don't do that anymore.
No!
Please don't touch me like that.
If you continue, I'll be...
Oh?
You're so wet.
Don't say such things.
You've never done this before?
I know you are an innocent princess.
Please stop now.
You will want more soon.
You shouldn't go down there.
Yes, I should.
You are so beautiful.
I can't take this...
Sir Gooseman!
Maya?
Why are you here?
Where are my soldiers?
I'm sorry.
You saved me?
I don't appreciate it.
You should be somewhere else.
I'm sorry, sir.
I have no clue how
to save the princess.
The Flying Dragon Clan...
What a horrible enemy.
But we have to imagine what kind of
pain the princess is going through now.
I'm all right.
I can return to the castle on my own.
Don't hesitate!
Go!
Yes, sir!
Much obliged, Maya.
You are the only hope for our princess.
Save our princess!
I now grant this medal of
honor to Commander Gooseman.
Keep up your good
efforts for Asronia, Gooseman.
Oh, no!
Lord Andreas!
It's so good, Andreas!
Now, let's begin, Yurie.
We will become one.
I can't do that, I can't!
Don't be scared.
Leave everything to me.
Yurie, I'm coming inside of you.
I've been waiting for
this moment for a long time.
I can feel you
squeezing me so passionately!
D-Don't say such things.
I feel his shape, size, and movement!
No!
Yurie, is it good?
L-I'm coming, I'm coming!
My soul is being blown away.
Somebody, help me!
Release everything that is you!
Awaken your feelings!
No!
Where am I?
I'm not scared.
I feel so comfortable here...
What's going on?
I knew it.
Lady Roletta, please stop.
Lady Roletta, please.
She looks good in this dress.
Oh, I should also bring this.
Lady Roletta, please
pull yourself together!
The King is going to the battle of Hita,
we don't know about the princes yet.
What did you say?
So, we're not going to the princess.
Oh, no...
We shall defeat the
Flying Dragon Clan at Hita!
Yes, sir!
Commander Gooseman has arrived.
Gooseman.
I can stand on my own, let me go.
Yes, sir.
I'm glad that you are still alive.
Your majesty, I would like to report.
In your condition, you
shouldn't be speaking right now.
This dawn, the Flying Dragon
Clan has left the Village of Hita.
What?
The Demon Dragon King's
invasion plan seems to be postponed.
Why, why now?
B-Because...
The princess?
Yurie saved us?
That is...
Somebody, take care of Gooseman!
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry, Yurie.
With this size army, we can't
rescue you from Castle Esten.
Looks like you have some appetite.
Where's Andreas?
Can you hear the soldiers' voices?
Put your voices together!
The power of the Flying Dragon Clan!
That's our oath of battle!
We fight until the
world is painted in blood!
In the name of Shutaam!
In the name of Shutaam.
The Demon Dragon King is going to kill
the rebel army in the Gostaria mountains.
There are still some fools
left who would oppose us.
Then what
happened to the Hita village?
He kept his word.
He left that area.
This isn't good enough.
I must clear my mind.
Otherwise, I can't beat that sorcerer.
Oh no, I'm having that same feeling.
Why can't I forget that woman?
Princess, please be safe.
You look tired.
Master Andreas
must have worn you out.
What are you doing?
It's all right, Princess.
I was told to train
you by Master Andreas.
Do you think I like serving you?
Honestly, I would kill you if I could.
But if I did, my master would kill me.
Well, I really wouldn't mind that.
Don't worry.
But I will do this!
Stop that...
You swallowed the
master's energy from here.
Yes...
So how many times did you enjoy it?
No!
Answer me!
T-Two times.
Oh, my.
I just touched you a little
and you're already so hot.
Please stop.
You're not getting off so easily.
Now, bath time is over.
Princess, please be patient.
I'm coming to rescue you soon.
Look at it.
That's impossible.
So, surprised?
Master Andreas did it for me.
Isn't it wonderful?
That's impossible.
Now, I want you to
taste this cute little thing.
I can't do that.
I can chop off your head anytime!
Yes.
Hurry up.
Oh, this feeling...
This feeling...
Very good.
Like that.
That's right...
Straighten your throat.
Widen your mouth and suck harder...
You are pleased, aren't you?
This is used to be my brother's,
to whom I dedicated my virginity.
No!
Brother, open your eyes!
Please!
One more time...
Hold me one more time!
When he died in battle, the Demon
Dragon King saw how depressed I was.
So he transplanted it for
me with his magical power.
Maybe she and Andreas
still have some humanity left.
That's...
Don't do it on your own!
I just want you to enjoy it more.
Very good.
If you understand,
let's go one step further.
You know what you need to do.
No.
Put this inside of you by yourself.
I can't do that.
You disobey me?
I know you want me.
What a look on your face.
That must drive master Andreas crazy.
Don't you want it now?
Yes.
Then, do it now.
Good.
You're so tight.
Go on, move yourself.
Yes.
Good, it's so good.
That's the way.
I'm coming!
That's my princess.
She's not been released yet?
The rebel army
numbers about two hundred.
Instead of going around the mountain,
shouldn't we go straight to the seaside?
What do you think, sir?
I leave it to you.
Yurie, open yourself and come to me.
Where?
Where are you taking me?
You were very obedient to my
training, so I will give you a reward.
A reward?
Here we are.
You can do it as usual.
What, what's going on?
Don't be so slow!
Another person?
Hey, lick this woman's toe.
Yes, master Karla.
That voice.
If you don't obey, this guy will get hurt.
Unless, you like others
to get hurt because of you.
It's so good that you
are such a merciful slut.
How about some appreciation?
Yes, thank you very much.
That voice.
I can't believe this!
Hey, don't you want to see his face?
Stop this!
That's enough, please.
That voice can't be...
What a reunion!
N-No!
Princess Yurie!
Lord Elias...
How about reuniting as
slaves after being engaged?
Please, don't humiliate
me in front of the princess.
Elias, don't be shy before her.
Please forgive him.
I'm sorry.
I'm so ashamed to
have you see me like this.
At least now I know that you're alive.
You two make me want to cry.
Now, let's begin.
I will let you enjoy each other.
That's...
See, he can get ready
as soon as I touch him.
Oh, master Karla.
Don't you want him?
Don't you?
Princess Yurie!
No!
Somebody, somebody, help me!
Demon Dragon King!
Andreas!
Sorry.
I need it for now.
Move on!
We've got enough enemies!
Keep fighting them!
Follow our king, we are
stronger than our enemies.
Open yourself to me, Yurie!
Release your soul!
I have to serve Lord
Andreas in order to live...