Princess 69 - Midnight
Gymnastics Vol. 1
Sis!
Miku-nee, wake up! lt's me, Fubuki!
What did you think of my performance?
How many points would you give me?
Sis...
Well? Are you surprised?
This is the ''Midnight Gymnastics.''
''Midnight Gymnastics?''
''Midnight Gymnastics...''
Women compete by displaying their beauty and sluttiness.
lt's a secret event that's more extreme than...
...your regular gymnastics event.
What exactly is that?
Ordinary people like you wouldn't know about it.
Celebrities like myself are the only ones who can view these events.
But l really feel sorry for Miku.
Tomomi-san, what happened to Miku-nee?
Miku was training very hard everyday.
But she was caught by the darkness of Midnight Gymnastics.
Darkness?
l couldn't tell this to anyone.
That's why l'm taking care of her at this mansion.
l understand.
Thank you so much.
l was worried since she disappeared all of a sudden.
But l didn't know she was in such a mess.
ls she going to be okay?
There's only one way to save Miku, but it will be difficult for you.
Please tell me! What should l do?
l'll do anything to save my sister.
l can withstand anything.
l see. Then take your clothes off.
What?
Take off all your clothes!
What's wrong?
You're willing to do anything right?
Take your hands out of the way.
But...
Hurry!
Not bad for a cute-looking guy like yourself.
Ouch!
Hey Miku, take a look at this.
That...
l want that too...
Sis...
l really want this..
Stop it, Sis!
Don't worry about it. lt's not like you two are related by blood.
You two are not related, right?
But, but...
Tomomi-san...
l'm coming...
l'm coming, Sis...
Sis!
l can't believe you're still hard.
How does it feel?
lt feels so good, l think l'm gonna melt.
Me too...
l'm coming, l'll climax...
Tomomi-san...
Do it. Release it inside me!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Fubuki Haneoka, l'm appointing you to be the coach of Midnight Gymnastics.
This is Miku-nee's...
l want you to teach them a lesson as their coach.
And find out how to rescue your sister from the darkness.
That's the only way.
l understand.
l'll do it!
l'm Tomomi Shirakawa, daughter of the head of Shirakawa enterprises.
Shirakawa Academy, that my grandfather has established...
...was designed specifically for me.
l can do whatever l want.
So l can get Miku's younger brother...
...Fubuki into the school dressed up like a girl.
Midnight Gymnastics...
l already had a target, Koyuki Fujimiya.
She has talent.
l'm sure of it.
Ouch!
You're very stiff, Haneoka!
l'm not used to gymnastics.
l doubt that.
You're a tomboy, Haneoka.
We don't see people like you in gymnastics...
Of course we don't.
She's a guy.
What are you saying?
lt's weird that she has no boobs.
So what?
lt's better to have small boobs in gymnastics.
Right? Haneoka-san?
You two boobless girls get along well, huh?
What did you say?
You!
Excuse me...
But why is Koyuki-chan doing nothing?
Other girls dislike her.
Why?
The Manager's followers think she's associated with Shirakawa-san.
When the manager's not here, they all treat her bad.
But that's just wrong!
Haneoka-san!
Hey, it's starting to get interesting.
Please let Fujimiya-san practice!
What did you say?
That's none of your business newbie.
But she's one of your members.
She's one of Shirakawa-san's.
Do whatever you want.
l will.
Let's go.
But if you do this, you will...
lt's okay.
Way to go Haneoka-san!
That was cool!
Yep, only if she had bigger boobs.
Thank you.
Now let's practice.
You're very kind.
Tomomi-san!
But you're dying to use this right?
Not here...
What's wrong?
Tell her you're getting hard.
l can't!
Nothing. Carry on.
This is bad...
What's wrong with her?
l think she's not feeling well.
Fubuki-chan?
Did you throw up?
Yeah, but l'm okay now.
Take it easy.
Why don't you lie down?
l'll wash it for you.
Koyuki-chan...
What's wrong?
l'm sorry for making you wash that.
lt's okay. You helped me out earlier.
See? lt's all clean.
Thanks.
This leotard was used by this academy not too long ago.
Yeah, it's my sister's.
Your sister was into gymnastics too?
ls she still doing it?
Well, she's kind of sick right now...
l'm sorry, l shouldn't have asked.
You don't have to apologize.
Tomomi-san didn't come to practice today either.
She's a genius, so she doesn't need any practice.
Tomomi-san's a genius?
She told me.
l'm sure she is.
There's Tomomi-san.
Who are they?
Her fans.
Fans?
From her fan club.
l don't really know the details, but l heard she has lots of fans...
...from several different schools.
l didn't know she was so popular.
She's pretty and good at gymnastics, but she seems lonely.
What?
Nothing.
lf you need anything, just let me know.
l will.
You know Fubuki-chan, l...
What?
Well, see you tomorrow.
Attention please.
Fubuki Haneoka of the gymnastics club.
Please come to the principal's office.
Excuse me.
l'm Fubuki Haneoka.
You're late.
Tomomi-san? What are you doing here?
My grandfather is the principal of this academy.
This is his room, so this room belongs to me.
Got it?
What?
You don't feel comfortable being in a small classroom right?
But...
Never mind that!
What's going on with Koyuki Fujimiya?
Nothing l'm afraid.
But l can't see how she has the talent...
...to compete in the ''Midnight Gymnastics.''
What about Miku? Was she talented?
Then mind your own business.
Yes.
But you need a break once in a while.
You saw it didn't you?
No, it's just...
Get up here.
But what if someone comes in?
l told you this is my room, you chicken.
Principal's Office
lt looks funny every time.
What a weirdo.
What do you want to do?
l want to stick it inside you.
Stupid!
Ouch!
Remember what you're doing.
You're saving Miku, right?
l know.
You masturbate by thinking of me right?
Well, l...
Tell me the truth.
You think of me when you masturbate.
Yes, l think of you when l masturbate.
And how many times do you masturbate each day?
Twice.
Then l wonder how many times you'll masturbate today...
Since this will be your first one.
Okay, we're done.
Make sure to clean that up.
And make sure to clean this room everyday.
Tomomi-san.
What is it?
l saw you the other day at the station.
Where did you go when you were skipping practice?
Mind your own business.
Tomomi-san...
The movie l saw the other day was really good.
No, stop it!
That's Tomomi-san!
Who are you people?
We used to be part of Tomomi's fan club, but we just quit.
l was pissed off by her attitude.
She's so cute!
Look at those nice white panties!
No!
Let me see your tits!
Smells good!
No!
Stop!
Stop it!
l'm begging you!
Stop! Stop it, stop it!
Koyuki-chan!
Let me go!
Hey, this one's a male!
Really?
Let's take a look!
What the hell?
He's dressed like a girl and goes to an all-girls' school?
Stupid!
Fubuki-chan...
Hey, let's have this guy rape that girl!
A pervert sneaks into a prestigious academy and rapes a fellow student!
This scandal will be great!
Why should l do such a thing?
lf you don't do it, then we will.
Smells good!
Stop, stop...
Fubuki!
You really want these animals to violate Fujimiya?
Tomomi-san...
lf you think about it, it's better for her to be raped by you than them!
But these guys know who l am.
We can take care of that using my family's connections!
But you won't be able to take away her emotional pain!
What are you waiting for? Hurry!
You're willing to do it now?
Koyuki-chan...
Ready?
l'm coming, l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
Good job!
Tomomi-san...
What is this?
You wouldn't make a move, so l just simply helped you.
What? You tricked me?
What are you saying?
l'm just worried since l felt you forgot about Miku!
What?
You do it when you have to.
That's what l expected from a coach of ''Midnight Gymnastics''...
l was never wrong about you.
Fujimiya-san, you're going to help us too, right?
You can't say no, since l have this.
l'm the leading actress in this world.
The rest of them are just supporting actors.
l have the power to do anything l want.
Even the things that are going to happen from here on.
Hey, stop slacking off!
Koyuki-chan!
You helped me out twice already.
Twice?
First, you helped me from the other bullying members.
Second, what you did the other day...
But l raped you...
l'm glad you did it.
lf you didn't, those men would've.
But...
You did what you had to do.
l'm sorry l pretended to be a girl.
l still can't believe it... That you were a boy.
l was very surprised.
But now, l feel very determined.
What?
l was asked by Shirakawa-san if l wanted to take part in ''Midnight Gymnastics''
At the time, l didn't know what it was, so l refused since l was scared.
Tomomi-san likes you, Koyuki-chan.
What about you, Fubuki-chan?
What?
Do you like me?
Yeah, from the first time l saw you.
Thanks.
lf l'm with you Fubuki-chan...
But Koyuki-chan...
lt's okay, l've already decided.
You have your reasons for coming here dressed up like a girl, right?
Does it have something to do with your sick sister?
lf l can solve your problems by participating, l'll do it.
l'll do Midnight Gymnastics.
Koyuki-chan...
l like you Fubuki-chan.
lf you take part in Midnight Gymnastics, there's no going back.
Plus if you're caught by the darkness...
l'll stick by you no matter what.
lt'll be fun working with you, coach.
Today's the first day, so l'll check your body and your sensitivity.
Plus don't forget, this is practice for Midnight Gymnastics.
We're not playing games.
Yes.
l want you to relax.
Looks like your leotard is on pretty tight.
l'll make you feel comfortable.
Feels much better right?
Very elastic.
How about over here?
You're sweating down here.
No, don't say that.
No, l'm screaming out loud.
lt's embarrassing.
Pretty.
Your crotch is all wet and shiny.
No...
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
But...
Delicious.
Your cunt is exposed.
lt's embarrassing.
Suck on this.
Open your eyes Koyuki-chan!
Open your eyes!
l know your weakness.
You get excited easily.
But you can't express your sensations to the public.
That's why you're not smiling.
l'm just embarrassed.
That's unacceptable!
Women compete by displaying their beauty...
...and sluttiness in Midnight Gymnastics.
lf you can't express your feelings to the public, you can never win!
Don't be afraid to smile!
We'll work on that smile of yours from here on!
l'll go as hard as l can.
No!
Smile! Smile for me!
No! Not yet!
Smile! Come on!
That's it.
That's what you have to show the audience!
Your strong feelings when you endure pain...
Joy you get from pleasure.
Express the feelings you get when we connect with each other.
l'm sure you can do it.
l want to be honest with my feelings.
l'm coming, l'm coming, Koyuki-chan!
l'm coming too!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!