Delicious!
Ten of these per day is just not enough.
Maybe l should tell my grandfather to increase the limit.
You're eating them all by yourself.
How's the progress?
There hasn't been much progress.
l'm sorry.
Geez.
l'm going to have a bad after taste by looking at your face!
l only want to hear good things! You know that!
Yes.
Come with me.
Tomomi-san, someone might see us like this.
You're the one who's rock hard.
But...
Look, l see some juice pouring out from your tip.
lf l rub this against the tip, it becomes a lubricant.
lt feels good!
You've become very sensitive.
l can see your ballsack is getting bigger.
A man's body is very interesting.
Are you going to climax?
Yes.
Then do the rest on your own.
What?
No fair!
Just do it.
Tomomi-san...
l'm coming, l'm coming.
l'm coming!
Tomomi-san...
l did a huge favor for you, so you better do a good job.
Got it?
Yes, l'll do my best!
Princess 69 - Midnight
Gymnastics Vol. 2
Now, let's begin.
Ready?
Smile Koyuki-chan!
Smile!
Okay.
Ouch!
Fubuki-chan, are you okay?
Koyuki-chan, you almost snapped off my cock.
l need you to concentrate more!
l'm sorry.
Maybe l'm not good enough for this.
Don't be pessimistic.
You can do it!
Let's give it our best.
Midnight Gymnastics...
Okay.
We're going to practice here?
Yeah, you need to be able to express your feelings.
But...
Think of these people around you as judges and spectators...
...for the Midnight Gymnastics, okay?
Koyuki-chan, you're already wet.
You're excited.
No...
Don't say no.
lf you're excited, then say it.
l can't...
Just pick it up.
No!
What are you embarrassed about?
lf you're excited, then you have to let them know.
That's why we're doing this.
l'm sorry...
Here we go Koyuki-chan.
Ready?
Koyuki-chan, does it feel good?
l don't know...
You're excited right?
lt feels good right?
Be honest.
lt feels so good.
Then smile!
Express your feelings with your smile!
But...
These people are here to see your cute smile!
You don't want to disappoint them.
l can't climax here...
lt's embarrassing...
No, l...
l...
Me too!
You were able to do it until the end.
Yeah.
That smile.
That smile will get you a perfect ten from every judge!
The world revolves around me.
But l'm not satisfied.
This world is boring.
This world should be destroyed with my command.
l'll never be happy.
l'm just a sad, miserable woman.
l'm tired.
Yo!
Thanks for cleaning up.
Where's Fujimiya-san?
She's in the shower.
Speaking of Fujimiya...
l'll show you something good.
Who is he?
Fujimiya's boyfriend!
l have more.
Give me that!
Give it back!
Where did you get that?
l saw them near a convenience store.
They seemed very happy, they're madly in love.
Koyuki-chan?
You took a candid shot?
How rude.
What, are you jealous?
You're jealous, aren't you?
Don't worry, you'll never get a boyfriend.
What did you say?
You have no boobs nor sexiness.
Who are you to say such things?
Hey, who's this in the picture?
My boyfriend.
This one.
That's my second boyfriend.
This one
How about this?
Probably my fourth.
Fubuki-chan.
Lie against the wall and sit down.
What are you going to do?
Stay still.
Excited?
You probably get excited with any man you do it with.
What?
Fubuki-chan, what is this training?
This isn't training.
What?
No!
This is a punishment.
l can't let you see other guys behind my back.
What do you mean?
Don't fool with me.
Stop!
My stomach hurts.
Please stop this Fubuki-chan.
Who's that guy you were with?
You two seemed very friendly.
No! That was...
lt hurts... My stomach will burst.
Please, let me go to the bathroom.
My stomach hurts!
l'll put a cork in it.
That guy was banging you like this, right?
My ass hurts...
lt'll burst!
You were having lots of fun behind my back, right?
l didn't do anything!
There's been a misunderstanding!
No!
No, no, no!
Oh no, it's flowing out...
Painful, right? Unbearable, right?
My heart feels the same way!
No...
l feel sad that you can't trust me!
lf l'm with you, l can do anything.
Trust me, Fubuki-chan.
l want you to trust me.
Then who was that guy?
l've known him since l was little, he's a childhood friend.
What?
l bumped into him by accident.
Then what happened?
He wanted to go out with me, but l refused.
That's all.
That's all l did!
Koyuki-chan!
l'm sorry Koyuki-chan.
l'm sorry.
l'm happy if you're satisfied.
But l can't hold it in!
Don't look...
Tomomi-san usually acts tough but l think she might be lonely.
She might kill me if l say that.
She's cute when she's quiet.
l want her to be more honest.
Why did she turn out like this?
Oh no!
l fell asleep.
l finished cleaning.
You didn't clean my area.
l'm leaving so you can clean the rest.
You better do a good job.
Do you smell something?
Smells like ink.
l don't smell anything.
Okay, then do a good job with the cleaning.
She's leaving early again?
She does whatever she wants...
Huh?
Oh no!
These are...
Nobody can step into my heart.
Nobody...
Why don't you go accompany her?
You're right.
Nurse's Offiice
What? She's not here?
What are you doing?
Classes are in session.
What are you doing here, Tomomi-san?
Me?
l'm trying to maintain peace for this academy...
l see.
Come on, where are you going?
Koyuki-chan supposedly went to the nurse's office but she's not there.
Fujimiya?
She better not have ran away.
That's impossible!
Could it be...
Fubuki-chan!
Koyuki-chan, what are you doing?
l know classes are in session but l couldn't take it anymore...
l see...
l'm sorry for being so selfish.
lt's okay.
You were able to be honest with your feelings.
You became the girl l was hoping for!
Fubuki-chan, make love to me.
lt feels good.
You make me feel so good.
Fubuki-chan...
More, more...
Koyuki-chan!
l'm coming Koyuki-chan!
Me too!
l want you to climax with me!
l think we can do it now.
Yes.
Koyuki-chan, don't forget to smile.
That's it Koyuki-chan!
Keep some distance between our bodies.
Yes.
We did it! lt's perfect!
Thank you Fubuki-chan.
Good job.
You did better than l expected, Fujimiya.
You did real good, l'll give you credit.
lt's all because of Fubuki-chan.
You're lucky to have such a good coach.
Yes.
l need to talk to your coach, so can you leave us?
The darkness of Midnight Gymnastics...
...is a condition where you stop opening up to others.
lf you don't accept Midnight Gymnastics in your heart...
...your feelings of denial eventually take over you...
...and prevents you from opening up to other people.
l see.
Koyuki-chan was able to express her feelings honestly.
That's why the darkness didn't take over her.
Really?
So in order to get my sister back to normal...
...we just have to start over from scratch.
Of course, l'll be the one to help her.
Tomomi-san?
You're just too good.
What do you mean?
Do you still believe in these Midnight Gymnastics?
That was all a lie.
You were too serious, so l just wanted to tease you.
lt can't be...
You're kidding right?
You were too serious about all this.
You must be kidding me.
lt can't be...
But l can tell you one thing.
That Fubuki Haneoka was a real good toy.
l'm just your toy?
Am l wrong?
l know you care about your sister.
But who's dumb enough to dress up like a girl...
...to go to an all-girls academy?
l can't believe you even wore leotards.
What's the matter?
You realized how dumb you were?
You're a really sad person.
Huh? What are you saying?
Those are...
This is the reason why you stopped opening up to others, right?
You're just trying to forget this humiliation...
...by pretending you're a person of strong will.
You're the one who's caught in the darkness.
So what?
Are you threatening me with those photos?
How much do you want?
Ouch!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Now, let's begin.
We'll start training for the Midnight Gymnastics.
l'll teach you real good.
My hands...
They'll snap off.
Ouch, ouch!
My boobs will be uneven! My nipples will come off!
Let me go.
Shut up!
You don't need these!
No.
lt hurts!
lt hurts?
Stop lying!
What's this?
l'm asking you to answer me!
You get excited with things like this!
Be honest, you want more stimulation.
lsn't that right?
No!
You want more? Huh?
Okay, let's move on to the back.
Can't you hear me?
Right here!
l'm gonna stick this in here.
Stop!
Anything but that!
Shut up!
So tight.
But now the front is all vacant.
l'll fix that.
No, stop it!
You probably don't know this but your oblique teeth feel real good.
l'm coming again.
This is yours, wear it!
Get up!
No!
Stop!
What are you doing?
ls that what you call a brilliant performance?
Don't take the Midnight Gymnastics that lightly!
What's that expression on your face?
Do it like you're having fun!
Get over here!
You need some encouragement!
No!
No more!
This world belongs to me.
This man, Fubuki Haneoka, just stepped into my world.
This man may...
This man might save me from this world of loneliness.
So l...
l think l'm a very lucky woman.
Good! We're done with the warm-up!
Yes coach!