What are you reading?
Ms. Sayaka!
How long were you standing there?
Did I surprise you guys?
You know you did!
I'm embarrassed!
Let me take attendance.
Did you forget to bring
the attendance book?
Even Ms. Sayaka forgot something?
Don't worry. All of the
names are already in my head.
But you have been at this
college for only one week.
Amazing!
She is way smarter then you.
Come on, now!
Of course, she's our professor.
Chapter One: Lady
Teacher Sayaka and...
This is done.
Hey Makoto.
Makoto Yuuki!
Can you bring this to Ms. Sayaka?
Oh, okay.
I'm in a hurry to get to the club.
Have you decided which club to join?
No, not yet.
But it's been 3 months since
you transferred to this college.
What about the literature club?
Why?
I heard Ms. Sayaka is
the manager of the club.
You don't have to hide.
It seems like Ms. Sayaka is interested
too, you two make a great couple!
Stop teasing me.
You had better be hurry up. Otherwise,
the Bear will come and shout at you.
Who are you calling the Bear?
Shit! It's the bear.
Hey! Don't run in the hallway.
Ms. Sayaka likes me?
Teacher's Lounge
Ms. Nanjou, we've got a problem.
You should be more
strict with the students.
I don't think it's a good idea to
be too friendly to the students.
But the students need
more freedom on campus.
Balance is important in everything.
They still need discipline from us.
Otherwise they will think
they can control the teachers.
But we must also respect
their consciences.
Didn't you learn your lesson from
the trouble you made at your last college?
That's enough. She is
concerned for her students.
Do you think its okay to have
an affair with a student?
No, no way. What I'm trying to say is...
Excuse me.
Wake up, Shin.
Finish your breakfast or you
will be late for the class.
Where is Mom?
Your mother's visiting father.
She'll come back in two weeks.
She's just left.
She didn't tell me that.
On the phone, he told me that
the wife of his boss had a stroke.
I don't know exactly what happened.
So this is our first time
since you came to live here.
What do you mean?
We are alone in the
house for the first time.
That's right.
What are you doing, Shin?
Kisumi.
On campus, you had better
call me Ms. Takane.
Especially after
your affair with Sayaka.
You are right.
Are you thinking about Sayaka again?
Yeah.
Don't be silly.
Because she's concerned about you,
she decided to leave the college.
Don't waste her decision.
Yes, I know.
I appreciate your ef forts for us.
Never mind about me.
If you still love her, you
should graduate from college.
That's the best thing
you can do for her.
Bye, Ms. Hasuda.
I'm going. See you, Yui.
Bye.
I used to be sick in bed
all the time, alone at home.
From my bedroom, I always
looked outside of the window.
Have you seen any changes after
my family moved next door to you?
Yes. You came and played
with me. You took me outside.
You didn't like it?
Oh yes, I liked it!
So what do you want to show me?
Um...
I love you, Shin.
I fell in love with you way
before Sayaka came into your life.
Yui...
Why do you still treat me
like your little sister?
Don't you find my body beautiful?
I mean, it's so beautiful.
Really?
Please, Shin, make love to me.
Oh yes. I've waited for this.
You make me feel so good.
I'm so happy...
It hurts.
Be tender.
Yeah, that's it.
I'm embarrassed...
That feels so good.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm so hungry!
Me too!
Shall we go?
Yes.
You are a little late today.
Did you meet Yui?
A-Ah, yeah...
We bumped into each other.
I'm cooking your
favorite dish for dinner.
Wow, that's great.
Let me change clothes.
Okay.
Let it simmer for a while.
Is she masturbating?
What's the matter? Why
are you in the dark?
Are you taking a shower or...
I'm sorry. Are you in
the middle of changing?
No, that's okay.
Are you going to take a
shower first or have dinner?
Well, I will take a shower first.
Okay, let me bring you a bath towel.
What is going on, Shin?
I love you. I fell in love
with you a long time ago.
I always wanted to take a
shower together with you.
No, Shin, you shouldn't do this.
Tell me what you think of me.
Yes, I love you, too.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Please be gentle.
Shin...
No...
This is embarrassing, but I'm happy.
Let me touch yours.
It's so big...
It's hot, and hard.
Yeah, that's it.
Don't tease me.
No don't stop there.
I want your cock deep inside me now.
Does it hurt?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Do you feel good, Shin?
Yeah, you feel wonderful, Ms. Sayaka.
Call me just Sayaka.
Sayaka, is it okay if I move?
Shin...
Shin, harder...
So great!
Shin, give it to me more.
Harder!
So good
Yes, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Shin, I'm coming!
Give it to me harder!
I'm going crazy!
Oh Shin...
Shin, let's come together!
Shin, I can't hold it
anymore! I'm coming!
Please stop it.
Forgive me, Shin...