Chapter Two: The End of a Dream.
It hurts.
Sorry.
Never mind...
Thank you so much, Yuuki.
He reminds me of Shin...
Stay with me for a while, please.
That hurts, Yuuki.
Please, be gentle...
Okay.
Oh no...
No...
You drive me crazy.
Oh, no, no.
Feels good...
Yuuki, please give it to me.
Come to me right now.
No, it's not there.
Move down a little.
No, up...
Yes, right there.
I'm about to come!
No...
Not yet!
You came home so late today.
Sayaka, have you gotten
used to the college?
Yes.
If you have any troubles, feel
free to talk to my husband.
He is the president of the college.
I understand, thank you.
Taking a bath makes me relax.
Did Sayaka come back?
Let me bring some sake for you.
Later.
I hope she is not going to
cause any trouble this time.
If the heir of the Takane family had
not helped her, she wouldn't be here.
But next time, she will
end up on the streets.
How did she get acquainted with Takane?
She is the best friend
of Takane's daughter.
How have you been, Sayaka?
I'm doing fine.
I know you want to know
about Shin more than me.
Shin is doing fine, so
no need to worry about us.
What are you doing, Shin?
Kisumi.
On campus, you had better
call me Ms. Takane.
Especially after
your affair with Sayaka.
You are right.
Are you thinking about Sayaka again?
Don't be silly.
Because she's concerned about you,
she decided to leave the college.
Don't waste her decision.
Yes. I know.
I appreciate your efforts on us.
Never mind about me.
If you still love her, you
should graduate from college.
That's the best thing
you can do for her.
Bye, Ms. Hasuda.
I'm going. See you, Yui.
Bye.
Shin.
We now have fall weather, don't we?
Wait, Shin.
You have been ignoring me
since the end of summer.
What's wrong with you?
Answer me, Shin!
Is this related to Ms.
Nanjo's sudden leave?
Shin...
Sayaka!
Shin, I miss you.
But...
I love you, Sayaka.
I love you very much.
I can't hold it any longer...
You are so beautiful.
Your pussy is so wet and shining.
I'm embarrassed.
Let me suck your cock.
Oh, this feels so good. Sayaka.
Suck it harder.
Please, lick me.
Shin, I can't wait any longer.
Okay...
Oh, my God!
Oh, Shin!
So great!
Feels so good!
I'm about to come!
Please come in my mouth!
Okay, now come!
Well, this goes here.
Shin, what are you doing here?
I have never seen you here before.
I asked him to help me to find
the books I need for class.
Thank you, Shin.
Can you help me organize books?
Well, okay...
Can't you say anything nicer than that?
We used to run around
on this beach back then.
Yeah, you had just
transferred to my college.
When the class was preparing for
the college festival, I broke a signboard.
I was fixing it all by myself, but
then you helped me to fix it.
Is that so?
Don't you remember?
You used to be so
kind to me back then.
I saw you were crying,
so I helped you out.
You used to be gentle
and sweet back then.
I didn't cry!
And I'm still gentle and sweet!
You're joking.
You don't see my charm.
Why are you looking at me like that?
No, well, I'm trying
to find your charm.
What do you mean by that?
I don't know whether they
are getting along or not.
Are you jealous?
What?
You can't hide it from me.
W-What are you talking about?
I know this must be kept secret,
but I guess he couldn't help it.
When he came to the nurse's office, he
told me everything about you and him.
He knows you and I
are very close friends.
But it's not going to
be easy for you guys.
Don't let the faculty
or the students notice you two.
Shin is a nice boy.
I'm on your side, Sayaka.
I'm sorry...
I want to see you, Shin.
Look outside the window.
Shin...
I just want to see your face.
Oh, no.
No!
Please stop!
No...
But your pussy is so wet.
Please, stop now.
Aren't you really wet?
Tell me who made you so horny?
No...
You have to tell me.
No!
No, please stop.
Please.
No!
Stop...
Please stop.
Please stop, I beg you!
No!
Please don't do this...
No...
This feels so good...
Do the same thing as I do.
Yeah, Sayaka, you are doing great.
Don't stop.
You aren't going to stick
that thing into me, are you?
Stop...
No!
Please stop, it hurts!
Stop it!
It hurts!
Please stop it!
You are making me crazy!
So great!
Feels so good!
Oh no...
Harder! Harder!
I'm going to come!