Master...
Coincidences really do happen!
You have the same face as me, and
we both have the same last name.
On top of that, we've
both majored in the arts!
It really is a miracle that
I was able to meet you!
Yes... Master...
I never would have guessed that
you used to be a teacher, Tomoya.
You look young. I thought you
were the same age as me.
M... Master. Please make me go
crazy with your big hard cock.
No! Master! I want it... Give it to me.
I want your cock so much,
I can't stop thrusting.
I'm going to the College
of Sacred Maidens...
...to do my student teaching
internship, starting tomorrow.
I'm sure you know about it. It's
the famous rich girl college.
It's filled with hot women. It's
paradise. I can't wait until tomorrow.
Hurry, Master...
I want your cock... Please... I
want you to stick it in my pussy.
No fair... I want it. Give it to me...
Yes! Master! I... I... I'm going to...
Your fingers... They're touching
me where it makes me feel good...
Professor... Professor... Professor Ishiguro.
Professor Ishiguro.
Ow!
Are you okay, Professor?
Yeah... The class ran late last
night, so I didn't get much sleep.
Asuka Minamoto.
You know my name?
Of course I do. You're going to be the
lead actress in the theater club show...
...even though you're actually
a track club member.
Plus, you're cute, so it didn't take
much for me to learn your name.
Um... Professor Ishiguro...
What is it?
Professor Kirishima was calling
for you in the faculty office.
Kirishima...
Oh shit!
Captain Seira. Have you been using it
lately? Your time isn't getting any better.
Yoko... But that... It smells
weird and it makes me feel ill...
You have to!
You were able to do so well at the last
tournament because of those herbs.
Anyway, the herbs are safe.
They're sold on the internet.
You have to keep taking them.
Seira Himeno, the captain of the
swim team, and Yoko Yuuki...
Professor Ishiguro! Didn't I ask you to
submit that report during lunch break?
Now, now, Professor Kirishima. I think
that's enough. He's still a student.
He's hasn't learned what it's
like to have responsibilities.
He doesn't know exactly what
it means to be a teacher.
Who the hell does he think he is? What
an idiot. I used to be a real teacher.
This phys-ed professor is dating Kirishima...
...but he's trying to fuck
her sister Yumi. Sick fuck.
Let's go Seishun. Go! Go! Seishun!
...but he's trying to fuck
her sister Yumi. Sick fuck.
Let's go Seishun. Go! Go! Seishun!
They'll be my next pets.
Asuka Minamoto is helping out the
theater club because she accidentally...
...injured Miki Tachibana, but there's
something dirty going on there.
Seira Himeno, the captain
of the swim team...
...has an amazing swim time
record, but she's doping up.
They were saying "herbs," but I
guess these girls don't know...
...that there are drug-laced herbs being
sold on the internet. If the cops found out...
...it wouldn't end with them not being
able to participate in swim tournaments.
Master. I've done my best and collected
as much information as I could. Please...
I want my reward...
Shut up, you female pig. I'm
thinking. Go fuck yourself.
The third one... Yumi Kirishima...
Yumi is getting sexually harassed by
her phys-ed professor, Samejima...
...but she can't tell anyone. Can't
blame her... He's dating her sister.
That stupid idiot. Of course Yumi's
going to run from you if you do that...
Professor Kirishima, look!
It's my costume, but Miki lent it to me.
Now we'll make it in time for the show.
That's wonderful. I'm glad
Miki let you borrow it.
Yes! I've caused Miki so much trouble,
but when I explained the situation...
...she lent it to me.
I see. I'm glad you two
were able to make up...
...after what happened between you two.
Yes, Miki was supposed to wear
this costume, but because of me...
Asuka, what's happened has happened.
Good luck as the lead actress...
Make sure you lock up, because
things have been getting stolen...
...from the theater clubroom lately.
Professor Ishiguro, what are you staring at?
Oh, sorry!
I know Asuka is beautiful so you want to
stare at her, but you're interfering here.
Please understand, you're an educator here.
I see...
Yumi, could you help me clean up the gym
storage room after the club activities?
Um... Okay...
I knew I could count on Satsuki's
sister. Everyone else is lazy.
You're a cheerleader, so
you should tie your hair up.
Yumi! Can you show me where the gym is?
S... sure!
Thanks. This place is so
big, I can't seem to find it.
Professor Kirishima, I'm borrowing
your sister. Please excuse us.
Are you all right?
Um, Professor Ishiguro...
I... Thank you very much.
Do you not get along
with Professor Samejima?
Um... That's...
It's okay. He's not my favorite person either.
You too?
Professor Samejima touches me
and brings his face close to mine...
I really don't like it.
So you don't like people touching you?
No, that's not what I meant. I don't like
it when it's Professor Samejima, but...
I wouldn't mind you...
You wouldn't mind me what?
Nothing! Goodbye!
Well, well...
Who's he?
He's the student professor that
came here three days ago, Captain.
Why is he here?
I don't know.
I don't like it.
Captain!
Who gave you permission to be here?
You need permission to
come look at the pool?
Of course. It's distracting to the members
when outsiders are coming in and out.
Plus, it's absurd to have a man
come look at a women-only pool.
I wanted to know everything
about the school.
Who do I need to get permission from?
You get it from me, the Captain.
Then can I get permission?
Absolutely not.
Professor Ishiguro... Why does an art
professor need to check out the pool?
I bet you're only here to see women
in bathing suits, not the pool.
That's just like a pervert. Please
leave, Professor Ishiguro.
Now! Or else I'll call the other professors!
Damn it! What a bitch. Who does she think
she is? I'll have to give her strict training.
No, stop professor!
What are you saying? You came
here because you love me, right?
No, stop professor!
What are you saying? You came
here because you love me, right?
You're wrong. I'll tell sis!
Go ahead. I wonder how hurt she'll be?
Her lover taken from her by her
younger sister... She'll be so shocked.
We'll keep it our secret. That should be fine.
No, someone help me! Professor Ishiguro!
What? Why are you calling his name?
Professor Ishiguro! Help!
Professor Ishiguro...
It's useless. No one's coming
to help you, so do as I say!
This way!
That was a close one.
Are you all right, Yumi?
Not even a "thanks" when I saved her...
Miki Tachibana
Asuka Minamoto
I'll never forgive you... Asuka Minamoto...
Miki Tachibana
Asuka Minamoto
I was injured because of
her and she took my role...
Miki Tachibana
Asuka Minamoto
Do you have any idea how hard I worked?
If the stolen tickets are found
in Asuka's costume, it's over.
Everyone will have no choice
but to select me as the lead.
Amateur. Stolen tickets aren't going to do it!
Let's see ... The preparations for
the hunt are pretty much done...
It's going to get fun, starting tomorrow.
Here it is, Master.
This must be the site the swimming
team has been ordering the herbs from.
I knew it. It's not herbs, it's drugs. Now
we know exactly what she's taking.
Wow! Master, how do you know?
Because I've used this site before.
Now I know that little bitch
Seira Himeno's weakness.
I'll chase her down until
she becomes my slave.
I can also use the story about
the stolen items Asuka has...
Let's see, which should come first...
Master. Yumi Kirishima just
gave me a letter to give to you.
Let's see...
"I want to thank you for the other day."
"I'll be waiting for you at the gym
storage room after club activities."
How interesting... It's decided.
Yumi, you'll be my first prey!
Mira. Madoka. Have the cameras ready.
Right.
Yumi?
Professor Ishiguro?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Huh?
What's wrong, Yumi?
Well it's... It's... I thought
you wouldn't come.
I was assaulted by Professor
Samejima, then you saw it...
I thought you would hate me... I was
so worried while I was waiting for you.
Yumi...
Everyone said "let's go home", but I stayed
here by myself waiting for you... I...
I love you, Professor Ishiguro.
Professor, please don't hate me.
You love me?
Yes, if it's you... I'd be
able to give myself...
Professor?
You love me? How funny!
I love you too, Yumi!
I love you so much that I
want to make you my pet.
Pet?
Professor Ishiguro... Stop...!
What? I thought you said you'd be
able give yourself if it was me.
Was that a lie?
It's not a lie... But we haven't even kissed.
There you go.
No... I'm scared Professor!
No!
Professor... I'm not ready for this...
No! It hurts! It hurts!
What? Only the head is in.
Stop! Please! No! It hurts! It hurts!
I'm going to break!
Professor, please pull out!
Do you get it? I'm your first man.
A woman's pussy is made so it can take
a man's cock. It's not going to break.
But... But... It hurts... Please stop,
because it hurts... No more...
If you hate it this much, I guess you
can't be with me, even if I love you.
Professor?
If you love me, prove it to the end.
That's right, Yumi... That's
good. I'm going to let it all out.
Let what out?
I'm going to cum!
Good job, Yumi. If you listen to
what I say, I'll treat you the best.
It hurts! It hurts!
Don't move!
Good footage.
Come in.
Why did you call for me? What
do you want, Professor Ishiguro?
It better not be to ask for
permission to visit the pool.
This is the one and only reason
why I wanted to speak to you.
That's...
Where did you get it?
Did you get it from my locker? You criminal!
Oh! Who are you calling a criminal?
You! You snuck into the women's locker
room and stole a student's belongings.
That's terrible! This is the
end of the line for you.
I'm going to tell Professor
Kirishima and get you kicked out!
Are you saying all this,
knowing what's in this bag?
What's inside? They're just
herbs that make you feel good.
Do you honestly believe that? You're
starting to figure out what they are.
They're illegal drugs that make you high!
I guess you didn't figure it out all the way.
You know what's going to
happen if everyone finds out?
You and the entire swim
team will be suspended.
So what are you going to do, Captain?
Tell 'em.
What?
Tell the police, or whoever. I'm not gonna
be blackmailed by a lowlife like you.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
You're such a bitch!
Ow! You're hurting me, you bastard!
You have nowhere to run. You
have no choice but to be my pet!
What are you talking about? A
pet? What are you, an idiot? No!
What a beautiful body. You don't
even have any beauty marks.
No! You pervert! Let go! Let
go of me! Someone! Anyone!
Give it up. There's no use struggling.
You scum!
No! Stop! You pervert!
What? Is this your first time?
You don't strike me as a virgin.
No! Stop!
No... I'm sorry. Please stop.
Make sure you watch this moment,
as you become a real woman!
No!
You're fit, so your pussy's really tight.
Can you see? It's proof that
you've become a woman.
No... No more... Stop... Please...
You still don't understand your position,
do you? We've only just begun.
Let me take my time to teach
you what it's like to be my pet!
But...
Let me baptize you as my pet! Take it!
No!
Seira Himeno is mine. The last one...
One more to go...
Professor Ishiguro.
I'm sorry to bother you during
rehearsal. Is Asuka here?
Did you come for Asuka? She's in the back.
Thanks.
Miki, thank you so much for the dress.
It's going to be a great show, thanks to you.
Sure... I hand-made it, so you
better take good care of it.
I will. Um... Miki, in the chest pocket...
Asuka.
You're almost on, right? I'll be
watching from the curtain. Good luck.
O-okay...
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to call you. I know
you're tired from practice.
Not at all. Why did you want
me to come in costume?
There's something I wanted to check.
You know that things have been
getting stolen in the theater club, right?
Yes, but so what?
Your costume's strange chest
bulge caught my attention, so...
It's nothing. I have to leave.
Are you trying to hide something?
Of course not!
Then there's no need to
run. Here, let me see.
I knew the stolen items would be
there. Did you steal this, Asuka?
No! It wasn't me.
Then was it the owner of the
costume? That would be Miki...
Please wait, Professor...
It was me. I did it.
Then you lied?
Y... yes... I was scared... But... I stole it.
Wow! You're bolder than I thought. Your
parents are going to be disappointed.
You stole tickets, and this?
That's...
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine...
...one hundred thousand yen.
That's a lot of money. On top of that...
...there are several thousand
dollars in the bank.
What are you going to do
about this? You'll get expelled.
You know what's going to happen if
you get arrested by the cops, right?
B-but...! No! It wasn't me! I really didn't do it!
What? But this is the
proof. You can't get away.
Or are you covering for someone?
That's...
Miki Tachibana?
I knew it... I won't say a word...
R... really?
Yes, really. But but only if
you listen to what I say.
Thank you so much. I'll do anything,
so please don't tell anyone about this.
Okay.
No!
Stop! Please stop! Why are you doing this?
I have to lie to the professor in charge.
So I should get something in return.
But...
You'd better work hard
for your friend, Asuka.
No... Stop...
Please stop...
You really think we can stop now?
You're squeezing me. Great pussy.
Stop... No...
What are you saying? The fun starts here.
See? It went in all the way.
It's your first time. No wonder it's so tight.
Miki... Miki... Help...
Please... No...
Do you honestly think the friend who
framed you will come to save you?
You have a lot to learn.
Who's fault is it that you're getting raped?
Miki was injured because of me... So...
A beautiful friendship... but look
at what's happening to you!
No... Someone help me...
This is... This is... No...
No... Stop...
No more... I can't anymore...
Please let me go.
I'm going to break. Please
pull out, Professor.
No... No... No more... Please...
Please stop... Please...
The curtains have just opened.
Now I'm going to move on to training them.
It'll be interesting to see how they turn out.