Kenji!
Let go of me!
Why are you doing this?!
Master Shingo is waiting for you, Yuko.
Forgive me.
SACRlLEGE
Kenji!
Yuko!
This subtitle made by hentaiguess.com
Not for sale, rent or ebay.
An accident?
Kenji!
Yuko...
So, you lost the only
good subject you had?
That's really unfortunate.
We're putting everything
into finding him right now.
The spies seem to be snooping around.
Finding the subject right now...
...is the top priority.
The woman you got a hold of...
...can be used to draw out the subject?
We have very little time left.
I hope you understand that.
Yes.
Why is this medicine here?
There's a limited number
of people who have access to it.
Is it a top secret new drug?
Kaizear Pharmaceuticals.
Is it an anabolic steroid?
If this was found at
the site of the incident...
I'm sure it has something
to do with the experiments.
You think it has something
to do with that monster?
Kenji, do you remember anything
about those who kidnapped Yuko?
Uh, I'm sorry.
It was all very sudden.
I don't remember it too well.
I see.
What do you think those women were?
The one's that looked like priestesses?
I hear you were no match for them!
Can it! You keep your mouth shut!
Jun...
Get as much information you can
on Kaizear Pharmaceuticals.
Okay!
And Atsuko, we're heading straight in!
All right!
No, Kei! It's too dangerous!
Don't worry.
We're just going to take a look around.
And I'm also worried about Yuko.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
You don't have to worry about Kei.
Besides, Atsuko's with her.
Nothing to worry about!
And this is our work, after all.
And I really don't mind
doing this work for you.
Thank you.
We're all linked up here.
How about over there, Jun?
It's all set. Just hang on.
How is it?
Leave it to me.
I'm really good at this sort of thing.
I can figure out any
password they ask for.
When it comes to hiding treasure,
dogs and criminals are the same.
They'll dig a hole and bury it there.
But they always hide
it in the same places.
Such fools they are.
There! Bingo!
Human genome?
Human genome?!
Wow, this is amazing!
They've even tried to analyze
the human aging process.
I know you're excited about this, Jun.
But tell us what's going on?
Have you figured something out?
There's a genetic map here.
And some sort of anti-aging substance?
Th-This can't be!
You mean to say that the
new drug they're developing is...
Hey, what's going on?!
I was just on to something!
What? What just happened?
Huh? That's really strange.
I thought I invalidated
the protection system.
Hey, something's really weird here, Kei.
Wh-What did I do again?
Mari.
Yuko...
Hurry, there's little time left.
No, please. I beg you. Let me go.
A wretched woman.
Getting all wet like this.
Oh, you're so terrible.
It is tough? Are you suffering?
But there's no choice in the matter.
It's penance, after all.
It's all the result of
your brother's karma.
M-My brother?
What did my brother do?
That man!
My sister is not one who should
associate with the likes of you!
Could your sister possibly be Yuko?
This subtitle made by hentaiguess.com
Not for sale, rent or ebay.
Please, no more...!
I'll show you mercy!
Writhe and moan!
Consider this to be a divine duty!
Oh, no!
Whoa!
Hey, why are you doing this?
Let's go.
Uh, Hang on!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
More importantly,
I'm worried about Kei and Atsuko.
Thank you.
Yuko...
The time has finally come
for my wish to come true.
What?!
Yuko!
Kei!
So, you've come. But it's too late!
I want you to watch
what I am about to do!
Yuko!
We're almost done, sis.
What?!
A good-for-nothing beast.
Take this!
Is that all you've got?!
You little insect!
I'm sorry for taking so long!
I'll untie you!
Jun.
Kei!
Kei, are you all right?
Yuko... Yuko...
Mari...
Mari?! Why, you!
Kenji!
Mari!
Watch it!
Sis...!
You've come back, sis.
I've been...
I've been waiting so long.
Why did you leave me, sis?
The smell of my sister...
Sis...
My expectations were too high.
Things don't always go
the way you want them to.
Well, I'll have to come up
with another plan.