This subtitle made by hentaiguess.com
Not for sale, rent or ebay.
Master Shingo...
The pot has been filled.
I believe it has been a fruitful night.
There.
What's your plan for lunch?
I noticed a new pasta place
opened up near you.
I'll meet you in the basement
level of the Mega Mall.
That Atsuko...
Oh, Kei! Are you heading
out on a date now?
Wow, I'm so envious!
You bet!
I hope you find a good
man sometime soon, Jun.
And not just on the lnternet.
I'm impressed, Atsuko. That you'd
notice such an out-of-the-way place.
So, are you impressed with the
investigative abilities of us at lCPO?
Oh, we'll have two ''Specials''.
And I'll have an iced coffee
to drink and...
I'll have an espresso.
Fantastic!
I've been so busy lately I haven't
been eating anything good.
Have you been working on
that job they're talking about?
Yes. The multiple international
simultaneous rape incidents!
Atsuko!
Oh, darn. I wasn't
supposed to tell you that.
Well, anyway...
That's the story. Sorry.
Sorry I've ignored you for so long.
I'll be sure to make it up to you.
Don't you cheat on me.
Of course I won't.
So, haven't there been any
leads or anything yet?
We've got a witness.
So far all of the victims
have been killed.
But one survived from
an incident the other day.
It turns out the culprit
was the victim's lover.
She was attacked while he was
taking her home after a date.
What?! You mean like a
wolf committing a date rape?!
Bingo!
That's very good.
You were even right
about the wolf part.
Let's see you move!
Now, raise those legs higher!
Um, are you all right?
No!
Do it.
I guess these pills don't work either.
Kenji, the doctor said you must be
patient with the treatment.
But that'll take too long!
If I don't recover and get
back to my running, I'll be...
Shit!
Kenji...
Yuko...
Kenji!
There's something weird
going on with me today...
Kenji...
What do you think, Mari?
Yes. This is the list of subjects.
I've been disseminating the
test drug over a wider area...
to keep the authorities
from noticing.
And based on the follow up...
the effects were
noticeable two days...
after the subjects
had taken the test drug.
In each case,
the responses are irregular...
and all loose ends
have been dealt with.
It's just that...
Are you saying that
this schedule is too tight?
There's a pressing demand to
complete it as quickly as possible.
I'll go have a word with them.
Not now! We're on patrol!
Why not?
It's been a while since
we've been together like this.
But still...
There's people around...
No one's going to bother us
this late at night.
Besides, no one could
see us in this darkness.
Oh, Atsuko...
Uh, not there...!
What do you mean?
Look how wet you are!
You're such a tease!
I can't help but tease you,
because you're so adorable.
Atsuko!
It's about time you stopped resisting.
I'll give you all the pleasure you want.
How are you feeling?
Those pills I bought
on the lnternet sure work!
I can't believe I was feeling
so sick until yesterday.
Well, I'm glad to hear that.
What's the matter?
W-Wait!
Hang on, Atsuko!
What the hell is this?
Why, you.
Bastard!
Atsuko!
Kei!
Hold it, you bastard!
How strange.
You sure he went this way?
Atsuko, look.
What the...?
That took a while.
I'm very sorry.
I got caught up in
dealing with the subjects.
And what about the drug?
Not ready yet?
Unfortunately not.
Then why did you come here?
You'd better get back to your work.
Something has happened
that keeps me from continuing.
A spy has infiltrated our work.
We have a loose cannon somewhere.
I'd like to postpone further
experiments for a while.
No.
Unlike you, we don't
have much time left.
I understand.
This is the only good subject
we have discovered so far.
His name is Kenji Naruse.
I don't remember seeing
his name on the list.
I didn't find him through
the usual routes.
Which means?
I got a report about missing
samples of a test drug from a lab.
I found out the subject took the drug
from the firm without permission.
So you took longer in discovering him.
Keep a good eye on him.
It seems that you've
forgotten something.
Pardon?
You forgot to report to me about
the man who took medicine...
...from his firm without permission.
I'm still looking into that case.
I intended to report on it
at the next meeting.
I don't want to hear excuses.
If this is something that
we've been waiting for...
...isn't there just one
thing that you must do?
Never mind. I'll be
waiting to hear from you.
And it seems like the woman
he's with is no ordinary one.
Master Shingo...
Oh, Master Shingo!
Sis...
This completes the list.
All right, Jun. You go through
all the contacts in this case.
You got it!
And you and I will go
to the subject's house.
What? The police have
already checked that out.
One more time.
We really don't have much
to go on right now, after all.
We have to go back
to basics and check it ourselves.
I see.
In that case, we should get
the data on all similar incidents.
Good idea. I've leave
that one up to you.
Okay! Let's go as soon as we're ready!
Kenji! Yuko!
Kei.
Are you going home?
Yeah. Are you on your way to work?
Yeah, I'm in the middle of a case.
Um, Kenji.
I'm a little concerned about Yuko.
Make sure she doesn't leave the
apartment on her own.
Did something happen?
There's a serial rape case.
Oh, my!
I saw one of the crime
scenes around here recently.
I've never seen anything so terrible.
So please be careful, Yuko.
All right. We'll be careful, Kei.
Well, I'll see you later, Kenji!
And Yuko, too!
Yeah, see you!
Hey! What're you trying to pull?!
This all seems pretty creepy.
I don't know what this is all about,
but coming after me...
...is something you'll regret!
Outta my way!
Step back.
You're no match for this one.
After all, she managed to dodge
that beast on her own.
A tough and wild physique.
Just my type.
What're you talking about, bitch?!
Wh-What're you doing?
S-Stop it. Don't do this.
You feel awfully good.
I'm liking you even more.
A boxer out running?
He doesn't have anything on him.
Half his body's burned.
This corpse is in such horrible shape.
Huh? This medicine...
There's something suspicious about it.
Kaizear Pharmaceuticals!
That's my brother's company!
Kenji!
Kenji...