I did it!
How was that, Asuka?
Just as I promised, a hat trick!
Really, I can't believe it!
That's incredible, to be able to score
3 times in one game, Tohru!
Plus that last goal was the winning goal
in lost time, like in the TV dramas!
I was moved!
Cut that out, it's embarrassing!
You're so cute, Tohru!
Silly!
If you win next time, you're the champion!
Yeah!
If you win...
maybe I'll give you
my most treasured thing.
Asuka! Look out!
Tohru? Tohru!
No!
A dream?
No, it was real.
That incident. This scar...
Asuka?
Since that incident,
our relationship isn't right.
It's not like I'm regretting
the fact that I got hurt saving her...
and I'm not blaming her for anything.
But every time we see each other
I feel strange.
And here through this lens
I can look at her without a problem.
The Distance Between the Two
Good morning, Tohru!
Camera again?
Yeah.
Did you eat your breakfast?
Your parents are out of town
for a funeral, right?
I don't eat breakfast.
You feeling sick?
No.
Before you used to go
for seconds all the time.
That's because I had soccer
practice back then.
But you still should eat breakfast.
Hey! Where are you looking?
You're boobs never grow.
Pervert!
Noah Cram School
So about the problems about...
the trigonometric ratios, in other words
the theorems of sine and cosine.
The trick is to make sure that you realize
that there can only be one triangle drawn...
with the given side and angle,
or in other words, the conditions...
so you must find
the remaining angles and sides.
Thus you need to use the theorems
of sine and cosine.
As an example...
please take a look at the problem
on page 115 of your textbook.
If you look at the pictures...
you will see the steps
to get the answers on the next page.
Now, does anyone have any questions on...
What, so you have a crush
on Miss Saki, too?
Asuka's watching, you know.
Who cares?
Well what about you?
Aren't you interested?
I'm a freelancer.
It's my policy not to go after women
who'll become troublesome. I'd get burned.
Policy?
But it wouldn't be bad to make a cool...
intellectual girl like her soar
with my technique?
Shit!
What's wrong, Tanaka?
That camera is for note-taking purposes.
Isn't that going to be
your excuse, right, Shioda?
No.
Quiet!
I'm confiscating this.
Come to the faculty room to pick it up.
Yes.
Cool and beautiful indeed.
Excuse me.
Anyone here?
I didn't say that!
Fine, I got it. Men are all pigs.
Listen to me!
Forget it.
You're coming home tonight, right?
It's always your way.
Miss Saki...
No! Don't touch me!
I'm just here to get back my camera.
That's right.
Shioda, lately you're not into your studies.
You're a cram student, you should know
how important studying is right now.
Yes, I understand that, but...
Then you don't have time for other...
Yes, you're right.
Then could you become a model...
for my pictures
so that I can focus on my studies?
If you want, how about nude?
So how was it?
Make Miss Saki soar?
No, she made me sore.
Painful burn?
All right then, when classes are over,
let's go chick-hunting.
Where does that come from? I'll pass.
Thinking about Asuka, are we?
Asuka has nothing to do with this.
She's just a childhood friend.
I see. Then I'll just quit girl-hunting
and go after Asuka...
isn't a choice, so that's why chick-hunting.
- But I...
- Come on, don't worry!
See you later, then.
He's such a character.
You don't just kick the ball
in front of the goal!
That doesn't matter now.
Miss Saki was acting weird.
So does she hate men, like they say?
Tohru!
So there you are.
I'm sorry. It was my fault
that you had your camera confiscated.
No it wasn't.
What were you doing,
you were watching soccer!
No I wasn't.
You know, why don't you play
soccer again?
You're through with rehabilitation.
Cut that crap, okay?
I'm sorry.
You haven't had lunch right?
You can have this.
No, I'm not hungry.
Come on, just one bite, please?
Stop pestering me!
You know, I'm not very good at cooking,
so it looks bad.
But it's still edible.
Why don't you ever get angry at me?
Asuka, what are you to me?
What am I?
You and I are childhood friends and...
Childhood friends.
Listen up, this ain't no drama
or soap opera here.
Boy and girl childhood friends...
are supposed to become distant
as they grow up!
If it wasn't for that accident, you wouldn't...
That's not true. Even if that didn't happen
I still like you.
Then let me kiss you.
See? You're just saying that.
I'll do it for you.
No, Tohru, I can't go any...
We've come this far, how can we quit?
No, wait, Tohru! No!
Stop it!
If I do this maybe it'll get bigger...
Or maybe it's better like this.
I don't know.
It hurts!
Tohru, be gentler.
I can't help it,
your boobs are small and hard.
This should be the only place hard!
Since your tits are hard,
over here should be...
You can't, not there!
You don't need to worry,
I'll finger you directly.
Don't make that noise.
Your pussy is pretty hairy.
It's hard to believe it was smooth one time.
That's a cruel thing to say.
Tohru, you can't!
No! No!
In return, I'll show you my grown thing.
See?
What do you think? Not like old times.
Now, I think I'll have your pussy
see how much this has grown!
Not in a place like this.
Anything but that!
No!
Tohru!
See, this is me now.
Forget soccer,
even you can just push me over.
This is the reality.
I'm sorry!
Damn it!
She forgot to put in chopsticks again.
That's just like her.
Hey, you want to go for a spin?
The weather is perfect for a drive!
That's a cool car!
I got a nice stereo system!
It's the greatest feeling
pumping the volume up...
and cruising down the highway!
What CDs you got?
Glayve, L'ars, and Dragon Lash.
Hey, you have good taste!
Don't you think I have good taste
in women, too?
What do you think, Miho?
I kind of want to ride in this car.
You have a weak spot with foreign cars.
Then it's a date! Hop in!
Miho, was it? You want shotgun?
Can I?
Hey, Tohru, you don't mind
the backseat, right?
No.
It's mine.
Hello, Kenji! What are you doing?
What, for real? Where?
Don't worry!
Meet you at the usual spot.
Sorry, Miho. So that's that,
take care of the rest.
"Take care?" Hey...
Sorry, she's always like that.
But you're still open, right?
What should I do?
I want to ride in this car, but not alone.
I got it. Which means...
What?
Sorry, Tohru.
I feel like I butted in.
It's okay. It's more my style
to walk around with this anyway.
This is how he his,
so you don't need to worry.
You get along well.
Yep. Later!
That Tanaka, always so suave.
Scare you?
Yeah.
Can I sit next to you?
What were you doing?
Can't you tell?
No, I can't.
I can tell you were looking
through the camera...
but you don't seem to be looking
for something to take.
That's my decision.
I'm satisfied just looking
through the viewfinder like this.
You're a strange one.
Are you just escaping reality?
Did I hit the mark?
That's not how it is.
I'm Mao. What about you?
Tohru.
That's a manly name.
Is it?
You don't play games?
Nope. I don't see what's so fun...
if you can't feel the pain
of hitting or being hit.
Yeah, you don't feel pain or ecstasy.
Yeah.
You may not be the type
to escape from reality.
See?
You see what's so fun?
No, I...
Surprisingly big, aren't they?
Are you sure it was okay
to leave your friend there?
Don't worry about him.
He's holding his own, I'm sure.
What a heartless friend you are.
Besides, he's got insurance,
a girl who's waiting for him.
What do you mean by that?
I'm getting interested.
Hello? It'd be nice
if you showed a little more interest in me.
Here I am!
So this is your car?
That's right. Get in!
You're going kind of fast.
This feeling of speed is the greatest!
You scared?
No, but you should fasten your seat belt.
Yeah. This should do!
No, not what I meant.
It's dangerous, keep your eyes forward!
This thrill! This ecstasy!
I can't get enough!
Yeah, so just drive safely, Okay?
We're here.
Whoa!
Boy, she goes at her own pace.
I took up her Mao's offer
and followed her here, but...
should I?
I think it's a bit late for that question.
No, but...
You have a pretty nice body.
You do any sports?
Not really, that's...
Scars like this on a man are kind of sexy.
Is that so?
That feels good!
Hey, spray me with the shower, please!
Please!
Okay.
It's so strong, I can't suck you anymore!
Then you want me to stop?
No, don't stop. Just put in it!
You sure?
Hurry!
It's rushing through me inside!
Should I turn up the pressure?
Or push it in more?
Yes! Push it in farther!
Yes! Your cock is big and long.
Your pussy is tight
and movement is so intense.
It's moving on its own,
plus the water is coming into my pussy.
I've never felt so good.
Then, how's this!
It's all the way up there!
It's hitting my uterus!
I'm gonna come, I'm gonna come!
Me too!
Come with me. Today's okay for me!
So come inside me!
Yes!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I told you it was okay.
You're actually pretty careful?
No, well...
Or do you have someone
to be worried about? Not that I care.
I see, so since that accident those two.
It's so irritating seeing those two.
I guess their distance got to close.
He should just be true to his feelings.
That's right, just like me.
Hey, wait.
Mao, she said that,
but what does she want to show me?
Having sex with you felt good.
As thanks, I'll show you something good.
Come to the room at the end of the hall
on the 2nd floor after a while.
It's about time, I think.
What's that noise?
You brought in another man, didn't you?
I heard all of your dirty moaning!
This voice!
Forgive me! But that was...
Don't you dare talk back!
It looks like whips don't have much effect
on you anymore, you masochist.
She wanted me to see this? Why?
It hurts!
Of course it does, it's punishment!
Besides, despite your crying,
look at how hard your tits are.
I'm sorry, I'm a perverted, shameless girl.
So please, punish me more.
At least you talk like a first-class bitch.
You're always like that.
You like getting me angry.
It can't be, but that habit.
I'll make you enjoy this.
Not from the start!
Your cunt seems to be enjoying it.
My, my, it went in all the way.
It'll break! My pussy will be damaged!
Don't be having fun by yourself!
Here, suck it!
Is this okay?
More, more!
Lick my clit, you dirty whore!
Yeah! Now stick it inside.
Like this, Mistress Saki?
So it is!
This is the finisher!
Please do, Mistress Saki!
One with Mistress Saki.
Isn't this so much better
than men's dirty cocks, Mao?
Say it's better!
Say it's better, Mao!
It's better! It feels so good, Ma'am.
Mao, you are all mine.
My one and only Mao.
Mistress Saki.
But still, Mao...
Did she know that I was a student
of Miss Saki?
Or was it a coincidence?
But that sure surprised me,
seeing that side of Miss Saki.
She had a side to her I could never imagine.
There's one to me.
My most treasured person.
Another me, that wants to fuck her up
because she's my most treasured person.
Tohru.
So, you ate it.
Don't just go making lunches anymore.
When I want you to make one,
I'll ask you, you got that?
Okay. I'll do that from now on, Tohru.
You can start now, Asuka.
Even if you say that. I'm embarrassed.
I want to see everything of you.
Spread your legs.
I can't see your pussy like that.
It's already getting wet.
It looks like you're hornier than usual
because you're being watched be me.
That's not true.
Keep it up with me, too.
Since your mouth seems to be open.
Okay.
You look good, Asuka.
That's good, Asuka.
Now, this is it, Asuka.
I am going to capture
your greatest moment on the camera.
Here I go, Asuka.
Now we're not
just childhood friends, are we?
That's right, we're not.
I'm so happy.
A dream?
No, it wasn't.
He snuck me into my room
so that my parents wouldn't notice.
Tohru.
Morning, Asuka.
Good morning.
Today, if you want,
could you make me lunch?
Yes, it's okay.
Don't forget the chopsticks this time.
Sorry.
That and...
Tonight, again.
Pervert!