Why don't you go and knock
on the front door?
You found what she wanted, right?
No way! I am the mysterious thief,
Keith Ryan! I won't do that!
I just won't do it!
That's some pride.
I'll hand this
Silver Rainbow directly to her.
My hand slipped!
That hurt. But, we're saved.
Beauty.
Who are you?
Just a guy. My name's Keith Ryan.
And you? What's yours?
I'm Lyon Rumzeth.
Careful! Hold on tight!
Look! Open your eyes!
Look at me, and hold onto me tight!
Good, that's better.
That was close! You okay?
Yes.
You were after it?
All right, hold on tight! Giddy up!
The wheels are falling off.
Gently! Gently!
Romance is in the Flash of the Sword II
Episode 3: Oh no, Cursed Song!
Got rid of her?
She didn't look like someone
who'd stubbornly come after me like that.
She must've really cared about this.
Who would have known that this little...
What the hell is this thing?
It's here!
What is this junk?
This stuff must be some kind
of ancient treasure to that old hag.
So long as I get paid for delivering this.
Look at all this.
Isn't this the lute of Rumzeth?
It sure is!
Made by Alan Rumzeth, the world renowned
maker of string instruments!
This is the rare and precious!
Lute of the Moon Singer!
This is an incredible treasure after all!
Lute of the Moon Singer?
That's not the deal!
Just give up!
It's no fun if she gives up too soon.
Smarter the prey,
more pleasurable the conquest.
Is that right?
It certainly is.
Of course it's all right!
What a huge estate!
Get up the speed.
Open them.
Yes, much better.
Stop it!
Let me hear it!
Almost there! Once I enter
those woods, I can make it.
I won't let you escape!
Just a bit more!
Not so easy.
No, please don't touch me!
Please don't come near me.
I'm asking you to stop.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
No, please don't!
It hurts!
It's too big!
I'm bursting!
Duke, a messenger from the King is here.
All right, then. Let us take
these girls to the basement.
I guess we lost him.
I apologize for roping you into this.
No, if it weren't for me, you wouldn't
have let the thief escape.
Is that the...
Looks like the robber's cart.
No one's around.
Let's check out the antique dealer.
What is it?
A town like this always has a couple
of dealers who specialize in stolen goods.
You're really knowledgeable.
- It's my job.
- Your job?
Why don't you wait here.
I'll go and get some information.
Yeah. I'll see you later.
Jut stay here, okay?
Wow, what a swift person.
That was close!
I almost revealed my true identity.
Well, let the investigation begin!
I wonder what his profession is.
The music festival will be held here.
Let us drink wine to King Loon
and his excitement about the event.
What an honor. The Queen and the rest
of the royal family are to accompany him.
Of course, they won't miss the performance
of the famous Lute of the Moon Singer...
produced by the famous Rumzeth.
Certainly. But...
What is it?
There's a rumor about a group
of insurgents...
who intend to assassinate the King.
The elite force is to accompany
the King, but...
Make sure to keep tight security.
As you wish.
Let's go. Get the horses ready.
Why didn't you tell them
that you are...
the insurgents they were
talking about, Duke?
So it's you, Duchess Jarl.
Perhaps after tonight...
I'll be addressing you as King.
It all depends on how you perform tonight...
By the way, have you
got the Lute of the Moon Singer?
I will soon. Meanwhile...
Yuck.
That old hag,
she's seducing him. Disgusting!
This plot's horrible!
They're planning on killing
every single member of the royal family!
How do you know
they're planning to kill them all?
Because, this isn't just a renowned lute.
It has another face.
A scary face that it keeps hidden.
Look at them.
Sickening!
Who's there!
- It's me!
- Idiot!
Who are you?
I'm just here to deliver
this lute for you, sir.
Lute of the Moon Singer?
It's you. You got it then. Well done.
But, why are you here?
When I went to your house,
I was told to come here.
Our security is tight, but how did you...
I am a great mysterious thief
named Lord Bagas...
and I can deal with any security.
Thanks for your trouble.
Wait a second there, Granny.
This job is worth way more
than the petty cash you offered.
Do you know what I mean?
Are you trying to up the price?
Too bad.
So, you heard everything.
Wait. I'll agree to the payment
that we negotiated.
I didn't mind it really.
It's worth the trouble.
I'm nothing more than a petty thief.
Goodbye!
Please, don't!
I heard that
a suspicious man with a scar...
entered this underground water outlet
with a lute.
What do we do?
I've got no other clue.
I've got no choice but to follow.
You mean, in there?
You'll be much safer if you wait here.
But I'm the one
who got you into this mess.
I don't want to put you in
any kind of danger.
If I'm not too much of a burden,
take me with you.
All right. Let's go!
- I won't let you escape!
- Please let go!
- I heard someone's voice.
- Female.
It hurts! You're ripping my tail off!
If you come quietly with me,
I won't hurt you. Too much.
No way! I'll never return.
It was supposed to be maid service.
They deceived me!
If you don't return,
they'll do the same thing to me...
so you better come back!
Hey, you okay!
Help please!
Okay, hold on!
I will not let you escape!
Careful!
I'm falling off again!
Let me hear the performance.
Hey, treat me with respect!
Hey, say something!
! I don't care about the performances,
please, untie the rope!
Don't leave me here!
Why are they locking the door?
Looks like they're going to experiment.
What?
What experiment?
Cursed Song.
Is the old hag going to perform it?
Lyon! Lyon!
Where did she go?
Probably fallen down elsewhere.
This place's a maze.
I could have sworn
I got away form them.
Keith.
Keith!
I wonder just where he ended up.
I'm in trouble.
I let that bunny girl escape.
Now, I'll be the one hunted down.
Keith!
I got an idea! As long as
it's a woman, the Duke's happy!
I know just how to fix this mess.
There seems to be no effect, Master.
Looks like the renowned instrument
only plays...
for a performer of its own choosing.
I agree.
Go right away and search
for a proper performer.
Yes sir!
Shit. What an old fix I got myself into.
It's better than being killed,
look on the bright side.
Well, I guess you've got a point there.
That old hag! Making me listen
to that performance without any pay!
I tried to tell you,
the bad performance saved us all.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Now, tell me!
Where's the owner of that lute?
I don't know! That old hag, she was...
she made me deliver the hot...
It's too much for me to handle.
I don't know anything about...
So, you'll pardon me?
I really don't know! She followed me
through the woods...
what was I supposed to do?
Where about?
Just outside the town.
By the river, near the woods!
You heard him.
Yes sir.
I have a bad feeling.
He might've been better off dead.
That's the Duke's voice. This way!
Come on!
That's too bad.
Duke! I brought you a woman in place
of the bunny rabbit!
I guess he's not just into women.
The thief who stole my lute!
What!
The owner of the Lute of the Moon Singer?
The light!
We finally got out!
Just like Master told me:
The best way to get out of a maze...
is to always keep to the left!
Now I can go back home!
I'm so happy!
Where's Lyon? She's still not back.
Here, take this.
- Carrots?
- Sign of my gratitude.
Thanks.
Bye-bye! See you later!
- I won't go back, no!
- What are you?
Disappeared!
Above us!
Good instinct!
What's this?
I can't breathe.
Sleeping vapor.
This is not an impossible request.
Simply use your lute
and sing the Cursed Song.
Play it less powerful. Just enough
to make the listeners fall asleep.
Because you see, my dear,
we have to keep everyone happy.
I will not do it.
Very well.
You'll soon feel better.
Stop.
You bitch!
Duke, I'm so sorry for the delay.
We caught the owner
of the lute by the red cart.
Who's this woman?
Keith!
He helped me.
Lyon.
Excuse me, Duke. The King
and his company have arrived!
What have I done to deserve this!
I'm sure Keith will sort this out.
How could you do this to me?
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Let me introduce the renown singer
Lyon Rumzeth.
Who shall play the Lute of the Moon Singer.
I trust you'll enjoy the performance.
What're you up to?
Forcing her to perform like that...
that's really cruel!
You don't know? Lute of the Moon Singer
can produce the Cursed Song...
which will kill the listeners
after driving them insane.
You mean to kill the King and all?
Yes.
But I asked her not to unleash
the full power of the instrument.
Otherwise, even if we couldn't hear
the song, we'd be in danger.
The Cursed Song is as terrible as that.
And that's why, all we want
is for them to fall fast asleep.
I'll pull this lever, and the boat,
along with them all, will then sink.
And they will all be drowned together.
Don't you think
it's a beautiful plan, my boy?
You mean to kill her, too?
But of course. You're friends
in the basement, too.
Under our feet.
No loose ends. Don't worry, though.
You'll be following right after.
How will you feel when you're struggling
for your last breath in the water?
You devil!
Let's see...
It's almost ready.
That woman, she must really like this lad.
- Get him to stand up.
- Yes sir.
What a lucky fellow.
Jealous?
Look!
Keith?
I'm okay! Continue singing!
Just keep going.
But...
We'll all be killed! Quick!
Duke?
Let go! Otherwise, you'll be dead too!
Along with your friends.
Never!
- I'll take you with me!
- No way!
Stop! Please stop!
- Keith.
- Lyon.
You did it! How about the King!
They're fine.
They all fell asleep with my lullaby.
But why aren't you affected?
What did you say?
Look.
It's strange.
Earplugs usually don't work.
Really, no way.
Maybe that means I'm special to you.
Maybe.
Really, you mean it?
- Lyon?
- Yes?
I want to hear your love song.
You'll let me sing it?
Be gentle.
It hurts.
You're so wet.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't tease me.
Really wet.
- Can I go inside you?
- Hurry quick!
Don't make me wait!
Open your legs wider!
I want to see more.
Don't tease me.
I'm going crazy!
This is so incredible!
Elfarcia!
I'll enter from the front door.
A flower girl?
This early in the morning?
I guess I'll get some flowers for Elfarcia.
Where's she going?
Hey, you left your basket!
Kind of strange wood.
Where did she go?
Beauty.