Elfarcia...
Alright!
I'll enter from the front door after all.
Huh?
Flower girl?
This early in the morning?
Well, let me get some flowers for Elfarcia...
Huh?
Where's she going?
Hey, you left your basket behind!
Hmm? Sun's setting all of a sudden.
What's going on?
Kinda strange wood.
Oh well, what about her?
Where'd she go? Hmm?
B-Beauty...
A legendary unicorn!
Yup. Unicorn!
Hush... Be quiet!
B- Beauty...
It's a job I got from a dying geezer.
I've looked for it over a month,
and I finally found it.
M... Mysty?!
Tut, not even recognizing
your childhood pal...
Keith, you aren't after it yourself, are you?
Lt?
The horn of the unicorn,
known to heal any illness...
Wait! You're after that female elf, are you?!
Geez, you haven't changed a bit...
But, I think it's gonna be trouble...
Don't know why, but unicorns only make
their appearance in front of virgin girls.
And, that means, she's gotta be a virgin.
Elves are puritanical to begin with,
and she's a virgin to top it off...
Is that to anesthetize it?
Yup, if I could capture it alive,
I'll have endless supply of the horns...
because they regenerate after being cut off.
Wow... she's grown up. Yeah.
What?
Oh, no-nothing, nothing at all...
Oh, I finally found it!
Get the net ready, would ya?
The girl... Capture the girl too?
There's no point without her. Just go
and get ready! And clean yourself up.
Yeah, yeah.
Shit! I won't let you!
Mysty!
Romance is in the Flash of the Sword II
Episode 4 "Unicorn... Oh, Hurry up!?"
Humph... Where'd Keith go?
Look at that. Leaving us here with
all the work of the restaurant...
How could he subject us to this
physical labor? How could he?
Well I get what you're sayin', but we didn't
really ask you to help, alright.
Oh, no, Slimester!
You can't treat me like that!
Oh no. You have to be good to me.
You cannot tease me. I'm to be treated
with respect, you know. So don't be...
What's that?
From the Forest of Deception...
See the plume of misty water?
It was a big noise.
Wonder if the volcano erupted...
My lady! Are you okay?
Oh, I'm glad you're fine.
I just heard a violent explosion. Hmm?
How dangerously close... Oh... That's...
Mr. Angel! He's going away.
This must be a sign
for me to follow after him!
I shouldn't just wait for him to come to me...
Gramps!
Why, yes?
Gramps! Let's follow it!
Yes, ma'am. As you wish, my lady.
You okay, Mysty?
Stole my booty! I won't let them escape!
Tut, the gale blew me so hard,
I latched onto this, but what's goin' on?
Help.
Hmm?
Help me, please.
Don't worry! I'll rescue you! Stay there!
You are?
Keith Ryan!!
Keith... Keith Ryan.
What's that?
It's not a bird.
I saw people hanging from it.
Wait! Wasn't that Keith?
Oh no! He was with a girl! Hmmm?
Say, I smell some treasure.
The winner's shield is encrusted with
the King's treasured jewel then?
That's right. The winner of
the Toolux Darby tonight...
shall receive it from King Lune
to celebrate the 100th event.
The race is open to anyone...
and that's why the best of the best around
the country and abroad are gathered here...
But, we know who's the winner.
It should be Farlanks,
the Chief of the Royal Elite Force.
Tut, the Chief of
the Royal Elite Force, Farlanks.
With them competing, I can't fix the race
or drug the competition. It's not fair.
You've privatized
the Horse Racing Association...
and always rigged the races
without interference.
This is your reward
for pilfering the winnings, I say.
Cut it out!
All you have to do is to win the race
as I ordered you. Just do it and stop talking!
And, without rigging the race
or risking anything...
you'll win your bets and make money,
loads and loads of money. It's great!
That's right.
If you, a nameless rider,
can beat the strongest candidate...
the Chief of Royal Elite Force, Farlanks,
and steal the victory...
then, I'll pay you the money I promised,
along with the winner's shield!
Good. Stay calm and quiet...
It sure is extremely fast,
but what about the rider?
Don't worry.
Everything's already been taken care of...
Oh, Geez, they can't fly this thing for beans.
Couldn't they land
without slamming it down?
My head hurts, it really does.
You're finally up!
Stop jabbering and help me down from here!
Geez! Come on!
Nice view...
No! Please don't!
I smell a virgin...
Smells delicious...
No...
- No... Please don't!
- Nipple... nipple... Found it.
- Rub, rub... squeeze, squeeze.
- Stop!
Let me stick my finger in...
It hurts... no... no, don't... please don't...
- Oh, no... please, no... don't!
- How about my other finger?
This is the bowler's grip.
Squeeze, squeeze. Nipple, nipple.
No...
You say don't, but you're very wet...
Please, stop.
No...
Instead of one, let me try two. How's it feel?
No, stop, please.
Please!
Keith, please help me now...
Please help me. No, don't!
No!
Don't... please...
Don't...
I want her! But I was told
to restrain myself...
But just a little...
Maybe just the tip of my little...
Yeah, I want it!
No!
Don't!
Oh, no!
Keith, where are you?
You, idiot! If she loses her virginity,
she'll be worthless to me!
I'm... l'm sorry...
Now... You must listen to me.
It's simple. You must win the race
riding that unicorn! Understand?
- There's no second place.
- Why... me?
There's only one elf among all elves...
who can ride on that difficult
and headstrong unicorn.
And that's you.
But... l'm just...
You're just... begging the unicorn...
to save the villagers who suffer
from that strange infectious disease?
Please, Unicorn.
Help the villagers with your power...
How'd you know?
Because, this is the cause of the disease.
It was you?
That's right. And that's why it's easy
to make all the vaccine we need.
It'll be more reliable than
the horn of a unicorn, wouldn't you say?
Good girl. Alright, put some clothes on her
and take her away.
Now, I'm guaranteed to get
the King's treasured jewel!
It's too good to be appreciated by those
interested only in money, wealth and power.
Shit!
Don't be a fool.
If you dive in right now,
you'd be overpowered.
It's not like she's in a dire situation.
Let's wait for the right opportunity...
Er... nothing.
It's just that I realize, Mysty,
you've grown up a lot since I saw you last.
Careful!
Keith... Don't hold me so tightly.
It's getting me in a strange mood...
Me too...
What're you doing?
Stop... what're you...
No...
No, I'm embarassed.
I can see yours clearly, Mysty...
Don't...
You're... already wet...
Don't... stop teasing me...
Then... l'll get inside you...
Teaser... don't stop...
Then how's this?
I'm bursting... no... gently...
Harder... no... no... more... more...
I'm going crazy... more...
Falling... falling... I can't take it.
No... l'm coming... coming... coming...
Mr. Angel.
He disappeared over the horizon...
I'm sorry, my lady.
You must understand, this is an antique,
handed down from our ancestors...
Oh, Gramps, your face is dirty...
Ah, my lady, don't bother.
How thoughtful you are.
Oh no, I made it even dirtier...
Gramps... Funny! Oh, Gramps,
don't make me laugh like that...
Are we lost now?
That never happens.
What are you talkin' about, you idiot?
We lost sight a long time ago.
My sense of smell is superhuman,
you know.
You're smelling the treasure?
Nope... The scent of Keith!
Eeek... Nauseating!
Oh no, Slimester! It's yucky!
Our majesties are seated now.
Soon, the race should begin.
Woa, what glitzy costumes!
It helps celebrate the 100th anniversary.
This'll help not to draw attention
to the elf and the unicorn.
Oh, I gotcha!
As soon as she reaches the goal, secure
them! I'll go get the shield! Understand?
Right!
Anyway, she's chained,
so she won't be able to escape...
Keith Ryan...
Hmm... a shooting star...
Mr. Angel, I suppose I shouldn't have
come after you...
Oh, this marshmallow is delicious! Yummy.
Success, my lady, it's finally repaired!
Gramps... Let's go home.
I'm sure Mr. Angel will make my wish come
true if I wait patiently. So, let's go home.
Please, let's go home.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, hey, ladies...
You're totally distracting from the race.
Those jewels of yours
are dying to rest in my pocket...
I get it. We're here for Keith, aren't we?
What are you thinkin' about, man?
Ah, no worries.
I'm sure Keith's working hard,
doing his thing.
You know how he does it.
Keith'll be angry to hear that.
He's not a pickpocket
or small-time sneaky thief, you know.
Incredible! There's no comparison
with any other jewels I've...
Gramps...
Yes?
It was fun.
Will you take me out like this again?
As you wish, my lady.
What do I do?
Because this is the cause of the disease.
It was you?
That's right. And that's why it's easy
to make all the vaccine we need.
It'll be more reliable than
the horn of a unicorn, wouldn't you say?
You see, Farlanks is winning.
With a big lead... as expected...
Looks like it's gonna work out.
So, what's the plan?
Once she reaches the goal,
we'll bring her and the unicorn back.
We'll get rid of those two men,
so that they don't cause us any trouble.
There's no reason to give up
the winning shield.
We'll just make sure not to let
the Elite Force notice anything...
Crap, I think I hit something...
Hey, can't you do better?
Why don't you fly this then?
Er... no, I trust you. So, what's next?
Don't you know? We'll get the unicorn back
using their method!
Great idea...
You, ready?
Where'd you go?
Set up a trick...
A trick?
Yup, to get that treasure, you know.
That treasure up there...
I see her!
Alright! Get the net ready.
Sure will!
It's about time...
Oh, yummy! My favorite!
Meanwhile, I'll get the treasure!
The horses have gone wild
for all of the carrots!
Our plan! We didn't even have the sex...
Ellis!! I'm here to rescue you!
Keith Ryan!
Woa, was that Keith just now?
I got it!
We'll take her back to her elf village...
and they'll let me have the unicorn's horn
as a reward... That's it!
You sure it's okay?
Yes. The unicorn promised
to save the villagers.
As for me, as an elf, I must fulfill
my elfin pledge to my rescuer.
So, it's alright...
You'll be gentle, will you?
I'm embarrassed...
You're beautiful, Ellis...
You're already wet...
I want your strength too, Keith Ryan...
How muscular... and big... hot...
That's good, Ellis...
That feels really good, Ellis.
I want you... but I'm scared... it's so big...
Don't...
I'm going crazy... l'm scared... hurry, Keith...
I'm scared... no... oh, no...
Don't... it hurts... slowly... it's hot... it's hot.
Don't... l'm... I'm so full... oh, no.
It's good... it's good...
Makes me feel... l'm coming...
Finally! I can see the forest of unicorns
right up ahead!
Hey, Keith! We'll be landing soon!
Keith? Hey, Keith!
Say something? What's wrong?
You promiscuous man!
Get out and cool your head!
Hmm... lt's cold...
Mr. Angel, please hear my wish once again.
Ah, Mr. Angel!
Mr. Angel... You've heard my wish...
Your wish?
You must be here to deliver
my Silver Rainbow...
Yeah. I'm here to...
I can't come out for a reason.
Can you come over here?
Yes!
Here! Is this it?
Yes! Oh! So, you are my Mr. Angel!
It was not really a big deal.
What's that?
Nothing! It's nothing!
I don't mean to take advantage,
but if you like what I've done...
Oh, yes...
To my wet lips,
your soft, sweet and melting...
Yes...
Now, come here... soft... Elfarcia.
Soft and sweet, melting.
A kiss from you... melting... Melting?
Hmm? Marshmallow!
Yes, my favorite, sweet and melting.
Delicious, isn't it?
Would you like another one?
I bet you'd really like it.
Oh, Mr. Angel...
Oh, he must've left.
My Mr. Angel...
I haven't left yet!
Ouch... My butt... my butt... it hurts!
If the moonlight wasn't this bright,
I could go home naked...
but anyone who sees me will treat me
like a pervert... Hmm? That girl.
She's Spika, I'm sure.
Oh, I'm lucky! Hey! Spika!
I'm sure she's Spika... but not Spika?
Eeek! What's that?
B... Beauty...