If you like what I've done...
Yes...
To my wet lips
your soft, sweet and melting...
Yes...
Now, come here... soft... Elfarcia.
Soft and sweet, melting.
A kiss from you... melting... Melting?
Hmm? Marshmallow!
Yes, my favorite, sweet and melting.
It's delicious. Would you like another one?
I'm sure you'd like it.
Oh, Mr. Angel...
Oh, he must've left.
My Mr. Angel...
I haven't left yet!
Ouch... My butt... my butt... it hurts!
If the moonlight wasn't this bright,
I could go home naked...
but anyone who sees me will treat me
like a pervert... Hmm? That girl.
She's Spika, I'm sure.
Oh, I'm lucky! Hey! Spika!
I'm sure she's Spika... but not Spika?
Eeek! What's that?
B-Beauty...
Geez... I got no treasure. That's not fair.
Blame your greed for your loss,
not me, you big numbnuts!
Interference...
- Hey! Wait! Wait!
- Hmm... What was I? Keith?
Pervert.
Romance is in the Flash of the Sword II
Episode 5 "For the sake of... Ellise!?"
I just said you took it wrong!
Say something for me, Master!
That idiot, Keith!
Spika!
Hey you, give it up! I said...
Sorry... Sorry.
Alright, I understand why you're so mad.
What went wrong with Keith last night?
He was acting so weird.
How exactly would I know?!
How would you know... how would I know?!
In the middle of the road!
Even with your charm.
You're not the most desirable date, I'd say...
What date?! Who and who?
There was a man and a woman.
It was a romantic night.
The moon was out,
and the man was so excited.
I mean, he was a hussy, she was a hussy,
and they were hussing each other.
The romance... oh.
What a wicked hussy, I mean,
a man playing a hussy.
Woa! That's gotta hurt.
Oh boy.
I hate homosexuals!
Hey, did you see just now?
Another woman right next to Spika!
No...
So tell me, am I delusional?
But, I could really see that girl...
that pretty girl...
Not nice... really.
But I wasn't on a date with him!
Yeah, I know.
You didn't have to do that though.
What's this? I did it?
If it wasn't a date,
what were you two doing there?
Hmm, you know... I can't remember...
Hmmm, how mysterious!
It's a puzzle... Hmmm...
What happened to Keith, I wonder?
Hey, you! What're you doing?
Oh... What's happening to me?
Humph?
What's this? Is this...
Did Mr. Angel leave this behind?
Gramps! Gramps!
Hmmm... Spika... Where's she going?
I don't know. But, look at this fog
coming down... on a bright sunny day.
Body Conditioning Center?
It's the popular massage parlor.
Spika's got a great body,
but she's been complaining about her thigh.
She says it's too thick.
I don't know what she's talking about.
Women are never satisfied.
I think it looks great.
You can't live with them,
you can't live without them.
Master said she left hurriedly
after work yesterday, too.
I don't know what's going on,
do you?
Actually, I do. That means
the secret is right here.
What do you mean?
Ouch!
What I mean is that I'm the only one
who can see that pretty girl.
That's why I have to find out exactly
who she really is, you see?
This guy, he's sure loaded
with a lot of dreams and desires.
You don't need to tell me,
I can see the effects.
Thanks to you.
But, I can't allow too much...
I want that beauty to massage me too...
For whom is it
that you want to be beautiful?
Oh yes, my secret.
Keith...
Not that spot...
This? Or, how about this?
See, you're getting wet.
You'll be feeling more... You like this?
No... l'm embarrassed.
- Don't stop. Yes, more!
- Do you regularly masturbate alone?
Don't... l'm embarrassed... I feel it...
A lot harder...
Hey, Keith... Something's wrong.
That's not like the Spika we know...
Didn't know Spika gets that excited...
That's not what I mean.
Oh, boy, this guy.
When you masturbate,
what do you think of, me?
Keith... This is better than masturbating...
No... no... no... no...
It's good...
I'm going crazy...
No... no...
I've never felt this way before...
What're you doing?
It's the best way to deal with
that poisonous fog... come on.
What are you talking about?
Poisonous fog?
It was really close.
This is what happens
when you two try to outsmart me, see?
Hey, where's Keith?
No idea.
I followed you and entered
that courtyard below...
and I found you unconscious
because of the fog.
There was nobody else there.
It's totally deserted.
No Spika there either?
That high-strung girl was with you too?
Well, no one's there.
And the worst part of it all is I can't find
any hint of a treasure anywhere!
No, we weren't after it to begin with...
What? You were not after a treasure?
Then, what on earth are you doing here?
Why were you inside
those dangerous ruins?
What, ruins?
What is this all about? I just don't know.
It's good...
Oh, yeah!
Oh, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, fuck me!
So, you're saying, Keith and Spika are
both imprisoned in that world?
Yeah... They vanished without a trace.
That's the only answer.
I can't believe it!
It's up to you to decide
if you want to believe it.
It's just that, I've heard that long ago
this village was totally destroyed...
by poisonous fog that suddenly burst
from the ground.
Since then, either because of the dead
villagers' curse or the poisonous fog...
travelers have been known to get lured in...
only to go mad and die
after a painful struggle.
Apparently, before they die,
they all say...
"I feel so good, as if I'm in a dream..."
Is that so? I'm happy for you.
Huh? You... that pretty girl!
Anyone who enters here finds pleasure.
I wonder how many men
I seduced and slept with...
But, my body's never satisfied...
You did?
Borrowing that one's body...
I tried to feel the pleasure and pain
men failed to give me, but...
You borrowed her body?
I used her body and sought
pleasure from you...
but in vain, as usual.
It's not my body after all.
Why are you doing that?
I was born an aristocrat...
and because of that, I was raised
under the strict eye of my guardian.
And, before I could taste any freedom,
I was forced to marry for political reasons.
It turned out that the man I married was gay.
He'd lock me in my room while he brought
home man after man, night after night.
That's horrible...
Despite that, he was extremely jealous.
He'd whip me just because
I spoke to an errand boy...
then he'd chain me in a flooded basement.
At the end, he threw me out
and left me here.
So tell me, why do you cry?
I'm sorry for you... Come to me...
Every man took fright once I revealed who I
was, trembling and begging for forgiveness.
They all went mad, turned crazy and died.
But, why not you...?
Hold my hand.
It's not possible.
It's possible. So long as we
understand each other. I'm sure...
Doesn't work.
Don't give up.
Why, it's warm...
You are so gentle.
You are so beautiful.
I can feel it.
Please be gentle...
It's unbelievable...
Oh no... I can feel it... don't...
Don't hurt me...
No, don't stop...
Oh, come quick!
I can feel it...
Oh, yeah.
It's good.
Good... it's good...
I feel it... l've never...
My lady, how far do we need to go?
I'm not sure, but we're not there yet.
I think this sword really misses him,
you know?
Really?
Oh, gramps, that way,
let's head towards that cliff, right over there.
Yes, my lady.
You're no longer translucent...
I can finally leave the earth... thank you.
What do you mean? You're finally...
I had to get my body back.
Without doing that,
the curse couldn't be broken.
I would've had to keep haunting this place
for ever and a day.
Now, finally, I can take my leave.
Thank you.
I'll go. But before I do, tell me your name.
Alright... Keith Ryan. And you?
It's Ellise, but I don't remember
my last name.
Ellise... it's a good name.
Nice to meet you.
After all I've done for you,
how dare you!
You're not a masseuse?
She brought me back from
the world of dead... A she-demon...
A she-demon?
You've used me yourself, just as much,
and enjoyed the taste, didn't you?
You mean the pleasure victims I ate?
Ate?
That was just an hors d'oeuvre.
The main dish is your
resurrected bodies, pure...
Eating your bodies will give me
eternal youth and life.
That's why you brought me back...
It's promised to all demons.
Your white leg should be fried...
your brain, sherbet...
- your eyeballs and nipples for salad...
- Stop dreaming!
Stop it!
Don't interfere! I'll eat you up later, slowly.
But first, it's time to slaughter!
Shit!
Huh? What was that?
Big earthquake, wasn't it?
Look! The poisonous fog's clearing!
Thank god!
This thing's really uncomfortable...
Damn! It's that lady over there!
What a wreck of a place.
Hmm, there's someone over there.
It's here, I'm sure... Excuse me...
I think it might be here...
That's right. I'm certain it's here.
No way! Look at that!
Isn't that Keith's Shadow Blade?
What are you doing, my lady?
We've played enough. Now, die!
Watch out, my lady!
Shadow Blade?
Take this blow!
Incredibly... powerful!
What really happened?
Humph? What was I doing?
Good-bye, Keith.
Good-bye, Ellise.
I just remembered... That girl.
She loves you. Did you know?
Did you?
Spika?
Thank you, Keith Ryan!
Spika? Spika?!
So, Spika loves me...
Keith...
Oh, yes, that feels so good!
Oh, yes.
I've been waiting for so long.
Keith, I love you!
Spika...
Please be gentle...
No... don't hurt me...
Don't worry... You're so wet.
See, you can hear it...
Oh, yes!
Oh, no.
Oh, no...
Oh, no, it hurts... don't tease.
Don't stop... it's big... l'm bursting...
Oh, yeah!
I'm full! Don't... don't...
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes!
I'm coming...
But really, Keith and Spika,
where did they go?
I'm sure they'll eventually show up.
But he's... but he's... my Mr. Angel...