No...
No... I can't take it... No.
No... please.
Stop.
How about this, then?
It hurts... more... harder... no...
This way? Or this way?
Give it to me.
That's right...
That's good... lt feels so good... just right.
Come, please, quick. Please.
It hurts... no...
More... more...
I'm going crazy...
Good.
Come on now! Unlock and reopen
the gate that's been closed far too long.
So, this woman isn't the right one either.
Will my wish ever come true?
Who's this?
It's her! I finally found the right woman.
Go! And bring that woman to me!
Romance is in the Flash of the Sword II
Episode 6 "Oh no... is this the very last!?"
Mr. Angel...
But he's... but he's... my Mr. Angel...
Hmm? It's just that...?
Mr. Angel... Gramps, let's go home...
Yes, my lady...
If only we could stay like this forever...
What?
Oh, it's really nothing...
Hey! That's Elfarcia.
Wait!
It was Elfarcia!
She brought this to me and then...
Take this blow!
What the hell! Shit!
Elfarcia!
I'm coming, my lady!
Save Elfarcia! Hurry!
Right!
Damn it!
Not quite yet! Just hold tight!
Hold on! No worries!
Isn't that Keith over there?
Oh, no! Just as soon as we find him,
he runs after another girl!
He's always running after
other girls he sees.
A servant demon of an evil wizard?
You mean that disgusting monster?
That's right.
It's been rumored that within the ruins
in that lake lives a powerful wizard...
and for centuries he has wanted to
destroy the world.
They say he commits evil acts against any
travelers or villagers who come close.
But why does he want to destroy the world?
It doesn't make sense.
From what I hear,
he wants to change the world...
...so that it will look like
the place he used to live.
That story, I want you
to tell me more about it.
What are you?
A priestess warrior, Rena Carmine.
A friend of Keith.
A friend of Keith?
We serve food here,
so will you leave your dog outside?
He's not a dog, but Albion, out.
If the rumor's true, and evil wizard lives...
that might explain a number of recent,
mysterious disasters and disappearances.
We've lost track.
Oh no... my lady...
My lady!
Elfarcia!
Mr. Angel is... here to rescue me...?
Help me!
My lady!
Brought some extra trouble with her,
so it seems.
Please... let me go...
Welcome. I apologize for the rough
invitation, my lady. I hope you accept.
And, you are...?
I finally found her...
I'll fall!
Like I said, this cliff's... too tough.
Please don't worry.
I'm prepared to go through
fire and brimstone to save my lady.
Anything for her sake, so help me!
Yeah, I understand, but to tell the truth,
you're more of a burden than anything else.
Finally, we've got rid of that extra trouble...
Hmm? That's enough! Stop that!
I have a deep relationship with Keith,
you see.
Your relationship? I think mine's
much deeper than yours, you know.
How silly they are. Depth. It is with me.
He's popular.
Oh, he's my Keith.
The ritual to transform the world
is about to begin!
Are you alright?
Hey!
Please, you must go on without me
and rescue my lady at all cost.
Just promise me.
Now, no more load on me. Now I can
move faster. Alright! Time to speed up!!
Elfarcia! Where... where are you?
Elfarcia... where are you?
Wake up.
You and I shall change
and transform this world...
so that it will resemble where
I can no longer return... my home world.
Elfarcia! Shit, she's nowhere.
Elfarcia... Hmm? What's this sound I hear?
It's this way?
Now, come here...
Now, let us unite!
Get wet! Get wet! Wet yourself!
Elfarcia!
Just a bit more...
Elfarcia! Elfarcia!
Tut, how is he still alive!?
Elfarcia! Damn it!
Can't you move anymore? That's no fun.
Now, you die!
Well done, my friend.
How will you escape now?
Spika!
Keith!
Jannette... Why you're here?
Meddlers!
Keith! We're here to rescue you!
What?!
A priestess warrior?!
Tell me, are you the wizard
who defiles god?
Good! Well done!
She's in trouble!
Here goes!
We'll lose our balance!
Help!
Fireball!
Albion!
For my lady I will withstand any torture...
rocks, arrows, slings... even rectal itch!
I will do it!
I never said anything about monsters
raining down on me!
Oh no, I'm back at the bottom again.
Oh no, my dear lady!
Don't scare me!
Let go!
I won't!
I won't give up Elfarcia to anyone!
Keith...
Keith... please.
Elfarcia belongs to me.
Mr. Angel...
How obstinate... Tell me, who are you?
Keith Ryan!
The famous thief known throughout
the Continent of Destragoon? It can't be.
I'm the rightful successor to the greatest
thief of this century, the Shadow Blade!
Today, that lineage will be terminated.
So far, it's been just foreplay.
In the name of the world, which I'm about
to transform with this woman...
let me inflict much greater destruction...
Mr. Angel, please escape and don't die...
Elfarcia, I came here just to rescue you!
Until I do, I won't die!
Mr. Angel...
You, bitch! What did you do?
Keith... I hope he's alright...
I'll return right away and organize
a search and rescue operation...
No, you don't.
That's just "inconsiderate" I say.
She's right on.
Well, you see,
that's how fate would have it...
Hey! I'll take them all back!
Don't worry! Okay?
Thanks so much, Bagas!
Now everyone...
Well now, he's acting like a man.
So what happened to him?
I know it wasn't part of our plan,
but I'm glad we could set these girls free.
Now that the wizard's spell is gone,
they don't seem to remember anything.
I don't know, they all seem
like they're from wealthy families.
I think he's just after gifts of gratitude.
He'll get to know where they live.
And if all goes well, he could end up
marrying one of these rich women.
You never know. Oh, boy.
Now, everyone!
I, Bagas, will take you home safely.
Yes!
I mistakenly thought you were an angel.
I really did, you know.
I am a thief, who's after your heart.
You didn't know that?
Keith Ryan, why don't you steal me?
Please steal me, Keith Ryan.
Alright.
You're warm...
Please, Keith, please be gentle.
I'm embarrassed.
No... don't hurt me...
Don't tease me...
It hurts.
Oh, no... no... no.
Please, please, no.
Mr. Angel...
It's like flying!
Fly, baby!
Feels so good.
Mr. Angel... Keith... you're so warm.
I'm hot... l'm burning up...
No... l'm coming...
Keith... Keith... Keith...
Beautiful!
You're more beautiful.
The End