Romance is in the Flash of the Sword II
Episode 1:
What? The Demon Returns?
It's gone! The pendant my mother
gave me. My Silver Rainbow.
Not here. It's gone!
I must've lost it when...
How pretty. They look so delicious!
Lady Elfarcia, if you really want them,
please just ask me, your servant.
My lady.
That's not it, Gramps.
All I want is to be able to go
out like this sometimes.
Lady Elfarcia, you're the only heir
to the noble house of Arcline.
Your father doesn't want anything
to happen to you.
Am I a caged bird?
It's not...
Excuse me.
You okay, Gramps?
I'm fine.
But what a rough fellow!
Yes, that must've been it.
What should I do?
That pendant has been handed down
from my ancestors of Arcline.
I have an idea:
My mother used to tell me
that if one can spot a shooting star...
when the moon shines brightly,
an angel can make one's wish to come true.
Master came up with
a great invention once again.
This way, I can service
a lot larger area as an adventurer.
This is absolutely fantastic.
But, the only types of jobs you get are
delivering things or searching for lost stuff.
I'm sure I'll get a good job
that suits me, soon enough.
Hey, don't lose control!
I can't believe your
father was the famous and honorable thief...
known throughout the Destragoon
Continent as Shadow Blade.
I can't take this!
You're killing me!
You stole this cigar from my client,
didn't you, you little bandit.
Are we thieves, or what?
You just want me to give it back.
You just want me to give
it back to them.
It's no use to you,
you who don't even know how to use it.
You're right-I can't appreciate it!
That's not the point!
What's this burning smell?
A shooting star! Dear Angel,
please let my wish to come true!
It's you, Mr. Angel.
Get off of me!
Who's the angel?
Mr. Angel, please hear my wish.
Please hear it.
My precious "Silver Rainbow" has been
stolen by someone. Please find it.
Can you help me? Please help.
Silver Rainbow?
Please find it and return it to me safely.
All right! I'll see that your wish comes true.
Lady Elfarcia!
Lady Elfarcia! I heard some
very loud noise just now.
Are you all right?
Gramps.
It was an angel!
And he heard my wish!
He's going to help me
find my silver rainbow pendant.
So, Silver Rainbow's a treasure
of historic value.
Master, do you know of a place
that specializes in stolen goods?
Curio dealers or some antique stores.
Anything like that at all?
Spika!
Sorry! Sorry!
Hey Spika, what's up with you?
Where you been?
What's up with Keith, do you know?
I don't know anything about him.
He's been acting weird since last night.
Wonder if he's found another woman.
Something like that.
Who knows. Do you think I'm
his supervisor or something.
Don't get so excited.
I like you. I can remember everything
until we fell out of that hang-glider.
I can't remember after that.
Everything that happened
to Keith, I mean.
Hey, you. What are you doing there?
Let me up.
Welcome!
Let me take your order.
What would you like?
An adventure. A job offer.
An adventure? Yes!
She's a reporter of ruins, is she?
She's to write about the Ruin
of the Glurd Palace.
I say, it's a beauty's encounter
with the mystery of an ancient ruin.
This region is loaded with bandits.
I guess you're her bodyguard.
Are you grumbling?
With the reward and the thrill...
it's a perfect job for the adventurer Keith,
don't you think?
Would you rather sit around?
You probably have another reason,
don't you?
What do you mean?
I don't have any dirty thoughts
about my employer.
If that's what you're talking about.
Sorry to disturb your conversation.
This road. Isn't this a detour to the Ruin
of the Glurd Palace?
I hear that the area surrounding
the ruin is rather dangerous...
so I'm planning to hire an excellent guide.
A guide?
Master told me about this excellent
guide named Rycure, in the town of Gido.
Why do they think they can
take advantage of me, stupid hicks!
This isn't cheapo stuff.
They're not going to fool me. No way.
Vannessa!
Bagas.
What're you doing here?
You look really annoyed, Vanessa.
Frankly speaking, I am annoyed!
Don't say that.
Just let me be on it.
What're you talking about?
Don't hide it from me would you?
I have nothing to hide
from a sneaky thief like you.
I'm talking about that treasure.
You know the one that's getting all sweaty...
between the valley of your breasts.
Know what I'm talking about?
That's you?
That's right. I'm Rycure,
an excellent guide to the ruins.
Got any problem?
None, no problems at all.
If you want to worry,
worry about that lady waiting outside.
There's a rough-looking rogue's advancing
on her, and won't leave her alone.
Help!
What's up?
He's actually manly. What a surprise!
Is that right?
Hey, wait! I haven't
done anything to you yet.
Murderer!
As I expected.
That dagger is Shadow Blade.
He scared me.
Window repair will be charged along
with the guide fee, okay?
Didn't know it was your place.
- This way!
- Hang on tightly!
Why am I doing this?
Really, don't worry about it.
You know what?
Keith's got no problem
using people roughly.
Except that he's gentle with women.
How dare you!
Are you implying that I'm not a woman?
I didn't mean it that way.
Rycure, calm down. Don't worry about it.
I'm sure he's looking
for a delicious mushroom just for you.
How did this happen to us, Vanessa?
A man and a woman, traveling together.
It's a natural thing.
So, this dagger?
It's a memento of my dead father.
Is it?
So big.
Very well, let me have a good time.
I can't wait. Come on! Hurry!
That's good.
No, don't be rough.
Not there.
Don't tease me.
I'm coming. I'm coming!
Stronger! Harder!
The fluid of the descendant
of Shadow Blade.
With this, the seal will be broken.
Did I catch a little cold?
That's what happens when you sleep naked.
With ladies accompanying you,
how come you slept naked?
It was too hot to sleep.
Let's get going.
You're saying that woman
has the key to the treasure?
That's right.
We'll take both the treasure and the women.
Ready! Let's go!
It's getting hot. Aren't we there yet?
Once we pass over here, we're there.
Keith, you lack patience.
What's wrong, Rycure?
A danger is approaching.
A danger?
What's going on?
A danger is approaching?
Something will fall down.
Something'll fall down,
but, with this good weather?
What's that?
We're saved!
Can't believe rocks would fall.
Go hide!
Come on, Bandits! You'll learn the power
of Shadow Blade, the second generation!
It's really bad.
I was right about avoiding that fellow.
Anyhow, there's no way he'd win
against that mob.
Jannette!
Jannette's here to help us!
But, there's too many of them.
What's next?
What are you doing?
Be quiet. The power to you too.
Fireball!
This is the Ruins of the Glurd Palace.
Thanks. I'll start the research tomorrow.
Good! It's ready. Where's Jannette?
She said she wants to be alone.
Indeed, a lonely warrior.
Hey, it's me!
What do you want?
Have some! I'm not as good
as Master himself...
but as the branch manager,
I'm learning to cook, too.
Thanks for the help today.
So, could you find
what you're looking for at the battle?
I mean...
Who told you?
Master told me.
After being a mercenary for so long...
you don't see
the meaning in it anymore.
And that's why you're on the road.
That blabbermouth.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm not hungry.
Would you like mine?
What? Really?
By the way, who's that woman?
I say, she's a tragic female warrior,
who can no longer find romance in battles.
Just leave me alone!
Suit yourself then!
What's wrong?
I said that she's a girl and she should
try not to risk her life so much.
Then she said that attacking
bandits was her hobby.
She didn't want to be lectured.
Let's eat!
She risked her life to save us,
not for a hobby.
They're finally asleep.
This is the right way to go.
Vannessa?
Thanks to the stew loaded
with the sleeping pill, they're fast asleep.
Now, no one can interfere.
The fluid of the descendent
of Shadow Blade is in this stone.
It shall break the curse
that seals the demon and free him!
What? It's not the treasure she's after.
She wants to resurrect the Demon Dune!
Did it need more fluid?
It wasn't enough?
I will draw his blood.
No! You're a poor little sad lad.
Hey! Found her.
She's right here. Fast asleep!
They weren't all dead then.
She's a good looking woman, isn't she?
Instead of the treasure,
why don't we take her back?
The Chief will be excited!
Let's do that.
Yeah, let's. Here, pick her up.
She's heavy!
Demon Dune! Enjoy fully, the blood
of the descendant of Shadow Blade!
What's up?
Nothing.
This place...
I'm too excited to sleep
with the ruin and all. Shall we...
you know, do it?
The time has come to break
the seal that binds...
Demon Dune and for me to usurp his power!
As a reward for leading me here...
I'll allow you the honor
of seeing how I will unite...
with the Demon Dune!
And you shall die.
Rycure!
Are you the reincarnation
of the Palace Witch?
Take this!
With the power of the light and the air,
I shall seal you again...
to where you belong, Demon of darkness!
Rycure!
Did anything happen?
Rycure! You okay?
I'm too full to eat any more.
No! I've done nothing!
It's the bandits
who took that female warrior!
Jannette's kidnapped?
Where's their stronghold?
You assholes! You bastards!
Let me go!
This one's a good one.
Let me get my satisfaction
I couldn't get from the treasure.
Stop it!
No!
No, don't!
Stop it!
Well, you pretend you don't like it,
but your nipples don't lie.
What about this? Like this one?
You're getting really wet.
Don't! Stop!
Once this special lotion is applied,
you'd be the one crying for more.
Now, how's it?
Please don't!
Well, it's about time now.
The way she moves gets me horny.
Jannette! I'm here to take you back!
Keith!
Get him!
He's using our weapon against us!
What's wrong, Jannette? You okay?
Please, Keith. My body's so aroused.
I can't bear it. Please, I want you!
I want you.
Be gentle.
No.
Don't stop.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm going crazy.
No, don't.
No. You're breaking me apart.
More! Harder!
Here, the next one.
So, what shall I cook next?
How is it, Master? Is it yummy?
But of course! Nope, none of that.
Too bad, but I guess...
I can't cook for Keith.
Where's he anyway?
Since I saw him last.
There's been no messages
from Mr. Angel.
Elfarcia, I'll find your Silver Rainbow.
What? What an enormous dog!
Beauty.