Beautiful. l've never seen a more
beautiful woman. What a find!
lrresistible!
l can't stand anymore!
W-Who are you
No!
Who are you guys
Let me go! Let go of me!
Well, well, this lady
seems to be quite a handful.
That's perfect. Resist all you want.
Our clients love it when you do.
C-Clients
Well, let's get this started...
Koji, are you ready
Yes, you're going to get raped.
Y-You can't...
Right here, by me.
No! Stop it!
Hey, you've got more than l thought.
What are you guys doing
You know you won't get away with this!
W-What are you laughing at!
S-Stop, you can't...
Please.
Pretty good reaction over here.
How about this
Not there! Don't!
Don't touch me!
Damn, you talk too much.
l got no problem
letting you out with a...
ripped uniform and
your tits hanging out.
l'm sure everyone will
know what happened.
You'll get kicked out of
school. The neighbors will talk...
ls that what you want, Miki Serizawa
How do you know my name?
Don't look at it.
lt's embarrassing.
Look, Koji. Her pussy's a pretty pink.
l think it's never been used.
Let's see now...
Your first time is a rape...
That is definitely dramatic.
Just try to enjoy it.
You'll get more out of it.
Don't! Not so hard!
T-That's...
Oh my God! Oh my God!
This bitch is feeling it on
her first time! She's the real thing!
Masaki!
Sorry, but we wasted too much
time. Now we're low on tape.
So hurry up and stick it in.
Damn. Too bad.
Sorry, but you heard the man.
l'm popping your cherry now.
N-No. Don't!
lt hurts!
Wow, she's really tight!
Mother!
Okay, this time show me your ass.
lt's... lt's going in so deep!
l can't hold it.
l'm going to cum inside. l'm cumming!
N-No! Not inside!
Director, make sure you get this!
Who do you think you're talking to
Here l go!
No!
Why-Why are you doing this?
What have l ever done?
That's a good question.
Just consider it bad luck.
Yeah, you had the bad luck
of being in the wrong place...
at the wrong time, and
meeting the wrong people.
All of them look like they
have it way too easy.
Don't say that. After all, we're
able to make a living off of them.
Yeah, but people get sick of
the same type of woman every time.
What happened to that nurse?
We can't use her anymore.
l mean, she was completely covered in
cum and way too happy about it.
You just always take it too far.
And that test...
Reality is the cornerstone
of my movies.
lf we didn't really rape someone,
then it's an insult to our viewers.
You do realize, you're going to hell.
Then l'll see you there.
You got me there.
Grab your camera. Shoot straight,
then pan right. Hurry up!
What's going on
Right in front of
the pachinko parlor...
Looks like a mother
and daughter walking together.
Wow, that's a private
school uniform.
Definitely a rich bitch
kind of school.
Nice, she's just my type.
Check out her mom. She's got a
killer body for someone that old!
Look at those tits!
They're amazing!
You thinking of having a
mother-daughter sandwich
First, we get some information.
Roger that.
Script writer and director,
Koji Miyamoto.
The lead actresses will be the
beautiful mother and daughter.
And the title will be...
Chains of Lust - Beginning -
Sorry about this, Miki.
Just wait a bit longer.
Don't worry. We'll make
you feel good real soon.
No matter what they say,
a woman loves it when you're...
rough with her, raping her,
and smacking her around.
l'm sure that's what love is all about.
But man, l wish l could have
filmed her violent squirming,
and all the tears as
she lost her virginity.
Just don't fuck up with her mother.
lf you do, l swear l'll kill you.
Yeah, we still got Miki's
mother, Hiroko, right
We'll just grab her when
she's shopping, like we did with Miki.
Then we film the mother-daughter
scene and we have chapter one.
What do you think, sound good?
No, that's just not going to cut it.
Then what do you want to do
Hiroko's husband is out
of town starting today, right
Yeah, he's going
overseas for like a week.
Get the tape we made of Miki ready.
You have to strike
while the iron's hot.
l wonder what she's
doing out this late.
Yes, who is it please
Good evening.
l'm with the local shop owners' union
down at the shopping center nearby.
There was a woman passed out in an...
alley by the shopping center.
When we found her she mentioned...
that her name was Serizawa,
so we stopped by to bring her home.
Oh, l see. l'm so sorry
to have caused you trouble.
l'm opening the door now.
Thank you for coming by so late.
W-What are you...
l'm going to call the police!
Hey, quite a mansion you got here.
Seems too big for a family of three.
W-What are you talking about
l had no idea a bond
company paid so well.
And to think your husband left such...
a beautiful wife at home
to go work overseas...
l'd be too worried
to leave you like that!
l'm calling the police.
What's so funny
Oh, l'm sorry. lt's just that you're
so similar to your daughter!
Miki. What have you done to Miki?
l'm calling the police, no matter what.
Suit yourself.
Her expression is great.
Your daughter has natural talent.
M-Miki... What have you done...
We'll return Miki, but in exchange,
we'd like you to do something.
So, how about we trade
Do you think you can
get away with this
That depends entirely on you.
Hey, this is rough on me too. l can't
go against Masaki's orders though.
You just don't get it.
Your daughter goes to
a top-ranked, private school!
Go ahead and call the cops!
lf this goes wrong, then not only...
will her life and future be ruined,
but you might lose your house too!
You think l'll fall for a threat like
that l call and your life is over!
Wow! Some mother.
What did you say
l thought a mother was supposed to
think only of her daughter's happiness.
Well, l guess l thought wrong.
W-Why the hell do l
have to be lectured by you
You're absolutely right.
Miki's well being doesn't concern me.
Just think about it.
You're the only one who can save Miki!
l promise, l will return Miki!
You coward.
l love obedient women.
T-This is...
As you can see,
it's an adult video store.
Most of the store's earnings come
from the amateur videos we shoot.
Every single one of
them is a masterpiece!
Miki! Where is Miki!
Miki! Miki! Where are you!
lt's your mother! Answer me!
Where did you put Miki
She's not here.
What do you mean
That's not what you promised!
l told you that l was holding Miki.
lt's an exchange.
So if l do anything for
you tonight, l get Miki back
Yes, of course.
But only if you can fully satisfy me.
Such amazing elasticity. The size,
the softness, Miki's can't compare.
Your nipples are hard.
l think you're starting to feel horny.
The husband not giving
you enough action lately
That's not...
You're pretty sensitive,
but the real spot is down here.
Both mother and daughter
sure are strong willed.
You can moan. l told you
that l love obedient women.
lt's incredible.
My mind's going funny.
l can't... lt's so...
lt's incredible.
Stop!
Very nice. A housewife
definitely has more technique.
l'm jealous of your husband,
who gets it every day.
You're starting to enjoy it more.
Let's move on to the main course!
No, anything but that!
l'll do anything else!
Lady, don't say that
after you got me so hard.
l definitely get more excited
fucking some guy's wife.
l'm sorry, honey. Forgive me.
Looks like you have room in your mouth.
What do you think of our star actress
Very nice.
Oh man, l'm about at my limit!
Here l go!
Make sure you drink it all.
l'm about to cum too.
l don't know when your period is,
but that's not really my concern!
Take it all!
We'll return Miki soon. But l can't
guarantee it'll be the Miki you knew.
You beast!
lf l'm a beast, and you were
raped by me, that makes you a bitch!
That's for sure!
''My lovely Miki. lf you want some more
torture, please call. Love, Koji.''
Die, asshole.
You have to eat. We have
more work for you, Miki.
You have to keep your strength up.
Please let me go home!
l don't want to live like this!
Why do you say such things
when l love you so much
l absolutely hate you!
You're going to say that now
That's not very convincing.
You guys did that to me!
l guess my love isn't enough yet.
No.
Will you accept my love
Now you can't run
away from me, Miki.
This is so humiliating.
You must be horny for your
nipples to get this hard.
That's because you keep playing
with them! lt's making me funny!
Wow, Miki, your pussy
is so wet it's sliding right in.
lt's... lt's so deep inside of me.
Stop! Take it out!
lt's too strong!
Do you want me to take
the vibrator out of your pussy, Miki
Take it out. Take it out. Please.
lf you don't, l'm... l'm...
Then you'll have to ask properly.
Where is the vibrator
The vibrator's in my dirty pussy.
Please take it out!
l'm cumming! l'm cumming!
Miki, you really are a slut. Do you
really want me to see your asshole
Yes. Please look
at my dirty, little asshole.
Sorry, l couldn't hear you.
Please look at my dirty,
little asshole.
Very good.
l'll give you a little reward.
What are you doing
Haven't you ever had an enema
What an enema...
No!
Now we're all ready. And now...
Now we film the climactic moment!
N-No. Not here.
lt's not good to hold back.
Come on now, Miki. 10,000
of your loyal fans are waiting for you!
l can't hold it anymore!
lt's coming out!
No! Please don't look!
l can't believe l did it.
No one will marry me.
Now then...
Now that you feel all cleaned out,
why don't you work on cleaning this.
lt's like a dream being able
to do this with you, Miki.
Amazing! lt's big... lt's so big!
That's it. Move your hips like that.
See, you can do it if you try!
lt's amazing. l'm going crazy.
l'm going crazy too!
My lower body's so numb!
l'm going to die!
Here l go!
No more!
l'm cumming!
Hi!
Sorry to just come by, but l
made too much dinner. Want some
Hey, Hiroko, what's wrong
What's wrong with you, Hiroko
Miki... Please help Miki.
Hiroko, tell me exactly
what happened.
Man, l just keep
getting luckier and luckier!
Shizue Sasamoto.
This is a definite find!
So this is the tape that
Masaki filmed. "Chains of Lust", huh
They're pushing their luck, as always.
Yeah, yeah, l'm coming.
Hello, this is Peach Paradise!
You're...