What happened
You just started crying!
l can't understand you. Try to
calm down and tell me what's wrong.
The truth is, it's Miki!
Hello, Serizawa residence.
Hello madame, remember me
Y-You're...
So is that your sister who's there
l know everything, you know.
After a beautiful mother-daughter pair,
now we have beautiful sisters!
And you're both married!
That really gets my engine going.
Leave my sister out of this!
Then you'd better not tell
her or the cops about Miki...
if you don't want
your sister involved, that is.
l don't need to be told
by you! l know that!
Good. Just remember
that we still have your Miki.
Chains of Lust - Finale
Masaki...
What's with the sad face, Koji
You're really killing my buzz,
especially when l'm on a roll!
Really. Well, l'm glad to hear that.
You seem to be very happy, Masaki.
Didn't see you there.
Seiji said he wanted to talk with you.
He waited till you came back.
We already sent you your
kickback for this month.
Don't get defensive.
lt's not about money.
Then what
Actually, it's about the video.
lt's highly regarded by my friends.
l told an informant that l know the
filmmakers personally, and he said...
he'd exchange information if he
can meet the mother and daughter.
You mean...
You want us to introduce him to them.
You catch on quick. l always
liked that about you. Yes, that's it.
Sure, we'll happily arrange that.
l'm glad to hear it!
Now we can go on with the exchange.
l appreciate it, Masaki.
Gross.
No.
Getting horny
You want it bad, don't you
We prepared a special
guest for our horny Miki.
No matter how good it feels today,
try not to moan, okay
What do you hope
to gain from doing this
Oh, just a little event
we put together.
No!
There's something to be
said about two women. This is hot!
Why are you stopping
Because it's...
Because it's what
Well...
Go on, say it.
lf it's nothing, then
keep going. l said continue.
This is great. Good job.
You're as good as any porn star.
Your huge tits make you quite a slut!
l can't take it. l can't sit still while
watching this. Let me do it, Masaki.
Do what
Let me drive my hard cock into her.
No, shut up and film.
What! Why not
Just shut up and keep shooting!
l'm going to... Going to go crazy!
Me too! l'm going crazy!
Yes! Use your tongue more.
Well, aren't you two getting
tired of just using your tongues
l want it.
Me too.
Didn't you learn how to ask for
something at school
Please. Stick your hard, manly cock
into my dripping pussy. lt's waiting...
for your manhood like a hungry
mouth waiting for its meal.
Hey, if you want it too, you
better ask with your own words.
Please, please, l want your cock too.
What a helpless couple of women.
Go ahead. Stick that cock into her.
How is it?
lsn't it better
than only being with a women
lt's good! l like this better!
Hey slut, your pussy's so tight.
My cock feels like it's in a vise.
Give it to me hard! Break me!
Miki, that's so good! Really good!
Yes! Yes!
lt's going so deep!
lt feels so good! My hips...
My hips are moving on their own!
Miki is mine, and l'm
not giving her to anyone.
Nice. That's a very nice view.
No more! l'm going to cum!
lt's too early to cum yet.
Not so hard!
l'm going to cum!
l can't take it anymore!
lt's about time. All right, let's have
you see each other as you climax.
Miki!
Mom!
Just as you both wished, l let
you see each other! How touching!
No! Don't look!
M-Miki, no.
Miki, your mom wanted to help
you, but ended up losing to her lust.
lt's okay Miki, you can cum
whenever you want.
Just like you always do.
No! Anything but that!
l'm going to cum soon.
Don't hold back, and cum inside her.
H-Here l go!
l'm cumming!
That was pretty fast. Whoa! Me too!
Now, what's next...
Umm... Excuse me,
who are you
You must be Shizue Sasamoto.
That's right.
How did you know my name
l actually want to talk
a bit about your sister.
Did something happen to Hiroko
Has there been anything
different about your sister lately
Actually, just recently when
l went over, she started crying.
The quicker we get this done,
the better. Will you come with me
Now's not really a good time.
Oh, don't worry...
Because l'll just take
you against your will.
W-What!
See for yourself.
What's the meaning of this
Shut up.
Hey, Masaki, let's get started.
What are you saying
What's going on
Now, pleasure isn't
always about feeling good.
Sometimes pain can
turn itself into pleasure.
Stop with the damn explanation
and let's get started, Masaki.
So, now we're going to
teach you all about real lust.
Don't! Please, let me go!
Relax, Miki and Hiroko
both said that at first.
But in the end they were loving it.
So anyway, this is Masaki's idea and
we're going to try something new.
lt may be painful
at first, but it'll be okay.
l'm sure that you'll feel
pleasure in no time, Shizue.
Hey.
l want to talk more, but
Masaki wants me to get started.
Stop!
Nice sensitivity.
l can see where Miki gets it.
But this time we're going to
try something a bit more painful.
You're an experienced woman, so you
should be able to take three easily.
Please stop it! l beg you!
Going in!
Now for the cork,
or it'll all flood out.
Koji, you done
Yeah, we're okay here.
Well, we've got some business,
so hold on for about two hours.
Please stop.
Let me go home.
l have to answer, ''no.'' Don't worry,
you'll meet your niece and sister soon.
Bye bye!
Please stop this!
How're you doing
My stomach... lt's bursting.
But my body... lt's strange.
Leaking from just getting kicked
You're a hell of a slut.
N-No. My body...
lt's strange.
lt's so hot.
Yeah, it's not that Shizue is a slut.
lt's just that there's a
special chemical in that enema fluid.
Koji, you got that camera rolling
Yeah, it's filming.
So let's just take this out.
My stomach is hot.
My ass and my pussy are kind of...
Kind of what
You want someone to
play with both your holes, right
Then you better ask the two of us.
Please put it in me.
Covered in crap and you still want it.
Definitely a slut.
Okay then. Hey, Koji.
Yeah.
Tight! lt's like a death grip.
Not yet!
l'm cumming!
Me too.
Miki, you didn't eat
dinner last night.
You have to eat, Miki, or
else your beauty will never last.
l want to die.
Don't say that, Miki.
That makes me sad.
Hey, Masaki!
What the hell's going on!
What's the matter
You're all amped up.
Why the hell is Miki pregnant
lf you cum inside her that many times,
of course she'll get pregnant.
l avoided her on days that
she was ovulating. So how
Then it must have happened when l
fucked her when you weren't around.
You did what!
l didn't know you cared
about her that much.
From now on, l'll leave her all to you.
More importantly,
we're going through with our plan.
lt looks like they're having the business
talk at the same time as the meeting.
We'll call the police after
we leave and leak the info.
Then we don't have to worry about
that bastard Yamamoto anymore.
You're in the way just like Yamamoto.
Treat me like a slave?
Just you wait... Damn it.
Masaki, we've been waiting.
Everyone, the main dish has been served.
Please enjoy until you're satisfied.
Masaki, can l have a word
What is it, Mr. Yamamoto We have
a lot to do, so can we keep this brief
Don't worry, it won't take long.
l just wanted to give you
a special thanks for doing this.
You don't have to thank me.
We're friends after all.
Yeah, l thought we were too.
However, it looks like l was
the only one who thought so.
lt's too bad, Masaki.
What are you talking about
Koji told me the whole thing.
Say goodbye!
Now Miki is all mine.
l'm cumming!
Miki, from now on l'll be
taking care of you every day.
Don't worry, l won't leave
your mom or aunt.
From now on we can all be together.
We've identified the name
of the man killed at the hotel.
He is Seiji Yamamoto, age 41.
You tried to pull a fast one.
Don't worry,
l'll take care of you to the very end!