Take.
l see that you thoroughly enjoyed yourself.
But we still have a ways to go.
Takeshi.
The Bizarre Cage.
The 2nd Chapter
Act 3 Thou Shalt Not SpeaK
Currently all entrance gates are closed.
You cannot enter Fantasien.
lts all right, now.
The exit is this way.
Please watch your step.
lt may be time-consuming,
but well just have to manually...
unlock all of them one-by-one.
After that, we can control them
from the Security Room...
directly with this cable.
This is all thanks to Carmila.
Yukari, go ahead.
Thats right.
lts thanks to Soichiro.
So whats next?
Yes, wed better hurry!
Please stay calm and watch your step!
Follow our directions!
Please, stay calm and watch your step!
l just dont get it!
lf only Miss Amano was here...
How long is gonna take!
Come on!
Damn! lt doesnt look like we
can hold out any longer!
Over there!
Hey, Kurumizawa!
Were here to help out!
Did someone call the police for us?
lts Miss Amano.
Saito, good job.
Miss Amano!
Werent you on administrative leave?
Anyways, l got a grip of whats going on.
Leave the visitors to us.
You three hurry up and repair the system!
Yes, maam! Leave it to us.
l leave it to you.
Whos there!
Let her go!
l will take her place.
You serious?
All right, all right!
There is no need to worry anymore!
Please keep calm and watch you step!
lve connected all of them.
We did it, Shimamoto!
Well, it seems that we were able
to avoid a disaster.
Good job.
This is all thanks to you, Miss Amano.
Thats not true.
You worked your hard, too.
Whats wrong? lts working!
Something on your mind?
The system revert back to normal.
Thats good to hear.
We can take a breather now.
Saito.
Tamami.
Dammit! lts not budging!
Yes, according to what she told us...
it seems that the missing lnoue
is located here.
Yes, with the other two.
Understood.
At any rate, we are going to search
the Castle basement...
where they are believed
to be located. Roger.
Are you sure, Yukari?
Yes. That basement is the only thing
l cant bring up on the monitor.
That and....
Not just Tamami, but l cannot locate lnoue
or Kitazawa either!
But that area was closed off
due to expansion, wasnt it?
Are those three really there?
We believe they are all there.
Tamami and Kitazawa are....
Shit! Hang in there, Tamami!
Yes, l understand.
A bit quiet here are we?
l thought you were going to please me.
That enduring face of yours is great.
Tamamis pussy was nice and tight.
How about yours?
How long can you keep that straight face?
Whats wrong?
Come on, more! Cry out some more!
Yeah. Could you clean this for me?
And dont you think of biting.
Thats right, nice thorough.
Well. You pretty good, arent you?
You suck Kajiwaras cock all the time?
Come on, keep it up.
Youre doing good. Just a little more.
Come on, swallow it.
ls someone here?
All right!
lt opened!
Lets hurry and find
Tamami and the others.
Let me go with you!
l dont want Masakazu to repeat
any more offenses l beg you!
Okyo.
l became vaguely aware of it,
but l didnt have the guts to ask him.
lts my fault! So....
l got it. You guys and l go back
a long way, you know.
Thank you, Kazuko!
Now, lets hurry!
Okay.
Hey, where are we going?
This ways no good either.
Whats going on here?
lts like a maze.
Plus the wall and shutters
are closing on their own.
lts like as if we were
being led somewhere...
Well have to go back to that
machine room we just past.
lll try to access the main system from there.
All of the visitors have now evacuated
to the outside of the park.
There are no reports of any injuries.
Thats good to hear.
That, and l havent heard anything
from Kazuko or the other two.
What the? lts been overwritten?
No way!
Look out, Kazuko!
Sasazuka!
Okyo!
Shit! lts not budging! Shit!
Okyo.
lm done for.
Forget me, Masakazu.
Help Masakazu!
Sasazuka!
lf only l--
Thats enough, dont speak!
lll get this off you.
l didnt have the courage.
Dont let him commit any more crimes.
Okyo! Okyo!
Masa kazu....
Okyo!
Where are we?
This is where you will confess your sins
and will be punished.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
lnoue!
What are you going to do with them!
Shit! Stay back!
This is the police! Give it up!
You cant escape! Let the two go!
lts over. Everythings over!
Because lve killed a man.
You murdered Makoto Kajiwara, didnt you?
Thats right, l killed him.
So then you planted that evidence
in order to frame Morimoto.
Thats what he gets for snooping around!
l dont think lnoue knows its a girl,
so l left it at he...
lnoue! Did you kill Ruriko Zaizen
and Sasazuk too?
Masakazu, Okyo is dead!
She fell victim to the system
you messed with!
Miss Amano, it connected.
Everyone is in the Sanctuary.
lm bringing it up on the monitor.
Kusakabe!
So there you are.
lve been looking for you.
This is....
Soichiro!
Thats right, this is Kusakabe!
See for yourself!
What, so you are dead.
l thought you came back
to life or something.
Then again, itd be impossible,
being all dried up like this.
You killed Professor Kusakabe?
Yeah, thats right, l killed him!
He started blabbering about MAOS
having some fatal error.
And then he was trying to close Fantasien,
which just opened, to repair it.
l mean, you see? lf that were to happen,
wed have to pay a huge reparation.
Plus everyone, including me,
the middleman, would be affected by that.
Despite that, he--
Youre not going to change your mind?
l cant let that happen. But, look at this.
lts over.
Hes the one to blame.
He didnt listen to his friends favor.
No, Soichiro.
Hang in there, Shimamoto!
And thats when you got your hands
on Carmila?
Carmila?
ls your leg okay?
Yeah.
Sorry to bother you, but....
About this thing that lnoue was carrying...
ls it true that you can control
all of Fantasiens...
security system just by using this?
Yes, thats right.
ln other words,
you can interfere with security...
and purposely cause the system
to malfunction.
Well, the suspect is dead,
but l guess we can assume...
that this case was all set up by lnoue.
You seem a lot better.
Yes, well....
So whats wrong?
Calling me here at this time of night.
Youre going to visit Kitazawa, l heard.
Kurumizawa arranged
a special meeting tomorrow.
Theres something l need to ask her.
Shimamoto.
l want you to fuck me. Please.
This is so sudden. Shimamoto.
Just this once, call me Kazuko!
Please.
ls that what he called you.
lm not him. Do you still....
Kazuko!
Go ahead, lm....
Whats this?
But still, shes being detained
for an awfully long time.
l mean, wouldnt that be considered
self-defense?
lf l didnt let my guard down,
l wouldve whooped his ass good!
l bet you wouldve.
lm sorry to have caused you all this trouble.
No, its okay. Anyway,
l believe this belongs to you.
Shimamoto told me.
Takeshi, what is this?
Fantasiens system crash wasnt
actually set up by lnoue...
but was the fatal error
Professor Kusakabe...
was talking about, wasnt it?
So in order to punish him,
you and Kajiwara conspired.
Because you still love Kusakabe
to this date.
You found it inconceivable
that Kusakabe...
would just disappear without a word.
Soichiro!
Don't worry. I'm sure he'll understand
once I show them Carmila.
And then, when Kajiwara found his corpse,
you two planned for revenge.
lnoue, being played by the mystery
mail from the initials S.K.
Fell into your trap and dug his own grave.
You had lnoue admit to all the offenses,
framed him for the system crash...
and on top of that, you killed him.
Plus, in order to camouflage the fact
that it was a premeditated murder...
you became a victim yourself.
What went wrong was that
your conspirator...
Kajiwara, was killed by him.
No, it may be that you were
able to put up with that...
humiliation thanks to that.
lf Kajiwara was alive,
he would have stopped you.
He would never let the person
he loved go through that.
Despite knowing about you and Kusakabe,
he still loved you.
lll protect you, Makiko, no matter what.
Even if your heart still belongs
to Professor Kusakabe l....
But, l have no intention
of telling anyone else.
lm partially responsible for this, too.
That day, if only l hadnt broken
the Guidance Display.
Kajiwara may have never discovered
Kusakabes body.
Or if Kajiwara wasnt the
first one to find it...
This revenge tragedy may
have never taken place.
Welcome to the dream park, Fantasien!
Fantasien is a wonderland brings
legends and fairy tales to life!
Here at Fantasien,
all the legends and mysteries...
fold out before your very eyes!
Heart-pumping, eye-popping,
breath-taking adventures...
are waiting for you to explore them!