Well, isn't this wonderful?
Cursed Amusement Park.
Thanks to this incident,
the number of visitors...
has dropped radically.
On top of that,
the medias been snooping around...
ruining the corporations image.
POISONED!
Fantasien Suspected of Excess Debt
With the stocks falling,
we'll have to reconsider our plans.
The corporations administrative strategy
will be extensively restructured.
Morimoto.
Our loss is immense.
You wouldn't be able to pay for it
even if you...
worked your entire life.
To begin with,
despite being in charge of the park...
your risk management, or lack thereof,
is the entire cause of this mess!
Do you understand?
And how do you plan
to take responsibility?
Well I--
Well, at any rate, since I'm here...
the executive committee
is taking a wait-and-see attitude.
But if anything else major were to happen,
a decision must be made.
I'm afraid we'll have to say good-bye to you.
Just relax! Theres nothing for you
to worry about now that I'm here.
Cheer up.
The Bizarre Cage
The 2nd Chapter
Act 2 Thou Shalt Not Covet
The bride holds the secret bouquet.
Kajiwara! Kajiwara!
Gotcha!
You look down! That's not like you at all!
It wasn't your fault.
But I wasn't able to do anything.
Takeshi, it's okay.
What the hell are you doing
at a time like this?
That's it! That's the Takeshi I know!
Now this is my Takeshi!
Thanks for worrying about me, Tamami.
There, there.
I'll let you off with a classy dinner!
Yeah, right.
No way!
Why were you pretending to be a guy?
Looks like you have a reason.
Three months ago.
A girl died at this park.
Yeah, that suicide case.
That was my little sister.
That wasn't a suicide.
She, Ruriko was pushed off
from Draculas Castle!
Her body showed signs of rape.
Not only was Ruriko raped,
she was murdered by someone.
The police took a pessimistic view
of the evidence and declared...
that she took her own life afterwards.
They still haven't found any evidence
on the culprit so he still.
So, I'm going to find him myself!
You're Hiromi Morimoto, right?
You are under arrest under suspicion
of the murder of Makoto Kajiwara.
What do you mean?
This container was tested
for the poison used in the murder...
and came back positive.
And?
Hiromi Morimoto, your fingerprints
were also found on this.
Wait, there's got to be some mistake!
Stop it! Just hear me out!
I don't know anything!
Let go of me, damn it!
Hey, wait! Why so sudden!
Let her speak!
Saito, no!
Saito! Let go of me!
This is some mistake!
I don't know anything! Believe me!
Don't, Saito!
I've nothing to with it!
Morimoto!
Hey! Let go, god damn it! Saito!
If you attempt to interfere,
I will have you arrested...
for obstruction of justice.
Morimoto.
Takeshi! Bad news!
Who is it?
Saito?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
If I had done a better job, maybe....
You don't have to blame yourself.
I'm leaving because it is part of my job.
It's a supervisor's job
to take responsibility for things.
I liked this room.
I'm sorry.
Miss Amano?
Saito.
I can't see Morimoto as the culprit.
There's someone else.
This case isn't over!
I see.
The reason I asked the main branch
for help was because...
I was suspicious of MAOS bugs.
MAOS does not have
a central control system...
a main computer.
Each block contains its own computer,
which is connected to a network...
and utilizes their shared
correction program to process...
the data and manages
each other as a whole system.
But lately an unknown error
has been occurring...
frequently in the management system...
and the entire system
became very unstable.
But, all the computers are managing
each other...
and I just can't imagine that all the
computers went haywire all at once.
A virus!
No, that's not possible with this system.
Plus, even if someone were to attempt
to hack this system...
they wouldn't be able
to understand this code.
Then what would happen
if MAOS were to crash?
No way! It's inconceivable
for MAOS to crash.
But if it were to happen
while the park is closed...
the people inside would be
trapped in a dangerous environment.
As if they were trapped inside a cage.
Fantasien being a cage?
Does it have anything to do
with this unknown number?
I don't know. But it did start happening
around the same time.
What could it mean?
A warning from MAOS.
No, it may be an S.O.S.
S.O.S.?
Besides that, look at this.
The one of the cage
returns before the bride.
The time of vengeance has come, S.K.
What's this?
It came two or three days
before Kajiwara died.
But it seems that it was
accidentally sent to me...
instead of the intended receiver.
What could it mean?
I dont know.
But I have a feeling that these two incidents
have some relationship to each other.
Who could this S.K. be?
You have an idea, dont you?
Who is it?
Professor Soichiro, Kusakabe.
Good Morning!
How are you all doing today?
We're going to work our asses off
and make some money!
Due to the recent incident
we've been losing customers...
but with you guys' help,
we'll find a way to pull out of--
No way.
That's impossible!
Soichiro isn't the type of person
to do such a thing!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to have disturbed you all!
What are you guys doing
at a time like this!
Where was I? Yes.
Soichiro was my upperclassman in college,
and he was...
in the same club as Masakazu and Okyo.
He was nice and compassionate.
He's not the person to do such a thing.
Professor Kusakabe is the person
who programmed MAOS, right?
Yes, that's right.
He was so smart,
they even called him a genius...
in the Artificial Intelligence
Development Club.
Part of his fundamental research
is the MAOS system.
But he disappeared without a trace...
right after Fantasien was completed,
didn't he?
But no one else seems likely to be able to
hack into the system.
Did they use something?
Maybe.
If they used Carmila, then maybe.
What is this Carmila?
Well, Carmila is a system
that Soichiro developed...
as an upgraded version of MAOS.
I have a copy of it myself
and use it to gather data.
But it's still incomplete,
so its capabilities are pretty limited.
But if they used this, then maybe.
So, is there a complete version of Carmila?
No. It was almost complete,
but before it was finished Soichiro.
Disappeared.
I just don't get it.
During the entire incident with Kajiwara,
all of Fantasiens...
security system
was functioning properly...
yet there isn't any recording
that contains a single clue.
So did the bad guy fiddle
with the system, then?
MAOS condition is still unreliable.
Something can happen again.
So that means someone
else is being targeted?
But who? And for what reason?
Anyways, we have to find the culprit fast!
For Morimoto, and Miss Amanos sake.
Youre right!
Takeshi, I'm going to help out, too.
Then I'm going to check MAOS
again for anything.
That is all I know.
I see.
All right. Dont feel so down, Kitazawa.
Takeshi and I are here for you.
If there's anything, feel free to ask us.
Thank you very much, you two.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I still have work to do.
Her boyfriend was just killed
and she has work?
But that may help divert her sorrow,
couldn't it?
Yeah.
I'm going to check over there.
Then I'm this way!
I'm counting on you.
Yes!
Hey, Kazuko. This part, isn't right.
Saito!
It's you, Sasazuka!
What's wrong,
bringing me all the way here?
So what? Something personal?
No. It's about Masakazu.
That's a coincidence.
I was just looking for Inoue...
so I can get in a few questions.
Lately, have you noticed anything
strange about him?
Well, it's nothing big, but....
Saito! Come here, hurry!
There's a big problem with MAOS!
Anyways, just come here!
I got it.
Sorry, Sasazuka. Well finish this later!
Hey!
So, what happened?
I contacted Tamami,
so she should be here any minute now.
Enough of that, MAOS is going crazy!
Shortcut? If you cannot read the
last character, replace with a !
That number is in direct proportion
with MAOS instability...
and it seems that it becomes less stable
as the amount of zeros increase.
Several programs have
already gone haywire...
and the limiter has already
stopped functioning.
On top of that, it rejects our commands,
even if we input it in manually.
Then, if all the numbers were
to become zeros?
Game over.
All of Fantasien
would become uncontrollable.
A cage.
Shimamoto, any clues on the culprit?
Right now, there isn't any sign
of being hacked by someone outside.
But....
Is another crime being committed
as we speak?
Anyway, our first priority is to shut down
Fantasiens operation ASAP...
and have Egashira schedule
a complete inspection of MAOS!
We've got a problem!
The emergency stop mechanism...
won't function due to unstable power.
At this rate, the coasters going to fly
off the tracks!
Wait a moment! Kazuko!
Calm down, Yukari.
I'm going to connect it to a bypass, so wait!
Okay!
This is Pharaoh Land!
The door to the Mask Room won't open,
trapping visitors inside.
Can you control it from there?
This is the Viking Ship!
The feed tank won't close...
the pool is overflowing!
Please do something!
Mr. Egashira! It's still not too late!
Give the evacuation order!
This can't be.
Dammit!
Shimamoto! Hurry up and sound the alarm!
Kazuko!
Looks like, we're too late.
Takeshi!
Shit! Hang in there, Tamami!
Don't let him commit anymore crimes.
It's like as if we were being led somewhere.
Kusakabe! So there you are.
I've been looking for you.
Let her go! I will take her place.
I want you to give this back to Kitazawa.