R
Ri
Rip
Ripp
Rippe
Ripped
Ripped B
Ripped By
Ripped By H
Ripped By Ha
Ripped By Han
Ripped By Hana
Ripped By Hanak
Ripped By Hanako
In ancient times, the peaceful planet
of Blade Star was destroyed by
the evil Imperial Empire of Godram.
Although most of the inhabitants were
massacred, some of the Bladdians
fled the invasion, coming to Earth
with their secret energy source,
the "Super-Laker Crystals."
Today, the Bladdian descendants rise
to defend the Earth from it's foes.
Today, they are known as Star Laker,
Kung Fu Laker, Judo Laker,
Soul Laker, and Bunny Laker.
Led by Blade Knight, who commands
the "Ultra-Space-Time-Battleship,"
the defenders transform into the Lakers
with the help of the Laker Crystals.
In their effort to protect the Earth
against the invading evil Godram empire,
the Lakers don
their special Laker battle suits.
What happened to the lights?
Sorry! Sorry!
I 'm so sorry. I think the power cord
must have come out.
I 've had it! Chiaki and Yayoi
are causing trouble again!
That's why retards shouldn't be allowed
to touch any mechanical equipment.
Hey, I 'm apologizing.
How can you say something like that?
Chiaki, don't get so upset.
Couldn't you at least get miffed
on my behalf?
I 'm the one who is always getting
inconvenienced by all these retakes.
They're driving me up a wall!
Natsune, you too?
Don't cop such a nasty attitude.
It's Chiaki who's being nasty.
Do you really want to mess with me?
Chiaki, cool it!
That's fine... Come on!
Oh, Natsune.
Both of you, give it a rest!
Chiaki!
Natsune!
Drop dead, you moron.
Drop dead yourself, you clown.
Both of you... that's enough!
Are you okay?
Hey, Akira, get yourself together.
Ouch! It hurts!
Enough! The two of you, cut it out!
Tomorrow is the school festival,
and we only have today left to practice.
Don't you feel badly for Reiko?
She's willing to perform
without even getting paid?
I didn't do anything wrong!
There... there...
Be a good girl and don't cry.
I 'm sorry Chiaki.
I just got a little upset.
Me, too.
I 'll behave better next time.
Reiko,
I 'm so sorry about all of this.
Don't worry about it.
I 'm singing because I truly enjoy it.
Okay then. One more time.
Reiko are you ready?
Sure.
Okay then, from the top... Go.
Great, Reiko, it's perfect.
Lakers, you shall amuse me.
See you. Okay, I 'm going this way.
Okay. Let's do our best tomorrow.
Yup, good night.
Reiko, hold on...
What's that?
I have something important
to talk to you about.
Can I walk you home?
What is it?
You're in show-business,
and it's so hard to talk with you.
If I don't speak with you now,
I don't know when I 'll get the chance.
Okay.
Okay, everyone...
Please be careful on your way home.
I envy Reiko.
Akira...
Rats!
Experiment?
Yes. I have an idea on how to more
effectively power-up the Laker suits.
Can you help me?
Does it have to be tonight?
Tomorrow is the show.
The day an idea comes into your mind
is the best day to act on it.
Don't you know that? Come on,
transform into Star Laker... Quickly!
You're so pushy!
Star Laker, crystal conversion.
Good! Now we can start the experiment.
What's that?
With the most-popular singer
as my rival... I have no hope!
Home at last.
Oh Chiaki, you're so late.
Welcome home.
A-A-Akira?
You are so late, Chiaki.
I 've been waiting so long for you.
What are you doing here?
I thought you went to Reiko's.
Well,
I just had a sudden urge to see you.
Come on, what are you talking about?
Huh... I see. It's a grudge.
You're teasing me
because I belted you this afternoon.
Unfortunately,
I 'm not so easily deceived.
Don't you know my real feelings?
But you like Reiko...
Well, I now know in my heart
that it's you I really love.
Are you joking?
I will prove it to you... Now!
What has happened to you
all of the sudden, Akira?
Natsune, I like you.
Please stop toying with me, Akira.
Yayoi, I 'm serious.
Akira, it's okay with me,
but what about Reiko?
Don't tell me about her.
Yuka, you've always been my type.
As you know,
Laker suits increase in power
in direct proportion to the energy level
of the person wearing the suit.
When a person wearing the suit
reaches the maximum mental charge,
the suit will be
at its maximum performance level.
Mental charge?
See. The charge is rising, right?
That's good... Now, louder.
What's the voltage say, Akira?
Whoops, I forget to check the meter.
So you're just getting off!!
Good morning... A-Ki-Ra.
What? What happened to you?
It was so wonderful last night.
You're coming again tonight, aren't you?
Last night,
what are you talking about?
Oh come now Akira, it's impolite to make
a woman discuss such things publicly.
Yo-o-o, Akira!
I was so satisfied last night.
You should've stayed the whole night.
Huh?
I 'm such a tomboy, but last night
was the first time you, or anyone,
or anyone,
ever treated me like a woman.
I was so moved.
Akira, thanks for last night.
I will never forget how passionately
you took me in your arms.
Akira
From this day onwards,
we are lovers.
Huh?
What are you doing? Why are you
coming on to someone else's man?
What are YOU saying?
Akira is my man.
What a wild imagination you have.
Akira, unequivocally,
professed his love for me last night.
Me, too! He said that to me too!
Forever and ever!
What?!
He said the same thing to me.
Me, too!
What?
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?!
I... I just don't know.
So, you didn't just have me last night,
you had to go and EXPERIMENT
with all the others as well!
But wait a minute.
This is all just a misunderstanding.
A big misunderstanding!
Don't come near me.
Oh, I see... That's what it is.
It was I who was played for the fool.
And I trusted you just because
I 've known you since we were kids.
This kind of man is clearly
the enemy of all womankind!
You disappoint me, Akira.
Wait a second, this is all wrong!
Wait a second... Please...
I have no interest in hearing this...
I 'll teach you a lesson!
This is from Hell's Fury!!
Help! Help me, Reiko!
Lakers,
you have been completely tricked.
Look! A Mythical monster!
This is no time for an argument.
Lakers, we must go on the offensive.
WE ARE NOT HERE TO TAKE YOUR ORDERS!
KungFu Laker, crystal conversion!
Soul Laker, crystal conversion!
Judo Laker, crystal conversion!
Bunny Laker, crystal conversion!
Star Laker, crystal conversion!
Battle Team Lakers!
Let's go everyone...
Yes!!
W-wait a minute,
you can't do this by yourselves.
Damn!!
Laker Base, clear dimension!
Knuckle blast!
Sharp-angle, grind punch!
Tomoe Vulcan!
Imperial flash wave!
Bunny crusher!
It's gone??
Don't attack individually.
Re-assemble yourselves.
Don't tell us what to do!
We don't trust you.
Just leave us alone.
Bunny Crusher!
Tomoe Vulcan!
It's no use throwing the tomoe
or crusher at such short-range.
Soul wave attack!
Sparrow, super kick!
You idiots,
you are not reinforced defensively.
Don't go on the offensive until you've
shored up your defensive position.
Soul Laker... Kung Fu Laker...
I told you!
Oh! You look good, Lakers.
Oleana!
You made us work hard;
but truth be told, you're nothing more
than a troop of fools...
Not even a threat
to the Imperial Empire of Godram.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Haven't you figured it out yet?
The men who visited you last night,
they were produced by me.
Phonies?
Oh no! I made love to a robot?!
You tricked us!
You all fell apart
because you covet one man.
Earthling relationships are so fragile.
How can you say such a thing?
I won't forgive you.
What?
What's this gas?
Damn it!
My powers...
Oh, no...
God damn it!
My Laker suit's power is dissipating.
Please, power up!!
Akira, I 'm sorry I didn't trust you.
That signal indicates
that Star Laker's suit is off.
They can't crystal converge
without their mental energy level
being increased once again.
That's easier said than done:
They're in enemy territory.
Raise their mental energy using
the method you employed last night.
Was it really effective? By the way,
how do you know about last night?
Now, all I have to do is take
the Laker crystals out of your bodies
and the entire galaxy will be in control
of the Imperial Empire of Godram.
But let me enjoy myself before that...
You're going to feel much better soon!
What? What's going on?
This is...
Blade Knight!
Too early to rejoice. You should watch
as your prince is completely destroyed.
Everyone sit tight...
I 'm on my way!
Look at your prince's miserable attempt.
For us...
Blade Knight!
Don't get killed!
The real fun is yet to come.
Akira, don't come in here!
Reiko!
Oleana!
I 'm going to rip you to pieces
before their very eyes.
Are you having problems?
How is this happening? Are you really
a descendant of The Royal Blade Family?
Akira...
Pull yourself together, Akira!
Akira!
Star Laker, crystal conversion!
Please!
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you now feel my power?
This is good-bye...
Blade suit... Break!
What?
Akira, are you okay?
I 'm okay; and you, Reiko?
I can't transform
into Star Laker anymore.
Don't worry, leave it to me.
Akira, what are you doing? Now?
You also must touch the others.
It will help them recover their energy.
But... But... Akira.
It's no time to get embarrassed.
Quickly!
I 'm sorry, Chiaki.
W-w-wait a minute, Reiko.
Akira, don't...
It's really tacky
doing it in front of everyone.
It's embarrassing!
There's no time to explain right now.
We all must embrace each other.
It can't be true. Their energy levels
will rise through such an act.
I 'm even starting to feel
a little strange.
Now we'll start the real battle!
Wait!
The Mythical monster!
This one, again?!
Laker base, back us up.
Let's attack!
ROGER!
Here it comes.
Soul Laker and Bunny Laker,
attack from a safe distance.
Will do!
Imperial flash wave!
Bunny crusher!
Kung Fu Laker and Judo Laker,
attack at close range.
Will do!
Extreme explosive punch!
Tomoe Vulcan!
Now, Star Lakers!
Crystal power formation!
Star Saber!!
Star cyclone!
We've destroyed it!!!
Don't think you've defeated me, Lakers.
I will still get your crystals,
mark my words!
Akira...
Akira, after all, you were innocent.
I feel badly for having doubted him.
He's always been too horny;
and he's a space cadet...
But he's never cheated on any of us.
That's the problem...
What?
The first one Akira attended to
was Reiko, no one else.
But they do make an attractive couple.
It was a busy day.
I 'm so glad we were able to have
our school festival without incident.
The concert was a big success, too.
I was thinking during my performance...
the Lakers exist to protect
everyone's happiness and dreams.
If we prevail, everyone will have
the opportunity to learn,
to have romance in their lives,
to live and fulfill their dreams.
So, we must do our best.
Reiko, let's dance!
All Right!