(I think we don't
understand the real self)
Nao, are you at home?
Hi, Takuya.
Come on in.
I think neither you nor I
understand the real self.
What are you writing about?
This is what I feel right now.
Feeling.
You're rediculous.
I mean it.
I'm confused.
So confused.
What do you mean?
What happened to you
in the athletic team?
Did you get ripped-off?
Silly, no.
Unlike you who fool around
in recreation center all day
I have noble cares.
Really? Noble cares?
Then tell me.
You know Momoka, huh?
Momoka?
The innocent young girl,
Yes. That's her.
I told her that she could
visit my home anytime.
It's cold.
I want a cup of
hot cocoa milk.
Today Takuya said
he'd be home at 4 pm.
He might pay Nao a visit
on the way home.
In fact,
I gave her my home key.
So She would clean the house
or do the laundry for me.
So that's the relationship
between you two.
No. It wasn't
like that before.
Alice Doll.
Episode One
You Don't Understand Me.
Nao forgot to take out
the trash again.
It's cold.
I forgot that the heater
has broken down.
Bummer.
Yes.
I'II take a bath
until Nao comes back.
I'm so smart.
So she heated up the water.
Then you...
molest her.
I did not!
Hear me out.
Peach aroma.
I'II use new
bath powder today.
It's nice and aromatic.
It freshened me up.
Momoka, are you home?
Nao.
You're back.
It's warm.
So you warm up your body
by taking a bath.
Nao, do you want to join me?
May I?
I'II go in.
Weird.
Why is my heart
beating so fast.
Could be it's the first time
I take a bath with Nao.
What are you laughing for?
It's gross.
You use new bath powder?
No. I can't face you
when you're like that.
Do you want to
take a bath first?
I'II take a shower
outside first.
It's peach aroma.
Very nice.
You don't have to wait.
I can take a bath.
I am a bit off today.
Why did I suddenly invite
him to join me in the bath.
Momoka, what is it?
Why are you not talking?
If you don't mind,
I'II scrub your back.
Pass me the sponge.
I can hear Nao's heartbeat.
It hurts.
Momoka, are you okay?
Nao, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
You didn't mean it.
No.
Actually, I...
I did it on purpose.
Don't be silly.
Is it hurt?
Very much.
It might swell.
Momoka, what are you doing?
I want to kiss you.
No.
Please let me kiss you.
No. We're not a couple.
No.
Momoka.
I always want
this experience.
Please.
What can I do with you.
Just once.
Nao's lips are soft.
I really like Nao.
It's smaller than Momoka's.
Only one hair.
I know.
Stop touching.
It's soft and warm.
Stop. I said stop.
Why is it getting hard?
So that's what
happens to men.
I like this and Nao.
Nao, lick it.
It's wet and uncomfortable.
What's this?
It feels so good.
I'm losing it.
What should I do.
In a place like this.
Nao's cock enters my body.
Momo...
Momoka, stop it.
I'm cumming.
What's coming?
But I can't stop.
Momo... stop it.
Because she can't
control her body.
Takuya.
Don't peek.
Oh. It's kaio.
Oh what?
Don't you go to recreation
center today?
I would if I had money.
Then come over to my place.
Dad and Mom are
coming home late today.
I always thought you
were stil a little girl.
Didn't know you would
come on strong.
I'm back.
Are you lonesome?
I didn't want you
to feel lonesome,
so I brought a guest.
So that's why she
brought me to her place.
I can understand
that you have a collection.
But you're not a kid anymore.
But Bangaro is adorable.
Bangaro?
Bangaro.
That's its name.
I can't believe her.
Now that I'm here,
today I'II definately...
Kaio.
What?
Today I'II definately...
I'II definately get it.
May I?
It hurts.
It always ends up like this.
The taste and the body
are still a kid.
So.
I want to ask for a favor.
What favor?
Takunya, please.
Make Kaio a real woman.
A real woman?
It's rediculous.
It's not good to mess
with friend's girl firend.
It's fine.
I'm not interested in virgins.
Please.
That's not the point.
And why me?
What are you talking about?
Because I'm your good friend.
You don't ask a friend
to do things like that.
Don't talk as if
you were a saint.
It's beacuse you're
a pedophile.
A pedophile?
Didn't I tell you that?
That was not like
what you said.
It was Momoka's problem.
Who made her do that?
It was you.
Was it me?
I ask you, sincerely.
Hope you can make her
a real woman.
Please.
Gosh. Why me?
I think we don't
understand the real self.
What is it?
Momoka, you're here.
It's because
you're a pedophile.
It's hot and stuffy.
I just took out
the garbage for you.
I forgot that again.
Did you see Takuya?
He just went out.
No.
I haven't seen you
for a long time.
You've been busy with
the athletic team, right?
Nao, do you get online?
Occasionally.
They charge you
for logging one porn sites.
I think that's a
waste of money.
What do you think of me?
Mine is bigger than Nao's.
(It's because you're
a pedophile.)
Look.
Nao entered me from here.
Momoka.
Don't do that.
I didn't feel weird when
bathing with her before.
But why now...
Because the room
is too bright,
I don't want it now.
Momoka.
Don't call me Momo.
But someone says
I'm a pedophile.
So don't do that.
It's fine. Let him talk.
I just want
to make you happy.
Besides...
Smell here.
Did you smell peach?
Peach?
No.
I knew it.
I don't want to lose
the peach aroma.
Why not?
I was afraid that
without this aroma
you would not wnat to
make love to me.
Momo.
You're putting me up.
Nao, stick it in.
Faster.
Stick your cock in here.
Momoka.
I'm always by your side.
I'm not a porn photo
in the computer.
Besides...
Momoka.
I am always fond of you.
Take your hands off.
No.
I'm so happy.
Go take a shower.
Wipe yourself dry as well.
What are you going to do?
I'm going out for a while.
How can you do that.
Seems that
it's going to rain.
The garbage
has been taken out.
No laundry to do, either.
Momoka, I'm sorry.
I didn't like you beacuse
I'm a pedophile.
I just want to make sure.
She cut class.
Could it be...
It's Kaio.
She didn't
attend the gym class?
Kaio, it's me.
I want to talk to you.
Are you going to cut class?
Where did they go?
I planned to set up a trap.
If it works,
I'II have the chance to
have sex with her.
But if I don't find them,
everything will go down
to the drain.
Where on earth are they?
I got it. In the lounge.
There's a strong odor of men.
It's the first time
I come here
and the first time
I cut class.
Whatever. Next will be
the loathful math class.
I'm feeling a bit guilty.
Fortunately,
I bumped into Nao.
Otherwise, I didn't know
how to kill time.
Everything is fine.
I accidentally entered men's
secret lounge,
feeling so excited.
The whold setting is perfect.
Am I weird
to talk so much alone.
It's not like usual Kaio.
Is it?
How Nao thinks
of me all the time.
I'm sorry.
I forgot you have something
to tell me.
I'II get right to the point.
Is Kaio sexually frigid?
Why?
Sexually frigid?
What do you mean?
Nao is serious this time.
Kaio is to blame.
It's far from usual
childish kaio.
Nao, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I just wanted to ask
if you're sexually frigid.
No, you don't have to say it.
I'II know when I check it out.
Wait. Check it out?
Doing this is not like you.
You say you don't
but you really want it,
don't you?
No, stop it.
What no?
A piece of clothes
cannot hide how hard you are.
You're more sensitive
than I thought.
And you're enjoying it, man!
Weird. Why did they
both become silent?
Did you cum?
You're far more sensitive
than I thought.
The pants are soaking wet.
No. You'II stain the pants.
So you want me
to lick the inner side.
That's not it. No.
You're very sensitive.
That's nonsense.
Do you want it?
Do you want me?
To prove that you're not
sexually frigid.
Prove it to me now.
Someone said I'm a pedophile.
Someone said Kaio is
sexually frigid.
Why did Kaio
never do it to me before.
Kaio, you're really lovely.
Let's end it.
If it goes on, I might
hurt my good friend.
Why?
Why did Kaio seduce Nao?
Momoka, I'm sorry.
If I run away now,
I am not a man.
I'm cumming.
Here I cum.
(I think we don't
understand the real self)
What does it mean?
Kaio. It's Takuya
who asked me to do it.
I knew it.
Were it not for him,
who would mention frigidity.
So you deliberately...
I didn't plan on doing it.
But you woke me up.
Besides, you said stop
which made me want it more.
I shouldn't do it to Takuya.
Forget about him.
He is not being romantic
when making love.
Only Takuya didn't know
that you're not a virgin?
You can't tell him the truth.
He'd be angry about it.
But he is eardroping now.
What am I doing.
I'm the only one
who is not in the know.