Grandmother!
I won't be too long.
Listen to me very carefully!
Grandmother!
If Onimaro takes
Dominion over this world...
none will be able to survive it.
You both saw the hell
the city has become.
And it's only going to get worse
as time goes on.
Kijyu brought the Evil Sex Spirit
to force Onimaro to be their King.
Where Might is the master,
Justice is the servant.
Do you think we have a chance
to get him back?
There's one thing you can do.
But it's no guarantee.
Grandmother, does the King still
have memories of Onimaro?
That memory is the only way...
to help the world
and Onimaro himself.
Speaking to him could
get his memory back?
It's hard to say.
He has both Kijyu's blood
and our Tenjin's blood.
Ai, Mai...
Go back to the Amatsu House...
and find the room
underneath the alter.
That room didn't burst into flames.
Inside, seek out a pot of
a miracle plum tree.
You'll be protected by God
as long as you possess it!
Listen! Never give up on
believing in Tenjin!
Believe in the true faith and the
Celestial Raiment of Twin Angels!
Both of you must
combine your powers.
Please help save Onimaro.
You two have already
taken over Tenjin's mission.
Grandmother!
Don't leave!
I've got to go.
Please, carry out your tasks!
Grandmother!
She must be given her peace.
We have to let her go!
I'll crush the Kijyu who've taken
our grandmother's life from us.
I will too.
See me ride this pony.
Oh...oh...yeah...oh, yes!
You like it, you horny bitch...
Aaaah, so good!
My young Lord, can you hear me?
It's your guardian, Dekunobo.
Lord Onimaro.
Have you forgotten my voice?
It's Dekunobo, yours truly.
Since you were born,
we have done everything together.
Remember the sounds
of the breeze...
that echoed in the forest
where we played...?
Lord, you can't drown in the
shallow area. Stand up and see...
Lord, my Lord!
Please wake up!
Oh, thank God...
I am hungry, Dekunobo.
Oh, yes, yes!
Let's grill some fish right now.
Here, Lord.
This is good for your little prick.
Eat up!
Lord Onimaro!
Do you remember?
Please remember...
Remember the time
when you almost died?
I stayed up all night
at your side.
Dekunobo...
I'm right here, Lord!
I thought you went away.
Don't be ridiculous, Lord.
Where would I go without you?
As your guardian,
I will never, ever, leave your side.
Please relax.
Am I...going to...die...?
You are NOT going to die.
You are the flesh and blood
a direct descendent of Tenjin God.
His good will has blessed your soul.
You won't die over a silly flu.
God will have to take my life
before yours!
I had the strangest dream.
Beasts with scary faces were
trying to take me away.
What!?
And all of them had horns like me.
They were very nice to me, though.
My Lord!
I was wrong to keep you in
exile like this at his tender age.
I must take you out of the woods
and provide some female company.
The Tenjin nuns will be
happy to take care of you.
My Lord, you must remember.
Our King!
What is the matter?
You don't look so well...
Is this Orgy Ceremony
wearing off on you?
Who is Onimaro?
Who is Dekunobo?
Who AM I?
You are the Master who binds all
of Universe with the Indecent Spirits.
The one and only
King of Kijyu Demons.
What is the matter, King?
I almost forgot!
King,
how about some mature woman
if you're tried of virgins.
Please get a piece of
this ripe pussy.
There... look.
Nice and juicy on the outside,
smooth and tight on the inside.
I have personally
prepared this one.
Please, have yourself a ball.
Sir Tokihira.
Have Ai and Mai shown up yet?
I thought you two were
delivering them yourselves.
They got away.
Ai...Mai...
Ai? Mai?
Do you recognize the names?
Vaguely...
That's possible.
They are the infamous Tenjin sisters
that have caused us much trouble.
Enemies!
Indeed!
I had planned to make a special
sacrifices of them to you, King.
Beasts, do not spoil the party!
Get that horny professor
over here for the King.
What is the matter?
The King is not himself.
If he should regain his past memory,
our ritual will not be consummated!
But we have Sutra...
Of course! Sutra!
Such an eager beaver.
Queen of Seduction, after all.
Kama, mix a bit of Kijyu potion
with the wine...
and give it to our King.
As you say.
We must not allow
any more mishap.
Oh, did I mention about old Gensyu?
She's quite finished.
Oh, yes?
Not Gensyu!
Well done, Kama.
She must be dead as
a door nail by now.
Here we have the Tenjin nuns,
begging for more.
They are a disgrace to Tenjin.
True, true. Now we only need to
take care of Ai and Mai.
We don't need to look further.
They're bound to show up for revenge.
Curiosity killed the...pussy.
We have already laid the traps.
The Raiment is useless against them.
The wine!
Bring on the wine!
Be gone, Demons!
Here comes Tenjin!
Bestow us the power, Lord!
Finally!
Show yourselves, Ai, Mai.
Demons that spread
the Evil Orgy Spirit!
We, the Tenjin Twin Angels, will be
the punishing hands of our Lord!!
For the sake of Gensyu!
Beware!
Such kidders.
Why don't we reunite you sisters
with your old granny.
No escape!
Sister!
You just fell into our hands,
Ai, Mai.
Take down the sacrifices.
I want them! I want them!
Tonight's main course,
it's all yours.
You bastard!
Damn you!
Miss Ai! Miss Mai!
Dekunobo!!
Lord Onimaro
no longer remembers...
You mustn't, Lord Onimaro!
Get away!
No, I will never!
What are you going to do to them?
You owe your life to them.
Rape them!!
You have lost your mind,
Lord Onimaro.
Who? Onimaro? Fuck off!.
No, I will not budge!
If you want to get to them, then
you'll have to get through me first.
Stupid Onimaro!
Dekunobo, just go!
Come on, beasts. Kill him.
Dekunobo!!
Lord...no,
you heartless Kijyu King!
I am so...ashamed...
Wise old Gensyu,
I am so...sorry...
No!
Onimaro, you idiot!
Where are Ai and Mai?
I want them right now.
They are not going anywhere.
How about a little foreplay,
Master?
I'll put on a show for you.
That is, those sisters deserve
more than just regular deflowering.
We must return all the trouble
they caused us...ten-fold!
Beasts, prepare the torture sets.
Those are what we call
''cherry eel,'' a Kijyu creature.
They can sniff out virgin pussies
and penetrate them...
only to tear off their cherries,
if you know what I mean...
Bring in the sisters!
Sister!
Oh, what a sight, Ai.
Tenjin Angel,
show us your Raiment dance, eh?
How interesting...
Sister!
Watch closely, my dear.
You're next, Mai!
Sister...!
Sister...
Oh, that tight pussy
has choked them.
Sister!!
Kama, get her out of the tank.
We're not finished with her, yet.
Oh...no...
No...no!!
Sister!
Your Highness, look.
I see you approve...
No!
Now it's your turn to look.
Mai...
No...
Enjoy the ride, Angel.
Mai!
Sister!
Oh, what a lovely view...
No!!
Such sublime pleasure!
Mai!!
I wish that someday I would be
able to look you straight in the eye
Instead, I'm running away,
speeding my bike like a fool
''Shall we walk together?''
you said and smiled
Such a coward I am
I couldn't answer your smile
with honesty
Good-bye, weak girl
I can only run away and hide
The wind against my cheeks
whispers how I fail my heart
And with the words of courage,
lifts my fears and regrets
''I'll give you good luck.''
Maybe tomorrow, I say to the wind
Maybe I can open up
and tell him that
My actions are really
the opposite of my true feelings
That I really, truly, love you
No!
Now it's your turn to look.
Mai...
No!!
Mai!
Ready angel?
Enjoy the ride, Tenjin slut.
Mai!
Sister!
Oh, what a lovely view...
No...no!!
Such sublime pleasure!
She appears to be
unconscious, my lord.
I can't wait any more!
Give me the sisters!
Don't rush, my King.
They are not going anywhere.
It's no fun raping those sisters
in their sleep.
We applied some potion
on their pussies...
which will burn their inside with
such overwhelming lust that...
they'll be begging for it.
And once you stick it in, they'll be
wriggling their asses like whores.
Ai and Mai will be
wriggling their asses like whores...!
Yes. I just knew
you would like that.
But before you eat the cake...
we must first proceed with your
Rite of Ascension to the Kingdom!
As the King of Kijyu, you will
reign over the Sex Orgy World.
You shall now command all evil
forces to spread over Universe,
and carry on this mission till we erect
the infinite world of lust and orgy.
What is this...?
Miss Ai!
Dekunobo, you're okay!?
I can't believe it myself.
- Help Mai.
- Certainly.
I am the King of Kijyu!
I shall lead this world
into infinite evil and lust!
Congratulations!
You have been crowned
with the coveted Kijyu throne!
Oh, how long
I have awaited this day!
How long we the
Kijyu Clan have waited...
I want Ai and Mai, NOW.
Yes!
Bring in the sisters!
Yes, Sir.
And now my lord, I will gladly
present you the ritual sacrifice!
Do what your wild heart desires,
do those pussies until they rip!
What happened?
They're nowhere to be found,
my lord.
No!
Search! They couldn't have
gone too far. FI ND THEM!
Get me Ai and Mai!
Y-yes! Search!
Search them out.
Without sacrificing
those Tenjin Angels...
the ceremony is not complete.
Indeed!
- Women...
- Get lost!
Search with your
noses to the ground!
Just a sleeping bum.
Miss Ai, Miss Mai,
I have disappointed you both.
It is all my fault. If only I had
taken better care of Lord Onimaro.
Please, chin up, Dekunobo.
We are grateful that you're alive.
They defiled the poor nuns and...
and now even you sisters...
I let them subject you to such...
such shameful acts.
And now they've killed Gensyu
after all she's done for me...
And failing my Lord.
What a pathetic piece of shit I am.
But Dekunobo,
we can't give up yet.
We have to keep believing
in the miracle of Tenjin.
It will save us
as Grandmother promised.
The miracle of Tenjin...
You mean his good will is
still left in this hellish world?
We were filled with thoughts
of revenge, Dekunobo.
We had forgotten
Grandmother's last words...
Gensyu's last words...?
She mentioned a pot
containing a plum tree...
hidden in the burned down alter
at the temple.
Let's look for it together.
We still have a chance at restoring
light and peace to the world.
At your service!
Sister!
There it is.
Stand back, I'll get it.
We found them!
Dekunobo,
you get the plum pot!
- Let us take care of them!
- All right!
Here, Miss Ai, Miss Mai.
It's not safe here. Let's go
to the Temple, to grandmother.
What a hellish sight!
Sister, we'd better transform.
Right!
Here comes Tenjin.
The Raiment of Twin Angels!
Miss Ai, Miss Mai.
Women!
We can't transform...?
We have been so shamed
by the sex demons...
that the Raiment must have
lost its power to transform us.
In that case, we better run as fast
as we can. Follow me this way!
There! Don't let them get away!
This is pure hell...
the world is in chaos.
It feels...so...good...
Oh Gensyu!
I am so ashamed!
Grandmother...
after what they did to you,
I almost lost my mind.
In the heat of vengeance,
I have exposed Mai to such impurity.
It's not your fault, sister.
I also lost control of my senses
trying to avenge Grandmother's death.
- Look! The plum tree!
- It's a miracle!
Look, Grandmother is weeping!
Grandmother, are you alive!?
- Grandmother!
- Grandmother!!
I am no longer of this world.
Grandmother!
Nevertheless, I am always
with you in spirit, Ai and Mai.
How could I leave you?
Ai, Mai, you must defeat Kijyu
and restore the world to peace.
Don't give up.
But, we have disgraced you...
and the holy Raiment
you bestowed upon us.
I am sorry...I am so sorry...
We have lost our powers
as Tenjin Angels.
We can't transform
because they...
We are so sorry, Grandmother.
Do not despair.
That plum tree will
provide new Raiment.
The heavenly maidens!
Those maidens will weave you
the new celestial Raiment.
Really?
Wear it and
face those Kijyu demons.
With the blessed Raiment and
the power of Tenjin Enlightenment,
you must restore faith to the world.
- Tenjin Enlightenment...
- Blessed Raiment!
To wear such a sacred gift
from God...
you must first recite the
ancient Tenjin incantations...
passed on in the Amatsu family.
The ancient Tenjin incantations...?
Words of living souls.
Once spoken, they release the
souls from the Temple of Tenjin...
who will answer your prayers and
protect you through your mission.
You mean we're not fighting
all alone, Grandmother?
Just remember that all of
Heaven is behind you in your battle.
Ai, Mai, as the maidens weave,
I shall teach you these holy words.
Repeat them as if they were
the last words you will ever speak!
Yes!
Miss Ai, Miss Mai,
I will do my best to
not let the demons disturb you.
The fate of our world is
in your hands!
So long.
We call to the ends of the skies above
upon the heavenly Tenjin mistresses!
And we call upon the army saints,
a hundred-strong, of Tenjin!
We call to the ends of the skies above
upon the heavenly Tenjin mistresses!
And we call upon the army saints,
a hundred-strong, of Tenjin!
Servants of Tenjin,
such as the master saint of chivalry.
Under the spell of the moon,
those who have fallen to earth,
are to be purified by you all,
to be rid of their sins!
May you all hear,
the servants of Tenjin!
There he is!
With one foot in the grave.
I, Dekunobo, am here to fight.
But first, I have something to say
to the King of Kijyu.
Let me see him!
You don't know when to say when.
Where are Ai and Mai?
Perhaps, you'd like to join
in our festivities, eh?
King of Kijyu! Who was once
my beloved Lord Onimaro!
I claim your life with my own hands,
and you can take mine as well!
What...?
Lord Onimaro, destroy me with
your own flesh and blood if you can!
Don't just stand there!
Kill him! Rip him to pieces!
We will reunite in death.
Ai and Mai must be in there!
You demons of Kijyu who have
brought hell upon this earth...
We the sisters of Tenjin Clan will
put an end to your misery.
Oh, how cute.
Do you really think the two of
you can conquer our evil empire...
with your little trick?
Where are they?
Over there!
Ai Amatsu, before your eyes.
Mai Amatsu, in the flesh.
Attack! Attack!!
Just try it you beasts!
Why, you!
Make my day!
How dare you!
I'll whip your ass!
You sluts!
No escape!
Kama!
Kama!!
Don't let them get away!
Ai...Mai...!!
Mai, we'll recite
the incantation now, okay?
Yes.
We call to the ends of the skies above
upon the heavenly Tenjin mistresses!
And we call upon the army saints,
a hundred-strong, of Tenjin!
Such as the master saints of chivalry,
of exorcism, of Time, and of Space.
All that serve and
follow the teachings of Tenjin.
Crimes committed by demons of Kijyu!
Under the spell of the Tenjin moon,
those who have fallen to earth,
are to be purified by you all,
to be rid of their sins!
Under the spell of the Tenjin moon,
those who have fallen to earth,
must be purified by you all,
to be rid of their sins!
Now we cleanse all harm done
against Tenjin.
Restore the light on this land
and crush the darkness!!
King! Why, you Tenjin bitches!
Gone with Tenjin!
Welcome the Kingdom of Evil!
How's that, Sister?
Go ahead and enjoy it.
Ah...how sweet...
Sister...?
I feel...so...good...
Evil be gone!
Here comes Tenjin!!
Don't be fooled by the illusion.
They can't ruin our incantation!
Okay, sister.
Those who sin against Tenjin...
Be cleansed! Be gone!
Tenjin God erect the Column
of Enlightenment.
Evil be gone! Kijyu be gone!
Tenjin God erect the Column
of Enlightenment!
What is this...?
It's the great light of Tenjin!
The Evil Spirit,
brought on by Kijyu...
Tenjin has shown you the way out:
follow it!
Evil Spirit, this land is ours!
You sisters!
Here comes Tenjin!
Twin Angels!
Of the Blessed Raiment!!
- Be gone, Evil Spirit!
- Ready?
Be gone, Evil Spirit!!
King, but why?
Why...!
Why!
Miss Ai, Miss Mai...
What is happening to our lord?
Miss Ai, Miss Mai!
Lord Onimaro!
It's really you.
Ouch!
Hey Mai! Hey Ai!
Why are you crying?
What a terrible dream I had.
You fool.
Oh, oh, Dekunobo!
I have to pee bad, hurry.
Just a second,
hold it in, hold it in...
Um...Dekunobo!
Lord!
I'm all wet...
Sister.
We did it, Grandmother.
Thank you, Grandmother.
I wish that someday I would be
able to look you straight in the eye
Instead, I'm running away,
speeding my bike like a fool
''Shall we walk together?''
you said and smiled
Such a coward I am
I couldn't answer your smile
with honesty
Good-bye, weak girl
I can only run away and hide
The wind against my cheeks
whispers how I fail my heart
And with the words of courage,
lifts my fears and regrets
''I'll give you good luck.''
Maybe tomorrow, I say to the wind
Maybe I can open up
and tell him that
My actions are really
the opposite of my true feelings
That I really, truly, love you