March on, march on.
Where does this narrow
passage lead to?
This narrow passage
leads to Tenjin God.
May I please go this way?
Only if you have a
worthy purpose.
The Star of Evil is
our symbol of fortune.
Times are corrupt and ripe...
for Lord Onimaro to become
King of the Kijyu Keeper.
It is time for my
dreams to come true.
Now is the time!
My instruments of seduction,
Kama and Sutra.
Kama as requested.
Sutra at your service.
It is the time to
manifest our evil empire.
By the power of the star
of evil...
we will have Lord Onimaro
grow to full manhood...
and hold this ceremony for
his ascension to the throne.
It is time to break the
Barrier of Space and Time.
Our enemies, Ai and Mai
and those of the Tenjin Clan.
Kill them all!
Ai and Mai, prepare
yourselves for our attack.
See you later, grandmother!
Hey you!
Lord Onimaro!
You don't stop, do you?!
Mai, help me!
Ai's trying to get me!
Lord Onimaro.
Mai...
My lord, behave yourself!.
Dekunobo...
Cut off the naughty guy's horn
and he might calm down.
Don't be so cruel!
I'm sorry for his rudeness.
I'll make sure to punish him!
Hey, what are you doing?
You're hurting me!
Stop it, Dekunobo!
Get off of me!
Ai, Mai,
take care of yourselves.
- Mai.
- Sister!
What is this...!?
This is a blessed wand
of Tenjin.
Look! They're everywhere!
Mai, get everybody out
of the University! Hurry up!
Here's the wand again!
- Ai!
- Professor Iijima!
It's an emergency.
Tenjin University has to be
closed down for a while.
I can't stop this spirit even with
the power I received from Gensyu.
Tell Gensyu about this, now!
Okay, I'll tell her!
''University closed
due to emergency.''
What?!
The blessed wand of Tenjin?
Grandmother, is this about
the Kijyu Demon Clan?
Most definitely.
What's going to happen?
The demons from the Kijyu Clan
are coming out for a take-over.
Ai, Mai!
Be careful and ready!
Okay!
Watch over Lord Onimaro!
Tell Dekunobo to stay with him
and not to leave his side.
As you command!
Our Holy God, Tenjin!
Please listen to our hope!
We have come upon an
event of the Star of Evil.
Please, grant us the power of the
Transforming Raiment of the angels.
I'm scared, Ai and Mai!
My lord, my lord,
where are you going?
Thunder is the incarnation
of Tenjin God.
My lord, you shouldn't be
afraid of thunder!
You are the only direct
descendant of Tenjin.
I want to be with Ai and Mai!
Don't be so difficult!
Ai and Mai are staying in the temple
to help grandmother!
My lord, just stay close to me.
May our prayers reach Him.
Please, God, please.
Grandmother.
Grandmother!
The altar is...
Be careful, Ai, Mai!
Grandmother, hurry!
Protect Lord Onimaro
at any cost!
- Wise one!
- Gensyu!
This is not a normal fire.
You won't be able to
get it under control!
Everybody, head to safe shelter!
Don't worry about me!
Get Lord Onimaro, hurry!
Take care of grandmother,
will you?!
Yes!
Mai. Let's go.
Right!
Lord Onimaro!
Dekunobo.
My lord!
Ai, Mai.
Where's Lord Onimaro?
Ai, Mai, help me!
My lord!
Ai, Mai, it's hot!
Lord Onimaro,
I'm here to lead you to safety.
Who are you?
Lord Onimaro,
let me make you feel good!
- Lord Onimaro!
- Where?
You're...
My lord!
He's passed out.
Lord Onimaro,
you're going to be okay.
Let's get you out of here
before this place burns down.
Gensyu!
Grandmother, hang in there!
Grandmother!
Lord Onimaro? Is he all right?
It's okay. We got him.
As long as
Lord Onimaro wasn't hurt,
our clan will survive
without the temple.
Little old me...
I was useless
in the face of Evil.
Grandmother,
don't go blaming yourself!.
Is there anyone who can hold back
these enemy forces besides you?
I'm the only one
of the Tenjin Clan.
But it is possible that someone
at the Tenjin University...
studying the Master's Course
in spiritual powers could do it.
It's raining.
That's a sign of
Tenjin's good wishes.
There is still hope,
Ai and Mai.
No matter what happens to me...
you are both to combine your powers
and protect Lord Onimaro.
Yes.
I understand grandmother,
but you must get some rest.
Professor Iijima.
Amatsu sisters, I'm sorry to hear
what happened.
How is Gensyu?
Is she okay?
She got burned, but she was
fortunate enough to escape death.
It must have been
a terrible ordeal.
She's our sole protection of the temple
and badly incapacitated.
Is anyone at the university
training...
for a Master's Course
in Spiritual powers?
Well, I will ask around
and take care of it.
I'll come back later to see her.
But in the meantime,
you two just stay positive.
Okay. Thank you very much.
The fire destroyed everything.
Mai, be strong for grandmother
and Lord Onimaro.
Yes.
Lord Onimaro, we have long
awaited the coming of this day.
For today is the
Day of Kijyu's Orgy Sex Ritual.
You will reach full manhood
through this rite of passage.
And then you will become the
King of the Orgy Sex Demons.
Me?
I'm going to be your King?
Yes, indeed.
Please enjoy your mutation
and the fine ceremony.
Your mighty sexuality shall
bind all of the universe!
Oh, Ai and Mai will
get mad at me!
When you become King,
they are merely your servants.
Do whatever you wish
with them.
I mean anything!
Kama, Sutra, bring the
sacrifices for his coronation!
As you wish.
I'll bring them right away.
Very soon...
Onimaro will be King
of Demon Sex World.
Sister.
We have to be strong, Mai.
Amatsu!
Professor!
The University will be
sending a young man...
who's studying the exorcism.
That's great!
He's performing
his prayers right now.
He's one of
Tenjin University's best.
His name is Hideto Fujikado.
You know, he's the most
handsome man I've ever seen.
Wow!
Professor Iijima,
we'll be there right after
we change into sacred vestments.
Okay, I'll be at the University.
Sister!
Bestow upon me the power
to purge all evil!
Here goes!
Isn't he gorgeous?
I'm going ga-ga!
Amatsu, look! Look at him!
His chants are powerful,
but his looks are more deadly.
So true.
Who is his assistant?
She's one of the 1 4th level
named Miyako Fujikado.
I've never seen her before.
Besides, she looks
a bit like him.
Fujikado...
- Could she be his sister?
- Bingo!
She recently transferred here
from another college abroad.
Her brother, Hideto, spent time
studying abroad as well.
I wish I had a brother like him.
Their type seems well deserved.
That piece of impurity has vanished.
Mai, let's go meet them
and give them any help we can.
- Amatsu!
- Yes!
Allow me to introduce you.
They're the granddaughters of Genshyu,
protector of the Temple Tenjin.
This is Ai and Mai.
So you're part of Amatsu Clan.
I'm sorry to hear
of your misfortune.
Thank you for your concern.
This is normally our clan's duty...
but due to our recent misfortune,
we aren't able to.
We greatly appreciate your help.
We can help you place blessed wands
with hemp and paper streamers.
That's great!
I'm Miyako Fujikado.
I'll cover the points
between North and East.
You two might want
to cover South and West.
Okay.
Okay! Ai and Mai,
if you please.
I'm counting on you, Miyako.
Sure, Brother.
Sister, this wand doesn't
look like the Tenjin kind.
- What kind of wand is this?
- I was thinking the same thing.
- Oh my god!
- Mai, get rid of it now!
What!?
It's not for protection.
This might even
invite the sex demons.
Which means...
Mai!
Mai! Are you all right?
What the hell is this?
There's something
suspicious about those two.
Mai, hold onto my hand!
Well, we shall soon witness the
rebirth of the Sex Demon World.
I am the King of the Kijyu.
We shall subjugate this world!
It's time
our dreams become fulfilled.
- Ai.
- Sister.
Finally, we have broken through.
The Kijyu Clan's power will
spread out into this world.
Sister!
What's going on?
What is this?
Sister!
Mai!
Mai! Mai!
Sister!
Are you okay?
I'm glad to see you.
You're okay too, sister.
Oh, my poor sister,
let me clean your wound.
Sister!
What are you doing?
Why?
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it, sister!
You're a liar!
I know you've been waiting for this
for a long time!
No, sister!
You want more of this, right?
Oh sister...
Why?
Because you made eyes at Hideto.
Sister!
Mai, you're mine.
Sister, stop this!
Do you really want me to
stop this, Mai?
Sister!
I love your body
when you get this hot.
Sister!
To be continued...
In the sky,
the moon at noon is white
It makes me feel
somewhat melancholy
Your eyes which are
reflected in the mirror
Are telling me that
you want to change
I'm crying more than ever
I want to fill the void in my heart
Forget everything that
makes you feel bitter
And then, your song will reach out
everywhere in the world
Live strong for the moment
Because you have to stand
and face tomorrow
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it, sister!
You're a liar!
I know you've been waiting for this
for a long time!
No, sister!
You want more of this, right?
Oh sister...
Why?
Because you made eyes at him.
Sister!
Mai, you're mine.
Sister, stop this!
Do you really want me to
stop this, Mai?
Sister!
I love your body
when you get this hot.
Sister!
This...?
What's going on?
Ai!
Mai!
Ai! Here?
Dekunobo, where is Mai?
Oh, sister!
Mai, suck and
lick my pussy hard!
Stick your tongue
deep inside it!
Hurry! Hurry!
I can't wait!
Sister.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Cum!
That heavy breathing is...
I recognize it!
That sounds like Mai.
Mai!
Mai, I have something
special for you.
Sister, what are you doing?
Don't worry.
You're already wet.
Whatever I put into it
will make you feel good.
Sister, no, please!
Shut up and listen to me!
Stop it!
Shit, Mai was all ready to
become mine.
Imposter,
show your true form!
How?
There are two Ai's before me!
Mai!
That one must be on a mission
from the Kijyu Clan.
Don't listen to her!
Damn it! You...
I am the vicious goddess Sutra!
I was trying to get Mai
as a sacrifice for the King.
Ai!
I would have you as well.
No way!
I will not let you!
You're not bad, not bad at all.
But it's too late!
Our Sex Orgy Evil has started to
spread out into the world!
Behold and see this world!
But all is only an illusion!
- What?!
- You bitch!
Mai, be careful!
- Is that...
- Hideto Fujikado!
Show your true self!.
I know the Kijyu sent you.
I am the dreadfully evil Kama.
You look like a beautiful woman
who can satisfy a man's lust.
I'll teach you how to be a good slut
before you become a sacrifice.
Get yourself ready!
I won't let you do that!
Ai, Mai!
Protecting Onimaru is the highest
priority we have at this moment!
Dekunobo!
I know where they're running to.
Then let's start off with
killing this Tenjin lackey!
Evil Sex Demons
come forth to serve!
Attack the Tenjin Temple
and rape them all!
It's me! Open up!
Ai, Mai! I've been
so lonely without you.
I've got no time for this!
Grandmother, terrible news!
The Kijyu has come to this world
using a Space-Time portal!
Oh my goodness!
That means...
He can't be...
He is not Onimaru!
Let me make you feel good!
You bastard!
This is...
My lord!
Where is my lord!
I wasn't sharp enough.
I got careless!
Well then,
where is the real Onimaru?
Grandma!
They must have
taken him in the fire.
I guess they've kidnapped him
and left us this fake.
My lord! My lord! My lord!
This is the gravest sin
Dekunobo has ever committed.
It can't be...
Can't be...Onimaru...
This world has already been
devoured by Kijyu.
What are going to do?
Lord Onimaru!
Ai, Mai, Dekunobo!
Everyone, everyone!
Be careful!
Mai.
Tenjin!
Spirit!
The celestial raiment of the angels!
That is going to be
your final pose!
You're unworthy of
even being our opponents.
Both of you!
Gensyu Amatsu of the Tenjin Clan
will be your opponent.
Come on!
Get yourself ready!
Fight with me!
So the Tenjin Angels have
come out to play.
I shall take your corpses
as souvenirs for our King.
This is no place for
an old woman like you!
Shut up!
Grandmother!
Take these Tenjin wenches back
alive and unharmed.
Well use them as sacrifices
for King Onimaru ceremony.
Dekunobo!
Did you hear that?
Grandmother!
Onimaru has already
become their King.
Go to his side and
talk to him right now.
While he still has
his memories as Onimaru!
Don't worry about me!
Just go to him now! Hurry!
Alright!
Get out of my way!
Dekunobo, hurry up!
Got it!
Damn it!
Sutra!
Create an evil sex barrier!
- Grandmother!
- Don't do anything!
Don't move! It's a trap!
My King!
Here are the beautiful women
I promised you.
All hand picked from
the Tenjin University!
Pledged for the ceremony!
The best thing is that
they're all virgins!
I see, you like them.
Women!
Get your hips up and legs open
so that the King can get a good look.
Can you see this virgin pussy?
Her petals are so fresh, and are
quivering with excitement for you.
This could be the one for you.
Oh, it's really tight...
And the inside is all bumpy.
And the massaging action
is fantastic.
Beasts!
Strip these women naked!
Ripping off their clothes
is part of the pleasure.
My King!
Let me give you some lessons!
In order to make it wet...
First of all, you suck and lick,
suck and lick with your tongue.
And then,
you do it like this!
Finally, you just do
whatever makes you feel good.
Oh, she seems to be already useless.
These are more Tenjin followers.
Good job!
What happened to Ai and Mai?
Kama and Sutra will be here
soon with them.
All right, beasts!
Take these 3 virgins...
consecrated to their deity,
and rape them hard.
Don't let them confuse you!
They aren't real!
They are only phantasms.
The pair that aren't moaning
may be the real ones.
Sister!
Don't become confused!
It's a trap. Look at me!
Focus your heart and mind so that
you don't fall prey to their trap.
Don't act rashly!
Be careful!
Ai, Mai!
Damn you!
Damn you to hell!
Get out of my way!
Don't try to help me!
Right there!
Damn you, old woman!
- Grandmother!
- Are you okay?
Don't worry about me!
- Take care of her!
- All right!
Beasts, follow
and chase them down!
Brother!
Please everyone forgive me!
I can't go and help you now.
If I go in and
try to stop things now...
I'll ruin any chance of getting
Lord Onimaru back from them.
Gensyu told me how important
this all was to do this.
May Tenjin understand...
Forgive me!
Forgive me, everyone!
My lord,
what the hell are you doing?
I should have kept a more
careful watch on you!
This is...
This obscene evil has
already reached the streets.
Sister!
The Evil Sex Spirit has come and
has taken possession of people!
We have to find shelter
from all of this!
Rajyoumon Temple!
We're almost there!
I can't take any more of this!
We need protection
from all of this.
The only way is by calling
for Tenjin's protection.
We must get ourselves
into a Shinto temple.
With Tenjin's protection we can
regroup and figure out what to do next.
Grandmother!
Are you okay, grandmother?
I'm going to die.
Grandmother!
Listen to me very carefully.
If Onimaru take dominion
over this world...
none will be able to survive it.
You both saw the hell
the city became.
And it's only going to get worse
as time goes on.
Kijyu brought
the Evil Sex Spirit...
to force Onimaru
to be their King.
Where Might is the master,
Justice is the servant.
Do you think we have a chance
to get him back?
There is one thing you can do.
But it's no guarantee.
Grandmother, does the King
still have memories of Onimaru?
That memory is the only way...
to help the world
and Onimaru himself.
Speaking to him could
get his memory back.
It's hard to say.
He has both Kijyu's blood
and our Tenjin's blood.
Ai and Mai...
Go back
to the Tenjin Temple...
and find the room
underneath the altar.
That room
didn't burst into flames.
Inside,
seek out a plum tree pot.
You'll be protected by God
as long as you possess it!
Listen! Never give up on
believing in Tenjin!
Believe in the true faith and
the celestial raiment of the angels!
Both you must
combine your powers.
Please help save Onimaru.
You two have already
taken over Tenjin's mission.
Grandmother!
Don't leave!
I've got to go.
Please, carry out your tasks!
Grandmother!
She must be given her peace.
We have to let her go!
I'll crush the Kijyu who've taken
our grandmother's life from us.
I will too.
No, no.
You may be saying ''No'' now,
but soon you'll be begging for it.
No more, no more.
No more?
Does ''No more'' mean
anything like this?
No, please!
Well, panting now, are we?
Everybody pant hard!
For today is the day of our
King's ascension to the throne.
Oh, so good!
Our King, hooray!
My King!
Are you having a good time?
That's great! Wonderful!
I'll also be enjoying myself
all night long!
Here comes Tenjin!
God, protect us!
Crush the enemy!
To be continued...
In the sky,
the moon at noon is white
It makes me feel
somewhat melancholy
Your eyes which are
reflected in the mirror
Are telling me that
you want to change
I'm crying more than ever
I want to fill the void in my heart
Forget everything that
makes you feel bitter
And then, your song will reach out
everywhere in the world
Live strong for the moment
Because you have to stand
and face tomorrow