The inconspicuous girl who suddenly
takes action during summer camp, Nami.
We wandered into a giant mansion,
as if it beckoned us.
But still, why is she all over Natsuki?
So that's what's going on.
Let's go, Natsuki! Time to transform!
Septem Charm Magical Kanan
Palpitating Summer Camp Part 2
So that means everyone's...
Mafuyu.
Miss Taeko.
This is wonderful, Mafuyu.
Miss Taeko, I can't wait.
It's okay, just shut up.
You want more?
It feels so good inside of you.
No, stop it!
Let go of me!
What the hell!
Why do I put up with this crap?
Chihaya.
Who can I loathe?
Tell me!
This is the heart of the Netherworld Tree?
Is anyone in there?
It's no use here, either.
Time to go!
Chihaya, you can't just keep running.
You can't, Nami. Now's not the time
to be doing that.
I was so happy when you asked me
to play with you.
Come on, Natsuki, let's play.
That feels good.
It's only just begun.
Damn, that feels good.
That's it. You can come on my breasts
if you want to.
I can't do that. I have Chihaya.
Is that so? But Chihaya can't do this,
can she?
You can't...
To being with, it's all Natsuki's fault...
for being such a man whore
and becoming Nami's bitch.
Not being where he should
be when he should be!
To top it off, we get lost in this
humongous mansion.
Chihaya?
I'm not letting you go.
Nami.
You're mine.
I'm not handing you over to Chihaya.
I'm going to come.
"Come?" That's it!
Wasn't that good?
But it's even better inside of Nami.
Natsuki?
Chihaya!
Hey, what's going on?
What do you think you're doing?
At this rate I'll... Natsuki!
Natsuki, give me power.
And look at only me.
I don't want to do it with anyone
other than Natsuki.
Natsuki, save me.
Right now, the only ones
who can stop the Netherworld Tree...
are Chihaya and Natsuki
I have to find them.
No!
Save me, Natsuki!
You can't.
Chihaya!
Sayaka!
Wait!
Please don't harm Sayaka.
I have her replacement right here.
I won't run away anymore.
I can't sit there and let Sayaka die.
I won't do it.
Tsuyoshi became a Seed human?
Stupid Natsuki!
Stop it!
Chihaya!
Natsuki!
I won't lose now!
Carmine Eco-Shower!
The Eco-Shower won't come out?
Why?
Chihaya?
Natsuki?
I'm sorry. I wasn't at full power.
Natsuki!
My power.
Chihaya?
Chihaya, you okay?
Natsuki, where's everyone?
The mansion was burned down by lighting.
The only ones they found
at the front were us two and Sayaka.
No way! It can't be,
everyone was still in there?
- You shouldn't move around yet.
- But...
Sayaka wants to see you.
Sayaka does? Where is she?
She's next door to us, but...
There's no need to worry, everybody's safe.
Really?
All right!
But...
They are being swallowed
by the Netherworld Tree.
I met another me there.
There was a cave underneath that mansion.
That's where I disappeared to.
Everyone must be there!
Yeah!
It's so lonely there. Please save them!
Of course we will.
Natsuki, let's go!
Yeah!
It's so lonely there, the Seed is...
The problem is getting out of here.
We can't worry the parents
any more than they already are.
You know?
Natsuki, come here!
Chihaya, you don't have to do
it at such a kinky place like this.
No, you idiot!
Then what is it?
This!
The size doesn't fit at all,
but I'll have to make do.
Let's go, Natsuki!
Where are you looking at!
Do you sense anything?
It's a wonder how good
just a change of clothes is.
God, I can't believe you!
What are you thinking at a time like this?
Acting cute. Don't play with me!
I can't believe him.
What's that?
It seems a bit different then
the Dark Undulation.
- But everyone must be in there!
- Yeah.
Let's go, Natsuki!
Roger!
I'm slipping!
Stay still! I'll lift you up.
It's fine, I'll climb myself.
No, I'm fine. Wait, stop!
That wasn't very nice.
Miyuri! Mafuyu!
Miss Taeko!
It's sucking energy from everyone!
That's right.
This is the other Seed that fell
from the magical kingdom of Ever Green.
But it looks like this place
had too little energy for it to grow.
So that's why, it's showing dreams
to people and using that as energy.
So then, where's the kidnapped people?
Probably at the bottom of this lake.
No way.
That's unforgivable!
Don't be so hasty.
You're opponent today isn't me.
- Nami! Tsuyoshi!
- So you're safe!
Of course, my desire
is to be with you, Natsuki.
Nami, her heart's been stolen
by the Dark Undulation!
Natsuki! Time to transform!
Okay!
Burning with eternal love!
The crimson warrior!
Magical Angel Carmine!
Carmine Eco-Shower!
How's that?
You did it, nice job!
Or did you?
The Eco-Shower didn't work?
That can't be!
Too bad, wasn't it?
Those two aren't under the control
of the Dark Undulation.
They're not under control?
That's right. The Dark Power
is merely lending them power.
To fulfill their desires.
Desires?
You call yourself the warrior of love...
and yet you don't know how
to love one another.
- What do you mean?
- You still don't get it!
I love you, Chihaya.
He became like this all because
you didn't realize his feelings.
No way!
And you know Nami's feelings, don't you?
It wasn't me, she forcefully
injected magic into me!
That's my present.
Go make Nami's wishes come true.
Natsuki!
Natsuki, love me.
That was nothing.
The warrior of love, losing to love.
How ironic is that?
Tsuyoshi, stop it! I'm begging you!
Love.
Carmine is the warrior of love.
Only the power of love
can save everyone.
No way! What can I do?
I got it, Chihaya!
What?
Nami, there's no way I can ever love you.
But I can teach you how to love!
It's so different from before.
He's in pain because I never noticed him.
I'm sorry, Tsuyoshi.
I wasn't able to realize your feelings for me.
You loved me so much
you became like this.
It's okay, Tsuyoshi. Make love to me.
I'll show you inside.
I'll show you what love feels like.
That's the end of that.
Thank goodness everyone was safe.
Yeah, but what was wrong with
Tsuyoshi that time?
He probably figured it out.
That it's not love if it's by force.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey Carmine, why are you not
reverting back to yourself?
The battle's over.
I was thinking if I should do you.
"Do me," you say?
Didn't you tell me
that you like them really big?
You see, I may be in this form...
but as long as you
call me Chihaya, I'm okay.
How is it? Feel good?
Hell yeah!
Really?
It's okay, give me your come
on my breasts.
How's that? You satisfied?
- Incredible.
- You wanted me to do this?
I'm sorry, If it was that good...
it would be nice if I could do it all the time.
You want me to do it again?
As long as you call me
Chihaya, I'm happy.
I'm happy.
I want to come inside of you, Chihaya.
Natsuki.
You called me Chihaya,
I heard you say it.
Of course. That's because
you're the Chihaya I know and love.
I'm so happy.
Please, don't stop,
give it to me to the end.
Please say it!
Say my name!
Chihaya!
Natsuki!
What?
- I felt like saying it.
- Why you! I'll tickle you!
Quit it!
What's wrong?
Come to think of it, that last time.
Why weren't you at full power?
You punk, you didn't!