Once upon a time...
only 10 or so years ago...
evil came forth in the city of Meihou.
In order to defeat that evil...
a warrior from the kingdom of magic...
alongside the magical warrior
he found in that city.
Combined their forces to seal the evil.
And...
it disappeared from the memories
of the people.
But the warriors knew it in their hearts...
that the seal was not perfect.
Septem Charm Magical Kanan Vol. 4
From Carmine with Love
It is nearing.
The moment fate has woven.
I trust you in case something happens.
Okay, I only follow your orders,
Master Bergamot.
Let's ride on that next! Over there!
You really like the scream machines.
I think I'll pass.
Come on, don't say that.
Come ride with me.
So where is your boyfriend today?
Who are you talking about?
You're not fooling anyone, Natsuki.
That asshole isn't my boyfriend!
That asshole!
I got it! 10:00 at the front gate?
I'll see you tomorrow!
Meihou Rainbow Town...
I've always wanted to go there.
Natsuki!
Mafuyu wanted to know...
if we wanted to go
to Rainbow Town with her tomorrow.
Natsuki!
It's so soft.
And what, may I ask, are you doing?
It's not like that! I was doing some
investigating, but I slipped and...
Investigating my ass!
My goodness.
Chihaya?
That lecherous asshole.
Lecherous? Did something happen?
Something? Of course not,
there's couldn't have been anything!
Say, where did Mafuyu go to?
Mafuyu left to go to the restroom, why?
The restroom?
A flower in here?
Don't peek now.
I wonder if Chihaya's still pissed
about yesterday.
She left without even telling me.
This voice is...
Mafuyu!
What the hell is that?
It's not a Seed human.
Why you!
Take this!
It worked!
Mafuyu!
Hang in there, Mafuyu!
Thank goodness.
Mafuyu!
Hot. My body's so hot!
Give me some of this, please.
Mafuyu's been captivated by the magic.
At this rate she'll be crushed by the energy.
In order to save Mafuyu...
I need to have sex with her
and absorb her power.
Mafuyu's awfully late.
She is, isn't she?
I'm going to go look for her.
Okay, Chihaya.
Now there's nothing to worry about.
Natsuki!
Chihaya, don't get the wrong idea,
this isn't what you think.
Natsuki, you...
Natsuki, I hate you!
Natsuki, you asshole!
Chihaya, wait up!
What's all this?
What are they?
Chihaya, listen to me.
Let's transform, Chihaya!
- But...
- We need to transform!
Carmine! Let's hurry and save everyone!
Carmine!
What are you doing
standing around? Hurry!
I got it.
Let go of those people!
Shoot!
Stop it!
Master Hazuna!
Carmine's in trouble! Let's go!
Yes!
Carmine!
Cerulean Boomerang!
The sparkle of justice of the deep blue sea!
Now's your chance, Carmine!
All right!
Carmine!
Eco-Shower!
No way!
Carmine!
Shit!
What is this? I can't fight back.
It's like it's sucking power out of me.
Carmine! Cerulean Blue!
Save me Natsuki!
Septem!
Why?
Follow me.
Wait!
Follow her!
Magical Kanan!
What are they?
They are Stamen.
As in the plant organ?
But why didn't the Eco-Shower work?
The energy of a magical warrior is love.
The stronger your faith is,
the stronger love becomes.
But Carmine has distrust surging
through her heart.
That is...
But Septem, why did you save us?
Isn't all that your doing?
I only follow the orders
of Master Bergamot.
Bergamot?
Is that the name of the person
who stole the Seeds from Ever Green?
That's right.
So you're the cause of all of this!
You're a resident of Ever Green aren't you?
Why did you do that?
I was sent to this city, Meihou,
under the order of Queen Tsuyuha.
My duty was to destroy
an evil presence there.
Long, long a ago, a Seed fell from
Ever Green to the earth by accident.
It absorbed the hatred
and malice of the humans.
And grew into a monster.
I met a girl who had the makings
of a magical warrior.
And we fought together.
But we could not destroy it.
How come?
If we had used the full power
of the magical warrior...
it would've been possible to destroy it.
But, that would mean killing the new soul
inside the magical warrior.
New soul?
That's right. Carmine.
You were inside that magical warrior.
Then, that means...
Make no mistake, I am your father.
Then Mama's a magic warrior?
So that's why Emi looks like her
when she was young.
I created Septem in the image
of Carmine's mother.
The time of resurrection is near.
If it awakens, our daughter,
having magic energy, we'll be attacked.
I stole the Seeds to give my daughter
the strength to prevent that.
So that's why you...
So that means...
Mafuyu.
Miyuri.
Tomoe.
Sai.
And Ayumi all went through
all that all because of me?
That's cruel.
That's too cruel!
Carmine!
You guys are all so selfish!
You couldn't beat it because I was there?
You're the ones who made me!
Natsuki, too! You said you loved me,
and you did it with Mafuyu!
But that's...
You're all...
so selfish!
Carmine!
Chihaya.
Stop it!
I'll protect everyone with my powers!
It's here!
Carmine!
Where am I?
This is what I've been yearning for.
Who are you?
The very magic you possess
is the key to my resurrection.
Your magic shall be mine.
No!
Such warmth. This is power.
Not enough.
More!
Look! The bud is...
What's that?
She turned back into Chihaya!
It sucked up her magic!
- Septem!
- Yes?
Wait!
I leave it to you.
Bergamot!
Chihaya!
Natsuki.
Cerulean Blue.
And also, Septem.
Chihaya?
Chihaya. What's going on?
I was saved by Chihaya.
So was I.
Mafuyu's memories have returned!
The magic around here is getting weak!
Cerulean Blue!
Sayaka?
Mafuyu, Miyuri!
Please cheer Chihaya up!
What's going on?
Right now, Chihaya needs
our support more than ever.
Chihaya!
Hang in there, Chihaya!
I can hear all of your voices.
Chihaya!
You have me and the others!
Chihaya! You were born because you
had a father and a mother!
You're the embodiment of love!
The embodiment...
of love?
Stop it!
Septem!
Septem, why?
I was created by Master Bergamot.
I follow the orders of Master Bergamot.
Septem!
Chihaya!
Natsuki, hurry and come!
Give me strength!
Chihaya!
No! I hate the darkness!
Chihaya, purification!
No, there's no need for purification.
Chihaya!
Poor thing.
You were lonely, weren't you?
Carmine.
- No, this is...
- Yes.
That's it.
Bergamot!
Why?
My life was already at its end
when I stole the Seeds.
He attempted to evolve Carmine,
even at the cost of his own life.
No.
It's okay, Chihaya.
It was destined to happen the moment
you formed inside your mother.
You had no choice in the matter.
I'm sorry to have made you go through this.
I will watch over you
and your mother from here.
Father!
Dear.
The inhabitants of Ever Green transmigrate
into a tree when they die.
But I've never seen such
a splendid one as this.
Hazuna, Natsuki, Chihaya.
You have done well.
I will plant this Seed
in the pure soil of Ever Green.
It will surely bloom beautiful flowers.
Natsuki?
Your duties have been fulfilled.
Return to Ever Green.
He can't!
I don't want that!
Chihaya.
I'm sorry.
Natsuki.
Natsuki!