Hold it right there!
I finally found you.
Let that lady go, right now!
Chihaya, transform!
The crimson flame of love and passion!
Magical Angel, Carmine!
Septem Charm Magical Kanan
Enter the Crimson Magical Warrior Carmine.
Suzuhara, 1 meter 50 cm, cleared!
Incredible, she beat her own record!
You did it, Miyuri!
You go, Meihou's Queen
of Decathlete! All right!
Yeah!
I'm Chihaya Hiiragi.
I'm a normal girl that you'd find anywhere.
That strange creature I took in
was hurt badly and was weakened.
But as it lived with us, it got a lot better,
and I was happy for it.
It was a normal story up until then.
To my surprise, it all of a sudden
transformed into a human!
I was so surprised, he was naked
and all, never mind that.
Chihaya Hiiragi! I'm going now.
So Natsuki, his name is Natsuki.
This is what he said.
"I am a warrior from another world,
the magical kingdom of Ever Green."
The Temple of Darkness,
the area forbidden to all.
The seal has been broken.
Someone has stolen the Magic Seeds...
filled with the power of darkness,
and escaped to the human world.
The Seeds will multiply,
possess humans...
and create a horde of demons
living for nothing but their desires.
Hazuna. Natsuki.
We understand completely!
In my current condition,
I only have enough magic...
to send you two brothers
to the human world.
I leave it to you for the sake
of Ever Green and the human world.
And on top of that!
I'm still not done.
Listen to me, I'm sorry.
It seems I have the rare predisposition
to react with Natsuki's magic.
When I kiss Natsuki...
I transform into a magical warrior
in order to beat the bad guys!
Here I go!
Carmine Eco-Shower!
Hey Chihaya. He's not coming today?
You know, your cousin!
Natsuki's here already.
He's probably inside.
I came here to investigate.
How'd it end up like this?
Stop it, I can't hold it in anymore!
You don't have to hold it in.
I mean, you came all this way to peek.
You need some?
No, I didn't come here to peek.
I was here to investigate.
Anyway, it was an accident.
You accidentally hid under the bed?
I felt a presence,
so I came to look and got lucky.
Unlucky is what I meant.
You're young. You're still okay?
- Natsuki is the same age as us, right?
- Yeah.
It'd be nice if he'll be
in the same class as we were.
I don't really...
Of course. You want to be with him.
He's your boyfriend.
We're not like that.
You're all red. That's so cute.
Miyuri!
Miss, I have to stop. My magic...
Call me Taeko, I need it.
Miss, I'm coming again!
Sayaka Mizuki. Here I come!
Mizuki, let's give it another try.
Sayaka is as clumsy as usual, isn't she?
Sorry about that!
Are you okay?
Tamura!
I'm perfectly fine!
I don't' mind at all,
so keep hitting her all you want!
You're so mean, Miyuri.
Come now. She's exuberant
being able to talk with him.
Forgive her, Chihaya.
My.
Emi!
Are you feeling fine?
I thought you were resting in the infirmary.
Not anymore.
Natsuki?
Where'd you go, Natsuki?
Natsuki!
A new breed of rats?
No, a raccoon!
This is an amazing discovery!
I need to dissect it right away!
- Wait!
- Run!
Stop running away!
Someone! Capture that thing!
I heard that some guinea pig
bloodied Miss Taeko and ran away!
No, that was a guy from Class 5.
He said that the raccoon can transform!
No, that's not it! If you catch the rat,
Miss Taeko will give you head!
Man, she's hot!
Let's get him!
It's so cute!
Is it a raccoon?
What's this?
You naughty boy.
You mustn't!
Please don't move!
What's this? It's swollen.
You're right. It's getting bigger.
The tip seems to be wet.
That's funny. Take this!
- And this and this and this...
- Don't touch that.
Man, I'm tired.
I'm sorry Chihaya. I didn't mean it.
The commotion at the infirmary
was you, too, wasn't it?
Why are you in that form anyways?
Well, this is because
I lost my magic energy.
You did something that would
use your magic, did you?
No, it's not always like that.
I'm not in my stride yet.
And a bunch of factors played a part.
It was by chance, I had to do it.
I see. It must've been hard.
Yeah! It was!
You lecherous pervert! Dirty bastard!
Don't ever come close to me again!
Wait up for me, Chihaya!
Is anyone here?
This is Tamura of the basketball team.
Could you shut the door, please?
Where?
Just shut the door?
It's you. What do you want?
What do I want?
I've been watching you
ever since I saw you.
The truth is,
I think I love you, Tamura.
I have practice. I need to go.
Tamura, do you know what this is?
I'm not wearing anything.
I'm so wet because you're watching.
Look how wet I am.
Tamura, the equipment will get wet.
Want to watch it get even wetter?
Could you clean it?
With your mouth.
Tamura, you're so hot.
Magical Kanan!
It's so big, Tamura.
Tamura, you want to keep going?
Or do you like it in here?
Cute little boy.
Chihaya! Regain your temperament already!
This is not the time for that.
We have to think of powering up
so we can handle new enemies.
Shut up already!
I'm sorry I got you caught up in this.
But I don't have time!
I need your power to save the world!
That's your problem.
What's this "power up?"
When you transform, I inject
my magic energy into you, right?
Inject? Isn't there a better word?
The injection of magic
is the injecting of bodily fluids!
So all you have to do is to take
my thick juice deeper inside your body!
In other words...
Thick juice my ass!
You stole my first kiss, and now?
Quit fucking with me!
You beast! You beast!
Stupid perverted rat!
- I'm going, Mama.
- Take care.
Chihaya...
I said, shut up!
I think she's a whore.
But she helps people, right?
- What's going on?
- You haven't heard?
There's a rumor of a warrior in town.
She comes and saved you
if your attacked like this!
Sai, don't do that. They're getting hard.
A heroine of justice, you see?
A heroine of justice!
She's just a slut, isn't she?
She may be a exhibitionist!
Her clothes were frilly,
but she was wearing doggie panties.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing! Nothing at all!
I'm not ever, ever, ever...
transforming again!
Chihaya!
You shouldn't let those rumors
bother you.
Right, Chihaya?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Good morning Chihaya,
it's nice to see you.
Sayaka, morning!
The scent of magic!
Nothing gained today.
This is a Seed undulation?
This is so embarrassing.
Are you sure that this will
cure your disease?
You don't believe the words
of your principal?
Yes, I do.
Very good.
Now let's begin your examination.
Not bad.
How about here?
Natsuki?
Mafuyu!
What is this?
What are you thinking?
Stupid!
I have to go!
What was that?
You have to go?
Go where? Come on!
No, please!
What is this? What's going on?
There's no doubt about it!
It's the work of a Seed!
Chihaya, let's transform!
For the sake of Mafuyu!
That's not fair.
You're such a naughty girl,
dirtying the floor.
I'll plug that naughty hole of yours.
Come here.
Stop it, you pervert!
Who are you, barging in here?
The flame of love and anger!
Magic Angel Carmine!
- Carmine! Purification!
- Okay!
Carmine Eco-Shower!
Mafuyu!
Carmine, it's not over!
Carmine!
Why?
You purified him!
Is that all you got, Carmine?
- Who are you?
- I am Septem.
Don't get so cocky because
you purified copies of the Seeds.
You went too far.
And it's past your time.
- To be done.
- Because of you! You did this!
I'll have you feel the power
of the real thing.
With that body!
Carmine!
Shit! Let go!
Let's wait here and watch Carmine
get raped. Her ultimate fantasy.
Stop it!
No!
No don't.
Stop it!
Carmine!
I think I'll take your magic now.
What do you think you're...
You're so hard and erect.
You getting excited watching
your partner get raped.
It's delicious.
Stop! Stop it!
No, stop!
I'm scared, save me. Natsuki!
To Be Continued