Here I come!
You fell again?
You're so clumsy.
My bad!
I scraped it.
Angel Kiss's specialty!
Ultra Super Deluxe Parfait!
Are you sure, Chihaya?
Don't worry, I got it.
It's sticky.
Chihaya.
Tsuyoshi, can I come in?
Septem Charm Magical Kanan
Palpitating Summer Camp
Part one
What the hell are you doing?
It's still noon!
Hey, you too, sister!
Just because we're twins,
doesn't mean we have no privacy!
I already told you that Chihaya
has a boyfriend named Natsuki.
That pretty little sissy.
Sissy? How old are now?
I'll be sure to turn Chihaya's head
during summer camp!
It is true that Natsuki can't come along
to the summer camp tomorrow...
because he's not a student
of the Meihou Academy.
But that doesn't necessarily mean
that you'll become her boyfriend.
Good luck, now.
Goodbye, goodbye.
The earth is in danger.
Someone is using Seeds stolen
from the magical kingdom of Ever Green.
...and is setting traps of chaos and erotica.
As long as I live...
I'm not going to let wicked things happen!
Let's go, time to transform!
Got you!
Hey!
Carmine!
Eco-Shower!
And that end today's purification.
All that's left is to erase
the couple's memory.
You've been getting good at this.
Sayaka's still not feeling too well.
So I need work for the both of us!
I won't forgive you!
I'm sorry, Sayaka.
Why?
I'll save you.
Chihaya.
Chihaya!
But what was that transformation scene?
I thought it'd be cool
if I did something.
Come on! What we're doing
isn't some game.
It's a noble and rigorous duty.
And what, may I dare to ask, are you doing?
I was just thinking that unlike Chihaya,
Carmine's got some big breasts.
Carmine One-Hand Top!
It doesn't really matter, but...
Don't you think you're overdoing it
with those breasts?
It's because Natsuki said those things.
I'll get myself a wonderful boyfriend
and show him!
Now then, everyone,
go enjoy this summer camp.
But make sure that you do not leave
the premise of this beach.
I'll be watching.
Okay!
Hey, Chihaya.
What's up with those breasts?
Natsuki?
What are you doing here?
Angel Kiss Beachside Cafй?
What the heck is that?
Right after you guys left,
Mama decided all of a sudden...
It's not fair that only Chihaya gets to
have fun at the beach.
I say we go to the beach, too.
There you have it, that's how
we all decided to go to the beach!
Come in! Welcome to Angel Kiss
Beachfront Cafй!
Hi! There's empty seat right here!
Ramen, grilled squid,
and shaved ice coming right up!
And so, I've been dragged here to help out.
My, my. Isn't that too bad?
What were you planning to do
with those breasts while I was gone?
It doesn't matter to you.
Not now. People are watching.
Unforgivable!
Hey, Natsuki,
will you rub suntan lotion on me?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're so good at it.
Man, I'll take the real things
over fakes any day.
Damn you!
Take this!
Death Blow! Breast Missile!
Chihaya!
I'm not like him!
I like your flat chest and straight waist!
What was that?
Well, excuse me for being flat-chested!
So what if I am straight-waisted?
Of course that would upset her.
Chihaya!
That stupid Natsuki.
What's wrong?
That girl, what is she doing over there?
She's still in her uniform.
That's Nami Minami.
Nami Minami?
It seems that she has a weak body
and is always resting during PE.
She looks gloomy and hard
to get along with.
You're Nami, right?
Want to play with us?
Come on, it's okay.
You can play with us.
Nami!
Don't go that way, Chihaya.
There aren't many people.
Lately there's been
kidnappings around here.
Kidnappings?
She has grown up to be
such a splendid lady.
Here you go.
Thank you.
No, I should be thanking you.
Natsuki.
No, I'm not fit to be with him.
Plus...
What's wrong, Chihaya?
Did you hear something?
No.
That's odd.
I will answer it.
Your prayers, they shall be answered.
Stop it! I'm still...
I wasn't aware a Seed was sprouting here.
Magical Kanan!
That punk!
I will answer it.
Your prayers they shall be answered.
You're Nami?
It's kind of romantic, isn't it?
Yeah, how beautiful.
It's true. It's such a beautiful sunset.
That's not it, I'm saying you're beautiful.
Natsuki.
Hey, were Nami's breasts that big?
Natsuki, you idiot!
Hey, what are you?
You don't like this stuff?
Stop it!
I already have a person named Chihaya
that I've decided on.
That's not what I was trying to say.
There's no point in underwear,
since it's sticking out this much.
No, I can't!
It doesn't matter.
You see, all you have to do
is rape Chihaya in your heart.
Rape her with my heart?
Baby.
It's still not enough.
In that case, there's a much
better "mouth" down here.
Look.
See? Right here.
Go ahead and lick it.
The horizon looked round?
It looks like that from that point.
I thought you were late,
that's where you were?
Natsuki!
Nami wants to go see
the round horizon with you!
They're round all right. Round.
Was she like that before?
She's become daring.
I wonder if something happened.
But the principal told us
not to leave the beach.
Sounds interesting.
I'll go along with you as a chaperone.
I want to see it too. That round horizon.
That's impossible.
We have permission. Now let's go, Natsuki!
Okay.
Tsuyoshi, let's go!
What's going on with those four?
Man, the clouds sure look ominous.
I hope this doesn't turn into a storm.
This is relentless!
I'm scared!
There's nothing for you
to worry about. I'm here to protect.
Natsuki, Natsuki!
Tsuyoshi, I'm scared of the lightning.
Brother.
Chihaya's audacious.
But, with someone other than Natsuki.
I wonder if it's okay.
Isn't this place a bit dangerous?
You're right.
But where?
There's a mansion there.
Is anyone here?
There's no one here.
I can tell that!
It looks like it hasn't been
used in a long time.
Javantich would faint
if he saw how dirty this is.
Natsuki, I'm cold.
We need to dry ourselves off.
But, how?
Let's find something that burns.
And something dry to wear.
That might be impossible.
But we need to look.
Tsuyoshi, let's go.
We'll go this way.
Please, wait!
Where did Miyuri go?
She was just here.
Maybe she's searching a different room.
Let's go.
What? What's this?
No! Let go!
No!
It's was only the wind.
Who's there? Come out.
That scared me. It's just a mirror.
Where's Sayaka?
I don't know. Bathroom, maybe?
I'll go get her.
She'll get lost.
What's that noise? A ball?
Sayaka wasn't at the restroom?
I'll answer it.
Who's there?
I will answer it.
Your prayers shall be answered by me.
Your wish is to punish yourself like this.
Otherwise, you would remember it.
About that night.
You're so well-developed.
Juvantich must be enthralled.
No, stop it!
Forgive me!
They were men who loathed my father.
As a stress reliever,
they used my body as a toy.
You remember now?
I'm the you of that day.
Who can I loathe?
Tell me!
So that's how it is.
Let's go, Natsuki. Time to transform!
Natsuki's not...
He's not here!
No!