As I thought.
Septem Charm Magical Kanan Vol. 3
Clash! Carmine vs. Cerulean Blue
Come on, Chihaya!
No!
Carmine's source of power is love.
We need to deepen our relationship. Right?
No.
You may by talking big,
but what's that over there?
What is that?
This is the sad nature of men.
We have no control.
All that's left is to take by force!
The crimson flame of love and passion!
Magical Angel Carmine!
What the hell were you doing?
Why did you transform me?
I do like Chihaya's
underdeveloped breasts.
But having those voluptuous breasts
of Carmine squeezing me is also good.
Natsuki! Reporting to duty!
Who's breasts are underdeveloped,
you bastard?
This has its own sense of ecstasy.
Still saying that now?
That's too hard!
Sipping?
Don't mind me and continue on.
Queen Tsuyuha!
The queen of Ever Green!
I have felt a quiver of darkness in this city.
How could that be?
The work of Seed humans?
No, we can't be sure of that.
But there is no doubt
that there is something going on in Meihou.
So that was Chihaya Hiiragi?
Man, that scared me.
The queen of Ever Green
came to see me.
But now she's gone.
Come now!
It's time for our moment of love.
Natsuki! Reporting to duty!
I said "no" didn't I?
Natsuki, you idiot!
Time to clean up.
My, my. Stop being so mischievous.
Mama!
This is quite a nostalgic thing we have here.
Why is Emi's picture here?
How long has it been?
This is a picture
when I was still a student.
Mama's student days?
But this face...
Faster, faster.
That's it, more!
Give me more of your energy!
It's so hot! Let me drink some that.
Do it, baby. You are so good.
I like it.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I've regained
most of my power.
Septem, the battle has already
moved to the next level.
But our preparations are not complete.
Leave it to me, Master Bergamot.
I have already prepared our next move.
I want to go in first.
I love wearing my suit,
it makes me feel so pretty.
Hazuna! This is part of my investigation!
Natsuki, I'm going back
to Ever Green for awhile.
But why?
We don't have enough information.
You must've seen it too,
when you came to this town.
The person who stole
the Seeds from Ever Green...
...may not have come to Meihou by chance.
No way, but if we didn't come
to this town...
I would've never met Chihaya.
So blue.
It was a beautiful blue sky like this,
the day I met Sayaka.
It's no good.
The magic circle is pulling me in!
It is Cerulean blue tea.
- Juvanitch.
- Yes?
Can you leave me alone?
But, Mistress...
Leave me alone!
Are you sure, Mistress Sayaka?
I have looked at the sky since that day.
The blueness of the sky
is too bright for me.
That day, I was investigating city of Meihou,
but I lost to the power of the magic circle.
And I got Sayaka mixed up in this.
There was only one way to save Sayaka.
The profound warrior of azure
Cerulean Blue has arrived!
But there is something I mustn't forget.
Cerulean Blue's magic circle.
It's proof that she's still incomplete
as a magical warrior.
Welcome! Come on in!
But this is incredible, Sayaka.
Riding in such a fancy car
like this every day!
Not just her car,
but her house is incredible, too.
It's as big as a castle
and the has a bunch of butlers and maids.
Maids?
Man, I want to go there.
And for what reason?
Chihaya, Natsuki, you're both so funny.
It's your fault we were laughed at.
Why is it my fault?
We're already here.
Man, that was so fast.
Thank you Juvantich!
You're welcome.
Sayaka, I'll see you later.
It was very entertaining.
I will see you tomorrow. Goodbye.
Goodbye! I'll see you, later!
Man, I want maids.
Still saying that?
Shouldn't I be good enough for you?
If you'll say that,
at least let me screw you!
Maybe I don't want to
because you put it like that!
What? Tonight's okay?
Stupid!
I'm sorry, Chihaya!
Hey, that's...
It's a joke.
It's Emi.
Magical Kanan!
Why was Emi there?
I don't know.
She might be planning something?
A general hospital?
Let's go, Chihaya!
The nurse is...
Chihaya! Transform!
Okay!
Stop right there! Let go of that nurse!
Septem!
You feel for my trap.
Go get her!
Stop it!
What!
Cerulean Blue Eco-Shower!
I'll remember this!
Thank you Cerulean Blue!
Really, I whish you wouldn't trouble me
with the likes of these enemies.
You very silly girl.
Master Hazuna is busy right know.
Farewell, then. Take care of yourself.
Sayaka sure does change
personalities when she transforms.
It can't be helped.
When you transform...
you become the embodiment
of your desires.
But I don't have any desires.
What are you talking about?
When you transform,
your breasts are bigger!
You always worried about how
your breasts were underdeveloped.
I have returned, Master Hazuna.
The results? Do you have them?
Here. As you can see...
I wish that she would be able to
handle something as easy as this.
Don't say that. She's trying.
Cerulean Blue. What's wrong?
Come on, get her! Get her! Bitch!
After you're done, I want her. Hurry up.
Blame it on your dad!
We were put out of business
because of your dad!
Stop taking so long, I want some.
Come, here, to me.
Cerulean Blue! Blue!
No!
Chihaya!
How dare you peek into a girl's shower,
you scumbag!
No, it's a Seed undulation!
This is Sayaka's house.
I feel a strong Seed undulation here.
No way, it can't be.
Anyways, let's go, Chihaya.
What's going on?
Everyone's dominated
by the power of the Seed!
Sayaka!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Hazuna!
Watch out!
Cerulean Blue has been dominated
by the Seed!
Sayaka had darkness within her heart.
The seed got her there.
It was my fault.
I didn't notice that darkness.
Natsuki, let's transform!
We'll save Say...
I mean Cerulean Blue!
I got you! Chihaya!
The flame of love, friendship, and hope!
Magical Angel Carmine!
That day I was raped.
By some men of a subcontracted
company that my father abandoned.
From that day on,
I was unable to look up at the sky.
Despite that.
You were always so happy.
I'll show you the all pain
and sadness that I have felt.
Sayaka...
I will rape you.
- What's that?
- The Seed!
It responded to Cerulean Blue's desire!
You're getting wet.
You shouldn't have all the fun.
Now it's my turn to have fun.
It's not over yet.
My pain is far greater than this.
Carmine!
Stay back!
I didn't even realize it.
That you, Sayaka, were suffering so much.
That's why.
I'll take in all of your feelings.
That's all pretty talk.
There's no way,
that you understand my feelings!
How's that?
Feels good, doesn't it?
That's right, Carmine!
Feel it even more!
And expose everything!
Expose your all!
Expose yourself, Carmine!
Raise your voice higher!
Higher, higher!
That's it! Does it feel good?
I'll make you come, Carmine!
Now climax, Carmine!
It's okay, Sayaka.
I'll take in all of your feelings.
Chihaya.
Sayaka.
All right!
She purified Sayaka's heart!
Hot! It's so hot!
It's hot. It's hot.
Sayaka!
Chihaya! It's a rebound!
A rebound?
Sayaka has absorbed
too much magic power.
At this rate, she'll be crushed by the magic!
What can we do?
There is only one way.
You have to absorb the magic!
You know the process.
Have sex with her!
You're the only one who can do it!
Hazuna!
It's hot, it's hot, so hot.
Save me.
Save me!
All right.
So, what'd you find out?
It seems that the person
who stole the Seeds...
is a scientist that was dispatched
to this city 10 years ago.
So like us, he has to...
Yeah.
It seems he also fought alongside
a magical warrior.
Why did such a person steal the Seeds?
I couldn't find that out. But...
But?
There definitely is something to this case.
I'm sorry, but we're closed for today.
Welcome home.
To Be Continued