No! No, please, no!
I'm scared. Save me, Natsuki!
Cerulean Blue Eco-Shower!
What?
Who're you?
I am the profound warrior of Azure.
Cerulean Blue!
Septem Charm Magical Kanan Vol. 2
Angel Kiss in Danger
I'm sorry, Chihaya.
I was with you,
and I let that happen.
Who the hell was that bitch?
Damn you!
Carmine! You okay?
Yeah.
Thank you for saving me.
Are you a magic warrior, too?
Unable to purify
such an easy situation as this.
The red warrior of passion.
Carmine the magical warrior
is nothing but a petty girl!
What'd you say?
I suggest that you allow me, Cerulean Blue,
to handle the recovery of the Seeds...
Don't worry, stay home.
What do you mean?
My, you're not only lacking
in strength but brains too.
I'm saying that you're no longer needed.
What'd you say?
You wouldn't happen to be Hazuna's
magical warrior, would you?
That's right. She's my partner,
Cerulean Blue.
Who's that?
He's my older brother.
Your older brother?
Under the order of Queen of Ever Green...
He came to the human world
with me to find the Seeds.
Natsuki, you should power up
your partner some more.
It's too dangerous at this rate.
In other words, you're in the way!
I don't care if she's green or yellow,
what is up with her?
I'm sorry, Chihaya,
for being too unreliable.
If only I had more power,
Carmine would be more powerful.
If I had more magic,
I could've released power of love and hope.
Natsuki.
But it's not like there isn't
a way to power up.
Is that what you were talking about
earlier, about sex?
I will inject my magic energy
directly into your body.
I'm not saying this to get with you.
I want to help you, Chihaya.
Natsuki, do you like me?
Of course I do.
This power up relies heavily
on the relationship between the partners.
It has to be between people
who love each other.
People who love each other.
Okay, let's do it.
It's for the sake of powering up.
It can't be helped.
Chihaya.
Hold it right there!
I just noticed, but since when
did you end up in that form?
That was when Septem...
My chastity was at stake,
you were doing what?
Fuck you!
Chihaya, quit pouting!
That was an inevitable accident!
If you had been given head like that,
even you would...
Shut up!
Leave me alone!
Just when she was getting into the mood.
Stupid me!
But still, I wonder what kind of girl
Hazuna picked as his partner.
Natsuki, you idiot!
I had decided to give you my virginity.
You're still out there
doing it with other girls.
Love each other my ass.
You're such a liar!
Natsuki, you idiot!
- Give me the ball.
- I want to play too.
This is great.
It seems that she was at it again:
Rumors there was a warrior around.
I heard about it, too.
This time there were two, red and blue.
Red and blue?
The blue one, I heard,
is strong and beautiful on top of being cool.
Bullshit!
I want to see them some time.
Mafuyu, you don't remember
anything about yesterday?
Yesterday?
In the principal's office yesterday.
Principal's office? What are you
talking about, Chihaya?
Natsuki erased her memory of yesterday.
Come on, Chihaya!
And what is it?
Are you still angry?
Maybe I am.
Anyway, I feel a Seed.
I'm not transforming anymore!
What're you saying?
I'm going to investigate it,
so if anything's up...
I'm call you with my heart!
Call me with your heart?
Those who love each other
should be able to hear each other's hearts.
All right, I'm going now!
Those who love each other...
What happened?
My, this isn't good.
Tamura!
What's wrong?
Tamura! Tamura!
Hang in there, Tamura!
I felt the presence of the Seed
somewhere around here.
That girl.
I'm sorry to scare you.
I need to ask you something.
I know. You're Chihaya's cousin.
What are you doing here?
I'm Emi Kojima.
Emi, is it? That's a good name.
Emi, you were at the principal's
office yesterday, weren't you?
What were you there for?
Principal's office? I didn't go there.
That can't be.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry, I...
really don't know.
Don't know?
The trace of the Seed is gone.
Miss Taeko isn't here yet.
You guys go back to class.
I'll watch over him.
Miyuri, you want to be alone
with Tamura, don't you?
Come to think of it,
you've always looked up to Tamura.
That's not it! He needs someone to watch.
Let's leave these two
young ones to themselves.
Come on, quit joking!
Let's leave it to the nurse specialist.
Nurse specialist?
No worries. Undivided attention
and devoted nursing...
they are the perfect medicine for princes.
That's right.
I hope that Miyuri and Tamura
both get along well.
So do I.
Prince...
Please stop it, Tamura.
I like you, Tamura.
But this. Not like this!
It hurts!
No, don't stop now, Tamura!
Make me feel even better. Please!
I'll make you feel better.
If you become one of us,
then I promise I will.
I will, so hurry!
Chihaya...
are you sure it's okay
not for you to go home with Natsuki?
He could rot and die, for all I care!
Natsuki, you liar!
I don't hear anything!
Lovers can hear each other's hearts my ass!
Chihaya?
My ride has arrived,
so I must be going. See you later.
I'll see you tomorrow, Sayaka!
Goodbye, Chihaya.
Bye-bye.
Now, then.
Chihaya.
Is it okay for us to stop
by Angel Kiss now?
That would happen to be a date?
That was a bit nosy of me
to ask something like that!
Man, why did Chihaya go home
by herself without me?
Emi?
Natsuki.
What's wrong?
Natsuki, I'm scared, I'm frightened!
What's going on?
This is the first time Angel Kiss's
been full at this time of day!
Chihaya! How are you?
You came home at the right time!
It got crowded all of a sudden,
and we're just so busy!
Come on and help us.
Where's Mama?
She said that she's going to the National
Family Restaurant Association meeting...
and won't be back until nightfall.
I got it. I'll go change, then.
Hey, Sai, Miyuri's on her first date,
so take care of them!
Okay!
Magical Kanan!
I can leave that on!
Okay!
Perfect!
Time to head back to Angel Kiss!
Tomoe! Sai! Ayumi!
Miyuri!
Tamura, you too?
Don't worry, they'll all feel
good soon enough.
I can't remember anything.
Another me is doing
something I don't know.
I'm losing my own self.
Emi.
Miyuri, that isn't...
Miyuri, stop it!
Please!
No! Stop it!
No! Not that!
Mayumi...
I'll make it feel all better.
No stop it help me.
Please help.
Help me! Natsuki!
Chihaya.
Natsuki?
Emi, I'm sorry, I have to go...
I'm sorry!
Wait, Natsuki, please!
That voice was definitely Chihaya's.
That was Chihaya's voice.
Chihaya's in danger!
Chihaya!
No!
No, stop! Help me, Natsuki.
Chihaya!
Natsuki?
Natsuki!
Let go of Chihaya!
What was that?
Yes! More! Harder!
Yeah! Deeper! Fuck me deeper!
More! Harder! Harder!
It's out of control.
They're all affected by the Seeds.
That's right.
Emi!
I had everyone become my friend.
No way.
I'll make you our friends as well.
Miyuri!
Miyuri, you can't!
Stop it!
What?
Really, you're so careless.
Cerulean Blue Eco.
No you don't!
Look out!
Hazuna!
Master Hazuna!
Get them!
Damn it!
No!
Cerulean Blue! Damn it, let go!
No, stop it!
Sayaka?
Sayaka's Hazuna's partner?
Humans are so weak.
What?
Take a good look at those who have
lost themselves in ecstasy!
The Seeds stimulate human emotion.
You give them an inch of ecstasy,
and this is what they become.
That is what humans are. Truly.
Chihaya!
See the power of the Seeds?
She is already a slave of ecstasy.
Chihaya.
I am your dear opponent, Natsuki.
You seem really happy again.
Stop it.
Chihaya.
Don't worry.
Your partner is feeling better by the minute.
Chihaya.
Natsuki.
Unforgivable!
I'm not going to forgive you!
Natsuki, transformation!
Yeah!
No way! She beat the powers of the Seed?
The flame of truth, hope, and dreams!
Magical Angel, Carmine!
Carmine!
Eco! Shower!
Curse you!
Septem! You stepped on the feelings
of Miyuri toward Tamura.
You played with everyone's hearts!
I will never!
Ever!
Forgive you!
I'm home.
My.
Everyone's napping together?
Did you really hear my voice?
- Yeah.
- I heard it too.
Your voice.
I guess people who love each
other can hear their hearts.
I've decided to do it.
Sex.
I want to become stronger.
So that I can protect everyone
and their feelings.
If our relationship grows deeper,
Carmine will be stronger too.
Well, yeah, but...
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy.
I'm happy, but...
It's like I'm forcing you out
of duty to do so.
I figured it out!
When you came to save me, I was so happy.
I figured out that I love you.
Chihaya.
Natsuki, give me your power.
And look at only me.
Natsuki, I'm so embarrassed.
Natsuki!
I can't...
I can't wait any longer.
Carmine is fine, now.
Let's go.
Yes, Master Hazuna.
It's not over yet.
True.
It has only begun.
Isn't that right?
Master Bergamot.
Natsuki.
Chihaya.
God, you made me transform! You idiot!
You're the one who kissed me!
No, you did!
No, it was you!
It was in such a good mood.
Stupid! Stupid! Natsuki!
So what're going to do now?
Well, let's see...
Let's do it again!