Ah, oh well!
Please get out of the way!
Watch out!
Hey, are you all right?
I'm so sorry.
The parfait!
Phew, that was close!
I caught the parfait... Your chest! Your chest!
It's showing! It's showing!
No!
Thanks for today...
I'm Nami Koishikawa.
Umm...
I'm Chisato Yamane. I just started today.
Nice to meet you.
I see. I just started here recently, too.
I really liked their uniforms.
And the manager is really nice.
WOMEN'S LOCKER ROOM
Really? That wasn't the impression I got.
Really?
Taking out the trash?
Don't worry about it. I'll
take it out when I leave.
See you later!
Oh my god!
Wake up! Are you all right?
I can't anymore...
Hold on. I'll call for some help...
Take this...
Take my place... Please...
What is this?
Come to think of it... She gave
me this weird-looking thing, but...
I wonder what it is? It kind
of looks like an eyeball...
A... A pervert!
N... No...
No...
No. Stop.
No... no... Please stop...
C... Cosplay?
What the... An exhibitionist?
She's so sexy!
N... No...
No... No...
No... No... No!
What's going on!
Y... Yes...
N... Nami!
Nami! What are you thinking,
coming home dressed like that?!
I don't believe it...
I ended up cumming
because of my little sister...
Listen Katsuo!
I can explain...
I won't allow it!
You will absolutely not take
part in that kind of thing!
I'm going out.
What do you want me to do...?
So much happened today. I'm just exhausted.
What am I going to do?
Katsuo's not home yet...
I better answer it though.
Yes? Who is it?
It's Mr. Sasao.
Mr. Sasao... my... manager?
Coming!
I can't open the door looking like this...
Good evening...
I'm coming in.
Is... Is there something you wanted?
It's so late...
Yes, there's something I wanted to give you.
It's your new uniform.
Your current one doesn't fit, right?
Yes... But did you come all the
way here just to give this to me?
Please try it on.
R... Right now?
Yes. I had it made especially for you.
O... Okay...
Then... Please excuse me...
What the... No...! You can see everything!
How does it fit?
Very nice... Do you like it?
M-Mr. Sasao... This is...
I designed it just for you!
Why?
What are you doing?
That smell... You smell so good.
It's simply irresistible.
Please stop.
Mr. Sasao, this is sexual harassment!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
A... monster?
That's not a nice thing to say.
I'm not a monster.
I'm a Sex Demon.
A Sex Demon?
Yes, that's right.
What?
What the...
You better try harder or else
I'll be able to see your nipples.
No... No...
Don't look at me!
You definitely deserve the Eye of Lust.
Such nice breast... They're so jiggly...
Oh yes, I was telling you about Sex Demons.
Our favorite treat is the
cum of young women.
You really don't know anything, do you?
How fortunate for me.
You're a virgin. I could just eat
you up! Poke. Poke. Poke...
Guess I'll just help myself.
I've had enough! Why... Why?
First at my job and then
perverts on the train...
Why do all these perverted
things keep happening to me?
It all started when she gave me
that weird-looking eyeball thing.
Well of course!
That's because the Eye of Lust
is elevating your pheromones...
...and I can smell them all around you.
The Eye of Lust?
You use it to lure demons to you...
I don't know what you're talking about!
No! I don't need it, so...!
That won't work.
As long as you don't really want to give it up,
no one else can take the Eye of Lust.
Now that's more like it!
The cum from a Hunter is the finest there is.
A Hunter?
Yes, you hunt down and destroy us.
B... But...
Yeah, just go ahead and try.
Come on.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
No! Katsuo help!
Katsuo!
You! What do you think
you're doing to my sister!
Why you...
Who the hell are you?!
You need to...
...stay out of this!
Katsuo!
This spot isn't exactly relaxing...
Let's find somewhere quieter...
Stay away!
Tsk... Tsk... Leaving without me...
N... Nami!
That's...
Nami!
Is something wrong?
You're...?
I'm Nami's friend. Where is she?
She was attacked by some
strange looking guy and...
I see...
Damn it! What's going on?!
I understand!
No! Stop following me!
You say such cute things... So
sweet... You're so adorable...
You've caused me enough trouble... Now...
it's time to get started...
Let's fuck!
No!
How do you like that?
No...
N... No!
No! Stop...
No... No... Stop!
No...
Nami!
Chisato?
Well, well...
Hello, Chisato...
I knew it! You're a high ranking demon!
I was hoping to savor you later, but...
...so much for that idea.
Electric Wave!
Oh no! A barrier portal!
Chisato...
She smells so good...
Hey... She's a Hunter.
Are you serious?
Fine... You guys can have her.
Oh? Nice...
I got the best position. Lucky me!
I can hear... Chisato screaming...
What am I...
What am I supposed to do...
I'm going to be reborn
as a high ranking demon!
That was awesome!
I'm next! My turn!
Come on! Hurry it up!
She's still flowing! This Hunter's
pussy juice just keeps coming out.
Suck, suck and suck away!
I'll fuck you all day long!
Plug all her holes!
Use your mouth!
Chisato...
Chisato... I have to save Chisato...
W... What the...
Chisato.
I won't let you interfere!
Take that!
You piece of shit!
You got what you deserved!
Th... these guys are... amazing...
Who are you guys?
Nami.
Stay away or I'll kill this little bitch!
Damn it! I wasn't planning on
being surrounded by Hunters!
She'll die along with me!
Nami!
Damn it! There's nothing we can do!
I have to... I have to do something!
Die!
What?
Please! Transform!
Nami!
That was amazing! You were so cool, Nami!
Pretty impressive.
You're pretty good.
N... Nami!
Nami!
K... Katsuo!
Katsuo!
Katsu...
Huh?
Katsuo! Katsuo!
Nami...
Those who hold the Eye of Lust are
duty-bound to destroy the demons.
But...
You accepted the Eye.
Don't you think you should fulfill your duty?
You can definitely do it!
I look forward to working with you!
I said no! Absolutely not!
My little sister is not going to be
joining a cosplay group! Absolutely not!
I am absolutely opposed!
I... don't hate cosplay. I'm really
rather fond of it. I even love it!
But that's not the point!
What the hell am I saying?
I didn't know you liked cosplay Katsuo!
But that's not the point!
What the hell am I saying?
I didn't know you liked cosplay Katsuo!