Super Sexy Android Pinky
Let's go. You know where to meet right?
Yes!
Pinky, the spy android.
A gift from the Japanese industry.
They sure made a bombshell.
Yeah, she's all that and a bag of chips!
Huh? What?
No!
Ahh, what the hell?
Ahh!
Shit, this secretary. She knows that I'm checking her out.
Shit!
Ah, this...
Um, toys again?
Fuck,
I want to fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Wow, I feel something big going up in me...
Yes, I don't care whose it is, just give me a big one!
You don't care who?
Ah, fuck me more!
Somebody, just fuck me!
Cum inside!
I want to cum inside!
Tadokoro Kenichi. This one's a horrible
worker, but he's cute, so he's the one I
sometimes fantasize about when I masturbate.
How stupid,
he's a conservative fool.
Ah, I can't be doing this because I'm going into overtime.
This is a shitload of work. Damn!
That secretary, she must be criticizing me and talking trash. Shit!
No, I can't do this now. I'll go home and come back tomorrow.
I couldn't finish again today.
At this pace, I'll have overtime tomorrow, and the day after.
In the worst case, even on the weekend.
Hey! Tadokoro, you didn't do a damn thing!
Ah, the same old jeering from the chief.
How depressing.
Damn, what a hot body!
He he, it's dangerous walking in the streets at night.
Ahh, no, no. Why do I always think pervertedly?
I just jerked off right now too.
I have to work!
Work, work, focus on work!
Huh? Wait a minute.
Ahhhh!
What the hell is this?
A camcorder?
Where is the cameraman?
Fuck, what's happening?
No, if this isn't a video,
this might be the outdoor stripper that I've dreamed of!
But damn, she's cute.
And look at her body.
Wow, but look at her.
She's looking this way,
but with no expression.
Did she cum already?
Aha, Kenichi!
Aren't you cold?
No, I'm fine.
Even if you're naked?
Nope.
Um, why do you know my name?
I read your business card with my x-ray vision.
Huh? She's got to be nuts.
Which means it should be easier to get some of that ass.
She's beautiful. I can't let this one go.
Hey, you, would you like to come to my house?
Huh?
Umm, it's kind of a simple question.
Yes?
Why are you naked?
I've been like this since the time I was created. It's the most natural for me.
Oh, man, she's really psycho.
That means I can do whatever I want with her.
Maybe I can get away with some bondage.
Fuck her over and over like three times a night.
No, I can fuck at least five times.
I'll make her my sex slave. Yup, she'll be my bitch.
She'll listen to whatever I say.
Yeah, lick all over. And you will be the sex slave that can't survive without me...
What do you mean?
No, I meant that you're like an idol. It's nothing.
Ha ha, yeah, aren't you hungry?
I'll make you something.
I, I'll do it.
No, sit down, Kenichi.
Wait and be a good boy.
Okay.
Do your best.
Thanks for waiting!
Hurry, hurry, Kenichi.
What was I looking at?
There's plenty to eat, Kenichi.
I'm digging in.
It's a cutting board!
Let's get some sleep soon.
Yes.
Okay, Kenichi, move down a little.
I can't stand it. I'm moving in!
Huh? Oh my, are you really...
Umm...
Already jumping into this...
Ah, I'm cumming too fast...
Ah, but this is too good to be true.
Umm, now it's my turn.
No, no you can't. I can't do it this soon.
Don't worry. Just stay relaxed, Kenichi.
No, I can't...
Does it feel good, Kenichi?
Feel good? Kenichi, how is it?
Ahh, I feel like melting. Oh, look at her tits.
Yeah, these are some really nice titties!
What is your name?
My name is Pinky.
I see Pinky.
Kiss me.
I'm cumming, cumming...!
Ah, no more. I want to get down and dirty.
Huh, what? What's wrong?
Hey, It's so hot right here. Ah, it's amazing. Look at me.
Ahh...
Hey Kenichi, hey, is Pinky a pervert?
Hey Kenichi, ahh...
Ahh, fuck me, please fuck me with your hot one.
Ohh, this is perfect. The perfect girl too.
This bitch is like really horny.
The Japanese beauty changes ferociously at night.
Ah, excellent, excellent.
Ha ha ha ha...
It feels so good! Yes, yes...
More Kenichi, talk to me dirty!
No, more, more...
Idiot!
What's this? You haven't done jack shit, huh?
Huh, Tadokoro? Do you want to work overtime everyday?
No, that's a negative. Um, I'll work hard today.
Our accounting period is coming up soon.
You're a slacker.
Don't we have somebody better in this department?
He he, I knew this was going to happen, but today Kenichi's a little different.
Hmm, I can probably finish this by today.
Since Kenichi has his sweet lover Pinky.
Kenichi, Kenichi, wake up!
Kenichi.
Good morning.
Ah, Pinky.
It wasn't a dream!
This time, I made coffee with eggs and ham.
Wow, looks great. But did we have ham?
I went to the grocery store to shop.
I see. Huh?
Then, the workers were really surprised.
Does Pinky look that attractive?
May I have this?
Ahh, no Pinky. You can't walk around like that outside.
Really, I can't?
I don't want to let other fools check her out.
Umm, do I have anything?
Nope, not this one.
How's this?
Cute sheets. Yeah, yeah, good.
Then, I'll be leaving.
Work hard today.
I'll cook up a great meal and wait for you.
Yeah.
I changed. I was able to change my life because of her.
Ha ha ha ha...
What are you grinning for, dear?
Oh, um, nothing. It's nothing to do with you.
Oh really? I bet you were remembering someone's body.
Ha ha, no joke. I am not interested in old hags. You're so funny.
What! Grr...
You'll get more wrinkles if you get angry.
But, you'll still fit in with those old farts.
Sorry, but I need to get back to work.
Could you be on your way now?
Ha ha ha... It's so hard being a pimp. Ha ha ha!
How stupid!
Well now...
Arg...!
Ha ha ha... I'll come home on time, so I can do Pinky and snuggle with her.
Ha ha ha...
Her breasts, her legs, and the butt, plus she has a good personality. Gentle...
Ahh, I'm finished!
Chief, I'm finished!
Ha ha, done with the project!
That's good for you.
Well, ha ha ha, I can come through if I really try. Okay, I'm out of here!
Hey, not so fast.
Take this, please.
What?
You have like 15 hours until morning.
Oh man...
What? Tadokoro?
I can't finish this load by tomorrow!
You have 15 hours until morning, right?
Isn't that enough time for you?
Well, step it up.
Mmmmm... Fuck!
Oh Pinky? It's me, Kenichi.
Yea, I can't make it. I don't think I'll be able to come home.
I've got a ton of work that they just threw at me.
So you're troubled, Kenichi.
Yeah, it's pretty rough. Wah, I want to go home, Pinky!
If Kenichi's in trouble, Pinky will come to help you.
Ha, ha, ha, I appreciate your sympathy, but even if you do come, it doesn't matter.
Don't worry, don't worry. Bye
Huh? Hey, Pinky?
Kenichi, don't worry anymore!
Oh, she hung up. But damn, Pinky's really cute.
She said she'll help me out. Ha, ha, ha...
Fuck, I have to do this. Huh?
What?
It's all right, Kenichi.
Uh, umm, Pinky?
Yes, yes. Just have a rest, Kenichi.
Hey, hey, how did you come here? Hey, hey.
What's this?
Ha, ha, ha, this is an impossibility for you.
It's advanced accounting software.
I'm balancing for next year, and it's a very tedious job.
Oh, the small thing right there is called a mouse.
I made you lunch so will you have some?
Ha, ha, ha, all right, all right, I'll have it.
Wow, looks so good! Excellent!
It's so good, Pinky! You really helped me just by bringing this!
I'm finished, Kenichi.
Ahh, ha, ha, ha... A great help, Pinky.
Now let me see... Huh?
Wow, it's all finished.
Wow, Pinky. You're amazing.
Now it's okay to go home, Kenichi?
Yup, it's all right. Pinky, you're the greatest.
Ah, no. Pinky can't do it...
Please, Kenichi. I just want to lick.
Ah, Kenichi, you're tasty.
Ahh, I've been wanting this, Kenichi.
Pinky.
Kenichi, you're good, good...
So tasty, Kenichi.
Pinky, I can't hang anymore...
Ahh, me too...
From this point on, my life had changed dramatically.
The boss has been bringing in new work everyday so they're putting the heat on me.
But no matter how much they throw at me, it's the same.
Okay, finished.
Pinky is excellent at getting the jobs done quickly.
Not only that, but she started negotiating contracts that deal with company financing.
Chief Takada, isn't this what you wrote?
Yes. One of our employees stumbled upon this idea.
Whatever, just bring him to me.
however...
Listen, this is the request of our president.
Whoever came up with this brilliant idea should be in the finance department.
What?
Ah, Mr. Takada. Finish those files by tomorrow morning.
Manager Tadokoro, that is impossible.
What are you saying? You still have 15 more hours until the next morning.
Ha, ha, ha, well, just do your best. Ha, ha, ha...
Damn it!
Manager Tadokoro.
Well, well, isn't this the old secretary?
Well, you sure talk rude.
And, anything else?
Tadokoro Kenichi. I knew you would come through.
Oh, that is something to be proud of, but are you trying to flatter me?
How rude! I brought you a present for your promotion.
Hmm, what's that?
It's me.
Well, I'll be going now, since Pinky's waiting for me.
Good bye, manager. Keep up the good work.
I made it.
Whoa?
No! Don't look!
No!
My life is on a roll!
Pinky, I'm home!
Welcome back!
Kenichi, you're back!
Yes, yes.
Hey, hey, I told you not to be nude.
It's because we're inside the house.
You...
Perverted slut!
Don't look at her! Don't look at her!
Ahh, sorry.