We'd been broken, but
time wasn't on our side...
ISHIKI FAMILY
Wake - June 17 (6:00 PM)
Funeral - June 18 (2:00 PM)
FAMILY IN MOURNING
The funeral...
That's when it all began.
No, it may have begun
even before then.
Our destiny may have
been decided before that.
Our freedom... To come and
go, to choose what to do...
Our will...
When that traffic accident
took our parents from us.
...we lost all of that.
This is your destiny now.
We were prisoners of a secret
organization and being trained.
We were both to be sold to a client...
...to become sex slaves.
Once we were "first-class women"...
...our client will make sure
we don't live in poverty.
This is the only life
we have to live now.
We have no other
options open to us.
If I can't do this, I'll be killed.
Leaving my sister alone.
Leaving me sister alone...
Sis...
This can't be...
This is reality.
Slave Sisters
(PART TWO)
My sister had learned of the
situation a little before I was told.
Urination...
Enemas...
Anal sex...
Vibrators...
Humiliation games...
Soft S&M...
Masturbation with aphrodisiacs...
Public sex...
Is this really...
Really... Really my sister?
This isn't the sister I know!
We once lived a normal life.
We had a house.
We had a home.
We had a family.
I can't say we were rich...
...but we weren't
desperately poor, either.
We were brought up like
so many other people.
She's devoted her mind, her
very being, to getting us money.
She's worked harder than I ever could.
To be kind to people.
She never let it show on her face...
...no matter how sad she
was or how bad things got.
She kept her wounds hidden inside.
She cries only when she's alone.
My gentle sister is
trying so hard for me...
So hard...
Why did this happen?!
What are we both doing?!
I just want a normal life!
To live normally!
To find love normally!
To do normal things!
That man...
Yes, ever since we
first met that man...
Yeah! If we'd never met him...
...we'd both be living normal lives now!
Why did he have to show up?!
Shunji Iwashiro...
Shunji...
Why? Why?!
Why did it have to be Shunji?
I thought he was going to be...
...a nice, handsome big brother for me.
I was genuinely looking
forward to Sis marrying him!
I was ready to give
that man everything.
Wow, you don't say.
You're a funny girl,
you know that?
You bet!
And so cute and innocent, too.
Oh, you... You think so?
How... How do you feel
about girls like that, Shunji?
Hmm... Let's see...
They tend to be cheerful,
obedient, honest with themselves.
...and maybe a little selfish...
...but they're usually dedicated
and really very strong.
I like girls like that.
Girls like you, Miku.
R... Really?
I'm not like that at all!
Anyway, it's late. Better
go back to my room now.
G'night.
What's wrong?
I'd better go.
Yukari's waiting for me in our room.
I... I'm sorry!
This wasn't... I just... I mean...!
You're... You're engaged
to my sister, so...
Good night.
I loved you!
When I learned everything...
I accepted Shunji...
...and our destiny...
I thought I was prepared for it...
...but I couldn't stop crying.
Even though you'd decided to
give your virginity to Shunji...
Okay, yeah, I did think that, but...!
You wanted Shunji to do it to you.
No! Not like that!
But it doesn't change
anything, does it?
You're wrong! I did it for my sister!
Liar.
It was what you wanted whether
your sister was involved or not.
No! No!
You wished your sister
wasn't there to interfere.
I never thought that!
Even though you'd gladly
spread your legs for Shunji now.
It's not true! It's not!
You won't just do this for training.
You'll think about Shunji
and play with yourself...
Stop it! Don't say that!
It's fitting behavior for
a little slut like you.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Sis, it's not true! It's not!
It's not true!
Goodbye.
So, you're awake.
What's wrong? Tired?
Was I... asleep?
You were waiting
for me to wake up?
I figured it was time to take a break.
If you're tired, we can call it a night.
Is that all right?
Your training is going fairly well.
It's important for
you to get your rest.
You're so nice...
Yum...
I'm fine. A little nap and
I'm ready for anything.
TRAINING - DAY 25
Yes! Yes...!
Shunji!
I'm going to...!
It feels so good!
I love Shunji.
And I love my sister.
This may not be the
destiny I wanted...
How this crazy situation will turn out...
...I don't really know.
But no matter how hard or
sad this new life is for me...
...I think there are
small joys to be found.
And so, for now, I'll try my best...
...and try to live as best I can.
Slave Sisters
(PART TWO)
What is it?
I happened to
overhear a rumor.
Oh...?
That, lately, some of
our trained women...
...are being returned to us...
...for 20 to 30 percent
of their original price.
Yes. It's in response to requests
from some of our better clients.
Why?
I thought returns were
prohibited in our contracts.
If I don't take them
back at low prices...
...our clients will sell them cheaply
to amateurs and collectors.
That would send our
market value into a tailspin.
No, that's not what I meant.
Why would our clients want to
return such first-class women?
Because people have desires.
No matter how fine
a woman may be.
...after a few years they
seem to want a new one.
A different type than
what they have now.
Something newer and better.
Well, you know how it is.
My God. These aren't
things we're talking about.
Yes, they are.
As a trainer, you see
them as individual people.
To our clients,
they are merely...
...things which exist
to fulfill their desires.
Don't be upset.
All the returned women are
collected by our organization.
The foreign market for
them has expanded lately.
A the market price rises,
we'll still make a profit.
The women you turn out
are highly sought after.
They fly off the shelves, so to speak.
It won't affect you at
this point. Don't worry.
In the end, even if I make
them as good as they can be.
...they still won't be able to
find any happiness, will they?
What the hell am I doing?
TRAINING - DAY 30
Hey, Shunji...
Or should I call you Shun-chan?
I remember when we were kids...
Your family moved into
the condo next door to us.
...and we used to play
together all the time.
I think we used to talk all the time.
Don't you remember?
It was only for a year.
And then your family moved again.
I remember it so well.
I never thought we'd
meet again like this...
Stop it!
Don't think about it! And also...
Never call me Shun-chan
again! Is that clear?!
Yes, sir.
Hey, Shunji...
So, you once knew
the older sister, huh?
I'd forgotten, but
it looks like I did.
Maybe she's hallucinating.
That girl's snapped.
We still don't know that.
I'm impressed, Mr. Iwashiro.
Even if she's returned, she'll
still sell for a good price.
She may be nuts, but
she's a tiger in bed...
...although she goes
at it a little too hard.
She's just a nymphomaniac now, right?
Although inside her head... Well...
I wonder how well a client will
treat a brain-damaged woman.
Right, Mr. Iwashiro?
TRAINING - DAY 45
Hey, what's happening with my sister?
You're worried about her?
Have you and she been
doing it day after day?
Yeah. Because this is my job.
You'll be with Yukari again soon.
You two are going to
try some lesbian sex.
And then menage a trois.
But... I can't...!
You've learned all
sorts of techniques.
Use them on your
sister as best you can.
You said you would do
your best, like her, right?
Can my sister really...?
Don't worry. Yukari said she'd
be happy to do it with you.
I don't know how to do lesbian sex.
Just do what you want.
What you want to do and
what makes you feel good.
And then do to your partner the
things that feel good to you.
Do this to make both you
and your sister feel good.
You must always keep your
partner's feelings in mind.
Just do it as you do it with me.
Do that, and your body
will move naturally.
Sis...
Shunji...
You know what?
I've been having this dream
since we started the training.
Stretching out all around me...
...are the sands of a huge desert.
I'm walking through it, all alone...
Day after day after day...
...I keep on walking, as
though wandering and lost.
My mind and body changing...
Becoming worn down
to be another person.
And then a voice cries
out from somewhere.
It's you and I, doing it.
At first, I was embarrassed and scared.
I just wanted to run away.
But something would hold
me back before I could run.
Day after day after
day, I had this dream.
But as the days passed,
as I kept watching...
...I saw the me in the
dream looked so happy.
How she felt so good
doing it with you.
And as I watched, I... I...
I was getting off on
watching us have sex.
It makes me laugh for some reason.
I must be losing my mind.
You see, me playing with
myself isn't enough.
I go to the me that's having
sex with you in my dream.
...and kill her.
And then...
...in the dream, you and I...
...just fuck and fuck.
Over and over...
I keep taking you again and again...
Until I wake up.
It's gone on day after day.
I kill myself in the
dream for that reason.
What do you suppose it all means?
That...
...it doesn't matter.
I suppose you're right.
Your training's over for today.
But I... I want more!
I want to do it with you.
I want to feel good.
Don't worry. Just sleep there, Shunji.
I'll do it all by myself.
Yukari...
Menage a trois tomorrow?
It's almost over.
What did you call Mr.
Ishihara about yesterday?
You've seemed strange since then.
It turns out this isn't
my last job after all.
So, it's not so easy to
leave this business, is it?
You'll work and work
for the organization.
Training women forever.
Working for our clients to
make sex slaves for them.
That is your destiny.
And yours.
I'm going to get to
the top at any cost.
Sis...
Miku...
TRAINING - DAY 49
Sis, you've changed.
Have I? You seem to have
been trying hard, too.
Look how that's changed!
Stop! Sis, not so fast...!
Sh- Shunji's watching us!
No! This is wrong!
Sisters shouldn't do this!
Well, Miku? Doesn't it feel good?
Your little pussy tastes so good...
Sis...!
Relax a little more.
What cute little breasts...
What did you just say?!
You can't leave the
organization just yet.
But, you said...
There's still some
interest left to pay off.
N... No... How much longer?!
Oh, you'll pay it off soon.
Don't worry about it.
Yes, sir.
Hmm... You're taking this rather well.
I thought you were desperate
to leave the business.
I've learned over the years
that resistance is futile.
Well, once you've finished
with those sisters...
...you can train me some new girls.
Well?
So good! It feels so good, Sis!
To me, too.
I'm going to...!
Miku...
Now you do me, okay?
Lick me!
What's wrong?
Just lick me gently, like
you do to Shunji's dick.
Do this to make both you
and your sister feel good.
You must always keep your
partner's feelings in mind.
Just do it as you do it with me.
Do that, and your body
will move naturally.
Yes, that's the way, Miku...
Yes! Right there! That feels so good...
Yes!
Hey, Shunji...
I wonder if I'm losing my mind.
If I... If I do lose it...
If I do...
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
No, I guess not.
That's one thing you can't do for me.
Sorry for asking such an odd thing.
Okay, Miku. Here we go.
That big thing won't fit in me!
It'll be fine. Just relax.
I'm going to come!
No... No more...!
We're just getting started!
Shunji, would you...
Go in from the rear.
Shunji, please!
Hurry! Do it, please!
Shunji...
Yes!
Yukari, why don't we...
Why don't we run far away?
Do you love me?
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Do you understand?
No, I don't think I do.
Something in my heart feels warm.
And it feels natural to cry.
What's wrong with me?
Never mind. Never mind...
Let's end this.
Miku...
So, you're awake.
Good morning.
We've been here for three days.
How do you like living here?
A long as you're here, Shunji...
A long as I can love you every
day, from morning till night.
Just that makes me happy.
I see...
We'll always be together from now on.
Yes. I'm glad...
Come to me!
It looks like they're here.
A long as I'm with you...
I'll go anywhere.
And I won't be afraid.
Just stay inside me.
Until the end...
I understand.
Three days...
It took you longer
than I expected.
TRAINING - DAY 56
Yes. Yes. I see.
Understood.
Your sister and Shunji
Iwashiro are dead.
The poor fool...
You're really running
away with the older one?
What's happened to you?
You've fallen in love
with the merchandise?
That's not like you.
I'm just... I'm just
tired of everything.
Someday, you'll
understand, too.
You'll never get away.
What about Miku?
If I take her as well, it'll
cause trouble for you.
Besides, she's still
sane. And she's young.
I'd rather she live a while
longer than take her with us.
There's happiness in life,
even as merchandise?
I have one favor to ask.
Hypnotize her to forget
about Yukari and me.
No need to ask.
I'll erase all feelings...
...that interfere with her duties.
It's better if she forgets.
Just leave the message
to live as best she can.
What's wrong?
You're stopping!
I don't have a sister...
...and I've never heard of
anyone named Shunji before.
...but I feel a stab
deep in my heart...
...and feel a little sad.
And... And...
And I'm starting to
cry for some reason.
Why is that?
Some lingering memories...?
No matter. I have four more days.
No need to rush your training.
What's wrong with you?!
Start sucking!
Y... Yes, sir.