If we don't do something,
how far will we fall?
ISHIKI FAMILY
Wake - June 17 (6:00 PM)
Funeral - June 18 (2:00 PM)
Funeral 2:00 PM to 4:00 PM
FAMILY IN MOURNING
Sis...
Why didn't any of
our relatives come?
It'll just be the two
of us from now on...
It'll be okay.
So don't cry.
So, what's Mr. Iwashiro like?
Sis...?
Don't worry. You'll be able
to go to school from there.
Well, he's your boyfriend.
He's nice, right?
So, how come you've never
mentioned your fiancйe before?
I want to meet him soon...
Here.
We'll be living here from now on.
Come on, let's go in.
Sis...?
Slave Sisters
(PART ONE)
Thanks for dealing with the family,
the police, and the hospital.
I'm about to commence training.
Right on schedule. They should
be ready in two months.
Yes, sir.
Carry on. You may use whatever
means you deem necessary.
However, the client has
made certain requests.
They are not to be
addicted to any drugs.
And he wants their
skin to be unmarked.
Yes, sir. I'll keep it in mind.
This is Takamura, whom I
mentioned to you before.
Like you, he's an expert
in psychophysiology.
Teach him everything you know.
Yes, sir.
So, this is your last job, huh?
It's a real shame when someone
as talented as you quits.
I'll have to train someone to
take your place as soon as I can.
Forgive me, sir.
No one will ever be as
good as you, though...
Train Takamura well.
TRAINING - DAY 1
Excuse us!
Hi! What kept you guys?
It... It's been a while, Iwashiro...
Go on, introduce yourself!
H... How do you do?
Oh, never mind the
introductions. Come on in!
R... Right...
You, too, Miku!
Sure! It's a pleasure!
The living room's down the hall.
'Kay!
Whoa! You've got this huge
condo all to yourself?!
I lived with my family
up 'till two years ago.
They're living overseas now.
Huh? Overseas?
Yeah.
We expanded the business and
opened up a branch in L.A.
They live there now.
L... L... Los Angeles?!
Ooh...! That totally kicks ass!
Miku, that's not a very
lady-like thing to say!
Forget it.
Once we're married, we'll
all be family, anyway.
So, when's the ceremony?!
Do you have the license yet?
Well...
Miku!
Huh? Oh... Sorry...
Sorry. You're still in your
mourning period, aren't you?
And here I was, talking
about my parents...
It isn't right, especially since
you're still in mourning.
No, I should be the one
making apologies here.
I'm still a little numb from everything...
Aren't you sad, Miku?
I cried for two weeks straight.
I guess I wore myself out.
Oh, I have a roommate.
Let me call him so
I can introduce you.
Huh? What do you mean?
He was my junior in college.
He's shy and can be
pretty weird at times...
...but he's pretty harmless.
I'm sorry about what I said.
I just got excited all of a sudden.
It's all right.
You're so cheerful that you
always get forgiven for stuff.
What's that supposed to mean?!
If we used drugs, we could
put them into a trance state...
...and speed up the
brainwashing greatly.
That girl Miku will be easy to break.
What we most prefer
for this merchandise...
...are people who can
manipulate their emotions.
Only amateurs try to force post-
hypnotic suggestion on them.
Suggestion only works
on their subconscious.
Using drugs to speed up the process...
...can cripple a person with status
nervosus or memory disfunction.
Sometimes it ends in suicide.
You have to take them in by stages.
Otherwise you risk
destroying their minds.
And your method, Mr. Iwashiro?
I use words.
Words?
Words reach the conscious
and the sub-conscious.
I also use thorough
training of the body.
The strongest thing I'll
use is an aphrodesiac.
So, with time, care, and a
few obscene practices...
...you break their wills and
make perfect little puppets.
The client's going to want
you for the next job.
Come out so they can at
least see you and say hello.
Is that an order?
All right. I'll be out in a minute.
Nice room.
Shunji said it used to
be his little sister's.
I see...
How about your room, Sis?
Well, Iwashiro and I will be...
Whoa! You'll be sleeping together?!
Ooh! I am, like,
so-o-o jealous of you!
Sis, are you happy now?
Well, yeah...
Huh? You don't seem happy.
I'm happy. Very happy.
I'm so jealous you
found such a great guy.
He's cool and nice and
seems really honest.
He's great at conversation...
...and he is so-o-o sexy, too!
I wish I had a boyfriend like Shunji...
If he wasn't your boyfriend,
I'd go after him in a second!
Uh, that doesn't mean I have
a crush on him or anything!
I was just saying he's
a really cool guy, and...
Sis? Sis?
Uh, yeah! You're right!
So, are you going
to school tomorrow?
Yeah.
I'd better get back to my room.
You'll have to stop sleeping
in your underwear, you know.
I hear you.
We're living with two
guys now, after all.
I wouldn't want to
tempt your boyfriend!
Better get to sleep. Good night.
Nighty-night!
Excuse me.
Take off your clothes.
Yes, sir...
Don't be so serious.
Today's your first day.
First, I want to
gauge your technique.
For now, treat me
as you would a lover.
Yes, sir...
I... I'm sorry! I just
wasn't expecting that!
You were doing quite well
before I surprised you.
Juices flowing, I see.
This is how you kiss.
Your sensitivity is good.
Just a kiss can make a girl wet.
Remember that.
Yes, sir...
Never blown somebody before?
Just once before.
Your tongue movement is pretty good...
...but you don't know the
right places to go after.
Well, I can teach you that, of course.
Yes, sir...
Okay, time for penetration.
Get on top of me,
with your hips apart.
Yes, sir...
Stop that.
Listen, it's not enough to
just pump up and down.
Use your hips!
Y... Yes, sir.
All right, that's enough for today.
By the way, have you ever
had an orgasm before?
Uh, n... no... Never.
Your sexual technique is business-like.
You sort of get into it...
...but you've yet to understand
how to really feel it.
If the woman doesn't throw
herself completely into it...
...the man loses his excitement.
That's vital to know. I'll
make you remember it.
Hmm... It has a lovely color.
No! S- Stop it...!
Remember this feeling.
How did you like your first time?
You want more, don't you?
You must be tired
after four orgasms.
What I showed you
tonight was ordinary sex.
Tomorrow, your training begins in full.
You'll learn all that it
takes to please a man.
This is the only life
you two can live now.
You'll have to try your best
for the next two months...
...work together, and then
you'll be sold together.
You're crying?
Will you cry at every training session?
Don't worry.
I'll never cry again. Tonight
will be my last time.
So please... Please...!
Can't you just let me
cry all I want tonight?
Ooh... I have to start going
to school again. Aw, man...
You've had a two-week
vacation, haven't you?
Hang in there.
But you and Shunji will be
leaving for three days, right?
We asked Takamura to take
care of things while we're gone.
Are you sure you'll
be okay by yourself?
I'll be fine! Quit treating me like a kid!
Oh, yeah!
There's a holiday the day
after your business trip.
Why don't you take a
day off and have a date?
Don't worry about me, okay?
All right, I'm off!
See you later.
All right. Let's not refuse
her kind offer, shall we?
We have an extra day. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
TRAINING - DAY 2
You will be living and training
here for the next four days.
Everything you'll need
has been assembled here.
First, you'll be taught every
type of sex play known.
And how to feel them in your body.
First is the bath room.
Disrobe and follow me.
Um...
Before that, I'd like to go to the toilet.
Good timing. It's in the
bath room. Follow me.
Um, where is it?
Right here.
Do it in front of me.
I... I can't...
Yes, sir...
What's wrong?
It won't come out.
I gave you a diuretic this morning.
The truth is you want to
go, but you're holding it in.
Is this part of the training, too?
That and more.
I'm trying to overcome
your natural inhibitions.
There's nothing shameful about
seeing the act of excretion.
Conversely, someone who can
do it while being watched...
...is willing to do almost anything.
The training helps with this.
I'll help.
St- Stop it, please...!
No!
It's coming out!
You're ashamed? But...
Your urine has a stickiness to it.
Good. Feel it more.
And then you'll want to
perform any disgraceful act.
Your body will long to do it!
We're almost finished.
I'll help you feel it fully.
Yes, sir...!
I put 2 liters into you. How does it feel?
It's hard to hold in...!
Is it about to come out?
It... It's coming out!
Hold it in!
Hold it as long as you can,
then release it all at once!
No... I can't...
No...!
You've come around a bit
over these past four days...
...but in order to fully free you
of your existing inhibitions...
...you'll have to endure
these procedures.
What if I can't take it
and nothing changes?
It's all right. Just trust
me and do as I say.
I know you can do this.
Go in.
Yes, sir.
And so my training began,
starting with the bath room.
Then anal sex...
Vibrators...
Humiliation games...
Soft S&M...
Masturbation with aphrodesiacs...
We did it over and over again...
And when the auto-lock
on the door opened...
...I went for a stroll completely naked.
Public sex...
Finally, I went out onto
the busy streets outside...
...with a vibrator shoved inside of me.
Back to the condo, where
my sister awaited us.
Welcome back!
We decided to take
you up on your offer.
No problem! No problem!
Anything happen while we were gone?
Yeah! What's up with the
Takamura guy, anyway?!
He doesn't talk, doesn't say
hi, and you never see him!
He'll occasionally
just stare at me...
...and I get the creepiest feeling!
If he looks at me weird again,
I'm gonna pop him one!
Oh? Well, I hope you
don't really do that.
Oh... Okay...
So, aside from that,
nothing happened, right?
What's wrong?
I'm just a little jealous.
When I'm feeling sad or depressed...
...I'd like to have someone I
love nearby to comfort me.
Ever since Dad died...
...you were so depressed
that I was starting to worry.
But now you look
free and cheerful...
You're happy again!
R... Really? Thank you.
I... I'm a little tired,
so I'll get to bed early.
Good night.
Nighty-night.
Did those four days
free me somehow?
I lie so easily to my
little sister now.
I'm not even sad about my
father's death anymore.
And besides that,
little by little, I'm...
That feels great!
My training was showing me
how good sex could feel!
But was it really just the training
that led me to this as well...?
What's this? You
kept it in all this time?
You didn't say I
could take it out.
And your sister?
Don't worry! She didn't notice it.
All right, that's enough for today. You
must be tired from the last 4 days.
Yes, sir...
Aren't you coming
to bed, Iwashiro?
I have something to attend
to. Go to bed without me.
Um...
Could you just kiss me once?
Are you up to something?
No! I didn't mean it like that!
It's just that your kisses are...
I want to memorize
how good they can feel.
Very well. Your reward for
four days of good work.
Good enough?
Yes... Thank you so much.
That night, for the
first time in my life...
...I pleasured myself completely.
And by force of will,
brought myself to orgasm...
Slave Sisters
(PART ONE)
19 DAYS BEFORE TRAINING
Have you decided yet?
I don't care what happens
to me, but Miku...
Please spare my little
sister! I beg of you!
I think you've misunderstood me.
It's your sister the client wants.
No, please...
You should blame your
parents for this situation.
Your choice is to either
be sold off seperately...
...or be sold together as a set.
If you become skilled to
the client's satisfaction...
...I guarantee you and your
sister won't become destitute.
The choice is yours.
What will you do?
Don't bother going to the police.
Our organization has a long reach.
You'd be eliminated quickly.
So, slavery or death?
Better to be saved along
with your sister, isn't it?
Yes, sir...
If they can be made into
high-quality merchandise,
stable lives will be guaranteed for them.
I believe it's their only hope.
This is my last job... The last one!
After these two, I can...!
TRAINING - DAY 10
Yes, you've improved
greatly. I'm about to cum...
You've gotten used to
the flavor of sperm.
Yes. It tastes good
once you're used to it.
Starting tomorrow, I'm
switching her to someone else...
...and beginning her sister's training.
I see... It seems to be going well.
Tell me, do you recognize this girl?
She's one of your creations.
I've been using her for 5 years now.
I just can't get tired of her!
Make those girls as good as this one!
The client would love that!
You little... I get hard just
hearing her voice!
So, want to talk to
your former student?
No.
TRAINING - DAY 15
Use your strength to
hold it in. Try again.
Yes, sir.
Remember, tightening and
loosening your pussy...
...like it's a living animal
feels great to a man.
Practice it every day.
Yes, sir!
Your pussy's a little rough
inside, but you can use that well.
Learn to control it from the inside
and any man will fall for you.
They'll be your slave.
E... Even a master, like you?
What's...?!
We begin training
your sister tomorrow.
If she sees the photos and
video we're taking now...
You can't...!
What's done is done, and
you have to accept it.
I'm trying my best, so help
your sister try her best as well.
Yes, sir...
Don't get shy on me now.
Get into it the way you always do.
No... Be louder and
give it all you have!
Use the techniques to
enhance your reactions!
Now, what do you want?
Fuck me deep and
make me feel good!
Right...
Well? You like that?
It feels so... good...!
Good, you're using your hips.
Using them feels
good, doesn't it?
Yes, sir...
So good... It feels so good!
I have explained your situation.
Do you understand?
You need to learn to use your body...
...and your sexual techniques
as weapons to survive.
To that purpose, I will train you.
This can't be...
This is reality.
No! Don't touch me! If
you do, I'll kill myself!
A perfectly reasonable
reaction to learning about this.
But if you do that, what
will happen to your sister?
Your sister has thrown
herself fully into this.
Trying her best so that you
wouldn't be left all alone.
Look at that. Your
quiet sister Yukari...
...yelling and enjoying it so
much as she lets me into her.
Even without training,
you'll still be sold.
Then you'll lose your
virginity to a strange man.
You'll be sold over and over,
ravaged by one fiend after another.
Your mind and body will be destroyed...
...and you'll die a miserable death.
No...
Help me with my task.
I can make the two
of you work as one.
Train you to assure you
both a comfortable life.
It's the only way I can help you.
Think it over tonight and see
how you feel in the morning.
A goodnight kiss, like
I gave you yesterday.
Yukari...
Will she be ready in time?
Unlike her sister, Miku is
ruled by her emotions.
Once she's ready for it...
...she'll throw herself
gladly into the training.
So you filled her head with thoughts...
...of her sister and
her beloved "Shunji"?
All for the job.
You use every tool
you can to succeed.
In the end, you have
first-class merchandise.
We sell them to a rich client and
ensure a stable life for them.
There's nothing "stable"
about being a sex slave.
Which is why I train them so well...
...in technique and pleasure.
You talk like your heart
really isn't in this job.
I didn't come into this
profession by choice.
And the only weapons I
can use are my words.
TRAINING - DAY 17
So, how do you like both
holes filled at once?
It feels great!
I'm going to...!
You should lick it clean
before it all soaks in.
Yes, sir...
Miku's training begins today.
We'll knock off here for
now. Go take a shower.
Yes, sir...
If you have anything to
tell her, I'll pass it on.
Tell her "Do your best".
You seem ready to do this.
No, I'm not ready for this.
But I decided I have to accept
this the way my sister has.
Yukari's tried her
best for my sake.
And you've thought
about my well-being, too.
If somebody's gonna take my
virginity, I'd rather it be you!
Very well. Come here.
No! Not there!
Does that feel good?
Y... Yes, it does...
Do you want to feel even better?
Yes.
Hey, what are you doing?
Spread your legs.
Just get them up.
Like this?
The Pink Rotor will
make you feel good.
It sort of tickles!
The vibration is unbelievable, isn't it?
No! Stop it...!
You're getting wetter than
I'd expect a virgin to.
Don't say things like that!
Is it because you've been...
...masturbating every
night, thinking about me?
H... How did you know?
We have cameras to watch you.
Your sister never
played with herself before...
...and yet you did it night after night.
Stop it! Why are you saying that?!
Because I care about you!
To train you and teach
you all the techniques...
...I'm going to do much crueler
and more embarassing things!
You can't let something
like this faze you!
I'm doing this for both
of you! Understand?!
Yes. I'm sorry...
Okay, and here's your
reward for understanding.
What's that?
It... It's hot!
No! Stop it!
Well? Does it feel good?
It feels good! So good!
You came?
Well, there's something that
feels better than a finger.
W... Wait! I'm not ready!
Let me prepare myself! Please, wait!
I covered by penis
with an aphrodesiac.
It'll hurt at first, then you'll feel
the most incredible sensation.
It'll send you straight to heaven.
TO BE CONTINUED