I'm sorry to have asked you out
this late, Mr. Oasa.
No, no, when the Main Family
summons me, time is of no issue.
What can I do for you?
Well.
I'm so hot tonight,
I can't go to sleep.
I wonder why...
Well. That's beyond me...
Miss Kaori...
Whatever you are planning to do
with Aunt Himiko...
...I want to know all the details.
But I'm sure...
...you won't honestly tell me what I
want to know.
I really can't...
So I borrowed the spider
from Akira and...
...played a little trick on you.
Now you will tell me
everything you know.
Do you still have some power left?
You don't know when to quit.
Descent Third King!
Stop it!
No, not there.
No! Stop it!
Well, well, you were
so much trouble.
But you will be very obedient
from now on.
Inma Seiden
So, Moeka, how is Mao doing?
She won't even answer me
when I talk to her.
She is always looking down
during class.
Miss Mao doesn't even show up
to the club these days.
Could it be the Iron Mask's doing?
Ayano, you shouldn't make
ridiculous jokes out of something like this.
Think about it, though.
Strange things have been happening...
...ever since people started talking
about the Iron Mask.
Teachers quit all of the sudden,
girls transfer out to other schools.
A girl named Reiko Koga recently
disappeared from the Academy as well.
I still haven't told you about
how Sena disappeared.
What troublesome girls!
Cutting classes and doing whatever
pleases them.
How is your arm healing, Akira?
I am fine.
But the fact that I could not protect
My Lady is...
Akira! Please make sure not
to act too hastily.
I just hope those girls...
...and their activities
don't interfere with my plans.
I see. A God took Miss Yamamoto.
Then when Sena was kidnapped by
the Iron Mask and disappeared...
...I thought she had transferred to
another school, but...
...if there is someone who hurt
Mao and Sena, I won't forgive him!
I will find out the perpetrator,
on my own, if necessary!
I will help you. I'm worried
about Miss Mao.
Why does Kaori
ignore Himiko's activities?
What would happen to the
world if the calamity increases?
How is the investigation into
Ohtori Academy coming along?
Our usual special assignment
teachers may be not up to this!
On that regard, I have already
sent in my agent, Melanie Cool.
Come on, Kao, come down.
Tell me if something's happened.
We're best friends, aren't we?
We are all waiting for you in the
club. Please come.
I can't even begin to figure out
Minako's whereabouts.
How can I report this to the Main
Temple Headquarters?
Why not take up on Himiko's offer?
For someone like you to want to
investigate Her Highness Himiko.
Who is it?
My name is Takashi Shimura.
I'm here because Her Highness
Himiko demands you.
Come, Militant Chari King!
No!
Mr. Yashagami!
Mao.
What's going on?
Something's wrong.
Stop hiding like a rat
and come out!
Why does Mao always hang out
with nosy people like you?
Wait! Miss Kameyama, do you
know what happened to Mao?
None of your business.
I'm Mao's best friend.
I have the right to know.
Mao is not very stable right now,
so don't bother her, okay?
What's wrong with me worrying
about Mao?
I'll tell you this!
You are free to do whatever you
want, but get involved in this...
...and you might lose your life.
What? Why?
What do you mean by that?
I mean that Miss Hitomi
knows something.
Why don't you just
ask Miss Mao yourself?
Mao doesn't really answer me,
even when I talk to her.
Besides...
Besides?
Well, Mao looks very friendly
with Mr. Yashagami.
Mr. Yashagami is staying with the
Ohtori Main Family, isn't he?
Then it's no wonder she worries
about Mao all the time.
Yeah. That's true.
So, please do your best, Moeka.
I shall talk to Mao again tomorrow.
This is too much for a joke.
It was just like this when we were
attacked the last time.
Whoever it is, we don't have to
go look for him.
Inward Bound Fist!
Come on out, you coward!
Who the hell are you?
Moeka, watch out!
Be careful, this prayer summons...
Whatever comes, I'll fight it!
Outward Bound Fist!
Let go of Moeka!
No! Help me, Mao!
How dare you interfere with us?
I shall take my time tormenting you.
Moeka!
Are you all right?
Miss Ayano, Suzune.
Miss Moeka.
You, juvenile delinquents!
You amateurs are no match
for that one!
Who are you?
Stay away from trouble,
and go on home.
Stop worrying.
Don't call me anymore.
I told you, it's not your fault.
Don't worry.
I have to get up early tomorrow,
so I should go now.
You act like you hate her,
but you worry a lot about Mao.
Either way,
when you were attacked...
...it was I who saved you.
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean by this?
For the School Chairperson to do this...
Saeko, you look nice when you're
trying to act tough.
You could very easily
take over Minako's job.
Minako? You mean Minako
was here, too?
Rikako. Rikako.
My dear Saeko, now that
we've become friends...
...l'll reveal to you my intentions.
Something horrible is going to
happen, isn't it, Bodai?
Aren't you going to help her?
No way. That would spoil
all the fun.
No way. If you repositioned
Mt. Shumi...
...that would turn the Earth's
rotational axis upside down.
I sure will miss you, Saeko.
I might not see you again,
while you have your sanity.
Rikako. Rikako.
No! Open it! Please!
Rikako.
Mao...
I've been looking
all over for you, Mao.
Miss Matsumoto was transferred
to another school!
Just like Miss Yamato was.
Something strange is going on!
What's it got to do with me?
Miss Mao! Miss Ayano and I
are investigating the weird incidents...
...happening around
this Academy.
You will help us, right?
You must have a lot of time
on your hands.
Why don't you work this hard
in your clubs?
Mao, why?
Why have you changed so much?
What happened to the old,
cheerful Mao?
Miss Mao, Miss Moeka
is really worried about you.
Please say something.
We were attacked last night...
...and Moeka was captured
by a monster...
Moeka and a monster?
Sorry. Leave me alone for now.
Miss Mao!
What are the three friends
plotting over here?
Mr. Yashagami.
Miss Ohtori, your sister is waiting
for you in the Student Organization Room.
My sister?
Suzune, I'll see you later, at the club.
Okay.
So, we don't know
who used that God?
I was attacked so suddenly.
All I know is it was a woman.
A woman.
You're lying! How could
Aunt Himiko be...?
It's true. You've been aware of it,
haven't you?
I should have told you
a long time ago.
Hitomi saved my life.
It was too bad
what happened to Sena.
Stop it! I don't want to hear this!
Miss Kaori, please stop. No more.
Mao, it is our duty to respect our
mother, Rikako's will and...
...protect the Ohtori Family.
The Kameyama Family is trying
to take over our family.
There are only two of us left of the
pure bloodline of the Ohtori Family.
Aunt Himiko intends to sacrifice
more Academy students...
...to the Chaki Nan God.
You know what that means, do you?
Good girl. For now,
just follow my instructions.
Suzune is waiting for me.
I'm going to the club.
Miss Mao.
Are you girls still playing this
detective game?
I just want to find out what's
happening at this Academy.
What's happening to my friends
and schoolmates...
Come on over.
Suzune, do you know
what you are involved in?
I knew something was going on.
You knew it,
but you kept it from me.
Talk to Moeka and Miss Ozawa,
and wash your hands of the whole ordeal!
No! I hate it when you act
unilaterally like this!
Suzune!
Suzune. I've been telling
you not to...
What does Miss Kaori intend to do
with My Lady?
I've always known Himiko and
Hitomi would have to be eliminated...
...if they keep on tormenting
My Lady, but now...
...if Miss Kaori is not going to be
there for My Lady...
...I will have to defeat her, too.
Come in.
Miss Toyoda!
What can I do for you?
Are you in love with someone?
What? No, nobody in particular.
What about Mao?
What about her?
My Lady is...
I love you, Mr. Yashagami.
Miss Toyoda, if this is a personal
matter, please come back later.
I appreciate it, but I am busy now.
Please, Mr. Yashagami,
make love to me.
Stop being so irrational.
So you do love Mao, don't you?
It's just I've been watching after
My Lady since she was a child.
Please do not misunderstand.
All right?
Miss Mao does know something.
I will expose the truth,
no matter what.
Who are you?
For Her Highness Himiko's sake,
I will examine your body.
The chairwoman?
No!
Stay away!
No, stop! No!
No, stop it!
So, do you like it?
I'll make you feel even better.
No. Stop it. Stop it!
You shouldn't get so involved
in someone else's business.
It's none of my business
whatever Takashi does.
Good. Just think about the time
I made love to you.
Ouch!
I hope Mao suffers more.
No.
You're so wet now.
Who's saying, "No"?
It feels good.
I love the noises you make.
You can't control yourself,
can you?
I will make this easy for you.
It hurts! It hurts.
Bear with me, soon it'll
feel very good.
No, you're ripping me.
It hurts.
What's wrong? Your ass is
pushing back against me!
I can't.
Everything's becoming different.
It feels so good.
I knew it.
I see. That is
very worrisome, Moeka.
But Mao says she doesn't want to
get involved with others. I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Suzune has disappeared.
Mao would be worried about her, too.
Please, give me Mao.
Please let me talk to Mao.
Mao is, as you know, straight-laced.
Please understand, she'll be upset with me.
What about Suzune?
What would happen to Suzune?
Don't worry about Suzune.
She'll be back in school tomorrow.
You're so much trouble.
Where could Suzune be?
That reminds me.
There was a strange Spirit rising
from the Kichijo Heaven Temple.
But whether it has
to do with Suzune...
...I highly doubt.
The Kichijo Heaven Temple?
How hasty she is.
Sis!
Oh, Moe, how long
have you been there?
Who called?
What happened to Suzune?
Don't you worry. Have a nap.
You said the Kichijo Heaven Temple.
Is that where Suzune is?
She's so much trouble.
She's still too naive to inherit the
Ohtori Family.
Is that okay? To let her go?
It's too late for her anyway.
Well well, your sister will learn
to hate you soon.
Three now.
Halfway through.
Suzune, Suzune!
Suzune!
Suzune, what happened
to you? Suzune!
- Suzune.
- Suzune!
Stay away! Don't go near Suzune!
Moeka...
Mao, you're not our friend
any more!
I heard Miss Saeko was transferred
to another school.
- Tsk! I so wanted her!
- Idiot, you never had a chance.
They said Suzune also transferred
to another school.
Rise!
I'm Melanie Cool.
I'll be teaching your health class.
How do you do?