The stars have landed.
Inma Seiden
Hey, do you know students at
our Academy have been attacked recently?
I know!
Rumor has it, the girls who left
school voluntarily or are long absent...
...were actually attacked
by a giant with a facemask.
I heard he is called the Iron Mask.
Look, look. Miss Kaori is about to swim.
Ready.
Wonderful, Miss Kaori!
Miss Kaori is awesome. Living
as a daughter of the Academy Principal.
Oh, no! Miss Himiko
is the Acting Principal now.
Oh, isn't she Miss Kaori's aunt?
Nice swim, Sis.
Say, Sis.
What happened to
your Archery Club practice?
If you don't participate
in the club activities...
...you won't be a good example
for everybody else.
Well, Sena is in the Swimming Club.
She looked somewhat sick today.
So I came to take a look with Moeka.
Right, Moeka?
What? Yes. Hello.
Sena is not here.
Miss Ohtori, do you have
any idea what happened?
Well, let me see.
What about Mr. Iron Mask?
Isn't everybody talking about him?
Whenever someone disappears,
it's blamed on Mr. Iron Mask.
- Let's go, Moeka.
- Mao!
Did I say something weird, Bodai?
You could take her a little more seriously.
They're acting too openly these days.
The rumor is spreading,
even amongst the students, Akira.
This sure is a problem.
My Lady is a little too straight-laced
to be your sister.
Oh, that is a nice thing to say.
Until we know for sure
what Aunt Himiko has in mind...
...I wouldn't want to involve Mao.
- Do you understand?
- Sure.
Should I look into it?
You look like you're in pain, Sena.
You want to be
relieved of the pain, don't you?
Then accept me.
What?
Who are you?
No!
Stop it. Please.
You're inside my energy shield.
No!
Resistance is futile.
No. Mao, help!
About ready now.
Come, the Great Commander King!
No!
No...
No more!
I found the First Sheath.
What?
Personally, I wouldn't mind
leaving you alone.
But I'd hate to see My Lady sad.
Help me, Mao...
You failed. How can you show your face?
You had to lose her
to Yashagami of all people.
You've caused so much trouble.
In the first place, you are...
Oasa! Don't worry.
Kaori and others haven't realized
what the Sheaths mean.
- Yes.
- Sagawa, I hope you're aware.
I will not tolerate any more failure.
Next time, I won't.
Mr. Yashagami, you have to explain this.
Ms. Matsumoto...
...are you thinking that I was in
the girls' bathroom with Miss Yamamoto?
Don't be silly!
I'm not even suggesting that.
I couldn't say this
when Miss Ohtori was around...
...but Miss Yamamoto was raped.
- You knew it, didn't you?
- Well, sort of.
She's not the first one.
I haven't been here long, but...
...I have already taken care
of rape victims here.
But then all of them
have disappeared from this school.
Why does the Academy keep this secret?
You used to have a teacher
named Minako Yamato before I arrived.
- I wonder what's happened to her.
- You're thinking too much.
I think you should talk directly to
the Academy Principal...
...regarding such matters.
Mao, why don't we go visit Sena now?
Moeka, go ahead to the infirmary.
I have something
I want to check out on my own.
- But...
- Do as I say!
If someone's playing tricks,
I won't forgive him.
Ladies' Room
What? How?
Leave them alone, Hitomi,
I thought you hated them.
None of my business, I know.
What could be the purpose of
such a energy shield?
I'll find out who did this and punish him.
There!
These things... Why so many?
Who is it?
You...?
No way. You're from the Land of Death.
Gold Steel Blossom!
No way.
Hitomi?
Ouch.
Hitomi, why?
I'm your cousin, don't you dare
show yourself to me when you're pathetic.
Besides, my mother
would be sad to see you like that.
She will be sad.
Auntie would be?
Hitomi, tell me.
What is that Iron Mask?
He is not an ordinary God.
- He must be...
- You make me so irritated.
Hey, wait for me.
That was close.
Had Mao been captured by him...
...things would have been quite difficult.
I'm sorry.
It was a rather complicated situation.
But I never imagined
Miss Hitomi would help out My Lady.
Auntie must have her own plans.
Whatever she is after, this is my Academy.
I don't intend to let her get away with
whatever she wants.
It's okay by me so long as My Lady is safe.
By the way, Mr. Yashagami.
This is a girls' shower room.
Is it? Oh, well.
You got me.
Principal!
No matter what you say...
...Ms. Yamato resigned
and left this Academy.
I don't know what's become of her.
Don't you even care?
Minako, Ms. Yamato would not
simply disappear without a word.
You and Ms. Yamato.
Do you two have something going on?
Something...?
Saeko, you're very attractive
when you're upset.
Can I call you Saeko from now on?
Excuse me!
No...
Rikako? Rikako!
Rikako!
- Rikako.
- No.
My name is Minako. Minako Yamato.
I'm not Rikako. No, don't!
- Rikako.
- No, I'm not!
No!
Don't.
Stop it already. I don't want it.
Rikako, it's so good!
No more. Not any more.
So? Is your father still alive?
He's in a prison,
he's got nothing else to do.
He must be raping her
whenever he's awake.
I wonder what it's like
to get laid by a man.
Listen, Hitomi.
I'll be the first man to lay you, you got it?
Don't sleep with other men before I do you.
I should've let Mao get raped.
If you want, I can go kidnap her
and lock her in the prison with your father.
It got in my ear. Oops.
It's not coming out!
Let's go home,
Mao and I will take you home.
But how can I explain
what happened to Mom and Dad?
You just got sick and fell in the bathroom.
Happens all the time, right?
You say that because you don't know.
Sena...
I've got an idea. Sena, Moeka, why
don't you spend the night at my house?
- At the Ohtori mansion?
- What do you think, Sena?
You have nothing to worry about
at my home no matter what happens.
We'll have Sis and Akira...
No, Mr. Yashagami with us.
What do you think?
Yeah.
What do you mean,
no matter what happens?
Don't worry about it. Let's go.
- Hey. What is it?
- Shh!
Who is it?
No!
Force field!
- What are these?
- No.
Sena was attacked by these.
Come, Inma, Great Commander King!
Damn!
No!
- Moeka.
- How dare you attack Sena!
Moeka, no!
Oh, no...
Naughty girls.
Women shouldn't be
in a place like this so late at night.
- Akira!
- Mr. Yashagami.
I'm not willing to fight a King, but...
...I can't forgive it for tormenting My Lady.
Watch out, Akira, he's powerful!
You don't have to worry, My Lady.
I'm stronger than you are.
I'd think an extended battle
may be problematic.
I shall get rid of it once.
Present!
Warrior!
Fight!
Human!
All!
Post! Rip!
Be! Forward!
Awesome!
Sena...
Sena!
Bastard!
My Lady!
What is this?
The Temple of the Peacock God?
Sena!
An energy shield.
Sena, wake up! Sena! Wake up, Sena!
So good.
More! It feels good!
Sena! Sena!
More...
Stop it! Sena!
No!
On!
Here is one.
Sena!
Sena! It's all right, Sena!
Sena! Come on, Sena!
Open your eyes, Sena!
Sena, open your eyes. Sena!