West Cape Corporation
The West Cape Corporation
Presents
A Project Team Mu
Film
USAF 13th Bomber Wing
1944. The outskirts of Berlin.
Headquarters of the Vrill Association.
What is it? My God!
Now, let my god Astara Odin
be brought forth!
Are the gates of hell beyond
even your abilities?! Munhi Hausen!
Cowards... Don't they realize
that only HE can give...
...the Third Reich dominion
over the 3 realms?
Now! Begin the process!
What are you doing?
Papa! It's overloading!
- Something's wrong...!
- Impossible!
My Lord of Chaos comes!
Mein Fuhrer!
Munhi Hausen!
What's gone wrong?!
My Lord of Chaos...
Your failure to the Fuhrer
will not be tolerated!
What is this...?
TOKYO 199X
You called,
Munhi Hausen?
You wasted
no time, Kohoki.
You're the only human who
never runs from me.
So?
What is it this time?
Do you wish
to kill the Overfiend?
THE OVERFIEND?!
Sure, I'd love to.
But I'm not crazy enough
to actually try!
Whoever kills the Overfiend
will control the 3 realms.
No thanks.
Unlike certain humans I know,
I rather prefer staying alive!
Do you wish
to return to Hell?
W-wait! All right!
I'll help you!
I'll help you...
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Demon Womb
"A Prayer for the Resurrection
of the Lord of Chaos"
Trouble!
We've got major trouble!
Hold on!
Who do you think I am?!
FRONTIER OF PRISON'S GATE
I hate this stupid place!
Where're you taking me?!
Hey! HEY!!!
Where can he be?
He's gonna be too late!
I won't let you take
another step in here!
Why do you
defile this place?!
What's keeping him?
And he has the nerve to say
what a high and mighty...
Boss! Where were you?
I've been waiting!
What is it?
What happened?
That did it?
No?
Human...
A human did this?!
A human who controls
a demon? But why?
Overfiend's...
natural enemy.
Natural enemy?
Beware, Amano Jyaku...
Boss, look at this!
It's the guardian
deity of my people!
So you guys have
someone you worship?
Actually, my grandpa says
these ruins are 4000 years old.
What?! 4000 years old?
That's impossible.
They'd be older than the
legend of the Overfiend!
And nothing's
older than that...
Something's up, outside.
Come on, Kuroko!
Yessir!
What's going on?
Amano Jyaku...
It's Mimi!
Lady Mimi!
You alone? Why're you out
here at Prison's Gate?
I thought we could do it here,
without Grandpa to stop us.
Okay, I getcha.
A quickie?
More than that!
Boss, wait!
If the Elder finds out you're
with his granddaughter...
Oh, you're so good,
Amano Jyaku...
You're just gonna do it
out here, you... ANIMAL!
Shut up and go help Megumi
keep an eye on Nagumo!
Yes, sir...
We watch him all the time,
and nothing ever happens!
Don't talk like that!
It's the Boss's orders.
Boy, you're all smiles.
Are you really that happy?
Of course! I haven't seen
my cousin in 10 years.
I wonder what
Takeaki's like now.
You're that close...
I think I'm jealous!
You two were
like brothers.
Oh yes! Maybe even closer,
don't you think, dear?
Oh yes. Tatsuo must be
quite the young man, now.
You'll have fun with him,
like when you were children.
- They're not kids anymore!
- Yes, you're right!
Is that it?
Yeah!
That's the plane!
Captain! We've got a
problem in the #4 engine.
Captain? Captain!
What the hell?!
Mom!
Mom! Dad!
Takeaki...
- Takeaki!
- Nagumo!
Demons, I'll bet...
But why?!
Hold off on that side!
Careful, now!
Over here! Hurry!
I think he's still alive!
Takeaki... Takeaki...
He's gotta be okay...
Takeaki...
He needs blood
immediately! Hurry now!
TAKEAKI!!!
No!
You can't go in there!
- Lemme go!
- Hey...!
Takeaki!
TAKEAKI!
Doctor, you gotta help him.
He's my cousin!
My blood... Give him my blood!
We're both type O!
Doctor, please!
Come with us.
Megumi, a transfusion
from Nagumo...?
And so Takeaki Kiryu,
the lone survivor of...
...the airline crash 4 days ago
is set to be released tomorrow.
Congratulations! Let's hope he
gets over this tragedy soon.
And on that note, next up
is the Mu Orchestra...
...with "Sole Survivor".
Enjoy!
Yeah...
Like that... Yes!
Oh yes...
Can't believe how
horny she is... Oh well!
Perfect!
Yeah, just try and
catch up with me!
Pretty fast.
What's he driving?
Did you hear
news this morning?
Yeah. On the the highway.
What's happening to this city?!
I'm scared...
Don't be! I'm always with you,
and I'll always protect you!
- You mean it?
- Sure.
Same old,
same old...
So, Megumi, do you think the
Demons caused the latest murder?
Nope...
We've lost Nagumo!
Forget him. I'm waiting
for someone else.
Megumi-i-i-i!
She's always here.
Hurry up and find her!
Megumi?
Are you here?
Where are you,
Megumi?
What do you
want this early?
Megumi!
Please have some! I hope you
like this batch, too!
Again?
Oh well...
- Captain!
- Captain, snap out of it!
Still...?
Yeah...
I want him! If we had
him on the team...
Hold it!
Try me!
You're strong, but I don't
think you can beat me.
It's him...!
I don't fight girls.
You win!
Megumi!
Sorry. I guess I went
a little crazy just now.
By the way, you really should
wear something under that.
My name's
Takeaki Kiryu.
Sorry I acted like that.
I'm pleased to know you!
Not half as pleased as me!
We need a guy like you!
You're incredible!
Same 'ol Tatsuo.
I guess... But when did you
get so good at fighting?
The whole school's
talking about you!
I got good at it in school
when I was in London.
Man! And you were such a
crybaby when we were kids!
You only just got out of
the hospital yesterday.
Don't push yourself!
Thanks for worrying
about me, Akemi.
I was worried, too!
Megumi...!
I'm Megumi Amano.
How do you do?
H-hi...
You were great.
A real champion!
Strong men make
me weak in the knees.
You're a cheerful
one, aren't you?
But!
Next time, don't hold
back when fighting me.
You won't lose, then.
S-sure...
You fought Megumi?!
The secret's out!
So, tell me about yourself.
Gotta girlfriend?
Oh no you don't, Megumi!
You're not corrupting HIM!
Oh, too bad.
There's the bell.
Guess we'll have to continue
this after school. Let's go!
Jerk!
I suck at Math and Chem...
They're just too boring.
Takeaki!
See ya later!
Megumi... huh?
Hey Takeaki!
We gotta go!
Almost had him...
Megumi, shouldn't we
tell the Boss about this?
Megumi?
Huh?
What's with you?!
- Really?
- That's right.
I can't believe you were
released only 3 days ago!
Yeah...
I'd really like to thank you
for everything you've done...
Especially finding that
apartment for me...
What're you talking about?!
We're family, right Mom?
Exactly.
And if there's any problem there,
be sure and ask us for help.
Or if you need
anything to fix it up.
S-sure...
It's a shame
about your parents...
But you survived, and that's
something to be thankful for.
I wish we could've done more
for the funeral service, though...
Would you two cut it out?
He's just gotten over it...
Forget it, Tatsuo. You've all
been so great to me.
Sorry I brought it up.
Forgive us.
Oh Dad, you should get Takeaki
some sportswear next time.
He's turned into a real jock
since we were kids!
Yes, I can see that.
He's looking great!
A real man, now.
- Yes, a fine young man...
- Very fine...
You'll have fun with him,
like when you were children.
- They're not kids anymore!
- Yes, you're right!
Not again...!
- What's wrong?
- Are you alright, son?
I'm fine.
Just a little dizzy.
Maybe you have
been overdoing it.
Yes, I think you should go
home and get some rest.
Oh man, it's just
like with Ozaki!
Takeaki!
Need some help?
I'm fine, really!
I'll take you someplace
really great tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Tatsuo.
I hope he's all right...
I guess he's going
home alone... Huh...?
Where'd you go?
Megumi?
In other news, a man's
body was discovered...
...in Nishiguchi Park
early this morning.
The man, identified as
Mr. Masahiko Aida of...
...Nerima District, is believed
to be the latest victim...
...of the so-called
"Night Stalker".
The discovery of a lady's handbag
on the scene supports this theory.
No... I don't know
anything about it!
I don't know...
No! It isn't me!
Dad, Mom... Help me...
He's fighting
the blood inside him...
Damn!
Where'd he go?!
It's ready.
Looks good.
I try my best!
Shall I open the wine?
Sure. I'd love some.
There you go.
Thanks, dear.
Oh, Takeaki,
you're home!
Come in. I'll let
you drink with me.
Dad... Mom!
What's wrong, son?
Come in already!
Awaken, Takeaki.
Awaken...
I've been waiting.
Who...
Who are you?
My name is Munhi Hausen.
And I am here to lead
you to your final form.
Final form...?
This form you now take
is merely temporary.
Takeaki Kiryu died
in that plane crash.
I have caused
you to be reborn.
So that we may
carry out our destiny.
No! My parents died in
the crash, but I'm still alive!
And my cousin's family
has been so kind to me...
I owe them so much!
Kind to you?
You really believe
their hypocrisy?
Human kindness
is merely a sham.
Humans always feel superior
to those they see in need.
They are kind only to absolve
themselves of the guilt they feel.
That is the essence of
"good will towards others".
Let me show you the true
nature of the human heart!
I'd really like to thank you
for everything you've done...
Especially finding that
apartment for me...
You'd better be!
It costs a bundle!
As if the funeral
didn't cost enough!
My goddam brother dies and
leaves me his kid to pay for...!
Do you realize how much
trouble you're causing us?!
What are you up to?!
You must be the
Beast-Girl, Megumi.
And you're no
ordinary human!
We will meet again.
In good time...
Who the hell was he?
And what does
he want with Takeaki?
He's gone!
Relax, it was
just a dream.
But...
I said I'd take you
to a great place, right?
Here it is!
THIS is it?!
I'm outta here...
Wha- Takeaki,
hold on a sec!
I'm blowing my whole
allowance on you, man!
Cut it out! Tatsuo, l...
Leggo...!
Well?
Pretty cool, huh?
Tatsuo... Do you come
here all the time?
Loosen up, man!
I'm going next door.
I can't handle this...
Oh man...
Hand job, sir?
Only 3000 yen.
It's just too much...
Hand job, mister?
Only 3000 yen.
A h-h-hand j-j...!
No thanks! I'm fine!
Megumi! What are
you doing here?!
I followed you!
Come on, Takeaki. I'll make
you feel REAL good...
No...! Cut it out! I can't
believe you're doing this!
Cut it out...
First time?
That's so cute!
Hey, for another 5000 yen,
I'll let you suck them.
Huh? What's going on?
I feel so strange.
I feel like they're being sucked,
but there's nothing there!
Kuroko, you little...!
What're you...?!
Megumi, please...!
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?!
Let's book.
Hold it! Someone's
gotta pay for this!
Come on!
There's no more...
What the...?!
Megumi,
how are you...?
I'm not human.
Surprised?
You're not quite
human either, now.
Relax, it's okay. I know
what's been happening to you.
You may
not believe it...
But not all the people in
this world are human.
There are Demons and
Man-Beasts here, too...
So Tatsuo is this...
this "Overfiend?"
Yes...
That blood transfusion made
you a "quasi" Overfiend...
That's what's causing the
changes in your body.
So that's it...
I'm sorry if this
is all such a shock.
Maybe I shouldn't
have told you.
That's okay. But can you
tell me one more thing?
What?
What's going
to happen to me?
I don't know...
But I had no idea Tatsuo has
such an important destiny...
It sort of makes my
destiny look unimportant.
He'll have his powers
manifest someday...
I can't do anything
about that.
But I'm going to fight it!
This blood inside of me.
Yeah! I know you
can do it, Takeaki...
Oh yeah...
Here. The King of my
realm gave it to me.
Take it, for good luck.
Thanks, Megumi...
Yokohama!
- Beautiful...
- Isn't it?
I mean you.
Oh for Pete's...
Don't say that! Come on!
What's wrong? Something's
draining my powers.
Megumi!
A demon!
Let's go!
That creature...
Takeaki!
Megumi!
Who are you?!
Lemme go!
It's only been 100 years.
Have you forgotten my name?
I'll help you
to remember!
What are you
doing here, Kohoki?!
Don't be so cold.
I came to the human realm
so that I could win you back.
That's one way to put it!
Take over my mind, more likely!
You still really believe you
can take me as your wife?!
I fell in love with you.
100 years ago.
When my queen found out,
I was cast into Hell for all eternity.
It just made you all
the more desirable.
So you broke
out of Hell, huh?
I broke out so I can
have your lovely body!
I thought Takeaki was
causing all those murders...
But there's more, isn't there?
Kohoki, are you in on that?!
That's my secret.
Just take my word:
Stay away from that kid,
for your own good!
So there
is a connection!
And that human's
behind this, too!
What do you
two want?
All I want
is your BODY!
What's wrong, Megumi?
Quick today?
We'll be joined together
in a grand, eternal climax!
I can't fight it.
Help me, Big Brother...
Help me...
TAKEAKI!
Yes...
He awakens.
With this,
the 3 realms are mine!