Here's one.
How dare you...
How dare you kill Sena!
Inma Seiden
The earthquake near Ponape Island
in the South Pacific...
...caused damage throughout
the coastal area of the Pan-Pacific region.
The extent of damage
is yet to be confirmed.
The government issued a warning
regarding aftershocks and tidal waves...
How is Mao?
She should be good
and has gone to school today.
She seemed quite shocked
by Miss Yamamoto's death.
This incident caused trouble for you...
...the Main Family, Kaori.
Sena Yamamoto has transferred
to another school, will that do?
Aunt Himiko?
By the way, there's a rumor that a
Forbidden Ritual is being performed lately.
Auntie, please make sure
not to get involved.
You could get burnt.
Sagawa called.
He's found a girl he thinks is a Sheath.
Place our deity Dakiniten
at the Temple in the World Without Color.
That should be our priority.
Besides...
You can't. Mr. Sagawa, the class...
Who cares? We don't have
a music class first period.
Oh, no.
Are you hot already, Reiko?
- Your undies are wet.
- No!
You're so mean.
No, not there.
You're so cute.
Mr. Sagawa!
I love you, I love you.
Aggressive, aren't you, Reiko?
Mr. Sagawa...
Mt. Shumi floats
in the Ocean of Fragrant Water.
The 33 Heavenly Buddhas
are easily affected.
The human world that we live in...
Moeka knows nothing.
- Not even that Sena is dead.
- Miss Ohtori!
Is my lecture that boring?
Mao.
Mr. Yashagami. I can't follow your lecture.
I am excusing myself.
What can I say?
You look delicious.
No. Mother.
Mother? I just ate her a little while ago.
What a laugh!
The livelier ones are worth eating, but...
...I will rape you first!
Listen, Hitomi!
You're my woman. Don't forget that.
You poor thing.
Now that my sister Erika's
Energy Sheild has disappeared...
...a monster like that
could take advantage of you.
You're my daughter from today forward.
Okay?
Mother.
Hey, Hitomi, the class has already started.
So good.
Please give it to me. I can't stand it.
Do you want it that badly, Reiko?
I want it. I want it. I'm going crazy.
What do you do when you want it?
Please, hurry.
You're coming inside me.
So nice, Mr. Sagawa.
More.
Mr. Sagawa!
I can't.
No, no, no.
She's all yours now.
Hey, let me rape you, all right, Hitomi?
Don't tease me.
What happened, Bonno?
Is Hitomi being mean to you?
Mao!
Don't spoil him too much, will you?
Hitomi, I have something to ask you.
Who summoned that Iron Mask?
You know something, don't you?
- You want to know?
- Yes.
I don't know either.
But you know Sena is dead.
Don't make fun of me!
I saved you from the Iron Mask for Mother.
Otherwise...
I might have killed you.
Bonno!
Mao is shaken. Seize this moment!
I will take care of this, Sagawa!
Yes sir, I'll handle Hitomi!
I won't let women like Himiko
and Kaori boss me around anymore.
You don't look well, Miss Mao.
What's wrong?
I'm fine, Suzune.
Now, I'm focusing.
What?
Energy Shield? Who is it?
Blossom Fire Arrow!
Come, Third King!
No way.
I've got you!
Captain! Miss Mao!
Miss Mao, get a hold of yourself.
What's wrong?
Don't worry, I just got dizzy.
But...
You worry too much, Suzune.
What was with that fox?
Who is it?
Mr. Yashagami.
I slipped and fell.
Hitomi, I think you know this, but...
...you are spending
too much time with Mao.
I did it for you, Mother.
Don't you see?
This is too dangerous for you.
Please let Oasa and the others handle this.
You have to stay in this school...
I shouldn't worry?
What?
Shouldn't I worry about you, Mother?
What do you say?
Go home now.
I have my club, so I'll be late.
Gloomy old bitch!
Hitomi...
Mr. Yashagami.
What's up, the two of you?
I heard you got hurt, so...
I'm sorry.
Thank you for your concern.
It's nothing.
If you touch Moeka,
you won't get away with it.
I wouldn't do anything to trouble My Lady.
- Shouldn't you rest some more?
- I'm fine.
I will walk you to the teachers' lounge.
Oh, well.
Maybe you have some idea
how Mr. Yashagami was injured.
No, I don't.
What's that?
Miss Kaori, anything wrong?
I'm sorry, I'm not feeling too good.
Please continue with the meeting.
Then let's hear from you
about the recent rumor about...
...the mysterious Iron Mask
and his identity...
This is the second time.
On!
Two.
Looks like we're too late. I think
this is Miss Reiko Koga of the Tennis Club.
- She's the second victim.
- Yes.
Let's give it a try, Bodai.
Now I see.
This Kanzeon Temple is connected
underground to the Peacock Temple.
The Temple of the Peacock God?
The place where Miss Yamamoto
was sacrificed just the other day.
I still cannot fathom
what Aunt Himiko is planning.
Once, I might have to
get into the Great Cathedral.
This happens every time I summon you.
Should I be your partner?
No. I can hold it.
But now that things
have advanced this far...
...I might need to probe into it.
Rikako. Rikako.
Pull her out of there now!
Idiot! No!
Don't take away my Rikako!
We need to find another girl
to give him as Miss Rikako.
I have an idea for that.
Don't go away, Rikako.
Rikako. My Sister.
Miss Matsumoto is so persistent,
but I don't know anything.
But, Akira...
I hope nothing happens
to My Lady while I am asleep.
Why does Akira show up
whenever I am in danger?
I've been living with him
ever since I was a little child.
And yet I know nothing about him.
Sis.
It's not good for you
to stay in hot water too long.
It's been a long while
since I bathed with you.
You and I and Hitomi used to
enjoy baths together when we were young.
Hitomi saved me.
I know.
But you can't take risks like that.
Sena is dead!
Mao!
They might come after you.
I beg you, don't make me worry.
We're the only family we have.
Hey, Sis.
What would I do
if anything happened to you...
No!
Mao.
Look what she does at school at night.
I just don't get what she does.
How is it? Did you break a record?
Do you enjoy tormenting yourself
that much?
Why don't you do what you like?
For example, if you want to kill Mao...
...l'll give you a hand
whenever you're ready!
Hitomi!
Are you practicing this late?
What's with you? You're flushed.
Am I? Must be because I ran.
You aren't trying
to do something dangerous again?
What's wrong with that?
Do whatever you like!
Some irreconcilable differences
they've got!
Just the two of them.
I should get them to be my prisoners now.
I knew this would happen!
It's not my fault.
They're coming.
Hitomi!
- Why did you save me?
- Because you're slow!
Great Commander King!
My Lady!
No!
Mao!
Don't touch my girl!
Stop!
No!
Stop it!
It hurts.
What?
Stop it.
No.
No!
It hurts! Stop!
Stop!
Mao!
Stop it.
Stop.
Don't!
It hurts.
It hurts!
You're ripping me apart!
Don't!
Mao...
It hurts! No!
No, you're breaking me.
I don't want it!
No more.
How easily she came.
At this rate,
I might be able to rule this world.
Next, Great Commander King!
No!
Don't!
Hitomi!
What?
She's mine!
Hitomi, I've been waiting for this day!
I will rape you here, now!
Damn! I was so close.
I will rape you! Don't forget that.
I'm sorry to have asked you out
this late, Mr. Oasa.
No, no, when the Main Family
summons me, time is of no importance.
What can I do for you?
Well.
I'm so hot tonight, I can't go to sleep.
I wonder why.
Well. That's beyond me...
Miss Kaori...
Whatever you are planning to do
with Aunt Himiko...
...I would like to know all the details.
But I'm sure...
...you won't honestly tell me
what I want to know.
I...
So I borrowed the spider from Akira and...
...played a little trick on you.
Now you will tell me everything you know.