Please, no!
Let me go!
Don't do this!
This feels good, doesn't it?
Good!
Sister!
Sister, hang on!
Hurry up, my lady. We must go.
You can't just come here
and take her away.
Let her go right now, or else!
All, hostile intruders...
will be...
stopped!
Right...
now!
I won't let you get away.
She got away.
Hitomi.
This devil finally dies.
The Holy War against the Devil
The sixth part
I heard that Kaori took a sick leave.
There were four other people
who didn't even show up.
How long can
the college stay open?
Why do you bring me here?
The members of the Ootoris
never rely on men.
In the underworld, Dakini has switched
their bodies...
so they can reincarnate as witches.
So what?
Since long ago,
the Ootori were from the witches' family.
Rikako and her mother were
the daughters, leaders of the underworld.
I've been here to serve them
for generations.
Is Mao one of them?
Your sister Mao,
is not really your sister after all.
But she cares for you more than the Ootoris.
Himiko is attempting
to take over the Ootoris.
But she just wastes her time.
You can decide to side with her or with us.
It's totally your decision.
Do you want me to betray my mother?
What if I say no?
Maybe I should put you
out of the way here and now.
Come on! Settle up your quarrel!
My lady.
Eavesdropping is a terrible habit.
If you don't hurry up, I'll take over.
Come on! No need to trouble
the head temple.
What can you do now?
Just as I thought,
you don't think much of me, do you?
If you really wanted to,
you could've saved more people.
You know that, don't you, Kaori?
Do you really care
about the Ootori's business?
You won't turn against
the head temple now?
Are you talking about Himiko?
Sometimes overconfidence
will lead to failure.
Just like this time.
I won't stop here.
You know that I won't.
Even Hitomi is going to get her revenge.
Something fishy's going on!
I'm warning you, get out of my way!
Stupid boys.
Kaori, how dare you!
I'll be back here tomorrow
when the sun is eclipsed.
And you'll have a lot
to worry about then, won't you?
Takashi, need you to do
your very best at this.
Leave it to me.
We're almost there, Rikako.
- Hitomi, let me take care of it!
- No!
Bonno!
Let me go, let me go!
She won't kill the classmates...
even though she looks pretty unfriendly.
Kaori, you're dead meat!
Takashi!
You see, Kaori is going to launch
herself forth.
Very well, let's put an end
to our struggle.
Kundalimyoou!
Stop!
Wake up, people!
How can you do this to me?
No!
Help me! Help me!
Hitomi, let me save you!
No, Bonno!
If you go, they'll be hurt.
Don't you know that?
Stop!
Hitomi!
Please no!
No! I'm begging you!
Stop!
Akira.
Do you know that Hitomi
was gangbanged?
Yes, and I heard it had something
to do with your sister.
My sister?
It hurts.
Please stop.
Not anymore.
Hitomi!
Bonno, don't look at me!
Please stop. No! No!
Stop!
No, please, no...
Protection Cloak!
Hitomi!
Mao, what are you doing here?
Don't worry. You're safe now, dear.
I can't believe this.
Mao, I'll let you go this time.
Stop Mao!
This spell is not from my sister.
Merani, stop! Mao!
Kaori, after all this time
I can finally get rid of you two now.
I won't let the chance slip by!
You know that.
No!
Mao!
Don't touch me.
No!
Mao!
Don't look at me!
It feels good.
Hitomi.
I'm coming!
Me too.
How sweet you two.
You can both go to hell, silly girls.
Unbelievable.
Merani, I thought you'd take care
of these students.
Isn't that right?
You know, I'm not a real teacher anyway.
I'm the evil spirit.
Hitomi, are you okay?
Leave me alone.
Hitomi.
There won't be a next time.
Are you going to keep fighting like this?
Hitomi probably doesn't know yet.
Wait, she should already know,
I'm her sister.
I'm sorry. It wasn't my place...
It's okay. Merani should have never existed.
The solar eclipse will be here tomorrow.
Himiko will have her last ritual.
I wonder if Mao is okay.
I hope.
No, stop!
I hope she won't be set back.
Don't worry. My lady
has become very strong.
Hitomi, what are you thinking?
I'll kill if my mother says so.
I've decided!
I'm going to stop Auntie Himiko
and get you out of this mess.
Tomorrow we'll be apart.
If my mother wants to take my life,
I'll obey her.
Sorry I can't stay with you anymore.
Here we go.
Mao, you've already been awakened
by Dakini's power.
But in case you can't be merciless,
I'll have to...
My lady.
Auntie Himiko, I won't easily
let you get Hitomi.
Mother, I feel so...
Hitomi!
Himiko! What are you doing to Hitomi?
Soon, my sister will be mine.
Mother...
I finally meet you, Rikako, my sister.
Hitomi. Hitomi.
What goes around comes around.
Like the fight between
mother and Auntie Himiko.
Then Mao and Hitomi got involved.
Maybe this is the karma
of the Ootori family.
Sister!
Hitomi!
I won. Now my beloved Rikako is all mine!
Hang in there, Mao!
Sister!
Take my power!
What happened?
Has Rikako come back?
No! I'll try again!
I'll bring back Rikako.
We've lost to the Ootoris.
I'll die with you, mother, I promise.
No! Where's my sister? No!
- Let's die together.
- No!
Hitomi!
It's Mao!
Hitomi, I can only save you.
You must come here now!
No, I can't leave my mother behind.
You now that.
- Don't do that!
- Goodbye, beloved sister.
Goodbye.
Hitomi!
Hitomi.