Koizumi...
Minako!
Lena!
Arisa!
Honami!
Damn! They're not who I want.
Shizuka!
Kousuke!
Oh, I can't be patient anymore.
Ah! Kousuke!
Shizuka!
Kousuke!
It was just a dream?
Man, that was really realistic.
Hi, my name is Kousuke Atami.
When you're a young man with a healthy body,
mornings can be a real pain.
But if you can't make it go away,
you might as well accept it.
I don't understand myself...
New Angel 1
Morning!
Kousuke!
Oh, no! I'm still dreaming.
Good morning!
Shizuka!
Hey, Atami! Get out of my way!
I almost caught Shizuka!
Shinoyama?
You may suck at sports and academics,
but you're an absolute genius when it
comes to the science of perversion.
Well, excuse me!
I was thinking about giving you a discount on this batch
once I'd developed them,
but now I've changed my mind.
No! I was admiring you!
Shinoyama, I love you!
One two! One two!
Oretin! Why can't you take more elegant pictures?
What fun would that be?
Here comes Shizuka!
Hey, look at that! A woman with a bat
in her pussy, coming down the street!
What? Where is she?
Her underwear clinging to her gorgeous ass is so sexy!
There was no woman
like that, you liar!
Why are you following me?
You'd better stay away from Shizuka.
Got that, Shinoyama?
What for?
Well, because...
You have no right to interfere with my artistic endeavors!
How can you call this art?
You got a problem with my work, Atami?
You can take pictures of any other
woman you want, but not Shizuka.
What gives you the right to tell me that?
It's not a right!
I'm just begging!
It's none of your business!
What? Since when do we have
such a beautiful girl in our school?
I think she was looking at me!
Yoo hoo!
Do you know who she is?
I'll check it out later.
It's on my schedule.
Oh, it's much too hot and humid.
What's with this weather?
I'm getting sick.
Kousuke, what's the matter?
Shizuka, do you know her?
No.
I knew it!
What about her?
You both look so depressed.
She walked by Atami in the hall yesterday,
but we checked her out and learned
that she's not a student here.
That's odd. Maybe she's a new transfer student.
That's what I thought, so I asked at the office.
They said there'd been no new
transfer students for two months!
What? Who is she then?
We were thinking that she might be...
...a ghost!
She is the woman with the disappearing face.
I know that woman.
Say what?
A woman with a disappearing face!
Oh, my God, a disappearing face!
He could be a ghost too.
He's not a ghost.
I think I've seen him before.
Shizuka!
I can't remember who he is.
A woman with a disappearing face?
Sounds like a real ghost story.
I've heard the story before.
Fifteen years ago, there was this guy at this school
who promised a girl he'd marry her.
Then he had sex with her, over and over again.
She got pregnant, and he made her get an abortion.
Then he got tired of her and found a new girlfriend.
When she learned the truth, it
left her in state of total shock.
So she left him a letter that said,
"I died because of you,"
and jumped in front of a train!
I've heard her head was cut clean off!
That guy said this girl in the picture
is the "woman with the disappearing face."
That means she could be the ghost
of the girl who killed herself!
Shizuka!
What's the matter?
You're looking at the wrong side of the picture, Shizuka.
Don't scare me like that, Shizuka.
Sorry, but the girl in this picture is my sterious.
Give it back!
Give my head back to me!
Good grief! What a nightmare!
Hello!
Hi, Shinoyama. What's your problem, calling me this late.
Atami, you're going to die.
Don't mess with me like that.
Remember the picture I took of
you after taking that girl's picture?
I checked that picture again, very carefully,
and there's a woman's head behind you!
Oh, my God! Are you serious?
I'll show you the picture tomorrow.
I'm sure she's a ghost.
Maybe the girl who killed herself at the train crossing
came back to find the man who abandoned her!
Maybe you look like him and she's hunting you down!
Hey, Atami!
Are you listening to me?
Shinoyama, can you keep this a secret?
Sure thing.
Can you go shopping with me today?
Yeah, sure.
Hi! Good morning.
And then...
Why are you running away from me?
Wait up!
All right, you.
What's the matter?
I don't want to die.
Don't come near me, you possessed man!
Shinoyama!
Shinoyama, you rotten skunk!
You betrayed me!
Kousuke...
I'm back after twelve years.
Minako! More, more!
Stop that, Atami, you pervert!
Atami?
I don't believe it.
You aren't my Kousuke, are you?
You can't kill yourself just because your canary died,
even if you loved it very much.
Kousuke, you have never had such a sad experience before.
You can't understand how I feel.
Oh, your haircut's so cool!
You must be a bad boy at your kindergarten!
No, you're wrong.
A bully from the elementary school cut my hair this way.
I was so depressed I wanted to die,
but if I do, I'm the one who'll lose.
Even if you're hurting and depressed,
if you let yourself die, you lose.
Be strong, Shizuka.
I left town twelve years ago
When my father got transferred.
When I came back twelve years later,
I couldn't find my strong, brave Kousuke.
Shizuka!
Cheer up, Kousuke!
I'll stick with you, so don't be afraid.
I've heard about you being haunted by a ghost
and how nobody wants to come near you.
But I'm not like them.
But I might be haunted just
like the rumor says.
I don't care. I'll be with you.
No! I won't let them kidnap you to their world!
I won't let you go by yourself!
I'm going by myself!
No! I'll go with you!
By myself!
With me!
Alone!
Not without me!
By myself!
Me too!
I will!
What is that?
Sounds like a woman moaning.
A woman's voice!
Kousuke, I'm scared!
Shizuka...
Chemical Storage And Preparation
Why not exchange information with your ghost?
I can help, no matter what the problem.
There it is! We found it!
Shizuka, I don't want to visit this medium.
What are you talking about?
We can't solve this ghost problem
without the help of a psychic.
Do you really believe that?
Whether I believe it or not isn't the point!
If we're going to solve your problem,
we've got to do whatever's necessary.
You think that much of me?
I asked around and finally heard about this psychic.
Let's give her a try.
She's got a good reputation.
I understand your story.
Now, you, gentleman, come here.
Excuse me...
I need to talk to a person alone, so I can concentrate.
I see. Well, Kousuke?
It's okay. I don't want any ghosts possessing you, Shizuka.
I understand.
I'll wait for you outside.
BIG GOD
Please wait one second.
What? That old woman wasn't the psychic?
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Do the same.
What? I need to take off my clothes too?
My approach to sympathize with your
ghost begins with physical contact.
To sympathize means to exchange feelings.
Physical contact is a means to sharing.
You understand, correct?
I guess.
I'm not good at logic.
This too is a way.
I wonder if I'm doing the right thing?
Shizuka, I'm sorry.
Kousuke...
Bye, see you tomorrow.
So, is she your girlfriend?
What? You mean Ruri?
I guess it's not unusual to have a
girlfriend when you're in high school.
No, she's not that kind of friend.
We have a very platonic relationship,
like hand in hand.
By the way, Shizuka,
would you like to have some tea with me on the way home?
What are you looking at?!
You're a pervert and a wimp!
You weren't like this twelve years ago.
I think you were better back then too.
Yes! Good! Like that!
Kousuke!
More!
Oh, no!
Ghost who wants to kill this man,
Kousuke Atami, come into my body.
Oh, so good! More, more!
Please sympathize with me.
Yes, Ma'am!
Kousuke!
Oh, it's coming, coming to me.
Not that coming!
I feel like I'm coming soon!
Hold on, Kousuke!
Once you've done your penance,
I know you'll be saved from this haunting!
Oh, I'm coming!
Wait a minute!
I came a long way to see you
and I don't want you to leave without hearing my story.
Can you hear me woman with the disappearing face?
If you hear me, please respond.
My name is Kousuke Atami.
I am not the man who dumped you!
You've made a mistake, do you understand?
If you know I'm not the one, please
find your way back to Heaven!
I'm coming!
You can come but I won't.
However, I can't hold it anymore.
Excuse me?
Give this envelope to the old woman.
I like you so I won't charge you.
What? But...
Come to see me again. Take care.
Thank you very much.
Well, that was a surprise. Is this
a secret sex club or something?
Hey! How was it?
Did the ghost leave?
Are you relieved now?
I don't know whether
I'm relieved or not.
If I don't do something,
I could be killed
by this ghost because of a stupid mistake!
Hey, Kousuke, wait up!
Shizuka, would you please leave me alone?
Why? I'm worried about you, Kousuke!
This is my problem, not yours.
Stop sticking your nose into my business!
What the...
Please, just leave me alone.
That's stupid!
Kousuke, you jerk!
Shizuka, I'm sorry.
I don't want you getting involved with this ghost thing.
Try to understand.
Now, I have to fight!
I'll find her!
This is that man we saw the other day,
the one who knew the "woman with the disappearing face."
If I can find him, I'll get some
useful information about her.
Have you ever seen this guy?
Excuse me but have you seen this
man? Do you know what class he's in?
Excuse me. Do you know this man with a weird face?
All of the students at this school
already know I'm being haunted.
School Office
Kousuke is such a stubborn jerk.
Well if he's going to be like that,
I'll just find my own way to save him!
You've got to give us a present if you want to join this gang.
If you've got no money,
I'll take your watch.
Oh, will you please forgive me, "sister?"
You little bitch!
Aw, shucks! I cut in the wrong place!
Scared? Pissed your panties and want to go home?
Just take a dump in the dirt, say
you're sorry and give us a present!
You bitch! Stop that!
I, Kousuke Atami, won't let you get away with this!
Hey, jerk off!
You can't be a man like that.
Damn you! You hurt an innocent man!
How about that?
Kousuke, you came to help me because you care about me.
Stop that!
Shizuka?
You jerk!
Shizuka!
What?
The hairstyle is similar but this can't be him.
There's no information with these pictures.
This drawing's just not good enough to identify him.
I've heard you're looking for me.
Oh, you're here!
Good timing.
I was looking for you too.
About a woman with a disappearing face.
She wants to see you.
What did you say?
She said she'll be waiting for you in the
old chemistry lab after school today.
Can you "sympathize" with a ghost?
You poor thing!
Poor thing?
Oh! Hey!
He appears and disappears with too much melodrama.
And what did he mean by "poor thing?"
The old chemistry lab isn't used anymore.
It's located in the most remote portion of the old building.
Rumor says it was also used for
washing dead bodies, during the war.
Chemical Storage And Preparation
I'm not scared of no ghosts!
It can't be!
It sounds like someone's washing blood off of the floor!
It's just an illusion.
I must be hearing things!
It's just a ghost.
Even though the ghost is a woman,
I'm not going to forgive her!
Hurry up and show your face!
Who do you think you are?
Oh, what happened?
Oh, what am I feeling?
It feels so good!
Ghost pussy!
Oh, you're awake now!
Oh, a ghost is giving me a blow job.
What the hell is this?
If I was a ghost, I couldn't give you such a good blow job.
But...
It's all right. I'm licking up the
liquid quite nicely, pee and all.
If you're not a ghost, why was your
face behind me in that picture?
Oh, was my picture taken?
It must have been when I was hiding in the bushes.
Why?
I was following you.
When I saw you in the hallway,
I thought you were my "type."
That's why you were staring at me.
Now, it's my turn to pee on you!
Who are you?
I'm sure you're not a student here.
Are you sure you're not a ghost?
Oh, feels good.
Answer me!
Wow! What a close up!
I'm a student at the Hayasaka
Girl's School next door.
What? But you're wearing this school's uniform.
That's because my older sister
was a student of this school, and...
I borrowed it from her.
So, you sneaked into this school by
pretending to be a student here, right?
Exactly, and now it's your turn to sneak into me.
I've got more questions.
What was that weird sound we heard after school?
That was me.
It sounded like this.
Oh, feels good.
You were doing like this?
Yes, I was doing this with my ex-boyfriend.
Ah, good.
Oh, ouch! Well then, who's your ex-boyfriend?
He gave you my message, didn't he?
You poor thing.
He called me "poor thing."
What was that about?
Oh, no! Did he say such a thing?
Tell me, what are your real intentions?
I just want to fuck you.
He's gotten really, really thin
because we had sex too much.
He spoke to you ironically because he thought
you would have exactly the same experience he had.
Do you like fucking that much?
Yes, I need it everyday.
I need this again and again, everyday.
What a surprise! No wonder he became such a thin man.
It's not my fault.
I think you can hold up.
Why do you think so?
You're as perverted as
I've heard you are.
You can take a licking and keep on
ticking. You're tough and very hard.
You fell for me, didn't you?
However, the biggest question still remains.
What do you mean?
Who's the woman with the disappearing face?
A disappearing face?
Yes, if you are not a ghost, your
face can't disappear, can it?
I see. He said that, did he?
No more excuses.
Having sex with a ghost is the most
unsettling experience of my entire life.
A mid-summer night's day dream or wet dream.
Maybe if I have sex with you
and think of a song in my dream,
you can find your way to Heaven.
How about Cock-me-all-night?
You mean Cavilian Night?
Keep your eyes on me.
The rhythm burns me up!
Keep looking.
So fast... I've never seen a blow job this fast!
"The woman with the disappearing face" might mean...
She disappeared!
Oh! I'm gonna die!
I'm Kousuke. Is Shizuka at home?
Hikawa Shrine? She went there?
I have to apologize to Shizuka.
Ninety-eight...
Once I've prayed 100 times, my wish
will come true, or so I've heard.
Just two more times.
The ghost of the woman possessing
Kousuke will go somewhere else.
Kousuke is perverted and it's his nature.
But I can't hate him.
Hey, hey, Minako. Let's fuck.
No way! You're too obnoxious to have sex with.
What do you want?
Pervert! Idiot! Shame on you.
Shame? What?
What? You don't understand?
Sorry, Shizuka, I understand.
Do you want some more violent advice?!
I'm just kidding.
You jerk!
Shizuka, If you go out with me,
I won't talk to other women.
I won't have sex with other women.
I promise, Shizuka! Don't go!
No matter what he says, I already
know he's just a normal pervert.
It's his energy.
I can't handle his energy.
Because I am a single woman waiting for marriage.
Shizuka...
Ninety-nine!
I wanted to be more feminine and
stop ped being a gang member
because I found my Kousuke again.
He wasn't quite the man I expected,
but he's attractive enough for me
especially since other women were chasing him.
I'm a woman who's fallen in love with Kousuke.
Oh, God. Please protect Kousuke from
that ghost, even if he is a pervert.
I will make your dream come true.
Kousuke!
Shizuka, please be with me.
I won't leave you anymore.
Wait!
One more time left to complete my prayers.
Shizuka!
Thank you, God.
I think Kousuke's okay, for now.
Kousuke's the only man for me.
Please keep watching over and protecting him.
The haunting problem has been solved!
But there's someone I can't forgive!
You're an asshole, Shinoyama!
Making up and spreading stories about
suicides jumping in front of trains!
Taking off my school uniform
Taking out the ribbon from my hair
Whispering "beautiful" without planning
A different girl
I will change to be
I will learn for you
Bravery to believe, it's the power
Bravery to love
I can hear your voice even though we are far apart
I know the danger instantly
Keeping your promise to me
I love you forever
Yes, close your eyes in your dream
You touched my hair
You reached deep inside of my heart
Now I am waiting
Being close to you
Including your whole heart
I am falling in love with you