Mao!
Wow.
Mr. Kameyama!
Mao!
Mao! Hang on!
Mom, look what they did to Moeka.
Mao.
What the hell is going on
around here?
HOLY WAR AGAINST THE DEVIL
THE FIFTH PART
It's so boring!
Mao?
Watch out, Himiko.
She wants to kill you.
You are born by Rikako and I.
I don't want to hear about this.
Himiko wants to utilize your body
to resurrect Rikako.
She couldn't take control of Rikako
when she was alive.
So she decided to let her die
and then take control of her.
That's none of my business!
Don't bother me!
You're the daughter
of the Ootori family after all.
You just brood on your difficulties...
and never listen to the advice of others.
Even knowing that might cause destruction.
Sena! Suzune! Moeka!
Don't leave me!
It's indeed hard to understand
human beings.
Know what I'm talking about?
Although I don't understand
what Himiko's purpose is...
it's true she caused the trouble.
It's just...
Just what?
I'm kind of worried about
how Kaori behaves recently.
I found out she's weird, it seems
something related to her sister Mao.
Can't let this keep going on like this!
We've got to make a deal with Kaori,
and stop Himiko!
Understand?
If it doesn't work, then
kill Fujio's family, the Kameyamas.
Kill the Ootoris of Kaori as well
if it's necessary!
You do whatever it takes.
So, Kaori, Mao was...
My mother was utilizing
Mao's body for her incarnation...
it wasn't me.
How come it was Mao?
I don't understand all of this.
Hey! Ayano is it...
Ayano, my sister?
Yes.
Hitomi, come with me.
- I need you.
- Okay, then.
Ayano, you saw something
you shouldn't have seen.
I know Kaori, but...
I swear, I didn't tell anyone about that.
So...
Darn you.
I'm sorry.
No!
Are you okay?
Hurt yourself, Ayano?
Get away from me!
Good girl, take it easy, Ayano.
- Stop it! Sister!
- Mao!
Ayano!
Mao!
Mao, you shouldn't have come here.
It wasn't a good idea.
I'll take care of Ayano.
Sister, what did you want to do to Ayano?
That's great, over there!
I can't stand it.
I'm coming!
Just one more if all the weapons
had been collected.
Everything would be under my control.
Himiko?
What's wrong with you, Himiko?
Himiko, you're not acting normal.
Sister Rikako.
You said you're going to be
with me forever.
No way!
It's your duty to protect the Ootori.
Rikako.
Himiko.
Rikako, don't get married.
Himiko, you're really spolied.
Don't say something stupid.
Fujio's a great guy.
I hate that ugly guy!
Himiko, no!
I still have to say something.
If I let you be touched
by another man I would rather...
I would rather kill you!
Don't talk nonsense.
I love you.
Himiko.
- I love my sister.
- Rikako!
Himiko!
If all the weapons had been collected,
then Rikako would belong to me again.
After the ritual at Benzaiten Shrine
has been done...
all the plates underground
will combine together.
If this going to happen
wouldn't it become trouble?
Got to ask Uncle Fujio about this.
Got to ask him.
Ask that guy?
I don't know
what Himiko's purpose is...
it feels so good!
But her available resources are limited.
I'm coming.
Auntie Himiko.
I won't let you make it.
Sister, Hitomi.
What the hell is everyone thinking about?
Mao.
It seems that you don't believe
it's Auntie Himiko who caused this matter.
Am I right?
You should have known
the duties of our Ootori family.
It's worshiping Dakini Goddess
and protecting Eurasia.
But Auntie Himiko made us
use the students as sheaths...
in order to obtain the weapons...
then keep offering them
to the Buddha Gods.
Consequently, a shift of rank
among the Buddha Gods is happening.
It'll cause the plates transform
of Eurasian Continent as a result.
And constantly cause disasters
all over the world.
Therefore, no matter our Ootori family
or the Kameyamas...
one family should be vanished.
It isn't true, is it?
It is true, Mao.
Hitomi is a child of the Kameyamas.
What if...
If Auntie Himiko was the one
who killed Moeka?
Then I'm...
I'm not going to forgive you!
Auntie Himiko!
Hitomi!
Just ask me if you have any questions.
Where is Auntie Himiko?
Stop yelling!
Don't you understand, Hitomi!
If this is going to happen, do you know
what you would become?
Mind your own business, Hitomi.
And then what?
I'll become like Sena and Suzune,
got killed by Tetsumask?
Hitomi!
Are you related to Tetsumask?
It can't be true!
Okay, Mao, if you want to stop
my mother...
Even if it's you,
you know I'll not let you go!
Namu!
Hitomi!
Yes?
Hitomi and your sister, well, well.
What's the deal that Head Temple
offered to Ootori?
I've got to stop them both.
I've got something to do now.
And furthermore...
I guess Hitomi wouldn't really hurt Mao.
What do you really want to do, Hitomi?
You're such an unbelievably
simpleminded fool.
I'll go and die...
if my dear mother
wants me to do so.
I'll go and kill if my dear mother
Now, can I eat her?
Mao, how was that?
Make a promise, never interfere with
what my mother would do.
Don't be such a damn fool!
How can I stand aside
when my friends are being killed?
Really?
What do you want, Hitomi?
To make you become nicer.
Stop it!
No, don't! I'm going to get angry!
Look how interested you are, little girl.
Mao, I'm really sorry, I am.
Because you won't listen to me.
I beg you, please!
No!
You bastard!
What the hell! I was just going to...
Giving special care
to specific students...
it's forbidden in this college.
Teacher Akira.
That's you, Akira!
I've got to ask you something important.
Can I take Mao back, Hitomi?
It's up to you.
Hitomi.
It's you.
Long time no see, Uncle.
Get away from me.
Don't be so afraid, I won't hurt you.
But just right.
Uncle, you're still clear-headed.
I know absolutely nothing.
Really? Are you telling me the truth?
It's just because of you doing that...
Iosing yourself in the lust of flesh...
- and violating my mother.
- I did love Rikako very much!
I did love her.
Believe me, I've had no idea that
things would turn out this way.
I didn't expect any of this, honestly.
All I thought was...
You possess an odor like Rikako.
- Smells good.
- Don't touch me!
It's all your fault.
You made my mother die Uncle.
It's Himiko who killed her.
It was not my fault!
I'm in a lot of pain,
you've got to believe me!
I don't exactly recall what happened.
But, I know...
Now, come on, tell me!
Why did Auntie Himiko choose
Hitomi as the last Sheath?
Twins? Me and Hitomi?
Akira, tell me it's not true.
I don't know what Kaori
is thinking about.
I can't leave you suffering.
It's my duty to take care of you.
If you want I can
become an enemy of Kaori.
Don't say that!
I don't want to hear it anymore!
Why! Why!
Why does everyone hate each other?
Mao.
What do you mean?
Mao wasn't the daughter of Uncle?
But weren't Mao and Hitomi born together?
So, Mao actually is...
So that's what it is.
Can't believe it. I was a fool.
Tetsumask!
Possessing Fujio, it can't be!
You.
That's him who did something
that shouldn't be done.
I wouldn't have let him stay
alive if he was of no use.
Auntie Himiko.
I guess it's still within office hours now.
Sneaking into someone's house...
It must be my sister
didn't teach you very well.
I am going to give you a good
lesson on behalf of my sister.
What the hell is this?
How come it doesn't work?
I've just withhold your spell
from my Kongouketu.
Bodai.
That precious little kiddie.
I've just converted him
to be at my command.
No!
What the hell are they doing?
Both just pushing the college aside.
However it may look to other people...
I think it's good to let Kaori
suffer the torment by herself.
It hurts! Stop it!
How can you treat us like this?
My goodness! Kaori.
What happened to you?
Aren't you always so tough?
Help!
Wake up!
How terrible it is.
You can't even cast a spell.
I'm never going to forgive you!
It's not been that long ago,
but you've gotten mature.
No, don't!
I heard Kaori is fond of masturbation.
Let's see how wanton
she can be right here.
Let me take a close look.
Auntie, please don't look, please!
It's so watery!
Kaori gets excited so easily.
It's just the same as sister Rikako.
Mom! How come Auntie!
No, don't get inside!
It's got inside!
No!
Don't look, Auntie, no!
What am I going to do?
Feels so good! It got inside!
It seems like you get more excited
when someone's looking at you.
Well, just let me take a good look.
In this way.
How embarrassing.
Feels so good.
So good. Feels so good.
Look, just look.
Look how raunchy I am!
I can't stand it.
No!
I can't stand it anymore!
I'm coming!
How wonderful, Kaori.
In this case
you can compete with Rikako.
But before that...
No! Don't!
Got to be careful with you.
Can't move my legs!
How dirty!
Is this how the master
of the Ootori family supposed to be?
Rikako! Rikako!
- No, don't!
- Rikako!
No, don't get inside! Auntie Himiko!
Stop him!
No!
Help me!
Often, a serious person
could become terribly wanton.
Mao would go and save her definitely.
That way I can go and eat her, right?
Sister.
Kaori wasn't at college.
Yeah?
She's never been so late before,
without making any contact.
She doesn't need
to be worried about, right?
That's true.
Mao! What are you doing in here!
Teacher Merani!
Somebody like Kaori...
could also take a tumble.
What happened to my sister?
She's in the dungeon of the Kameyamas.
What?
However, it's for your own good.
Maybe this way is better.
Right, teacher Akira?
What are you talking about,
I've got to save my sister!
I knew you'd say so.
Akira!
Let's go! We've got to get her out!
Please stop it!
Please let me go!
How does that feel?
It feels good.