So far, three weapons have been collected.
And if all of the guards
get a weapon, then there's...
So, what will happen?
The world as we know it will end.
I don't know why
the Auntie went so far.
But one thing is for sure:
The students have been destroyed,
and become the guards' sheaths.
Why is this happening to our college?
This has been a sinister land
since a long time ago.
That's why I've been
worshiping the Dakini Goddess.
Moreover, our college is located
right in the center of the land.
So it's easy to have some girls
with a certain tendency...
like Sena Yamamoto,
and Reiko Koga. And Suzune Takasu.
But even if Auntie is egoistic...
she won't want to destroy
herself along with the world.
There's just no way, I'm sure of it.
I guess you could be as egoistic as she.
Don't eavesdrop, Takashi.
That's not fair.
The only thing we know for sure is...
we can't allow this to continue...
we can't keep it a secret.
We need to tell the students about it.
Don't you agree?
So, people with the Sanskrit tattoo...
Will become the targets of Ironmask.
So, Suzune?
I surrender.
Don't stand there.
How can we concentrate like this?
Moeka, Mao said she'd help us.
- Moeka...
- Don't touch me!
Why now, then?
What do you want, now?
If you had only had the presence
to come down a bit...
Moeka, stop it.
Moeka, I'm sorry.
My apologies.
No!
Moeka...
Are you sure you want to be like this?
It doesn't matter anyway.
Mao's no longer my friend.
That's not what you really think.
What? So you know everything!
But you that's not what I was trying to say.
What happened?
What can't you tell me?
What's such a big secret?
I'm scared.
Yes.
Feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
What's that?
Is that the Sanskrit that Kaori
talked about?
I don't know.
If so, I'll be killed. This isn't good.
Mao, what happens then?
No, that's awful.
Well?
Don't expect that of Mao.
That's what happened to Suzune.
So, what should we do?
Don't worry, I would protect you!
- Ayano.
- Takashi!
You haven't come
to the tennis club lately.
Sorry. I haven't had time, that's all.
Sorry. I told her not to go.
Please don't blame her. Blame me.
Moeka, stop it.
I don't mean to blame her.
I'm one of the old boys
at the tennis club.
Moeka, you have to be quiet.
Sorry, Takashi.
- Miss Hitomi!
- Get out of my way.
Watch yourself, and don't get too far.
Don't get too far!
I'm sorry.
Moeka is right.
I got you killed.
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
But I've made up my mind.
I won't let the Ironmask
to hurt anybody anymore.
I'll protect everybody!
Please bless us.
Sena.
You're just in time!
I've been waiting for you.
Aren't you going to wait?
Haven't you been looking for me?
Wait! Tell me something!
Who's your next target?
Please tell me!
It's interesting.
The Ironmask seems to care for Mao.
Yeah?
Anyway...
Ironmask doesn't
seem that evil today.
Who cares what he thinks!
My job is to protect my lady.
If any more of Mao's friends die,
she will never recover.
We can't let that happen.
The streets are filled with obscenity.
It's easy to have girls to become sheaths.
Wish I could understand
Auntie Himiko better.
Right, Bodai?
He is a puppet.
Is that right? He's a puppet.
All I'm saying is that
he's just totally useless.
Nothing more than that.
So, he should be fired.
Anyway, we should return
to Mao's kindness.
No, don't go.
Could it be the Forbidden World?
Oasa! What's going on?
What are you doing? Oasa!
I summon you!
Let me go!
You're disgusting.
No!
What's going on? Strange feeling.
Stop it!
No!
It hurts!
Protection Cloak!
Mother.
What, Oasa, you look terrible.
I knew what you and Sagawa were up to.
You can't accomplish anything anyhow.
That's why I'm going to let you go.
But I won't allow you to hurt
my lovely daughter Hitomi.
I don't know why I put up
with you, you're crazy, Kaori!
You must know that
I accept your challenge, Kaori.
Hitomi, don't stay up so late, go home.
Why don't you just leave me alone?
Hitomi, what happened?
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
I'll be okay now.
You silly!
I watched you grow up...
I should be trying to protect you,
don't you now what I'm talking about?
Sister Rikako, it's all your fault.
So, this is where...
they were attacked by the monsters.
And the Ironmask took Sena away.
Moeka, it's okay!
Sena will be back.
Soon we'll make up with Mao.
You'll see. Please don't cry.
No!
I don't need Mao! I don't need her!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
But for now, it's better to discuss
with Mao and Kaori.
What's going on with all these crows!
Takashi! The target is Ayano!
Takashi.
You shouldn't do this
to your own pretty schoolmate.
So it's you that's in Oasa's way!
Overconfidence will lead to failure.
Good, that's good.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Stop!
I'm not Rikako, let me go!
No! Please stop, Fujio!
Enough! I'm tired of wayward women.
How could you! My sister!
Poor Himiko.
Rikako, I've loved you
for a long time.
How can it be? Poor Himiko!
I'm so sorry Himiko!
Please forgive me.
Feels so good, Rikako.
Rikako, yeah!
I'm not, please!
Rikako, don't go!
Rikako!
Rikako, don't go.
Beware of Himiko.
She wants to kill you.
Yeah, right there.
Baby!
Excuse me, Madame Himiko.
Saeko got out of the prison.
Go away.
- Get out of here!
- Yes, ma'am.
Takashi!
Why?
Rikako! Sister!
Himiko.
It's all your fault, Rikako.
You didn't listen to me.
Stupid girl.
I am going to ruin everything
precious to you.
Himiko, so those kids...
you hurt them.
I won't let you do this again.
Rikako Sister, die then.
Himiko, stop!
It's your fault, right.
Right, it's your fault.
Yeah, yeah.
Baby, yes.
So good!
What's up, Saeko teacher?
Kaori!
- You'll catch a cold.
- Kaori!
Himiko.
Good.
You haven't told anybody about Himiko?
Have you?
Kaori.
We don't want any more rumors.
You're appointed.
You must have understood!
Saeko teacher.
So, am I right?
I'll leave her to you, Bodai.
What do you want me for at this hour?
Suzune's dead.
Ayano could be next!
What's it got to do with me?
Takashi, were you spying on us
in the park today?
Watch your mouth!
Please don't hurt Ayano.
What should a woman do when
she asks for help from a man?
What? Don't you want
to save Ayano?
Mao.
As you desire, sir.
Don't waste my time, okay?
Hey, sometimes it's good
to have small ones.
That's it. Be good.
Then Ayano will be okay.
How pure!
What a naughty girl.
I'll give you a lesson.
Not there.
No, not there!
No! Don't put your fingers in there!
No!
Don't you care about Ayano?
Yes, Moeka had disappeared after she
said she'll meet someone.
She's gone?
Where could she be?
- We've got to look for her, now!
- Okay.
Moeka, please take it easy!
- Let me go.
- No way.
No!
Be quiet!
Little bitch!
Trick me?
Help!
Stop!
Why don't you give up, little girl?
Please let me go.
It hurts!
How about that? I'm all the way in.
It hurts.
Virgins are so tight.
No, stop!
I hope this will...
She's got the same...
I can't take it anymore!
What is that?
Kishibojin Shrine.
Number four.
Moeka.
Get up, Moeka.
What happened, Moeka?
What happened?
Moeka!
I'm so sorry.
No.
Moeka.
No! Moeka!