Shizuka!
Kousuke, you can do whatever you want to me.
Please, be gentle.
Oh, it feels so good!
More! More! Lick me more!
Oh, it's so good, Kousuke.
Do you like it, Shizuka?
Yes, it feels so good.
Oh, fuck me!
Hurry, Kousuke!
There, Shizuka...
Kousuke! Kousuke! Kousuke!
Shizuka!
Let's fuck!
New Angel 2
.
Flying Angel
Man, I was so close to having sex with Shizuka.
Atami!
Yamada, don't scare me like that!
I got a premium video.
A premium video?
Hold back! Can't you see this?
Yes, Sir.
There! "Make Me Come,
You Pervert - Special Edition!"
What the fuck is this?!
Sorry! Wrong tape.
I went sky diving in my father's helicopter recently.
Sky diving? You?
Now that's something hard to imagine!
Okay, so let's see this
"pervert" tape already!
What's wrong, Atami?
There was a girl here just a minute ago!
She's going to jump and commit suicide!
What's she doing over there?
Stop! Don't be stupid!
Don't come any closer!
Are you going to kill yourself?
I want to die alone.
But why? What horrible events have driven you to this?
College entrance exams?
Family problems?
Did your boyfriend tell you that
your vagina has a bad odor?
It's none of your business!
I hate my life!
Keep away from me!
Hey, Yamada!
Are you really sure you're going to kill yourself?
Yes...
What a waste.
What a waste, you slamming into that hard ground
and dying with your brains splattered all over.
Hey, if you're going to die,
you probably won't have to
worry about birth control, right?
How about this?
Since I don't have any
luck with women,
would you let me have sex with you before you die?
Please, let me into your tunnel of love!
Well, I'm going to die anyway.
All right...
What? Really?
Playing with myself and watching girls' panties...
Underpants!
Playing with myself and watching... Why?
You know, you could be right.
It might be a good idea to help
someone less fortunate before I die.
I'll just lie down here like a doll.
You can do whatever you want to me.
What?
You may die soon, but you're
feeling good right now, aren't you?
Hey, even though sex makes you
feel like you want to live forever
why are you in such a big hurry to die?
I see.
I guess you're not going to say anything.
Then, I'll have to use my secret weapon to make you talk!
Oh, that feels so good!
Very good! Really good!
Wonderful!
Okay, the reason Miki Ochiai wants to kill herself is this:
There's this boy she's been in love with
ever since she started school here.
His name is Kunihiko Kawamura.
Although it embarrassed her terribly,
she finally got up the nerve to
slip a love letter into his locker
but the very next day, she found her letter in the trash.
What?! Are you saying there was
a letter in my locker yesterday?
How could you tear up that letter and throw it away?
Couldn't you imagine how she'd feel?
That's right!
I don't know of anything about that sort of letter.
You bastard! You're lying!
Have you gone nuts? I've never
received a love letter in my life!
Can't you understand that, you moron?
Kousuke, there's something's fishy here.
I think there's more going on here than meets the eye.
Hey, look out!
I took my eyes off Miki for just a second and she vanished!
I told you to watch her!
Sorry, I was concentrating on my tape.
This new tape I got is really stimulating.
New tape?
Hey! Looking for Miki is the most important thing.
That's right. Let's go!
Someone who's tried to commit
suicide once might try it again.
He hasn't read your letter, so he doesn't how you feel yet.
Don't die, Miki.
I have no choice except to kill myself.
Good bye, me!
Good bye, my enjoyable educational experience!
There she is!
Miki, stop! This is stupid!
Miki, listen! I just talked to Kawamura
and he said there was nothing in his locker.
Impossible!
Somebody must have taken your letter
and shredded it before
Kawamura ever saw it.
Kawamura doesn't know that you're in love with him.
Give it another try!
You're just telling me this to stop me, aren't you?
It's no lie!
Stop trying to trick me into
feeling better! I really love him!
She's not going to listen.
I'll stay here and keep an eye on her.
You better hurry and find
Kawamura, Kousuke.
Why's he in such a rush?
Who tore up that love letter? Damn!
How many times do I have to say this?
I'm not lying.
There was no letter in my locker!
Even if I did see a letter, I'm not
some monster who'd just rip it up!
I don't care! There's a girl out there trying to kill herself.
Come on! Please! You're the only person who can save Miki.
Miki?!
It's a girl named Miki Ochiai who's trying to kill herself.
Miki Ochiai?!
Hey!
What's the matter?
How could this have happened?!
She hasn't read my letter!
What's that, Kawamura?
You mean you love Miki too?
Don't come any closer!
I'm also in love with someone who doesn't know it yet.
I'll tell him someday too
but even if it breaks my heart,
I won't regret it,
and I can't imagine trying to kill myself.
Just being in love is wonderful enough, isn't it?
And besides, you really haven't told him you love him, so...
Shut up! I know Kawamura hates me!
Idiot!
I can't believe Ochiai loves me too.
Ah, twisted destiny!
Kawamura...
Hurry up, let's find her!
All right! This way!
What the hell did you do to me?
Kawamura is mine!
I won't let Miki Ochiai have him!
Oh, no, what the hell?
Shizuka!
Kousuke! Kousuke!
Kousuke, wake up!
Shizuka...
What happened?
Oh, where's Miki?
I'm so relieved.
Idiot!
That was too close.
Damn! I've got to catch that girl.
Which girl is that?
I don't know all the details yet, but
there's another girl who loves Kawamura.
Watch Ochiai, Shizuka! And tie
her up tight so she can't escape!
Damn! Where'd that girl go?
Meow! Come here, little boy.
Bitch!
Hey, wait!
I'm a bit of a pervert myself.
Would you mind sticking your thing inside me?
Ah! Hurry up and fuck me!
Why are you doing this?
Where'd you hide Kawamura?
I'll tell you, but you have to put
your thing into my deep, wet spot.
Please...
What the hell?
Still, it feels so good.
Why did you tear up Miki's love letters to Kawamura?
I won't tell unless you fuck me.
I see. All right, if you say so.
I guess I'll have to make you tell me the whole story.
How about this?
Oh, oh, delicious!
I didn't want to do this.
I'm sorry, but you might try to kill yourself again.
Just be patient until Kousuke brings Kawamura.
Yamada! Don't you think that tying
her up like that is a little perverted?
Is this too crazy?
Yamada, watch her carefully.
Sure!
I wonder if it was a good idea to ask Yamada to watch her?
It's like leaving a wolf to protect the sheep.
Anyway, the most important thing is to find Kawamura.
What a perverted scene! A woman,
wearing just a slip, all tied up.
Ah, it's coming deep inside of me!
Ah, it feels so good.
Okay, how about it?
I've screwed you like you wanted.
Ah, I feel like my pussy's going to burst.
Oh, Kawamura!
You bitch!
Where'd you hide Kawamura? Tell me!
Oh, good. More. More!
If you don't tell me...
Please, don't stop! I'll tell you!
Where's Kawamura?
He's in the gym warehouse.
Oh, I'm coming!
Gym warehouse? I see.
Damn!
Wait for me!
I'll get Kawamura to you.
Shizuka!
Kousuke, I was looking for you.
What? What are you doing like that?
Well, standing fu...
I mean, I was taking a piss back there.
Is there anything back there?
No! No!
You sound like you were doing something wrong.
Ah, I don't have time to do this.
Did you find Kawamura?
Yes, I think he's in the gym warehouse.
How about Miki?
Yamada's watching her right now, not that I trust him.
Why don't you go and see how they are doing, Kousuke?
I'll go to the warehouse.
Okay!
Kawamura?
Where are you, Kawamura?
Hey!
He's not here.
Who are you?
That's not important.
I know where he is.
Come with me. This way.
Oh, what a perverted scene this is!
Oh, it feels so good! I'm coming!
What a mess. I see it all now.
It's just like Shizuka said.
Hi, Atami.
Let me go!
Why are you putting me here?
Because you didn't listen to a word
I said. Kawamura loves you.
I can't believe that.
Kawamura will get here soon, just be patient.
Liar!
Everything you say is a lie, you liar!
Let me die right now. Let me die!
You want to die that badly...
She's fainted.
I guess I over did it a little.
What the hell is this?
The boy in that picture's your boyfriend, isn't he?
He raped me, you know.
What are you talking about? I know
you engineered the whole thing.
I'll tell the school board that he raped me.
Then the school will kick him out.
If you want to keep him from being expelled,
tell Miki Ochiai to give up on Kawamura.
I know what you're up to!
If you even try it, you bitch,
I'll make sure you regret it!
Miki's out of her mind from the
shock having her heart broken.
The least you could do is have
compassion for a fellow student!
And don't think I'll go easy on you
because you're a girl, you bitch!
Where'd you hide Kawamura?
Hey, time's running out!
Where am I?
I remember. He tied me up, and...
The rope's untied now.
Now I can finally die.
Help me!
Oh, no! What's going on?
I asked Yamada's father to make
the same thing as the school locker.
I see.
I really appreciate it. I can kill
myself by falling from here now.
Do you think I'm still lying even though
I am doing such a thing?
For the last time, try telling
Kawamura about your feelings again!
If you really love him, your life is worth the gamble!
Kawamura's waiting for you on the ground.
Can't you feel his eyes?
Can't you hear him calling?
This is weird. Kousuke told me to take Kawamura to the
schoolyard and to watch the skies but I don't see anything.
Miki!
Miki! I love you! I didn't know you gave me a love letter!
Kawamura!
Miki!
I hear him! I hear him!
I can hear Kawamura!
Miki, I love you. Please don't die!
I don't want to die.
What shall I do?
Shout out how you feel now.
How I feel...
Playing with myself and watching girl's panties...
I love Kawamura!
I don't want to die before
I tell him I love him.
I really love Kawamura!
Miki...
Kawamura...
Man, was I scared.
Kousuke...
How's about you give me a booby prize?
Kousuke!
Still, I am glad you're safe.
Shizuka, I can't breathe.
I got off just by looking at a woman's underpants.
Thanks, Dad!
Seifuku o nuide
Kami no ribbon hodoke ba
Omowazu kirei da to tsubuyaku
Betsu na onna no ko
Umare kawaru jibun ni
Anata no tame mi ni tsukeru no
Shinjiru yuuki, sore ga chikara
Ai suru yuuki
Hanarete ite mo, ima
anata no koe ga suru
Sugu, pinchi wakaru no
Yakusoku mamotte te
Dai suki itsu made mo
Nee, yume de me o toji te
Anata ga kami ni fure
Todoi ta mune no oku
Ima, watashi matteru
Anata no soba ni ite
Anata no kokoro goto
Koi shi teru, eien ni