Shizuka!
Guess who!
You're so bad, Kousuke.
Oh, no! Kousuke!
Now, let's eat!
It's delicious!
That was our chef’s famous
hamburger-steak.
Next, we'll introduce you to one of
the most delicious ramen houses
in the Ginza district, right
after this commercial.
New Angel 4
A Bride for a Week
Something's not right.
Usually by now,
supper is on the table
even though it's not always
the greatest.
Wait a minute.
Last night, I had dinner delivered,
and this morning, I overslept,
so I didn't get any breakfast.
I had lunch at the school's cafeteria.
That means...
Mom hasn't been home
since last night!
Geez, Mom! What is she doing leaving
her starving son here alone?
What's up, Shizuka?
Good evening.
Anyway, come on in.
It wasn't raining when
I left my house, and...
Kousuke?
Yes?
My clothes are soaked, so is it
alright if I change here?
What? Get changed? Why do you have
a change of clothes with you?
Don't look.
Sorry!
Let's see... Let's start with the laundry.
Laundry?! Why do you have
to do it at my house?
The laundry room is down this hall.
Oh, yeah! Kousuke! How long have
you had on that underwear?
These? Two days, I guess.
Hey! Stop!
What are you thinking,
taking off my pants?
Wait a minute! You shouldn't be
doing this so fast. Shizuka!
Let's do washing, washing.
Oh, no. My panties are soaked too.
Oh, shoot! I left all my spare clothes
in my bag by the door.
Hey!
You've been watching me
all this time! Pervert!
What does all this mean?!
What does all this mean?
You came into my house,
tore off my pants,
and in the chaos, you grabbed
my very important part!
I didn't! I didn't grab it!
Have you heard anything from
your parents or my parents?
Heard what?
Oh well, what sorry parents I have.
Okay, I'll explain it to you if you bring
me that bag from the hallway.
Are you listening to me?
Hello, Atami residence.
Collect call from Mrs. Shiho Atami.
Will you accept the charges?
A collect call? Yes, I'll accept it.
Hello, Kousuke!
Hello?! Are you going to starve
your own son to death?
Aloha!
Aloha?! Mom, where are you?!
You know where. We're in Hawaii.
I told you. Your dad won
a jackpot on the horses,
so we went on vacation.
Or did I forget to tell you?
The two of you went to Hawaii
after winning a jackpot?
Also, Mr. and Mrs. Himenogi's daughter
will be staying with you for a week.
All the details are in the letter
I gave her, so ask her about it.
What did you say?
Oh, well. I think she's much
more alert than you are,
so I don't think there'll be any
problem, but be careful anyway.
Kousuke! Don't do anything crazy!
Honey!
I'll call you later!
But what am I going to do?
Man, this sucks! They just left and
didn't tell me anything! Damn!
Some parents!
If that's the case...
That's strange...
I've got it! Kousuke must have
hidden it somewhere!
So, Shizuka and I will be together
under the same roof.
Well, it that's how it is...
Seeing this beautiful girl constantly...
How I can hold back my throbbing
teenage hormones!
Kousuke!
According to Shizuka,
her father suddenly had to go
to London on a business trip,
and for some reason,
her mother went along.
Well, I hope you like it.
I spent a long time to cooking this.
You could eat it with
a bit more passion!
What time is it?
I'm sorry it took so long.
Would you get me some sauce?
Yes...
Here...
Idiot!
No bra or panties in front of a man...
Well, you know, someone hid my bag.
Do I have to sleep like this?
It's in the shoe drawer!
Oh, I see.
I'm going to take a bath since
I'm soaked with rain.
Aren't you supposed
to be taking a bath?
Hey, Shizuka!
I hope all goes well, Kousuke.
Six more days of living alone together.
How long are you going to sleep?!
That's blinding me! It's Sunday!
Can't I sleep a little more, Mom!
Shizuka! Why are you in my room
with only a negligee on?
I accidentally brought my mom's
negligee instead of my pajamas.
I'll go get them later.
Here are your clothes!
I can't get that flash of her boob
yesterday out of my mind.
She should've been more considerate.
These are...
Too small for me.
I guess she's not here.
The room my mom used when she first
married has become Shizuka's room.
To actually be living with a girl
I am so interested in...
Surely it can only get better!
And of course, I want to be with her!
The situation is almost like
God telling me to go for it!
Today is Sunday.
I should approach her slowly,
and I am going to do it!
What?
Kousuke, what are you doing in here?
Oh well, I mean the pool...
Yeah, I was going to ask you if you
want to go swimming with me.
Hey, Kousuke!
Hey, it's Sakai!
Hey, it's Himenogi!
Hey, is that your new one?
How long have you been together?
Hey, Kikuchi.
You dropped something.
What? You live with that boy?
I'm so jealous! My nipples get
hard just thinking about it!
Oh, by the way, did you know that
there's straight ones and curved ones?
What?
Come on! Don't act so innocent!
I know you've done it!
His curves to the left.
Oh, that.
At first it was so fascinating.
Something so small and soft
becoming as hard as a rock.
And then, when it penetrated
all the way inside me...
I'm getting wet just thinking about it!
Come on, let's go!
Hey, wait Himenogi!
Since you're staying at his house,
you have to let him do it at
least once if he asks you.
At least once...
Oh, this water is cold!
This feels so good!
You're so pathetic!
She's living with you, and you
haven't fucked her yet?
Hey, man, Kousuke Atami's
name is being ruined.
Moron! At least I'm not
like some people
who're low enough to do it
in an elevator!
Oh, okay.
I was going to tell you about the spell
that enables you to do it
with a girl for sure.
For sure?!
Master! Please punish one
who is so self-centered!
Sir, is that spell for real?
Himenogi!
Are you serious?!
I went to the pool just
to have a little fun,
but I got some great news instead.
Shizuka! The pizza should
be here anytime now.
Do you want some juice?
Oh, sure! Thanks!
Ouch... That was the first time in
a while that I've been swimming,
and my legs are really
starting to stiffen up.
Ouch...
And I'm getting really stiff too.
Listen up, Atami. First, put
some juice in a glass.
Then, put your dick in there.
Then say, "she is mine" three times,
and mix well.
She is mine. She is mine.
She is mine!
And have her drink that juice.
Her body will be yours tonight.
Everything...
Shizuka...
Yes!
I'm coming right now!
Thank you for ordering!
How much will it be?
One special pizza, and one supreme
pizza - that's 4000 yen, please.
Here...
Shizuka!
Here's your juice.
Oh, thank you for being so kind.
Not for you!
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Gross!
He really believed in that phony spell.
That's so good!
I wonder how he's doing now?
It's inside.
More!
Right there!
I'm coming!
Something's wrong with Kousuke today.
You ordered pizza, and you're
not eating any of it.
Did I say something to upset you?
Not really.
You don't understand.
No one understands my feelings
about not being able to be with
someone I have feelings for.
What do you mean?
I said that girl is not cute at all!
You mean this girl?
How can she become a cute girl?
Ouch!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry, Shizuka. Are you okay?
How pathetic!
What a sorry mistake.
Oh! I'll get it!
Excuse me.
Hello, this is the Atami residence.
Is that you, Shizuka?
Oh, hi, Mom!
How are things there? Anything wrong?
No, not at all.
Five more days of living
alone together. Oh, well.
Hey! Today's not over yet!
Hey!
What is it?! What's "hey"?
Oh, it's nothing.
Shizuka, the reason we're in London
is because we're researching.
Marshmallow, Marshmallow!
What? Researching what?
We went to places where
not many tourists go.
And because...
Mom, you are coming back
in one week, right?
Come back soon.
Yes, well...
Let me talk to her. Let me
explain this to her.
Hi, it's your dad.
Even though we're here
for my business,
this is more like my job's...
Hello, hello?
She hung up.
I hoped she wouldn't take it too hard
when she found out about this.
Well, there's nothing we can do.
Big boob, squeeze, squeeze!
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze.
Shizuka...
Could you at least tell me that size
which can't be measured in public?
My IQ?
You know?!
I don't like this.
Even though you want it,
I can't help you.
I did not come to your house for this.
I'm sorry for not being a cute girl.
That's the best I can do for now.
Shizuka!
Shizuka...
Kousuke...
It's only been two days,
but it's been great. Thank you.
Hey, wait a second!
Wait! Stop!
Why are you going home?
Being home by yourself
is very dangerous.
Won't I be a burden
if I stay with you?
I thought things would've
gone more smoothly.
But I guess, after all, a high
school boy and girl
living in the same house
is not a good idea.
I won't try anything with you anymore.
Will you believe me?
Is it too late?
If you don't hate me, come back
with me please!
Look! It's turned red!
I want to spend as much time
with you as possible!
Oh, yeah!
You two are so cute!
Cheers to our friendship!
Cheers!
Oh, I'll get it!
Hello, Atami residence.
Oh, Shizuka. It's your father.
I'm sorry I hung up on you last time.
Oh, don't worry.
What?
To make a long story short, I was
assigned to the London office.
We will all be living here in London.
That's why your mom and I are here.
We've been looking for a house.
Are you there, Shizuka?
I'd better repeat that.
We'll all be in London by next month.
Let's all live together as a family.
Seifuku o nuide
Kami no ribbon hodoke ba
Omowazu kirei da to tsubuyaku
Betsu na onna no ko
Umare kawaru jibun ni
Anata no tame mi ni tsukeru no
Shinjiru yuuki, sore ga chikara
Ai suru yuuki
Hanarete ite mo, ima
anata no koe ga suru
Sugu, pinchi wakaru no
Yakusoku mamotte te
Dai suki itsu made mo
Nee, yume de me o toji te
Anata ga kami ni fure
Todoi ta mune no oku
Ima, watashi matteru
Anata no soba ni ite
Anata no kokoro goto
Koi shi teru, eien ni