Cheers to our friendship!
Cheers!
Oh, I'll get it!
Hello, Atami residence.
Oh, Shizuka. It's your father.
I'm sorry I hung up on you last time.
Oh, don't worry.
What?
To make a long story short, I was
assigned to the London office.
We will all be living here in London.
That's why your mom and I are here.
We've been looking for a house.
Are you there, Shizuka?
I'd better repeat that.
We'll all be in London by next month.
Let's all live together as a family.
New Angel 5
.
The Last Night
Impossible! It's so sudden. Dad!
Dad...
What's going on?
Oh, nothing.
Well, then!
Too many things have happened today.
I'm going to take a refreshing shower.
Shizuka!
We just toasted our friendship.
He's not a Peeping Tom, is he?
Shocking!
They're still warm.
Kousuke, are you there?
Yes! I just came in to get my razor.
Do you want to take a bath with me?
You're kidding, aren't you?
You shouldn't say things that
play with my emotions.
Two people living together only
have five more days left.
We've spent the last few days together,
but nothing has happened.
Of course, Shizuka and I have
a wholesome relationship.
Two people living together only
have two more days left.
Here it comes!
Okay!
Well, your father was transferred
to London so you're moving.
I'll miss you.
But London sounds very nice.
Don't be so distressed.
Before you leave, you want to
lose your virginity to him?!
There are several techniques
you can use to seduce him.
Really?
Listen...
Hey!
What, him? Surely not!
Atami's very lewd, isn't he?
Thank you for the nice advice.
Ouch! You knew the ball was coming!
You, Himenogi! Idiot!
That was a nice, hot bath.
Good timing, Kousuke.
I'm making a cake.
Would you like to taste the batter?
A cake? Sure I would.
Well?
Delicious!
That's good. I'll taste it too.
Kousuke, my hands are full. Please?
Sure!
The number one way to seduce
him is to suck his finger.
He'll imagine your soft lips are sucking
his penis, and he'll get excited.
Well? It tastes good, doesn't it?
Sorry!
The second best way to seduce him
is to lick his nipple.
Any guy will enjoy that feeling.
Stop it! What are you doing?!
You're acting strange today!
I'm going to bed now.
Two people living together only
have one more day left.
Kousuke!
What is it?
I stubbed my finger today while
I was playing volleyball.
I can't use both of my hands, would
you help me wash my body?
But tomorrow when your finger is
better, you can wash by yourself.
I'm a lady. I can't stay dirty. Please?
Trouble! I'm in really big trouble!
It was only a couple of days ago
that Shizuka told me she couldn't
have sex with me.
What's wrong with you?
Hurry up and wash me.
Because she has a stubbed finger, she
asked me to wash her perfect body.
Ah! You're tickling me.
I'm sorry.
My back...
Isn't all there is to my body.
But I can't do more than this.
Please?
The next best way to seduce him
is to have him wash your body.
If he's an ordinary guy, he will without
fail screw you from behind.
If I get anymore excited, I'll break
our promise not to have sex.
The washrag is hurting me. Please
wash my breasts with your bare hands.
What?!
Am I just washing her, or are we
having sex? I'm getting confused.
Kousuke, our shared life ends tonight.
Kousuke, do you like me?
You're my favorite!
Yes, I like you too.
Do you think you would like
to marry me in the future?
Marry?
Hey!
Look, look.
What's wrong with you? You haven't
been acting like yourself, Shizuka.
That's right, ever since
your dad called.
It's nothing.
Please, hurry and wash another part.
Shizuka...
Mr. Atami, trouble!
There's a fire at your front door!
Trouble! Fire!
What's that? I don't believe it.
I'm going to London a couple
of days from now.
My dad was transferred.
I am not sure if I'll have to live
in London forever.
Because...
Because of that, Kousuke...
I understand.
Damn it! Damn it!
Who the hell did this?!
The smell! It's dog shit!
I tricked you! I tricked you!
Hi! Good evening, Atami.
How are you, Kousuke Atami?
Are you getting along with her?
Jerks, what do you want?
I heard you are living with the most
beautiful girl in our school,
so I came to interrupt you.
Go for it, go for it.
Folks, thank you for waiting.
For my entire eighteen years, I haven't
paid attention to my studies,
but have dedicated myself to
learning this ultimate show.
If I am doing well, please clap for me.
Hey! Yamada!
And this, and that, and this,
that, this, that, this, that.
Well, well, I will not show you my
unmentionables for even one moment.
And this, that, this, that.
I almost showed them.
Red ball picking, picking.
And this, and that, red ball.
And next in celebration of Kousuke
and Shizuka's last day together,
I'm asking your best friend Mr. Yamada
to say a few words.
According to the Yamada Group's
secret investigation,
which thoroughly investigated
your first encounter,
thirteen years ago when
she was five years old,
her favorite parrot died and
she was so shocked,
she jumped from the
condominium's balcony.
Kousuke was walking below and he
caught Shizuka with his face.
This is the very beginning of the story.
However, only one week
after they met,
her father was transferred
and they both...
The train's door is closing now.
Please be careful.
Shizuka!
Kousuke!
For twelve years, a tremendous amount
of time, they were forced to be apart.
But the red string pulled
them together again.
Yes, everything is all right between
Kousuke and Shizuka.
Even when they will graduate,
their love will continue forever.
Soon both...
Shizuka, I will not leave you,
is that okay?
Kousuke, Shizuka is so happy!
Well, that's it. We should leave now.
Shut up! Nobody interrupt us.
Yes, yes, our love is forever.
Shizuka, can I do this?
No, Kousuke, you're a pervert.
Shizuka? Shizuka, may I come in?
Shizuka! Shizuka!
No!
Stop it! Stop it! You can't do this!
Stop it!
Shizuka, you're beautiful.
No, no, your face is
so scary, Kousuke!
Can I do this? Can I do this,
just a little?
No! Stop it!
I will not forget the happy
times with you.
My angel, Shizuka.
Kousuke...
Kikuchi?
You went back to your room in the
middle of everything, what's wrong?
Are you not getting along
with Himenogi?
I'm sorry, I misunderstood.
Shizuka will be going to London soon.
I see.
Atami! Come out, where are you?
Well, well, don't start
foreplay by yourself!
Let's go. We unwelcome
guests should leave.
It's too early!
I agree!
Come on. It's okay.
Kousuke, will you be gentle?
Finally, we are...
Well, we are soon...
...leaving.
So long, goodnight.
Atami, keep it up!
Be quiet.
What happened?
Nothing...
Kousuke, I will without fail
be back again.
Don't forget.
Then...
Then?
We'll be married.
Geez!
What is it now?
Don't forget a rubber.
Damn it!
You don't have to see us out.
I want to check to make sure
you guys really leave.
No, no, see you.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Well, we have no choice. Should we
go to the park to be voyeurs?
Nobody will come again.
I love you, Shizuka.
I love you too.
Shizuka...
No!
Please relax.
Please be gentle.
You're beautiful.
I'm embarrassed.
I love you.
Ouch!
Kousuke, I'm okay. Please come in.
Are you ready?
Good, Shizuka! This feels so good!
Kousuke...
Shizuka!
You're wonderful, Shizuka.
I'm close to coming.
I love, love, love you, Kousuke!
Kousuke!
I'm coming!
Kousuke...
Long memories end,
you were always here
Following the direction of your eye,
I'm always here
Waking up from a dream, you look
like a child as you cling to my side
There are some important things
that can't be translated into words
I will not forget your tears that
caused me to understand too
You were the only person that stayed
with me when I was depressed at night
With a true love, both people's
best wishes live
Husband, two ice coffees please!
Aye, aye!