HARDCORE HOSPITAL
FIRST CHAPTER
MOU FUJIMIYA
Dr. Date! I've been waiting for you.
She's Saeko Morishita. She'll
be your special nurse aid.
Hello, I'll be in charge of your care.
I'm Saeko Morishita. Pleased to meet you.
GREETING
SMILE
ASSERTIVENESS
ORAL SEX
Amazing. . .
It's been so long since I've gotten a hard on.
Is this the special nurse
care I keep hearing about?
Yes. Do you like it?
Of course I do. Your
thighs are such a turn on.
Your name. . . It's Saeko, right?
Y. . .yes.
Your mouth was great, but. . .
I wonder how your pussy is?
Right there. . .
What's happening with your pussy?
Saeko, answer him.
Y. . .yes. . . My. . .pussy is. . .
Mr. Fujimiya's finger is. . .rubbing
it. . .and it feels so good.
Smells wonderful. Let me have a taste.
Y. . .yes. . .
Its so big...
Your cock is so big, Mr. Fujimiya.
If only my female employees could hear you!
My body is moving on its own...
Please forgive me.
Young workers these days, they're all talk!
They have no respect for their superiors!
All they do is complain,
and they don't even work.
All they keep saying is. . .
''Sexual harassment'', ''sexual harassment''. . .
Shut up already!
This was beyond anything
I'd imagined, Doctor!
Yes, she's the best at what she does.
She used to be a nurse at
a rather big hospital, too.
No medical equipment is as effective as her.
It's an amazing system you have in place.
My company will fully sponsor you.
Thank you very much. Our company
also does pharmaceutical research.
This medicine makes men
invincible. I guarantee an effect. . .
. . .that can't be matched by
other pharmaceutical products.
Well, it's not approved yet, but. . .
I see. . .
I developed this medicine. Let
me put it on you myself. . .
This is amazing! I feel like I'm full of energy!
Let me put some on your Saeko.
She'll be dying for more. Come on.
D-doctor. . .
But. . .
Nooo!
Well? How is our medicine working?
I can't believe how well it works.
Mr. Fujiyama.
Are you ready?
Saeko cums instantly when
she gets fucked in both holes.
See how her pussy is begging for you?
Of course, her ass is very skilled too.
Please go ahead and take your pick.
But Saeko actually likes it the best when. . .
Yes, I like it the best when
someone cums inside of me.
Take me, please.
It's amazing! I can feel you inside of me!
Yes! I'm gonna. . .
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Works marvelously.
He's going to fuck every hole.
I'm going to cum! Cum inside of me!
I want your hot cum. . . All of it. . . All of it. . .
As you wish! Here I cum!
I just came, but it's still so
hard that it's almost vertical!
Might as well keep going
and fuck you up the ass.
But I have no medicine on there. . .
I'm going to go crazy. . .
1 0 million dollars. . . Humans
are such funny creatures. . .
Praise the ''Special Nurse'', huh?
Knock before you come in.
Sorry, Director.
I hate being called that.
Then why don't you quit being director?
What to do. . .
My father wants to know when the
next special nurse will be ready.
This is supposed to be
a respectable hospital. . .
We need to do official business too!
Well, comparatively this is easier
than getting involved with...
...who's the next director at
my father's hospital, but. . .
Rich boy.
Being the successor of a big hospital
brings a lot of hardship, you know.
I don't believe it.
That I'm the successor, or
that I have a lot of hardship?
Both. . .perhaps. . .
No. . .
This medicine is working too
well. We have patients to tend to.
No. . . No! Don't stop now! More! I want more!
Fine. . .
W. . .why are you. . . That's. . .
I like tight asses. I have an ass fetish.
Doctor! You're going to break me. . .
What do you think about
a virgin's pussy juice?
We'll stimulate the virgin's
asshole and give the patient. . .
. . .the pussy juice that comes out.
But nowadays, they're all whores.
You're the one who likes to fuck the
virgins and make them into women.
You're right about that.
Ah. . . Not yet!
Its time. I have to go. Sorry.
I'm sorry!
Doctor. . .
What are you doing? Hurry and clean it up.
Right!
I'm sorry. We'll have to start
five minutes later than planned.
Okay. . . I'm counting on you. Who is she?
It's Sayaka's third day. She's very
hasty and makes a lot of mistakes.
I'm finished!
Hurry up and ready new ones!
S. . .sorry!
Are you getting used to this?
I'm so sorry!
No. . .I'm sorry for startling you.
I don't think I'm meant to be a nurse.
My mother was a nurse, and I wanted
to be one ever since I was little.
It's not an easy job, and it was lonely when. . .
. . .my mother couldn't be home
much after my father's death, but. . .
. . .I think the fact that she was
saving lives encouraged us.
I was so proud of her, but she passed
away three months ago from her illness.
My dream is to become a nurse just like her.
Dr. Date. Please come to the ER immediately.
A patient that was in a car
accident has just been carried in.
Dr. Date?
OPERATING
You're late, Sayaka! What took you so long!
I'm sorry.
What are you. . . Sayaka?
Masahiko!
Dr. Date...
Is Masahiko. . . Is Mr. Honda
going to be all right?
I can't say for sure, but I did my best.
Unless he's extremely unlucky, he'll be fine.
Is he your boyfriend?
We were childhood friends.
He just got his license. . .
I bet he got in an accident because
he wanted to surprise me.
How long have you been dating him?
He told me how he felt the
day before I came here, so. . .
. . .we've only been dating four days.
No wonder your boyfriend drove the
way he did. His brain is in his dick!
No, it's not like that! We
haven't done anything. . .
Oh?
Well. . . Um. . .
My mother was really strict, so. . .
My friends kid around and say I
should be a national treasure. . .
I'm still a virgin. . .
Virgin love juice.
Nothing. I understand you're very
concerned about your boyfriend.
I'll have to discuss some more
serious matters with you, then.
Let's go to my room.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
You'll have to amputate his leg?
Isn't there anything you can do, Doctor?
We did an emergency operation,
but that's all we can do here.
The general hospital will have to
do the rest, but at this rate. . .
But. . . Masahiko. . .
But, there is one possibility. . .
What's that?
If I operate on him, I think I could
avoid having to amputate his leg.
But with our set up and technology. . .
Yeah, we can't do it here. We'd have
to do it at my father's hospital.
Have you ever heard of
Date General Hospital?
Yeah, there. We have a lot going
on, so we can't make this public.
AIso, you have to do me a favor in return.
A favor?
Yes. You'll be a Special Nurse.
A Special Nurse?
Yes, I want you to become a Special Nurse.
Special Nurses need to be hard workers,
and be able to keep their mouths shut.
Will you save Masahiko's leg
if I become a special nurse?
I'll do it! No, I'll do my best to become one!
I see. Then sign this.
Let's start your Special Nurse training.
What are you doing, Doctor?
Why do we have this, when we
don't have a gynecology office?
Sayaka, you were thoughtless. . .
Didn't you wonder why you were
going to be called a ''Special Nurse''?
No. . .
A Special Nurse's duty is to take
care of the patient's sexual needs.
You'll need to learn how
to satisfy the patients.
This might be hard for you
because you're a virgin, but...
No! I don't want to! I can't do that!
Please untie me! Please, Doctor!
I didn't know what a Special Nurse was. . .
If I knew, I wouldn't have agreed to do it!
Then I'm not obligated to keep
my promise about Masahiko. . . .
But. . . That's. . .
Caring for a patient's sexual
needs is important too. . .
Masahiko. . .
Well? What are you going to do, Sayaka?
Please operate on Masayuki. I'll do it.
Oh, you've never kissed anyone
either. Too bad for Masahiko.
Masahiko. . .
No! Stop! N. . .no. . .
You have no pubic hair.
Were you embarrassed?
Is that the reason you've never had sex?
No, don't say that!
That's fine. It's cute. Your pussy is so cute.
Ouch. . . Please don't pinch it. . .
You're a virgin, so you're not
feeling it. . . How about. . .
You feel it when I touch your
breasts. How do you masturbate?
I don't masturbate! I've
never touched my privates!
You're such a liar. You know you have. See?
You're getting wet.
You're lying. That can't be. . .
Amazing! It's a miracle!
How does it feel to have
someone else see you naked?
No. . . Stop it. . . Please let
me put on my clothes.
You don't understand, do you?
Lips, nipples and the vagina
are sensitive openings...
...and are made to feel pleasure.
Let me pay special attention to down here.
What's going on? This can't be. . .
I think I'm going to go crazy. . .
But that's. . . Please stop! Not there!
No! No! You can't. . .
There it goes!
Please...stop!
Let's try one that has more girth.
Relax. . . Or else you're going to bleed.
No!
No! It went in. . .
I still have a lot of different
sizes. I'll loosen it up over time.
Nooo!
OPERATING
Okay! A four centimeter one went in!
It hurts. . . I'm going to break. . .
Amazing. What an impressive asshole!
It's your first time, but you took
the dildo in without any blood.
It goes back to its normal shape no
matter how wide I spread it. Next is. . .
No. . . Please. . .
Let's see. . . You're nice and loose
now, so let's go for the real thing.
No! Don't come near me!
No. . . Masahiko. . .
I could fuck you easily in the pussy. . .
I'll save it for your precious man.
But your ass is mine.
No! I'm going to break if
you stick that in! Stop!
It's coming in! It's so big!
It's coming into my butt. . .
What an interesting situation.
I'm fucking a virgin up her ass while
her boyfriend is hospitalized here.
No!
Swallow it.
Good job. I'll give you a reward.
I'll clean our insides with
this every day from now on.
This isn't normal. . .
NURSE'S LOCKER ROOM
Jeez! You need to concentrate
more. You keep screwing up.
Sayaka!
Ichijiku Enema. . . Sayaka. . . Are you. . .
Give her a break.
You've guessed it.
She's started her training just like
you, to become a Special Nurse.
That can't be. . . Sayaka?
Saeko?
According to Sayaka...
...it's not normal to feel pleasure
getting fucked in the ass.
As her superior you should show her.
But. . . Not in front of
Sayaka. . . No! Please, Doctor!
Doctor. . . No. . . It feels so good. . .
Come on Saeko, tell Sayaka about it. . .
I'm getting fucked in my
pussy and my ass and. . .no. . .
I feel like I'm going to go insane.
Saeko. . .
Sayaka, Saeko's having trouble cumming.
Give her a hand.
Touch her where you liked
it the most last night.
Yes. . .
No!
I'm going to cum. Nooo!
Saeko. . .
Saeko!
Morning.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Today's my first day on the job.
My name is Minako Kisaragi.
Nice to meet you.
Good morning.
Good morning!