Hi, I'm the president of Date
GeneraI HospitaI. I'm Ryuichi Date.
Is your idea of a hospitaI a
pIace just fiIIed with medicine?
Tsk. Tsk. Tsk. ActuaIIy, it's not.
The scent of other peopIe. . .
There's no better pIace to smeII. . .
. . .the scent of a woman, than at a hospitaI.
What? ''Isn't a hospitaI a sacred
pIace where Iives are on the Iine?''
OPERATING
What? ''Isn't a hospitaI a sacred
pIace where Iives are on the Iine?''
ExactIy.
Excitement, tension and the constant
battIe to restrain your urges. . .
When you are reIeased, your body
submits to Iust over and over. . .
As the pIeasure juice oozes down your. . .
Without further ado, I'd Iike
to introduce our new nurse.
I'm Minako Kisaragi.
HARDCORE HOSPITAL
FINAL CHAPTER
It's been two years since I've
worked at a hospitaI, but. . .
My passion as a nurse hasn't Ieft me.
Nice to meet you. I hope we
get to know each other weII.
Wow. . .
PIeased to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I want you
and Sayaka to work together. . .
. . .under Saeko, untiI you
get used to this pIace.
Yes sir.
Nice to meet you. I'm Minako.
Nice to meet you too. I'm
Sayaka, and I'm new here too.
You can chit chat Iater. Let me
show you around. FoIIow me.
Sayaka! You too!
S. . .sorry!
Good morning, Dr. Date.
You're a wiId woman when you get fucked.
How is the medicine you deveIoped working?
It's so amazing. . . Even
my fingers get numb. . .
I doubt any woman couId resist this medicine.
You are such a pervert.
You're the compIete opposite of
the new hire from this morning.
What a terribIe thing to say.
Minako Kisaragi. . . She
used to be married, right?
ReaIIy?
It's peopIe Iike her who are reaIIy wiId in bed.
I heard she's a widow, but I
wonder if she masturbates...
...to her dead husband?
DarIing. . . DarIing. . . My
pussy misses you so much. . .
See? Look how much it misses you. . .
Oh my goodness! It's so
much bigger than before!
Why did you Ieave me, after
making me so hot for you. . .
It's so big! It's so big! I know I'm acting
Iike this because of the medicine, but. . .
Oh, not that. . . No. . .
Doctor. . .
No! Don't stop! I want you to cum! More! More!
You're so naughty. . .
A weII endowed widow's masturbation, eh?
Today's my first day. I'm Minako
Kisaragi. Nice to meet you.
I never asked to get such
big breasts, you know!
She's so Iucky. I wish
mine were a IittIe bigger.
Good morning. It's time
to take your temperature.
Hiroshi, your sheets are a mess.
Let me fix it. . . Excuse me.
That's. . .
Oh, I'm sorry.
I won't teII the other nurses...
...so make sure you hide it
somewhere better, okay?
Don't be ashamed. It means you're heaIthy.
I didn't think guys Iike him
wouId read those things. . .
Sayaka, what are you doing?
Sorry!
You're stiII making a Iot of mistakes.
A SpeciaI Nurse isn't just a nurse.
You have to be abIe to sexuaIIy
reIieve the patients as a pro.
If you can't be a nurse, you're mereIy a sIut!
On another note. . . What's your excuse?
Didn't I teII you to give
yourseIf an enema every day?
But I can't do it myseIf. . .
I'm too embarrassed.
Then it's okay if other peopIe give it to you?
Wait! That's not what I meant. . .
No!
I can't fit anymore. . . PIease, no more! Stop!
My stomach. . .
It's going to break. . . My
stomach is going to. . .
Don't worry, that was nothing.
You'd be surprised how much can go in.
The probIem is from this point on. . .
See?
D. . . Doctor. . . Bathroom. . . PIease
Iet me go to the bathroom. I can't. . .
I can't hoId it anymore. . . PIease, Doctor. . .
PIease undo the rope and chains. . .
If you want to go to the
bathroom, make me cum first.
That's right. That's right. Good, Sayaka.
What do you think of my cock?
Say it! TeII me exactIy what you're thinking!
It's so bumpy. . . The veins are
popping out and. . . It's hard, and. . .
Doctor. . . PIease, Iet me go. . .
I'II do anything, so. . . What
do I. . . What do I have to do?
Just sucking it back and
forth isn't going to do it.
Stick my cock in your mouth aII the way.
It's so nice to see a hard-working gaI. . .
PIease. . . I beg you. . . I think
I'm going to go insane.
PIease Iet me go to the bathroom. PIease. . .
Sure, might as weII unpIug
you and Iet you go.
Go ahead. Take a dump in there.
But this isn't. . . You said earIier
I couId go to the bathroom!
Did I?
I encouraged you because you wanted
to go, but I never said you couId.
You're terribIe! Liar! You're a Iiar, Doctor!
No! I can't hoId it anymore!
Nooo! Don't Iook at me!
Just three days ago, you stiII hadn't
kissed a boy; and Iook at you now.
You're a virgin, but I've given you an
enema and I've seen you take a shit.
Maybe I was a IittIe too harsh on you.
But there's no time to reIax!
Here comes number two!
But. . . You can't. . .
No! No! No! PIease, no more!
This is. . . This is terribIe. . .
No more, pIease!
It's cIean now.
This is aII your fauIt, for not
giving yourseIf enemas.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's finaIIy over. . .
No. . .
We've onIy just begun.
But. . .You promised. . .
Who promised?
Raw ass action is great.
It's swoIIen and it's nice and tight.
No! No!
That's it. . . I'm impressed
how much energy you have.
You're reaIIy great!
I toId you just moving back
and forth isn't going to cut it.
You shouId know what to do.
Yes! That's it! You've finaIIy got it, Sayaka!
It's necessary for a nurse to have
a change of attitude Iike this.
You feeI so good, Sayaka.
Your body is so amazing...
it makes me so horny.
I can't beIieve you've never been with a man.
You just tightened up a Iot.
You aImost made me cum.
By the way...
...did you know there's something
Iike a hyman in the ass, too?
If I can't fuck your pussy. . . I know
your boyfriend's in the hospitaI, but. . .
Doctor. . .
You'II enjoy getting it up the ass
soon enough. Don't be scared.
I'II give you a feeIing you've never feIt before.
I don't want it! What are you
going to do now? HeIp, Masahiko!
No! No! Don't move! No!
Why?
I don't know. . . But this isn't. . .
That was great. I couId go for another one.
I'm exhausted, what a
workout. She's sucked me dry.
No, this isn't right. . .Hiroshi.
Why did you stop?
Dr. Date! How Iong have you been there?
There's no need to stop. Stop
using that test tube and use this.
It's smaII, but it sure moves a Iot.
What are you doing?
I figure this is a good opportunity to
see how weII you can resist things.
When you puII this string, the
buzzer in Sayaka's room wiII ring.
Knowing how hard she works...
...she'II come running here no matter what.
So, where shouId I start, Minako?
PIease stop.
My breasts. . . My breasts. . . No, I'm feeIing it.
You just rang it. Who knows
when Sayaka wiII burst in.
Doctor! PIease Iet me go!
I don't want Sayaka to see me Iike this!
No. . . Hiroshi. . . Why?
You toId me you had the night shift, so. . .
I was coming to say hi. . .
Don't Iook at me, Hiroshi! Don't Iook at me!
You're doing this to Minako too? Why?
Hey! Took you Iong enough.
You want to join in, right?
Sayaka, you've stiII got a Iot
to Iearn, but you have taIent.
Your taIent is that you're abIe to
sacrifice yourseIf to heIp others.
That's what's necessary to
be a nurse. Understand?
Sayaka. . . Hiroshi aIready came three
times, but he's stiII fuII of energy.
PIease. . . HeIp me out. . .
Minako. . . I. . . I can't stop. I can't stop!
Come on, Sayaka!
There's a patient who's in
need of a SpeciaI Nurse! Go!
I understand.
I'm Sayaka Ogata, who wiII
be giving you speciaI care.
I'II care for you with aII my heart.
It feeIs so good. Doctor!
Yes. Yes. I know.
Minako! I'm going to cum again!
Hiroshi! Cum! Cum aII over my tits!
Amazing. There is no other
treatment better than this.
MedicaI treatment just isn't
enough. Don't you agree, father?
Is she ready? Is she just as father requested?