We're currently at 1.5 million yen.
Will anyone raise?
Yes, we have 1.51 million.
Anyone else?
Sold to number 146.
Congratulations!
Please don't do this!
Let me go home!
Well, see you at the next auction! Good bye!
Good bye!
Virgin Auction Vol. 1
This is how l show my love.
l've been tied up for over 8 hours...
Excuse me, Shirohebi-san...
But what are you doing?
l thought l might give you a reward.
Well, that's a rare treat...
Did you say something?
No, l'm very happy.
l thought so.
You've given me so much love already.
Why are you grinning?
lt's nothing.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Shirohebi-san...
Shirohebi-san?
Did you think l was going to kiss you?
No, of course not.
Now...
Don't make me laugh so much.
But if you arouse me like that...
Don't make such disgusting noises!
l'm trying not to but...
Are you dissatisfied?
What is it? Tell me!
l don't want you to stop.
l can't hear you!
Please do it!
What do you want me to do?
Shiroheb-san, you're such a...
Well?
Say it?
Well, l want you to press your foot against my cock...
...use your toes and play with my glands...
...grab my cock with your feet and go up and down...
l don't want to hear such roundabout things!
Just tell me what you really want!
Well, in other words, l want you to give me a footjob.
Why didn't you say so from the beginning?
Honesty is the greatest virtue.
l can't believe you got hard from this...
You're really a masochist.
l can't help it...
lf you do things like that, anyone would...
You're getting real sticky from your clear cowper's juice...
You can't deny it right?
Admit that you come from a line of masochists.
lf you don't, l'll have to stop doing this.
lt's not like l have to play with your dirty cock.
Yes. l'm a masochist, just like you said.
l can't hear you!
She heard me all right, she's so mean.
Yes, l'll admit that l'm a masochist!
So please keep going!
l feel sorry for the descendants of the guy who came up with Cowper's juice.
l'm sure they're getting picked on.
Hey, your grandpa is Mr. Cowper, right?
How did he come up with the term?
By playing with his cock?
Shirohebi-san...
You're really into this.
lf you bend your toes like that...
She looks lovely when she's focused.
She really loves me.
You're rebellious.
Shirohebi-san, even l have some pride too.
Don't spit it out.
l know it's mixed with her saliva but...
And how did it feel to taste your juice for the first time?
lt tastes bitter.
Very good.
Lick it.
Don't you spill a drop.
Yes.
Your crotch area looks very lively.
Shirohebi-san, you're going too fast...
Don't climax yet.
lf you climax before l tell you to, you know what will happen, right?
Shirohebi-san, you're grinding too fast.
You're not making it easy on me.
Unbelievable...
You're such a worthless guy!
Shirohebi-san! lf you do it that hard, l'll come!
Yes!
You gutless punk!
You'll last longer like this, right?
You're gonna torture me like this?
Shirohebi-san, let me come.
lf l don't, l think l'll go insane.
Hang in there a little more.
Just a little more...
Shirohebi-san...
Good morning.
Usually women are the ones who lose consciousness.
You're such a wimp.
That's not a nice thing to say.
l'll let you off the hook since you did pretty good this time.
Even though you don't have that much stamina...
...you're awfully confident.
As a slave, you belong in the lowest rank and...
Hey, are you listening to me?
You need me to do something right?
How did you know?
lf you didn't need my help, you wouldn't come to me after having sex.
Don't get carried away!
Yes, l'm sorry.
Now, what can l do for you?
Those girls will be arriving soon, right?
What do you have on them?
Oh, you mean those girls...
Then...
Well, look what we got.
They're looking real good.
Shirohebi-san sure knows her stuff.
Which girl does she like most...
l'm sure they told you about this, but...
...you'll be staying here until the auction starts.
That's roughly 2 weeks.
Are you the manager?
Did you hear that, manager?
l'm the manager Rongai Shijima.
l was hired for this position.
Now this is Shirohebi Sukamu.
She's involved, but she serves a different purpose.
This is all safe right?
l mean, we're gonna be okay, right?
Yes, of course.
lt's just like any other sex service out there.
l see.
You probably know this since you'll all be auctioned.
You don't need to use your real names here.
l'll give you names for the auction.
First off...
You will be named Yukina, since your skin is white.
Next...
You're Umi since you're big.
Gin!
Your hair's silver too, so it's good, right?
You're just naming them the first thing you see.
lt's easy to learn, right?
l guess you're right.
You're free to use this living room, bedroom, shower, and bathroom.
You can use any appliance in the room as well.
You may eat whenever you like.
We'll pay for the food, so you can get anything you want.
But you can't enter our rooms.
Obviously, you can't go outside, either.
lf you can't follow these rules, you never know what will happen.
Oh...
l see.
Shirohebi-san? l would like to know their personal info, too.
They already told you about them, right?
They say l'm kind and too sympathetic towards the girls...
...so they won't give me any info on them.
They certainly know what they're doing.
Well, it's not that you're kind, you just get carried away.
You're not kind.
ln fact, you probably don't have any feelings at all.
Please don't refer to me like some kind of heartless beast.
lf we know more about the girls...
lt makes things much easier for both the buyers and the sellers.
That's not the kind of words l expect from a guy...
...who enjoys getting stomped on by me.
She's very tough on me.
But then again that's...
Well, what have we here?
What is it?
l got this info from someone l know.
Not even our superiors know about this.
Oh no, Shirohebi-san...
lsn't this illegal?
Don't get all worked up.
This is gonna get interesting.
Shirohebi-san, you're hurting me.
Don't tell the bosses about this.
l understand.
Shouldn't we introduce ourselves?
We're going to be living together for 2 weeks, you know...
Did l say something wrong?
You speak fluent Japanese for a foreigner.
Don't you think so?
Yes, you're right.
l'm sorry about that.
lt's just that you were much better than we expected.
Oh, l see.
Since my Japanese was so good...
You girls were very surprised.
Well since l brought it up, l'll introduce myself first.
l may look like a foreigner on the outside...
But my father is Japanese.
He deserted me and my mother.
You don't have to feel sorry for me.
l don't consider him to be my father at all.
And why are you here?
Why? Oh, you mean the reason why l'm here?
ln order to get revenge.
That's why l need the money.
His job is to trick people. He's a swindler.
l just can't wait for him to go to hell.
Anyway, why are you here for this auction?
Well, it's a bit more complicated.
l actually had a fiance.
Uh-huh.
His father had lots of debt and...
What's wrong?
l'm sorry. l lost control of myself.
Were you sent here to pay back his debts?
Oh my god!
Are you telling me she got a guy who's good-for-nothing at her age?
Umi-san, you're a very beautiful Japanese girl.
These girls...
By the way, why are you here?
l don't really have much to say.
Don't worry about it. l'll tell you one of these days.
You made us talk all this time. lt's not fair!
One week later
Wake up kitties!
lt's time to examine your hymen.
Also known as rock-n-roll time!
This foreigner doesn't look different down here.
Shirohebi-sensei...
Can't you just tell by looking at it once?
Shirohebi-sama.
What?
Call me master.
l understand.
But what l'm talking about is...
This is my hobby.
lf you interrupt me, you'll receive cruel treatment.
That tickles.
You're not very sensitive.
This is why l hate virgins.
This is good.
Usually women who are very physical like yourself...
...tend to get their hymen torn.
Then you'll be worth nothing as an auction item.
l don't really care about that.
But there are idiots out there who need the hymen intact.
And that's why this stupid business is profitable.
Please, stop touching me down there.
Did you have a boyfriend?
Even though you didn't have sex, you guys did touch each other, right?
Actually, that's not the only thing we did.
Oh come on.
We're pretty much married.
But...
Please!
But you promised that we'd avoid sex until we're officially married.
Can we change that?
l know you can use your mouth.
l'm coming...
lt smells bad...
Hey, we got this far. Let's just do it.
But...
But look how big it's gotten!
What are you doing?
l'm sorry Umi.
But l was nice enough to do it in your ass.
No, it hurts...
No!
lt hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
That's what happened.
lt wasn't just once was it?
We did it every two days or so.
Then he became addicted to it.
l saw him and became so worried...
You really don't have any luck with the opposite sex.
What?
Since he was obsessed about sex, l was just doing him a favor.
Whatever.
But l'll tell you one thing.
Even if you pay off his debts and return to him...
He will leave you.
Or he'll become a pimp.
That can't be...
l'm 100% sure.
Okay, your examination is over.
Go and get me Yuki-chan.
Hey, hurry up and do the examination.
You know something?
What?
Those who lie will get punished severely.
No, it smells bad.
lf l'm covered with this much juice, l can't get rid of the stench.
No!
Why are you doing this?
You fooled us!
You lied to us!
You're not a virgin!
That's not true!
There's some kind of a mistake!
You'll know if they investigate!
No, no, no, no!
Please stop!
l'll do anything!
Please let me go!
Pull it out!
l'm begging you!
No!