Virgin Auction Vol. 2
She's not responding.
Did we mess her up?
No, take a look at her face.
She's in heaven.
That's what's gonna happen.
Well, l'm done.
Don't use me to create your delusions.
Then how about this?
Why?
l'll be nice.
l won't take away your virginity.
lt hurts!
Pull it out!
My cock just went into your ass, of course it hurts.
Let me go, let me go!
What did l ever do to you?
How the hell should l know?
All l know is, you were in my way.
l'm gonna release it.
No, stop it!
Anything but that!
No!
Well? Looks fun doesn't it?
How?
Don't worry.
l'll treat you real nice.
What's wrong with you all?
Today's not the end of the world you know.
Umi.
Think of this as a way to cut ties with your fiance.
lt's up to you to take advantage of this opportunity.
There are many people out there who suffered because of their pimp.
Compared to them, you still have a chance to start over, right?
Gin, you are...
You should pray to god that you'll be bought by bidder number 3.
Unfortunately l'm not like you folks.
l don't have any god to pray to.
You're very kind today.
Be quiet, stupid.
Hey!
l need to speak to her in private.
Shirohebi-san, we don't have much time.
Make it quick.
l know.
Just leave us.
Rongai is like a dog.
You're right.
Shirohebi-san, what happened?
She escaped.
Are you okay, Shirohebi-san?
l'm sorry for troubling you.
That's all right.
lt's the provider's fault for not giving us a decent girl.
l'm sorry, we have some business to attend to.
l'm sure our replacements are gonna get here soon.
Just go with them.
Bye.
We have really good items for you today!
Plus one of the two is very rare!
We'll start off with item number one.
Let's get this thing started!
ltem number one will go to bidder number 271!
Now, for item number two...
Wow, this is amazing!
We've never seen this kind of money for an item!
Plus he's the highest bidder!
lt's not the right way to bid on an auction.
But it's okay.
Sold to bidder number 3!
The person who bought you resides here...
l'm counting on you.
You're finally here...
Don't just stand there, come on in.
l told you to come in!
l am your master!
l can't see where l'm going.
lt's too dark in here...
You shouldn't talk back to me.
Are we there yet?
l'm getting tired.
This is our master's room.
You're finally here.
l was getting tired of waiting.
You're much cuter than in the photo.
My spiritual powers will grow stronger with a girl like you.
Good job in finding a girl like this.
Thank you.
Now, let's begin our ritual.
Yes.
You don't have to be nervous.
l can even make you my court lady if you want.
Your job is to participate in this ritual twice a day.
Simple, isn't it?
Anyway, l'm a generous man.
Well?
l'm sure you came here in search of work, right?
Umm...
You don't have to be that nervous.
This is nothing religious.
This is completely sound, it's a secular act.
l pay you money, and you provide me with the service in exchange.
l'm assuming your country doesn't have that kind of a system...
l don't need anymore explanations!
l'll just do whatever you say!
Thank you so much.
Now do it.
lt's sweet.
lt's so sweet.
The secret for eternal life is definitely the golden shower of a virgin!
Umi. Think of this as a way to cut ties with your fiance.
What's the matter?
Hurry up and take your clothes off.
People who stay indoors all day have no strength at all.
What are you gonna do?
Well, it looks like you're very clean.
Since your hair is all over the place, l thought you never take a shower.
Wait a minute.
Did you take a shower just because l was coming?
What are you doing?
l'm your master.
What are you saying?
Listen up.
Your brain is all soggy because you've been a NEET for so long.
l'll explain things nice and slow so you can understand.
You only bought me for sex just this once.
And you think you're my master?
You gotta be kidding me!
Even if it's my first time, you can't do me right!
You thought that if you could do it with a virgin...
...she wouldn't reprove your inexperienced cock.
But l've taken it up the ass so many times...
ln other words, l'm an anal master!
l was able to change.
Thank you Shirohebi-san!
l'm a virgin, just like you said.
ln school, they always called me ugly.
They forced me to take off my pants and masturbate in front of girls.
So l thought l could change if l had sex.
l'm sorry for doing this.
l'm sorry.
Could this be...
You wanna do it with me?
Your cock looks good.
Sorry for calling you inexperienced before.
l'll guide you, so you don't have to worry.
lf you move that much, l'll come.
Umm, how can you do that?
l mean, you're a virgin, right?
My fiance deceived me.
l was forced to do lots of unpleasant things.
So l thought it wouldn't be bad to do you.
Was your fiance a bad guy?
Yeah.
l don't even know why l liked him in the first place.
Anyway, it looks like you're still good down there.
You wanna continue?
Yeah.
You can stay where you are.
You don't know where to stick it in right?
Are you okay?
Leave it to me.
lt hurts, but it's not bad.
Yes, yes!
Your ass is great!
Finish quickly, finish quickly, please!
Back then, l had to tolerate him doing it up the ass.
Do you want to release it?
Try to hold it in.
l want to enjoy it since it's my first time too.
l'm coming, l'm coming...
l'm coming!
l think l'm gonna climax too...
l didn't think l'd see you here.
l guess this is what god wanted.
lt's been a while, my daughter.
You're still doing these childish acts.
Don't hate me so much.
You made mother's life miserable!
Well, l really feel sorry for what l did.
Many things have happened since then.
l became second in command of this organization.
l think the master really likes you.
Can you believe a Philistine like him is in charge here?
Here's the thing.
lf you cooperate with me, this organization will be mine.
Listen up.
This organization has two million followers nation wide.
lts overall assets are about 10 trillion yen.
We're not very well known to the outside world...
...but we'll eventually control this nation.
This can all be ours.
Aren't you excited about this?
ls that all you have to say?
What?
lf you were sorry about what you did, l would've let you go.
You're so stupid, father.
You're trying to make a profit by using a religious organization.
You should go to hell.
Since you're so stupid and l feel pity for you...
l'm gonna let you live.
l think l need to punish you more.
That's much better.
Hey...
l mean, if you don't mind...
What?
l want to see you again.
Are we meeting as lovers this time?
lt's not like that!
l just feel that l need a person that scolds me like you do.
l'll try to go back to school to think about our future.
lt's kind of a weird thing to say but l have money, so...
lf you're doing this since you're troubled with money...
l can help you out.
What should l do?
Hey, did you transfer the money?
lf l don't get the money by tomorrow, l'll be in deep trouble.
lt's not like you're gonna die.
Stop calling me about such stupid things!
lf you want to marry me, go take care of your father's debts on your own.
Don't ever call me again.
Hey! What are you saying...
Now, where were we?
Rongai.
You shouldn't take your job too easily.
l didn't take it easily at all.
l'll admit we underestimated them.
But don't you think you should be much tougher judging the girls?
We don't want to be in charge of security.
You're never at a loss for words.
You're a pretty stubborn guy.
l'm honored.
l see.
lf we won't suffer any losses, you can keep doing what you do.
Just tell her not to do anything outrageous.
And what are you gonna do to me?
ls anybody here?
lf you're trespassing, you'll be in deep trouble.
l suggest you leave immediately.
What are you doing, Shirohebi-san?
Can't you tell?
l'm having fun with her.
Why is she here? l thought she ran away.
And why did you leave the hospital?
Didn't you know l was just acting my part?
You know l faked my injury.
And what about Yuki-chan?
l bought her.
She said she doesn't have any other place to go.
You're so dumb.
l'm only gonna explain this once.
You know that Yuki-chan has a disease right?
l'll start off with why a virgin like Yuki-chan got that disease.
To make it short, it was because she was raped in the ass.
As a result, she caught the disease.
And her parents...
lt happens all the time, but...
They thought she brought shame to the family.
Since Yuki-chan was full of despair, what she chose to do was...
...to take revenge on the world that made her life miserable.
ln other words, people that sell and buy virgins at auctions should go to hell.
l don't care what happens to those guys.
But if we deal with them, this cute-looking Yuki-chan will be gone forever.
Now that would be a great loss, wouldn't it?
That's why l had to play some tricks.
Tricks?
You could've just handed them the money before the auction began.
At the time, we already said there would be 3 girls right?
lf we made a move, the organization would've looked down upon us.
Then the injuries l sustained were all for nothing.
Don't be mad.
l'll let you take out your anger on the ones that raped Yuki-chan.
Why do l have to do such a thing?
Yuki-chan and l reached an agreement.
We'll buy Yuki-chan and take care of the ones that raped her.
Right?
Yes.
That's all there is.
l'm gonna get it on with Yuki-chan now.
l'm very kind so you can keep watching if you like.
No, l don't want that.
You never said someone will be watching us.
But it's more exciting this way, right?
You're too cute.
Plus you're not an idiot like him.
Aren't you gonna get the disease by doing that?
Now why would l catch a disease?
Yuki-chan, you're getting very sensitive.
No, don't say that.
You don't need to be embarrassed.
lt's a sign that you're actually getting over that terrible event.
Shirohebi-san isn't serious at all.
Now let me see your cute face.
l think l'm...
l think l'm gonna climax too, you wanna climax together?
Ok then...
Don't be mad.
lt's okay.
l'll just sit here and think.
Like be worried or pretend to protect you...
l guess it's because l'm stupid.
Don't get sulky.
Your cock is so big.
You were excited by watching us, right?
Stop it, Shirohebi-san.
Since you did a good job this time, l'll do it nice and easy.
l'm sorry l can't use my hands.
Since it's a 69, l really want to pleasure you.
l'm only doing this once!
You get carried away when l'm nice to you.
Shirohebi-san, if you move that much l'll...
Hey you released too much!
l'm sorry, l guess l had too much inside me.
Don't get carried away!
You don't have to move.
Actually, don't move at all.
l'll do whatever l like.
You're not doing it nice and slow.
lt's your fault.
l'm sorry.
So they're doing each other all the time.
But l guess Shirohebi-san is in charge.
l'm getting wet.
l'm getting excited by watching others do it.
l think l'm about to climax.
Me too, Shirohebi-san.
Now, let's get back to work.
Rongai.
Before the other girls get here make sure to do the things l told you.
Yes.
And Yuki-chan...
Yes?
You shouldn't be masturbating on your own.
You can just join us for a threesome next time.
Oh brother...
l really hate doing things like this.
l just want to look at the virgins that come in...
With Shirohebi-san quietly by my side.