Shoujo Koakuma Kei
#Anime-Legion@Immortal-Anime.net
Hey, what the hell is going on?
My god, that's my car!
Jesus Christ!
This is my parking spot, damn it!
Hey, who is that woman?
Good, she's driving the Porsche.
What do you mean?
Most of the time, she drives her Land Cruiser.
About the arrangement...
Please sign your check first.
It's still light outside.
I've made proper arrangements.
Wait a minute!
It had better not be the woman with the Porsche!
I see, she's a very pretty girl.
Yes, but she won't be attending your needs today.
You requested...
A girl that looks very young, I remember.
No, this girl will be just fine.
Youri, please take the gentleman to his room.
Please...
That little prick, what the fuck does he know?
So, you don't party with clients here?
My position here is to escort
clients to their rooms, that's all.
He's making a fool out of me.
So you follow his orders?
Yes, he is my boss.
I want another girl.
You can't do that.
I'm the client here!
Have a good day.
Can't you be more diplomatic, dear?
I'm sorry!
But...
I...
Your job may not be to fuck him, but
there's no need to piss clients off.
I just started here today.
This is a business.
Don't go wrecking it.
I'm sorry.
So, do you want a different girl?
No!
This is wonderful!
Are you sure, daddy?
Well, then you own me an apology!
I'm sorry!
That's kind of boring.
You can bark like dog!
What?
Bark like a dog?
Sir, I know you have a fetish for young girls.
If you want to fuck a little girl...
you can kiss your life goodbye.
What the...
Okay doggie, I'm commanding you to sit!
Look at him.
You're doing it wrong!
That's too wimpy!
Can't you bark like a fierce bulldog?
Bulldog?
I'm not sure that I can.
Shut up and just do it!
Is this room for watching clients?
It's for safety.
And possibly an asset, for us.
Hey, daddy!
Should I remove these?
No, please leave them on!
My shoes?
Those little girl's shoes turn me on like crazy.
Pervert!
Yeah, keep calling me names!
Gross, you have a sick fetish!
What a weirdo!
You're a pervert!
Don't look!
You're really built like a girl.
I thought...
that was exactly what you requested!
Yeah, I prefer bodies like yours,
because it looks like a little girl's.
I prefer innocent little girls that
haven't been corrupted by other men.
No!
So?
How is it watching other people fuck?
I don't...
She's about to give a blow job.
No, don't cum so quickly!
You're very skilled at sucking cock!
I'm sorry, I'm a dirty girl.
A dirty girl.
The funny crap that comes out
of that girl's mouth is amazing!
What's wrong, am I hurting you?
Yeah, we'll you're going to
have to take it, sweetheart.
It hurts!
You're tearing my pussy apart!
Yeah baby, take that!
Daddy, your cock is so huge!
My god, it's so thick, I can't handle it!
That other girl...
Does she attend to clients like you do?
Answer me!
I don't know.
Why don't you know?
I met her for the first time today!
Hear that?
Clients are interested in you.
So, what are you doing here?
Kyouichi refuses to tell me who
you are, or what you're doing here.
I work here.
Ow...
Wow.
You have nice breasts.
It's okay, tell me.
Who are you, really?
No!
Hey!
Sweetheart!
I think we can have all kinds of fun with you.
Let's have some fun.
Are you okay?
So, I take it he brought you here afterwards?
Yes.
That's so fucking obvious.
What?
You really don't get it?
That was a set-up, dear.
I was set up?
Come on fool, it's clear as day.
That dick Kyouichi set you up!
That's not true!
You must be in love with him,
since you want to believe him.
I don't love him.
If you don't leave here
right away, you'll regret it.
Who are you, anyway?
Think about it.
I'm Kyouichi's...
Lover, okay?
She's not resisting me.
He really knows how to pick women, doesn't he?
It's sucking my finger!
This is amazing!
You've got one hell of a pussy!
I'll prove that you were set up.
You will attend to one of our clients in a minute.
I'll make sure Kyouichi
watches you in the viewing room.
If he comes in to stop this...
Then he loves you, and you win the bet.
He's a brand new client.
He's the one that wants to buy that draft from me.
I'm willing to buy all of it.
Please, name your price.
I don't care about the money.
I've heard a lot of rumors
about you from my colleagues.
Then do we have a deal?
Well, that depends on...
The quality of the girl.
Here, open up and suck on my dick!
Come on!
What's wrong, just suck on it!
Kyouichi!
Come on, open your damned mouth!
No!
I said open it!
Please help me, Kyouichi!
Yeah, I want you to take it deep into your throat.
The poor girl's choking on that thing.
Yeah!
You're not that bad, baby!
Kyouichi, why won't you come and rescue me?
That's good, now I'm going to
pound my cock into your wet pussy!
I'm going to have a lot of fun with you.
Come on, spread your legs, damn it!
You're pussy's dripping wet and ready!
You were worth the money
that I paid, for damn sure.
Kyouichi, why won't you
come and help me out of this?
Good, let me take a good look
at your slippery, pink pussy!
Help me...
Kyouichi!
No!
I'm starting to feel like I'm
really raping you, and I like it!
Shit, your pussy's gripping my cock!
No!
Stop!
Look at the tears on your face!
Cry, you fucking whore!
No... no... no...
Keep on crying!
Scream!
Look.
Poor girl, getting raped while
waiting for her prince to rescue her.
So, what do you think of all this?
Mr. Prince Charming?
She doesn't like sex, nor is she submissive.
Really, I could have sworn
she would be a cum whore.
No, I'd be willing to bet that
she's the extremely faithful type.
All right, keep going just like that!
I want you to scream and cry!
She's the type that only wants to
have sex with her one, true love.
That's rather pathetic and naive.
But that's not reality.
Are you getting wet?
You can see Youri in action perfectly!
Be quiet, fool!
I'm not a pervert!
I'm cumming!
All right, your asshole drained
this jizz out of my cock.
Lick it off!
How is the new girl doing?
See for yourself.
Wow, she's letting the client do anything!
Ayaka, that girl's a much bigger slut!
Unbelievable!
I might lose to her!
All right, make sure not to
waste a single drop of my cum!
This feels too fucking good!
I'm going to fuck you hard
until I can't get it up anymore!
She'll be able to pay off the
money you spent setting her up.
I only spent ten grand.
So you set this one up!
Don't accuse me of that!
I told her nothing but the truth, all right?
What did you say?
I told her she was set up.
But she stayed.
Youri was trying to test me.
That stupid girl lost.
Wait, does that mean I'm dumb, too?
You're not exactly the brightest bulb, either.
Hey, that's not nice!
Yes, you are a dumb blonde.
What!
My little devil!
I want a treat, Kyouichi!
You're talented at finding all
kinds of sick women, aren't you?
I think she's pissed.
That's not like her.
How is it, does it feel good?
Yeah!
Don't do that, I'm afraid of the dark!
Now, now.
My little darling.
You, her, and Youri are all my
precious little devils, all right?
This is one fine bitch, for sure!
Come on, scream louder, damn it!
That's right, your fucking
job is to please my cock!
Little devil.
Great job, Youri!
Escort your client outside.
What the...
Hell...
What happened here?
So what happened?
Her pussy is a rare, amazing weapon.
Why don't you see for yourself?
I see.
I guess talking to her body
would answer my questions.
I'm going to join you, too!
Wait, what's going...
Now tell me.
Tell me what happened earlier!
Youri!
God, my cock...
it's getting sucked in!
You're going to be all mine, Kyouichi!
Youri!
My cock can't stop getting hard!
Who are you?
All of you?
Kyouichi, you're the one that called
all of us your little devils, right?
Yahoo!
To be continued...
(Volume 2 was never produced)