http://www.hentaiparadize.net
Man, life is boring.
You study like crazy when you're a kid...
...then you go to a good college by paying high tuition and graduate.
And what do you know, I'm working as an underpaid intern.
When I finally became a doctor,\NI had to clean up messes like this.
One kid with broken bones, two kids with gashes...
And an idiot who got run over by a truck, then died on the way here.
It's the same thing every single day.
Please, cut it out already!
You're so cold.
You must be in distress everyday with that voluptuous body of yours.
I can manage just fine.
Don't be so mean.
Ouch!
Well I'm going now.\NThank you very much.
Take care.
My, it's really bad.
What a horrible patient.
You don't seem dissatisfied.
What?
What are you saying, doctor?
You know you like it.
With your pheromones going crazy...
...I bet you wanted to be violated by that guy.
I won't allow you to say such a thing, Doctor.
You won't allow me to say such things?
It hurts.
Doctor, we still have to do a check-up...
Shut up!
Look over here, it's wet already.
You slut!
My life is boring but...
I'll take my frustrations out on you.
Doctor, no!
This is great.
This is the reason why\NI can't quit my job.
No doctor...
I feel it, I feel it.
Well, I'm about to come.
I'm gonna come inside of you.
Don't come inside!\NNot today!
Too late.
It's inside...
Your cock juice is flowing inside me!
Don't worry.
If you get pregnant,\NI'll perform an abortion.
It's almost time, doctor.
For what?
A new doctor is arriving here today, so we need to greet him.
Oh, I totally forgot about it.
Since I'm in charge of surgical operations...
...I guess I have to go to the director's room.
Gosh.
Internal Medicine Vol. 1
This is Dr. Sugiura, he'll be working with us starting today.
Hello.
My name is Makoto Sugiura.
Nice to meet you all.
Well, Dr. Sugiura will take over Dr. Shoji's position...
...and will be in charge of internal medicine...
Dr. Sugiura was recommended to us by\NProfessor Takeuchi of Tokyo University.
I'm expecting great things from him.
Hey, he's from Tokyo University...
I wonder if he's married.
He's my type.
I hear he's single.
What? No way!
So, who's working with him?
I'm appointing nurse Mika\NTachibana as his partner.
Help him out and good luck with everything.
Yes. Pleased to meet you!
Same here.
I may be a bother at first, but\NI'm happy to work with you all.
Well Dr. Sugiura, I'm counting on you.
We tried everything we could, but she didn't make it.
Wait, I thought it was supposed to be a simple operation.
Hmm? Is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
I hope I can meet your expectations.
I finally found you.
I see.
He's name is Tadahiko Mizuno...
I never expected him to be the director of this hospital.
Plus three of his daughters are working here...
I believe they are\NShione, Nanami, and Sango.
So many patients on your very first day!
You must be tired.
Thanks.
It tastes so good.
I feel very comfortable and relaxed.
I'm very flattered, Doctor.
Doctor, I couldn't have...
I was able to enjoy my work since I had your support.
Oh, you're so good, Doctor.
But if it's for you, I'm always willing to help.
Nurses are so gullible.
Soon, I'll get my hands on the director's three daughters...
...and show them lots of pain.
Doctor, I want this inside me.
Doctor, it feels really good.
Please stroke me deeper.
Like this?
No, I don't want to let go now.
It feels so good.
Then how about this?
No Doctor!\NNot there.
Please, it's embarrassing.
What is it that you're embarrassed about?
I haven't been pleasured back there yet.
Your cock is entering my ass.
It feels weird...
But it feels good.
Now I want you to play with your clitoris.
Yes.
I've never felt this good in my life.
I never knew my clitoris could swell up and get this big.
I'm almost done.
I'll come!
Me too.
Please let it out inside my ass.
Your cock juice is running wild inside me.
I can feel your warm cock juice...
Doctor, I'm going to expose this to the public. Is that okay with you?
Enough already!
This month's quota has been fulfilled already.
We need to make a report so there needs to be improvement.
That's why we need you to do something about it.
I can't do that.
My father will scold me.
Are you sure you want to say something like that?
Fine, I'll let you know after I conduct further investigation.
That's the spirit.
You're great doc.
I'm counting on you.
She's...
I'm late, I'm late!
Ouch!
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, Dr. Sugiura.
You shouldn't be running in the hallways.
There are seriously ill patients too, you know.
I'm really sorry!
Sango Mizuno
I'm glad you bumped into me and not one of the patients.
What are you doing?
Ah, big sister.
You're so careless.
I'm sorry Dr. Sugiura.
Oh, I'm all right.
Are you all right Sango?
Ah, yes.
I'm so sorry.
I suggest you walk even if you're in a rush.
Bye.
Dr. Sugiura remembered my name.
I guess he has a softer side as well.
Sango, don't you have to give that to dad?
Oh that's right.
I gotta go.
Bye!
Man, it's so boring.
The Director pretends he knows nothing.
The nurses are going crazy for that new doctor.
But Dr. Sugiura...
I've heard that name somewhere.
I'll ask Shiori to find out about him tomorrow.
This is it for this month.
I can place another order after two months.
That's the spirit.
Thanks a lot, Doctor Shione.
Don't get fresh with me!
How would you like to go out to dinner with me?
Who are you kidding?
If you keep threatening me like this, you're gonna be in big trouble!
You're really scary.
I understand, we'll just keep this a business relationship.
If Nanami didn't screw up and provide the wrong medicine...
I wouldn't be doing what you tell me to do!
Well, if you weren't there, Doctor, that patient wouldn't have made it.
You really care for your younger sister.
Listen, you better not let my family know about this.
Okay, okay, I understand.
So she's the oldest sister, Shione.
I thought she would be the most difficult of the three to get, but...
...it just might be easier than I thought.
Come in.
Excuse me, this is Sugiura.
Are you busy?
I just want to ask you something.
Oh, what could a brilliant doctor from Tokyo University ask me about?
Oh stop it.\NNot you too, Dr. Shione.
It's just that I wanted to ask you about the medical supplies.
You already have a dealer?
Yes, my father...
I mean, the director chose the dealer.
I see.
It's really not a big deal, but there's something that I need you to decide.
What?
Well, it seemed to me that you were very friendly with the dealer.
"If Nanami didn't screw up and provide the wrong medicine..."
"I wouldn't be doing what you tell me to do!"
"Well if you weren't there, Doctor, that patient wouldn't have made it."
What's this?
What's going on?
I need you to do me a favor.
I'm calling for help.
Please, go ahead and do so.
But I think you're going to be in deep trouble.
What do you want?
Oh, it's really nothing.
I want you to do what I tell you to.
If you don't, your cozy relationship with your dealer...
...and your sister Nanami's medical malpractice will be made public.
Thank you for waiting.
I hear that you're the director's oldest daughter...
...and that you're very popular at this hospital.
Please stop it.
I can give you lots of money.
Money huh?
That's why I don't like doctors.
You think money can solve everything?
What is it that you want?
What did I ever do to you?
In life, money isn't everything.
Plus a quack doctor like you needs to be punished.
If you make another mistake, the patients won't be happy, you know.
Well, you're wearing something really sexy.
It's not so bad to be stripped down once in a while right?
Let's see how they look...
Titties belonging to the daughter of a crooked doctor.
Let's examine them.
It hurts, stop it!
See? You really are a quack doctor.
Your body is very excited.
I'll give you a present.
I'm offering you a bribe.
Make it erect with that pretty mouth of yours!
N-No way!
A smart doctor like you can't see what might happen?
You're gonna be in big trouble.
Please begin, Doctor Shione.
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh man, that's not the way to do it!\NIt's not like this is your first time.
Put it in your mouth.
Don't pretend to be innocent.
I'm sure you sucked many cocks in your life, right?
That's it, you're pretty good.
Now, let's take a look at how you're feeling down here.
It's getting really moist down there.
Let's use these fingers and examine it shall we?
Stop it, please!
Your examination isn't over yet.
You keep yourself very clean.
After all, you are a doctor.
Let's see how this hole looks.
Well, I can't see it very well.
Please lie on your stomach.
Yes, that's it.
Now turn your ass this way.
If you don't show me everything, then I can't examine it.
No!
Amazing, it's very clean.
No.
I'm begging you, please!
Don't you know that only quack doctors lie?
Your cunt juice is pouring out.
I hate female doctors since they have so much pride.
The body doesn't lie.
If you're a doctor, then you should know that, right?
Now, let's check your sensitive area.
No!
Please! Not that one!
No...
I can't...
Oh, you're urinating doctor.
This is unbearable.
Since you made such a mess,\NI'll have to punish you.
No!
The body doesn't lie.
Look at you shaking your hips.
No!
Now, I'm going to come inside.
No, not inside!
I'll come back tomorrow.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
It's better for you to not know about it.
We tried everything we could, but she didn't make it.
Wait, I thought it was supposed to be a simple operation.
When we made an incision in the abdomen, it was worse than expected.
I'm sorry.
But wasn't it supposed to just be an examination today?
Yes.
But when we examined her, it was already too late.
The cancer cells had spread to other parts of the body.
If you didn't operate on her, maybe she would still be alive.
Are you saying I made a mistake?
I didn't say that.
But I would like a copy of the consultation chart and medical sheet.
I can't do that.
Why?
I must follow the rules of the hospital.
I'm very busy.
If you're going to falsely accuse me of medical malpractice...
I'll countersue for ruining my reputation and interfering with my business.
No...
I won't...
I'll never forgive him!
I'll ruin his daughters and this hospital!
Oh, Dr. Sugiura...
I'm sorry if my little sister caused you any harm.
No, don't worry about it.
Are you cleaning up by yourself?
Yes. We don't have enough people right now.
It must be very hard.
You nurses have lots of work to do as well.
By the way, does this hospital give physical check-ups for the nurses?
Let's see, maybe once every two years?
That's not good.
If you don't get a check-up at least once every six months...
You won't be able to perform well on your job.
Health is a precious asset for us hospital workers.
You really do care about the nurses.
I'm really surprised.
Really?
I don't think it's surprising at all.
If you like, I can do a physical check-up for all the nurses.
Nanami, can you ask the head nurse about this?
Yes.
You're going to do our check-ups?
I'm very happy.\NThank you very much.
He's getting carried away.
Just you wait.
You won't last long.
Doctor Shione, do you have some time right now?
There's a patient I would like you to see.
Yes, of course.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I was just preparing some things.
What are you planning to do here?
We'll save the best for last.
Stop it.
What if someone sees us?
That would be fun wouldn't it?
Should we charge them an admission fee?
I'm sure there are many people out there who will pay...
...a couple hundred bucks just to see you like this.
If that happens, I'll give you half of the take.
First, we sterilize them.
Someone's coming.\NPlease stop!
You're late. Get over here.
Sorry I'm late.
Just shut up and start recording.
What are you people up to?
If you don't keep a record of the surgery, it gets kind of messy later on.
That's why I asked your friend to help me.
Man, Doctor Shione is really sexy, all right.
This is a crime!
You think you can get away with this?
Those words came from a doctor who's trying to cover up a malpractice?
You just keep quiet and do what we tell you to.
Plus I'm kind enough to use anesthetic on you.
This is much better than what you people did to...
Are we rolling already?
We haven't even started.
This is where the fun begins.
I was getting really pissed off at this bitch's attitude.
You can't even do anything on your own.
Now it's all set to go.
I'll let you do her first.
Go ahead, do her up there or down there.
Then I'll just start off at the top.
This is something!
Is this a dream?
You're done already?
You're pretty quick.
Well you can do her down here then.
You're satisfied right?
Now hold her down by the shoulders.
Stop it, please...
Don't do that...
If you make too much noise, people are gonna come.
It hurts!
Tolerate the pain.
Do you know how many patients suffered because of you?
I like that. Your expression.
How is it? It feels good doesn't it?
Hey, answer me!
Yes.
Now you're my slave.
I'm going to go after your sisters now.