S... stop!
You still don't understand your situation.
I'm your master, and you are my slave!
I won't forgive this kind of humiliation!
You are beautiful,
but you must show more obedience to me.
Well, you'll obey and like it
once you get this.
What, what're you going to do to me?
A... Ayaka!
What's the meaning of this?
What's going on? Why are you here?
It's not my job to train you girls.
This is not what you promised me!
You said you wouldn't
tell anyone if I did what you wanted!
Yes, but don't worry,
this girl, like you, is my love doll.
Don't treat me like her!
Do you realize what you're doing?
I'll have my grandfather fire you now!
S... stop!
I know your boyfriend left you, bitch!
Kaori, even if this room is sound proof,
you'd better not to be loud.
You don't want the other girls
to know about this, do you?
It's stupid for you to do this.
No, no. More people enjoy this
than I would have imagined.
Go ahead. Do whatever you want!
It is against my aesthetics to force others.
I'd like you to beg me.
Why don't you stop him, Ayaka?
Your dear grandfather
might enjoy seeing these.
Uh... please give me an enema.
Oh, that's not a very refined request.
N... no!
Your farting, too, is beautiful,
like the efforts of an aspiring musician.
It's show time!
No! If you're going to do it, do it quickly!
Please do it more slowly.
Yes, we must let her savor the experience.
I can't stand any more.
I'm sorry that
I did not act when I felt I had to.
Oh, I haven't done it with you.
Why do you enjoy doing this?
Any man would enjoy tormenting bitches!
Wait and see;
soon you'll be unable to resist me.
Shit, I was so close.
She ruined my aesthetics!
Come on, hurry up!
Wait! Don't run so fast!
Don't touch me!
Rules, rules, rules... What bullshit!
Rules mean nothing to me!
Miss Maejima, I don't treat you special
if you are the Chairman's granddaughter!
Is it your business
what kind of skirt or underwear we wear?
You're here to study.
I can't let you wear things that
attract attention from people.
And it's already past curfew.
I didn't know about any curfew.
Pink underwear is against
school regulations!
Don't say that out loud!
In any case, you will be punished.
Moeko Fujimura!
I will talk to you, later.
You caught me!
Shiho, it's Nagisa. I'm coming in.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Nagisa, I'm almost finished;
could you just turn your back?
Yes.
And... the door, please?
I'm so sorry. And I'm sorry
for dropping in without notice.
No, don't be sorry.
You are always welcome, Nagisa.
You know so many things.
That's why I like to talk to you.
Bathroom
Chiaki, you are not a child anymore.
You don't have to follow me everywhere,
okay?
But I'm happy anywhere
as long as I'm with you.
Oh, well...
Are you having stomach problems, Asami?
I'm fine.
I just took some medicine for this.
Don't tell anybody
because it's embarrassing, okay?
Damn it! She confiscated my skirt!
She also made me wear
these embarrassing gym clothes!
I think it's better than going home
without your panties.
She confiscated my skirt, too.
My panties, too! And they're expensive...
...not like that bitch's cheap rags!
Plus, I wanted to wear them
when I see him.
In any case, nowadays...
...no girls wear plain white undies,
not even elementary school students!
It gives me shivers to think that bitch
has my underwear!
I think you look good in
any clothes because you're so shapely!
Do you think so?
Me, I have a big butt.
Whenever I move,
my panties cut into my flab.
Hello.
Yes, this is Kaori.
Yes...
I'm at the dormitory.
Really? But I have to go have dinner now.
Well, ok, so talk to you later.
I'm glad.
Yes, okay. Talk to you later, then.
Moeko, don't misunderstand!
My... my brother is dropping by.
Anyway, change your clothes,
and let's go to dinner.
Oh no! Did you forget?
I was looking forward to it because
you said you made sweets for us!
Nagisa...
Show respect for Nagisa!
You are so strict, Asami.
That's all right. I want her to call me that.
We have lots of sweets, so don't worry.
Let's eat. I can't wait any longer!
You already had dinner,
so you don't eat too much, otherwise...
Again!
Miss Kurihara was a little strange,
wasn't she?
I know why, but it's a secret.
By the way,
where did you hide the sweets?
I won't tell anybody, so please tell me!
I like to know people's secrets.
- Can you find it?
- Yes, I'll get it!
Ouch!
Are you ok, Miss Minamigumo?
Nagisa, you weren't looking at my panties,
were you?
I'm sorry.
I knew it!
Now I have to check out yours, too!
Nagisa, I'm coming in, ok?
Nagisa, please wash these.
I didn't know you were here,
Miss Minamigumo.
Wow! Kaori, are you having Nagisa
wash your underwear?
I can trust her.
I wash my own things myself.
What are you trying to say?
It's okay. I don't mind doing this.
Never mind. Sometimes
it's a good idea to do it yourself.
Nagisa, don't worry. I won't tell anybody.
And please don't tell anybody
that I was wearing pink panties, ok?
Sure!
Mr., Kato. It's Minami. I'm coming in!
Mr. Kato, I got the evidence!
So, on Monday...
Well! He's not here.
He sure slipped out quietly.
Excuse me! Could you give me
some toilet... paper?
I have changed to white underwear.
You don't have to ask Mr. Kato
for toilet paper and tampons.
Oh, yes. It looks dangerous
if he comes into the bathroom.
Well, ok, I'm leaving!
Miss Fujima, wait!
Overexcited girl...
By the way, it's a little smelly in here.
I can't breathe...
Amazing he knows how to operate
this thing...
...Messy guy that he is!
Wow! It's cute!
You know what?
It feels really good if I touch here.
No! Miss Minamigumo!
Take it out, please...
I keep telling you, call me Chiaki, ok?
Chiaki... Stop it...
Forgive me. This is my first time.
That's why I'm savoring it really well!
I can't move anymore.
You'll shut up if you don't
want me to tell about those pictures!
I could show them to Asami,
what do you say?
No! I don't want her to see them!
She'll hate me.
Put your face in a crotch,
you deserve to be hated, don't you?
Please don't!
There's just one thing you can do.
Tell Asami that there is no difference...
...between bitch and bitch!
You didn't do this to Asami, did you?
Asami is smart, not like you...
...so it might be hard
to take embarrassing pictures.
Can you forgive me...
...if I get Asami for you?
Wow, you are thinking a frightening thing.
Because I don't want her to hate me!
Do you know some secret about her?
I know... Asami's secret.
Did you girls see Chiaki?
What about Miss Minamigumo?
I haven't seen her in a while.
And her room's locked.
Hasn't she gone to sleep already?
With her door locked?
She doesn't usually do that.
Did you hear something?
I don't think so. Well, I'm leaving.
Are you leaving already? You aren't
going to that girl's place, are you?
Of course, not.
But, yesterday you were acting
friendly with her.
I'm sorry, I'm so childish.
I believe you.
Good night.
You're not there again today.
Hello. This is Minami.
I feel like I've forgotten
something important.
Well, I was so surprised.
I never thought I would see you like this,
Miss Minami.
Well, why don't you sit down?
Why did you want to talk
about Miss Maejima?
Before we get into that,
why don't you have a drink and relax?
This is not a glass you use, is it?
Of course not. It's for guests,
but sometimes other girls use it.
Miss Maejima, too?
She won't touch anything that I serve her.
Shit!
Oh, it's Kaori.
Your clothes are too much as usual.
There are only girls here!
Kaori!
Don't worry, I'm won't smell anything.
Oh, well.
Japanese style toilets
are really old now and inconvenient.
I have to ask my grandfather
have them replaced.
I'm sorry. I was in a hurry...
As I told you several times,
I'm going to tell the Chairman about this.
If the Chairman learns of this...
...there'll be big trouble.
It's Miss Maejima's fault.
He is... just tricked..., I think.
Why are you on his side?
Don't ask me any more questions.
What is it?
What's this feeling? I feel uneasy.
Welcome, manager.
Don't treat Shataro like that!
Your mouth is not for complaining...
...but for servicing me!
I'll let you taste this with your upper lips...
...before tasting it with your lower lips!
I long for you, Mr. Manager.
Stick out your tongue and lick up!
If you bite my dick with your teeth...
...other girls will be jealous of you,
so be careful!
Are you going to do this to other girls?
You've already betrayed your best friend,
how can you ask that?
Why don' t you take it in deep
and lick it well?
- No, I didn't mean to betray her.
- Do it!
Do you know what kind of picture
I took of Asami...
...thanks to the secret you told me?
You'll want to kill yourself if you see them!
Put your arms around my shoulders.
Otherwise you'll fall down
and be embarrassed!
Well? What's that?
Stop it! Stop moving!
You can do it. I made
an easy position for you, so you can shit!
Let me go to the bathroom!
It's very good to do it
while you're being fucked.
I can't do it!
It's too late to be embarrassed now!
Don't say that... please!
Why don't you do it and feel better?
N... I can't hold it anymore!
Did you know that bitches
like you are usually masochists?
N... no.
You say annoying things
because you want us to punish you.
I can't take this anymore!
You're waiting for somebody
to let you show your real self. Right?
No... I can't hold...
Don't hide it!
No!
Asami.
You didn't know this, did you?
Asami can look this sexy.
That's the proof that she's a masochist.
And you, too!
So, you girls are masochistic friends.
No... I'm not...
Asami was surprised, too,
at what a mature woman you are.
Really?
Yes, I showed her everything
that I shot on videotape.
That's mean.
Your friendship deepens by
watching each other's embarrassing video.
Asami.
This is my present for you.
I'll come inside of you, ok?
I'll soak you with my sperm.
No, please!
I'm coming!
No!
Well, I can't believe there is no shower,
it's so inconvenient.
I was wondering what
that building behind the garden is.
What do you think it is?
I heard it's an old warehouse.
Nobody uses it now.
But it looks like the light is on,
wouldn't you say?
I don't think so.
It smells of sweat and perfume
mixed together.
Don't moan like a horny bitch! Shut up.
I dressed you up, but if you move,
it gets messy.
Don't do it, Moeko!
Nobody will come for a bath at this hour.
Besides, it's easy to shave after a bath.
But...
Your boyfriend won't
like you if you don't take good care...
I can make your body and mind obey.
Don't be shy. By tomorrow night...
...Iots of girls will be shaved just like you.
To Be Continued