It's ready.
How do you feel about...
...having your most intimate parts
shaved, Miss Minami?
I can't hear you like this.
Now you can talk...
You can't defeat me
by doing this kind of thing!
My body is not clean now,
but my heart is...
Indeed,
you are a teacher in a prestigious school.
Different from other bitches...
Do you mean to say you're doing this
to other students?
Yes ma'am.
Well, watching students' futures
is your job, too, isn't it?
Miss Kurihara!
Why won't you obey?
That doesn't feel good!
You are so stubborn.
How can you say that? You are so wet!
No! Stop!
Will you be able to obey
if I do this here?
No! Not anal!
Ok, I admit it.
I like it, so please stop!
Finally you're talking like a woman...
I can't take it.
No...
Now, you and I have a sticky relationship.
Miss Minamigumo, too...
By the way...
...you've pissed a lot.
You feel good now, don't you?
Now that you've relieved yourself,
aren't you hungry?
Yes...
...I want you...
Finally you want my sperm?
You stink, Chiaki!
Now you're full, so clean yourself up.
I can't stand your smell whenever I come.
Starting next week...
...why don't you practice your moaning?
You go to hell!
When I go to hell, I'll take you with me...
If you come inside me, I'll kill you!
You'd better start thinking of
a name for your baby!
No!
Please don't come inside me!
Don't!
Do I know something?
Mr. Kato!
What is it?
This isn't good.
This is against school regulations.
No! Give them back to me.
Oh, no...
Stop! Let me go!
Stop, Mr. Kato.
Did you check like I told you?
You sent that letter?
That camera has been set up
and filming all evening long.
You're a smart girl...
...you know what that means.
What do you think?
I think they all look good.
You're so mean...
Oh yeah...
...I saved the best ones for last.
For such a cute girl,
you sure take big ones.
When I went to get this camera...
...it still smelled in there.
Oh, Miss Kobe.
Hey...
...you don't usually
take a bath at this time.
I couldn't sleep, so...
Hey, do you want me to wash your back?
Moeko, don't be rude!
You have bigger breasts
than I thought, Eri.
You've got a great figure, too.
No, I'm just average.
If I do what you say...
...will you return that picture to me?
Of course...
...it'll be our little secret.
What are you going to do to me?
I have someone I like very much...
...so don't do anything dirty.
Oh, then you'll need practice...
First of all...
...I want you to change your clothes.
...because aesthetics
is very important in doing this.
Good night, Kaori.
Hello, Kenji! What?
I'm ok. I'm about to go to bed.
What? Now?
See-through negligee. Just kidding!
What?
What color do you think?
No, I'm not a child.
Here at my school, though...
...we're supposed to wear
plain white panties.
It's true, really!
So are you going to come
and check it out?
Be careful of people listening in
on your cell phone calls.
Bitch! You spit out my sperm!
It's very important to make you
an adult woman!
If you waste it,
you'll be punished!
Don't worry,
you're not the only tragic heroin.
N... no! Don't open the door!
C... Chiaki?
Nagisa, you too?
What's this?
Well, he told me to come in a swimsuit;
and this is the only one I have.
That's ok.
You girls will play with each other
as my pets.
No! Chiaki!
I'm the only one
who can give her orders!
No! Stop!
You have a big ass,
it's really perfect for sex.
No, don't!
You get all that shit from here, right?
No, don't say any more...
It's really smelly, isn't it?
I can't say such things!
Yes... it... smells.
Ok, so I have to give you relief
with my dick to make it stink less.
What? No... no!
Not there!
It's dirty... dirty... no!
Shut up! You said you wanted
to keep your chastity for your boyfriend.
...so I'm contenting myself
with your ass!
No... Mama... help me!
Mama? You got such big breasts,
how can you call to your mama?
It hurts! Forgive me!
You look happy.
Your nipples are hard.
If I stop now,
you'll be too excited to sleep...
Please... please...
Oh... good...
No! Please! No...
What? Really?
I'm ok, but isn't it strange?
What?
Come on!
What is it? At this hour?
Well, I have something here...
...that I want you to have a look at.
Can't it wait till tomorrow?
No, now, please.
Ok, I'll change my clothes.
I'll be out in a second.
Fu... Fujima...
It's mean to do this kind of thing...
I think it's a voyeuristic shot
that is quite popular these days.
I just found it in the bathroom.
Shiho, are you ok?
Have something to drink and relax.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Kato.
Have you told this to Miss Minami?
I called her, but she wasn't in her room.
At any rate,
I can't do anything with it by myself...
...so we have to tell somebody.
Oh, Nagisa! Let's tell her!
Did you watch it until the end?
Should I?
It would be better if you watched.
...There is a chance
that you are in here, too.
Na... Nagisa!
Oh, no... why am I so...?
No!
Did you get peeped?
You did.
Did you?
You got peeped...
You did.
You got peeped, Eri!
Why don't you give up?
Mr. Kato?
Now you're in the same situation as us!
You're cute and smell nice.
No... don't...
Is this a dream? Or...
Kenji is quite a maniac...
...but I'm a little excited.
Anyway, he's a little late.
What?
Mr. Kato, what do you want to talk about?
Do we have to talk out here?
Plus it's late.
Can't we talk tomorrow?
If Kenji's here, it could be trouble.
There's never anyone else
around here at this time...
This is kind of thrilling...
How do you feel?
You seem to get turned on
watching people going to the bathroom.
Whew, that's better.
Maybe I like this.
Mu. Kato!
Who's there?
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
You are late, Kenji!
Be quiet.
What's this?
You wet your pants
with your nasty juices...
...watching Moeko do her dirty business?
If I were to show the videotape
of how you behaved...
...what would Nagisa think?
Why don't you smile?
I've changed your soaking-wet panties.
They weren't so wet.
For a girl with such huge breasts,
you don't know your place.
It's so mean to say things
about my body.
I didn't want to have such big...
What are you talking about?
Your breasts are swollen
because you're always thinking...
...dirty little thoughts!
I'm not thinking about anything dirty!
Don't talk back to me!
Do you want me to give that picture away?
N... no! I can't take it anymore!
It hurts! Stop!
It's so good!
NO!
How do you feel
now that you've lost your virginity?
You're a grown-up woman now.
Please forgive me!
I'll forgive you if you find somebody...
...to service me.
I can't do that.
If you can't find a replacement,
you're stuck with me.
No, not so hard!
Well, do you have someone...
...who can take your place
and make me feel good?
Uh... I'm coming.
No, please don't come inside me!
Have you come up with
someone to take your place?
Na...
Na...?
What's the rest of her name?
Nagisa.
That's surprising.
I suppose if you're friends,
you can forgive each other.
Right? As long as you're ok...
...you don't care about your friend?
No, that's not true!
That's ok. That's the bare truth.
Peel away the skin
and it's all rotten inside.
Now you are one of my slaves!
While I'm doing this...
...I'll take you to hell with me!
What? No! Stop!
That's not what you told me!
No!
Lying is one of the basic skills
of a bastard like me.
No!
Come on, quickly!
What are you doing? Pull her out quickly!
Please, forgive me.
Someone will catch us.
If someone finds me like this, I...
So, why don't you move faster?
I'm not doing this because I like it.
But...
...if we don't follow him...
I don't know.
Ok, but look closer.
How is it?
Can't you smell your friend's fluid?
No! Really?
The girl who wet herself thinking of you
is waiting for you in the bathroom.
Are you ready, Chiaki?
Yes!
Wow, impressive meeting!
Shi... Shiho!
N... Nagisa!
Ok, main event!
Chiaki, show that video!
Have you come up with anyone
to take youu place?
Na...
Na...?
What's the rest of her name?
Nagisa.
That's surprising.
I suppose if you're friends,
you can forgive each other.
As long as you're ok...
...you don't caure about your friend?
No, that's not true!
That's about it.
Shiho chose you, Nagisa.
Shiho!
Wait! No! No!
I'm not that good guy...
...willing to give a virgin girl...
...to some other son of a bitch.
It hurts! It hurts!
I'm sorry, Nagisa.
Shoot it perfectly, Chiaki!
Nagisa...
Well, aren't you lucky?
You lost your virginity twice in one day.
No! Now I can't get married!
Nobody cares about
that kind of thing nowadays!
No! No! No!
This is just the beginning.
You're going to scream
a lot more from now on!
Somebody, help me!
Kenji ran off
once he'd had his fill of fucking me.
Oh well,
he should have stayed for some more fun.
Well, I'm going back, too.
Uh, cold!