I'm yours!
What? I can't hear you.
Whose fuckin' butt is this?
Whose!
My butt is yours, Kato.
Then you won't complain
no matter what I do.
No! No! Not inside me!
Please forgive her.
What?
If you come, come inside me.
Na...Nagisa!
So, don't do it to Shiho....
Ok, I'll do as you ask.
Stop. Mr. Kato. Don't hurt her.
I can take it, so come inside of me.
Inside?
Come, please.
It's too late now!
First of all, remember...
...why you lost your virginity,
which you tried to protect...
...by giving me your ass?
Shallow friendship, isn't it, Chiaki?
Why don't you show them
what deep friendship means?
No, Chiaki! Stop it, please!
I'm sorry, Asami. Sorry...
No! Not there, Chiaki!
I'm not going to hurt you, Asami.
Hey, this isn't study time.
Stop using your brain and use your body!
If you don't do it right...
...your friend will have to stay
in that embarrassing pose!
Nagisa!
Don't look away!
And rub me
with your breasts like you mean it!
Oh! You grip me so well...
...with your sexy body.
It's so good...
Now, have another taste of my dick!
Well, I'm still sleepy.
This is kind of thrilling....
Now I have enough to blackmail her.
Hi, Moeko.
Kaori!
You're not usually up this early.
You have to bleach your white panties
and wash them by hand.
Really?
Uh-huh.
But, I've never done it.
It's too much trouble, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Well, it's faster if I help you, right?
I've got a good idea!
H...hey!
-I can't believe it.
-Why don't you do it, too?
No, thank you!
It's a little cool,
but once you got used to it, it feels good!
No, thank you!
Don't say that!
Hey, stop, Moeko!
Stop it!
I'm a bad little girl!
What's happening?
Hey, come on, silly! It was a joke.
Don't be so angry!
It's just something naughty
that you shouldn't do but you do anyway!
That's why I'm apologizing.
You joke too much,
like last night for instance.
Anyway! I won't forgive you
if you do this again!
What's this?
What is this!?
Clean her up right, you hear?
What?
You want to pee or something?
No!
Don't hesitate!
Spill it in your friend's face!
What?
I can't!
Don't talk back!
If you don't do it,
tomorrow I'll make you famous at school.
Now, squeeze your bladder!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
No!
Watching your students pee
makes you come.
What a bitch you are!
Kaori, can you do me a favor?
Sorry, can I do it later?
Wait!
I really have to borrow something now!
What is it? Make it quick.
School uniform, skirt....
I'm not going to use it
for anything strange!
You see, teacher took mine yesterday.
Please! Your size is almost same as mine.
Something is about to happen again.
Thank you, Kaori!
It's weird. Why Moeko, too?
Is she also--?
Yes, how did you get this number?
What?
Are you crazy?
If Miss Minami find out about this...
...there's going to be big trouble!
Find out about this?
What if she found out about these?
In my job,
I can't stand by idly and watch...
...as the morals of this school
are corrupted.
I have to teach the correct way
to behave as a student in our school.
I'm going to teach it to this sexy body.
No, stop! Don't!
Kaori...I'm sorry.
It's the perfect size
for a lewd girl like you, Moeko.
I'm not lewd!
You're not very convincing,
especially when you don't wear panties.
But...all my panties are in the laundry.
Well then...
...I'll have to teach you...
...to have the sense of shame of a lady.
Hey, If I let you fuck me,
will you really throw those pictures away?
Let me?
Fucking bitch!
Lick my dick and
beg me to fuck you!
I'm sorry.
You're getting used to doing this,
aren't you?
Looks like you're already
quite good at doing this.
What are you waiting for?
Put it in your mouth now!
Not so slow!
Not so rough!
Shut up!
You're mistaken if you think I'll throw
away those pictures for so easy a thing!
If you understand,
put it in your mouth now!
We're not making love to each other!
You are servicing me, understand?
I can't wait to see my parents!
Me neither. I couldn't go home last week
'cause I was sick.
What's the matter, Miss Kobe?
Aren't you going back home?
I'm going to stay here this time.
Ok, good.
Like you mean it. Deeper.
Oh, you know what you're doing.
You have a way of using your tongue
that's so different from other bitches.
I'm coming. Swallow it all, you hear?
Don't spit it out!
You don't have time to cry!
No!
Not so fast!
No...not there!
I see that even you are virgin
in your ass.
No! Take it out!
It's inhuman!
Don't worry.
It's painful only at first.
You'll learn to enjoy...
...being fucked in the ass!
No! Stop!
What?
Good timing.
What is it?
Hello!
Well, we're waiting for you.
The door's not locked,
so you can come right in.
Is someone coming?
Oh, if you come,
don't forget to lock the door, hear?
No, I don't want anybody
to see me like this!
Yes, ok.
M...Moeko!
Kaori.... No!
Don't look.
I don't want you to see me like this!
Kato! What's this all about?
Stop it now!
Even if I took orders from you...
...this is too good for me to stop!
Stop talking nonsense.
Otherwise I'm going to tell my grandfath--
I don't care.
I think your grandfather will understand...
...once he sees these.
Oh, uh, not that....
How do you feel, Moeko?
Do you understand the sense of shame
even a little?
No...no...no...
Kaori, don't just stand there.
Why don't you prepare for next and wait.
What do you mean?
You should be wet
after I finish with Moeko.
What do you mean?
Don't you know? Masturbation!
You know you can't resist me.
Are you ready, Kaori?
No!
It's no use resisting.
Looks like Moeko can't stand it anymore.
Why don't you answer it
since she's tied up just now?
Well...
Quickly!
We shouldn't make him wait so long.
Ke...Kenji?
Good timing.
What? Now? Nothing.
Of course I'm by myself.
No...yes, I've got a cold and
a little fever....
I'm ok...really.
I'm sorry. I can't go today.
Sorry.
Please forgive her.
I'll take her place.
What a beautiful friendship.
Yes, this is Minami.
I'm not available right now,
so please leave a message.
Well, I think I have a fever.
Really, I'm ok.
Don't worry...n...no...
I'm ok....
Same kind of lie....
Why don't you tell him what you're doing?
I'm really ok.
Ok, talk to you tomorrow.
Wait! I don't want to do this!
Don't try to be cool to me;
we both know you're no virgin.
Not from behind!
Oh yes, from behind!
I can see all of your ass.
Now...
...Iift your butt higher!
I said no!
If you say anything more,
I'll shove my dick in here!
No, not there!
Then lift your ass!
Now, you too are
one of my bitches!
Oh...it's tight.
You look so prim,
but you've got such big breasts!
No!
It's too late to say no after all this.
N...no! Stop!
What a nice body you've got.
I can smell your tasty scent.
No!
I can't help being jealous
thinking about some guy...
...keeping all this to himself.
No! Don't remind me of him.
Don't tighten so much.
I'm not!
Well...are you getting horny
thinking about your boyfriend?
No way--
Don't worry, I'm going
to make you forget about...
...that son of a bitch.
No, not there!
Just as I thought: your ass is a virgin.
Now, you too have been fucked in the ass!
Take it out!
Don't forget...
...I'm giving you
an unforgettable experience!
Ka-o-ri.
I'm a little tired after all this-- huh?
You want me to fix the toilet now?
I don't feel comfortable
unless I use that particular stall.
That's strange.
I don't think that one's broken.
Well, ok, I'll check it right away.
Thank you.
STALL 2 NO WATER
STALL 3 OUT OF ORDER
I checked it out
and it looks fine.
Was it?
You must have been mistaken.
I'm sorry.
That's ok. It's my job.
Well, excuse me now.
Finally, I caught that girl
with her pants down.
Your days of spying on girls are over!
Kato!
You?
I know what you've been doing!
Oh really?
I know everything.
I checked all the data on your PC, too.
I helped Miss Minami when you forced
her into the old warehouse out back!
Wa! Stop!
I should have got you first.
That hurts, let me go!
To hell with aesthetics!
I'm going to fuck you right now!
N...no!
I called the police.
You're finished now.
Poor guy...
Not yet! I can't get caught yet!
I can't die yet.
I'll do it over and over again...!