W-what are you?
Just let all your
worries go free, Cas.
W-wait, whoa, h-hold on.
Once the war starts,
many people will die.
What use is rationality
in a world like that?
I, Casius Gile Palvis, was sent on
an important mission by my country,
to Constantinovale in 1618...
Slave Market (Dorei Ichiba)
I'm glad that you enjoyed that.
Y-yeah.
Actually, I arranged an even
better gift for you.
Huh, a gift?
Yeah, I'm sure you'll love this.
So please accept.
Your new slave.
She's beautiful.
It looks like she likes you too.
What's your name?
It's no use. She can't speak.
What?
Her name is Myia, and she's a
slave from around Kilkia...
When a girl is taken from
their village, they operate on them...
so they can't speak.
That's horrible...
But isn't she amazing?
Indeed she is...
You'll find out once you hold her,
but this honey-toned skin is said...
to be like a drug.
I'm sure you'll like her.
I can't wait.
Now, get in.
She's only a slave...
That's what I told myself.
I would just ignore the inconvenient
emotions. I was tired of being hurt.
Listen up. You are MY slave!
What a slutty ass you have!
Falco was right in saying
she was a drug.
I lost myself in the sensation of
melting into her honey skin.
I'm going off to work.
You stay here and stay quiet.
It's a dandelion seed.
Flowers grow producing seed,
which in turn grow more flowers.
It's the cycle of all living things.
Umm... are we really all right
without an escort?
Today's meeting is unofficial.
We cannot bring guards with us.
B-but...
Besides. If the capital really
wanted me killed,
even a hundred personal guards
would be meaningless.
I have been waiting for you, Sir Barbarico.
May the Gods smile upon you...
Oh? And who is this young man?
He's a soldier from the Republic.
A staff officer named Palvis.
This is the Prime Minister of
the capital, Sir lvansic.
It's an honor to meet you.
The Prime Minister of lmar is
the only idealist left amidst...
the corrupted country.
He was known as a moderate thinker,
and paid close attention
to the war mongers.
What's wrong, Palvis?
Oh. Nothing.
Whenever my lust came out,
it was as if I let out my evil half.
What is this filthy juice?!
You dirty slut!
You'll have to be punished!
You're my slave! Get it!?
You'll be assaulted here forever!
No matter how much you hate it!
I became the lowest of the low,
and spewed phrase after phrase...
of the filthiest speech, trying
to shake my criminal emotions.
You, where did you get that woman?
Talk! Where is Myia?!
Indeed.
I do smell Myia's vaginal fluids.
W-who are you?!
Pardon us. He's a bit upset about
losing our pet. Please forgive him.
What are you talking about!?
We're talking about the girl you fucked.
I have a deal to make.
Would you please give us back the girl?
And if I decline?
Then we take your life.
What?!
Then, at some point, we
will come to claim her.
J-just try it!
A-an illusion?
Myia has always been part
of the "Sages of the Hill."
Let us meet again soon.
Be well until then.
The "Sages of the Hill"?!
Yeah, I'm sure that's what they said...
If it's the legendary assassin group,
then I've heard rumors about them.
They say that none of their
targets have ever survived.
But weren't they defeated by the Horsemen
of Mongol hundreds of years ago?
I've heard rumors that a few of them
survived and now run black ops.
It can't be!
I'm going to lend this to you.
You know how to use it, right?
S-sure...
Well, you can never be too careful.
Okay, I'll excuse myself.
Alright. Thanks a lot.
Oh, I almost forgot the
most important thing.
Lately, the war mongers
have been really active.
You're sure?
Yeah, I do a lot of business with
some pretty important people.
The information is reliable.
I guess war is inevitable, then...
It stinks.
Here. Eat.
You're thanking me?!
You're grateful to the man
that's abusing you!?
Stop it!
If you promise not to run, I'll take
the chains off. You swear?!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. So sorry.
You're beautiful. It suits you.
Actually, there's something
I need to tell you.
I have to leave this country soon.
But, I want you to come with me.
Let's leave here together.
You won't have to be a slave anymore.
Myia!
What is it? Are you embarrassed?
No one's looking.
No, I don't care if people do stare!
I was drunk with my sudden happiness.
But I should have remembered,
hope quickly turns to despair.
Myia, you're beautiful.
Really beautiful.
Even here.
Do you want this?
Will you, please?
With your mouth?
Who's there?!
Sir Casius! The battle has started!
The war has begun!
What?!
The time had finally come.
My mission was to bring this
information back to my country.
Let us leave immediately.
The ship is waiting at the port.
Hey!
Myia!
What's wrong, Myia?!
Are you looking for this?
We already know that you're
a spy for the Republic.
What?!
But, as I promised, if you give us
Myia, we'll spare your life.
Dammit!
What do you...?!
You know already. She's one of us.
Or I should say, used to be.
You bitch!
Why did you betray us and run!?
She means she wanted
to make her flowers grow.
Pathetic! No one is allowed to
leave us. Return, Myia!
M-Myia...
If you resist, we will kill him...
If you want womanly pleasures,
then I will give them to you.
Stop it!
M-Myia!!
No!!
No! Don't die!
Please don't die!
You... Your voice returned?!
So you did heal.
Is that man so important?
Pathetic!
Go wherever you want!
If he's lucky,
he may be saved.
Are you alright?! Hang on!
That's coming from the
direction of Casius' house!
Casius!!
Casius! Hang on!
W-where am I...?
This is my mansion.
Myia brought you all the way here.
M-My... ia? Myia!
I... I...
Myia...
I wanted to... have your child.
Myia... Myia!!
I was ready to take any punishment
for failing my mission,
but it seemed as if I
was only a distraction.
Someone had somehow gotten the
information back to my country.
This later became known as
the Eastern Seven Year War.
Myia.
Cecilia.
Bianca.