I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
This is a very good find.
I'm glad you like it, sir.
Slave Market
(Dorei Ichiba)
The city of Constantinovale
lies across the ocean,
under a blue sky
clear of a single cloud.
A pagan city shining in the sun.
A stage for shocking dramas.
I, Casius Gile Palvis, received an
urgent mission from my country,
and was dispatched to Constaninovale,
an enemy nation, in 1618.
The first time I visited this
foreign land's capital, I saw...
Casius!
Casius, over here!
Falco!
How have you been? It's been
how long since I've seen you?
2 years. I haven't seen you
since you visited my country!
But I didn't think you'd
come out here to meet me.
A friend I haven't seen in a while
is visiting my city. My backyard!
Of course I'm going to come meet you.
I appreciate it.
But you know, you really...
The young man in front of me,
blessed with the looks of the Gods,
has also been blessed by Hermes
with a knack for business.
He became a merchant to the
government and achieved his wealth.
Falco, there's a lot to talk about,
but the mission comes first.
Actually, there's somewhere
I want to show you, first.
B-but the embassy...
We can do that later. I want to
show you something interesting.
Interesting?
Yeah. It embodies
everything in this town.
It has everything.
But you also can lose everything.
It's the dirtiest and noblest institution
in this town at the same time.
Everyone, out!
How do you like them?
Are there any items
that catch your fancy?
H-hey, Falco, what is this?
The slave market. Here, money is
all that matters, and you can...
do whatever you want.
Isn't this a great town?
W-wait a minute.
You wouldn't deny your old friend
a chance to be hospitable, right?
If you don't like girls, we can
always buy you a nice boy.
Q-quit teasing me.
I was at a loss for words at
the sight of such immorality.
The scent of prison came
wafting from the women.
The light had gone out from
their eyes, unable to even suffer.
Bianca! Quit hiding in the back
and show your face to the man!
Oh! Brother!
Brother, did you come to pick me up?
Brother? Me?
Bianca is a spoil of war
gotten from Romania.
Her skin, her hair color,
and those shining eyes.
I swear by the Parthenon that
she is from noble birth, indeed!
Casius, it's easier to keep it simple.
How old is she?
She is 19, sir.
19, eh? That's a good age.
T-that tickles!
Look at that translucent skin.
It's like she's never seen the sun.
This is an incredible find.
No!
And the feel of her flesh...
How about it?
You want to test her?
N-no, that's okay.
H-hey, aren't you going too far?
N-no more!
I don't want to! Stop!!
Brother... it hurts!
Hey!
No violence!
Please pardon us.
But you must be firm with a slave.
That's enough.
Brother...
From now on, this woman is my slave.
Don't handle her roughly!
Oh, an excellent choice, sir!
I am most humbly grateful for a fine
Venetian gentleman like you...
to be doing business with
a lowly merchant like myself.
Seems like you made a good purchase.
Don't misunderstand. I...
I understand.
So, are you going to pretend to be a
rock all day? If that's the case,
you've probably forgotten about
the mission too, haven't you?
Sorry. I think seeing that as the
first thing was a bit of a shock.
It's better to get to know the city
before you get burnt, right?
It's a small house, but it's got
everything you might need.
Use it however you want.
It's even got a nice yard.
Thanks. It's heaven compared to
the barracks. Too big for just me.
Did you think that you went
and bought some air before?
This is going to be your room.
Falco, there's something
I just have to ask.
What is it?
Is the war...
really going to happen?
Unfortunately, yes.
War is a giant wheel.
Once you get it started,
you can't stop it.
I see...
Can I warn you about one thing?
I don't know what kind of mission
you were dispatched here for.
To the country,
you're just another pawn.
If you like, you can always
go into business with me.
I am always ready to die.
I see.
I thought you might say that.
Then at least enjoy your life
here in the city, while you can.
Welcome...!
C-can I help you?
W... here... is... B... ianca...?
I'm sorry, but Bianca has
already been sold...
B... ianca...
Where is she?
Bianca isn't here!
Please leave!
So she isn't here.
H-help! I...
Well, I'll see you.
Yeah.
Thanks for everything.
Oh, it's brother!
Definitely a good buy. He might not have
been lying about the noble part.
Hey, brother, where were you?
I was waiting for you! I was lonely.
This girl is still mistaking
me for her brother.
It's convenient for you.
Well, I'm done here, so I'll be leaving now.
Okay, thanks for everything.
Don't worry about it.
Well, enjoy the city life, okay?
Thank you.
Brother!
Come on, let's go inside.
W-what was that?!
It sounds foolish, but at the time,
I thought that her innocent smile...
had breathed new
life into the flowers.
W-what is this!?
Brother!
Brother, where are you?
Brother.
Here, money is all that matters,
and you can do whatever you want.
Brother!
What's the matter, brother?
What is this place? I'm scared.
It's okay. Nothing to worry
about, Bianca. Let's go back up.
Okay. I like the sun.
I hate the dark.
After that, every day
was like a dream.
Bianca thought I was her brother,
and I acted the part.
What was the point of this act?
It was a definite reality that...
her existence was causing me
to forget about my mission.
Hey, brother?
What is it?
You won't leave me and
go off again, will you?
Huh? Oh, of course I'm
not going anywhere.
I'm so glad!
Thank you.
By the way,
where's Bianca?
Don't worry. I'm sure she's fast
asleep in the guest room.
Serena, go check on her.
That was the guest room!
Bianca!
Brother!
Get away from Bianca!
Dammit!
B... ianca...
Stop!
Don't you touch Bianca!
B... ianca...
Bianca...
What the hell was that?
Do you know the Romanian
legend about monsters?
Monsters!?
Yeah. After I left your house,
I wanted to know more about her,
so I went to ask Bytone about it.
Did you find out anything?
About a year ago, there was a revolt
in a part of Romania.
The national army went out
to quell the revolt...
but all that remained was
a mountain of dead bodies.
Burned corpses were hung
against the castle walls.
But something was
even stranger.
It was impossible, but the bodies
were all dried up...
As if they were stuck
in a fire that didn't burn.
And, among the corpses,
Bianca was the only one still standing.
B-but how is that?
The Romanian legend remains.
A family hated for cannibalism.
There was a rumor that the
monster lived in the castle.
The townspeople revolted
because they believed it.
F-Falco, what are you saying?
In the castle,
there were two children.
They were fraternal twins,
both with amazing silver hair.
What if she's one
of the two twins?
Just stop it! It's ridiculous!
I didn't believe it either,
until I saw that monster.
I'm thinking of your interests.
Return her to Bytone.
Brother...
Never! I'm not giving
Bianca to anyone!
N-No!! Brother!
I hate the dark!
- No! Stop!
- You saw that monster too!
You'll be safe hiding here!
- No! I don't want to!
I hate the dark!
- I'm doing this for you!
I didn't want to let her go.
The minute I thought that,
she had a simple
control over me.
A heightened sense of danger,
and anger, for no reason.
These feelings mixed together
and ignited my lust.
And the rest was
like tumbling downhill.
No! Stop!!
Brother! Brother!!
Now you can't run away, right?
- Brother, stop! Stop!
- This is to protect you!
Shut up! Here!
Don't. Brother, stop!
I'm scared!
Now, open your mouth!
Don't use your teeth!
It's bitter!
No!
B-Bianca! Bianca!
Stop!!
Please stop...
I don't like it... Brother...
Keep quiet.
Don't leak!
P-please stop!
What had I become?
Her every scream was intoxicating.
It was turning me
into a simple beast.
No! I don't want to hurt anymore!
I'm sorry.
I won't hurt you anymore.
It feels weird.
Casius! Cas! Out at a time like this?
What happened?
Casius...
B-brother...
Brother...
Brother, you feel so good.
Bianca!
Brother! Brother! Brother!!
Bianca... Bianca...
B... ian... ca...
B... ianca...
Have you... forgotten me...?
W-why you little humans...
Silver weapons. Bastards.
Brother! Brother!!
Don't come, Bianca!!
NO!!
B-brother!? You're alive?
What did you say?!
Bianca, together we
can take over everything.
Eventually,
our kind will rule this world.
I don't care about the world.
Just come here!
- I won't let you!
- Don't!
Bianca!
How do you like the taste of a
silver bullet, monster? Casius!
You freak!
Stop! Please stop!
So you're one of his friends?!
This is revenge! Move away!
Don't worry. He'll be fine.
Bianca, come with me!
Bianca.
I was afraid of this cursed body
that could only cause death.
To live forever into the future
in perpetual darkness.
Bianca!
I will go with my brother.
The cursed bloodline dies here.
- W-wait! I'm going with you!
- Stop it, Casius!
Goodbye,
my foreign brother.
Bianca! Bianca! Bianca!!
It was at that
moment I realized...
I had lost Bianca forever.
All that remained before me
was pitch black darkness.
I would never go back there,
or so I thought.
But I stepped beyond the
rusted gate once more...
Only, two weeks later...