What? An arranged marriage!?
Yes, they requested you
specifically.
He's the Prince of Savoia!
It's amazingly fortunate!
Y-yes.
I hope that he's a wonderful prince.
No!!
Open the door!
Whoa! This way's a dead end.
- No! Let me go!!
- Keep still!
I beg you, help me!!
Please!!
We've cornered your prey over here,
my Prince.
Well done, Bougette.
What do you think?
A splendid prey, is she not?
Yes. Not bad for a girl
from lower class royalty.
No!! Please, someone save me!!
No! Please stop it!
Stop! Don't!
Hey, calm down now.
Well, here we go!
Slave Market (Dorei Ichiba)
What's with the face?
It's not like you're the one being sold.
No, I'm just not
used to the smell.
Soon your dick will get hard
just from this smell. Come on.
Yeah.
I've come to this place again.
I thought I would never see it again,
but this is for the mission.
Palvis.
Yes! What is it, ambassador?
It seems that you like our slave girls.
W-well, I...
You see...
I am not judging you.
In fact, I encourage this behavior.
No one will suspect someone who
buys many slaves to be leaving soon.
B-but she has already...
Yes, I'm already aware.
I will issue you some funds.
What you do with it is up to you.
Thank you, sir.
My mission, in the event that
war becomes unavoidable,
is to get the information back to
the Republic as soon as possible.
Until then, the enemy cannot
know I am the informant.
This immoral action would seem
to be the perfect cover.
Unfortunately, this is not enough
to give her to you.
There must be something! Help me out!
I'm sorry, sir, but you must leave.
I guess you'll have to give up.
Give up? But...
We have to head back for now.
- H-hey! Quit pulling me, Ruka!
- They look like mercenaries.
Maybe they fell in
love with a slave?
I'm sorry to make you wait.
So, any girls you have your eye on?
Yeah, this one isn't bad.
What do you think, Casius?
How about that blonde haired girl?
Oh, that girl.
Come here, it's a customer!
This slave was born to a
good family in Lombardia.
I guarantee she can do housework,
read, and write.
A perfect mistress for a soldier
living alone, I would think.
Wait a minute, you fox.
You're trying to sell us damaged goods!
Look at those haughty eyes.
She's not a virgin. I knew it.
Oh, strong willed, eh? Take that!
Hey, Falco!
I-I'm very sorry. It is my fault that
I brought out a non-virgin.
But this slave does not have
a mark on her, inside or out.
She's ideal to use as you see fit,
and beautiful as well.
Don't bother. She's not a virgin,
and she has a bad personality.
No, I'll take her.
Hey,
Look, I'm warning you...
No, I've decided. I like those eyes.
Well, it's not my place to
tell you what you like...
Thank you very much.
The girl was delivered to me
the same day.
They had put her in an expensive
dress and cleaned her.
Her beautiful hair glistened in the sun,
and smelled of fresh cream.
What is it?
Well, there's no point in standing there.
Come in. I'll give you a tour.
It's not very big, but it's more
than enough for two...
I know you've been through a lot,
but I want you to relax and
use this place as if it were your own.
Oh...
Oh, I... umm...
Can you cook?
Yes...
Oh. I-It can be whenever you want.
I... don't want a servant.
Then what do you want?
Well I... I just wanted
to help you. That's all.
And how did you end up being here?
It's none of your business!
Wow, it's been a while since
I had such a feast.
Oh...
When I come back from my mission...
uh... from work, this'll be heaven.
From work?
I have a position at the Venetian embassy.
Oh, It's a little late, but I'm
Casius of Venice of the Palvis House.
Come to think of it,
I haven't caught your name yet.
I'm Cecilia.
Cecilia, huh?
I'll be counting on you.
C-Cecilia. W-wait, Cecilia.
That's not what I meant.
Then, what did you mean?
I... I just wanted
to say good night.
You really spent all that money,
just to rescue me?!
O-of course. I just...
I don't expect you to believe me.
S-stop that!
You're getting all hard, and you
expect me to believe you?
I c-can't help it.
I-It's just built that way.
You're just too cute.
W-what are you doing?
You can't sleep like this, right?
S-sorry, looks like it still
has some energy.
It's so strange.
I always thought men were filthy.
But you're clean,
smooth, and so pretty.
You're beautiful.
Don't stare at me.
Cecilia.
Flora...
From that day, we started acting
like a couple in love.
But I knew that it was all a lie.
If war started, then I would have
to go on my mission,
and Cecilia refused to speak
about her past.
We were simply looking away from reality,
and trying to be happy.
This momentary happiness...
Y-you! You're Cecilia, aren't you!
I finally found you,
you little cunt-on-wheels!
No!!
Come back here!
What's the meaning of this!
How dare you call the lady that!
Bastard! Do you know I am
Bougette of Savoia?!
Fine, then. I will have your hide
for this. I swear!
Cecilia...
Cecilia! Cecilia, what is it?
What happened?
I... I...
Don't be scared. I'm right here.
I'll protect you.
I was born in Lombardia, in Verona.
But I was born as peasant royalty,
to a family no one remembers.
Then one day, I was taken to the castle
in the Savoia Kingdom.
The Savoia Kingdom?!
Yes. They told me it was
an arranged marriage.
But I found out later that
my parents needed money.
T-they didn't?
They got 100 florins for
handing me to the kingdom.
Only 100 florins?!!
I never cared about money!
I didn't mind being peasant royalty!
That pig of a prince was already
promised to a French princess.
He wanted to get some actual
experience before the real thing...
A little more, Prince!
Bring glory to the Savoia kingdom!
Even after that, I was put into a
dirty room, becoming the pig's toy.
I wanted to die, but I couldn't.
I later found out I was pregnant.
Since I was no longer useful,
they sold me off to pirates...
and this is where I ended up.
I'm sorry. I made you relive
such a painful experience.
And the child?
At first, I didn't want that man's child.
But then, all I had was her.
All I had was Flora!
But she was sold off
and sent away too.
I have nothing now...
You have me. I'll always be here
to protect you.
Please, don't let me go!
Make me forget about the past!
Yes?
Yo, sorry to come suddenly.
And you are?
I'm Doracua, the leader of the
mercenary band Dragon Fire.
This is my second, Ruka.
Of course, there's only two of us.
Shut up. Let me do the talking.
So... what can I do for you?
Well, there's something I want to discuss.
Will you invite us in?
Is everything alright?
It's fine. Go back to your room,
and I'll take care of it.
Sorry, but aside from me,
there's a lady here,
and I'm not allowing
any strangers in the house.
The girl that was at Bytone's, right?
We need to borrow her.
I don't care what the circumstances are...
I don't care to hear them.
Whoa! Don't say that.
At least hear what we have to say!
We've been employed by
a Savoian named Bougette.
What!?
Look, listen to the whole story.
We're here to rescue Cecilia.
These strange mercenaries were hired
by Bougette to look for Cecilia.
According to them, they found out
their underhanded dealings, and...
decided to go back on their word,
and help the poor slave girl.
But why are they still after Cecilia?
What business do they have with her?
They're not after Cecilia.
It's her daughter, Flora.
Huh? What do you mean?
It seems the Savoian Prince
Bowman died suddenly.
Apparently, without conceiving an
heir with the French princess.
So they're looking for someone
who carries on the royal bloodline.
I see. But it's no use.
Cecilia doesn't know where she is either.
We know where the girl is.
What?
Are you serious?
Yeah, we found her in the hands
of some merchant.
And Doracua said he'd never let that
dirty Savoian have the kid,
so once again, we lose out
on getting our money.
Hey, it can't be helped...!
Where is Flora?!
Don't worry.
Flora is in a safe place.
Is that true?!
Yeah. I may not look it, but I have
pull with the Duke of Ferrara.
It's an easy thing to hide
a mother and daughter.
What? Then you...
Yeah, we were going to take you
to where you daughter is.
Really?! I can really see Flora again?!
Yes. And to prove it, we
brought you this.
Here.
This is the doll she always held...
I can't let you take Cecilia.
Please leave now.
This girl is mine.
Maybe you should rethink that.
If you don't leave...
You think you stand a chance?
You barely have field experience.
We don't want to hurt you.
So please rethink your decision.
They stink of lies.
Don't trust them.
Please! Let me go with them!
You would trust those
dirty mercs over me!?
I'm sorry.
You're running away from me?!
Stop! Not here!
Shut up!
No! Not like this!
P-please, remove the chains.
I-I can't hold it!
What can't you hold?
Answer me!
Y-you know what!
I can't hold it in!
I see... I understand.
H-hurry... Wait!
Where are you going!?
You're not serious!
We'll do this.
No! Not right here!
Quiet down!
You bastard!
What is it?
Please! Don't look! Look away!
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!!
You bastard! You say you want to help
but you're no different from the pig!
Stop it, you jerk! That hurts!
You lie. Look how much filthy
juice is flowing from you.
What... What are you...!?
Now, let's see about over here.
No! Not there!
Sorry to interrupt the fun.
No! Stop! Stop!
If you tell us where the
girl is, we will stop.
I don't know! I really don't know!
You bitch.
You underestimate me.
Do it.
W-what?
What are you doing? S-stop!!
S-stop...!
- Stop, stop... I don't know! I don't know!
- Now... if you don't tell me...
- Stop!
- Do it!
C-Cecilia!!
Well? Are you ready to talk?
What's going on?!
Y-you bastards!!!
C-Cecilia...
Sorry, but we're taking the girl.
And I don't forgive guys
who make a lady cry.
Don't!
Why would you... save him?
He may be a bad man,
but there was a time that he was kind.
Cecilia!
Hold on.
Here.
Thank you.
I'll only remember your kind side.
Goodbye.
Let's hurry...
I could do nothing as I watched
them leave, their images fading.
In my heart, I was crying out
Cecilia's name over and over.
As Falco once said, we would all be
swept into the insanity of war...
and I was to meet one
more fated woman.