I'm Yuzuriha Mizuki, the new
nurse at the university infirmary.
In addition to the usual nursing,
I'm sort of a counselor as well.
Somehow, the infirmary has become
the place to come for advice on sex...
...and I've had some strange
relationships with the female students...
...and Ms. Tsuchiya, a teacher.
Recently I noticed a male student,
Kirishima, and he's been on my mind.
Good morning, Ms. Mizuki.
Good morning.
Oh, Kirishima.
I guess they got together.
Ms. Mizuki!
Uh, yes?
Mr. Endo...
What's wrong?
You look a little dazed...
No, it's nothing...
You look depressed.
Why don't you, me and Ms.
Tuschiya go to karaoke after school?
That'll cheer you up.
Sounds good.
See you after school...
.
Ouch!
That hurt, Ms.Mizuki!
I'm sorry.
You all right?
There's something
wrong with you today.
What's wrong?
Is something on your mind?
Why do you come in here every
day when nothing is wrong with you?
I'm not in any extra-cirrucular
clubs, so I don't have anything to do.
But that's not...
Ms. Mizuki...
M-Ms. Tsuchiya.
Are you finished?
Let's go drinking.
But I still have a student...
Here, don't forget to lock up.
M-Ms. Tsuchiya.
Ms. Mizuki, I don't think
it's good to drink so much.
Ya know, young girls these days
have too much experience with sex.
Sounds like you're frustrated.
They just come in
to tell me their stories...
...I hardly ever get a
serious consultation.
What are you talking about?
Even if it's about sex,
they're really concerned.
Even me...
We all appreciate you
listening to our stories.
Y-You think?
So I guess it's not
such a waste of time.
Yeah, so I don't
understand what the problem is.
M-Ms. Mizuki...
Cheer up.
Mr. Endo would be shocked if he
knew I talked to you about dumping him.
You can't tell him.
Don't worry.
He's pretty naive
about those kinds of things.
You're horrible.
But, he is a good man.
Even after I dumped
him, we're still friends.
He was worried about you.
He said you looked depressed.
Hmm...
So, what's on your mind, huh?
Uh, er, it's nothing, really.
L-Let's drink some more.
What?
I'm being touched.
Who?
Kirishima?
Why, Kirishima?
Oh no, I'm naked!
N-No.
S-Stop.
Stop!
Oh no, I can't control my body.
Kirishima's touch makes me so horny.
I can hear my heart beating.
Something hot is coming inside me.
I can't believe it.
It's my first time, but I'm so wet.
I can't believe I feel so good.
Oh, god, it was just a dream.
What was. Did I...
D-Did the booze make me...
I shouldn't drink so much.
I left in such a hurry, I didn't ask...
...but I wonder what happened?
How am I going to face Mr. Endo?
Yes?
Excuse me.
M-Mr. Endo!
Ms. Mizuki, do you have a minute?
Yes, come in.
Er, uh, mmm, well...
Awfully humid today, isn't it?
Yes, uuuh, errr, it's uuuh...
Well...
Actually, I want to
talk about the other day.
Sorry, I don't remember a thing.
What?
I thought maybe we
could go to the movies.
So I will see you in front
of the theater on Sunday.
Did he just ask me out?
Sunday...
Oh, crap!
I have to return the book to the library.
Yes, it is Kirishima.
He wears glasses.
He looks different...
...so serious.
He's smiling.
He's thinking about something.
Looks like he's having a good time.
I'm sleepy.
I wonder how it's going
with Kirishima and Yoshinori.
Oh, I guess I fell asleep.
Please stop.
What is that?
Do you want it?
I do.
Okay, get on the desk.
Are you ready?
Hey, raise your ass.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Jeez!
I feel much better.
Really, kids these days do it anywhere.
Fortunately, they didn't
notice I was sleeping here.
By the way, I wonder
who put this on me?
What?
Kirishima, what are you doing?
Well, I just came in for some aspirin.
Ms. Mizuki's not here?
N-No, looks like she's out.
I put my jacket around her
because she looked cold in the library.
I can't go home without it.
So did you take any aspirin?
No, I can't get it without permission.
Don't worry, it's just aspirin.
Here, asprin and water.
Thank you.
So is it going well with Yoshinari?
I see you together
all the time these days.
You guys are going out, right?
Y-Yeah, we've been talking a
lot lately, but we're just friends.
Oh, really?
Yoshinari hasn't told
him how she feels yet.
She must really like him a lot.
We talk about video games and music.
We have so much in common.
Is that so?
I guess Kirishima is pretty dense.
I have to go.
Why don't you lie down till
your headache goes away?
Is it okay, without permission?
Don't worry about it.
Ms. Mizuki sleeps there all the time.
I wonder if she sleeps in this bed.
Oh, what am I doing?
What's this?
What's up with that jacket?
Nothing.
I was just asked to hold on to it.
Please don't touch it.
Anyway, you wanted to talk to me?
Well, I just...
Is it girl talk?
How do you know?
Well...
I want to ask your advice.
Okay.
Am I a loser?
What?
Well, it's always great in the
beginning, but it never lasts.
Like, she'll get a boyfriend...
I can't win...
...because I don't have a...
...you know.
I don't think it's just that.
You think there's a
problem with my personality?
Well, yes...
I have feelings too.
I understand that.
So can you comfort me?
I-I can't do that, Ms. Tsuchiya.
Why?
Don't you remember
having sex me with that night?
You were so into it.
We were sleeping
naked, does that mean...
I took off your clothes.
I wonder if Ms. Mizuki's back.
Stop, Ms. Tsuchiya.
I have to stop?
S-Someone's watching.
See you tomorrow.
I'll buy you lunch.
Thanks!
Okay, you can come out now.
Well, Ms. Mizuki.
I'm going to have you
come with me for a bit.
This is Ms. Mizuki's room.
What should I do?
Kirishima saw me.
So what did you see?
Well...
Y-You saw everything, didn't you?
It may seem a little strange,
but it's a kind of counseling...
The rumor is true, isn't it?
What rumor?
That you're a lesbian.
W-Who said that?
I wonder who it is?
A delivery?
Ms. Mizuki.
We've come to hang out.
Let us in.
Hide yourself, Kirishima.
Let us in!
Hi, Ms. Mizuki.
Jeezus!
Please listen to her, Ms. Mizuki.
Okay, okay.
You shouldn't drink so much.
That stupid Kirishima doesn't
even know how much I like him.
Why did I fall in love
with such a dense fool?
Oh well.
God, I had know idea she felt that way.
You didn't notice?
I thought we were friends.
And...
Is there someone else?
Yeah, there's someone on my mind.
I-Is that so.
I-If you like her, you've got go for it.
But, she's a little dense.
Then go for it with everything you have.
She's an older woman.
That doesn't matter if you like her.
Rumor has it she's gay.
Then show her
how good a man can be.
She's a teacher.
Yeah, but I like you,
and you're a student...
The woman you have on
your mind, is it Ms. Tsuchiya?
Well?
She's very dense.
So, is it true that you're a lesbian?
Well, it's a...
Why don't we find out?
Ms. Mizuki...
My heart is beating so fast.
I'm embarrassed, being touched there...
It's so hot it feels like it's on fire.
Oh, no, I'm all wet.
I can't stand it any more.
Come inside me, Kirishima.
Ouch!
Are you okay?
It doesn't matter, do as you like.
Ms. Mizuki, I'm coming.
Come!
I'm coming!
Ms. Mizuki.
Good morning.
Ms. Tsuchiya...
Something wrong?
You're especially
beautiful today, Ms. Mizuki.
Did you change your make-up?
No, not really.
Something's different.
Did you get a boyfriend?
No, that's not it...
Come on, tell me all about it.
What are you saying, Ms. Tsuchiya?
Hey, wait a minute.
Even if it's the same everyday,
today's lunch tasted particularly good.
Yes.
Ms. Mizuki, may I?
Yes, come in.
About our movie date...
...and what time we should meet...
Yes?
I thought we could have lunch before
the movie, so how about noon-ish?
Sure, sounds good to me.
Okay, then we'll meet at the
cafe across from the station.
See you Sunday.
I'm looking forward to it, right?
It's okay to have lunch with him.
Ms. Mizuki...
W-What's wrong, Yoshinari?
You don't like me?
Sorry, I never thought of you that way.
So then...
He dumped me.
D-Don't be so disappointed.
It's okay.
I sort of knew.
I just thought he was the best
man to have sex with for the first time.
Now...
Ms. Mizuki...
What?
Make me forget about Mr. Kirishima.
Is it all right?
Please, Ms. Mizuki.
All right...
Yoshinari, you know what...
I can do as I like, right, Ms. Mizuki?
I guess, if that'll make you happy.
We're both girls, so why...
It's so hot down there.
It's all wet and
slippery and feels so good.
Thanks, Ms. Mizuki.
I feel so much better.
I'm so tired.
What's going on Ms. Mizuki?
You look tired.
Oh no, nothing really...
Oh, yeah.
There's somewhere I want to take you.
Do you have time on Sunday?
What?
S-Sunday?
Okay, so I promised to
meet Kirishima at 4:00...
I can make it there
after the movie, right?
I'll have to since I promised.
Sorry, Ms. Mizuki.
Waiting long?
Not long, I just got here.
We still have time, right?
Yes, we can get to the
theater an hour before the movie.
Are you ready to order?
Coffee, please.
Sure.
I haven't been to the
movies for a long time.
Kirishima.
Are you okay?
Ms. Mizuki?
No, I'm fine.
Would you like to
get something to eat?
Yes.
Let me see...
What would you like?
W-Well, I guess the spaghetti soup.
Stop, Kirishima.
Not here...
What?
Oh no, I can't believe I moaned.
Are you okay Ms. Mizuki?
Yes.
N-No.
Uh, Ms. Mizuki?
Thank you very much.
Um, Mr. Endo...
I'm sorry...
...but I'm in love with someone else.
I'm sorry, Mr. Endo.
But...
S-Sorry, are you upset?
Come to think about it, I don't
even know how you feel about me.
I-I said it.
What?
I said it.
...to Mr. Endo, that
I'm in love with someone.
Ms. Mizuki.
I have a favor.
Can I ask it?
Yes.
Why did you bring me here
in the middle of the afternoon?
You said I could ask you a favor, right?
Yes, I did, but...
And...
What?
What is he thinking,
wanting to bathe with me?
Ms. Mizuki...
Let me wash you.
Okay.
AIready?
Not yet?
No, it's okay.
It feels so good!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Mr. Kirishima, you're...
Yes?
You're pretty sleazy.
And pretty experienced too.
You don't like it?
That sort of thing?
Meanie!
Haven't you forgotten something?
Mr. Endo!
What's wrong, Ms. Takeuchi?
You're in such a rush.
I have a question about the next class.
Okay, it's...
It's hard dealing with an intern.
I wish I had a female intern.
You're not thinking of hitting on
her because she's cute, are you?
You don't trust me, do you?
I've heard that you
seduce female students.
Okay, so I should prepare the papers.
And did you prepare
answer sheets from last time?
Oh!
You forgot, huh?
I'll do it right now.
Watch out!
You okay?
No need to be in such a hurry.
Calm down, okay.
Yes.
And so the intern's time passed...
Ms. Takeuchi, don't
you have a boyfriend?
I'm single.
Do you know somebody good?
How about Mr. Endo?
I heard Ms. Tsuchiya dumped him.
Oh yeah?
I heard things are
going well with Ms. Mizuki.
Really?
And the interns finally
completed their training...
Cheers!
Mr. Endo, thank you for
taking such good care of me.
You're welcome.
You worked hard.
You think so?
Yes, you did a good job, Ms. Takeuchi.
Yes, good job.
Yep, by the way, Ms. Mizuki...
Let's drink a lot tonight.
I can't drink so much.
Oh, come on.
Okay, so you'll take her to the station.
Jeez...
See you.
Take it easy.
Oh, are you okay, Ms. Takeuchi?
Mr. Endo, where should we go next?
What are you saying?
You're drunk already.
What?
You don't want to drink with me?
Ms. Takeuchi, are you an angry drunk?
Anyway, come with me.
Uh, Ms. Takeuchi...
I don't think it's good idea.
It doesn't really
matter what you think...
What?
When a girl likes someone...
...she wants it.
Wants what?
Wants that!
S-Stop it!
Mr. Endo, you're getting a little lively.
Well, it's a...
Looks yummy!
I'm gonna have some.
Mr. Endo, please.
She's wet through her panties.
Mr. Endo, that feels good.
Ms. Takeuchi.
You can put it in.
Make me come...
Oh, no.
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
I bet Mr. Endo did it with her.
She definitely had her eye on him.
M-Ms. Takeuchi...
But I want more.
No more?
I didn't say that, but...
I don't say that, but...
Then let's go drink more at your place.