Here she comes!
She's so pretty, pretty as always!
I'm a man, a man with passion!
I don't need logic!
What's with that man?
He's so hyper...
Shit, I was going
too fast and passed her!
Okay, it's still good, she'll come
up to me and ask me if I'm okay...
...and then maybe...
Um, are you okay?
Yes!
Oh my, just my type!
What kind of monster...
Hey, do you want to join me for dinner?
Forget it!
No, I don't want to!
How about a kiss?
I see, her name is Motoko.
What a pretty name.
What are you doing out here?
Do you live here?
Well, not really...
What was that?
Moko, good morning!
Good morning!
I'm out of coffee, can you spare some?
Sure, hold on.
Jogging again?
Yep, why don't you join me?
What a joke!
It's too embarrassing
to run at this time of day.
We can't help it.
We work evenings.
I'm a little embarrassed,
but at least it's healthy.
Oh, smoking's bad for your health!
Hey, aren't you enjoying being
embarrassed a little too much?
You know, it's only spring...
...but you already are wearing nothing
more than a tee-shirt and shorts.
And no bra, and you're always
showing off your belly-button...
It's obvious that you are trying
to attract the attention of men!
No, I'm not.
You're really over-sexed
and perverted, aren't you?
No, I'm not!
But, I feel sorry for the guys...
...they must be grabbing their crotches
and getting nose-bleeds over you!
I mean...
Oh, I got it!
You're really a sex maniac,
that's why you became a masseuse!
No, I wanted to dedicate
my life to public service...
...by pleasing men, that's why...
I understand, otherwise you
wouldn't wear these kind of kinky panties.
No!
You're so mean!
Talking to you always wakes me
up, I don't need any coffee now.
Also, you're a pervert!
See you at the parlor!
I hate you!
You really are a sex maniac,
that's why you became a masseuse...
I'm not a pervert!
I'm going to wear this!
Okay, time to get dressed!
Oh no, I look so sexy!
Why am I so excited?
You're bad!
I can't stop it!
God, I saw an angel!
You bastard, what
did you do to my stock?
Oh no, what was I just doing?
Hell, look at him!
Oh my, it's huge!
You must've been
peeping in on someone!
Oh, was I being watched?
No, Lisa will tease me and
call me an exhibitionist pervert!
How could that dumb
cop call me a pervert?
Anyway, where is she
going at this time of day?
Where is she going, is it on a date?
If I asked her out,
I'd take her to a trendy spot.
Why the hell is she
walking in this area anyway?
Is she lost?
Good morning!
What the hell?
Hi, Moko, your customer
from yesterday was very pleased.
Oh really?
Yes, he said that your
service was really kinky and special.
He also said that your technique was
something only a real pervert could do.
A real pervert...
I just don't
understand what's going on here!
Welcome, it's been a
long time, Mr. Hirooka.
Yeah, I've been busy, you know.
Oh, that's my Moko!
From every angle I look,
it says Massage Parlor!
Oh, I got it!
Hey, how long are you
going to skip on your debts, huh?
Please, bare with us,
just one more month...
Please...
Begging doesn't help, you moron!
Please, show us a little mercy...
Please, we'll pay you back...
Hey, you're quite good looking.
Okay, I'll take your
daughter instead of the money.
Come with me.
Help, father, help!
I see what happened to her...
If that's the case,
I must save this innocent angel.
Stop, Mr. Hirooka!
If you keep watching,
I'll be so embarrassed!
Oh, I just had to stare at you!
No!
It's more than just as good as it looks...
No, stop watching!
I can't...
...hold back!
I'm coming!
Me, too!
You're the best!
You're so sexy and kinky!
Did I see something?
Must be my imagination!
Is this the way?
It feels so good!
Is that her?
No, it's not.
I see, your friend told you that...
I always say I've dedicated
myself to public service...
...but maybe I just like having sex.
That sounds so filthy...
I don't think there's anything wrong with
being horny or perverted, or whatever!
Do you know why
I come to this parlor?
As the chairman of the
educational committee...
...I don't want our children to
become masseuses when they get older.
That's why I never came to
this kind of place before I met you.
I just couldn't.
But now, I'm your customer.
Do you know why?
It's because you like sex.
I was so happy to find
out someone like you existed.
I like the fact you enjoy having sex.
I bet your other
customers feel the same way.
They enjoy it because they
know you enjoy it with them.
I think being
perverted can be a good thing.
Yes!
If it pleases my customers,
I'll be happy to be perverted!
But, I feel like I just got a
lecture from a school teacher.
Forget that, it's just my
habit to preach like that!
Eat my fist of justice!
Mr. Hirooka!
Good, I did it!
My angel, Ms. Motoko...
...I've come to rescue you!
What are you talking about?
It's okay, don't say anything.
I know you work here
because of your father's debts.
You're being forced to do this.
Debts?
What was that noise, Moko?
Manager!
What?
It's you, then!
You're the one who's forcing her...
You're the loan shark!
Manager!
It's okay, Motoko.
What's okay?
You beat up my
customer and the manager...
Who are you anyway?
I came to rescue you
from this place, my angel.
You must be confused.
Me, confused?
Yes.
I'm working here on my own free will!
What?
I'm doing this job because I like it.
No!
I'm telling you, I love it!
No way!
I'm normal and I love sex.
No, that can't be true!
You're hopeless...
Why don't you try me?
You must be really
frustrated, aren't you?
I knew it, come on, I'll lick you!
Pardon me!
He left?
I guess he doesn't like sex...
...but it's such a good thing!
Welcome, I'm so glad
you came again, Mr. Funaki!
I'll give you really deep
service today, so be ready!
Y-Yes, please...
First, a blow job...
Chair wash...
A bath and a sixty-nine...
Be careful with the mattress wash...
I'm Masahiro Funaki, university student.
The reason why I started
coming to a massage parlor was...
It started half a month ago...
Hello?
Funaki, it's me, Madoka...
Sorry, were you asleep?
I'm in Roppongi now,
I can't catch a cab so...
Really, can you pick me up?
Great!
Well, well, what a night...
I'm on my way, Madoka!
Thanks for today, I really appreciate it.
So, if there's anything, I might call you.
Wait, Madoka, what
about our date tomorrow?
Oh, sorry, I have
other plans for tomorrow.
See you, good night!
Shit, I'm just another chauffeur...
...right?
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm okay.
Really?
Oh, your leg...
I must have fallen and scratched it!
It's not the kind of injury
I'd go to the hospital for.
Well, let me give you a ride.
Thank you.
Thank you for taking me home.
Oh, no, I didn't mean to be invited in.
It's quite all right.
I can't let you go, since you
were nice enough to give me a ride!
Here, go ahead.
What a difference from Madoka!
Please, go ahead.
Yes...
Oh, why is your nose bleeding?
Here, have some tissue.
Thanks!
What's wrong?
Well, um, it's too
much stimulation for me...
Oh, my god!
I'm sorry I was careless.
Oh, my pleasure...
Excuse me for asking you this, but...
You haven't done it
for a while, have you?
I'm so ashamed.
I knew it!
If you like...
...please come to
the parlor where I work.
You'll feel great!
Hello, this is Madoka.
Hi, Madoka.
Oh, it's you.
What, dinner?
Sorry, I'm real busy, so I'll
call you some other time, okay?
Hello?
Bye!
So, I'm just a chauffeur...
That's how I came to this
massage parlor for the first time.
What, she didn't even
let you hold your hand?
But she still called you for a ride?
Awful, terrible, I can't stand it!
I was okay with it.
If I kept doing whatever she wanted,
I thought she would one day realize...
Funaki!
I was hoping so, but not anymore!
Not another driver's sob story!
Hello?
Funaki, it's me!
I'm having a hard time catching a taxi.
Please, can you come over?
That's it!
Do you have any idea
what time it is, you crazy bitch?
Crazy bitch?
Did I say too much?
It's okay, I have Moko.
How dare he say that!
I'll never, ever forgive him!
Welcome!
That's how I started
coming to see Moko.
Welcome!
Hey, can you really
afford to come here so often?
What do you mean?
What about the money,
aren't you still a student?
Don't worry, I sold my car.
It's okay, I got rid of that woman.
I don't need to drive and be a chauffeur.
I can't stand it!
I was going to find out...
...how he could dump a gorgeous
woman like me, so I followed him.
He's a regular at this place!
Mr. Funaki, don't misunderstand me!
To you, I'm just a
lover for forty minutes...
You shouldn't be so
into it that you sell your car.
I feel responsible.
Hey you, hold it!
I found you!
Madoka!
Madoka, you're the one...
That's right, I'm Madoka.
You slut, how could you
steal someone else's man?
You were just using
him to save cab fare!
So, for a cab or
whatever, my man is mine!
I can't stand losing
him to another woman!
On top of that, you're a
professional masseuse!
My pride can't stand for that!
You just caught him with your
body, but I've got a perfect body, too!
Outrageous!
Splendid, you have a great body!
Kay!
Hey, who are you?
I'm another professional masseuse,
and I heard what you were saying.
So, Moko stole your
boyfriend by using her body!
Not my boyfriend, my man!
Well, he's the second priority anyway.
I don't care about his
ranking, he was stolen, right?
Then, why don't you get
him back with a showdown?
To find out who pleases him more,
you both should have sex with him.
That sounds fine to me, let's do it!
Moko, are you in too?
Yes.
Don't underestimate me because I'm
an amateur, I've had enough experience.
I'll go first!
First, this position...
Right there, right there, isn't that good?
For a taxi substitute
like you should be thankful...
...to have sex with me!
Not yet!
No, not yet!
You're a really lucky
guy, doing it with me!
Now, it's the professional's turn!
I made him come three times
already, he won't come so easily now...
Mr. Funaki, are you all right?
Moko, I'm so worn out...
I knew I was going to win!
We'll see...
You must be so exhausted,
why don't you take a break?
Sorry.
It's okay, relax, you don't
have to force yourself to have sex.
Moko!
You've recovered so
soon, you're so manly!
Fantastic!
Moko!
If you want a woman
like me, please take me!
Oh, that's great!
Finally, they're doing it.
Look at his face.
He looks different from
when he was with you.
What about it?
There's something very different.
He is moving himself.
That son of...
You're so selfish, you use sex as a tool!
You're not a caring girl like Moko,
you're just a low-life, Dutch wife!
How dare you?
I'm coming!
Me too!
I like you, I like you, Moko!
I'd say this decides the competition.
How could I lose him to a prostitute?
Moko!
I have to do
something about this, otherwise...
How could you
play with his innocence!
You devil, you cold hearted bitch!
No...
Yes, that's right, you vicious slut!
Cold blooded pussy!
Trailer trash!
You don't deserve Funaki!
Yeah, you don't deserve a
man, get yourself a vibrator!
Why don't you just kill yourself!
Stop it, don't be so hard on her.
I know she has a sweet side too.
Why did you stand up for me?
Because, I'm your man.
Funaki...
Madoka.
I'm sorry.
Moko, you called
her names on purpose.
If you insult a woman that much,
any normal guy will take her side.
Well, I'm relieved it
was settled the right way.
But, I'll kind of miss
one of my regular clients.
Hey you, I think you have
a good body and some talent!
The pay's good, would
you like to work here?
What, really?
Madoka, let's go!
Manager!
Moko!
It's so chaotic!
Let's see, Moko, who has big teary
eyes, and big breasts is an ex-nurse!
She switched careers to
cater to gentlemen's needs.
Any man will feel revived
after her sincere service!
Her favorite position is missionary,
and her sweet spot is right there...
Finally, Moko is
featured in this magazine!
I want her to be more popular!
Welcome!
Hi, I heard that you're in that magazine.
Yes!
If you become too
popular, I'll miss you.
No matter how busy I
become, I won't change.
No, I'll try to be even better.
To me, the most important
thing is to please my customers!
Come here, mister.
Moko!
I'm coming!
Me, too!
Thank you very much.
I'm so tired from
trying so many positions.
Oh, Moko.
Your next customer is waiting.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes, I was waiting for almost an hour!
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I saw this magazine and you looked
so pretty that I came here from the city.
Oh, I'll give you a
very special service then.
Yeah, you better.
Hello, Bunny in the Moonlight.
You'd like to book Moko?
She is booked until 8pm...
...is after 8pm okay with you?
Thank you.
Another one of Moko's appointments?
Yeah.
The magazine's effect is amazing.
Indeed.
Thank you very much.
Oh, finally I'm done.
Good job.
Staff room...
What're you doing in there?
Get ready for your next customer!
I'm on my way!
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
T-Thank you very...
Hey, Moko, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm okay.
You don't look okay.
Since you started
today, you haven't had a break.
Why don't you ask to call it a day?
Not yet...
I may have another appointment.
As long as I have
customers, I can't leave.
Moko, the manager says to get ready.
Oh, my!
I'm on my way.
Are you sure?
Don't kill yourself.
Are you feeling okay?
Your legs are shaking.
I'm fine.
Aren't you a little tired?
I'm quite all right.
What's going on Moko, it's not like you!
I should do some
stretching to refresh myself.
Are you really okay?
Moko, Moko!
Are you awake?
Where am I?
Staff room.
My customer?
I asked him to leave, I had no choice.
I'm sorry...
You're so clumsy.
You did your best, right?
Let's go home, it's past quitting time.
Moko, I'll give you a ride.
I have a car today.
Oh, I really appreciate it.
You're pretty stubborn, aren't you?
Why do you have to do it
until you actually pass out?
Because I should do
my best for my customers...
...they pay a lot to come and see me.
It depends on time and the situation.
Like today, when you have too many
appointments, you have to take it easy.
What, take it easy?
You've become such
a popular masseuse...
...so you need to know
how to handle your clients.
But, I don't know how to take it easy.
But if you get sick, it's going
to affect the other girls, too.
Won't you feel bad
for your customers...
...if you aren't available
because don't feel well?
Oh, I understand.
But I don't know how to relax.
Don't worry, I'll tell you how.
Welcome, I'm Moko.
Please to meet you.
Oh, you look prettier than in the picture.
Well, sir...
Yes?
I'm new here, I don't
know exactly what to do.
So, basically, say you're
too new to be good at it.
These days, customers prefer to
have somebody not so professional.
You know, 'the girl next door' type.
I see.
You don't know anything?
Oh, I got it, so let me teach you...
Actually, I like someone
who's not so experienced.
Oh, good!
Kay was right.
I don't know how to
wash a mattress or chairs...
Oh, don't worry about it.
That stuff is a little
bothersome anyway, so...
Oh, thank you.
It's so comfy!
I'll teach you how to
make love the right way.
Well, please be gentle...
Just let the customer
do whatever he wants.
I'm coming in.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back.
Wow, it's really easy.
Yes, easy is good, but...
I think something is missing.
I'll wash you, here, here.
See, you have to wash here carefully...
I'll show you how
to do wash a mattress.
Something's different.
I'll come again.
The customers seem to be
content, but I think something's wrong.
Here I am.
I don't know, they looked so happy...
Hey, young lady!
What are you doing,
ignoring the customer?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm Kawakami.
I heard about your reputation, and I
wanted to see how good you really are.
Therefore, I came all the way here.
Make me happy.
Oh, I'm so happy to have you here.
Let's get started.
Well, sir...
What!
You don't know anything?
Sorry, but I was hoping you
could teach me what you like.
Here, this is for you.
I'm leaving now.
Mr. Hirooka lost his
talent for finding good ones.
Wait, you know Mr. Hirooka?
Indeed, I personally
heard about you through him.
He told me you were really sincere,
and the best masseuse in the industry.
Well, so long.
Oh, I know...
I know what was missing!
Excuse me, sir!
That wasn't the real me.
That wasn't my kind of service!
The only thing I can be good at is
providing the sincerest service I can.
It's also my pleasure to see
my customer's happy face!
No more...
...slacking off!
Here, mister, let's try it
one more time on the bed.
No, I can't, I can't make it...
Yes, you can.
Ready?
Thank you very much.
Therefore...
I won't be 'taking it easy'
anymore, all right Kay?
Sure, I'm just a little
concerned about your health.
Don't worry about that!
One, two, one, two...
I started working out more.
One, two...
Suit yourself.
How did you like Moko?
As you said, she was incredible.
She's a nice girl, isn't she?
Yes.
I'll keep up my good
service, and my reputation!