A sex story can happen anytime, anywhere long as there's a man a woman.
I checked thoroughly.
There's only two girls.
I hear that they are loaded with cash.
Story 1: The Mansion
Hey, Bitch! Don't make me laugh!
Don't tell me this is all you got.
I can't leave this shit-hole without the
money from your dead husband.
This is pocket change.
Yeah, Ma'am.
Mother...
We don't have the money.
It's all at the bank.
We want the money now!
If you don't got the dough on you, then...
Mother...
Hiroko...
You know what, right?
You sure are pretty.
You look like a sister to your daughter.
Hey girl, how ya' doing?
Looks like you're still a virgin.
Let me help you.
Stop it!
What...!?
What a sexy bra you have on.
You have a good taste, bitch.
Lets see what's underneath.
Stop it!
You got great tits, bitch!
Wait
I will do anything, so please... not my daughter.
You have no money, right!?
Either way, she has a great body that we can't refuse.
C'mon
Bitch.
Why don't you suck my cock in front of your
daughter and show her how it should be done.
Never...
Ma'am, I don't think you have any decision in this.
Ouch!
Ma'am, if you don't listen...
Hiroko!
You don't want me to hurt your cute daughter?
Honey, forgive me...
Hurry up, bitch!
You have great tongue techniques!
Feels good.
Bitch, you are good.
Your dead husband must be proud.
Alright, it's your turn little one.
C'mon, girlie.
No!
Hiroko!
Can you feel it? Do you like it?
Hey, trade me.
Swap already?
You sure like young girls.
No time to rest.
Ma'am, show me your ass.
Mother!
C'mon Ma'am. Lie down and stick your ass out.
I said stick your ass out!
Ma'am, it's such a sexy view
Let me make you feel better by sticking mine in!
Take off your panties, Ma'am.
Hurry!
You are so fucking wet already.
C'mon, stick your ass out!
This used pussy sure feels great!
I'll have this girl then.
No!
Oh my, is this your first?
I feel so honored.
What are you... going to do to my daughter?
If you do not want to be hurt...
Don't move...
It hurts... help me, Mother!
Please stop... Hiroko... Hiroko!
This virgin is so tight!
How do you like it?
Ma'am, I'm thirsty. Do you have any beer?
It's inside the refrigerator...
Just as planned, Mother.
We have to protect Dad's wealth with our body.
A wooden mannequin again?
The school brochure said real girls modeling.
Class, I got a girl for you today.
Let me introduce.
Her name is Miyuki Yanagiba.
I have never modeled for something like this.
Hope I do well.
Story 2: In the Name of Art
She's cute.
Nice body too.
Her naked!?
Please take it all off.
Please be quiet class.
Ms. Yanagiba.
Please undress for us.
Take it off already?
You can keep your bra and panties on.
I thought he was going to say be completely naked.
I think this will be easy.
Is there a problem?
No, here I go.
Ms. Yanagiba, please sit on the edge of the bed and cross
your legs.
Yes, not a problem.
Maybe I'll take off my bra too.
The pay is good and I'm only showing.
I'll pretend that I'm a mannequin.
You can keep the bra on.
I believe that it will help their creativity.
Ms. Yanagiba, your body is a bit stiff.
Please relax and be more natural.
Thanks for the advice.
This is such an easy job.
But I need more excitement.
Wow, they all look serious.
I think I'm getting turned on.
Teacher.
Yes?
Her expression is like a doll.
Really?
That's a great smile.
Keep that smile.
I'm getting tired.
Ms. Yanagiba, you must be getting tired.
Undress your panties and take hold a pose.
But I can't... Alright.
It was part of the agreement...
Please.
OK.
I'm a bit wet, how embarrassing.
Wow, amazing.
Everyone is looking... I'm getting very excited.
Nice...
Everyone is looking...
Everyone, class is over
If you want to stay for the special
class, please pay the fees now
We will, we will!
Me too!
5,000 yen a pop for the special class.
That means 100,000 yen in all.
We will be starting the special class.
Don't close your legs.
We need to draw.
She's pink as a virgin.
I never seen a vagina.
All this attention is making me very wet.
Teacher, Ms. Yanagiba's vagina is
twitching and pouring something.
Teacher, can I spread them?
The agreement said no touching.
Please don't touch.
If we don't, we won't get any ideas.
They'll find out that I'm wet.
Ms. Yanagiba, your nipples are hard.
Wait a second, there's no touching!
Let go now!
What gives!?
If I don't touch, I won't get any ideas.
You're getting paid for this.
Teacher, Ms. Yanagiba is being
rude, making it impossible to draw.
Everyone, please work together
Stop it, stop it!
Ms. Yanagiba is very wet.
Someone please check out the toughness, the
smoothness and the deepness of her womanhood.
I will go first.
Crap, they are going to find out I'm excited.
We're paying her a lot, so have some fun.
Man, you are soaking wet.
Don't touch...
The model is overflowing with juice.
Don't look, I'm getting wet.
Please don't stick it in, keep looking!
That won't fit!
Keep looking...
No!!!!
This...
How is it, explain!
It's tight inside.
But also very wet.
Her ass is getting wet too.
I'll cum in her ass.
Teacher, this isn't the agreement.
Don't cum inside... stop...
Cumming!
Her ass is great.
So girls can cum in a gang bang.
How about yourself?
It's great.
You'll know what I mean once you try it out.
According to the seating order, I'm next.
Lets trade then.
I'll check out her mouth then.
I see.
The mouth stimulates the penis very well.
How do the anal muscles work?
Everyone, study well.
Hurry up, man.
My grade for this class is terrible.
Please... stop!!
Stop... no... no...
It's killing me.
No... no... no!!!!
Not the butt... it hurts...
People looking at me got me excited...
Hey, Model. There's still a lot
that needs to finish their drawing.
Hey, Model.
This is my new job.
I can't get excited without people looking at me.
THE END