Where are my glasses?
Linia...
Good morning, Sayaka.
You slept late.
G-Good morning.
Good morning, Sayaka.
Good morning, Linia...
Misuzu, I thought you
went to bed late last night.
No.
It wasn't very late, because
there was a sudden blackout.
Blackout?
Didn't you know?
N-No...
W-What's up?
What were you doing with Linia?
A-Aki is not up yet, right?
I'll go to wake her up.
If you are talking about Aki...
If you are talking about Aki,
she went outside with Lui.
Misuzu doesn't pay attention to me...
...ever!
Whatever human beings or androids...
...she can't keep her
hands off any cute girl.
Really, what's wrong with her eyes?
There is a beautiful girl right here, right?
Ouch!
Hey, wait!
I won't forgive you!
I feel stupid...
Misuzu...
W-Who?
W-What...
O-Ouch!
L-Let go!
Leave me alone!
Let go!
You are cute...
No!
Here's the old man...
I mean, this is our guy.
Linia, you know him?
No, but...
Maybe I just don't remember...
Misuzu, what is this
''Complete Chip Outline''?
I guess it outlines a Chip that was
abandoned after problems in development.
A-Again?
Give me a break.
It blacked out last night
when I was researching, too.
It's strange.
Were the cords unplugged?
You are careless sometimes,
so maybe you forgot something.
Linia!
Linia, you can hear me, right?
Don't try to escape anymore.
Give me the Complete Chip.
Otherwise, there will be trouble.
Who are you?
What do you mean
by the Complete Chip?
That's Lui.
What happened?
What's that?
Wait, what's going on?
A-Aki!
Aki.
Aki!
Aki, you are alive, right?
Wake up, Aki.
Aki!
Aki, you okay?
M-Misuzu...
Aki!
That's awful!
Who did such an awful thing?
Anyway, we have to
take her to the hospital.
Misuzu, help me.
All right!
Did you understand?
I'll tell you once more...
Give me the Complete
Chip without saying a word...
Don't escape or resist like last night.
Otherwise, the other
two girls will look like that.
Linia!
What are you doing, Linia?
Call the hospital, right now.
And get the first aid kit!
Yes.
It doesn't work, no matter what we try.
The phone circuit is broken.
Not only the phone, but the
electricity doesn't work as well.
Everything is because
of that android, isn't it?
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
I can't believe that Aki
was hurt because of me...
What should I do?
No, it's not your fault.
Anyway, the android really
said "Complete Chip," right?
Yes...
And she said I did
something last night...
You've done something?
Is that related to the Complete Chip?
Did the phone work?
No, I don't think so.
Okay.
Then we should drive
down to the hospital in the city.
Sayaka, please go with them.
What are you saying?
You're coming with us.
No, I can't.
I'll stay here.
Then I'll stay here, too!
Okay...
I'll take her to the hospital.
I'll be back as soon as possible.
Lock the doors up tight.
Yes, please be careful.
Linia, let's have tea.
Well, thank you but, I can't...
It's okay...
It's just this feeling...
...that I don't want tea by myself...
I'm really sorry.
Everything is my fault.
That's enough.
I just want to stay with you.
I'm sorry.
By the way, did you remember
anything about the Complete Chip?
I wanted to talk about it.
Misuzu said there was a
blackout last night, right?
Yes.
Maybe I'm the cause of that.
That kind of thing happened before...
After that, it happened again and again.
It's a defense mechanism,
which you can't control consciously.
Maybe it is, but for me it's not...
Wait here until I dispose of Linia.
I see!
Dr. Zen finished the
Complete Chip ten years ago!
You were the trial
product that was mounted with it.
I was the trial product...
That means, Dr. Zen made me...
I'm sure.
Efficiency of the
Complete Chip is very good.
Androids like you are
difficult to make, even today.
However, the
Complete Chip had a secret.
Robots with the Chip react...
...when put under certain stresses...
...by shorting out or destroying
electronics, as you experienced.
So, it's possible that there are some
dangerous people, who want to abuse it.
They are the ones after you now.
I can't believe it.
I'm scared.
I have such a thing inside of me...
But, if everything
you said was the truth...
...then I should never have been made.
A machine that
destroys other machines.
An android that can't
help humans be happy...
T-That's not true, Linia!
I think Dr. Zen hid you for ten years!
He wanted to guard you
from people who want the Chip.
It was the feelings Dr. Zen had that
made him put you to sleep for ten years.
I like you, Linia...
Sayaka...
Linia, you look so wonderful.
You shouldn't...
Linia...
Sayaka, I'm already...
Please come here...
Sayaka...
S-Sayaka, I love you...
Me too, Linia, I love you...
Sayaka...
Linia.
Linia!
Hold Lui and hide behind the couch.
Right now!
Please don't follow me!
I told you not to oppose me.
Linia!
You've been wasting my time, it's over.
Give me the Complete Chip.
No!
Linia!
Are you ready, Linia?
I can't give the Complete Chip to them.
I'll keep you from them.
Master...
Linia, I made you sad
because of my thoughtlessness.
At least, I want to
know that you will be safe...
...ten years from now
when you awake in the future.
This will protect you
when you next wake up.
But, it will also block your memory.
If that's what you want, it's okay.
I'm sorry Linia.
I'm happy that I have you
stored away in my memory...
...even if I can't remember.
Good bye...
Master, be safe...
Master...
Your defense mechanism worked.
Yes...
Is she broken?
No, I just interrupted her functioning.
Lui, because of you...
Thank you...
Sayaka, I must find my Real Master.
His name is Dr. Zen.
I believe my Real
Master is alive somewhere.
I have to look for him.
I want to thank him for everything...
Linia...
I'm really happy that I
was able to meet you.
Linia, can I see you again?