Misuzu!
Why did we come here in this old car?
An old car is perfect
for this environment.
It's rough and full of character,
unlike the car I always drive.
We should always get
this kind of stimulation.
Sometimes you're very old-fashioned,
although you're the head of Roboken.
I'm sorry.
W-What are you doing?
Where would you be if you couldn't
borrow the old-fashioned girl's note book?
I'm sorry.
I was able to hand in my final paper and have a summer break with everybody...
...all because of you.
It's okay...
I expect a reward later.
Why are we the only two?
I asked if you would like to go to the
Institute of Nature's protection area with me.
You didn't say we
would be the only two.
We haven't done it for a while.
I want to smell you.
This is all because of you...
Y-You planed this from
the beginning, didn't you?
You smell good...
You are lovely, Sayaka...
When I couldn't see you,
I touched myself everyday.
And I always thought
of when we made love.
Again and again...
M-Misuzu...
Oh, Misuzu!
It's a little early but
it's okay, you can come.
I found you!
Misuzu, what are you doing?
A-Aki...
You're mean!
You disappeared
without saying anything to me.
You weren't in the Roboken office,
and the library was closed because...
...they were reorganizing.
I thought I couldn't see
you until next semester.
I felt so sad, and I cried.
But, my sad heart reached God.
I was in front of the main auditorium...
...when Maiko came and
told me what you said earlier...
...about the school Institute
Custodian having a summer vacation, too.
She didn't...
Misuzu, Aki, I'll go and cook.
I'll help you.
No way!
You have to be with me.
Don't cheat on me.
Excuse me!
Lui, come on!
Don't go, please, Sayaka!
Get your hands off!
I said, no!
Sayaka!
Misuzu, say ''Ahh.''
N-No, thank you.
Where are you going?
What happened?
Is there anything outside?
Just a moment, I'll open the door.
Oh, hey! Lui!
Oh no, it's too dark to see anything.
I guess I should go see...
Lui, what's going on?
M-My goodness...
Is she dead?
E-Excuse me?
Is it an Android?
What should I do?
No!
Stop it!
She's awake.
You mean it's functioning, right?
Please, don't be scared.
We're not from the Inspection Bureau.
I'm Sayaka and she is Misuzu.
Why were you in such a place?
Did you do something wrong?
Or did you run away from your owner?
Good morning.
Misuzu, who is that woman?
She is an android.
Oh, an Android?
Isn't she a lost-roid?
Seriously, why did you pass out there?
I don't know anything...
I lost my memory.
Then, you don't even
remember your name?
Yes, I do remember my name.
I'm Linia.
What, a Black Broker?
Yes, it's an organization that
distributes unidentified and illegal androids.
I've heard they illegally
remodel those androids.
Do you think she escaped from there?
It's possible.
I don't think it's easy to
make such an elaborate android.
And, it's strange that she doesn't
remember anything except her name.
If it's true, don't you need
to call the Inspection Bureau?
We don't get that many
chances to inspect androids like her.
I want to examine her.
Linia, are you all set?
Well, do you feel refreshed?
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You don't have any
model or registration number.
You may be custom-made, but...
Your skin is really beautiful.
It's exciting...
S-Say...
I-I'm sorry.
You guys shouldn't do anything to me!
Why did you say such thing?
Linia...
You want to see, too?
You like Linia, don't you?
Um, Sayaka, I'm finished.
I like this one, is it okay?
Yes, it suits you, right?
Thank you.
I can't...
I couldn't restore her
memory past six months ago.
How come?
Her memory block
is very well protected.
I'm sure that there still
are memories in it, though.
Her newest parts are over ten years
old, and the skin damage rate is 0.07%.
Exhaustion is minimal.
Linia...
It seems you were carefully
stored somewhere for ten years.
Ten years...
I can't be absolutely positive
without researching more but...
I think this protection can be cleared
only by the person who devised it.
You mean, the designer?
Yes, he's a real master.
A real Master...
Anyway, this is all I know.
I have to access the
information bank at our school.
I'm bored!
Boring! I'm bored!
You don't play with me at all!
W-What?
We are sorry, Aki, but Linia
is a girl who needs our help.
Okay, fine.
Then, let's have a picnic.
We basically came here for fun...
I love you!
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I'll make a picnic basket then.
Yes, please.
Isn't it cold?
Stop it!
Wow!
Did you make all of them?
Yes, but it's not really...
Your fundamental program was
originally set up specializing in housework.
Yes!
Looks like Lui really likes your cooking.
Here.
I can't...
Oh, yes...
But, thank you so much.
You're bad!
You frightened me!
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, come on Lui!
She was unconscious because of av
temporary overload when you found her.
She had been running in
the woods for a long time.
Even though she overloaded...
Yes, I've never seen such a
perfect custom-made model.
Also, she was made
more than ten years ago...
Ten years ago, androids
looked like mechanical dolls.
Robot technology was still humble.
Do you think that has something
to do with her protected memories?
I don't know...
Are you talking about that again?
Anyway...
Linia seems like just a good housework
model, but she is something more.
She has some kind of secret,
which even she doesn't know.
It's okay, Sayaka, I'll do it.
I'll lose my pride as a human
being if I make you do everything.
But...
It's okay.
I want to be with you.
I see.
Thank you, then.
Sure.
I guess this is good...
Linia!
What happened?
Nothing, I'm okay...
Linia!
Misuzu, when will you finish?
Let's go to bed!
No way!
I have to research Linia.
Misuzu...
Hey, that's enough!
You're so mean!
I'm leaving.
Oh, well...
This is it.
Dr. Yusuke Zen, born in 1963.
His specialty is
android circuit control theory.
He published a complete chip
outline ten years ago and after that...
He's missing!
Oh, no.
Linia, what can I do for you?
I'm all right.
I'll be fine, soon.
No, you're not fine at all.
I'll bring Misuzu here.
Please don't leave...
Linia...
Linia?
Sayaka, I'm...
No, no...
No, Linia...
Before I escaped from...
...the Black Broker and
came here I was remodeled.
Now, sometimes I can't control myself.
Linia...
Master...
Master, you are wonderful...
I'm not your master...
No...
...you are my master...
T-That's...
I can be used by both sexes.
I wasn't asking if you were...
I love you, truly.
Linia...
So good, Linia...
Linia, I'm already...
Master!
I'm coming!
Linia...
Blackout?
That's strange, this place has its
own generator, so it shouldn't blackout.