You're finished already?
That didn't do it for me.
Yeah, but at least it's
better than last time.
Listen, Madam...
if you really want
to hold onto this inn...
you need to do a lot better than that.
You're on the brink, you know...
No!
SWALLOWTAIL INN
1st Night
I am the proprietor
of the Swallowtail Inn.
My name is Yuriko Shiratori.
It was a lot classier
before, don't you think?
The food isn't what
it used to be, either.
Ever since I lost my husband,
who previously ran the inn...
the business has been falling apart...
and I'm having a hard
time staying afloat.
The most serious set back is the
loss of our best chef, my husband.
Our cuisine has suffered considerably.
With things the way they
are, I can't really blame our...
...regular customers for staying away.
But I just don't have the
money to hire a new chef.
It's all I can do to
keep my head above water.
All I can do is try to handle
what I can and hope for the best.
I can't...
I can't even do this right!
I'm the most pathetic woman...
Ma'am!
Oh, it's you, Harumi.
You're supposed to be taking it easy,
you shouldn't be running like that.
You have to come, quick!
What happened? Are you all right?
Stay with us, now...
Are you all right?
Maybe you hit yourself when you fell...
No, I'm all right.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please, get some rest now.
What?
That's right. I can't
remember who I am at all...
Do you think it's amnesia?
I have no idea how I came to be
lying there when you found me.
How awful for you...
If you'd like, you could stay
here until your memory comes back?
You mean you'll take me in?
But you don't anything about me...
I don't mind that at all. I'm sure
that you ended up here for a reason.
Thank you very much.
I feel so relieved now, it's
made me hungry all of a sudden.
Well, then, enjoy your meal!
Thanks, I will.
This seems like a venerable inn.
Actually, we haven't
been around for that long.
Oh, I'm sorry, it just seems so rustic.
I thought that was just
a statue of a monkey!
You don't have to do that!
No, no, I have to do
something to earn my keep.
Now for this side!
Something was about to change.
That's the feeling I got, and
it made my heart skip a beat.
You're very good at that.
No, it's nothing.
The mistress told me that she didn't
know what she'd do without you.
She's letting me stay here for free.
If it's within my reach,
I'll do whatever she needs.
You too, Harumi. Let me know
if there's anything I can do.
Then, when I think of something,
I'll be counting on you.
You have to promise me!
It looks beautiful.
Is there nothing you can't do?
It's really strange...
For some reason, I
know exactly what to do.
Maybe you used to work
ata hotel or an inn...
Oh, no...
Itcan't be...
Now, then!
We have to come up with a name for you.
Oh, that's right...
Anything's fine, as long
as it's easy to remember.
Then, how do you feel
about the name Kenji?
Kenji?
Yes, using the characters
for "health" and "govern"...
Kenji...
It's a good name. I think I like it.
Yes.
Excuse me, do you have a minute?
Sure.
It doesn't open.
I know...
This outdoor hot spring
is just going to waste.
I know.
It's probably not my place to say this...
...but this isn't going to
help you to attract customers.
This place always used to be packed...
I know that I have to
do something about it...
...but the money just isn't there...
To tell you the truth,
I can't understand...
...how you're managing
to stay open atall.
Well that's none of your business!
I'm sorry, I was out of line.
So was I, I didn't mean
to speak so harshly.
Please forgive me.
It's true, there's a secret behind
the Swallowtail Inn's finances...
Something I don't want anyone
to find out, if possible...
I should serve them some tea.
No, it's just a casual gathering.
But still...
You don't have to do
anything for them, please.
That's strange, they didn't
even show their faces.
Uh-oh...
Why don't we play a
little roulette today?
Good idea, we haven't
done that in a while.
All right, then, Madam,
we're counting on you, now!
It would be damn nice to win for once!
That should do it.
Which room's next door?
All right, next!
Shit, I was almost there...
So you saw everything.
By accident.
I wasn't planning to watch, and
I wish I hadn't seen anything.
But now everything's clear.
That's how you're able to
keep this place running!
But it's so crazy! You're
turning this place into...
Stop it!
My husband built this
inn from the ground up.
I'll do whatever it
takes to keep it open!
Whatever it takes!
Please, don't you think
I've been humiliated enough?
Come here, Kenji...
Kenji is inside me now, running wild.
How did this happen?
Because I saw something of
my late husband in his face?
I don't have an answer for that myself.
All I know for sure is that I
could tell instantly that this man...
...this man was someone I
could rely on for everything.
I can't hold it in any
longer, I'm going to come!
So am I!
Come inside me, please! Kenji!
Yuriko!
Kenji!
I know you must be appalled with me...
No, I was too shallow-minded.
But now I understand how much you're
putting yourself on the line for this inn.
I want to do whatever I can to
help you keep this place running!
Thank you so much, Kenji...
I felt as though I
had 100 men on my side!
What do you think?
It's hard to say...
What's that?
We were trying to imitate one
of my husband's famous dishes...
...but it's not quite...
If we could put it back on the menu, that
would do something for our reputation.
Does it have a name, or something?
Yes, we call it "Sasame-Yuki".
Sasame-Yuki?
I know I've heard that name before...
Kenji!
I'm fine!
I'm all right!
What's this?
I don't know, my body just
started moving on it's own...
You did a wonderful job.
Kenji, you must've worked
as a chef somewhere...
I don't know about that...
I wondered if that was a sign that
Kenji's memory was starting to return.
It made me happy, butat the
same time it also made me sad.
Kenji continued to work hard, never
once cutting corners in any way...
...from fixing up the inn to
preparing meals in the kitchen...
and training me as an "entertainer".
Not yet!
What?
You're too self-conscious.
Let's go outside to the garden.
Louder, now!
I'm so embarrassed...
Ow!
That's the problem!
That's why you can't raise your voice!
You have to shout it out so
they know how you're feeling!
That's right, that's the way!
Move your hips more!
Right...
Is this all right?
I want you to lurch
backwards when you yell.
More!
That's right! Yuriko, enjoy yourself!
Your customers won't enjoy themselves
unless you're enjoying it too!
I've always been so
embarrassed until now...
So ashamed, and so full of guilt...
Well, you're not that person anymore!
Yes!
Yuriko! This is amazing!
I'm going to come!
And once in a while something like
this took place for our customers.
It scares me so...
the thought that I
might never get well...
that unless I do, I'll
be left behind, all alone...
I don't want to be alone and lonely...
I want someone to be there by my side...
Someone who will comfort
me, that was all I wanted...
I never knew that someone
else's touch could be so warm...
I'm coming!
I'm going to come now!
I know it was a lot to ask.
Thank you for granting me my wish...
After Kenji took over the kitchen,
our reputation slowly began to improve.
Soon, there'll be enough money to make
those repairs on the outdoor hotspring!
That's great!
If we can get that done now, it'll be
ready in time for the winter season.
Thank you so much, Kenji!
If it hadn't been for you...
No, I haven't really done anything...
Hello, this is the Swallowtail Inn...
Well, now, what a surprise...
I'm going to come!
Just the thought that one more push...
...and we'd get the Swallowtail
Inn back on track to profitability...
that was enough for me to do
even more practice sessions.
I want you to take a good look at these.
They all look the same...
...but I've cut each of these sushi
items into different sizes by type.
Let's start with the fatty tuna.
Next, thread fin.
Sea eel.
Shrimp.
Abalone.
Egg.
Halibut.
Now I'm going to mix them up.
No, it's going too deep...
No, stop, it's going in too far!
No, please, too far!
I know, you're going
to eject them yourself.
All right, start with the thread fin.
O-Okay.
This is the abalone.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that was the wrong one, wasn't it?
I could tell after I'd
started, let me try again!
You did it!
Did I really?
Now remember how you did that...
Yes!
All right, now eject
the rest, one by one...
Now I'm going to clean you up...
Is this all right?
Yes.
Hey! I'm getting a really great view.
Oh, please, don'tsay that...
A-All right, I'm going to start.
Well, now, you're treating
us to a sushi bar, are you?
You're adding a new dimension, eh?
I'd like to try that too.
I have to say the Madam's new
techniques are something else.
I know, seems like she's had some
kind of breakthrough or something...
She's improved a hell of a lot...
I was able to give my
customers so much pleasure...
...and it was all thanks to Kenji!
Um, what do you think?
Should I grind harder, or not?
No, that's fine, I'm
just about to come anyway...
N-Now!
Yuriko, you've really
gotten good at this.
Thank you for saying that.
They say that if you time it just right
and suck as hard as you can at the...
...moment of ejaculation, you
get several times the pleasure!
Uh... excuse me?
Fuyuka?
Fuyuka!
That's my younger
sister, Fuyuka Shiratori.
I have no idea what's
in store for us now.
All I know is that my head is
whirling and my groin is drenched...