Regarding what has happened
at the Swallowtail Inn so far...
So many things happened...
and the more I remember,
the more I think about it...
...the hotter I feel, and the
wetter I become between my legs.
Now then, let's move on. What
will become of the Swallowtail Inn?
SWALLOWTAIL INN
2nd Night
This is my younger
sister, Fuyuka Shiratori.
To tell you the truth, we're sisters-in-law
with a complex relationship.
O-Only employees are supposed
to be using the bath now!
Never mind that...
Listen, what do you want me to do?
Fuyuka, what do you think you're doing?
I'm offering a special service. Part of
the Swallowtail Inn's secret attraction!
W-Wait, whatare you doing?
Fuyuka, stop it right now!
He's not one of our customers!
I know, I said it was a special service!
Y-Yuriko!
Fuyuka!
Hey, what are you doing?
This is how it's done!
Me, too!
This feels good!
Let it out, Kenji!
I want you to let a LOT out!
Come!
I'm-I'm gonna come!
Fuyuka works at an office in the city...
...she told me she'd heard some
unsavory rumors about the Swallowtail...
that as a secret service...
The mistress of the inn was
entertaining guests in a risqué manner...
I'm going to put it in...
Fuyuka...
How's that?
You like that, don't you?
Yes, I like it very much.
Really?
Yes...
Those gyrations right there...
I've never experienced
anything like this before...
And you can't beat the visual effects...
I'm going to come again!
Come!
Come as hard as you can!
Spray it all over me!
How was that?
I'm sorry, I jumped to conclusions.
I was sure it was part
of the rumor I heard...
Oh no, that wasn't...
By the way, where did you
learn that technique of yours?
Well, I'm going to have
to say "no comment"!
Fuyuka, you know I'm happy
to have you back here.
But I can handle the
entertaining on my own.
Why do you say that?
If we do it together we'll
make twice as much money.
And if word gets out that there's a
pair of gorgeous sisters entertaining...
...they'll be beating down our door!
Fuyuka!
What?
Entertainment is not
just about the sexual act.
You're never going to get anywhere
unless you can provide your customers...
...with a high level of expertise.
I'll be just fine, thank you!
I'd never met you before until today,
but you didn't have a problem, did you?
I made you feel good, didn't I?
Well, as a matter of...
but still!
So I don't see why I
can't handle it too!
Fuyuka!
You have no idea what I've
gone through until now...
Excuse me, sorry to bother
you at this late hour, but...
when you get the chance, could you
please bring a cucumber to my room?
Yes, of course, we'll take
care of that in a moment.
I'm on the first floor, at the very end.
Then I guess I'll make the delivery.
Fuyuka doesn't have a clue.
Perhaps I can't blame her for that...
But I can't let her getaway with
taking the entertainment lightly.
That's why I decided to let her
getsome first-hand experience.
So this is the madam's younger sister?
These sisters arejust
as beautiful as we heard!
And she's so young.
Her skin's as tightas
these sashimi pieces!
All right, then, we
should give her a try...
Hey, you're not supposed to move!
S-Sorry...
And no talking!
W-What  are you doing?
Shut up and lie still!
Stop it, no!
Stop it, please!
No!
I can't do this!
What the hell is this?
She's got no manners!
This is no good! No good at all!
Please forgive me.
Let me take over from here...
Well, if you say so, Madam.
I guess we have no choice...
Let's start over from the beginning.
I'm so ashamed! I couldn't do it!
Now do you understand what
I was trying to tell you?
She's enduring what
they're doing to her...
Yuriko is so determined to
save the Swallowtail Inn that...
...she's willing to
risk her life, you see.
That's right...
I see what you mean, my
sister's such a strong person!
Forgive me if you found me lacking.
No, you really showed us a
good time. Here, take this...
Your patronage is appreciated...
Great view!
Perhaps I had been pushing myself...
...but even so, I should've
been able to take it...
While I was bedridden...
...Fuyuka made the decision to
undergo some entertainment training.
I've got to start entertaining,
we don't have much time!
Huh?
I know all about it.
Even if we get the outdoor hotspring
fixed, we'll still be losing money.
You don't know when the Sasame-Yuki
dish will be back on the menu, do you?
Sasame-Yuki...
Listen up!
You know what Sasame-Yuki is?
I got the inspiration for this
entreé from a woman's body...
As long as you've got this on the menu...
...you're guaranteed to
be deluged with guests.
I want you to learn how to make this...
Also, never forget the
spirit of hospitality!
The spirit of hospitality...
If we don't do something,
there won't be any future...
...for the Swallowtail Inn, will there?
More!
I'm gonna come!
I can't hold it anymore...
I'm coming!
Now I know what it is
you have to overcome...
And so began a series of harsh
training sessions for Fuyuka...
All right, straddle this rope.
Huh?
You mean this?
Now go ahead and walk!
Okay.
Don't say a word!
It's chafing me!
It's making me all hot down there...
It's hitting my spot!
Feels so good!
That's it, that's exactly
what's wrong with you, Fuyuka!
Why do you always try
to only come yourself?
There's no spirit of hospitality
in that kind of thinking!
Spirit of hospitality?
You're supposed to be
entertaining guests!
But look at you, you're
only enjoying yourself!
That's the reason why you failed
the first time you entertained!
I don't want someone like you to be
concerned with the future of this inn!
No! I always finish what I started!
I'm not going to sit around...
...and let my sister
do all the suffering!
Stop concentrating on that one area!
I could feel Fuyuka's pain
myself, right in my own groin...
That's good...
Feels good scraping against the bumps...
I'm gonna come...
I'm going to...
I can't hold itany longer!
Are you really going to
fix the outdoor hotspring?
Yes, we're going to start the repairs,
it'll be ready in time for winter.
Wow, I can't wait!
Kenji...
Kenji?
Oh, I'm so sorry...
Are you all right?
Once in a while I completely space out.
I wonder if that means
my memory's coming back...
Kenji will be going
someplace far from here...
I know that it's only to be
expected, once he regains his memory...
Ow! It's too strong!
S-Stop it!
You still don't understand, do you?
That hand shows exactly
what you're feeling inside...
You're rejecting your customers!
That's not true!
Do you think your customers will enjoy
themselves if you that's your attitude?
There'sjust no way in hell!
You must know the spirit of hospitality...
Not my nipples!
...no one will ever go near you!
No, stop it!
You need to be more flexible!
Otherwise you can't entertain!
Ouch!
Ow! That hurts!
Spirit of hospitality!
Oh, come on...
We have to do something to
correct your fidgeting, Fuyuka...
It's hot!
No!
No, I can't do this!
No, you must endure this some more,
and let me come now, like this.
Please don't make me do this anymore...
The spirit of hospitality, Fuyuka!
S-Spirit of hospitality...
Spirit of hospitality...
The spirit of hospitality, Fuyuka!
PRIME OF WOMANHOOD
S-Spirit of hospitality.
Spirit of hospitality...
In order to see if the training helped,
Fuyuka was subjected to one final test...
That's it, Fuyuka! Just keep that up!
Come on, Fuyuka!
Just a little farther, you can do it!
You did it!
You did a goodjob, Fuyuka!
Fuyuka!
Kenji...
Fuyuka, you passed the test.
Really?
Congratulations, Fuyuka!
I'll do even better
during the real thing!
This is how Sasame-Yuki should look.
Take a good look and don't forget it!
Yes, sir.
Sasame-Yuki...
It can't be, there's no way...
You did it!
Go for it!
She is notgoing to
run away like last time.
Please rest assured
and enjoy yourselves.
Let's get some fresh sauce on
her while she's still fresh!
This is great!
Gotta love the way it's mixed
up with all this sweat, too!
Lemme see...
All right then, this one's for you!
Let that cup runneth over, eh?
Thank you so much!
You know what Sasame-Yuki is?
I got the inspiration for this
entreé from a woman's body...
The road to sex leads
to the road of cuisine...
After all, we can't live
without either of them...
And then there's the
spirit of hospitality...
Don't ever forget the
This is the ultimate representation
of the Sasame-Yuki entrée
I was trained to make...
It's done.
It's delicious!
This is what had a long time ago!
This is it! It's Sasame-Yuki!
Kenji!
Well done!
If you were able to accomplish that...
...that means you must be on the
brink of regaining your memory!
Kenji...
Excuse me, but who are you?
Let me introduce myself to you all...
My name is Hibari Akisawa.
This is the Head Chef of the
Japanese Cuisine Department...
...of my father's hotel chain,
the Akisawa Tourism Group.
He's also my fiancé, Kenji Minasagi...
Fiancé?
Akisawa Tourism Group?
You mean the resort developer giant?
That's right!
Well? Are you starting
to remember, Kenji?
Then do you know why
everyone here calls you Kenji?
You used to train under the
former proprietor of this inn.
The master's name was also
Kenji, isn't that right?
Why, yes...
The mistress gave you the same
name as her husband, you see?
Try to remember now, Kenji!
Kenji...
My name is Kenji Minasagi...
My master's name was Kenji Shiratori...
My master's signature
dish was Sasame-Yuki...
My master's inn was
named the Swallowtail Inn...
Letter of Resignation
You can't be serious!
My master's inn is in trouble!
I'm going to go there and get
it back on track, no matter what!
But you've been chosen to take over
the Akisawa Group after my father!
You're not just going to
throw that away, are you?
That's right.
I decided to give up everything, and
made my way to the Swallowtail Inn...
The doctors told me
I shouldn't push you...
That I shouldn't try to make
you remember everything at once.
So I came here as a
guest to wait and see...
There's a place that
you have to go back to...
Please, come back with me...
I missed this!
I missed everything about you!
I don't want to have to use a
cucumber to comfort myself anymore...
I want you to churn!
You're hitting my spot!
Yes!
Better than a cucumber!
Please faster!
Faster!
I'm gonna come right now!
Kenji regained his memory in full.
So you're leaving tomorrow, aren't you?
It seems like it's all
been a dream, you know...
Yuriko...
Yuriko, I'll never forget
you as long as I live...
Now that I've perfected Sasame-Yuki,
you have nothing to worry about.
The Swallowtail Inn will be
just fine with you and Fuyuka...
Kenji, thank you from
the bottom of my heart...
I just don't know how to thank you!
I'll see to it that the
Swallowtail Inn thrives!
It was a bit of a shock to
learn that Kenji had a fiancé...
But I guess I shouldn't be
surprised, a man like that!
I'll do my best as an entertainer...
I can't believe how well
I've been feeling lately!
It's because Kenji made love to me, and
I gota taste of that Sasame-Yuki dish...
I owe my life to Kenji.
Thank you so much!
K-Kenji...
I'm going to come!
Kenji, I'm going to come!
I-Is it all right if I come now?
Is it all right if I come now?
I-I'm going to come now, too...
I want you to come, Kenji!
Let it all out!
I'm coming!
I'm coming now!
Yuriko!
And so Kenji returned
to where he belonged.
For us, he left behind a
newly reborn Swallowtail Inn...
Spring time has come again.
The season I met Kenji
for the first time...
And...
One Sasame-Yuki! It's ready!
All right! I'm coming!
The Swallowtail Inn was acquired
by the Akisawa Tourism Group...
and Kenji took over as the
Swallowtail's manager and Head Chef...
Just as they say, all's
well that ends well...
I really am a blessed woman...