No!
P-Professor!
Master!
Yeah, right there.
No!
I can't stop thrusting!
I'm gonna cum!
No!
Stop!
Not there!
Your finger's going in my...
No!
Temptation
Don't! Please stop!
P-Professor...
Morning, Miku.
We meet again; same train, same place.
You've been looking forward to this,
I bet.
No... that's not true.
No!
Don't!
What're you saying?
You want to be molested, right?
We share the same hobbies-
erotic comics and cos-play.
And here you're dressed all innocent.
You're a sex-starved college student.
Why do you say that?
Professor, not there!
You're gonna make me go!
You'll make me pee!
I can't take this!
Please!
Do it harder and rougher!
Pardon?
Five o'clock.
All students must promptly
leave the campus.
That feels awesome!
It's so good!
Gimme more, prof!
"Prof?"
It's too good!
I'm gonna cum!
Prof, ram it inside me!
I'm hot for you, Prof Ayabe!
I'm cumming all over!
Prof?
What're you doing, Prof Ayabe?
Who, me? Nothing special!
You leaving for the day?
Yup!
You got more work to do?
Yeah, I've got some stuff to finish up.
Oh... too bad.
What's up?
It's nothing, really.
Careful on your way home.
Thanks.
Good luck with your work tonight.
Well, bye.
Bye.
Prof!
What is it, Hotaru?
You've been peeping in on me
for a long time, huh?
No...
I mean, just cuz
I ran into you just now...
Do me, Prof.
W-Wha?
I'm not supposed to!
I can't take it!
All I can think about is you!
Feel.
See how hard they are,
just from thinking about you?
Down here, too.
See how wet I am?
Prof, go on and touch me!
That feels great!
Yes!
Do it harder, Prof!
Yes, there!
U- Unreal...
Oh, man.
Look how hard you are, Prof.
Prof...
C'mon, Prof.
I can't take it any longer.
Stick it to me.
Yeah, that's awesome!
That's the spot!
You're totally gonna make me cum!
I swear it!
Prof!.
Staff Room
You're a prof, yet you made it
with a college student.
How would the Board of Education react,
I wonder...
...if I decided to send them this tape?
Was this a set-up?!
Once I break them in,
they become my sex slaves.
My sweet pets.
That's enough.
Yes, master.
Rougher! Do it to me rougher!
What do you want to gain from this?
There are two photos
of students in here.
First, I want you to violate them,
like you did Hotaru.
I'd like if you videotaped
the whole thing, too.
Why would you want that?
You have no right to ask.
Also...
You might need these at some point.
Pep pills; a pharmacist friend
made them for me.
They contain an aphrodisiac,
and they're pretty strong.
Professor Kyomoto,
what's the meaning of this?
You'll have to obey me,
like everyone else does.
Oh, man!
Not there!
Keep your voice down, or we'll
be busted when someone comes in.
I'm gonna go!
You love pissing, right?
No, I can't!
You can piss all you want, in here.
I'll help you out.
No, not there!
I'm gonna go! I'm gonna pee!
See? You went tons.
That felt good.
P-Professor...
I want it.
I want your dick.
You know better than that.
You've gotta beg
your Master properly, first.
Master...
Please put it in me.
Stuff your dick in my hole,
where it smells like pee.
Violate me, good and rough!
Please, Professor. Hurry!
Stuff your big, hard stiffie in me.
It's huge!
That's good!
More!
P-Professor!
Professor?
Please don't stop, Master.
Keep going.
Will you do anything I ask?
Yes! I'll do anything!
I belong to you, Master.
So please, I'm begging you!
There's a good lady.
I'm gonna cum!
It's so good!
Master!
Hey, Hotaru?
How should I ask him, you think?
I dunno, that's a good question.
It's the first time I've done this.
He's here!
Professor Ayabe!
Good morning!
Morning, Sakura.
Good timing!
So...
How do you spend your days off?
Uh... I've gotta get ready for my seminar!
Excuse me.
Maybe he doesn't like me!
That's not true.
He's busy, that's all.
You think?
Yeah, definitely.
Cheer up, Sakura.
Professor Ayabe...
Woof, woof
Temptation
That's good, Kotoe.
Just like that.
Your dick's so big and hard, Master.
How is it?
Yummy.
But...
What?
My lips down there.
Give it to me, Master!
You're a naughty priestess, Kotoe.
Yes, I'm a bad priestess.
I'm throbbing down there.
Stuff it in me.
Please, Master!
Put your stiffie in my wet,
nasty twat and stuff me up!
Ram it in me, and bang me hard!
Fine request.
I'll grant your wish.
Lift your butt.
Yes.
It's going in.
Stuff it all the way in!
I can't take it!
I'm losing my mind!
It feels so good!
Pound me harder! Rougher!
I'm gonna cum!
I can't take it!
Is it good?
Yes, it's yummy.
There's more jizz on the floor.
This isn't what we agreed on!
I did receive Miku Mikuni
and Kotoe Yasaku's tapes.
Then what's this?
Like I said before.
Those two ladies were first.
You're just getting started.
There's no need to worry.
As long as you keep delivering.
I'll definitely pass along the tape.
Oh, and this.
What is it?
I heard some rumors,
so I checked her out.
A little shakeup in the news
and she'll be through.
Good luck.
One more thing.
My pet hasn't come to see me
for a few days.
Not even when I call for her.
Know anything about it,
Professor Ayabe?
I haven't heard from Hotaru
since our last time!
Temptation
Nearing Nishisumiyoshi Station.
Nishisumiyoshi Station.
The doors will open on the right.
No! A pervert!
What do I do?
Stop it!
Gross!
Who is it?
Not there!
Please don't!
Stop, what if someone sees?
Don't!
Don't, or I'll...
East Tamagawa Station.
Mind the gap to the platform.
Excuse me, I'm getting off!
Professor?
So it is you!
What's wrong?
You look exhausted.
Oh, so you're working part-time here.
That uniform suits you.
You think so?
You allowed to talk like this?
Sure, I'm on my break.
Still, it feels kinda weird.
You know, how we're not allowed
to hang with profs off campus.
Yeah, but this is a coincidence,
so it's different.
Oh, hey.
I have a favor to ask,
for once in my life.
What is it?
You make it sound so serious.
I'll do whatever I can.
Seriously!
Sure, since you're always helping
tidy up the room after my lectures.
The least I can do is return the favor...
You promise?
Yeah... sure.
H-H-Here!
What is it?
This anime is for those 18 and over.
Tempt-a-tion
Professor!
Sorry I'm late!
You promised to pretend
we met here by coincidence!
Yeah, right.
Let's go with that.
C'mon, let's go in.
Hey, hang on, Sakura.
Aquarium
Are you even listening to me?
It's my first time here!
I'm totally excited!
Quit pulling so hard.
Kuona Station
I had a good time today.
Seriously?
Yeah, it's been a long time
since I had such a fun day off.
Great! I'm glad you said so.
You look so worn out these days.
You better hurry,
or you'll be late for work.
Sakura?
S-Sakura!
I'd love to accidentally bump into you
at the amusement park, soon!
Cuz I had such an amazing time today!
Well, I'm off!
Hello, Miku?
Yeah, that's right.
Temptation
Come in.
Professor?
Professor Ayabe?
You don't need to be afraid.
Glad you made it.
You sounded doubtful on the phone.
Those photos...
I blew them up
so they're easier to see.
I had no idea there was a working idol
right here on our campus.
Let alone one of the "Birds."
Ayumi, the hard-working student
with perfect attendance.
Give me those.
First, lift your skirt
and show me your panties.
Wh-Why should I?
Maybe I should sell these
to a photo magazine.
What a shocker,
you both being lesbians.
You two crying
on each other's shoulders?
Think about your poor partner.
Cuz of you, her future as an idol
will be destroyed.
No, don't do it!
Don't ruin Hikaru's dreams!
She's just decided
to release a debut CD!
We've taken lessons for years,
and now our chance has finally come!
So... therefore!
Therefore...
Excellent.
We finally understand each other.
Come out.
Yes, Master.
She's going to help me out.
Miku Mikuni, from third year.
The pleasure's mine.
I'll warm you up nice and good.
You're a lez just like her,
so it's perfect.
Miku, do her, but keep her panties on.
Right.
Don't move!
You're tight.
You're already getting hot.
Your butt hole, too.
Feel good? Does it?
You're dripping wet.
What're you doing?
Just following Master's command.
His dick is my reward.
Unreal!
Look how hot you made me get, Ayumi.
I'll stick it in your pussy
and take you for a ride.
No!
Ow! Hey, calm down!
Chill out!
Master, I think
she knocked herself out.
Perfect.
I'll get the camera set up.
You strip her down.
Okay!
Hey, she shaves!
It's silky soft!
Interesting!
I'm Flying... Temptation
You've come to, huh.
What's going on?
Hey, what're you doing?!
Licking your smooth pussy.
It's salty and yummy.
Please, stop!
I can't film with you wriggling around.
Film? Film what?
On top of the news story, we're also
broadcasting you acting like a slut.
Hundreds of thousands of men
are watching you nude, on their PCs.
They're watching you from up there.
Th-They're watching...
Doesn't that make you hot?
You feel them watching you.
Ayumi, you should see
the yucky cream spewing out of you!
Looks like the pills are kicking in.
I'm on fire!
I can't take it! What's going on?
Their glaring eyes
are driving you nuts.
I'm being watched!
I can feel it! I can feel it!
Let me get a close-up
of you getting off.
You're a pervert, cumming at
the thought of being watched.
Miku.
Yes?
No, not there!
Nice titties.
Amazing! You're a real gusher!
I can't take this.
All right, I'm gonna stick it to her.
I'm gonna die.
So this is what a star's
tight snatch feels like!
Miku, you getting all this?
Yeah.
See where I'm stuffing it inside you?
Yeah, I see it.
It's hard! And good!
More!
Don't stop! Keep doing it!
How do you want it?
Doggy style!
Stuff your dick all the way in,
Professor!
Please!
You asked for it.
Unreal!
I can't take it!
I'm gonna cum... I'm gonna cum!
It's so good!
I can't last!
I can't!
Harder! Pound me!
I'm gonna cum.
I am too. I'm gonna cum!
What is it?
I kept my promise.
I got the pictures back, but I'm toast.
You're still a star.
Yeah, but...
That was all a lie.
I broke you in, but I was never
gonna sell it to anyone.
Feel better now?
Yeah!
Something else.
Would you do me again?
You're the only one for me.
You don't have the right to say no.
Understand?
A pervert!
Not there!
P-P-
Sorry! I've gotta do this!
W-Why?
Why are you doing this?
Not there! Not there!
To Be Continued