Not there!
No!
I love you.
I love you, Professor.
I love you, too.
P-Professor!
Temptation
Why?
You leaving for the day?
Careful on your way home.
Cute! It suits you.
Oh? You don't say.
It's been a long time
since I had such a fun day off.
S-Sakura!
Professor. Why?
A pervert!
What should I do?
No! Not there!
P-P-
Sorry! I've gotta do this!
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Not there!
That'd be unreal.
It hurts!
Temptation
No!
Staff Room
Out with it!
What'd you sneak in here for?
No, I wasn't doing anything!
Stop lying.
That hurts!
Please!
Stop!
Please, Master!
Not going to answer, huh.
That hurts! It hurts!
Stop!
Forgive me, Master!
It has to hurt,
or it wouldn't be punishment.
No! Please don't move it around!
That won't do.
What're you getting all hot over?
I'll end the punishment and give you
something to really make you hot.
Master, what are you gonna do?
Check it out.
I told you before.
You're gonna be raped, while I watch.
No...
Director.
She's all yours.
I've been waiting forever, Masaki.
Let's see the hottie.
Smells great!
- Nothing like fresh meat.
- No!
That feel good?
Did you piss?
You're a tight squeeze.
Stop!
"Stop?" What're you saying, pet?
It's turning you on enough.
It's so salty and good!
That feel good, honey?
I'm getting hot!
C'mere and lick mine.
Hurry it up.
Yeah, that's the way.
Here, suck on this.
It stinks!
Yes! That's it!
I'm gonna cum.
I'd love to bang you.
Masaki?
No skin off my back.
She's been given her pill.
Sweet!
What a nice, tight snatch!
Yes! Yes!
C'mere, sweetie!
How was she?
The best! Good and tight.
I'll buy her.
When I tell the guys,
they'll all want one.
Hurry and find some other ladies.
I've already got some lined up.
Isn't that nice?
You've been sold.
You'll have a new Master, now.
Answer me.
Yes, Master.
No...
Professor, Kotoe, Miku,
Ayumi and Sakura are in trouble.
And it's all my fault!
Professor?
I love your
penis and sex. - Ki
Temptation
I feel so alive... - Ma
Where am I?
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Professor!
Thank goodness!
Hotaru.
I'm so relieved!
I'm so glad!
I thought you were going to die!
You'll be examined shortly.
I see.
Hit by a car.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
It's all my fault you were hit!
I owe you an apology.
I promised I'd apologize today!
I knew how Sakura felt,
and still I did something horrible!
So you saw it.
I wanted to steal the video,
but I couldn't find it.
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
It's all right.
I'm in the same boat as you.
I've done some bad things to you all.
I'm in no position to blame you.
C'mon, stop crying.
P-Professor...
Now, about Professor Ayabe.
He's going to be off for a while.
So, I'll be taking over his class.
He's been gone for three days now.
I've got so much to ask him.
Like what happened, or why he did it.
I'm so confused.
Hotaru's not here today, either.
Any questions?
Temptation
It's you!
You're the one that hit me!
You're a doctor here?!
How are you feeling?
Any nausea or pain?
That was a hit and run!
Aren't you even going to apologize?!
Right, I apologize.
I was preoccupied.
I'll come back to apologize properly.
But for now, just let your injuries be treated.
Assistant Chief Surgeon Dr. Sugisaki.
Please report to Triage Room 3.
Look after him.
Yes, Doctor.
Hey, hang on!
I'm very sorry.
It's been deleted.
Woohoo!
Ayabe
What's this?
Take it, and forget the hit and run.
I see.
It seemed strange that
there was no police report,
even though it was a car accident.
Hush money.
Physicians have lowered the bar.
You're wrong!
I did this on my own.
It has nothing to do with Manami.
You mean you're willing to pay
all this money for that woman doctor?
If word of the car accident gets out,
then Manami's future is in jeopardy!
The board will pull her license!
She's always dreamed
of becoming a doctor.
So please, I'm begging you!
Take the money and...
I'll do it.
But on one condition.
Write it down: How she hit me
and how you gave me hush money.
Your attitudes are too much!
If you don't like the condition, then
we'll forget this whole conversation.
All right.
What's her problem?
Why didn't you get mad, Master?
Yeah, good point.
What do you think I should do?
Punish her!
That rude nurse deserves
a real punishment with your dong!
You've gotta break her in.
Yeah, but that wouldn't be punishment.
Feel good?
Yes!
It's awesome!
I'm gonna use you up!
Not me. My thing.
Your penis. Yes!
I love your penis!
I love it!
Why'd you stop?
Sorry, I'm almost ready to cum.
Go ahead and cum, then.
C'mon, get moving.
I can't take it!
I'm gonna cum first!
I'm gonna! I'm gonna cum, Master!
Ayabe
It's so good, Master!
More!
What's going on?!
This is a hospital!
Caught you spying!
Who're you?
Miku, that's who.
It's a party.
Slow response to my call button.
Got me all ready down there?
Now, it's time for your punishment.
No!
Temptation 2
Self-restriction
How am I supposed to lick you?!
That's better.
Now you can't get out of it.
Man, as if you're not loving it.
Your clit's hard, too.
Clit, clit, clit, clit!
It's huge!
Miku, how's she doing?
I can get three fingers in this slut.
Oh yeah?
It feels so good there!
It's just like pee!
Miku, bring her over
so I can stick it to her.
Coming!
C'mon, get moving.
You know you love it.
You're a slut.
H-How can it possibly feel good?!
You'd better do a good job.
Or what'll happen to Manami?
I'll reveal your written confession.
It'd get out to the media.
You wouldn't!
So, what're you gonna do?
Miku, you all set?
Yeah.
Kotoe, come and lick it.
So, that's what it's like.
Watch out; it's inside me.
Don't wiggle it around,
it feels too good.
Hurry and lick me.
I'm being licked.
It feels weird.
My nipples are all hard.
Nurse, stick your butt out.
All right, I'm going in!
No, stop!
Not there!
It hurts! It hurts!
Double penetration!
It feels great for me, too!
You're tight!
Taking it up the ass,
and squirting from her twat.
She's getting it good!
I'm feeling it, too!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
What, you both came before me?
Master!
I haven't cum yet!
I want it in my butt hole, too!
Stick it to me!
All right, I'll give it to you.
Okay, then I'll keep doing the nurse.
Yes, that's good, nurse!
Yeah, that's the spot!
Temptation
Science Preparation Room
Five o'clock.
All students must tidy up
and promptly leave the campus.
Professor, can I talk to you?
Why?
Tell me why.
Why did you do it?
It's not like you to do that.
There must be an explanation.
There is, right?!
Professor?!
There is a reason.
What happened, Prof?
Tell me!
I probably can't help, but at least...
At least I wanna try and help.
I'm begging you.
Don't leave me in the dark.
Professor, I have a favor to ask.
Yeah, right.
Good luck with your work.
I had an amazing time today!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry, Sakura!
You'll tell me then, Professor?
Yeah.
No!
He and Hotaru were blackmailed
by Professor Kyomoto!?
Let's get going.
It's late; I'll walk you home.
It's my fault.
I was tempted by Hotaru,
then forced to confess.
But you don't need to worry anymore.
I won't be touching you
or any other ladies.
I promise.
I won't be that woman's sex toy
any longer.
Even if it costs me my position.
Got that?
Professor Ayabe's gonna quit teaching.
He's gonna leave!
Professor's gonna-
No! I don't want him to leave!
I know him!
What's wrong?
He's so kind. He's my kindred spirit!
He's the best prof ever!
That's why I...
Why I love...
Professor!
Temptation
Are you sure about this?
Professor, you can keep teaching
as long as you take my video, right?
Yeah, but...
I want you to stay at the college.
But...
I'm okay.
Just be gentle with me.
Professor.
I can taste you.
It's kinda bitter, from smoke.
But it's so gentle, like you.
Don't look at me.
It's embarrassing.
You're pretty.
Really?
Yeah.
Geez, you're dripping wet.
See?
You getting hot?
Yeah.
Just thinking about you makes me hot.
I love you.
I love you, too.
No, not down there.
It's yucky there.
P-Professor!
You taste delicious, Sakura.
Professor, I...
I'm going in.
Don't bother with a condom.
It's my first time,
so I want to feel you.
Please... give it to me.
It's going in!
You're so big and hot!
Does it hurt?
A little, but I can take it.
I'll be okay.
I'll go slowly.
Okay, slowly.
Take me nice and slowly.
Yeah, I'll take you.
Go ahead, I'm all yours.
P-Professor!
Can you move?
No, I don't have enough energy.
Just go slowly then.
It doesn't hurt any more, right?
Don't thrust so deep!
You're a tight squeeze!
It feels great!
It's so weird.
It hurts, but it feels good.
Deeper, Professor!
Deeper!
I'll get a good price for her, too.
You got a good bang out of her,
considering she's a virgin.
This slut should be easy to break in.
Look at that foolish expression.
The world's full of idiots like her.
I transferred your share of the money.
Do a good job on the next woman, too.
Getting paid to bang fresh meat...
I'm the luckiest guy alive.
You're in good hands.
Professor!
Harder! Do it harder!
Yes!
It's good! More!
I'm gonna cum!
I love you, Professor!
Master.