Hey, Yuu-kun.
I told you to come home early because I had
something important to tell you, right?
What were you doing?
I tried to, but my friend asked me to go shopping with her.
I did, however, try to come home as fast as I could...
Friend, eh?
I see, your friend's a girl.
Y-Yeah.
That's right, but...
I get it now.
O-Onee-chan?
See? This smell...
Both your arms were around each other, right?
Well, it's because she...
Tried to score on my brother...
I can't just that let that go.
What?
No, it's nothing.
Which basically meant that you chose her over me today, right?
I really get it now.
I never intended to do that!
Forget it.
Anyway, let's get to the point.
Okay.
You see, I need you to check at something for me, Yuu-kun.
This is it.
You get it already, right?
These are panties, right?
Even if you ask me that...
Wait, you don't understand?
I already found it in your room, you know.
Then, maybe Mom just mistakenly placed it in my drawer instead?
And this weird smell...
Hey, Yuu-kun,
I'm not going to get angry, so tell me already.
Big sis here more or less knows about it already.
After all, you're still a guy, right?
I... took it...
from your laundry box.
Okay. Then?
Then, what did you do with it?
What did I do...?
W-Well...
No use hiding it now.
Okay?
Umm...
I sniffed it...
A-And... jerked off with it...
Show me.
What I want to say, is that I want you to show me how you 'jerk off.
I-I can't just do that!
Oh?
Do you really think you can say no in this situation?
But... that's...
Oh yes.
Let's get you changed before that.
This is really embarrassing.
Oh, why?
It suits you well though.
That's my middle school uniform, you know.
Why...?
Of course this is weird!
You're cute, so I was pretty sure that it would look nice.
Why did this have to happen.
Hey, stand up straight.
Show me more.
Now isn't...
isn't really a good time to do that.
Yuu-kun, try to understand your situation.
This is...
Are you aroused because you're wearing a girl's uniform?
No.
This uniform...
bears your scent.
Do you like my smell that much?
Yes.
I see.
Then, try doing it.
Do I really have to?
Show it to me.
How you 'jerk off.'
Here I go.
Okay.
Yuu-kun, does that feel good?
I... don't know...
It feels a bit different, compared to when I do it normally.
Onee-chan, Onee-chan...
Eh, what?
Ah, well... I didn't really...
It just... sort of slipped out of my mouth.
Oh, is that so...
0-0nee-chan...this is...
Don't mind it.
Just let Onee-chan do it.
Well?
Does it feel good, Yuu-kun?
Onee-chan, rub it... harder...
Harder?
Like... this?
It feels good...
Oh no.
I'm going to cum.
It's okay, don't hold back.
Show me how you cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
You sure came a lot.
Yuu-kun, do you know what 'fellatio' means?
Fellatio...?
I really need this to do that, but...
It doesn't feel fair if it's just you,
so I'm going to show you mine as well.
Here.
Oh my.
Okay, let's get started.
Nee-chan...
This is real...
It's really inside your mouth, Onee-chan.
That's right.
So it feels this good...
Onee-chan...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Oh no, my teeth might have grazed it.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
And I... want to continue...
No... this is enough.
I don't think we should keep
Hey, you shouldn't do this.
You shouldn't do this to your sister, you know.
Onee-chan... I'm...
You’re such a helpless boy.
Do you really want...
to do it with me?
Yeah.
We actually mustn't do this,
but if you really insist...
Onee-chan!
But, you can't tell this to anyone else.
You must absolutely keep this a secret, okay?
Okay, I'll never tell anyone.
And one more thing.
Even if you get into a similar situation with another girl,
you must never accept their invitation, no matter what.
Yeah, I understand.
I promise.
Alright let's move to the bed then.
Is it here?
Eh? Oh, uh... yes.
Right there.
I wonder if it will fit in this small hole.
It's alright.
I think.
Onee-chan, can I?
Yeah, it's okay.
Just go.
Go inside me.
It's... all the way in.
Wow, it's really all the way in.
That's great.
It's properly inside me now.
Onee-chan, your insides feel hot and nice.
Is this your first time too?
Of course it is.
When it comes to a real one that is.
A real one?
Even I'm a bit scared of these things.
Besides, I thought you might be scared if you found out.
That I... that I was practicing for this day.
I see...
I'm sorry, Onee-chan.
What did I just say?
I never thought you'd grow this big.
Wait, so that voice that I sometimes hear during the night is...
You heard then?
Yeah.
I was actually a bit scared of those weird sounds.
I'm sorry.
But I'm glad that I now know where it came from.
I probably won't ever do it again though.
Because, the real one is inside me now.
Hey, Onee-chan...
It's okay.
Try moving gently.
It's hitting me.
Your thing is rubbing inside me.
And we're really doing it despite being siblings.
Onee-chan, your insides feel really nice and tender.
It feels good.
I can feel it.
I can feel you reaching my very depths.
Keep it up.
It feels quite better now.
Hey, Onee-chan,
should I try moving faster?
Okay, but just a little.
Yuu-kun, you're fast!
You're too fast!
But, I just can't stop, Onee-chan.
Onee-chan!
No, this isn't what I meant!
No, this isn't...!
Don't!
Yuu-kun!
It feels great.
Your pussy is the best, Onee-chan.
No...
Yuu-kun, stop...
You can't keep on pushing it carelessly like that.
Oh no, I'm going to completely lose it...
Onee-chan, my... my...
Yuu-kun, you can't be...!
Wait, you mustn't do that!
Stop, stop!
You're really cumming inside.
My brother's cum is...
You shouldn't have done that.
I said that you couldn't.
Oh no, I might get pregnant.
Jeez, that was terrible of you, Yuu-kun!
It was my first time.
Now I'm going to get pregnant because of my own brother.
I'm sorry.
I was so happy that I...
Because I've loved you for a long time.
I understand that it's weird, because we're siblings.
But I've been imagining this very same scene in my head.
That's why...
I wasn't able to stop myself.
I'm really sorry.
Yuu-kun.
Onee-chan.
So you were thinking of me like that.
I would have wanted you to tell me that earlier though.
Then we wouldn't have gone through this.
Onee-chan...
I would have let you take me on instead,
and make it look like we've been this way for a long time.
Or something like that.
Big sis, you see
love you so much, that I'd never let anyone get a hold of you in any way.
Simply put,
we're both.
meant for each other.
O-Onee-chan...
From this point on,
us siblings... are also now lovers.
But, will it really be okay that way?
It's okay.
Because we're helplessly in love with each other.
Yuu-kun,
your thing is getting really big inside me.
O-Onee-chan, you're gripping me tightly,
and it feels amazing...
Yuu-kun, I love you.
What is this?
It feels completely different from before.
Your dick feels really amazing, Yuu-kun.
It feels really great.
The view here is amazing.
Then get a good look at it.
Look at how we siblings are showing love to each other.
1-1 can't hold it in any longer...
I'm about to cum.
Are you cumming?
Are you cumming again?
It's okay, it's alright.
Cum inside me.
Pump all of your cum inside me!
I'm happy...
I can feel you filling up my insides.
Still not done?
I really want more of you inside me.
Here I go then.
It's in.
Your dick...
This sensation, feels great no matter how many times I do it.
Hurry up.
Hurry up and rub it inside my pussy already.
Don't stop yet, do it more.
Push it even harder!
Oh yes.
It's rubbing deep inside me.
This is... this is really something!
I can really feel it hitting my very depths.
It, it feels really hot!
My pussy feels like it's going to burn.
Onee-chan, your pussy feels too good.
It feels really tender.
What's with this position?
It feels really lewd.
But, I can move easily so it's great.
It's rubbing different parts too.
It feels great.
Yuu-kun, you're really good.
It's rubbing my soft spots really hard.
I'm really happy...
I want to remain connected to you a bit longer, Onee-chan.
But it seems that I'm... about to!
It's okay.
Just keep on cumming inside me however you want to.
Onee-chan, Onee-chan, I love you!
It's cumming again.
Your feelings are going to once again reach me!
Onee-chan... Onee-chan...
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan, I'm about to cum.
I'm going to pump it all inside.
It's okay, just cum.
I also can't hold back any longer.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
There's just so much.
I might really get pregnant with this.
But...
I think that's actually fine...
I'm tired.
It's your first time, you might have overworked yourself.
You're right.
But it felt really good.
Don't forget your promise, okay?
No, I won't.
Oh yeah.
Don't take my undies anymore, okay?
Oh, alright, I won't do it again.
Also, you can't 'jerk off on your own anymore.
Eh? Why's that?
Because it's such a waste do it by yourself.
From now on,
you'll do it with me, okay?
It's got big again.
hat's because...
Mom's not home yet.
Let's do it again?
O-Onee-chan...