Mom!
It's all ready.
Got it!
I'm off!
Have a good day.
I'll see you later!
I repeat, I repeat...
The suspects are headed toward
the Moto Arashiyama District.
Roger!
Oh, no! Late again! I've
messed up again.
Under these circumstances, I must
get to class as soon as possible!
Takeshi Chimatsuri has just arrived!
What the hell?!
Who the hell are you, punk?
What are you doing here?
Chimatsuri, they're robbers! Robbers!
Robbers?
Chimatsuri!
Do what I say. Otherwise,
I'll kill her. Got it?
Atsuko, if you are a true Japanese girl,
you shall give your life for justice.
Don't decide for me! I don't
want to die yet!
I know. I won't let you die alone.
I will follow you after I kill them.
You don't understand at all!
Oh, my God.
I'll shoot her. I really will.
Takeshi Chimatsuri, age sixteen.
Don't get close!
Physical health, excellent!
Here I come!
Naifu no yona hitomi no okuni
Sunda nanika, gamusharani
nigirishimete
Hayari nado madowasarezu ni
Shinji tsuzuketa style,
just the hungry heart
Kutabireta heart ni sae,
Give me fresher mind
Samishisa o nigawarai
de kakusu aitsu
Tsuyogari ga dokoka niterukara
Oretachi dake no basho o neraooze
Victory over myself
Victory over yourself
Oretachi wa kachitsuzuke nakya
Victory over myself
Victory over yourself
Victory over burning blood, winning
Kagayaki tai anohito no tame
Naki wa shinai oretachi no tame
Chimatsuri!
That was quite a commotion
this morning.
Now, one more thing before we get
back to our lesson.
Let me introduce some new
students to you.
Girls, come on in and introduce
yourselves to the class.
Nice to meet you. I'm Akari Toki.
And I'm her sister, Kagiri.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, twins.
Yeah, and good looking too.
It's them!
What's wrong, Chimatsuri?
Miss Ayatsugi!
Yes, Torai?
Kagiri, how about going to a movie
with me this Sunday?
But...I just met you.
Hey, Torai, you're awful quick.
Don't be so negative. I'm just
being true to my heart.
Hey, Kagiri, how about going
with me, instead of Torai?
Uemura, what the heck are you doing?
Oh, shut up! It doesn't matter
who asked first.
Hey guys, cut it out! Kagiri,
why don't you
forget about these guys and
come out with me?
What, Tamahara?! Hey, you!
What? Freedom of speech
is one of our rights!
Everyone, please wait. You don't
need to fight.
Now...
I'll go on a date with you.
With who?
Me, right?
With all of you.
With all of us?
Now, please, you sort out who is first.
Oh, no!
What the hell are you doing?!
Ouch! Look, Sis, they said they all
wanted to have a date with me.
High school students need to behave
like high school students!
I was just trying to cut the problems
in between short.
Ouch!
I'm telling you that's the problem!
Violence doesn't solve the problem.
A man...
Touched me!
My hand is going to rot!
I'm so sorry. My sister has a phobia
about being touched by men.
Those two are like day and night.
Chimatsuri?
What are you doing? What are
you here for?
You know what. We want it back.
It? What is it?
Could this be it?
That's it. That's our family's sword.
Now, hand it to me, or I'II...
Toki, Chimatsuri, this is a classroom,
a place for study!
Our mission is to retrieve our
family's heirloom sword.
For the last ten years,
we trained in the remote mountains to
defeat Takeshi Chimatsuri.
No one's going to stop me now.
What?! You've trained for ten years
just to defeat me?
Didn't we live in the mountains
because Dad was transferred?
Ouch! You always hit me!
Allergic to naked women.
It sure looks that way.
Takeshi Chimatsuri, I challenge you to
a match behind the gym tomorrow.
Don't forget to bring the
sword with you.
Kagiri!
Yes, Sister?
We must go for special training to
prepare for tomorrow's match.
Yes!
Wait! You two!
Ouch! Wait, Sis!
Oh, you were old friends of the Toki
twins since you were little?
Actually, we're more like old rivals.
But the sword originally belonged to
the Toki Family, right?
Yeah, thirteen years ago, my father
and their father, Kagemaru...
Kagemaru Tki
For my family's honor,
it is my mission to prove
Kagemaru Tki
that swordmanship is not the
enemy of the art of the Ninja.
Raizo Chimatsuri
Swordmanship is a spirit.
Sword practice leads to
the path of warriors.
Raizo Chimatsuri
That is the way of the sword.
One with a pure soul cannot
possibly lose.
Nonsense!
If I win, I will take Kikuichimonji, your
precious sword as my own.
Understood. And if I win?
I'll give you the Toki Family
heirloom sword.
So, that's what happened.
Okay, I've made up my mind.
Atsuko?
I'll help you.
I'm not sure how helpful
I can be though.
Atsuko!
Thanks!
Wait!
I'll never forget this for the
rest of my life!
Chimatsuri!
I'll never forget this for the
rest of my life!
Chimatsuri!
I'll never forget this for the
rest of my life!
He's allergic to the female body,
but he sure doesn't seem to have a
problem when he's happy.
What a difficult personality.
I got it!
Yamaguchi
So, what's your remedy for my allergy?
Well, the plan is...
The plan is to...
I don't have a plan really.
What? The way you said that was so
seductive and mysterious,
I sweated right through.
Here, use this.
It's coming!
Atsuko, thank you!
I'll never forget this for the
rest of my life!
Thank me some more, Chimatsuri!
Closer! Hold me closer!
Like this?
Ouch!
Atsuko, I'm coming in.
Hold me! Hold me tighter!
Atsuko!
What was I doing?
What, Mother?
Atsuko!
Can I trust you? Mother can
trust you, right?
Get a grip, Mom. What did you want?
You have visitors.
Atsuko told us what happened.
We're here to help.
You can count on us.
We've got a perfect remedy for
you in this bag.
Remedy?
Nothing can happen.
She should be safe with her classmate
and teacher there.
Okay, Chimatsuri, we have to build up
your resistance to naked women.
Look through all of these by tomorrow.
Chimatsuri?
Torai, do you always read these
dirty magazines?
No way! We got these for Chimatsuri,
right, Teacher?
Wow! Oh, my God! They
show everything!
I wonder if it feels good? Wow!
Okay, so now you're used to
these a little bit,
we'll train you with the real thing next.
Teacher, you don't mean that we'II...
That's right. You and I are
going to do it.
Now, put this leotard on.
Oh, no! I'm not going to do this.
I'm too embarrassed!
It's no big deal. We're going
to do aerobics.
Now, you two turn around while
we change clothes.
Yes, Ma'am.
Atsuko, I've brought some tea and
cakes for your guests.
May I come in?
Can I trust you? Can I
really trust you?!
Mom, get a hold of yourself!
It's not what it looks like,
Mrs. Yamaguchi. Really!
Can I... can I still trust you?
It sounds like it's getting complicated.
Yeah, don't look.
If you look now, things will get
a whole lot worse.
Okay, shall we start?
I can't do it! I can't take this!
Hang in there, just think of
something else.
You need to hold on!
Okay, I've got it.
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter,
Saturn, Uranus, Neptune and Pluto.
So, how are you getting on?
He seems to be managing.
Here, Chimatsuri, wipe your
sweat with this.
Thank you!
I'll never forget this for the
rest of my life!
It's taking effect quicker.
Is he chanting some sort of spell?
No idea.
Here, Chimatsuri. Hold
me tighter! Tighter!
No idea.
Here, Chimatsuri. Hold
me tighter! Tighter!
Thank you!
I feel good after my bath.
I'm going to bother Takeshi.
What are you doing, Takeshi?
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars...
What's going on? I can't believe he's
so uptight, but reading
dirty magazines.
Who do you think will win?
Chimatsuri's skill is greater.
Yeah, but Chimatsuri has
that fatal weakness.
I know!
Are you ready? Let's go, Kagiri.
Yes, Sister.
Here I go!
It won't affect me. I'll show you the
results of my special training.
Don't hold back. Give
him all you've got.
Leave it to me.
Come on, Chimatsuri!
Here...
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars,
Jupiter, Saturn!
Hey!
Watch it.
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars,
Jupiter, Saturn!
You did it, Kagiri! Good job!
Thanks, Sister.
Now the sword is ours again.
Wake up, Chimatsuri!
Here, wipe your sweat with this!
Th... th... thank you!
I'll never forget this for
the rest of my life!
I can't breathe!
Let me go! Let me go!
Thank you!
You guys!
It's finished, isn't it?!
Maybe, I hope we'll have some peace
and quiet in class now.
I wonder if this is really over?
I doubt it.
It's been over a week since Akari
and Kagiri came to our school,
but my worries came true.
Takeshi!
I'm taking the sword back today!
Shut up! Take it if you can.
Here they go again.
Really, they're at it all the time.
Hey, want to bet on who wins?
I bet 500 yen on Chimatsuri.
I'm in for 500 yen on the twins.
Hey, stop it! They're quite
serious about doing this.
Hey, hey, let it go.
I bet 500 yen on our teacher,
Miss Ayatsugi.
What?
Stop it! We've had enough! Homeroom
has already begun.
Ouch!
See!
You're right!
Day in and day out, don't you get
tired of it?! Geez!
I see. Your family runs
an antique store.
All these unusual, old items...
My late husband had a passion for
antiques and loved collecting them.
Is that so?
Did Takeshi break something again?
Oh, no, not today.
Then, what?
I'm hoping you could convince Takeshi
to return the Toki's heirloom
sword to them.
The sword?
Yes, Takeshi and the Toki sisters have
been fighting over it every day.
Someone may get killed one
day if it continues.
Takeshi!
No way! I will not give it back.
No matter what anyone says!
I will never give it back!
I won't! Excuse me!
Chimatsuri, wait! Let's talk about
this, Chimatsuri!
Chimatsuri...
Father?
Oh no, I'm so late! I bet
Mom's furious!
Akari, I don't have time to
deal with you today!
Wait!
Are you scared, Takeshi Chimatsuri?
Hey, stop! Stop!
Wait! Please wait!
Big brother!
Takeshi!
There was no reason for you to barge
in while I was taking a bath.
I'm not a little girl, you know!
This is happening because you refuse
to return the Toki's sword.
What if one of us gets
hurt by accident?
Isn't that right, Mom?
Well, if someone gets hurt, it
will be painful, I imagine.
Isn't that right, Mom?
Well, if someone gets hurt, it
will be painful, I imagine.
Takeshi, you should return
it as she said.
See? Now go return it.
Big brother!
Takeshi!
Takeshi, I want to talk to you.
Open the door. I'm coming in.
It's locked.
Takeshi, open the door. Takeshi?
I'm going to get mad, Takeshi.
Answer me, Takeshi.
Takeshi?
Akari Toki...
Yes!
How long has it been since you
transferred to Arashiyama High?
Yes!
How long has it been since you
transferred to Arashiyama High?
I guess it's been about a week.
Shut up! How dare you call
yourself a Toki?
You returned empty-handed
again today!
You lack practice! Lack of practice!
Lack of practice!
Oh well, Mother, please don't
be so tough on Akari.
She's only a teenager.
You shut up!
Kagemaru, because you were not
good enough in the first place,
Raizo Chimatsuri stole
the family sword!
Really!
Wait a minute! I've got it!
Akari, didn't you say you
have a field trip tomorrow?
Yes!
Will Takeshi be there?
Good, good.
The proliferation of nuclear weapons,
the fear of a major earthquake,
unusual weather patterns...
There are many threats.
You are living in a very difficult time.
In order to survive such hardships,
it's imperative for you to know
what to do in a disaster.
Today's field trip focuses
on survival training.
We'll start with food preparation first.
Look, a bunny rabbit.
It's so cute.
You idiot! Hurry up and go
inside its left.
Who said, "I'll take care of it"?
What the hell are you two doing?
This isn't a battle zone.
What? We were trying to
get food for survival.
Excuse me, but this area is designated
as a wildlife preserve.
Hunting is forbidden here.
Then, what are we supposed to eat?
Listen, animals aren't the only
food source here.
It's possible to eat plants, roots,
nuts and some grasses.
You two simply have too much energy.
Now, there. It's perfect.
What is it, Sister?
Wait and see.
What do you think?
What? Where are you, Sister?
What happened?
What are you doing there?
Here! I'm over here!
What's going on?
Grandma taught me the Toki
family's secret potion.
If you drink it, it will camouflage
your body for a while.
It's called the magic of
the Seventh Elixir.
Miss Ayatsugi has gone
a bit overboard.
Yeah, "Go fetch some water
if you have all that energy."
Anything wrong?
Watch out, Torai!
That Akari, she never stops.
What? I thought I sensed
something over here.
That's strange.
Chimatsuri!
What?
She disappeared!
What? Seventh Elixir?
Yeah, it's one of the Toki
family's potions.
If you drink it, you can camouflage
your body for a while.
I see.
Wait, I couldn't see clearly,
but that means Akari is...
Naked!
Chimatsuri, I'll help you a lot this time.
You are so weird!
What's that?
Leave this to me.
It's an infrared sensor.
It senses body heat.
This way!
Impossible, I'm completely invisible.
There's no mistake. She's nearby.
I can sense someone over here too.
She's over here! I know I'm close,
so close.
I know I'm close, so close. What's this
soft, round thing like a bun?
A man touched me!
Torai?
Legs?!
Oh no, the potion is wearing off.
They're awfully late. I wonder
what happened?
It can't be!
Sister, please wait for me!
What was that?
What are we going to do now, Sister?
Now, we have no choice.
Kagiri, I need your help.
Yes, Sister!
I can't do anything so sneaky!
Idiot! Have you forgotten?
Deception is a ninja's specialty,
isn't it?
Yes, Sister!
Sorry to drag you out for my
shopping, Chimatsuri.
No problem. I'm happy to
come with you.
Boy, I am getting hungry. Aren't you?
Hey, Atsuko! Where'd she go?
Sorry, sorry. My shoelace came untied.
So, do you think you could
show it to me?
Show you what?
You know, the sword you are
all fussing over.
Oh, that, just a minute.
Takeshi, you'll be dead once you
pull out the sword.
Here it is.
Now's my chance!
Torai!
I can't leave you alone for a minute.
On a date?
Hey, no way. We were just shopping.
What's wrong, Atsuko?
You look pale.
A man...
Touched me!
Atsuko!
You're...
Ah, I've been found out!
Stop!
Hey, stop!
Hello, Chimatsuri. You know you'll hurt
yourself rushing around like that.
Teacher!
I knew it!
Damn!
Stop!
An arrow?
We have taken Atsuko
Yamaguchi hostage.
If you want to see her alive again,
bring the sword to the Toki castle.
Signed, Akari and Kagiri.
Atsuko!
A dream?
This is where Raizo and Kagemaru
battled for the sword.
So, that's why.
The sword reminds him of his father.
Good job, girls. If we're holding his
girl hostage,
Takeshi won't have any choice but to
come here.
Exactly.
Once he enters the castle, he's in
our hands.
With the best traps in the world,
we'll torture him as we please!
Boy, it hasn't changed a bit.
I remember I used to come to play
here all the time.
I forgot about the traps hidden
throughout the castle.
He fell into the trap.
Akari, Kagiri, go!
Yes!
What's this?! Damn!
Oh no, this doesn't look good.
I better find an exit soon.
Hello...
Mr. Toki? What?
I know Granny and the girls planned
this, but I feel a bit responsible.
Really?
Takeshi, it's been so long.
You've grown so much.
Mrs. Toki?!
This way!
But I thought you and my father
were enemies?
How can I explain this?
There's all kinds of friendship.
Takeshi, a cup of tea?
No, thank you. I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Mr. And Mrs. Toki, see you later.
Wait, Takeshi!
Well, since it's all prepared, would
you like a cup of tea, Honey?
Sure...
Did we give Granny too much control
of the girls' education?
Chimatsuri!
They're late.
Yes!
Damn! Where's the exit?!
Do you think it's okay to use this
without Grandmother's permission?
We have no choice. We've got
to go for it, Kagiri!
Yes, Sister!
Go for it!
Takeshi!
Atsuko!
Kagiri!
Sister!
Those idiots!
Kagiri!
It won't stop!
Ouch!
Atsuko!
Granny!
Takeshi, my sword! Give
me my sword back.
Give me my sword.
Granny!
Watch out, Granny! Granny!
Grandma... Grandma, I'd like you to
keep this for me.
Grandpa, but it's the Toki family
heirloom sword.
The most important thing next to your
life. I can't.
I can't take it with me to heaven.
What's wrong, Grandma?
It's the first time you've ever given
me anything.
Over here, a little further.
Careful!
I found them!
Okay, okay, okay.
Slowly, slowly.
Carry them out carefully. Careful!
They're hard as rock.
Hey, there's one more here!
Good job! Please have some!
Aren't you glad we came, Ayako?
Here you go!
Takeshi left this for you.
He said he couldn't keep Granny's
precious sword.
That fool!
That sentimental fool...
Where's Chimatsuri?
Where's Takeshi, Mom?
Maybe he's with his father.
With Father?
Cry Christmas tonight
Ima kogoesoona heyade
Setsunasa ga nijimu kara
Omae ni itehoshii
Cry silence tonight
Yume o terashiteta light house
Kuchizuketa ano yoru
mo sepia ni somaru
Futari aishi atta no ni
Nani ka ni chigirareta koi
Hitori no Holy Night
Kono yoru ni
Furi tsumoru aoi yuki tokashi
Ai ni yukitai
Kanaunara
Gin no michi chiribameta
Koe ni naranai
Sweet, I love you