Princess Etruria.
Tower of Etruria
Vol. 2 - The Enchantress Drowning in Lust
When I fought with my father
and ran away from the castle,
I came to this tower and made my first friend.
A friend that I met in this cave of nothing but monsters.
An enchanted sword, eh?
What's your name?
Don't worry.
Well, it'll be just the two of us
for a while, so let's be friends!
That's it! Why don't I give you a name?
Your name will be...
The sword's name was...
Don't worry. Just watch me.
See?
I knew it.
Yes, I knew it.
Well? Isn't that great?
Don't! Hey, stop it.
Hey, stop. I said no!
This can't be.
That's enough. You're a good kid.
Hey, wait
Th-That's enough.
Who are you?
Princess Etruria.
Wh-What?
Why? Why did you abandon me?
That man... What does he have that I don't!?
What's wrong, Cecilia? Are you having a bad dream?
She's blushing and in pain.
This is kinda turning me on.
No! No!
Cecilia! Cecilia! Are you okay?
Snap out of it, Cecilia!
Cecilia?
I must go.
Hey, Cecilia! What's going on?
Hey!
I... must go.
Cecilia?
I...
Cecilia! What's wrong?
I must go.
What are you saying?
Cecilia! Snap out of it!
Shut up, you guys. I can't sleep.
What's wrong?
Hey, Cecilia!
I must go.
A dark cell...
Balhara Cave.
That's what happened.
Are you listening, Albion?
Yeah. What do you think, Palmira?
This is silly.
I said it was silly.
It's your own nightmare. Deal with it.
I'm not sure if you know that girl or not
but could you please leave us out of it?
I mean, it's silly to expect us to believe it anyway.
Right, Sir Albion?
Oh, can we have another three helpings of this?
Y-Yås.
P-Palmira.
Albion, you agree with her?
Well, I...
Well, Cecilia, you're worried about what
she told you in that dream, aren't you?
Yeah.
But you don't know her name or where
she comes from or what she wants.
Don't be so cynical.
So she wanted you to rescue her?
Yeah.
But it sounded like she was jealous.
Doesn't she hold a grudge against you?
It's a hassle for me, so I'd rather stay out of this.
Palmira!
Yes?
I'll admit I'm not one to go chasing
after something I saw in a dream.
But I did see it. She was being strangled.
Anyway, let's go check it out.
And if it turns out to be nothing, that's all the better.
And if there is something there,
we can do something about it.
Either way, it's better than just
sitting around here. Right?
Good, then Balhara Cave will be our next destination.
Meeting adjourned!
If you want you can stay here.
We'll go without you.
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thanks.
Well, lets eat!
Aren't you eating a little too much?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Haven't you heard the phrase,
"Never go to battle on an empty stomach"?
Um...
If you don't mind my asking, are you going to that cave?
Yes, we are.
Sorry if I'm being intrusive...
but I'd give up if I were you.
I wish we could.
They're out there.
They? What is?
I cant explain it very well, but they're out there.
Things that attack people.
Many people have died already.
Well, it's a dungeon.
It makes sense if a hundred or so monsters are in there.
Will you tell us more details?
All right.
Balhara Cave is a five kilometer climb
up the mountain from this town.
It's a famous dungeon.
It actually used to be a tourist attraction.
It's the main reason why this town exists today.
This is the place.
Look at that!
It's exactly like a tourist attraction.
Anyway, let's explore it.
Good idea.
They say that many soldiers have been seen in there.
Soldiers?
Yes, though I haven't seen them myself.
Nonetheless, I hear they look like mummies.
Mummies, eh?
Then I suppose there are also vampires
and succubus monsters in there.
And a cave boss and undead minions.
A curse too, of course.
Can you think of anything else?
I don't care how crazy it sounds.
According to rumor, a sword was
taken from Balhara a month ago.
It was apparently a sword from the Tower of Etruria,
where a really scary enchantress lived.
Those things might be connected!
A really scary enchantress, eh...
That does sound heavy.
That was a nice workout.
Well, it seems like a normal dungeon to me.
But I don't see any mummified monsters.
If we go deeper in, well find our answer.
I agree.
Let's go.
Yes, Sire.
Cecilia, we're leaving you behind.
Wait!
Wait up, Albion!
Stop it please.
You want to cum. I know you want to cum.
Then I'll help you cum.
I'll make it feel even better for you.
Now. Cum into me.
I'm here. Hurry to me.
Hey, Cecilia! Cecilia!
Princess Etruria.
Princess Etruria, I've been waiting for you.
Come to me.
What are you saying?
Who are you? Tell me!
Come to my side. Come pledge yourself to me!
Hey, Cecilia! Snap out of it!
I must go.
Cecilia!
Cecilia! Wait up!
Palmira, were going after her!
Okay!
Sir Albion, what's going on?
Beats me!
Me too.
So she has friends.
And mummies at that.
What a hassle. I hate mindless enemies like this.
No help for that! We'll have to defeat
them quickly and go after Cecilia!
Let's go.
Right!
Please. Tell me. Who are you?
You abandoned me.
You didn't even want me.
I waited for you this whole time, Princess Etruria.
Was it you? Did you summon me here?
I finally have you, Princess Etruria.
I won't let you go. You belong to me.
We will be one forever, Princess Etruria.
I will not be lonely again!
Where did she go?
What's that?
What's this place? A palace?
Looks too creepy to be a palace.
Eiloppa, where is your Master?
Albion.
Cecilia! What's happened to you?
Why did you run off like that?
What's wrong?
You really had us worried!
Listen, Albion.
Cecilia?
Sir Albion!
Albion...
I have a favor to ask.
Drop dead.
Palmira!
Stay out of my way!
I say the same to you! What are you trying to do?
In that case, then you too must die!
So it's not a vampire or a succubus.
It's something completely different.
Though I guess it's an answer we didn't want.
Palmira!
I understand.
It looks like I'll have to fight it with all my strength.
What's wrong? Finished already?
Die!
Palmira!
If only you were dead, then Princess Etruria...
Shit!
Die!
No!
Wh-Why?
Hey! Cecilia!
Cecilia! Hey, Cecilia! Wake up
She's not waking up.
Cecilia!
Sir Albion...
Princess Etruria! Princess Etruria!
Please, save her!
If this keeps up... If this keeps up...
If this keeps up, Princess Etruria will...
Please save her! Please save Princess Etruria!
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Cecilia will be fine.
Shirera...
I knew it was you, Shirera.
Princess Etruria!
Your name will be... Shirera!
I'll call you Shirera!
Princess Etruria!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry I forgot about you.
Hey! Cecilia!
Don't tell me...
She's okay. She just lost consciousness for now.
"For now"?
Sir Albion,
may I ask a favor of you?
What do you need?
I ask..
I ask that you lie with me.
We will use my life force as a link
to bind you to Princess Etruria.
Sir Albion won't be in danger, will he?
No. You have my word. Sir Albion will be safe
And so will Princess Etruria.
Um, please help.
Sure.
Don't worry. I'll be gentle.
You're very wet, down there.
Don't say that!
Did it feel that good?
Yes.
Then...
Please put your manhood inside of me.
That is the best place to channel energy from.
I understand.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do with me as you will, Sir Albion.
I will.
It's okay. Come to me.
I... I'm about to cum!
Yes! Please cum! Please fill me full of yourself!
I'm cumming!
It's all fine now.
Princess Etruria will return.
Albion-san, thank you. And farewell.
Shirera!
Albion...
Thank you, Shirera.
So, what was she anyway?
My friend.
Your friend?
She sacrificed her life to save mine.
She was my precious friend.
Your friend, huh.
In that case, I wish I could've
become friends with her too.
I have to admit she's not a character you could hate.
Well, from now on shell be with you forever. Right?
Right?
How cheesy!
What do you mean?
Did I say something funny?
I was trying to cheer you up.
Sir Albion certainly is a dense man.
Palmira, did you just say something?
Nope.
Then that means...
But I'm happy. Sir Albion has found favor in me.
So I hope to serve you well, Sir Albion.
Sh-Shirera?
And so, Princess Etruria and Palmira,
I look forward to accompanying the two of you as well.
But Sir Albion is my master,
so I'm not letting you guys have him!
What was that?
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
Sir Albion is my Master!
I support his heart and soul.
What are you saying?
Albion belongs to me! You're number two!
But I too am supporting his heart and soul!
The past is the past.
He is my current Master now,
so I will not let anyone else have him.
Shirera, won't you listen to me anymore?
Yes. As long as you talk to me as a friend.
You really have got some nerve.
You realize this means war.
Bring it on.
Hey, girls, settle down.
You stay out of this!
Okay...
You've got no boobs anyway!
What? You perverted ghost!
You guys, cut it out!
We have to travel together. Let's try to get along.
Fine by me.