How are you feeling?
I see, I see. You cute little bastard.
The seal will break soon.
But until then, you must behave.
Tower of Etruria
Vol. 1 - The Bewithcing Magician
You may take her as your wife.
Oh. He's not that bad.
And what's more...
he's a handsome man. Just my type.
Are you in pain, Eiloppa?
So this man's life ends here.
"The Princess will be captured.
But then a highly skilled swordsman will rescue her.
And then the two will be bound together."
Fine! I accept the challenge!
Imbecile!
You try to solve every problem
in life with "Magic! Magic!"
Do you really think magic is the answer to everything!
How dare you speak like that Father!
We've entered a brand new Age of Magic!
Silence, fool! Why must you always be this way?
And what about you, Father?
Why won't you ever listen to me?
Because! Your magic is pointless!
How dare you! Your way of thought is outdated, Father!
C-Cecilia, you...
Wait! Calm down!
Let's discuss this...
Why... you...
Idiot!
And with those final words, my daughter ran away.
I hope she's doing okay,
but rumor says that she's been
captured by a magician in Etruria.
That's where you come in.
Can you rescue my daughter, swordsman Albion?
I'm a nomad swordsman.
I'm aware of the financial crisis engulfing this kingdom,
but if I'm successful in rescuing your beloved Princess,
then you will give me a handsome reward.
Do you accept?
If my daughter agrees, you may take her as your wife.
Leave it to me, Father!
Now for a valuable piece of information.
When my daughter gets overly emotional.
a symbol like this appears on her.
He's gone.
Kids these days.
Are you sure about this, Sire?
Having faith in the promise of
a lone nomadic swordsman?
It makes no difference to me.
In fact he seems a good match
for my beast of a daughter.
Don't you agree?
Yes, Sire.
He put up a decent fight.
All that remains is...
Just sit tight Magician of Etruria!
And then...
Wait for me, my Princess!
I'm coming to rescue you!
And when I do, I'll have my own castle!
Take that!
I wonder what she's like? I hope she's pretty.
Princess, are you hurt?
Swordsman, my heart ached
with anticipation to see you.
I have defeated the evil magician.
Everything is all right now.
My! I'm so glad!
Princess! What are you...
Please look. My body is the only way I can thank you.
And besides, I've become so wet waiting for you.
Please, don't restrain yourself.
Give yourself to me.
Princess!
Ah! That hurts!
"Ah, thrust into me harder!" shell scream.
Are you an idiot?
Etruria! Stay put!
You are the first to reach the top of this tower.
For that I congratulate you.
Shut up! Where is the Princess?
You needn't fret so.
Fine. As a reward for making it to the top of the tower,
I'll let you be my slave.
Shut up!
That face...
and those breasts...
Etruria is female?
And young, at that!
You're missing the point!
That's not what's most surprising about me!
That symbol on your forehead...
Aside from that
— she's kind or pretty!
— Are you stupid!?
— she's kind of pretty!
Well me.
Either way, it's clear my Father sent you.
Therefore, you're my enemy.
Come forth, my Eiloppa!
Don't tell me... a monster?
I thought I killed them all.
This will seal your doom.
Get him, Eiloppa!
Playtime is over!
I must rescue the Princess.
This is Eiloppas true form.
Rather impressive, wouldn't you say
Come. Have your fun with him.
Come on! Hurry up and kill him!
W-Wait.. stop...
Not me!
Hey! Stop it!
That's not the kind of "fun" I meant!
No!
Um...
Stop it!
Stop. Stop it now!
Not bad.
Don't look at me! Please!
No, don't!
Well its kind of hard not to look.
Don't... go in there.
Hey! Stop messing around and
tell me where the Princess is!
If you do, I might help you out.
I am a... magician.
I'm the Magician of Etruria!
Uh, yeah, but where is Princess Cecilia?
Don't!
There's one hurdle cleared.
There, I rescued you.
So tell me where the Princess is.
F-Forget about that. Can you get rid of this sensation?
Oh, fine.
A lot came out
I didn't know humans were so warm.
About that swordsman...
it appears he has found the Princess.
You understand what this means, Palmira?
Yes, Lord.
Tower of Etruria.
Shit. It just never ends.
This is the third time this has happened.
Just how many soldiers can Etruria make?
For the last time, its not me.
And I keep telling you, call me "Cecilia"!
Listen, you...
That hurt, you asshole!
Shut up already!
Well, monsters like that are no
match for the likes of me.
Not so fast. I defeated half of them.
Yeah, fine.
Hey, are you listening to me?
They were just bone monsters after all.
We're just swamped with bad luck.
Really? I've been having pretty good luck, actually.
That reminds me, how much longer
are you going to follow me?
Forever.
What!?
I see no problem with that.
Just pretend I'm Princess Cecilia. I'm your prize!
That again?
A real princess is no comparison to the likes of you.
You really are dense.
What?
So...
Why am I sleeping in the barn?
There are creepy things in here.
I wonder if he and Eiloppa are getting along.
Oh, well. Time to sleep.
What's this? This tingling sensation in my body...
My hands are moving on their own.
Is your body in turmoil Princess Cecilia?
Wh-Who s there!?
There are those in this country who
seek to usurp the Kings throne.
I was sent here to assassinate you.
But I've taken pity on you.
You wish to have intercourse with
me so badly that it's killing you.
Preparations okay.
Are you trying to use me to take over the kingdom?
Sorry, but I'm not into that.
No!
I can show you pleasures far more
erotic than those of a clumsy man.
No!
Not there!
Don't! Not there.
Jeez. What are you doing?
You came to save me.
l-ldiot!
I only came here to complain to you!
What's this smell?
It feels like my body is...
You were trapped under that woman's spell.
Wh-What are you doing, Etruria?
St-Stop.
You needn't hold back.
I don't mind doing it with you.
You always call me plain "you". Use my name for once!
Albion.
So, call me Cecilia.
Cecilia...
Cecilia, I want you.
I want you too, Albion.
Come in.
Cecilia, I'm coming in.
Yes! More!
Thrust into me harder!
More! Deeper!
No! No more!
I... I'm going to...
I'm almost there too.
Albion...
That sort of thing is meaningless alone.
Come here. I'll be your partner.
It's your fault that it won't go down at all.
Own up to it!
Don't worry. I'll be gentle.
Come. Take that thing out.
You're all wet.
Okay. I'm putting it in.
I'm about to...
I'm cumming.
Cum! With me! With me!
So warm...
What a relief.
You have some nerve,
doing it with another woman as I was
sleeping just a few feet away.
But that was just...
You little...
Like I said! It was because of her magic spell.
Hmph. Pervert
That makes two of us.
It does not make two of us!
I would never sleep with another man.
So you're jealous.
I'm not jealous!
Oh, I nailed it.
Never mind!
Hey, slow down, Etruria!
You're calling me by the wrong name again!
Sir Albion...
Tower of Etruria.
Albion, you did well in rescuing my daughter!
I will reward you.
As promised, you may have my daughter as your wife!
Are you dissatisfied?
No. I'm very grateful, my liege.
I love you.
We will have the ceremony tomorrow.
For today, rest well.
Palmira, you bitch. You're still lurking around.
What are you doing, Palmira?
You failed, yet you dare return?
What's wrong, General?
Uh, nothing, Sire.
Well never mind. For today...
Good for you!
Now you'll finally be lord of a
castle, just like you wanted!
What's wrong?
All the people of this kingdom
think you're Princess Cecilia.
You must've cast a really powerful spell.
You've got to be the thickest person I've ever met.
Still, that's partly why I fell for you.
Never mind that, what about tonight?
There's something you want to do, right?
Beautiful!
Not here!
What is this place?
I had no idea there was a maze
like this below the castle.
Oh my, oh my.
What's a pretty girl like you doing
in a dark place like this?
Oh, yes, I have an idea.
Why don't you become dinner for my cute little pet?
Dinner?
What?
This is...
It's an ultra-powerful magical being that the
royal family kept sealed up until now.
Isn't it cute?
What are you planning to do with it?
Destroy the world.
Every living thing will die,
starting with everyone in this kingdom.
Why?
It is the bidding of my Master.
Your... master?
That's right.
I won't let you do that!
The seal has been broken!
Come, release yourself from the prison that
held you here for the last 500 years!
That's right!
Destruction! Thrash around! And destroy them all!
Yes!
Right there!
Will you return the favor?
Does it taste good?
It's delicious.
You still have more in you.
I can't hold out any longer. Let me have it!
So hard!
More! More!
Deeper! Deeper! More!
This feels wonderful!
No! It's coming out!
Good! Keep going!
No! I can't...
No, I'm going to cum...
I'm cumming!
Albion... I love you.
I... I... think I love you too.
What?
Albion, are you okay?
Pervert!
Hey...
My castle!
I'm not sure what's happening,
but it came from under the castle!
It's an old monster that was sealed long ago.
And just what about that thing is sealed?
Someone must've released the seal!
There's no way we can kill that thing.
Yes. It's too big.
I think this is crazy, but I'd better try.
I'll help you.
Be my guest.
Just a minute.
Eiloppa says he'll help.
Eiloppa was created from that creatures life force.
That means the creature is like a father to him.
Oh, of course, I'm its mother.
My castles still gone.
Sorry about that my groom!
So I guess it's off on another nomadic journey.
My, my, that makes me happy!
I love traveling with you.
Me too! I am honored to travel with you, Sir Albion!
Why do you have to come along?
It's my burden of love.
What the hell?
Why do you have to be in love with Albion?
Hey! If you don't stop squabbling,
I'm leaving without you!
Coming, darling!
Maybe I should come too?
You're the last person we'd want coming!
Oh, is that a new gag?
Tower of Etruria
To be continued