Luticia.
What is it, Shou?
I only get to play with you at night.
It's really too bad.
I didn't mean it in a bad way!
It would be nice to see you...
smiling in the sunlight.
Lu.
Tragic Silence
"Girls Play"
Should I stop?
No!
Don't stop!
You want it?
Elena...
I'm coming in.
Rick!
Deeper, deeper!
Elena, I'm coming!
Yes! Yes, Rick!
I'll see you again?
If I feel like it.
Oh.
Is he coming?
Shou, is that you?
Did you wait?
No, I just got here myself.
Wow, have you grown again?
I don't know, maybe I have.
Of course.
You're growing older every day.
You really have outgrown me so quickly!
I've matured in other ways, too.
I've started working with Bob,
the village blacksmith.
The blacksmith?
I want to learn a trade...
so I can support you
wherever we choose to go.
I want to become independent...
so I can have you as my bride.
You want...
to marry me?
You don't?
His hands are warm.
But I'm...
No, we can't do that!
I can't...
live in the same world as you.
That doesn't matter, Lu.
You're always going to be my Lu.
So, will you accept?
Spring.
No, by summer, I promise I'll be ready.
Then I'll ask you again.
Please think about it.
Lu.
Spring.
No, by summer, I promise I'll be ready.
Then I'll ask you again.
Please think about it.
Lu.
Shou!
Hi, Levin.
Shouldn't you be watching Bob's store?
The store.
The new guy, Marcus can handle it!
What about you?
You look upset, and it's your day off.
Did your girl dump you?
I am right.
What's so important
that you have to leave work?
Do you have to ask?
My girl. I'm going to see my girl.
So, you're still seeing her.
This is a record for you, Levin.
Yeah, I love her!
If I had to, I'd die for her.
Levin, you...
What was that for?
He isn't from around here.
Know him?
No, never seen him.
Elena!
Wow, what a surprise!
I thought she was
Ms. Prim and proper!
She's having a secret affair.
Levin, that's really rude.
What! I thought you didn't like her, Shou.
Last year, you turned her down
after she told you how she felt, right?
It's not anything against her.
I'm in love with someone else.
That why I couldn't.
And now, you've been dumped
by your girl!
Not true!
Well, Elena's apparently moved on.
You need to find somebody new.
See you!
Levin, that jerk!
Yes!
No, don't stop!
No!
God!
I can't take it any more.
Yes!
Rick!
Right now!
I want this!
Yeah.
I want...
Elena!
Deeper!
Deep inside!
I feel it!
Yes, yes!
This is the last time.
We're not fated to be together.
You couldn't bring yourself to feed on me.
What are you doing?
No!
Yes!
Levin!
Go ahead.
What is it?
You want me on top?
No!
Levin, Levin!
I'm coming!
Me too!
We've been together for a while.
That's right, I think it's been
about five years.
Why do you ask?
It's nothing, really.
All right.
I saw a strange man.
This late at night?
No, earlier, but he gave me the creeps.
He didn't seem human,
but he looked like one.
It was kind of like watching a puppet.
He didn't seem human.
Yes Siris, just like you.
You both give off the same vibe.
I get it now.
I guess Elena and I are in the same boat!
What's this about?
Look at the commotion.
Who knows, maybe there was
a burglary or something.
How boring.
Yeah.
They've killed one of us!
It's a damned villager, a young female!
They're supposed to be used
for food, not sex!
We have to take action! Get revenge!
The villagers are an important source
of food for all of us.
What's going on? Both the village
and the castle are freaking out.
- Because...
- A murder.
Tia!
A village girl killed Rick.
What, Rick?
Everyone's upset.
They say it's wrong to play with your food.
Ha, he deserved it.
He was screwing around with a lot of them.
Well, our leader doesn't share your opinion.
We've left the humans alone for a while.
Eventually, they built this big village...
and now they're claiming it
as their feeding station.
The humans are upset,
so I'd avoid going near the village.
It's not my concern.
Right, Luticia?
Rick was one of us.
Right?
There's no need for you to defend
Rick at all, you know.
But...
What do you plan on doing, Luticia?
Keep seeing him secretly? Stop feeding?
Either way, I don't feel the need
to feed anymore.
You're in denial, so you're
forcing yourself to be happy, no?
This situation...
means we can't live in peace
with the humans right now.
Just like that girl from the village,
we need to make a choice.
Eventually!
Shou...
Can we get more men?
We need more than this.
Is he coming?
Lu!
Shou!
Lu, I made it!
Are you okay?
I had a hard time getting around
the guards at the exit.
But I'm here!
You know, this could have
happened at any time.
I know. The village is enraged
by this incident.
There are people that want to
destroy your clan.
Don't worry.
I promise, I won't let that happen.
Shou...
Elena, was crying.
Crying?
She wouldn't talk at all.
I think they were both in love
with each other.
But do you think my people can live
in peace with humans?
You have me. Right, Lu?
It's not all that difficult.
Don't you agree?
Warmth, the warmth of his hand.
As long as I have him...
Lu, I have a gift.
It's my very first creation.
I had to start over several times
until I was satisfied.
I want you to have it, Lu.
This isn't about my proposal
six months ago.
Take your time.
If you decide to accept my proposal...
then you can wear the ring.
I'll wait an eternity for you.
I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to upset you!
We have to make a choice!
Can I?
Luticia.
Shou.
Lu, you're getting wet.
No, stop it, don't say that!
Can I see?
I don't...
I want to know everything.
Will you?
Lu...
spread your legs.
Lu, it's beautiful.
It's my treasure.
Shou...
Shou!
I can't.
Please.
Lu.
Come inside me.
I want to feel you.
Lu, we're joined as one now.
Yes, Shou!
Shou!
Yes!
Yes, I'm coming!
We have a defector.
Who?
It's Siris.
She eloped with a male villager.
Damn it, with all the mess that's going on...
Siris.
We have to make a choice.
TO BE CONTINUED