The wind's started getting colder again,
and has been making that all too familiar 'swooshing' noise.
Once again, Kaoru's younger sisters are here.
SubDESU-H Presents
"A Wind named Kaoru"
We're back!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Nami!
It's good to be back, Mio-chan!
I'm Nami! I'm Kaoru-tan's younger sister, and I'm doing my best to grow up all lady-like.
And this is my kitten Tora-chan. Tora-chan and I are best friends.
You're great, Nami-chan!
Oh, not really.
I want to try too!
Me too!
Ah, the blessed ignorance of youth!
Huh? Mayuki-san!
Aren't you cold?
Me? Heck, I was a snow baby.
Ok, but do you really think it's a good idea to dress like that in front of other people?
Dude, there's nobody here but Kosuke and the girls.
Mayuki-san?
Hey, Hayumi-chan... You're taking good care of these, right?
How about I give them a massage for you?
Oh hey, Kanzaki, you're back, huh?
What are you doing to my sister?
Nothin'...
Hayumi-san, are you ok?
Holy crap! Mayuki-san caught a sword with her hands! That's awesome!
Uh, thank you.
Hayumi-san, don't encourage her.
Huh? Why?
Because I said so!
This is Hayumi-san. Just like Kaoru-san, she's a great sword fighter.
Came in 3rd in her district. She's pretty cool.
I'm over here, talking with the girls. I love coming to visit with them just to talk.
Wow! You're so good at that, Mio-chan!
This kinda thing is no big deal. {QCer's Note: This had "Meh," at the start of the line but that seemed weird so I cut it}
I can do it too!
Look out, Nami-chan!
Nami-chan!
What the hell are you guys doing over here, anyway?
What the... Are you ok?
Nami-chan, I'm sorry!
Uh... It's ok...
This is the kinda fun we get to have. It's a girl thing.
Oh, sorry to have kept you waiting.
This is the Sazanami Girls' Dorm, right?
Yes, that's right...
Greetings, I am Kanzaki Kaede.
Kanzaki...?
Please deliver this to Kaoru.
Well then...
W-Wait a minute...
Yes?
Are you part of Kaoru-chan's family?
Yes... I am her cousin. {This was down as "younger sister" but it sounded like she said Itoko which means Cousin}
Well Kaoru-san is actually here right now... You want me to get her?
No.
Kaede-chan?
Nami-chan...? Why are you...?
Hey, Hayumi-san! Kaede-chan is here!
What? Hayumi-san is here as well?
Oh, hello, Kaede-chan... What brings you here?
My parents asked me for a favor...
Kaoru.
Kaede?
Oh, I see... Your parents asked you to give me a message. Thank you.
It's no big deal...
You must be tired. You should rest for a bit.
I won't give you a choice, Kaede-chan!
So, as you can see, Kaoru-chan, Kaede-chan, and I all study at the same dojo.
That's awesome!
Really? So you both go around yelling 'haiya' and stuff, just like Kaoru-chan?
No... Unlike Kaoru, I wield one of the legendary weapons, a short sword called a 'Nagisa'.
Oh, really?
I specialize in a slightly different style which utilizes my favored weapon.
How cool!
That said, Kaede is still a beginner.
Yes, it might still be too early to call Kaede-chan a master.
What did she mean by 'legendary weapons'?
They are sister weapons.
I wield the katana 'Ittouryu'.
Hayumi-san uses a bow named 'Shinmeiryu'. {Was listed as 'Shintoryu' but that sounded wrong, could someone who can read Kanji check it?}
Kaede uses the short sword 'Fugetsuryu'.
Nami belongs to the Ittoryu school, but she doesn't have a weapon yet.
Oh really? So you must all have been too busy to really connect.
Not really... These two were always joined at the hip.
Oh...? Is that how it was...
I was just helping out Kaoru-san with her training, that's all...
Really? It looked like you were loving every second!
No! I was against it from the start!
Wow... You really are two peas in a pod! I bet you've always been best friends!
We are NOT friends!
Look out for the submarine!
You really are amazing, Mio-chan!
Kaede-chan... Shall I wash your back for you? {Original was "Shall I help you scrub?", but she said the same thing a few seconds later and the translation for that seemed more accurate}
N-no! I can handle this myself, thank you!
Oh...?
Kaoru-chan. Shall I wash your back for you?
Thank you very much!
But before that, if I don't get this little guy clean...
Alright then... I'll get you all clean, ok?
What... Kaoru-chan! Those wounds!
Don't tell me...
Oh... That's from a previous job.
Kaoru-chan... You aren't overworking yourself, right?
Hayumi-san, you don't have to worry about me.
Kaede, what's the matter?
Kaoru, will you go a round with me?
Sure. Let me get some wooden swords.
Kaoru.
Let's do it with live steel.
But...
Don't worry, I'm not a kid anymore.
Ok...
Ok... Here I come!
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
It looks like Kaede and Kaoru are going at it for real.
Secret Technique! 'Fugetsuryu'!
Commence!
Kaede-chan, you mustn't!
'Winning Strike'!
Looks like you came up with a great technique there. That was amazing!
When I was your age there's no way I could have done something like that.
If that's the case...
If that's the case, then why
won't you fight me seriously?!
Kaede...
How can you say that and
then still fight me like that...?
Kaede!
Kaede-chan!
Kaede-chan was crying...
It was Kaoru's fault.
Why was it my fault?
Why was it Kaoru-san's fault anyways?
Because Kaoru-chan is still fighting Kaede-chan with kid gloves.
But... But I went all out...
Kaoru... {I'm not sure if this is right, it was split from a line that didn't have this in there, I couldn't hear what she was talking over the line already in progress}
I think you know you didn't...
Weren't you holding back even a little?
Well, what do you expect me to do..?
I think you of all people know what you need to do.
B-but...
But I... I have no idea...
Kaoru-chan... You really haven't changed, have you? Even after all these years.
Man, it's quiet...
It is, isn't it.
Maybe it would have been better for you to go out with everyone?
Oh, I didn't mean I don't want you around...
Not at all.
Oh, right! I have to go swap out the laundry!
I'll help out!
Naw that's ok. Just relax and watch some TV or something.
But I...
Kosuke-san...!
Hello, this is Kanzaki Kaede.
Is... Is this the work Kaoru was talking about?
Finally done!
Kaede-chan! You want to go grab some food...?
What the...
Dear Kosuke-san, sorry I had to step out.
Thank you for the green tea
and sweet bean cake. Kaede.
Evil Spirit extermination, huh?
That must be it... The seals are corrupted...
It's no surprise that seals like that wouldn't hold back a spirit.
All right! Let's give it a try!
I did it!
Nothing is coming out!
Did I fail?
This... This isn't any Evil Spirit. It's a Demon!
If I can just defeat this Demon,
then Kaoru will finally...
All right... It looks like I can do this!
Secret Technique! 'Kanzaki Fugetsuryu' - Commence!
'Senyuuha'!
I did it! I exorcised the Demon!
I really can do it!
This sweet thing is delicious!
It's Marron-Glace.
Oh? Well, thank you.
Wow, you really are a good cook, Kosuke-san. This cheesecake is the best!
Kaede-chan...
What's with the cut on your neck?
Oh... Uh... It's nothing!
Oh, Kosuke-san, I'm loving the cake, but could I trouble you for something else to eat?
Oh, sure... I'll go grab you something.
Kosuke-kun, get me something too!
Me too!
I want more to eat too!
I guess I'll have some too!
Kosuke-san! One more round of cake for everyone!
Yeah, yeah...
Kosuke! Get some beer too!
Coming up!
Oh, Kaoru... We're having cake.
Thank you very much!
Mayuki-san, you're a manga writer, right?
Pretty much.
Wow, that's awesome!
Yes, this is the Sazanami Girls' Dorm...
What? The evil spirit...? The person I sent today? But I didn't send...
It must have been Kaede...
Yes... Not at all... Thank you for the business...
Everyone! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Took you long enough!
Kaoru... You want some cake... Hey, what's the matter?
Kaoru... Come have some cake! Look, we even have your favorite strawberry cake...
Hey... What's the matter?
Kaede...
What are you doing..?
Oh, you mean about your work? I took care of it for you! If it's just a spirit, then I can...
What was that for?
Don't you get it?
Why would you do that?
Well, you were out with the girls and...
You could have called my cell phone!
But... But I defeated it.
That isn't the point!
Evil spirits are a big deal...
What if you couldn't handle it?
You could have died!
But I'm still a Kanzaki! I can fight.
It's still far too early for you to be taking jobs...
There's nothing we can do about today, but don't let me catch you doing it again!
You're always like this...
You are always putting me down by acting so cool... When is it going to be my turn?!
I hate you, Kaoru!
Kaede-chan!
Kaoru-chan...
I'm at a loss...
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid Kaoru!
This is the...
From before...
But I definitely defeated this guy...
Kaoru!
Kaede! Where have you been?
I was so worried! I said some
things I shouldn't have...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?!
Kaede, what are you...
You've been possessed!
I can't... Move my body...
Kaoru...
You smell greaaaat...
I love you...
And this arm... This hand...
This finger... I love all of it...
She's being completely controlled!
Kaoru... Does it feel good?
Kaoru... You want me, don't you?
You know I adore you, don't you?
I want to be like you and take in all of you!
But you know what...? I can't be like you...
To be strong... To be able to
defeat powerful opponents...
Do you really want to be a master that badly?
When I first became a master...
On my seventh mission...
Just before I came across a powerful demon...
I was almost defeated.
Of course, at that time, I, you and Hayumi were all small children...
Our mothers were called upon to exorcise the demon.
However, the demon was too powerful,
and our mothers were unable to restrain it...
Then when mother fell unconscious, even I couldn't do anything,
and I had to call Oba-chan to help...
{QC's note Could someone check that Oba-chan? I'm not sure if she was saying aunt or grandma, she was talking about their mothers so I'm just guessing, it was hard to tell}
That beast was Kuon, and she sealed him in the body of a kitten.
But if he were ever to turn back and attack...
Perhaps attack Nami...
I would have to be the one to kill him!
And I know it hurts, but you know what?
I don't mind having to shoulder that kind of stuff myself!
I don't want you to have to
shoulder this kind of pain!
But... Even so...
It may be a bother to you, but...
I want to walk the same road as you!
Ka...e...de...
You really think I'll let you get away?!
I am...
You were possessed.
What about Kaoru?
She went after that evil spirit.
We're also heading out.
Well, then.
Wait!
Please wait.
Me too... Please take me with you...
Because I am also a Kanzaki!
Kaoru!
Kaoru-chan!
Don't look away.
This is what Kaoru... No... This is what we all must fight against!
If Kuon attacks Nami... I would have to be the one to kill him!
I'm fine shouldering that
kind of responsibility alone!
It's terrible isn't it? The work of an exorcist...
But you know what?
I'm glad I was born a Kanzaki.
Secret Technique! 'Kanzaki Shinmeiryu'!
Commence!
'Rakushousu'!
Hayumi-san...
Kaoru-san... Did that do it?
Kaede...
Kaoru... Let me help too...
I'm partly responsible for this!
Ok, Kaede! Let's do this!
Got it!
Secret Technique! 'Kanzaki Ittoryu'!
'Kanzaki Fugetsuryu'!
Commence!
'Fuka'!
'Shinkodan'!
Everyone! It's really been great!
Come again!
We'll always be here.
Nami... Are you leaving..?
I'm so sad...
Mio-chan...
It's ok. Nami and the girls will come back soon.
You mean it?
Yep. I mean it.
I swear I'll come back, Mio-chan, so...
Ok, then pinky-swear on it!
Ok!
Kaede. Please give my best to your parents.
Next time...
Let's have a real match!
Ok! I'll do my best to be stronger by then!
I can't wait.
And so, Hayumi and the others returned home.
Nami-chan seemed like she was going to burst into tears, but she did her best to grin and bear it.
It seemed like Kaede finally had a real smile.
And then...
I'm back!
Chika-chan?
Kaede-chan?
Has your fever come down?
Yep. Looks like it'll be gone very soon.
That's fantastic!
Hey! I brought cake, so let's dig in!
I brought your favorite!
I'm so happy!
All right, then see you downstairs, ok?
Thank you!
Everyone! I brought some cake home!
I want to eat it!
Looks awesome.
- You got it... Kaede-chan transferred to our school.
- What kind of cake is it?
- Please have some!
- You got it... Kaede-chan transferred to our school.
.
Oh, is Kaede back?
Kaoru!
- It looks like Kaede is really happy to be with Kaoru! It seems like it'll be a great time!
- I brought cake home! It's your favorite!
- Oh...? Is that so?
- It looks like Kaede is really happy to be with Kaoru! It seems like it'll be a great time!
I've become great friends with Kaede-chan as well, so I'm happy!
"The End"
"A Happy Ending"