I'm worried about you.
It'll be fine. I'll finish my mission like I'm supposed to.
I hope so.
Well, I should go now.
Be careful.
The human world is a tougher place than you think.
Thank you, Sadina.
Oh, by the way, tell my mom that...
You stupid girl!
You shouldn't turn around when you're that close to it!
H-How could I not worry about her?
Trouble Evocation
Shuuya-kun, do you believe in magic?
Magic?
I'm already under your spell.
Rei-san, your beauty is the magic you used to take my heart hostage.
Since the first time I saw you at the university library, I...
I'm so happy.
I wasn't expecting you to say that.
Rei-san!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'll show you a whole new world.
You're so mean!
I thought you were the type who'd accept a guy like me.
One Month Later
Wh-Who are you?!
How did you get in here?!
Nice to meet you. I'm a devil named Ria.
I'm sorry I'm a month late.
A month late? A devil?
Yes, that's right!
Right, right, right, right. Get out of here.
I'm not into weird cults like that.
You've got it all wrong. I'm the real thing.
Didn't you summon a devil a month ago?
Now that you mention it, I did do a summoning a month ago.
I was just trying to follow along as I was reading my old man's books.
Did I do it right?
Did you finally remember?
Although a little late, I'm here to grant you three wishes.
Thanks, but I don't care any more.
I don't care anymore. I don't care anymore.
I don't care anymore.
And that's how it is.
Please, now that you've summoned me, I can't leave until you tell me your three wishes!
Come on, you had to have wanted something if you summoned a devil.
Get out of here!
I'll grant any wish you desire!
I don't need that wish to be made anymore, so leave me alone.
So you had a wish after all!
Please tell me what it was.
I'll make sure it comes true.
I wanted to go out with a certain girl.
But it turns out that girl was actually a guy.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'll show you a whole new world.
So now you can see why I don't need that wish any more.
Sorry to disappoint you.
H-Hey!
You're so mean!
You summoned this poor little devil,
and now that I'm finally here, you're just sending me away?
I-It's nothing to cry about.
You're terrible!
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
What kind of place sends out a devil a whole month after it's been summoned?
It's obvious that people will change their minds if that much time passes.
I'm sorry!
Please!
I can't go back to the demon world until I've completed my mission!
That's not my problem!
I'm not wasting my soul over something like that!
I'll grant you any wish at all!
Shut up. Go home.
Sh-She's cute...
Are you telling the truth?
Can you really grant any wish?
Yes!
In that case, become my servant.
What?!
You said you'd grant anything!
But I don't wanna do that.
Oh, really? Well, then...
W-Well, then?
First, summon the Archangel Michael!
Second, summon Lucifer!
And third, make them dance cheek to cheek!
Go ahead and grant those right now.
I can't do that. I'm sorry!
Well, you can't do what you can't do.
Then it seems you'll have to go.
See ya. Bye bye.
I understand.
Wh-What are you doing?
We demons have a special custom to make a contract with a new master.
Really, you don't have to...
Please come here, Master.
Hey, hey, are you actually gonna do a demon?
But she's so cute.
She's still a demon!
But she's cute. She's so cute!
Oh? So it's all the same down here.
All right.
Amazing.
I'm really feeling it.
Please don't pull out yet!
Not my ass. No!
And that's how Ria and I began our strange life together.
Have a nice day, Master!
She's a good girl, but...
Master!
Master.
M-a-s-t-e-r.
I wonder if it'd be easier to nullify the contract or let myself die from sex.
[Fujiki Drug Store]
[Bokkin' Tonic Water]
Hey, Shuuya, are you all right?
I'm just dandy.
Hey, young man. Young man!
You look really worn out.
You can tell?
I could tell at a glance.
But for times like this,
there's Super Strength Charred Newt Stimulant Formula DX!
If you eat it, you can go non-stop for a week.
Starting today, you'll be a god among men!
Say goodbye to the sleepy you of yesterday!
Right, umm...
I'm having a special promotion for it right now, so it's free.
You're lucky, you know.
I'm the only one who'd give something like this away.
So I'll be on my way now.
You'll be on fire tonight, young man.
Wh-What the heck was that?
Welcome home, Master!
I'm back.
Ria, do you want to try this?
What is it?
Have a look.
Don't devils use this sort of stuff, Ria?
Ria!?
Hey, Ria! Ria!
You're afraid of salamanders and lizards?
I have been, ever since I fell into a salamander breeding pond as a child.
You know, you really don't act like a devil.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'm a failure as a devil.
I can't use magic well.
I'm even better at cooking by hand than with magic.
Ria...
Your cooking tastes good because it's made by hand.
You'll be on fire tonight, young man.
I might as well.
M-Master!
A-Are you okay?
Master, you're amazing!
Master...
What? Something's wrong.
Why am I acting this way?
Damn it, what's happening?
My body's moving on its own!
Set Ria free.
Just say, "I nullify my contract with you."
Hurry up and say it!
Ria.
Wh-What's going on!? What am I saying!?
It feels... so good...
This is my second wish.
Shit!
My contract with you...
S-Stop!
What's taking so long?
Hurry up and nullify the contract!
I nullify... my contract...
You were amazing today.
Master!
So that charred newt I ate increased my libido,
and by absorbing that libido you were able to use magic?
I'm very sorry.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
But...
You stopped me just in time.
And besides, this means...
you've leveled up!
Ria learned the lightning strike!
Or something like that.
Stop it already.
Don't be embarrassed.
I wanted this to end peacefully, but I guess it can't be helped.
koi no kiseki
[A miracle of love.]
okoshimashou
[Let's create one ourselves!]
dare mo konna watashi tomeranai
[No one is able to stop me right now.]
kisu kuraide furatsuiteta
[Something like getting dizzy over just a kiss,]
watashi tokkuni sotsugyuo shitano
[I've already graduated from that long ago.]
sonna oogesa ni warawanaide
[Don't laugh at me so exaggeratedly,]
mienai koto ga sugoin dakara
[there's a lot of amazing things that you can't see.]
imamade no koi nante
[For all the past loves,]
pinto no boketa oto kurai
[to be nothing but sounds out of focus.]
sukinandai sukinandatte
[I love you, I said I love you.]
uu ai wo ageruwa
[Oh, I'll give you my love.]
koi no jumon
[A spell of love.]
torae mashou
[Be captured by me!]
daremo kono jounetsu tomerarenai
[No one will be able to stop this passion.]
Fansub by Erobeat
August 2013