Mommy!
I feel so refreshed!
Well, that'll last me at least two weeks.
Trouble Evocation 2
Right there. Yes, it's amazing.
It's hitting me so deeply.
Does it feel that good?
Yes, it's absolutely amazing.
Ria!
Master, how do you like my pussy?
It's great.
Master, I'm reaching my limit.
No, I can't take it anymore!
Me too!
Master! Master!
Ria!
Master!
I'm going!
Master, your bag!
Thanks, Ria.
Now, time to clean.
This is my Master's...
What am I thinking about?
Let's see.
I have lots of time today, so I'll make roast beef.
You never change, Ria.
Who's there?
Sadina? It's you, isn't it!?
I didn't expect you to come here.
Don't touch me like nothing has happened.
What?
Why? We've been friends since childhood.
Ria, what are you even thinking?
I came to this world right after you.
I've already carried out several contracts and been promoted to noble demon, fourth class.
And in the meantime, you haven't even finished one mission, much less been awarded a promotion.
It's already been several months since you made a contract with that human named Yoshino.
And yet...
You have no excuses.
Unlike me, you're the daughter of a grand noble.
You're the successor to the demon noble family of Godzuike.
Umm... Sading, I'm not sure I get your point.
Our mission is to fulfill the three wishes of the person who summoned us.
The reason I'm living here is that it's one of my Master's wishes.
And we already exchanged vows according to our custom,
and my Master satisfies me, so...
W-Wait a minute, Ria.
Do you actually understand the rules for missions and contracts?
Unless you take the human's soul,
withing six months, six days, and six hours of making a contract in that world's time,
you'll be disqualified.
And that's not all.
If you fail now, you'll lose your right to succeed the Godzuike family for eternity.
Did you know that?
That can't be.
It's all right. You still have time.
I guess I can help you, too.
Do whatever it takes to find out his last two wishes and take his soul.
What's wrong, Ria?
What exactly will happen to Master if I take his soul?
Who knows? Humans are pretty much the same whether they have a soul or not.
I'm being serious, Sadina!
To put it simply, they become zombies.
They go on living without any memories or emotions.
What does it matter?
Listen, Ria.
You have to be the heir to your family. It's you destiny.
You can't forget about your responsibilities as a noble for the sake of one human male.
I know that, but...
It's just as Auntie, I mean your mother, had feared.
She gave me a message for you.
From my mother? What is it?
She said that if you didn't want to come back, you could stay here.
My mother... said that?
My poor little Ria.
I'll cheer you up.
S-Sadina...
I'll make you forget that man.
You're really enjoying this.
Just look at how you're reacting.
Make me feel good, too.
Yes, that's it! Do it harder, Ria!
Sadina...
How is it, Ria?
Isn't it better than doing it with a human?
Master...
Ria...
No!
What?
I'm sorry Sadina, but...
If that's your decision, then you leave me no choice.
Sadina?
I'll take over from here and finish the job.
You'd get in my way, so I'll make you wait in there.
What are you planning to do, Sadina?
It's useless. You can't break this barrier.
See ya.
This is a noble's mantle. Why am I wearing it?
You like it?
It was our dream to wear it, remember?
Sadina, where are we?
It's a barrier I made. Not too shabby, huh?
My magical power has grown a lot.
Using my magic, it will be easy to make Yoshino state his last two wishes and to fulfill them.
Then all you'll have to do is take his soul and go back to the demon world.
Don't do it, Sadina!
Then are you going make him cancel the contract,
and just wait for another human to summon you?
Make him cancel the contract?
But if I do that, I won't ever be able to see him again.
Enough of that already. I'm starting to get angry.
Take a look over there.
That's...
Mother!
I don't know why you're so fixated on that man.
But you can't go back to the demon world until you fulfill your mission.
Will you throw it all away?
Your homeland, and your mother?
I see.
I'm going.
You wait here.
Think about everything that's happened, and what will happen from now on.
Sadina!
You really saved me. Thanks!
I only did my duty, Master.
I see. I'm always in your care, Ria.
Sure.
Mom, Dad, hurry up!
Wait up, Konomi!
Hurry, let's go!
You shouldn't run off like that.
Sorry!
We'll eat something tasty today.
I want to eat omelet rice!
Maybe we'll be like that some day, too.
Don't be silly!
Humans are just humans!
They're deceptive, selfish, and cowardly, and despite all that, they're arrogant.
Why would Ria...
Excuse me.
You may be right that humans are pretty worthless in general.
But there are some good people among them.
Like me, for one!
Y-Yes, of course.
Ria, you're acting strange today.
Really? I think it's just your imagination.
My imagination?
Yeah, maybe that's it.
Let's lighten the mood.
Ria, come with me for a bit.
Huh? Where to?
Just come along.
Wow, I didn't know about this place.
Ria, I'd like you to fulfill that wish after all.
That second wish I told you about a while back.
Um, well...
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. Master, I forgot what it was.
You forgot?
Sorry.
There is that.
How could you remember something you never heard?
When did you notice?
At the very start.
I sensed a magic far more powerful than Ria's.
You were the one who gave me that charred newt earlier, too.
Correct. You're pretty sharp.
And you made another mistake.
The real Ria would've shared an umbrella with me.
Show your true self!
Where is Ria!?
She's in here.
She's trapped in here.
It's a barrier she can't possibly break.
Fool, do you think a human stands a chance against a devil?
Return Ria to me!
I already told you that you can't beat me.
We'll see about that.
Wh-What is this?
That's a holy powder used to exorcise devils.
I've carried it around ever since that encounter with the newt, just in case.
D-Damn you!
Where did you get that?
My father is an expert in this stuff.
He's a worthless father, but this time I'm grateful to him.
Now give Ria back to me!
You want her that badly?
I guess you would. She has quite the body.
What?
What have you done with Ria!?
What have you done!?
If you want to know that badly, I'll tell you.
You did that to her?
It was an interesting show. I wanted you to see it.
Also, she looked like she was enjoying it.
That girl loves sex.
You bitch!
Now you will feel what Ria felt!
No!
Ria...
Ria's a devil.
Do you really think she can live with a human?
I-I don't know.
Since she's a devil, she'll only be unhappy if she remains in this world.
All devils, including Ria, have to go back to the demon world eventually.
Don't you understand?
Why should that matter!?
Give me that jewel and release her!
Let her...
You fool. We demons can drain the vitality from a human we have sex with.
I didn't think you'd fall for my trap that easily.
And now that I've completely recovered my magic power, I'll have to thank you properly.
Now cancel your contract with Ria.
I refuse!
Oh, really?
I didn't want to do it the hard way, but...
There's another way to free her from you.
If the human with whom a contract is made dies for some reason,
the contract is automatically nullified.
It may not look like it now, but I'm usually a lucky guy.
Hurry up and say that you've nullified your contract with Ria!
Otherwise, I'll...
No!
Will you throw it all away?
Your homeland, and your mother?
My, my. What happened, Ria?
You know, everyone says I'm bad at flying.
They say I'm an embarrassment to the Godzuike family.
It's not being able to fly well that makes a noble.
But Mom, I want to be like you!
You should just be yourself, not try to be like someone else.
What's important is trying to be a better you than you were yesterday.
One day, you'll grow up, and you'll have to choose your own path.
When that time comes, follow what your true self tells you.
My true self...
Do what I say!
No!
How? How can a mere human resist this long?
Ria!
R-Ria! You managed to break my barrier?
Sadina.
Ria...
Master!
Are you all right?
Ria, this will be my second wish.
Don't leave my side!
Promise to stay with me forever!
I can't grant you that wish.
Is that because you're a devil and I'm a human!?
That's not it.
It's because it's the same as your first wish.
As long as you don't cancel the contract, I will always be by your side.
Forever, no matter what happens.
Ria, do you understand what you're saying?
I've decided, Sadina.
Is that so.
Then do as you wish.
Sadina...
Sadina.
We'll always be friends, right?
Goodbye, Ria.
Oh, that's right.
One last thing...
Be happy.
Thank you, Sadina.
Master! Master!
Could you stop calling me master?
But...
My second wish is that you call me by my name.
I can't do that.
But it's my wish.
You know my name, right?
Shuuya-san.
Speak up so I can hear you.
Shuuya-san...
Shuuya-san!
Louder.
I read your report.
I gave you a difficult mission.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm grateful for your kind words.
Let's stop with the formalities.
Stand up.
Auntie...
Was Ria's decision for the best?
Sadina...
Just like humans, we demons can live our lives in many different ways.
Ria chose her path of her own free will.
I'm proud of her for doing that.
My wish is for her to be happy...
no matter where she is.
I couldn't forgive her.
I thought she would make you sad.
And...
I thought we would always be together.
Sadina.
Shuuya-san, hurry up.
Did you really have to buy all this stuff,
just because we haven't gone shopping together for a while?
But you do look good in that dress.
Thank you.
By the way, Shuuya-san...
What is it?
Have you thought of your third wish?
I have, but it can wait until the right time.
Okay.
Fansubbed by EROBEAT
August 2013
koi no kiseki
[A miracle of love.]
okoshimashou
[Let's create one ourselves!]
dare mo konna watashi tomeranai
[No one is able to stop me right now.]
kisu kuraide furatsuiteta
[Something like getting dizzy over just a kiss,]
watashi tokkuni sotsugyou shitano
[I've already graduated from that long ago.]
imamade no koi nante
[For all the past loves,]
pinto no boketa oto kurai
[to be nothing but sounds out of focus.]
sukinandai sukinandatte
[I love you, I said I love you.]
uu ai wo ageruwa
[Oh, I'll give you my love.]
koi no jumon
[A spell of love.]
torae mashou
[Be captured by me!]
daremo kono jounetsu tomerarenai
[No one will be able to stop this passion.]