Whenever I see him my heart shakes.
Kurusu goes about practice very enthusiasticaly.
All in all, it is what he does everyday, how boring.
Is he that serious or is he a fool? It is really unpleasent.
If my first love were such a person...
He can be very good for a lifetime.
Mao you can't do that.
Who knows, if I don't say hello?
How can I...ah...
Does it matter? Today you don't have the heart to tell him. Oh. We will be rivals.
You're so casual....
However his eyes sought her...
He's...
Lie...a lie, right?
Me and him are breaking up.
I have already ended it since August.
I want to talk to you...
I'm sorry.
I have always had a crush on you.
He is now lost.
I would like to sccompany him.
He could not forget her.
Even so, it does not matter.
(Selection of memories for her boyfriend on Christmas Eve.)
Right, ah.
What should we do?
I have been by his side, accompaning him for one day...
(Good Night, see you in a dream.)
A little exciting is it not?
Will he dream about me?
Kurusu!
Zheng have you heard?
The P.E. teacher has been fired for doing that something?
He finally could not resist.
Check your underwear and hope he doesn't find you.
I didn't know I violated the school regualtions.
His things must be completely confiscated.
He is daring to do that sort of thing.
Do you know? Heard they got someone new for the position, so it has to be true, right?
Do not joke, and if he did do it, he will die very miserably.
That's the teacher's fault.
To cause such a deep wound.
Baseball club meeting, ah, then there is nothing I can do about it.
So next time...
I really wanted to tell him to come to my room so we could talk.
Use your chest.
Anyway, you are not wearing a bra.
Please do not say those words.
I'm not like...
What?
Please enough is enough, we do it in the middle of the night every night.
I'm late to class, my mother is starting to suspect.
Again take a look.
Then , I will, regardless...
engage with another woman.
No... I do not want.
What is this, ah?
Fine.
Teacher's penis.
You are acting like it is not familar.
Although stinky, it is hard and rough. Let em become a real woman.
Very brutally pierce my virginity.
Let my virgin area become dripping wet.
Let em feel your powerful penis fill my womb.
I pledge my life to my master.
She is obviously still our idol.
Now every night she is a part-time mistress.
However there is something I am sure of.
This gift was very effective.
So pretty, ah.
She will not come right?
No...no,ah.
Then I was deprieved of the virgin in this room, by that man.
The loss of the viriginity souvenirs...
Don't...
I would like to call her.
I will call Masada.
No, no, no, stop quickly.
Kurusu, come and save me.
What's the use telling him now?
Would you like him to come watch?
You might as well enjoy the pleasure I bring to your pussy.
Do not...
Sorry, my friend...
no longer a virgin.
It was...
a delusion to be your girlfriend.
Sorry.
You shall show me absolute obedience.
You should be aware of the growth of virgins.
No, do not...
Disgraced.
Do not...
And your development here is really good.
Today, at my house I have a lot I want to say.
Would like to join him ... but ...
Why?
Why is this?
Scared, you are shaking?
A good hot ass, ah.
But ... too much, too much
Do not ... Do not lick
Do not, ah ... dirty
Don't...
Disgraced...
You are really sensitive to masturbation, indeed, so like a virgin.
No ... I have not done
My first time, I only want my future husband to touch me.
Do not forget
Only you can protect the young madien.
Hey, go up a little
Sure enough, striped underwear is the most suitable for a young madien.
It feels hot, it feels hot, do not
Something is coming out, no...
Out...
Now...to do her homework.
Next, suck me with your sexy mouth.
You ... want me to do oral sex?
You want her secret to be revealed?
This is for you.
Today, we go home together.
I will wait for your club to be over.
Her elder sister, ah?
Before the big event you are taking a shower?
Well, because I sweat easily.
They say if your metabolism speeds up you are in love.
Not to wash the body clean, then ...
Kurusu ...
Now I have no way of
But one day ...
Kurusu ...
One day ... not today?
Seeing ... I beg you, hurry up ...
Do not ...
The third time, your expression is really very good.
When you urinate the expression is really sexy.
I have been watching you since I started school.
Unlike that guy Kurusu, I've been watching you.
I am going to yell in pleasure.
Please forgive me.
No ...
No, it is coming out.
Yesterday, I am very sorry, I was suddenly in a hurry ...
Oh, do not bite with the teeth.
Much better than yesterday, right? Progress?
How do I know this kind of thing.
Just ...
I just want to finish this.
When it comes to tennis she is number one...
But when it comes to peni you are the best.
I told you we had to make an appointment before Christmas or it would be full.
(Women's tennis community)
Others are looking, I do not want to speak here.
The penis club activities can not be put off.
I have a date with Kurusu!
Also have Fukui…
You do not properly understand the situation now.
Did you tell them?
Do not ... No, not me
If you are not honest, I will cum in your womb.
Do not...I don't want to be pregnant...I do not want to have children....forgive me
Last night, your friend here said she heard it from you.
No...
I have to cum and I have lost my life, ss I might as well make you a woman.
Spare me, would be seen
The reputation and the hymen, two for one.
My hymen is not, I'm a virgin...spare me
I can only meet him
I do not have the desire to inflate him, I can only listen to him.
Today, drink it all.
I would also like ...
I would also like to drink.
You want more, you just do not have a way to really get it.
Again...again he ordered me ot do naught things.
I want to become like the chaotic girls.
You serve me well, I can also make you happy inside.
Such a thing in front of him, unspeakable.
To say such a thing in front of you...
Kurusu, he does not know anything.
You have become my little private semen toilet.
That is true.
But let me drink your semen.
Let my breasts make you feel good.
Does my chest make you feel good?
Oh, it is definitely not the size of his.
So hurry up and make your penis hard.
From there, shoot out lots of sticky stuff.
All of it into my mouth.
I have been looking forward to Christmas for a long time.
Do not forget, after being on vacation from school, I will see you at the previous place.
So, I went to look at associations, such as meetings.
In the end would he also like to torment me? I simply want to find the teacher and apologize ...
Too despicable, dirty ...
Your penis, I can no longer resist. Ah.
Master, master, master ...
The one who told is me, I would like ot apologize to you.
Coming...coming...coming
Come, shoot it all inside.
Shoot all your semen inside me.
Fill my uterus inisde, shoot inside.
Such a thing should never happen, but at least ...
Today it is going inside...
Looks like you already swallowed the bait.
Ah? Here?
You should continue to be obedient.
Nasty, cold. Oh.
To ... Why?
It is going to come out, let me use the toilet ...
This should be enough, right?
Old ... teacher? !
How this is going on ...?
It is not good…
From the beginning, a trap ...
Feels strange, attacks of pain and pleasure at the same time.
This shy expression is too wonderful.
My friend here added a drug to the stuff inside you.
But that ...
Terrific, this is amazing, I also want to.
Just licking only, they are already doing the ...
My virgin thing is at the end of the month.
I want to...
No, there is a growing feeling.
You can see what is it?
I see the teacher's ...
What is it?
Penis is a penis ...
Very hard, but also shaking
Want to do it?
Never.
Because I have agreed, to only come at home.
But ...
You want it right? You are a virgin.
It was not I, my womb was the one who was wet all day, all day it to wanted to have your penis inside.
If I do not drink hot semen, it is wet non-stop.
You have also been protecting?
It doesn't matter, for today I am not protecting.
What was I saying? But already…
Do not let me wait, in one breath puncture it.
You see down there, right? You see my pink hmyen?
It is a present, today is a day for Christmas presents...
I have been constantly on guard till now.
Hymen broke.
I have fianlly fallen.
How such a sudden ...
Good... deep, good...
I wanted his dick for so long and it is so good I can not breathe.
My pussy was born for teacher's penis.
Come, inside my uterus.
With your penis mark me as your woman.
and mark my eggs.
It is the teacher's fault.
She was obviously our idol.
Life was shattered.
But...
This happened after...
The value of my collection will be more and more ...
My home page will also have a lot of people come.