What? ... ,Is that what you heard, Tate-kun.
Knowing Aya-chan, I guess she would say something like that.
Huh? As you always say, they have to be your type ...
But...
He is very handsome, huh?
Don't you think, it would be great together?
Huh? Me? I ...
Akihito?
But why would I like that idiot fan of baseball.
Aoi, shut up! Lower your ...
Pervert!
Yes, he always behaves like an idiot.
You heard, right? Can you believe it?
Sorry I opened the window so suddenly ...
It was warm.
Hey, you guys, really eavesdropping is the worst.
Huh, it is not something to laugh about.
Akihito and I, we're just neighbors.
She is my childhood friend ...
Kanzaki Aoi.
Moreover, in classical Chinese literature...
Since childhood, she was very pretty, she is well known,
And also, she is ...
the idol of the school.
Huh...
Kurusu trains very hard, eh?
Training is the only thing he takes seriously.
That fool...
How handsome he is, eh? ... A guy who gives everything in training.
Don't say that...
Well, don't take it the wrong way.
N-not that ...
Tate-kun, is ...
envious of me.
At least you are honest with him...right?
I...
Since we were little, we have always been together.
Huh ... Every morning is always the same ...
I would like to see just one day where you wake up earlier.
What?
Nothing.
Aoi, wait!
I always thought that we were going to be together ...
TRUE BLUE Episode 1 Fan Subbed by: Broodwarjc
All these students have such short skirts.
These young people are unbelievable.
The beauty of the school has just appeared.
What's with that look, Kurusu?
Please excuse him, Shoda-sensei.
What a pair of boobs you have...
I'll make him understand.
They can do a great many dirty things...
Come on, Akihito, you too.
So it doesn't cost you.
Even with the skirt on, you cannot hide those curves, I love both.
Penetrating that beautiful ass I would only endure a few minutes.
Because Kanzaki has apologized, I'll let you go.
Thank you, very much.
While stimulating her young body, I could tame her...
with my magnificent penis.
That bastard, Shoda,  was watching with an obscene look.
Who is the one who looked that way recently?
And what purpose does that serve now?
When we were little, you always wanted us to take baths together.
I still remember that, that was long ago.
I have to tame her, with my magnificent penis.
Because, that Kurusu, he does nothing.
What is with that fool Akihito.
He doesn't even remember.
But he seems to be growing out of his stubbornness.
I...
I have grown enough, no?
More than you believe, Kanzaki.
S-Shoda-Sensei!?
My penis is much better, right?
It is very hard and wet for you.
It is not...like his...
Just from seeing it, you fainted.
If you are wondering about Aoi, I don't know where she is...
Strange, we agreed to walk home together after the club activities.
This was to be expected of a virgin.
Enormous!
These are larger than I imagined.
I cannot stop touching them.
They are so smooth.
It hurts...
Damned youngster...No I will not limit myself to only your breasts.
So I will make you prove something.
She might still be changing, but it is taking quite a bit.
W-what...?
It would not be wise for you to shout.
Unless you want someone to see you this way.
I feel sick...
Please help me...
Please help me, Akihito...
That voice, it sounds like Aoi?
No!
You like that?
Now I will make you feel even better.
Your nipples are very excited.
Your mistaken...
Look at how your nipples have angered you.
It hurts! It hurts...
It is said some people, concentrate on pain to double the pleasure.
This is what you are doing, Kanzaki.
What are Aoi and Shoda doing...?
Incredible...What a grand sensation.
This must be a lie, doing this at school.
Certainly this is a dream...
This is a dream...
It so big...So much bigger than Akihito...
You hold them together or we will go outside.
Lie...Sure that is all this is, a lie...
Aoi...
Aoi!
Akihito.
Is something wrong?
I haven't seen you in the club activities.
It's...nothing.
I didn't feel well and went to the infirmary to get some rest.
Y-yes I see.
As much... as much as I wash...
The smell of teacher will not go away.
Everytime I remember it my body heats up and I feel strange...
The next day, Aoi did not come to wake me.
Hey, Kurusu, you came alone today?
It seems like you have been rejected.
All night I could not fall asleep...
You're a little late, Kanzaki.
Please stop doing weird things.
Now I am going to class, so here I go.
Could not sleep, remembered what happened yesterday?
Y-You're wrong...
I just want to quickly forget... That...
Once you have seen my perfect penis...
It is not something that you easily forget.
Really, it is not that!
That's not what you feel, so...
Stop, please.
Tell me what the school's rules say about underwear.
The underwear has to be white.
And you cannot wear pink or other colors...
But no one will see...
Straight!
As a member of the disciplinary committee, I cannot let this pass.
They are pink, how obscene.
Currently there are a lot of girls...
Are you saying you do not mind if everyone knew what you are wearing?
It is time we see your measurements.
Sorry, my head hurts a little.
I cannot concentrate in first period...
Becuase of that bastard Shoda.
Sorry.
Aoi?
I came to measure my body...
Huh? But if we did...
But...
You have to speak clearly.
Kanzaki.
Yes..The track uniform I have is too small.
Becuase my chest has grown a lot.
Aoi, again with Shoda...
And besides, it shows my panties.
So, if you want to take your measurements...
I understand. Then...
I would like Shoda-sensei to do it.
Wow, how big you are, Kanzaki.
65 waist and 87 chest. Right?
It's a Cup E.
54 waist and 86 hips.
86? You are well developed.
Puberty can give you health problems, you know?
You have aches down here, right?
You're wrong, I don't have any aches there.
If you really don't have any pain...
So, no problem, this shouldn't bother you at all.
Yes I have, recently.
A lot?
Yes, a lot...
So it must feell really bad?
Very bad.
Since yesterday, I got sick a lot...
Well, then, I will now administer a urine test.
Make an effort...
Do not let it get on that skirt.
Nothing, that's enough.
If this continues I will tell the education committee.
If you plan to do that...
Many would find out, what you are wearing.
Stop...
No, degenerate.
This degenerate could get you penis, Kanzaki.
What's, what's going on?
Aoi.
Your nipples have become hard just at the mention of my perfect penis.
Hey, hey, we have not yet begun.
Well, well... It is Kurusu.
Akihito...
You know you cannot go into the bathroom of the girls, right?
S-Sh-Shoda!
Akihito, no!
N-No you cannot hit the sensei.
Here and now I am giving extra classes, so do not bother us.
Aoi, what happened to you?
Aoi!
Forigve me, for before...
I really wanted to talk to you...
But I didn't know how to tell you.
Tell him you are in your room, with another man.
I have something important to say...
I'll be waiting in my room.
Now we will start with the panties.
I must hurry, Aoi is waiting.
How do my fingers feel? Kanzaki.
Yes, they feel very good.
It hurts, my breasts hurt.
What fun.
Damn, you have such a hot body.
I-I am a bad girl.
By god, you just have to see how wet you are.
You have the vagina of a student, hungry for penis.
It is sucking in my fingers.
Let me do something for you, let me make your penis grow.
It looks delicious.
It just moved...
Your penis, just moved.
How lovely...
This girl is very good, after all.
I'm going to make it move more.
It's delicious.
Penis...Penis...I want your penis.
Compared with that of Kurusu, which would you choose?
Please tell me or I will not let you suck my cock more.
Sensei.
What did you say?
Clearly, yours, sensei.
Your penis is bigger than Akihito's.
There is no comparison.
What are you saying, Aoi?
If Kurusu heard you he would feel bad.
Well...I do like Akihito.
But now, I like your penis.
It's so hot ... I want to keep sucking.
No, no ... I want to suck your penis more.
Let me suck more, come on, let me suck...
Idiot, do not move.
Aoi, though a virgin, all you want is my penis.
I knew that virgins are the best.
Moreover, they are so tight.
You are now considered a real woman.
It hurts, it hurts!
Soon it will not hurt.
Do not move.
It is time to go deeper.
How do you feel now?
Pull it out!
Akihito!
Aoi!
Akihito...
SHODA!
Aoi, you okay?
No...
Akihito...
Sensei is taking me ... my first time ... Do something ...
At least, let him see, this great scene.
No, do not move so fast.
I will cum!
Incredible, it is large and hot ...
How are you? Surely with Kurusu, you would not be enjoying it this much.
I'm going to die...I'm going to die!
Stop...
Let me die.
The penis is growing...
It has run into me ... It's all inside...
I do not want ... I do not want your baby.
What the hell are you saying?
I cannot stop cumming inside you.
Akihito...Akihito!
There is so much semen...
The penis of the sensei, is filling everything in me.
Akihito...Akihito!
Aoi...
Sorry.
All credit for subbing the original Japanese version into Spanish goes to the Forst Yume Fansub group. (Hard Part)
All that I did was convert it into English, me being Broodwarjc. (Not-as-Hard Part)