Ah, it's so cold!
I'm so close to finally graduating from college,
and then my roommate kicks me
out because he's got a girlfriend?
What a jerk.
So I guess I'm homeless now.
I wish I was the one with a live-in girlfriend.
Hey...
À-À goddess?
Are you Shinba Kosuke-san?
Uh, yeah.
That's good.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Aoi Sakura.
I've come to take you home.
Huh? Take me home?
Yes.
She must really be a goddess.
No, an angel?
Tsuma Shibori
Part 1: Strange Living Situation
This place will be your home
from now on, Kosuke-san.
It's a very lovely house.
Come. Make yourself at home.
Uh, okay!
I-I'm coming in!
Let me introduce my sister, Kototsuki Madoka.
Come on, Madoka. Say hello.
Hello.
Sorry. She can be rude sometimes.
No problem!
Kosuke-san, let's all have dinner together!
You must be hungry.
I've already prepared everything,
so I'll bring it out right away.
Thank you!
I'm in heaven!
Oh, my God.
I'm just starting to realize...
What kind of situation I'm in right now.
Um!
Yes?
Uh, nothing.
I'm sorry to bother you while you're making  dinner,
but I'm kind of confused right now.
Why did you bring me here?
You're right. I'd better explain.
Actually, I brought you here
to help find you a wife.
Oh, a wife...
I mean a wife? But why?
And who?
My little sister, Madoka.
You see, your father and our
father are best friends.
They were worried because
you didn't have a girlfriend,
so they asked me to fix you up with Madoka.
Stupid Dad. Sticking his nose in my business!
And to help the two of you get better acquainted...
They’ve arranged for you to live
here with us for a while.
L-Live here?
Damn, what a strange and sudden turn of events.
Stupid Dad. Why the hell does
he always try to run my life!?
But still...
Your father wants this for you, Kosuke-san.
I'll do my best to be a good hostess,
so won't you stay here with us?
She's being so nice to me.
Well, there are no bossy parents around!
You want me to live with this creepy-looking loser?
For the record, I'm not happy!
Living with her might be tough, though.
Wait a minute. Her name is
Kototsuki Madoka, right?
Her surname is different from Sakura-san's.
Then, does that mean Sakura-san is married?
A hot young wife, huh.
Kosuke-san?
Uh, yes!
Excuse me; I've come to wash your back.
Whoa, shit!
Uh, I mean...
Don't be so self-conscious.
Sakura-san...
Come! Have a seat on the stool.
Kosuke-san, I'm sorry about earlier.
What?
About Madoka's behavior.
Right...
She's a little confused right now.
Well, I don't blame her.
But still...
Will you also be living here, Aoi-san?
Yes! I will live here with you two.
Oh, really?
Yes.
After all, I have to observe you.
Observe?
Perhaps I chose the wrong word.
I meant that I want to see if you're
a good match for my sister.
Her breasts are...
If there's anything I can do, just ask me.
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
Now, let me wash your chest.
Uh, no! You shouldn't...
Come, come, don't be shy.
A-Aoi-san...
Sorry about that.
Don't apologize. I understand.
It's a natural reaction for a man.
Uh, yeah.
Sakura-san, what are you...!?
Kosuke-san, if you do marry Madoka,
I want you to be experienced.
So please let me teach you a few things.
Come. Please touch them.
W-Well, I...
Just like this. Slowly and gently.
Yes. Like you're drawing a circle.
That's right.
Please grip them a little more
firmly with your fingertips.
Pinch my nipples a bit.
You're doing well!
I'd better put more energy into my own fingers.
Come, please stand up.
Whoops, sorry.
What are you...!?
If you marry Madoka,
you'll need to do things like this to her every day.
Don't worry. I'll be gentle.
Îêày!
It's so big.
Holy shit!
Does it feel good?
V-Very good!
I'm glad!
A lot came out.
I'm sorry.
Well, we'd better clean it off.
That's enough.
You're young, so it won’t take long.
You don't have to go this far.
But I do.
You might someday be my brother-in-law.
I want you to be good to my precious sister.
We must take care of our family members.
Look, you're already there. Amazing!
A-Aoi-san!
You're still young. You have so much... so much!
I'm gonna cum.
I'll swallow it! I want to. Come on!
Kosuke-san!
Aoi!
Was that enough for you?
Yes. It was wonderful.
From now on, I'll take care
of you like this every day.
Good morning, Kosuke-san.
G-Good morning.
How are you? Do you feel at home here?
Uh, well, yes!
Good morning!
Yeah, hi.
Madoka...
I'm going out for a bit.
Say, Madoka, don't you want to stay
in Kosuke-san s room from now on?
I think that would be best.
Sakura-san?
What the hell, man? That will never happen.
Oh.
I don't blame her, Sakura-san!
It's a bit sudden for me, too.
Oh, I see. Living together with
your "future wife", huh?
That's a very strange turn of events.
I'm sure Madoka-san hates it.
Are you sure?
It's one thing to be forced to marry.
It's quite another to have to live together.
I wonder what I should do.
Here you go. The usual.
Thank you.
But a woman's heart is a complicated matter.
I'm not so sure.
By the way, Ko-kun,
have you had any experience with women?
"Experience"?  You mean, like...
Yes or no?
Yes or no...
I thought so.
Should I, the lovely Himeka-san, take
it upon myself to turn you into a man
who understands women a little better?
On Break
Himeka-san...
I've watched over you since we were kids.
Let me turn you into a man.
Don't worry. I'll show you how it's done.
Êo-êun, is it working?
Ko-kun...
Does it feel good?
Yeah...
but I'm kinda embarrassed.
Ko-kun, you're so cute!
Hey, Êo-êun, take off my clothes for me.
Don't stress about it. Take your time.
Okay, now touch them.
They're so soft.
You can press harder if you want.
Like this?
Yes. You're doing well.
Êî-êun, lick them now.
Yes, suck on them!
Twirl your tongue around my nipples.
Ko-kun, lick me here.
Himeka-san...
That's great!
Yes! You're amazing!
Now use the underside of
your tongue. And swirl...
Yes, Êî-êun!
Harder! Keep going. Keep sucking!
This feels great! Don't let go!
Êî-êun! I love you.
What?
That's strange.
I thought so.
But why are they closed at this
time of day? That's weird.
Oh, no! I wonder if Himeka-san is in trouble!?
I'd better go in the back way to check on her!
Tsuma Shibori.
What?
Don't get frustrated, Ko-kun.
Look. You put it in here.
See? It's in now.
Well? How does it feel to be inside
a woman for the first time?
It feels so good I might cum any second!
But you mustn't.
A man needs to hang in there
until his woman also cums.
Your penis is all the way inside of me now.
Himeka-san...
You can start moving now.
Look, I'll move for you first.
Wow!
Move more! Push your penis into me!
You're so soft and warm!
Harder! Faster! Put it in farther!
Amazing!
Yes! You're wonderful!
Himeka-san... I...
Ah, I'm sorry!
I'm gonna cum!
Êî-êun, don't stop.
I can't.
It's coming out!
But it's your first time!
I want... I want you to cum inside of me!
And here I was worried about her safety.
To think she'd go with Ko-chan!
Did I just hear something?
Êî-êun!
Even though you're finished, it's still big and hard.
Himeka-san. Not again.
I want more. I want more!
Hey, Êî-êun, wanna go again?
This time from behind.
Hurry up!
Himeka-san... I-I...
Wow! Put it in all the way!
Crab my butt hard. Put it in deep!
Himeka-san... Wow, this feels great!
It feels great for me, too!
You’re the first man who's done this to me.
I'm so happy!
Himeka-san!
Oh, vegetables.
I wonder if Saburo-san left already.
Wait.
Does that mean he was here while Himeka-san
and I were having sex?
That noise!
I hope not. Did Saburo-san see us?
Oh, crap. I bet he did.
That sucks.
That's...
Sakura-san.
Why is she out at this time of day?
Why am I following her? I'm not a stalker.
Àñê! That's Saburo-san's shop!
Do they know each other!?
They look really friendly.
Well, Sakura-san, you look lovely as usual.
You're just like a goddess!
Oh, Saburo-san, you sweetie.
Every man is head-over-heels for you!
My!
This conversation is taking too long.
Is he telling Sakura-san about
what I did with Himeka-san!
I need to know!
Sakura-san!
Oh, my, Kosuke-san. What a nice surprise.
I saw you at the grocery.
I thought I'd make a stew tonight.
Let me take that for you.
Oh, I could have handled that myself.
Um, what were you two talking about?
You were talking for a really long time.
Oh, nothing much. Saburo-san just loves talking.
We lost track of time.
Did he talk about me, by any chance?
Did he talk about you?
No, not at all. Did something happen?
Uh, no, not really.
Thank God.
Apparently she doesn't know about Himeka-san.
Himeka-san, Madoka-san, Sakura-san...
Kosuke-san, are you still awake?
Y-Yes!
Are you comfortable in this room?
Yes, very.
I never dreamed I'd be in such a big room.
Really?
To me, it's just a big, lonely house.
Â-But if you marry Madoka, it won't
be so lonely here anymore.
Sakura-san...
I want to touch you.
Kosuke-san.
Sakura-san!
Kosuke-san!
Good...
That feels great.
Down here, too.
She's wet.
Let me stay with you tonight.
Sakura-san...
Kosuke-san...
Good! I can feel your tongue!
Twirl it around gently and suck on it.
Kosuke-san, your mouth is coming loose.
Sorry! It just feels too good!
Me too. This feels so good, I can't concentrate.
Got it.
Very good, Kosuke-san!
That feels wonderful!
Dammit, I can't sleep.
Please stay still. don't move.
Sakura-san!
It's in!
Kosuke-san, you're so hard.
You're amazing, Sakura-san!
You're amazing!
Your penis is so big. It's wonderful!
What's going on?
Onee-chan...
With him?
Sakura-san, you're being really dirty right now.
Oh, Kosuke-san, don't be so rude.
Please, push it in deeper!
Kosuke-san...
Yes! Yes!
Your penis... deeper... deeper!
No way. No!
I'm about to cum.
Go ahead. Please cum!
What the fuck is going on?
I can't believe it.
To think she's doing things like that
behind my back in our own home!
Onee-chan, you're such a whore.
Why am I so freaked out?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I doing this?
No, I'm not like this.
I can't stop!
It feels too good!
Madoka? May I come in?
Y-Yeah!
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Madoka... I see.
You saw us.
I, uh, I didn't mean to see you.
I just happened to be walking by.
Oh.
Why did you do that anyway?
Sneaking around behind my back. You dirty slut!
B-But I wasn't ..
Bringing him here as my future husband,
was that your plan all along?
That's not...
I noticed when I first laid eyes on him.
He looks like your husband.
But he's dead. You can't bring
him back by using Kosuke!
You misunderstand.
I'm not trying to replace my husband.
I'm not using him to console myself.
Then why?
He's a very good future husband for you, Madoka.
But he's still young.
I wanted to help him release all his desires,
so he'd be faithful to you in the future.
What the hell? That's fucked up!
But that's just how big a young man's lust is.
Before I can trust him with you,
I have to suck all the lust out of him.
But that's supposed to be my job...
Not my sister's job!
If it needs to be done for the sake
of our future marriage, I'll do it.
But you still don't know him very well.
Of course I don't know him.
Because you won't let me do
what I'm supposed to do.
Madoka...
Anyway, I'll take care of him from now on.
You just butt out.
Î-Okay.
Then I understand.
I'll leave him to you.