First you lick slowly around the pussy.
Okay.
Yeah, that's it, lick
up and down on the split.
That feels good, Tsuzaki.
You're doing great.
Your pussy is pink and very beautiful.
How does it feel, Kanae?
It feels so good.
You should lick especially there.
But it's the most sensitive
part, so you must be very gentle.
Yes.
Kanae.
Tsuzaki...
Now touch deep inside my pussy.
Wow, you're so wet and shiny inside.
You silly.
You're embarrassing me.
I'm sorry.
It's so tight inside, it's like your
pussy is swallowing up my finger.
That's it, keep going.
Oh yes...
It feels so good.
Give it to me harder.
You can come now, Kanae.
Oh, no...
Yes!
Really?
You're teaching bookkeeping to Chiho?
Yes, it's nice that we can be alone...
...but since we're supposed to be
studying, it's hard to make a move.
No need to rush.
It must be hard for you
to see me during the day...
...and teach Chiho at night.
Don't worry about me.
I'm being given such valuable
lessons, I shouldn't be complaining.
I'm going to the convenience
store downstairs now.
I also have things to
buy, so let me come along.
Wife Eater
Produced by SOFGARE, Pinkpineapple
Chance Two: Wanna
Fall in Love With Me?
Maybe I should buy
tonight's dinner, too.
Oh, you eat
instant food?
I'm a single male.
I haven't eaten home cooking since
you cooked dinner for me the other day.
Your cooking was really great.
C-Chiho?
You two are shopping together?
No, it's not what you think.
Mommy!
Konomi!
Are you shopping with Daddy?
You look like a real couple.
Can I go through?
Excuse me.
That wasn't good.
What should we do?
Mommy, did I do something wrong?
Oh no.
You didn't do anything wrong.
What if she's still mad at me...
Yes.
Chiho, it's me, Tsuzaki.
Come in.
Oh good, I was worried that she
would never want to see me again.
Excuse me.
Something smells nice.
Good evening, Tsuzaki.
Are you going to have dinner now?
Then I'll come back later.
Well, if you don't mind, why
don't you join me for dinner?
You mean...
You mean I can eat your cooking?
Yes.
Of course, I'll join you.
This is the best day of my life.
It was a great meal.
Thank you.
I'm so glad that I
could eat your cooking.
But, why all of sudden?
Well...
There's no special reason.
I heard you said you always
eat instant food.
Sorry for making you worry about me.
No, no problem at all.
My cooking is just slightly better
than the food at the convenience store.
Compared to Kanae's food, mine isn't...
C-Chiho.
Lately, you're getting along with Kanae.
She cooks for you, and
you visit her place a lot.
Wait a second!
You've got it all wrong.
I just visited her to get some advice.
She's a married woman, so she
knows a lot about relationships.
Do you have a love problem?
Y-Yeah, yes...
Then, you can talk to me about it.
I was married, too.
How could I ask for advice
from the woman I have crush on?
Well, um...
Tsuzaki.
You must've noticed my feelings for you.
I like you, Chiho.
But Ryuhei is the only man I love.
I understand that you won't
forget about your husband.
But you don't have to limit
who you love, or who loves you.
But...
I love you.
Chiho.
Tsuzaki.
I love you.
Tsuzaki...
No...
Chiho.
Tsuzaki...
Tsuzaki.
You're getting wet.
You feel good?
No, don't say that.
Kanae said I shouldn't
mention things like that, too.
I'm sorry, but before your underwear
gets dirty, let me take them off.
I'm embarrassed.
Ah, no...
You're making me feel so good.
Chiho.
Are you ready?
Wait!
Do you have a...
Um, we should use a condom.
Yeah, you're right...
But I didn't bring any.
I don't have one either,
since my husband passed away...
Well, I've got to use
a condom, haven't I?
Of course!
Because we're not married yet, you know.
M-Married?
You and me?
Oh no, I didn't mean it like that...
I suppose I can do it with my mouth...
What?
It's hard for men when
they can't come, isn't it?
C-Chiho?
I'm not used to doing this,
so you must bear with me.
How's this?
This is great.
Keep doing it.
Yes.
Chiho, I'm so close.
If you keep doing it, I...
So sorry, Chiho.
That's okay.
It's been a while, I'm out of practice.
Chiho.
Master, give me some condoms!
No, I won't give them to you,
they're my merchandise.
I mean sell some to me!
Oh, yes.
Right now, a box of condoms
comes with free gifts.
Give me that!
Thank you for shopping.
A potion that makes people horny?
Some kind of love potion, eh?
This can't be real.
Hey!
No one is allowed on the roof top!
W-What the hell?
What's this? What is happening?
I feel so hot.
M-Mikoto?
I'm...
Tsuzaki, I'm feeling strange.
I can't...
I can't stand it any more!
Oh, Tsuzaki, you got so hard.
Mikoto, we shouldn't be doing this.
Who cares?
No one is watching us.
Here I'm supposed to watch out for...
...evil space monsters
approaching earth.
But I can't keep my eyes
off of these horny creatures!
Finish your masturbation quickly,
or the earth could be destroyed.
Finally, you went that far with Chiho.
Then, you have to
practice real sex today.
A practice for real sex?
That's right.
Then, may I ask a favor of you?
What?
Would you wear this dress?
Wow.
How did you get this?
It's free gift No. 2.
Free gift No. 2?
Never mind.
The landlord gave this to me but
I think it's too big for Chiho, so...
Hey.
In this kind of situation,
you're supposed to say...
..."I thought you'd
look good in this dress."
Sorry.
It's all right.
Let me wear this dress for you.
Thank you so much.
How do I look?
It looks great on you.
I'm not wearing any underwear.
Wow.
I'm on my safe day, so
we don't need this, but...
do you want to practice
putting on a condom?
No, I don't want to wear a condom.
It's good that you're honest.
Go ahead.
Well then...
Your pussy is tight as usual.
How's my dick?
It feels great.
But don't just stroke hard, you need
to use different speed and strength.
Like this?
That's it...
Feels so good...
Kanae!
So good.
I'm going to come!
I'm going to come, too...
Your pussy is so tight.
It's in so deep!
Kanae, I can't hold it any longer!
Let's come together.
I want to come together with you.
Yes.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming!
I can't hold it...
Just a little more!
You could have come inside.
But there's always a
slight chance of pregnancy.
Besides, you're a married woman,
I can't take responsibility.
You're right...
I'm not that good in
bed, but I'll do my best.
Me, neither.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just a second...
Tsuzaki?
Leave it on your finger, Chiho.
But...
I appreciate your concern.
But please don't force yourself
to forget about your husband.
Because you're the kind of person who
can't easily forget your loved one.
Tsuzaki.
But if you don't mind...
Would you call me by my first name?
Satoru.
Chiho.
He's so good at this...
You must know a lot of women.
No, that's not true.
I'm just trying my best
to make you feel good.
Thank you.
You're so wet.
I'm embarrassed.
It means you feel good, I'm glad.
You got so hard.
Satoru, you're ready.
Chiho, you're ready, too.
Oh, no.
Well...
Finally we can become one.
I love you, Chiho.
I love you, too. Satoru.
I'm sorry, Ryuhei.
But I'm sure you'll understand.
Ready?
Are you okay?
I'm fine...
It's been a while, so it's really tight...
or perhaps you are just so big.
Chiho.
Chiho!
Satoru!
This is so good.
I can't think of anything else.
This feels so good.
Your pussy is so hot and tight.
I don't think I can hold it any longer.
I'm coming soon, too...
Satoru, you're making me feel so good.
Chiho.
Let's come together.
Yes, Satoru.
Who could it be, this
early in the morning?
Good morning!
I cooked too much again...
Oh?
Tsuzaki?
Kanae.
I see.
Congratulations!
But whenever you need an extra
lesson, I can give you one anytime.
Satoru.
What's going on here?
Well, it's just a...
Excuse me.
It was just a celebratory
gift for you two.
Kanae?