Kosuke, I don't want you to fool
around with my sister anymore.
M-Madoka-san?
From now on, let me take care of you.
Darling, I'm sorry.
I think I love Kosuke-san.
Tsuma Shibori
Part 2: Sakura and Madoka. Which One will he choose...
Kosuke...
I-I'ts my first time, so be gentle!
Don't worry. I'll lead.
No! I'm too embarrassed!
Don't look at me like that!
You shouldn't be embarrassed.
Your breasts are beautiful.
Kosuke, you idiot.
No, don't!
Look, Madoka-san, you're already this wet!
No! Don't say that.
You're making fun of me!
No.
Your fingers are inside of me.
So much is spilling out already.
I'll lick it up for you.
Stop talking about it. You're embarrassing me!
Don't!
Oh, no. What's happening?
I had no idea it could feel this good.
It's freaking me out.
Madoka-san, don't be scared.
I'll lead you. Just relax.
Kosuke, be gentle.
Madoka-san, relax.
You're tensing up.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm fine.
You can go on.
Okay.
It's tight!
Madoka-san, don't push yourself too hard.
If it hurts, I'll stop.
No, I'm fine. Keep going.
Madoka-san.
So this is Kosuke's penis.
It's going inside of me.
Look, Madoka-san, it's all the way in now.
Whoa, you're inside of me!
Is it okay if I move?
Yes, it's okay. Do whatever you want.
But don't stop.
Please, whatever happens, don't
stop until you're finished.
Madoka -san...
Kosuke...
He's moving.
Kosuke's penis is moving inside of me.
It hurts,
but my body is hot all over.
And I'm so happy.
I had no idea sex was this wonderful!
Kosuke! You're amazing! I had no idea!
Madoka-san...
I'm almost there!
I'm fine! Do whatever you want!
Here I come!
My insides are hot all over.
It just feels...
so amazing.
So this is sex!
Here you go.
I made your breakfast this morning.
Kosuke, eat up!
Oh, thanks!
H-How is it?
It's good.
Why did you pause?
N-No reason, really!
Aw, you pig.
Kosuke, you've got rice on your face.
Ick, you're like a baby!
I-I'll be out all day today.
Madoka, take care of Kosuke-san, okay?
S-Sakura-san.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of Kosuke-san for you.
Oh, good! I know you will.
Well, goodbye.
Have fun.
You're a woman now, Madoka.
Wow! This is awesome!
Kosuke, you're extra hard today!
Madoka-san, you're extra rough today!
Kosuke-san...
Fuck me harder, Kosuke!
Stop thinking like this.
Kosuke-sans Madoka's future husband.
This is what's best. It's everything I'd hoped for.
Then why...
why does my body lust after Kosuke-san so much?
I mustn't...
I mustn't think about such things if I want
Madoka and Kosuke-san to be happy.
Even though we just finished, it's still throbbing.
If you're still in the mood, I want more.
This time from behind.
W-Wow! It's all the way inside! I can feel it!
My insides are resisting.
My insides don't want your dick in there!
I won't let you push me out, Madoka-san!
Fuck me harder.
You feel so good I'm going crazy!
I won't let Onee-chan touch him ever again.
Say, Kosuke...
It's about my sister.
About Sakura-san?
She's been leaving a lot during the day lately.
Do you know where she's going?
I wondered about that myself.
I don't know where she's going.
To the graveyard.
To the...   graveyard?
She still hasn't gotten over her dead husband.
I had no idea.
And actually,
you look just like him.
Kosuke...
Darling...
My sister was just using you because
you remind her of him!
Shit, she acted all innocent.
She said she was trying to help me out,
when she was just using you for sex.
I don't think she'd do that!
But...
So you need to promise me you
won't have sex with her again.
Î-Okay.
Good.
So that's what was going on.
Sakurà-san...
This is for the best.
I don't want to let her have you.
Oh, Sakura-san, you're back.
Hello.
Are you going out, Kosuke-san?
Yes. For a bit.
Have fun.
Thanks.
I see.
If Sakura-san goes to the graveyard a lot,
I wonder if that's where she was just now.
Sakura-san!
Say, where did you go today?
Oh, just a little shopping.
But you always seem to leave
at the same time every day.
I was wondering if you were going
somewhere in particular.
W-Well, I...
Can I come with you next time?
Kosuke-san, it's not your concern.
It has nothing to do with you!
Don't worry about me. You
should focus on Madoka.
Sakura-san!
I can't have feelings for Kosuke-san anymore.
It's best this way.
This way...
Damn. What's with Sakura-san?
She's usually so polite.
She used to be real sweet to me.
But suddenly she's become so cold.
I guess she was using me to
forget her husband after all.
Hello, Yukie-san.
Yeah.
And what about you? Are you going to your shop?
Yes. I have to set up and give orders.
Just because I'm a boss doesn't
mean my job is easy.
Sounds tough.
I have an idea, Shinba-san.
Why don't you stop by for a visit?
Because we're neighbors, I'll
give you a little discount.
Come, Shinba-san. Have another.
Well, if you insist.
My pleasure.
Gulp it down.
Thanks.
Bottoms up!
Two beers on table 5!
Four shrimps with rice!
Coming!
Sorry. The place has gotten a bit crowded.
I'm leaving for now, but please
stay as long as you want.
Thanks. I really don't deserve this. Thanks again.
Sakura-san?
Shit.
She was only nice to me because
I look like her husband.
I'm just a replacement for her husband.
Shit.
Shinba-san...
Shinba-san! Are you all right?
Shinba-san?
Yukie-san?
Aw, damn. I drank too much!
Sorry. I must've fallen asleep.
No problem.
You seemed to be sleeping very peacefully.
I'm sorry. I hope I didn't mess
things up for your business.
Never mind.
It's just the two of us here now.
Don't worry about a thing.
Oh yeah, the bill...
Oops. I actually don't have
much money on me today.
Oh, don't bother. You're my guest here today.
You don't need to pay.
I can't let you do that!
Can I pay you back some other way?
That's a good idea.
How about you pay me back this way.
Yukie-san?
Will you be my partner tonight?
Tsuma Shibori.
Yukie-san...
Shinba-san, you can start off by licking me.
Okay.
Oh dear. It's been so long for me.
I'm already soaking...
You're really pretty, Yukie-san.
And you're really good.
This is what I've been looking for!
I haven't seen a dick in so long!
Wow!
You taste great.
Yukie-san!
You're so hard!
And you're bigger than my husband, too!
You can't beat youth.
My husband doesn't touch me anymore.
I want him to make love to me.
But it's as if he isn't attracted to me.
My husband prefers someone like
Sakura-san from next door.
He's crazy. You're a very beautiful
woman, Yukie-san.
Shinba-san...
If only my husband were as sweet as you.
Yukie-san...
Wait.
That belongs to my husband.
My ass... Put it in my ass.
You mean anal?
Is this your first time, Shinba-san?
Yeah.
It will be tight at first.
But if you wet it with my juices,
it should be all right.
Okay.
Shinba-san, I'm ready now.
It's tight!
You're so big!
Your dick is so huge!
It's going in. It's going in my anus!
It's tight, but it feels amazing!
Wow!
I've never felt a dick this way before!
I really want you in my pussy.
But...
But my pussy belongs to my husband...
so you can’t go in there!
I'm almost there.
Yukie-san, I'm about to explode!
Keep going. You can cum inside of me.
Go ahead.
Do it harder!
I'm cumming!
I'm sorry. I couldn't control myself.
Not at all.
Thank you, Shinba-san.
But I have to apologize.
I was the one who seduced you,
and I couldn't keep going to the end.
Don't worry about it.
But please understand.
Even if he won't touch me anymore,
I still love my husband.
I really believe that a woman's vagina should
be reserved for the man she loves.
There fore...
I don't mind, Yukie-san.
I understand.
It should be reserved for someone you love, huh.
Kosuke-san!
I Miss Kosuke-san's body.
But his body is the only part of him I miss.
Kosuke-san has sex with Madoka every night now.
He is her future husband.
That's only natural.
But I...
I really do love Kosuke-san.
I mustn't...
But I do!
Kosuke-san...
I love you!
Sex binds two people who truly love each other.
But who do I truly love?
Good morning, Kosuke-san.
S-Sakura-san.
You're up realy early to today.
Good morning.
I couldn't sleep.
Me neither.
I'll make us some tea.
Kosuke-san, I have a confession.
I miss your touch. I'm lonely.
I thought I was teaching you for my sister's sake,
but I began to want you for myself.
Sakura-san?
I love you, Kosuke-san.
I fell in love with you.
I want you to make love to me like you used to.
Sakura-san.
Kosuke-san.
That's right.
Sakura-san is the one I really love.
She wasn't just using me to
forget the one she loved.
She took a risk and said that she loved me.
I love you too, Sakura-san.
I love you more than anyone else.
Good! I've brought a bunch of
lovely vegetables by today!
I hope Sakura-san likes them.
Of course, not even the freshest of
vegetables can compare to her beauty.
Whoa, cheesy!
Hey, S-Sakura-san!
My vagina is so hot!
You're making my vagina burn, Kosuke-san.
This is the flavor I want.
Sakura-san, you taste best of all!
Suck on me harder! Harder! More!
Kosuke-san, mess me up. Deeper... and harder!
My love is over.
Come in from behind, please, Kosuke-san.
You're in. You're in me, Kosuke-san!
Go all the way inside, Kosuke-san!
All the way inside!
Sakura-san, your insides are so warm!
They're so tight!
I'm throbbing like crazy!
Your hard penis is dancing inside of me!
This feels so good!
Kosuke-san, I'm so happy.
There's nothing more I can teach you.
I'm about to cum!
Then cum. Please!
This is how I feel about you!
I want... I want your sperm! I want it inside of me!
I'm cumming!
Kosuke-san!
What's your game, bitch?
Kosuke is mine.
I know that. But I can’t deny my true feelings.
You're fucked in the head!
I thought you wanted me and
Kosuke to be together.
That's...
You're just using him to replace your husband.
You don't really love him!
Yes, I do!
At first, I thought it was just because
he looked like my husband.
But I was wrong.
I wasn't attracted to Kosuke-san because
he looked like my husband.
I was attracted to Kosuke-san, the man himself.
This has nothing to do with my dead husband.
I really do love Kosuke-san.
I want to get over my past and start fresh with him.
Sakura-san.
But you can’t... you can't mean...
Madoka...
If what you're saying is true, then can
you say that to your husband’s grave?
Can you say it?
Yes, I can.
My heart can't lie.
Onee-chan...
Darling, I came here to return this to you.
I, Sakura, am saying goodbye to my former life,
and I'll make a happy new one with Kosuke-san.
I, Shinba Kosuke, swear to make your wife happy.
Kosuke-san.
Onee-chan... Kosuke..
M-Madoka...
Well then. I guess it’s time to go home.
Go home?
You and Kosuke being so serious in front of your
husband's grave makes things pretty clear.
I'm over it.
I guess we'd better tell our parents
I'm not getting married after all.
Madoka...
Hey, Onee-chan! Promise me you'll
be happy this time for good!
Thank you, Madoka.
Kosuke...
You promised to take care of my sister, right?
Yes.
If you break your promise, I'll kick your ass, okay?
Don't worry I'll make her happy.
This is the place where we first met.
I was so cold in the snow that when I saw you,
I thought you were a goddess.
Aw, Kosuke-san, you're so sweet.
But you really were a goddess.
A goddess who came down from
heaven to save my life.
Kosuke-san, will you make love
to me out here in the snow?
Right here, right now, I want to destroy
all the sadness I've felt until now.
I'll cut my ties with the past and
begin a new future with you.
I'll make love to you here, Sakura.
Kosuke-san! Harder! Harder!
I want you to destroy all the sad things in my past!
Sakura, I promise I'll destroy all of them for you!
And I'll help you start over again!
Kosuke-san!
Kosuke-san, put all of you
into me. I want all of you!
Let me come inside you... all the way inside!
So we can build a new future together!
Leave yours it inside of me.
Leave behind so much of yourself
that it's always with me!
Kosuke!
Sakura, the ceremony is about to start.
We still have time.
Let's not stop until we absolutely have to.
But everyone must be waiting.
But I want to be with you.
Even just for a second more,
I want to be connected to you.
Onee-chan, the ceremony's
starting. Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready!
You're not lying, are you?
I'll be there right away!
I'm almost there!
Let's cum together!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Shall we go?
Yes, darling.