Here we go.
Oops.
Hello there!
I'm Alice, the mistress of the house.
What? You want to introduce yourself?
He's Yukichi.
This episode is about a love
story with married women.
Speaking of married women...
Here we go!
How do I look?
Model: Natsume Kawamura
What? It痴 no good because there
isn't a bird printed on her apron?
That痴 a good point.
See you next time.
Cherry Blossoms...
It's been a year...
This is...
When Rokuro was cleaning his
closet, he found that photo.
A picture of a sad widow who
remembers her late husband...
This is gonna be a great picture.
What do you mean by that, Mikoto?
I'm not gonna give you the picture,
I'm living on these pictures.
What?
I mean we shouldn't depend on Rokuro.
If Rokuro works so hard
at his part-time job...
...he may fail the university
entrance exam for seventh time.
And people will call him...
..."Shichiro" Momota.
Wait, if he had seven in his
name, it would be lucky for him...
Funny.
I got a picture of the
precious smile of a cry baby!
You look better when you're smiling.
Then, see you later!
Ouch!
Brother Rokuro!
Mikoto!
Have you been causing trouble again?
No, that's not true!
Right, Chiho?
Rokuro...
Thank you for the picture.
I'll cherish this picture.
No problem at all.
I hope I wasn't being insensitive...
Don't be so cocky!
Well...
Daddy, come quickly.
Can I tell one more thing?
You're still young.
Don't you need a guy
you can depend on?
For example...
I'm much stronger than I look.
I only love Ryuhei.
That's enough for me.
Chiho.
Ryuhei.
I'm fine.
I can manage by myself.
Sister!
Know anyone in this apartment building?
Oops, sorry.
You have big breasts...
just like Mom!
Also...
You smell good like my mom.
Do you live in this apartment building?
I'm Konomi Momota.
Daddy!
You're so late!
You're too fast.
I'm a fast runner.
Excuse me.
You have a grown up child.
Oh no.
How can I explain?
She's more like my sister.
Daddy is younger than my brother.
A-Anyway, do you have anything to
do with this apartment building?
This is a nice apartment building.
Well, that's true. The rents are
cheap, and it's close to the station.
It's not a bad deal.
Appearing everywhere.
But many residents are peculiar.
Owner of the sex toy shop.
On top of that, the landlord is a pervert...
I mean he's certainly
an eccentric person.
I can't recommend this place to you.
It sounds fun, doesn't it?
I'll see you around.
So your name is...
I'm Satoru Tsuzaki.
I'm Kanae, Kanae Hasuma.
Oh no.
Are you excited by the sight of
the underwear of a middle aged woman?
You're so cute, Mr. Tsuzaki.
Wife Eater
Directed by Hiromi Yokoyama
Produced by Pink Pineapple
Chance One: Wanna Have Sex With Me?
Chiho...
Crying won't bring your husband back.
Ryuhei...
I've decided not to cry anymore.
I'm sorry, Ryuhei, I'm going
to be stronger from tomorrow on.
But tonight, let me see you in my dream.
Ryuhei?
If you cry like that all the time...
it's going to be hard for
your husband to rest in peace.
You're hurting yourself by crying.
Well, he is...
Um...
No, never mind.
Well, I'll do my best today.
I haven't seen you for
a long time, Ms. Mikoto.
Don't be so polite.
You're older than me, you
can be more friendly with me.
Well then,
cutie Mikoto...
You idiot! That's way too friendly.
What are you thinking calling
a grown up woman "cutie"?
You...
Anyhow, take a look at these.
C-Chiho!
You, bonehead!
You gotta give me money!
These are high quality
and very expensive.
Well, I changed my mind.
Bye now!
Hi, Chiho.
Oh, Hello.
Well...
Nothing...
Mikoto, play with me outside!
I'm very busy thinking
about making money.
Fine then, I'll play with Daddy.
No, wait, he is also busy right now.
I have to prepare lunch, so excuse me.
Are you going to take
a bookkeeping exam?
Well, I need at least a bookkeeping
certificate in order to get a job.
I have a bookkeeping certificate.
Really?
But it's nothing special.
You're smart, Tsuzaki.
Well, I don't even
have a driver's license.
I'm very slow and...
Oh, what am I saying?
Well...
I-If you don't mind, I can help
you out with your studying...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm moving in here today,
my name is Kanae Hasuma.
Oh?
I met you yesterday, you are...
...Tsuzaki.
Um...
I'm Kanae,
Ka-na-e.
Don't you remember?
Of course, I do.
Hello, I'm Chiho Mizumori.
Stupid.
Wait...
Why am I angry at him?
Hi!
Natsume?
Good morning!
What's the matter with you?
You're supposed to dream at night.
No, Stephanie, don't be rude.
Nah, she won't mind it.
Right?
N-No...
Hmm, are you angry about something?
You'll get wrinkles on your forehead.
No, I'm not.
You had a fight with
Tsuzaki, didn't you?
No, I'm not angry at all!
No, I'm not angry...
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
You can call me Master.
"Master."
How elegant it sounds!
I've got some interesting stuff.
The regular customers
love the wide selection.
I don't think that one
will fit you, Ms. Hasuma.
We also do custom-made,
if you're interested.
Oh, I don't need you to
tell me your measurements.
Bust 38 inch, waist 24 inch, hip
35, and brassiere size is 32G.
Am I right or what?
Well, I'll leave it to your imagination.
Whenever you need it, just let me know.
I have to go now, I still have
to clean up my new apartment.
But that must be hard while your
husband is away on a business trip.
I already have a very dependable helper.
Thanks for leaving
me all this trouble.
You have to make this up to me.
Aren't these underwear too small?
Some people prefer it that way.
Ms. Kanae.
This must be the last one.
Thank you, you were such a big help.
Daddy, you're great.
Don't mention it.
Konomi?
I haven't seen her for a while.
I don't think she goes out alone.
I don't see Tsuzaki, either.
I should have played with her.
Would you move to the right a little?
Okay.
That's good.
Wow.
That's so cute!
Isn't it so?
Oh no!
Oh no, no...
So sorry.
Never mind.
Yes!
Let me get the door.
Wow, sister!
This is the last one...
What are you doing here?
This is not your home!
Just come in here and look!
What is it?
Don't they look good together?
Daddy and Mommy.
What the...
Is that you, Tsuzaki?
What?
M-Mikoto!
Oh my!
So sorry.
More guests?
C-Chiho!
What are you doing?
You got me wrong.
I'm so sorry.
Konomi must've caused
you a lot of trouble.
I was a good girl.
Right, Mommy?
Don't call her mom.
Never mind, I'm glad she calls me that.
I'm sorry.
By the way, come here, Tsuzaki.
Huh?
She may not look like it,
but Chiho is a jealous woman.
You'll have a hard time
getting things straight with her.
However...
maybe I can talk to her for you.
This will do.
But be careful, there's
no smoke without fire.
And if you play with
fire, you can get burned.
Is this really okay with your husband?
What?
That I visit your place while he's away.
Don't worry, he's an understanding man.
But you really don't
have to do this for me.
Don't expect too much.
I'll be able to enjoy
whatever you cook.
Are you challenging me?
I'm going to make you say
"Delicious!", so be prepared.
You really look like him...
What do you mean?
I just think you're so cute.
You like Chiho, don't you?
W-What are you talking about?
C-Chiho...
I mean, Ms. Mizumori has
just lost her husband...
Besides, she doesn't
care about me at all.
You think?
I think she likes you, too.
If you are a real man,
you've got to be strong.
I'll be on your side and cheer you on.
Actually I used to be a
cheerleader when I was in school.
I like cheering on other people.
I don't think I have a chance.
Her husband was a really great guy,
I don't have that kind of confidence.
Confidence, huh?
Well, Tsuzaki, do you want to...
...have sex with me?
Ow!
I must be stupid.
She's a married woman.
Married women don't do things like that.
Then why do I care about them so much?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you'd
be that surprised.
That was a tasteless joke.
It's no joke.
I can give you what you need.
Stay still.
What I'm about to do is a sinful thing...
He's a man I just met...
But strange...
...I don't feel guilty at all.
Instead, I just want him to
have more confidence in himself.
I want to cheer him up.
That's right, I'm going to
do my best to cheer him on.
Feels too tight right here.
Is it my fault?
I'll make you feel better.
You have a very big penis.
You should be more
confident in yourself.
Kanae...
I spilled some.
You're getting hard again.
Well...
Then, come inside me next time.
Feel my pussy.
Feels good.
So good.
Come now.
Did I cheer you up a little?
I'm sorry, I just...
We're both adults.
We have to take
responsibilities for what we do.
Right?
Especially, if you're a real man.
Don't get me wrong.
I just hope you and
Chiho will be together.
So this was a lesson for you.
Yes, this was a lesson.
Don't worry, I won't have
any serious feelings for you.
You shouldn't either.
Okay?
You can do it, you're a man.
Thank you.
I woke up so early, I
cooked a little too much.
Thank you so much for
sharing your cooking with me.
I hope you like it.
Yes, I'm sure I'll like it.
I envy you, you're
beautiful, and you can cook...
My husband doesn't like Japanese food...
so I only cook Japanese
dishes while he's away.
It must be hard without your husband.
Yes, that's true, I am lonely.
A woman's body can't stand
being alone, don't you agree?
Even when we get old, women
don't stop being women.
By the way...
Satoru's mind is occupied with
a girl he has a crush on.
Maybe you can help him out.
I'm the one who said that
I wouldn't get serious...
What am I going to do?
I can't help but being attracted to you...
I know I shouldn't do this, but...
Wife Eater, Chance Two.
Please look forward to it!