This is Kazama.
This is Kubota from Panasony Records.
Yeah, hi.
It's about our new idol singer,
Ryoko Nishimura.
How's the song coming?
Uh, well...
It's not ready yet.
I can't seem to get the right image.
I was wondering if I could
meet her alone, once.
No problem, if that's what it takes.
I'll send her over.
Okay.
Oh, one more thing.
Have you got the title yet?
I'm writing the press release.
The title?
I've got it right here.
I'm in Love With a Statue.
I'm in Love With a Statue?
Sounds good! Thanks a lot.
Bye.
When Idols Fall Prey to Lady Luck
I'm Tsurujiro Kazama, 28 years old.
I'm a pop music composer, on the way up.
I write debut songs
for new idol singers.
Overworked and under incredible
pressure, I have only one relief.
That girl.
Akiyo Yoshizawa!
You're as beautiful as my first love!
Who is it?
Mr. Kazama? My debut is next month.
I'm Ryoko Nishimura.
My manager said I should come by.
Right. Come in.
Take off your clothes.
How do you want to finish,
from the front or back?
Whatever you like.
Back!
What a dirty mind, watching
those girls while you work.
It's not like that! I only found out
after I got the place.
I'm not that kind of guy.
Do you always sleep with
the girls before their debut?
Not at all! You were just too charming.
Come off it! I mean, look at this room.
I just prefer girls at their peak.
At 18 or 19, a girl's hormones
are out of balance.
She still has her baby fat.
A college sophomore is just right!
That slim body...
What's with the uniform?
The college sold them at a festival,
so I picked one up.
But it's secondhand.
So much the better.
Complete with rips and scorch marks.
It has the true-life smell
of a real college co-ed!
This is Kazama.
This is Sownee records.
How's the song coming
for Omoe Kunitachi?
Well, I can't quite get the right image.
I was wondering if I could
see her alone, once.
Okay, bye.
You framed this one.
Do you really like this type of girl?
Don't touch that!
Sorry, I didn't mean to be so rough.
She's very important to me.
She's just like my first love.
My love for her is a pure,
platonic love!
That's all. You can go, now.
No! I can't!
This is a pure, platonic love!
My first love!
Tsurujiro!
Akiyo!
Akiyo stopped coming
to the campus.
I don't know why,
but she was suddenly transferred,
But I still see her every day...
across from the campus.
She lives in the apartment
complex beyond the river.
Rivers have always
symbolized the flow of love.
They say a couple separated by
a river is easily reunited.
Yes! Akiyo Yoshizawa and me!
We'll meet on the left bank!
For just a kiss!
Perhaps just to meet and say hello!
I could die for that!
No luck today, either!
Why? Why has Lady Luck
turned against me?
I'm Masako Ishikawa,
I debuted last month.
My manager said I should come by.
What do you sing?
Oldies.
Figures. You'll have to practice
very hard to be a good singer!
Yes, sir!
Okay, go on home.
But I...
Christ!
Yeah?
Oh, Kume!
You've been promoted to Director?
Really?
You want me to appear
on "Reunited Lovers"?
I'll be there!
I'll see my first love again!
Suddenly, I'm filled with energy!
I may have missed Akiyo,
but luck must be guiding me.
Lady Luck is right!
I'll see my first love again!
I'm sorry I missed Akiyo,
but this makes up for it!
Now, Mr. Kazama,
hand the bouquet to your first love!
If you've chosen correctly,
she'll accept the flowers.
But all of them are so beautiful!
Will he pick the right one?
At last! It's been so long.
You were the inspiration
for all my songs!
Then...
I'm sorry. It's you, isn't it?
Then it's you!
Is it you?
You?
Look at that body!
It must be you!
Mr. Kazama is only speaking
to the cute girls!
What a wretched thing
man's memory is!
And it finally comes
down to just one girl!
Kazama! I never knew
how much you loved me!
It can't be!
It must be a mistake!
My first love can't be that ugly!
I wish you were dead!
Please stand by.
Who is it?
My manager said I should come by.
I'm going to debut this month.
I'm Seiko Nakamori.
Is that your real name?
No, my real name
is Akiyo Yoshizawa.
Hold on a second!
Akiyo Yoshizawa is
becoming an idol singer!
How could this happen?
Should I have sex with her?
No! My love for her
is pure and platonic!
It is!
What should I do?
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Dammit!
Yes! Trust in Lady Luck!
Please!
Should I have sex with her?
NO SEX
- Come on in.
- Thanks.
Where do you go to school?
Hori no Koshi University.
Okay, take off your clothes.
When a Virgin Steals a Man
(A Toyama no Benbei Adventure)
Good morning, President Toyama!
Good morning.
Good morning!
God, he's gorgeous!
They say all men are
created equal, but it's a lie.
When I see those cruel eyes,
I could just scream!
He's young, powerful,
handsome, and influential!
What kind of woman could
catch a man like that?
Thanks for loaning me
that Super Warrior game.
It's great, isn't it?
Did you get past level 16?
Not a chance.
I always die there!
Game over.
Yeah. How do you get past...
Mr. Toyama! Good morning!
President's Office
Mr. Toyama, good morning.
Good morning, Sakurako.
I have your schedule for today.
Your 10:00 meeting is
in the Daichi room.
Lunch is with the head
of the Economic Federation.
At 1:00, you see the French
Ambassador for a charity show.
From 2:00 to 2:30 is free.
At 2:30, you meet with
the Organization of Free States...
Nakadai!
Sachiko!
Happy Birthday!
What's this?
It's a scarf for your birthday.
I knitted it myself.
Stop it, Sachiko!
I told you we were through!
I won't accept this!
Take it back!
If you don't want it, just throw it...
Tatsuro!
Hitomi!
Sorry I'm late!
I just got here myself.
I'll make dinner for us, okay? But...
I'm still taking cooking lessons,
so it might not be very good.
Don't worry.
I always love everything you cook.
You're so nice!
Well, let's go.
Let's pick up some
wine on the way home.
Miss Honda! Good night.
It'll take a while to finish making the
beef stew.
Don't worry.
- What's this?
- I just got it.
How ugly. It wouldn't
look any good on you.
What's wrong, Sachiko?
You look miserable.
Sakurako, is there any
fate worse than death?
What's wrong?
This isn't like you.
There must be some way to stop her!
I'd like to rip the heart
right out of her body!
I... I...
What happened, Sachiko?
You can tell me, can't you?
We've always been close friends.
She took my boyfriend.
You can't mean Mr. Nakadai!
But you're engaged!
Yes, but Hitomi worked with him
in the accounting department...
She took him!
Nakadai!
He's the only man I've ever been with.
And then... he told me
that he'd only marry a virgin!
It didn't sound like him.
I'm sure it was her doing!
He said he liked her innocence.
It's a lie! She's no virgin!
She's lying!
Sachiko!
I was hurt and confused,
so I had her investigated.
She's usually going
with several men at once!
You should tell him!
No. I can't.
Sachiko!
I'm scared that if I tried to tell him,
he'd just hate me more for it.
Sachiko,
I know a man who will secretly
rape women, for a fee.
I'll introduce you.
You're not joking with me?
They call him Toyama no Benbei.
Toyama no Benbei?
I'll introduce you, but he
won't accept money for his fee.
You understand?
Unfortunately, Japan is
naive in world politics.
Japan is just like the USA was
after World War I...
It had a colossal trade surplus.
Then the great depression
of 1929 struck.
Are you saying that we'll
end up like America is now?
We're the world's largest creditor.
We can afford to return some power
to the rest of the world!
Japan must work for the
betterment of the entire world!
Thank you.
You've helped me immensely.
Toyama, I'd like to have these
discussions more often.
Certainly. You're always welcome.
Mr. President?
A customer will be waiting
for you at your BMW.
All right.
Get in.
You're Mr. Toyama no Benbei?
Yes.
I heard about you from Sakurako.
First, there's the matter of my fee.
You seem to have
the wrong impression.
She told you what to bring.
Is this really all you want?
I got it from my nephew...
The best game in America!
"Dragon Train" from Panic Software!
To think it exists in Japan!
So you're a game freak?
Now, Miss Honda,
I've agreed to your request.
Leave this to Toyama no Benbei.
Nakadai is horrible!
Getting himself sent to Osaka!
What a hunk!
Get in. I'll show you
a world made just for two.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
I saw you amidst the skyscrapers.
You were so beautiful,
I couldn't help myself.
All alone, in a parched
concrete jungle.
My heart thirsted for
satisfaction, but no longer!
You quenched my thirst like
a nymph from an enchanted well.
Even my car drives better,
now that you're here.
It's such a nice car.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Call me Mr. Benbei.
Mr. Benbei.
A toast to your beauty.
But your car...
is it okay to drink inside?
I don't care!
Anything for you!
I'd give my life for you!
No!
Your kisses are like heaven!
I'm 20 years old,
I've been kissed before.
Not there...
It's so wet!
I'm 20, I know what to do.
My bra is... That's my...
Please! I need you!
This storm of cherry blossoms
will transport you to heaven!
Mr. Nakadai, Miss Akimoto, good.
Everyone is here.
Miss Honda tells me her fiancé
was stolen by a phony virgin.
A phony virgin?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Nakadai, you don't seem
to know who really loves you.
Last night Miss Akimoto had
passionate sex with another man.
That's a lie!
According to the man,
they used several exotic positions.
A driving sexual experience.
What? Stop it!
She's not that kind of girl!
It's no joke.
She thoroughly serviced the man.
That's a lie!
You may be the president,
but I won't listen to this!
Apologize to her!
Hmm, then Miss Akimoto...
You're saying you've never
heard of a Mr. Benbei?
I've never met the man!
What do you take me for?
Mr. President!
Akimoto! Your charms could
ensnare any man!
You could trick almost anyone, but you
can't trick the Toyama cherry blossoms!
You remember this mark,
don't you, Akimoto!
This storm of cherry blossoms
witnessed everything!
Miss Hitomi Akimoto, you've
disrupted my company's harmony.
I'm ordering your immediate dismissal.
That settles the case.
Yeah! No! No!
Mr. Nakadai and Miss Honda
plan to get married this spring.
Mr. President!
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening. What happened
to that bitch, Akimoto?
She's claiming to be a virgin
at another company.
That's Akimoto, all right.
So, Sakurako, how'd you like to
drive out to Yokohama tonight?
Sorry, my mother's dying wish
was for me to stay out of BMWs.
Oh? When did your mother die?
Guess.
Dammit!
Oh, yes!
Why won't you marry me, Iwata?
Not yet, Tomoko.
I don't earn enough to support a wife.
But once we're married,
daddy can promote you.
One more time!
Kyoko...
That's wonderful!
When a Superior Takes Your Girl
(A Toyama no Benbei Adventure)
Good morning, Kyoko.
Iwata, good morning.
Your eyes are moonlit pools,
your lips are like cherries!
Your skin is whiter
than Kilimanjaro's snow.
Oh, Iwata!
You're more beautiful than a rose!
Save your flattery for outside,
hot shot.
What?
President Toyama! Good morning!
Very smooth.
Most men would have at least blushed.
I'm just sincere, sir.
She really IS that beautiful!
Such a romantic.
Mr. President, it's time
for the board meeting.
Sorry. Excuse me,
Iwata, Miss Itabashi.
Y-yes sir!
Mr. President, don't meddle
in the affairs of lovers!
Hey, that hurts!
I can't believe it! He noticed me!
He's so handsome!
I'm sorry, Kyoko, but I
have to break our date tonight.
Tomoko Umemoto insists
on seeing me every night!
I'm afraid I have to
see Mr. Umemoto tonight...
That family! They think their rank
lets them rule our lives!
Iwata!
Kyoko, I may not earn much yet,
but in a few years I'll make
enough to support both of us!
I know I can do it!
Papa, I want you to fire
Kyoko Itabashi! Right away!
I saw her with Iwata again!
She's always getting in my way!
Tomoko, what do you see in that gorilla?
He's just great!
What's so great about him?
It's just that he's so...
...twisted!
What's twisted?
I've become his sex slave!
Papa, please!
Out of the question.
I'm seeing Kyoko, I can't fire her.
Papa!
But I might have an idea...
Iwata raped your daughter?
Yes.
I can't believe it!
I have to think of Tomoko's future.
I can't press charges and
still work beside him.
Instead, I'd like YOU
to have him arrested.
If you can't, I'll be forced to resign.
You can't do that.
Your project would collapse.
Then...
All right, I believe you.
Iwata will be suspended... for now.
I don't quite understand, but... all
right.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. President...
I don't like Section Chief Umemoto.
Iwata!
I'm so happy!
Now we can spend all day like this!
Kyoko!
You said you had something for me?
It's nothing much.
I can't believe it!
I'm not saying that we
have to live together...
I can't. I can't accept it.
What? Why can't you see me today?
We haven't seen each other
for three weeks!
If I saw you, Umemoto would
just prolong your suspension.
So you're only staying away for my sake!
Try to understand, Iwata.
I understand.
I'll hold on, just for you, my darling!
Goodbye.
I don't care if I'm poor or unemployed!
Just as long as you're with me, Kyoko!
Who is it?
Tetsuo Iwata, of the
Oedo Production Corporation?
Don't open the door, just listen.
Who are you?
I'm with the Mossad.
The Mossad?
You've been suspended, haven't you?
How'd you know?
I'm with the Mossad.
I know everything.
Is it true that you raped Tomoko?
Raped Tomoko? Never!
She comes here every day
and uses me for sex!
I see. All right, I'll help you.
Legend of Belda, Legend of Kintaro,
Bad Muscles, Treasure of Kabocha...
What is this?
Take one of these games
to Azabu sports club at eight.
A man named Toyama no Benbei
will help you.
Toyama no Benbei?
Azabu Sports Club
Are you Mr. Toyama no Benbei?
Mr. Tetsuo Iwata?
Did you bring the merchandise?
The Treasure of Kabocha!
I've been briefed by Saku...
the Mossad.
Who should I rape?
Rape? Of course!
Rape Tomoko Umemoto!
Then I can blackmail
Umemoto into releasing Kyoko!
All right.
You don't know my father!
You lied to me!
Who are you?
A gangster!
Good. Everyone is here.
This situation revolves around Iwata.
Mr. Umemoto claims that Iwata
raped his daughter, Tomoko.
So I put Mr. Iwata on suspension.
It now seems that this was a mistake.
Mr. President...
Mr. Iwata?
Yes, Tomoko was raped,
but not by me!
Hold it!
What's the meaning of this?
And unless you want her raped again,
you'll release Kyoko!
Iwata, you bastard!
This is just another example
of his blackmail!
You should talk!
You screwed me over first!
What?
Wait a minute! I was never raped!
You don't have any proof, do you?
Proof? Well...
See? It was just another lie.
Stop telling lies!
Enough of this talk!
Mr. President!
Tomoko Umemoto! You asked for proof?
Then I'll give it to you!
Here's your proof!
You could never forget this
storm of cherry blossoms!
So the man who raped me
in the BMW was... the President!
Tomoko, is this true?
The two of you conspired
to have Iwata suspended.
Section Chief Umemoto,
you'll have to release Kyoko.
I have no choice. I don't want anyone
else to know about this.
Hurray!
No!
Mr. Umemoto!
Not even death can separate us!
My darling Kyoko,
I don't want to lose you, either.
What is this, Kyoko?
Didn't you ever notice how
much in love they were?
That's a lie! Tell her, Kyoko!
Don't you get it yet?
What an idiot!
Always dreaming, and ignoring
the real world.
Kyoko...
You'd live in poverty,
so long as we were together.
There's not a woman alive
who wants that kind of life!
I guess I'm not the woman
of your dreams!
I'm sorry, Mr. Romantic Egotist!
But...
Kyoko, you're the source of
this damaging relationship.
I can't forgive such a crime,
so I must ask for your resignation.
Of course.
Now you can devote
your time to Mr. Umemoto.
Mr. President...
Iwata...
You disgust me.
There are better men out there,
and I'll find one.
Mr. President, last night
was magnificent!
How can this be happening?
Just consider it a study in life.
The case is closed!