Now, hurry up and play with yourself.
I... I don't want to do this anymore...
It's too late for that now.
Don't worry, I promise I'll pay you.
Your embarassing image is being
sold all over the internet.
Guys all over the world are looking at
your dirty p**** and jerking off,
cumming all over themselves.
Oh no...
Now, let's take that underwear off...
Slowly, though.
What if someone... comes here...
No one's going to come at this time
of night. Come on, hurry up.
Yes, sir...
Very good... Now squat down.
Come on, spread those legs for me.
I can see everything...
Now, I want you to do everything
according to my scenario.
I-I'm going to masturbate
for you all, now.
Watch me rub my c-clit...
Speak up. The mikes can't pick
up your voice unless you talk louder.
W-watch me put my fingers into
my p****, and rub my clit,
getting it all wet for you.
Please enjoy watching
my dirty p**** show...
What are you waiting for?
Do exactly what you just said.
Yes...
Spread them, so the camera can
see all the way into your p****.
Oh, how dirty. Your juices
are mixing with the sand.
Kids play in that!
I'm s-sorry...
That's it! Keep going!
Now, let's try playing with some toys!
No... No, I don't want to!
You have two fingers in there.
A rotor shouldn't be a problem.
My fingers... They're my fingers,
but... That thing is...
Well, that's too bad.
How about you pee for me instead?
Huh?
If you let me film you peeing,
you won't have to use this.
Which will it be?
Choose whichever you like.
Good, good! Once more with feeling!
Close your eyes. Sleep is like a
detatched death. Dreamless sleep.
And so the days go by.
SIBLING SECRET PART 2
Why was that person smiling that day,
surrounded by the scent of lillies...
Does that person even know I'm alive?
Please come in.
Welcome to the Hungry Bear!
- Suzuhara!
- Y-yes?
Don't just stand there!
When a customer arrives, greet them!
Oh... Yes, I'm sorry...
Ritsuko is a bit much, isn't she?
Huh?
Well, she must take her job seriously.
I-I'm sure she does...
Excuse me!
I'd like some more coffee, please!
Oh... coming!
No...
Please excuse me...
I want to stand up for myself...
How did it come to this...
Maybe... Maybe it's all my fault...
Hey.
I was waiting for you, Suzuhara.
Hirukawa... I...
Now today, we're going to film
on the beach over there.
The camera is already set up.
I can't do this anymore...
What?
Please... I don't want to do it anymore...
I see. You can't, huh?
So maybe I'll take the mosaic off
the faces on all the video we shot.
They would probably
sell better that way.
Please, no!
You aren't allowed to go against me.
Wait long, Suzuhara?
Huh!?
I'm sorry.
Suzuhara and I promised to meet up.
W-what...?
Well, shall we go?
But I...
Just shut up and play along.
Okay...
W-w-what the...!?
Why... why did this person help me?
Feeling better?
Huh? Oh... yes!
Sorry...
Here, you should drink this.
I don't really... like to drink...
It might make you feel better.
Oh...
Just a little bit.
Okay...
Are you okay?
Y-yes, thank you...
I think...
I feel my body warming up.
Now tell me.
Huh?
Why you had to do everything
Hirukawa told you to do.
Well I...
I just want to help you.
Maybe... he knew who I was.
Me and my father. But then, why...
Around May... during the late shift,
there were sleeping pills in my food.
He took... naked pictures...
The pictures showed everything.
What do you mean, everything?
Down... there.
Down where?
Like I said...
Just spit it out already.
My... p-p****...
My p****. A picture of my p****.
He took a photo of my p****.
And so he blackmailed you?
It was partly my fault. I got...
greedy when he mentioned money...
My father... he caused a traffic
accident and... he committed suicide.
There were so many loans
he hadn't repaid...
What's this?
P-please give that back! That's...
The video Hirukawa took of you.
You had him make a copy.
Can I see it?
What...?
I told you. I want to help you.
To do that, I have to
figure out what Hirukawa is doing,
and exactly how he's using you.
I need to know it all.
But...
You don't want me to see?
Do you want to keep
being used by Hirukawa?
"I want to help you." Was it goodwill
or simple kindness? Perhaps...
perhaps he just hated me... If so, I...
So you get naked in a place like this.
They're really big.
They suddenly grew during elementary
school. It was embarassing.
Don't be embarassed.
Isn't it better if they're bigger?
They're beautiful. They're not just big.
Think of them as your assets.
Did you do that on your own?
N-no! Hirukawa was telling me what to do...
My nipples... My nipples are so hard...
But you seem to be enjoying it.
That's not...
No!
Hey, keep watching.
B-but...
Huh? W-what are you doing?
This video is in a very
accessible place, isn't it.
I bet you've seen this tape many times.
What were you doing?
W-well... l...
Oh, that's right. You must have
been masturbating.
You're a lewd, perverted woman!
You're just a little bitch.
I... l...
No!
No, please! Stop!
P-please... stop it. Stop.
Don't... Please don't do it...
Oh, your panties are all wet.
This doesn't look like sweat...
N-no...
P-please, stop!
But look how wet you are.
P-please stop... l'm serious...
Oh, you don't want to do
it with your panties on.
Please...
Is this what you wanted?
Looks like you have a little bit of
an exhibitionist side, Suzuhara.
I-I don't know... I... don't know
anything except that my body...
feels really hot... So hot...
Will you be my slave?
What?
You see, I have strange tastes too.
I like to torment
the girls that I like.
Torment... girls you like...
Right...
Say it.
Say you'll be your master's slave.
I-I can't...
If you say it, I can make
you feel even better.
I-I... I want to be your...
your slave, master...
Good.
Now, ask for your master's sch****.
P-please... Master, please
give me your sch****...
Where do you want it?
M-my p****... Please put your
sch**** in my p****, master!
Well said.
Huh? W-what are you doing?
I don't have to explain
myself to a little slut...
You get excited when people talk
to you like that, right?
N-no, not there!
- P-please, I don't want it in my ass.
- You know you like it.
- You're dripping wet.
- I'm embarassed! Don't look!
All this because of your ass?
You must really enjoy it.
No!!
P-please... Don't shove your fingers
in my ass. P-please!
Please... Not my ass...
l-it hurts! No!!
Try not to tense up.
It's coming in... It's in...
Your sch**** is in my ass.
Your sch**** is in me!!
- No... no, it hurts!
- Do you feel it?
It hurts so much... b-but... but...
Your p**** is soaking.
You're perverted for getting like this
just from your ass.
Yes... l'm a pervert! I'm perverted!!
Go on. Tell me how you're a slut
who likes it up the ass.
I... l'm a pervert. I'm a slut who
loves taking your cock up my ass!
He's smiling... Is this person
taunting me? Or is he...
I didn't know you loved
it up the ass so much.
Yes, yes, yes!! My ass! My ass!!
So you don't need it in your p****?
G-give it to me! I want it in
my p****... my vagina!
Give it to me, master!
Give me your sch****, please!
Well, that's a problem,
since I only have one cock.
For a horny little pig,
this should be enough.
Hm? You make it sound
like it's your first time.
It is my first... I never put anything
bigger than my fingers in my cunt.
Huh? How about Hirukawa?
Doesn't he sometimes fuck you?
H-Hirukawa only... films me.
He doesn't want to fuck my dirty p****...
He's right.
So how do you like getting your
virgnity taken by this thing?
I-I'm... v-very happy...
I see. You're happy.
I-I'm going crazy!!
Here I go. What do you want?
Your cum! Give me your cum!
Give me lots of your cum... please!
I... l'm losing my mind!!
I never intended... Something was
wrong with me. It might be the wine.
Don't blame it on the wine.
But...
Okay, then let's try an experiment.
An experiment?
Tomorrow... don't wear any panties
while you work. If you're not wet...
...then we'll pretend like
this never happened.
And if it is wet?
Then, I'll discipline you as my slave.
My ass and my vagina still hurt
from yesterday. It's not a strong pain,
but the pain feels heavy...
What intentions did he have for
doing this? Is this punishment...?
Suzuhara! There you go, spacing
out again. Go clean table five!
Oh, yes.
Don't... please don't...
Are you really going to do this?
Of course.
But...
If we lose our funding, we can't go on.
Even the head's daughter...
Excuse me.
You there!
Yes?
Dont' worry about over here.
Make sure no one bothers us for a while.
Yes, I understand.
Hey, who's that beauty over there?
Oh that's the Hungry Bear's chairwoman.
Chairwoman? A female executive, eh?
That's great.
Those hardass types always
are animals in the sack.
I want to do it with one, just once!
Perhaps... I am...
Come on.
It is all connected.
Connected in a thin little loop.
I don't care about strangers.
Forget strangers...
Sympathizing makes you human.
Let's see how your bottom half is doing...
l-it's soaking wet.
I got so wet, it almost went to the floor...
What if the manager or Miss Fujimiya
came, what would you do?
They'd all find out what
a pervert you are.
S-so would you...
I don't care, if I'm with you, Sayaka.
This smile, this smile is what makes me...
Did you... know who I was?
My dad hit Misato... your wife with the taxi...
I vaguely remember the face. You came
to Mistato's wake. But your dad...
I... I thought I was being punished.
Punished?
Yes...
It was so painful...
I was happy...
That time...
You were smiling.
That smile... I wanted to know
for a long time what that smile meant.
The tears won't come. Ever since
I lost Misato. So... I can only smile.
Sympathizing makes you human.
It's strange. It's so painful without
Misato... but my life keeps going on...
Can I... do anything... for you?
Is it really okay?
Once you step off these steps,
you can never go back
to a normal life again.
A normal life... there's no meaning
in a normal life for me.
It's painful, and every day is lonely...
This is what I want? This is it?
When I climb down these steps,
I won't ever go back to that world.
When I climb down these steps...
I'll be his!
Now... raise your ass.
Your vagina is soaked.
I-I'm very sorry...
Did you masturbate last night?
Yes, a lot...
Please... put your fingers
in my p****... in my p****...
What do you want?
Your sch****. Stick your sch****
in my vagina, in my dirty p****!
I won't give it to you right away.
H-hot! Hot! It's so hot!
It's strange. When I drip wax
on your ass, your p**** drips too.
L-it feels good. It pricks...
and then I feel the warmth all over...
Well then.
It's going in my ass!
My ass! It's filling me up!!
Awww, then my cock can't fit.
N-no please! Your cock!
Please give me your cock, master!
First, get that candle out yourself.
Yes, sir...
l-it's out...
Master! Hurry, please hurry.
Please put it in my dirty ass...
P-please... in my ass...
my ass. Hurry!
What a greedy little slut.
I-I feel it inside... the head...
y-your fat cock... so deep...
Yes! Yes, it's so good!!
Your cock, I feel it moving in my belly!!
Good. So good.
I'm going to cum inside you.
W-wait, please wait! My p****!
My p****!
Please put your sch**** in my p**** too!
Deep in my dirty p****...
in my vagina!
P-please!
You want it that bad?
Yes, I want it... I want it!
Please, I want it!!
Amazing. Your cock.
Your cock feels like it's hitting my cervix!
More! Fuck me harder in
my dirty p****! My p****!
Make me even wetter!
Now it feels like I'm taking the orders.
H-here I come.
Cum! Cum inside me! In my p****!
Cover me with your cum!!
And so, Sayaka became my meat slave.
Day or night, she seeks
to give pleasure,
like a good meat puppet.
I am my master's cum bucket.
My p**** is always wet,
because I am his slutty,
horny, cum pet.
Please let me have my master's
cock, and my master's milk.
I want master's milk.