Ritsuko... do that to Ritsuko...!?
I'll be leaving a bit early.
G-good work...
Goichiro Fujimiya... Ritsuko's father
is involved in credit management,
and he is trying to
take away our funding.
If they do that, we're finished.
But... you don't have
to do that to Ritsuko...
Fujimiya.
Huh? Oh... g-good work...
Good work to you too.
Hey! Why are you walking next to me?
We're heading to the same station,
so obviously we're on the same road.
I... then at least keep your distance!
The bank bases its image on trust,
and if she is caught in some lewd act,
and if some photos were
to leak out to the public,
or to their clients, Goichiro Fujimiya's
image would be ruined.
And for that you want someone...
to rape Ritsuko and take pictures!?
Hey! Are you listening?
I told you! It's not that I hate you,
it's just that I don't like men!
Oh, so you like me, huh?
Listen, you!
You're off this Sunday, right?
Want to go see a movie?
What!?
Maybe if you go out with me,
you'll stop hating boys.
None of your business!
I want to see a sweet dream.
But dreams fade. In a second.
That is their nature.
So I want to see a dream I won't wake from.
SIBLING SECRET PART 3
Please come in.
Welcome to The Hungry Bear!
Welcome!
So is that the girl we're going to do?
This better be okay.
The manager told us to, even gave
us money. We got no choice.
Look at that ass!
Here we are, gentlemen.
O-oh, it's you.
Just a fruit parfait, right?
Y-yeah.
Please, enjoy.
What do I do... I have a date with
a boy on Sunday... Me!
Wonder if he's the same
kind of man as my father...
Ouch! Hot!
I'm so sorry! I'm very sorry.
Where the hell are you looking!?
I'm so sorry...
Sir, I'm very sorry for her behavior.
I really hope that I can live
my life as strong as that woman.
Alright, smart guy, what did you think?
Let's see. Oh, the part when the cows mate.
That was the only good part.
What the hell is that? You're odd...
Something wrong, Fujimiya?
Goichiro Fujimiya, Head of the Outou Bank,
and Ritsuko's father...
So? You want to go in too?
Huh? D-don't be stupid!
Father... only thinks of me as a prize
he can sell to the highest bidder.
He wants to marry you
away to a rich home.
Yes, which is why he got me into
the best girls college possible...
If he found out I was part timing
at a family restaurant, he'd flip.
Are all men... as unfaithful as my father?
Don't know... I never cheated while
I was married, at least.
You were married!?
I'm sorry... I didn't know anything...
I think I misjudged you.
Misjudged me?
I thought you were more frivolous...
I mean, towards women.
Like your dad?
If he found out that you and I were
going out, what would your dad think?
He'd... probably get angry.
He'd get red in the face.
Then... let's get him angry.
When I'm talking to him, I lose
my place. I'm scared.
I feel like I'm not me.
So... how's your tea?
It's good...
But it tastes a little funny.
Probably because I put
a special medicine in it.
Medicine?
Yup. Some love medicine.
Quit saying stupid things!
Sadism and masochism...
This the kind of thing you like?
And you?
I-I'm not interested
in this kind of thing!
Scared?
Scared!? Why should I...
Stop...
Stop what?
S-stop that.
You can't.
Wait!
Isn't it... too soon?
Sooner or later doesn't matter.
All that matters is do you like it or not.
I... guess that's true...
You don't want to get
yelled at by your dad.
My dad has nothing to do with this!
Leave it to me.
It's your first time.
You can close your eyes if you want.
I'm not scared...
N-no please...
S-stop...
It's beautiful and so white...
It's no use. I can't fight him...
I'm losing... to a boy...!
Looks like the special
tea is starting to kick in.
No, no...
No...
No, no... stop!
P-please don't... No!
You sure are sensitive, Fuijimiya.
I-I don't... f-feel a thing...!
No... no...
P-please don't look... no...
don't look at me, please!
Don't... it's so... dirty...
It's not dirty. It's beautiful.
You should be more honest
about the things you desire.
Honest... to my wants...
I hated men, because they were
all like my father. A clump of greed.
But... thinking that way denied
my own greed... my desires...
Go ahead and say what
you really want.
Go on.
I-I...
If it's something you want to do,
I'll do anything. Even if it's dirty.
M-more... more...
What?
Give me more...
Give you what? Be specific.
L-it feels so good...
Where?
The place... you're touching
with your fingers...
Oh, you like it here.
Tell me how much
you like your p****.
N-no, I can't... say
something like that...
But look how wet it is.
No...! Don't say it!
Your vagina is amazing.
Look how tightly it's clenching.
M-my vagina...
my vagina is...
Your p**** is.
My p****... my p**** is feeling it!
I feel it in my p****!
You finally said it.
P-please don't swirl
around my vagina...
I'll stop if you want me to.
P-please! Don't stop...
Please, please!
Then tell me to play with
your p**** and your clitoris.
P-please play with my
p**** and my clit! Do it hard!
- Harder! More!
- You're so dirty, teasing like that!
So good! Rub my clit more!
Rub my clit and my p**** more!
I thought you didn't like it?
I love it! I love my clit!
I love my vagina. I love them both!
I can't... I can't...
I can't handle... I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
You want to cum that much?
Let me cum! Please let me cum!!
Amazing...
My p**** is melting...
You can feel even better.
I-I want... I want...
H-hurry...
Okay... then tell me specifically.
G-give me your cock!
Stick it in my p-p****... please!
Put your cock inside me!
Give it to my p****! Give it to me hard!
H-hot!!
Does it hurt?
L-it doesn't hurt...
it doesn't hurt at all...!
N-no! It's so hot!
My p**** is so hot!
Don't clamp on so tight.
It's hot! My p****,
my whole body is so hot!!
No, no, no, no...
I feel weird... weird... My p****...
My p**** is... don't... no!
It's cumming. I'm cumming.
No, no... help me...
Help! Help me!
My p****, my p****!
Help my p****!
A weird person, a strange person.
Why did he want me
to wear this thing?
I wonder why I agreed to this.
More to the point, why did that happen?
My body is still burning up from yesterday.
Like a fire...
Thank you for coming.
Please come again!
Did you... wear it today?
You idiot! Of course I'm not
going to be wearing that today.
For some reason...
the store looks different today.
All because I'm wearing this thing...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nobody knows that I'm
like this under my uniform.
That my indecent
underwear is soaked...
Is that your entire order?
Please enjoy.
It kind of feels... really good.
What the... is it a blackout!?
Oh, finally. Here we go.
Fujimiya, you're soaked.
What!?
Looks like a soy sauce stain.
When... did that happen?
I wonder how it got there?
W-who's there?
I'm going to call for help.
Don't struggle!
Here!
No!!
What's this?
No, please don't. Pervert!!
You're the pervert! Your nipples
are showing. How's she down there?
Wow, amazing here too. She looks like
a hardass, but she's a pervert!
L-let go of me! I'll start screaming!
Looking like that? Who's going
to believe a perverted woman?
Besides, we were asked
to do it by your manager!
What?
Let's see...
She's got a great ass. Look at it.
Yeah, let's hurry up and do it.
Don't!
Stop! Don't! Let go!
Hey! How do you take this thing off?
It's idiot-proof.
Are you okay?
Y-yeah...
These guys said they
were asked by the manager.
Yeah, but the puppet master
is the chairwoman, Yumiko Misaki.
What does this mean?
Will you let me handle this?
But...
Either way, you should get home.
Should I walk you home?
I can go home alone.
Okay. You're very strong, Ritsuko.
It's your fault, you know.
Making me wear this stupid thing.
Did you get excited? Maybe I should
have let you get attacked.
Jerk!
What's this all about? Calling me
to a place like this. I'm a busy woman.
Like I said on the phone, I got all the
evidence of the crime.
Y-yes, and what's your point?
I have a witness too.
T-that's why I was against this
from the very beginning!
But she told me to get Ritsuko
raped and take pictures.
The manager spilled his guts
when I put a little pressure on him.
Even things I didn't ask.
Like that book keeping scam.
Okay. Name your terms.
What do you want?
I don't have any intention of taking
money from you right now.
But I will take The Hungry Bear,
which you're going to sell me. Cheap.
What did you say?
Oh, and one more thing.
You should be thankful.
W-why the hell should I be...
The store's business is stagnant.
Sell it cheap while you can sell at all.
W-who the... hell are you...?
I'll tell it to your p****.
Good reaction. Did you learn this
in college? Guess you earned that MBA.
P-please... isn't that enough?
Let's stop this.
Okay, I'm cumming in your p****.
N-no don't! Don't cum.
Not in my p****! Not inside! No!
Here it comes...
P-please don't do it! Not inside
my p****! Not my p****!
I can't hold back.
Not in my p****!
Please! No! No!
Oh, Ritsuko? Can I head over there?
I took care of your little problem.
Chairwoman Misaki? She's very sorry.
She said she won't do it again.
You're so aggressive. This is the
first time I let a boy into my room.
Don't, my mom's going
to be home soon.
That's why we should.
B-but that's not... stop it...
You don't wear a bra at home.
Don't... no...
No... no...
You're already wet.
Were you masturbating before?
N-no, I wasn't. I didn't.
Stop... no, no, no...
No, no, no, no... I...
Don't... no... stop!
See, you're already so wet.
Don't...
It tastes good. Just like you.
Don't... don't lick that.
Then will you lick it for me?
I'm home!
Ritsuko! Ritsuko!
Looks like you have a friend over.
Amazing. Look at all the juice
coming from your vagina.
Ritsuko? Ritsuko?
Answer me, Ritsuko.
Thrilling... isn't it?
Ritsuko! Ritsuko!
She's calling you,
let's open the lock.
Ritsuko! Open this door, Ritsuko!
Don't waste it. Drink it up.
Is it good?
I-I don't know. My mother was here...
And we were... we were...
You get excited when you
taste cum, don't you?
Hey, I'm home!
Darling, it's Ritsuko...
S-stop... I hear m-my dad... No!
It's okay. Just tell him the truth.
Tell him you're busy drinking my cum,
and that your p**** is soaked.
N-no... I swear...
you're such a bully sometimes...
Ritsuko! I hear you have a friend over.
I'd like to meet him!
Should we?
J-jerk! We can't...
we can't meet like this!
Then what do you want to do?
Well, what?
P-put it in...
What, your father?
N-no!
Then my fingers...
Y-your sch****! Your sch****.
I want your cock inside of my p****.
My soaking wet p****...
p-put it in... Fuck me!
Your sch****.
Please give me your sch****.
Oh god, no! No!
Don't! God! No!
Ritsuko? What are you doing?
Ritsuko!?
Y-your sch****! Swirl your sch****
inside my hot p****! Please!!
Ritsuko!
Ritsuko! Ritsuko! Ritsuko!
M-my dad... my dad is...
No more! Oh god! No!
I'm cumming! Cumming!!
I'm cumming too... Ritsuko.
Ritsuko!
Ritsuko! Ritsuko!!
C-cum in me! Hurry!!
Well, shall we go meet your parents?
What?
And so... like the devil, he managed
to charm my parents...
I'm scared. When I'm with him,
I don't know what will happen next.
And that excites me...
And so... The Hungry Bear became
part of my dad's company, and I...
Jun. Where are you?
Where are you going?
I'll be waiting here, where the gold
sunset meets the silver sunrise.
On the beach we call eternity...