Where am I?
Finally I was able to come
to Rei Seine, but...
Why did this happen?
What am I supposed to do?
Sin Sorority
Chapter Two
Yurika the Queen
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Mistress...
From today on you'll live a
life fit for a Culy.
A Culy?
You'll live like an animal. A life of
pleasure, wanting nothing but sex.
You guys.
She's pretty hot.
It's been a while since
we had some fun.
What are you...
Stop! Don't come!
I'm going to mark
you as a Culy now.
S... Stop!
You're driving me wild.
Keep crying.
No!
It's not too crinkled and
you don't have much.
Stop!
If you move, your precious
pussy is going to get sliced up.
Take a good look.
It's your bush.
Nice flavor.
It's completely bald. I can see
all the way into your pussy.
No...
All right...
Now for the fun part.
Stop!
Don't come near me! No!
It hurts! No!
It's nice and tight.
Please stop!
We're just getting started.
It hurts! No!
P... Please!
I'll make your pussy cry harder.
Something inside me shattered.
It wasn't pain.
It was overwhelming ecstasy...
It's hot...
It's pounding me. It's pounding me.
She was hating this, but now look!
She's clinging onto me.
It's hot.
It's amazing. Yes...
I can't anymore...
I'm going to cum.
Me too.
Please. Cum! Please cum!
Sure I'll cum inside you.
No! Not inside!
Cumming inside is the best.
I'll pour everything into your uterus.
No! Not that...
Please.
I'm gonna cum!
It's hot...
That was a great show.
You were humping your ass on
a man. You're a Culy now.
M... Mistress.
The cum pouring out of
your pussy looks great.
But we're not done yet.
Take a look at this.
Th... That's my...
You'll feel pleasure every time
you get a call from a man.
No! No!
Guys...
Yes.
No! Please! Get away!
Don't! Please Mistress!
I don't want this!
I'll shove this in you.
It hurts!
Now that it's in her, put a lid
on it so it doesn't fall out.
What are you doing?
No!
You're going to wear that
and go to class today.
But...
I'll take it off after classes.
It's no use running. It won't
come off unless you use this.
No... It won't come off.
If I get a phone call during class...
Why is this happening to me?
About yesterday's assignment...
I didn't do it.
Y... Yoko.
What's wrong?
You're spacing out.
Asuna, you don't look well.
Are you all right?
Yes. I was just thinking something
about the student government.
That's all well and good,
but don't push yourself too hard.
So if we translate up to this part...
Fall has come and the mountain
range became rainbow colored.
- Then the scenery of the village...
- Please, be over soon.
A full moon lighting
the entire mountain.
No! Please, make it stop!
No! If people found out about this...
Asuna.
Asuna!
Yes!
Please translate this portion again.
Yes.
What's the matter Asuna? Hurry up.
As I climbed the mountain road...
The moonlight b... became light and...
I can't take this anymore.
The trees in the woods,
touched by moonlight...
were glowing as if they
were painted in silver.
And...
No! It's dripping out!
If people saw it...
I... I'm going to cum... No.
E... Everyone is watching...
I can't anymore. I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum. I'm...!
Asuna!
What happened?
Are you all right?
- I think we should call an ambulance.
- Asuna!
We should take her to the infirmary.
Hurry.
We should call an ambulance.
Asuna... Asuna...
Asuna, are you all right?
Yoko... I...
You scared me because
you fainted suddenly.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry. I suddenly wasn't
feeling well. But I'm ok now.
I'm glad, then...
I'll come by again after classes.
Thanks Yoko.
Stop it. We're friends.
I'll see you later.
Yoko...
I... I...
Asuna.
Huh? That's strange.
I wonder where Asuna went?
Wow. I wonder if this building is
for the student government.
Asuna. I'm glad
that you came back.
Mistress. Please take this off.
Asuna!
Yoko?
No! Don't look at me! Yoko! No!
Asuna!
What do you think you're doing?
Let go of me!
Yoko!
You bastard! Let go of me!
Welcome Yoko.
Why are you here?
What do you think? Look how
drastically your friend has changed.
Do you like it?
You're the one making Asuna
do these terrible things?
You're not even treating her
like a person! This is terrible!
What are you saying?
Asuna isn't a person.
She's my toy! My slave!
You're wrong! Asuna's a person!
She's my best friend!
Let go!
Damn it! Calm down!
Why? Why are you doing
something like this?
How can you call her a slave?
You can't treat another person like this!
We're all the same!
Same?
You're saying this scum who has no
talent whatsoever and I are the same?
What's so funny?
Silence!
How dare an insignificant
bug make a remark at me!
You should know your place!
What?
Listen to me. Even if we're
human, our worth is different!
A normal person and a genius
are two different species!
What are you talking about?
Normal people thrive off of geniuses.
A punishment will be given to fools
who forget about those privileges!
Mistress. You're not going to do the
same thing to Yoko, are you?
What do you guys want?
She has a great body.
Let go, you perverted bastard!
You sure are energetic.
But I wonder how long that'll last.
We're going to be having fun with you.
S... Stop it!
Wait please!
You can do anything to me!
But Yoko...
But please spare Yoko!
Silence!
Insulting me is a serious crime!
Mistress Yurika, please!
No!
Please. I'll do anything!
So please spare Yoko!
Mistress!
You'll really do anything?
Yes.
Then satisfy these men in front of
your friend while she watches.
Pee and engage in all of your
perverted acts while she watches you.
Show her how much you've changed.
She'll be disgusted with you and won't
be able to be your friend anymore.
If she has nothing to do with you...
I can forgive and dismiss
her as a stupid audience.
Don't do it Asuna!
That's crazy! Don't do it!
What are you going to do?
If you don't want to, that's fine.
Don't!
You bastard! Let go!
I'll do it.
Asuna stop!
Asuna stop! Please stop!
Take a good look if you're her friend.
Stop!
Asuna.
Asuna!
Yoko. Watch me... Be disappointed in me...
and forget about me...
Yes...
Asuna...
It's so amazing...
No...
I'm going to cum!
Good Asuna. Now pee!
Yes...
Asuna!
Stop!
Stop it! What do you think
you're doing, you bastard!
Stop! Let go!
Yoko!
Mistress! Please make them stop!
I can't.
Even I can't interfere with
other people having sex.
But... You just promised me!
Watch what you say!
A promise is something that is made
between two people who are equals.
You think a Culy
has that kind of right?
You're terrible! You're evil!
Don't forget there are others
that can deal with you!
Stop! Let go! Let go of me!
It hurts!
Stop! Please!
Come on! Shake that ass more!
Suck it.
I said suck it!
No.
I'm sorry Yoko.
It's my fault this happened... I'm sorry.
What a lame fuck.
She doesn't have any technique!
After her! Don't let her get away!
Run Yoko! Run!
Hang in there Asuna!
I'll definitely save you!
Masato!
What's going on?
Did Yoko just come this way?
We have to catch her!
It's Lady Yurika's order!
You can't get away now.
Come over here.
Don't come! Go away!
If you'll be a good girl
I'll take care of you.
Don't come! I'll jump
if you come any closer!
Stop babbling and jump then.
Let go! Let go!
What happened?
What just happened?
She fell off the roof.
Is she dead?
I think she's dead.
Call the police! Call the police!
It wasn't me...
She fell on her own.
That's right. It's her fault.
Asuna. Asuna.
Your friend Yoko Shimojo is dead.
It was a suicide.
She jumped off the roof.
That can't be...
That's too bad... And you were
about to make a slave buddy.
Dead? Yoko is...
Yoko's dead...
Yoko is...
It's my fault.
Yoko! Yoko!
No!
Yes...
More...
Rub me harder...
Harder please...
Make me forget it.
It's all right.
Lady Yurika will take care of it all.
But I'm scared... Her face is...
Calm down Nana.
We're not the ones who killed her.
Killed?
Masato's the one who killed her.
But we were there too...
We were only following Lady Yurika and
Masato's order to catch that girl.
Calm down Nana. You have me.
Yes...
Yes.
He killed Yoko!
I won't forgive them!
Yoko, I will avenge you!
I'll make him and Yurika feel
the same pain as you did!
Asuna, raise your face.
Look at me.
What are you doing? You can't
listen to your master's order now?
Don't be such a crybaby over
one dead insignificant bug.
Insignificant bug?
Yoko's not an insignificant bug!
You murderer!
Yoko... Bring Yoko back!
Lady Yurika!
L... Lady Yurika!
Don't touch me!
How dare a slave like you
do such an audacious act!
I'll instruct you so
you'll never disobey me!
It'll be fun to see how long
you'll be able to endure this.
I haven't forgiven you yet.
Next I'm going to use your favorite,
and thoroughly adore you.
Well Asuna? You like it, don't you?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Now say it. You're feeling it right?
I'm enjoying it... But I don't want to give
a woman like her the satisfaction...
I'm getting wet.
It keeps coming out.
Yoko. Please help me. Yoko.
You're a Culy... A slave!
You can't disobey your master.
Now...
I'll make you cum.
I'm bleeding!
Asuna! You're going to regret doing this!
I'll forgive you now.
Put the razor down!
No! How dare you murder Yoko!
I won't forgive you!
A Culy playing the
friendship game? What nerve!
Then, I'll toy with you
for the rest of your life!
Lady Yurika!
This can't be.
A Culy is disobeying me?
This can't happen.
Disobey me?
It can't... It's impossible!
I won't lose.
I'm going to avenge Yoko!
I'm not going to forgive that woman...
who treats people like her toy
and treads over people's emotions.
I swear I'll have revenge.
But how am I going to do it?
Please, help me Yoko.