It's so hot...
Yes...
It feels so good... Yes. Yes...
I'm going to cum.
Sin Sorority
Chapter One
Asuna, The New Transfer Student
I've finally been accepted to this school.
Everyone's dream school, Saint Rei Seine.
I grew up in a normal family. This is a
whole world I never knew existed!
OK! I'm gonna do it!
Oh no! I'd better hurry or else I'm
going to be late for the ceremony.
Ow...
Where do you think you're looking?
How rude!
I'm sorry!
I wasn't paying attention.
That outfit... Are you a transfer
student from the outside?
Y... Yes!
I see.
Then I guess you wouldn't know anything
about the school rules or who I am...
What's your name?
Mind your manners.
When you bump into someone,
the least you can do is introduce yourself.
I'm sorry.
I'm Asuna Sugihara.
I see.
I'm Yurika Ichinomiya, a second year.
Make sure you remember that.
Yes.
I'll forgive you this time
because it was the first...
but make sure it
doesn't happen again.
Yes. I'm really sorry, Miss.
Miss?
Call me Mistress here.
Mistress?
Yes.
Ow...
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
Grab on.
Thank you very much.
You must be a transfer student.
With all the flashy outfits here,
your outfit is actually a lot cuter.
Um... I'm in a hurry, so...
As a student of Saint Rei Seine...
I would like you to...
spend your days at this campus
filled with pride and dignity.
And now a word from the
Student Government President.
Quiet please!
She's...
I am the President of the Student
Government of Saint Rei Seine.
I am Yurika Ichinomiya.
There is one thing I
would like to tell you.
At Saint Rei Seine, the most valued
quality of a person is dignified behavior.
I would like you all to remember that.
I wish for all of you to become opinionated
leaders of this country in the future.
In order to make that possible,
I will do everything in my power.
The best environment...
The best education...
I will gather the best
of everything for you.
You are all chosen people!
She's so amazing. Oh right!
I have to call her Mistress.
You're Asuna, right?
I'm Yoko Shimojo.
I sit next to you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Asuna Sugihara.
Nice to meet you too.
I'm from a normal white
collar background and...
was accepted through
a sports scholarship.
I thought I wouldn't be able to make
any friends who I'd get along with, but...
I think you and I could be friends.
Yes. I'm from a normal
family background too.
I'm so impressed that you
got a sports scholarship!
Thanks.
What kind of person is Yurika,
the student government president?
Do you know?
Yup. Yurika Ichinomia.
She's the only daughter of the
world class Ichinomiya Enterprise.
She's a lady who's great in
both sports and academics.
She's the queen of this school.
Yurika is amazing.
She's someone way
beyond our reach.
Normal people like us should stick
together and be good friends.
I'll always lend an ear
if you need anything.
Thank you, Miss Shimojo.
Call me Yoko.
This is going to be fun!
Great to meet you.
You're so adorable.
Yes...
I'll make you more wet.
No...
My adorable toy...
I'm so hot...
Not yet! Keep writhing.
More...
You're so wet.
It keeps flowing...
It's so embarrassing...
They're both women...
And she's touching her vagina.
I can't believe it.
It feels so good.
I'll make you feel even better.
Yes.
Don't cum yet!
It's too much...
Who do you belong to?
I...
A toy doesn't call itself 'I'!
Yes.
Now... Who do you belong to?
Kazumi belongs to Mistress.
Kazumi? Mistress?
I'm proud you said that. Now you're
part of my adorable collection too.
Mistress. Kazumi is so happy.
I'll give you a reward for being good.
Here's a feast for you.
Make sure to savor it.
I can't believe Yurika is doing that...
Y... You're...
We bump into each other a lot.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You don't look well.
Maybe you should rest over there.
Over there is...
Here.
I can't.
Um... Excuse me!
Mistress.
More... Fuck me more.
Mistress?
Silence!
That's it for today.
If you want a fuck, do it yourself.
B... But... Mistress! No!
Mistress! Mistress Yurika!
Mistress Yurika?
There you are, Asuna.
Huh?
I came to discuss something with you.
Discuss? Yuri... No.
With me, Mistress?
Mistress, please explain this to me.
You have something to discuss
with Asuna and not me?
You're being rude! How dare you
butt in when Mistress Yurika is speaking!
But... Mistress and I...
Kazumi... was it?
You're being annoying.
I am having a
conversation with Asuna.
Asuna, I have good news for you.
Good news?
Yes. I would like to welcome you as
a member of the student government.
A member of the student government?
Mistress! You must be joking!
Out of all people, Asuna?
Shut up!
Take her away.
She's a nuisance.
Yes.
No! Stop! Mistress!
Kazumi...
Don't let it bother you.
So what do you think about becoming
a member of the student government?
Why me?
I chose your talent over the masses.
Are you saying I'm wrong?
No... but what talent
are you talking about?
All you need to do is believe in me.
I'll wait until tomorrow.
I hope to hear a good answer.
What are you going to do
about the student government?
What am I going to do? I...
Asuna, not everyone gets an
opportunity. You should be honored.
Yoko.
But it's your decision, so I'll support
you whichever way you choose.
Thanks Yoko.
Stop it! We're friends.
See you. I have club activities.
Hey. You're Asuna, right?
Can we have a word with you?
An upperclassman is asking you
to come. Come with us.
Y... Yes.
I have something to report.
There is something
interesting happening.
What is it?
It's about Asuna Sugihara.
Um... What is it?
How did you get on
Lady Yurika's good side?
A newly admitted first year is suddenly
a member of the student government?
B... But...
What's going on?
Who's making them do that?
I don't know. I speculate that they're
doing it out of jealousy and loyalty.
You may go now.
Very well.
We're the ones who have been
serving Lady Yuriko all this time!
We won't allow this!
Tell us! How did you get
on Lady Yurika's good side?
There's no way you would
have been chosen as a member!
What filthy trick did you use?
You whore! You deceived
Lady Yurika with your cute face!
Stop. I didn't do anything.
Then promise us that you'll turn
the student government down!
That's...
You're not going to say it?
Well? Are you going to say it or not?
So? Are you going to say it now?
Why are you doing this?
What a stubborn girl!
We're not holding back anymore!
Please stop!
Hold her down!
This doesn't compare to
how humiliated we were!
We'll beat you until you break!
We'll beat you thoroughly...
So you'll never think about
joining the student government!
Look at her bra! It's a cheap
bra she bought on sale!
It is! You were going to
be a member wearing this?
Don't make me laugh!
Oh, how shameless. This isn't something
you should be screaming about.
Do you think she might be feeling it?
Oh no way!
Let's strip her down to
see if her nipples are hard.
Don't! Stop!
No!
They're not hard yet.
It hurts...
She's feeling it even if it's
hurting her. She's a whore!
Please stop... This is terrible.
Shut up! Let's take her skirt off.
No, don't!
No!
Her pussy looks like it's wet.
I have a camera.
Let's take a picture of this dirty girl.
Give us a good look.
No!
That's a pretty good pose.
Please stop!
I'll do something
more interesting to you.
Stop! That's...
No!
Let me go! Please!
Here! I'll rub you harder.
Stop.
Great face!
Might as well. We've come this far...
The last one will have
to come off too.
Shut up!
Oh, I can see everything.
Hey!
What are you doing there?
Katsumi!
What is the meaning of this?
You've got it all wrong!
We're doing this because
she deceived Lady Yurika...
so she can become a member
of the student government!
Th... That's right!
We're doing this for the
student government,
which in turn is also
for the school!
I don't think she's the type of girl
that would do something like that.
B... But Katsumi!
Ladies!
I don't want to use force.
I'll take the camera.
Katsumi. Whatever the orders may be,
we'll obey someone like Lady Yurika.
But to someone like her...
Leave!
For Yurika's reputation,
I'll keep quiet about this.
Katsumi...
You're...
I'm sorry. I surprised you again.
Why are you here?
I was looking for you.
Asuna.
How do you know my name?
You dropped this notebook.
I went to your classroom
but I just missed you.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
Don't worry about it.
I'm Katsumi Kudo, a third year.
Come, I'll walk you home.
It'll be terrible if you
get assaulted again.
B... But...
There's no reason to
say no. Come on.
OK.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Today's the last
time this'll happen.
If you join the student
government tomorrow...
no one will be able to
pull something like this again.
Anyway, you should get
a lot of rest today.
Let's go.
Oh... I see now...
Morning! Morning! Morning!
Morning.
Asuna, have you made up your mind?
Asuna.
We'd like to hear your answer if you're
joining the student government or not.
Of course there can't be
anyone on this campus...
who would refuse Lady Yurika's offer.
Um... I...
would like to join the
student government.
You're going to accept
Lady Yurika's offer?
Yes. I'm much obliged.
I understand.
I don't like them, but...
Good for you, Asuna!
I wonder if I made the right choice?
But there's no turning back.
Yurika, there's something I'd
like to ask you. Is it all right?
It's about Asuna.
Why did you make her a member?
She's genuine and adorable.
I judged her on those charms.
Isn't that what you did too?
You can't ignore her
when she's around.
I see. I'm relieved
to hear you say that.
Now no one will be
able to lay a hand on her.
Lay a hand?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, take good care of her.
Yes, of course.
I'll be taking good care of Asuna.
Thanks. I'll see you later.
There's something I have
to discuss with you, so...
I'll be waiting at the fountain
area after school.
Katsumi.
I wonder what it is?
Katsumi! Katsumi!
Katsumi?
Who are you?
No!
Are you finally awake?
Who are you? Where am I?
What is this?
No! Let me go!
No! Help!
It doesn't matter how much
you scream. Nobody's around.
You've got a nice body.
I'll show you a good time.
No! Stop!
- No! Help!
- Suck it!
No!
Stop struggling or else
you're gonna get hurt!
Come on!
No!
Stop struggling and suck it!
If you're not gonna do it,
I'll shove it up your pussy!
No! Please not that!
There you go...
Jerk me off while
you lick the head.
Yeah...
Suck it like you love it!
I'm gonna cum!
Swallow it all!
Lick my cock clean.
Hey, you better not say
anything about this!
Or else something terrible
is going to happen!
Got it?
What just happened?
What's going to happen to me?
It suits you well, Asuna.
Mistress!
I made you a member so
we can be alone like this.
Mistress. W... Why?
Silence!
Did that hurt?
Asuna. Kindness and being genuine...
Things like that are the flip side...
of human ugliness and greediness.
It's all self-centered egotism.
Let me show you now what I mean.
What are you talking about?
Did you already do this with Katsumi?
No I haven't! Not with Katsumi.
Really... You haven't yet?
Good then, because I'm the one who's
going to be instructing you.
Instructing me?
Please stop!
No!
So sensitive.
That's...
You're a virgin!
Mistress...
N... no...
I'm going to...
You seem like you can't get enough.
Fine. I'll stick it in.
Stick what in?
I'll put this in your pussy.
But...
Stop!
Please... Don't do it...
Your scared face...
It's adorable.
It hurts!
Well? How do you feel?
I've broken you in.
You're terrible.
It's adjusting already.
You're such a perverted girl.
No...
Yes Asuna. Cry louder!
Asuna, you belong to me!
No...
Say it, Asuna!
Who do you belong to?
I... belong to M... Mistress...
I can't hear you!
Say it once more!
Asuna... is yours, Mistress...
Well said...
Here's a reward.
Asuna. You were pretty good.
P... Please... Let me go.
Silence!
You belong to me! I won't
allow you to talk back to me!
Mistress...
It's useless to disobey me.
It's best to become subservient fast.
Tomorrow I'll love you even harder.
Tomorrow...
Good night, Asuna.
Why... Why is this happening?
Please... Someone help me.