Miss Angela
Your father sends his condolences.
He was unable to make it due to work.
Clumsy bitch died falling down the stairs!
Maybe I used too much of this...
That's good Bridget!
Bridget... you deserve this.
Turn around!
John!!!
Miss? How are your lessons going?
It was boring, so I sneaked out!
Besides, you're the servant.
You can't tell me what to do!
Instead of doing boring yard work,
why don't you keep me company?
You know I can't!
Your father hired me to do the yard work.
As for company,
Bridget would be better suited!
Well, I'm sure Bridget is busy
with father right about now!
Miss Angela?
Her mother passed away six months ago...
It seems like
she's finally herself again, but....
No!
Stop!
My Master!
No....don't.... please stop!
Bridget, how is it? You like that?
More move your hips, harder.
Don't stop!
All women are such dirty,
worthless, whores.
Master.
The mistress was right there!
That can't be! She's dead!
Stupid bitch...
Bridget....
How is the master?
I was just cleaning his office.
All right. Well, it's almost dinner.
Will you help me?
Y...Yes!
Angela, I heard you vanished
from your piano lesson today.
You are a legitimate heir
of the Viddock family.
You need to become a lady
befitting your family name.
Understand?
Angela!
If you want me to be a lady, please
don't speak to me when we're eating.
It's very rude!
If it wasn't dinnertime,
you would run away from me.
Those two...why can't they
have a pleasant conversation?
Five years ago, when we first met,
Angela was such a sweet child!
Miss Angela?
What are you doing up this late?
I'm fine. It doesn't bother me.
This is not good.
The master would kill me.
I suppose Father might kill you!
But..Miss Angela
I can't sleep.
Miss...Angela
It's because
you wouldn't keep my company earlier!
It's not right! Please stop!
Please return to your room.
My father's a worthless scoundrel!
He thinks he's something special
because of his royal title!
The hypocrite's telling me to be a lady
while he's carrying on behind my back
with Bridget, the maid.
While mother was alive,
she wasn't happy at all!
He would be abusive,
and couldn't even make it to the funeral.
He thinks women are his property to use...
...like some kind of baby machine,
or sex slave!
Stop this! I can't..listen to this!
That man is no father of mine. I hate him.
I'm going to do something he will despise!
Miss Angela!
Look at me, John.
Do you think I'm pretty?
Miss Angela....
Touch me, John
Please stop. This isn't right...Angela.
No! I won't!
We shouldn't! Really!
You're not going to reject me, are you?
I'm not stopping!
That feels good...
your fingers feel better than mine...
More, move it more!
Angela....
Here, let me touch you.
This goes in here....
Ouch!
That hurts...
Please, let's stop.
No! We're not done yet!
Angela... please, relax.
What are you going to do?
If you don't get wet it's going to hurt more.
I'm coming in, Miss Angela.
I've...I've done something
absolutely horrible!
I can't believe I've disregarded my position
and slept with her!
John!
Miss Angela!
Last night was wonderful!
You're stronger than you look!
But...I can't believe
I've disregarded my position like that!
It's ok, I wanted you to.
Besides, we're lovers now, aren't we?
See?
Wet...
You're dripping wet...
Make me feel good, John?
What, feeling sick? You want this?
Not so fast! Not for free.
Good...
lick it off so none gets wasted on the floor!
I've never loved anyone like this before.
I'm so happy...
Don't ever ever, leave me!
Why? How did I get into this mess?
It started that day....
Nooo! Please master, stop!
Does it hurt?
If it hurts, here some medicine for the pain.
Noooo!
This should take care of it.
No! Please help me, Mistress!!
Master? Not here?
You seem to like it like that!
Your pussy is flooding!
My father's a worthless scoundrel!
He thinks women are his property to use...
...like some kind of baby machine,
or sex slave!
Bridget?
Bridget! What happened?
How long has he been
forcing himself on you!
I don't know what you're talking about!
There's nothing going on
between master and I!
I have to go. Dinner needs to get started...
Let's leave this place!
What?
We'll start over elsewhere!
Leave here?
That's right!
We can't. do that!
Bridget! I can't just watch you
suffer like this!
It can't be!
...There must be some kind of mistake!