Ouch!
Kenichi, do you want
anything to drink?
Sure...
What should I have...
I sewed your button back on.
I screwed up a little, though...
Yes!
Oh... yes!
Ah, no! N-not like this...
H-harder!
N-not inside!!
Hey, Yoshino!
I'm going to open this package!
Oh, I forgot.
It got here yesterday.
Looks like you won a
prize from Canabi.
Congratulations
on winning your prize...
Hey, I guess I really did win.
See, isn't that amazing?
Yeah...
But, why Canabi?
Because the bonus
prize was really nice...
Bonus prize, huh...
Hey, I think that's the prize.
Huh?
This CD thing here.
Oh, this is Canabi software... Seeker...
a tracking program maybe?
Then let's drive!
Huh!?
Hey...
I think we might be lost.
No, according to the Canabi software
we should be at the destination soon.
Oh... then maybe it's that mansion...
Episode 1: The Awakening of S
Wow, amazing! I always wanted to
stay a night in a place like this.
Good evening.
Oh, we're sorry to come at night...
We got here through the directions
from the Canabi prize software...
Yes, congratulations on winning.
I'm afraid the master is not in,
and it's already very late,
so please spend the night here...
Oh... I, but...
Thank you, we'd love to stay.
Huh, h-hey...
It's already so late, let's stay.
There was something unnatural.
Even if we did win a prize,
who would invite in complete strangers
in the middle of the night?
Wait long?
Well, you're being awfully forward.
Please...
Hold me...
Please... l'm already so wet...
Yes...
Wait. Tonight, I'll be on top.
Oh yes!
Yes... oh yes! Oh god, I can
feel your cock so deep, Kenichi!
Where?
I can't...
Come on, say it!
M-my pussy! In my pussy!
And I'm all covered in your juices too...
No, no... Don't say
things like that. Oh God...
I-I'm gonna cum.
P-please cum with me.
Yes! I-I'm cumming!
Right there! I'm-
It felt so good, I came inside you.
Don't worry about it. It's okay
today, so... let's go again?
Just like an animal...
No, please don't be mean.
You're looking like an animal too.
Then tell me exactly what you
want and where you want it!
In my pussy... My pussy...
Put your cock in my pussy, please!
Like this?
Oh yes... I can feel you fill me up!
So deep... Feels so good...
Oh god, my pussy's
gonna split open!
- Yes...
- What?
Yes... Play with my ass...
Please, give it to me harder!
Which one?
Your pussy or your ass?
B-both... My pussy... My ass...
Feels so good...
I'm gonna cum!
Inside! L-inside! Cum inside!
I'm cumming!!
S-so hot...
Good morning.
Are you awake?
Oh, yes!
We are ready for you at breakfast.
Thank you.
Breakfast is served...
Sounds good... let's go.
Good morning. Did you
rest well last night?
Y-yes, thanks to you. And this
breakfast... I don't know what to say.
Oh, it's no trouble. I'm the mistress
of the estate, Yasue Kurashiki.
And this is the maid, Yukio Sugihara.
I'm Kenichi Sakaki, and
this is Yoshino Ogawa.
Congratulations on winning.
If you like, you can stay longer.
We'll save the bonus prize for later.
Huh?
Really? Is it okay?
Yes.
H-hey...
Why not? It's not like we're in a rush.
It's settled. Please feel free
to look around the mansion.
Well, we got delayed a bit, but why
don't you have some breakfast?
Thank you very much.
Sorry about this...
I felt the incongruity again.
Yoshino and me in this fancy house.
Last night's sex, Yoshino's behavior.
- That was good.
- Yeah...
Hello.
Are you the guests, this time?
Y-yes... and you are?
I'm Anna Kurashiki, the daughter.
I'm Yoshino, and this is Kenichi.
Hey, can I call you, Brother, Kenichi?
Oh, sure.
You two must be lovers. Yoshino,
does Brother satisfy you sexually?
Eh...?
You want more. Don't you want
him to fuck you even harder?
C-cut it out!
Don't you want to cum again and again,
and feel so good you get dizzy?
Stop it! Kenichi, let's go back!
S-sure.
What is up with that chick? Weirdo.
She was definitely odd.
Hey, Kenichi. Why don't we
have a look around the mansion?
You want to explore?
Exactly.
Nothing in here.
Scared me.
Hey, looks like there might be treasure.
Eh?
It's a gun.
Maybe it's a toy.
It's real.
H-hold on...
Kidding!
Kidding, right... Huh!?
It's just a toy.
You idiot.
Next room!
Don't forget to put that back!
Y-yeah...
Hey, wait for me! Sheesh!
Wow, look at all these books.
What's wrong?
Oh, n-nothing at all.
L-let's go to the next room!
It was a text about S & M training.
How to train people, how to raise them...
Let's go somewhere else.
Y-yeah. Let's go.
Oh, hi Brother. Yoshino.
Hey, Brother.
There's something I want to show you.
Huh? Is it something interesting?
It sure is! Very interesting.
Please?
I-I'm going to go look
at another room!
H-hey!
No you don't!
Look! Now that wasn't very nice...
Hey...
What's the matter?
Don't you want to see?
S-stop that.
Quit doing stuff like that.
Too bad!
But, there's something else
that's interesting to see.
Eh?
Yup. In a different room.
W-what are you two...!?
Oh, Master Kenichi.
See, Brother?
Isn't it interesting?
Yukio-Mama never had children,
but she gives out milk!
Hey, Brother? Don't you want
to play with Yukio-Mama too?
W-what... what the hell
is going on with them!?
W-what is this... feeling...
Yoshino!!
Can I help you?
I-I'm sorry, I'm looking for someone.
Oh, I'm Kenichi Sakaki, a guest.
I'm Tamao Shinjo. I didn't see her.
Huh?
I mean, I haven't seen anyone in the
two hours I've been practicing here.
I see. Thank you.
Hey...
Yes?
If you'd like, how about some
tea in my room, okay?
S-sure.
Your tongue... Yes, lick my pussy.
Right... there...
Yes! Please... Put it inside me.
Please...
It's so big... Yes...
Yes... feels so good...
That's so good. Oh God,
I-I'm cum... cumming...
I'm cumming!!
So, did you enjoy that?
That was great. I came by myself!
Now, it's my turn with my mouth...
I'm going to make you feel so good.
It's so thick...
Interesting flavor too...
W-what is going on with
the women in this mansion?
N-no!
That's right, Yoshino! Where is she?
Hello, is this Mr. Sakaki?
Yes.
Please wait one moment.
Are you having fun? Weren't there
a lot of interesting things to see?
Who is this?
Is this the Mistress?
That's right. Have you found
your heart's desire yet?
Huh?
Your heart's desire.
Um...
A feral soul. Torture, oppression,
rape, humiliation, violation...
W-what are you?
No matter. Let's meet again.
Y-Yoshino?
I-I'm not mistaken. T-that was
Yoshino. This is what I wanted?
This is what I wanted?
Yoshino?!
W-who's there!?
P-please, punish me.