It's so simple.
What was making me so hesitant?
It's so much fun, I can't stop!
Chapter 3: The Intricacies of SM
Anna, we're all set.
You should come too.
Okay! I can't wait!
Brother, I'm sorry to interrupt your fun,
but I arranged something even more fun.
Go down that hallway, and make a
right at the second corner,
and go through
the door in front of you.
You finally came.
Anna!
I knew you and I would be two-of-a-kind,
Brother. Let's get started.
What are you going to do?
What?
What you've been doing, Brother.
What you wanted to do. That's all.
She's being whipped, but this bitch's
pussy is already soaking wet.
Look at how deep this goes...
If it feels that good for you,
why don't I add one more.
Fantastic.
You want to do it too, right Brother?
Are you still holding back?
Come on, Brother.
Let's play together.
This filly is pretty fun to play with.
The other day, I rode her around the yard.
Alright, then I'll train her!
Give me the whip.
Not even close.
Don't stop! Don't let her rest!!
Oh my. You were having so much fun,
Brother, I forgot to tell you.
Tell me what?
Yoshino!!
Move!!
Y-Yoshino, you okay?
Hey, Yoshino, snap out of it!
Master...
W-what are you talking about?
Quit playing. Let's go home.
Let's get the hell out
of this house, Yoshino.
Yoshino! Greet your master.
Kenichi, you can't leave here now.
What!?
You should understand by now.
What it is you were seeking here.
T-that's...
A feral soul. Torture, oppression,
rape, humiliation, violation...
Now, Yoshino, show your
master the proper respect.
M-master, please punish
this dirty bitch's pussy.
I can see everything.
Your clit, your insides, your anus.
P-please...
Be kind to me...
Say it! Where and what
do you want me to do to you?
In my dirty pussy... and my ass.
Please punish them hard.
My shoe is deep inside of you,
shoving deep into your pussy.
Cum! Cum with just my foot!
Cum!!
Yoshino, your privates are soaked.
Let me get you a plug.
T-thank you very much...
Yoshino's clenching her ass so
hard my wrist might fall off.
She must be cumming.
I-I'm cum, cumming!!
Brother!
L-it's so amazing... feels like Brother's
cum is flowing inside of me...
Oh no! It's so sticky! Why are you
covering me with such filth? Yuck!
Dirty!?
Ouch!
Now it's your turn. I've been
wanting to fix that attitude...
and punish you with my meat rod!
Brother, don't misunderstand.
You are not master of the house.
If you touch me, there's no way
you and Yoshino will leave safely.
Right, mom?
That's true. You shouldn't go
against the house's master...
Of course, Yoshino won't ever choose
to leave the mansion on her own.
She was the one that picked her role.
Humiliated, teased,
satisfying all of her lust with exciting
and shocking new experiences.
Dammit!!
You win, Sakaki.
Grandfather!
Father, when did you return!?
What I do is my own business.
Who the hell are you...?
I'm Ganji Kurashiki, the master.
I've been watching your actions since
you moved into the house.
You have exceeded every expectation.
You have must have realized,
but this is the kind of place it is.
I'm getting old. If you wish it,
the new master of the house is you!
F-father, what are you saying?
I thought I was the head of the house.
Y-you're kidding.
Yasue, it's time for
Anna's lessons. Get ready!
Y-yes, I understand.
W-wait a minute!
Mother, you're kidding, right!?
Grandfather... it's a joke, right?
I'm your granddaughter! So...
But, starting now, that changes, Anna.
NO!!
Go ahead, Sakaki.
S-stop...
N-no, what are you doing, that hurts!
Oh, my mistake! I thought you were
a shoe rag, turns out it was Anna!
No! It hurts! Stop! Quit it!!
Odd. This shoe rag talks.
I'm not a shoe rag. It hurts!
Sakaki. Why not use the
one you're used to the most?
It hurts! Please help me!!
P-please help me, mother!
Go on, Kenichi. Do as you please...
M-mother?
What's the matter, Anna?
You're all wet. Want to piss?
O-of course not!
Come on, take a piss.
Spread your legs.
You're going to need punishment.
Please... stop! I'll go!!
Just a bit more...
It's coming out!
L-it's over, right?
Stop! L-it hurts, please stop!
It's digging in!
Don't swing it!! It hurts!
Please don't swing it... stop!
Anna, you're actually happy aren't you?
Your pussy is leaking juices.
Y-you're wrong! It just hurts!
Now put me down!
Okay. Well, we're going to make it
so you become more honest...
No!!
Don't hold back.
I'm just going to keep going.
I'm impressed, Sakaki.
Just as I suspected...
Please stop it!
Kenichi, please forgive her.
Anna... hold on, I'll let you down.
Father! Father,
please make him stop!
Yasue... l'm not the master any more.
Sakaki is, so ask the Master.
Y-you can't mean...
You shouldn't go against
the house's master.
Such a fitting image
of parent and child...
M-mother, it hurts.
A-Anna, be brave.
P-please stop!
M-mother?
What? Your pussy is
already this wet?
Y-you're lying, I'm not...
You're really just a slut, aren't you?
What did you do to my mother?
I'll give it to you too!
After the accessories comes the make up.
M-mother, i-it hurts.
Don't rock...
It hurts! Mother, please don't move!
You want some make up too, Anna?
N-no! Stop!
H-hot! It's too hot!
A-Anna, please don't rock...
M-mother, don't rock either.
It's digging into my pussy...
I-I can't help it.
Ouch! H-hot!
It's useless.
M-mother, what are you doing!?
A-Anna... I-I'm sorry...
Mother can't...
Be happy, Anna!
I'm making you a sibling!
Please don't! N-not today! Please!
Just not inside! Please not inside!
S-so hot... so much cum...
I really might get pregnant...
W-wow. Look at all the cum inside mom.
A-Anna. M-mother has so much
cum in her, she might have a kid.
You might get a brother or sister.
Hot!
Something this hot goes inside...
Now, let's let Anna experience it.
No, no, no! Stop. Stop it! Please!
I don't want to get pregnant! No!!
Well... looks like you're looking
forward to having cum inside you.
Y-you're wrong! Ouch! Stop!
Now, look at yourself.
It's going inside of you, you little slut.
I-I can't believe something so...
big is inside of me!
It hurts! It hurts,
please stop, Brother!
Calling complete strangers "Brother."
Shut up! You're nothing but a slut!
P-please stop!
I don't want to!
You're my pet, right?
Y-yes... I'm yours, Brother...
You mean, "Master!"
I'm my master's pet!
Well then, I'll give you my milk.
Don't cum in me!!
Don't cum inside of me!!
No, it's so hot! Pull it out.
Don't leave so much cum in me!
So much of master's
hot cum is inside of me...
With this much cum, I'm going
to get pregnant! I know I am!
But... what is this weird
feeling... I'm having?
Shame on you! You shouldn't
waste your master's milk!
This will make sure
that you don't spill.
If you do that, I really will
get pregnant! Take it off!
Get the cum out of my stomach!
Anna, what are you to me?
Your female slave...
That's right... I'm... I'm my
master's female slave...
I've been waiting to meet you,
Master, for a long... long time...
Umm, I'm sorry to come at night.
We... won a prize through Canabi?
Welcome. Congratulations on winning.
Oh! So this is the mansion
we're supposed to be at?
Yes... let me direct you to meet the master
of the house. Come this way.
Oh, sure.
Welcome to my mansion.
N-no... no!!