W-what is going on with
the women in this mansion...
N-no!
That's right, Yoshino!
Where is she?
Oh, Master Kenichi.
See, Brother? Isn't it interesting?
That you, Yoshino?
W-who's there!?
P-please... punish me...
Episode 2 "The Charm of M"
Who are you...?
I'm a guest here.
Mr. Guest, please punish me.
Give me a punishment.
I can't take it.
Please punish me.
A feral soul. Torture, oppression,
rape, humiliation, violation...
Something broke within me.
O-over here, too. Give it to me.
The w-whip! Quickly, please.
Faster, please. Faster...
Don't you mean, "Please
punish my dirty little pussy?"
P-please punish my dirty little pussy...
P-pee...
I have to pee...
Hold it in.
I-I can't, it's coming out...
I have to pee!
I said no!
This time, I'll have some fun with this!
Why you slovenly little bitch!!
More, give me more.
Please punish me more. Humiliate me.
Please, punish me some more!
Please... come back!
What the hell is wrong with me?
Why did I do that?
Anna! Have you seen the woman
I was with? Her name is Yoshino.
A-Anna! H-hey!
Brother, you ran out in the middle
last time, so let's play together now.
M-master Kenichi, h-hurry... I need it...
You mean, "Hurry, please!"
Awww, now her pussy
is as wet as her breasts...
You don't have to just look,
you can fuck her too.
Right, Yukio Mama?
Hurry. Please, I beg you.
Awww, he got away again.
I'm not myself. What is this feeling?
I've never experienced this weird feeling...
that seems to come from deep inside me.
Huh?
I've never seen you before.
And you are...?
I'm Kenichi Sakaki, I'm a guest here.
I'm Michiru Tokutake.
I'm the personal nurse here.
Are you okay?
You don't look too good.
Huh? Well...
The nurse station is nearby.
Come with me, I'll take a look at you.
I'm okay, really.
No you don't. Now, come with me.
So, how do you like the house?
Huh!? I just came because
you said I didn't look too good.
Oh, the doctor thing.
But that's not what I really am.
You get it, right?
You already know what
kind of place this is...
Hold on one moment.
Yes, okay. Alright.
I'm on my way.
I'm sorry for interrupting our talk,
but would you mind coming with me?
Excuse me, Michiru!
Why is that person here too?
The bathroom, right?
Kenichi, please help me!
I-I don't want to!!
Now, now. Don't be unreasonable.
Please, Kenichi, don't look...!
Terumi!!
Y-yes ma'am...
That's right, Terumi.
You're a nice, calm servant, aren't you?
All of them too...
Oh, Terumi, you're very damp.
Did you wet yourself?
N-no...
Is it just my imagination, or is your
sweat warmer and stickier than usual?
P-please, Michiru,
don't tease me anymore!
Okay, let's take this cloth off of you.
N-no! Please!
Okay, no more crying.
Okay, Kenichi, would you mind
straddling Terumi on that?
No! L-let me down!
No, no, I don't like this!
Terumi?
Don't struggle. If you fall,
your injuries will get even worse.
Okay, now go ahead and release.
Whenever you're ready.
Don't hold back just
because Kenichi is here.
No!!
Oh my, that was a lot, Terumi.
D-don't look. K-Kenichi!?
Okay, this time
let's clean out your ass.
N-no more...
Make those dirty sounds as
you cover the finger with saliva.
I think we're ready.
Let it out.
You want to go, right?
S-stop, don't push...
Push harder!
Still nothing?
Well then...
Let's use this.
N-no! Don't pull it out!!
No, it won't stop.
Make it stop!
Now it's my turn to have some fun.
No more...
Kenichi, maybe you misunderstood me.
She's mine!
An innocent virgin kitten.
She's not someone you can just touch...
unless you were the Master.
By the way, weren't you looking
for someone? Was it Yoshino?
Better find her fast, or there's no
telling what might happen to her.
What do you mean?
Who knows?
More importantly,
shouldn't you be going now?
Dammit!
No! Stop it!
Y-Yoshino!?
H-hey, Yoshino! Yoshino!
Let go of me! Let go!!
Calm down, Mr. Sakaki.
Look more closely.
Tamao!
What's the meaning of this?
An order from the Mistress.
It's a present for you.
She's a vulgar bitch,
but feel free to discipline her.
Torture, oppression, rape,
humiliation, violation...
Huh, what was that?
Shut up!!
Awww, you spilled the water.
You'll have to be punished.
Maybe then your attitude will change
to that of the dog that you are.
Let's begin.
What's the matter, huh?
Master Kenichi, perhaps you
should take a break.
After all, you can't have fun
with her if you break her.
Care for some vodka?
It's a bit strong.
Yes, let me enjoy this slowly.
I sure got pissed on a lot today.
Hey, take that ball gag off of her.
K-Kenichi, why are you...
Are you... are you one of them?
I still don't like your attitude!
Don't you mean, "Master?"
N-no, don't...
P-please Master.
L-let's stop doing this...
You sure you want me to stop?
Look at your reflection.
You're enjoying this.
You get off on pain!
Stop!! D-don't move it!!
You're nothing but a bitch
who gets off on pain, right?
Y-yes...
No! Stop! Please don't
open it inside me!
More! Feel it more!
So... h-hot...
She completely loves it now.
I finally accepted it.
My true nature within me...
? The horse goes galloping...?
Your master will be here, soon.