I am God.
The People from the world
of Light and Shadow, listen to my words.
I've created light as well as darkness,
but that's not the final state.
One day you will finally get
a complete state.
Before that day comes,
I have built this in steel...
to divide the world
into light and shadow.
This is the story of Persia and April.
They are the swordswomen
from the Race of Light.
Another adventure of light and shadow.
Full of love and courage.
WORDSWORTH
No!
Stop!
Stop it!
Such pretty little titties.
Nobody is going to marry me now!
Norman! Norman!
Norman, I am so sorry.
Norman, I'm sorry!
It's never felt so good.
Stop it! No!
Push, harder. Harder!
Yes! Yes!
I'm coming!
Stop pretending that you don't like it.
I know you do.
Feel the horsepower.
Let me go, don't do that.
No.
Don't be rude to me please,
don't hurt me! Please.
No.
Please, please don't.
Norman, I'm sorry.
I may not be able to see you again,
please forgive me.
You may do it anyway you like.
But this is my very first time.
Please.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm going to lose my virginity...
but that's what I've been guarding.
What a beautiful pussy.
Look at that. What a pussy.
How embarrassing.
Embarrassing.
Yeah!
This is great!
What are you talking about, new stuff?
That's the two of us.
You bad boy,
you make us become crazy like this.
You bad thing.
I haven't touched a good guy
like this for a long time.
Are you feeling horny, honey?
Yeah.
I've got to keep my head.
What do you want?
Nothing. I just want you
to be yourself.
Be downright myself?
You're the same as that monster.
All you want...
I'm going to lose my virginity.
Yes.
It feels so good, so good.
So good!
No, it hurts!
So good.
Don't stop. No, don't stop.
What a big cock!
No! It hurts, it hurts!
No!
It hurts, do it faster, faster!
Yes!
It hurts but feels so good.
Harder! Harder!
Much better, much better.
So good.
I'm coming!
Don't stop!
Yes!
Miss Sabrina! No don't!
Thought you were fleeing
from the enemy?
But you actually cast eyes
at the man from the Race of Light!
But, that man was injured.
Don't feel sympathy for our enemies!
Don't forget, we are on the battlefield!
No!
You keep saying no,
but look, it has gotten so wet!
How many times I've told you?
On the battlefield,
you've got to forget yourself as a woman.
You don't understand
if you're being sensible down there!
No, don't stop.
Stop it, no, I can't take it.
How are you going to do if you've such
bad stamina and endurance?
Be patient, and hang on!
No!
Not that.
Right, very good, hang on
you're going to be a real fighter.
And now this, how does it feel?
Being a fighter of the Race of Light...
- I've got to keep hanging on.
- Persia, let's fight.
Miss Sabrina...
How does it feel this way?
I've got to hang on. Yes!
Now you do it to me!
No, do it like this.
Yes!
Let me try it.
Right, yeah, harder Persia, do it harder.
I can't stand it anymore.
Be downright myself.
Yes, I must not be eligible
for being a swordsman.
I've better go home
and wait for Norman there.
Goodbye!
What a strange woman.
How many times have I screwed?
Wow. That's so cool!
How far down must it go?
That's kind of scary.
I think a battle just broke out.
The main-force units of Fabrees
has begun their prime formation of attack.
Now hurry up! We've got to meet Fabrees.
Yes!
You humans are weird,
but so entertaining.
You claim that you have
a love of your fellow man...
and yet at the same time
you want to kill each other.
I would love to stay and watch
the swelling scene...
but unfortunately, I'd be suspected.
So off I go.
I've got to seduce him into leading
me to the ultimate destination.
The road of self-destruction.
What the hell?
That thing is cool,
but it's dangerous.
He looks strong.
Hope I don't need to fight him later.
Look at that pasty-faced old man
just came out of nowhere!
It's Shalom!
Can't get down from here.
I don't know. That old man
was able to get down from here.
Does this path lead to the Race of Light?
Who cares?
I better get to Shalom soon.
So, here it is.
Do you really think I would let you pass
from here and get to Fabrees?
How come the doors are closed?
You're trapped!
Look, the sister
on the wooden horse is back!
Shut up!
Mister Esterla.
Didn't you fall off the mountain?
But how did you get here
ahead of us?
You wouldn't believe
all the things that happened.
Who cares?
I'll kill all those who hinder my way!
Now and in the future!
I'm telling you,
and now you've been warned.
Damn you! I'm going to kill you.
Miss Sabrina!
Damn it Persia, don't forget our deal?
Persia, promise you won't forget
what I said...
you won't forget the deal we made
the other day.
Certainly not, and I won't escape
from the enemy ever again, I promise.
Then go and do it!
Beat the enemy, beat the Race
of Shadow. Beat them for me.
Yes!
Mister Esterla, prepare to die!
You bastard!
If you are a swordsman,
then you better battle it out like one!
Persia.
Come on! Do it, just kill me!
And get it over with.
You're not any good at fighting
or battles anyhow.
That's caused by the cannon
that's outside.
Watch out!
Mr. Esterla!
Miss Sabrina!
Persia, don't you forget our deal?
Go and beat down
the Race of Shadow.
Persia!
You are so tender.
My name is Esterla, what's yours?
Watch out!
I can't do it.
I just can't.
What's happening?
Mr. Esterla will also train me
to become a swordsman like him?
No, don't.
No, what are you doing to me?
Come on, you don't need to be
so reluctant, I'll be gentle.
Don't worry about it, you can make
as much noise as you want.
What a shame!
You can't become a swordsman this way.
Have to hang on...
I've got to stand the test.
Please get it in me!
I can't stand it anymore!
Give it to me.
I need it!
Give me more.
So, you really can take this?
That's beautiful,
let me make it get wetter.
I don't care at all,
I just want more!
Yes! Yes!
Okay, how about this?
No, don't do that.
You can't.
It's so warm, it's so hot inside you,
that's great.
It's the very first time and I'm going
to stand the test. I can do it!
It's great. Come on, go faster!
It's great to be a swordsman. Yes!
I love to be a swordsman.
I love to be a swordsman!
Don't stop!
I'm coming!
What am I going to do?
How am I going to get this door open?
He's got to leave.
I can't stop him from going.
But I can't teach the enemy...
the secret to the location
of the key that opens the door.
What should I do?
Yeah!
I can pretend to be talking in my sleep.
The jewel on Ms. Sabrina's sword hilt
is the key to open the door.
Thank you very much.
Dear Mister Esterla.
Go!
Good luck, Mr. Esterla!
Good Luck.
I am God.
People from the world of Light and Shadow,
listen to my words...
I've created light as well as darkness,
but that's not the final state.
One day you will finally
get a complete state.
Before the day comes,
I have built this in steel.
To divide this world
into light and shadow.