Fullscale attack!
The Tribe of Light is attacking us again!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Your breasts are so soft....
This man....
You're pushing it in again!
Damn beast!
Sir Astral!
I have to run!
What are you doing, sir?
Where is my ring?
It's true.
What are you talking about?
It's true!
There's nobody in there!
Step aside,
or we'll report you to the Great King.
What happened to that girl?
We are searching for Sir Astral
following Sir Wartoshika's orders.
Oops, this is bad!
What horsepower he's got!
You're so desperate,
you must be hiding something in here!
Huh? lt's true.
Go! Kill off the Tribe of Shadows
once and for all!
Die! You are all going to die!
What?
They came from the East Gate this time?
lt seems like a fullscale attack,
led by a giant machine.
Damn, the Tribe of Light
never learns its lesson!
Caesar and Sharon!
Yes, sir!
Gather the entire force!
We shall welcome them with full force!
Yes, sir!
l wonder why the Tribe of Light
is attacking us again so soon.
Could it be they have learned
the secret of the Words Worth Tablet?
Then l have to tell Astral the secret
of the Tablet as soon as possible!
Then l shall go look for Sir Astral myself.
Go!
Yes, sir!
Stop it! What are you doing to me,
l'm a prisoner!
Do we have to tell you?
lt's unfair, Sir Stallion
is the only one enjoying the girls!
Right, Brother?
Yeah, you've got nice tits.
Don't! No!
Bro, this girl's crying.
She's crying with joy
because we're so good.
How would l enjoy something this awful?
She's dripping so much. Slut!
Bro, do you think the Ladies of Light
have big pussies?
How would l know?
How could that be? We're all the same!
Then, Bro.
Yo!
lt hurts!
What're you doing?
We're going to check how big
you can take it in there.
No! Don't!
First, Sir Caesar's size.
Because you are attacking us,
we're too busy even to take a break.
How could we get by
without a perk like this?
Right, Bro?
Yo.
You started the war.
You destroyed the Words Worth Tablet.
We don't care for something
that happened so long ago.
We're just enjoying this moment!
Next, Sir Astral's size.
l'm melting!
This girl knows how to use her tongue.
Please, don't!
Sir Stallion's size. This will ruin her.
Before this makes her pussy too loose,
l'll use my own.
Bro, let me have the first taste.
Yo!
Don't come inside of her!
l'm going to use her, too!
Thank you for the dinner!
Miss Maria.
Silverna, are you all right?
You saved me. Thank you.
l cannot forgive these men
of the Tribe of Shadows!
I will never forgive that one man.
Who could make you so angry?
Who is this unfortunate bastard?
Astral.
That's what they called him.
The next time l see him,
l will use my magic and turn him into dust.
Oh, no! That's a little too much....
Yes, l absolutely will!
Someone!
Miss Maria.
l will go and free the captured men.
We'll attack them
from behind their defense line.
lf you could report it to
Sir Fabris coming in from the East Gate.
l will.
There he comes. There he comes!
Here you go!
Help me!
l did it!
Sir Fabris!
That idiot! So conceited.
Here they come!
The most powerful swordsmen of
the Shadows, Sir Caesar and Miss Sharon!
Finally, my worthy opponents!
l've been waiting for you!
Huh? There's nobody here.
Maybe they've all gone to
the Higher Levels?
l worked so hard to get the
Swordsman's Seal and now it's useless.
lf l have to climb all the way up,
l'll be exhausted before l get to the battle.
Sir Astral.
Hide? l see you're joining the battle, too.
Yes, after all, l'm a swordsman, too.
But l'm worried l might
just be a bother to everybody.
l don't think so.
Hide, you're quick and agile,
so you won't lose to the Tribe of Light.
Thank you. l'm just not confident.
You just need to do your best.
You're so right. Now that you've
talked to me, l feel more courageous.
What's wrong?
Just a little something....
Hide, go ahead of me.
See you later.
That was Nina, wasn't it?
That's Nina!
Welcome, cute girl.
No! Leave me alone!
Don't be ridiculous.
Why do you think l bothered to come out?
Stay away!
No!
No, help me!
How is it? You can't move, can you?
Soon your body will be cold,
and there will be no pain, no suffering.
l'm cold.
So? Do you like it?
When you can no longer feel cold or pain...
...l shall suck up all your energy and life.
Do you like it?
l'm cold.
Nina!
Sir Astral!
Nina, are you all right?
Sir Astral, l'm cold.
Get a hold of yourself,
Nina, don't fall asleep!
Oh, Sir Astral!
Good, you are awake now.
Sir Astral, you're so warm.
Nina.
Sir Astral, how long will this war go on?
Probably until either
the Tribe of Light or all of us die.
Why do we have to fight the Tribe of Light?
l've seen many people
from the Tribe of Light.
They don't look all that bad.
l agree.
We may be of different races,
but they must laugh and talk and cry...
...just like we do, l think.
Yes, the girls of the Tribe of Light
do smile and shed tears.
They have the same warm bodies
like you do.
Sir Astral.
How come you know
the girls of the Tribe of Light are warm?
l'm sorry.
Sir Astral, l feel something hard
against my tummy.
That's my bad boy.
He woke up with your warmth.
l'm sorry, Nina.
l love you, Sir Astral.
l know Miss Sharon lives in your heart.
But l don't care.
Even if you love Miss Sharon,
l still love you.
Nina.
Please don't say anything, Sir Astral.
Sir Astral.
Nina.
Sir Astral, l'm afraid.
How can l take something this big
inside me?
You don't need to worry. Here we go.
Yes, okay.
lt hurts!
Sir Astral.
Sir Astral. lt feels so good.
Meow!
Where is Astral?
l didn't find him in the castle.
Sir Wartoshika!
Did you find him?
Some have seen him earlier at
the swordfight training center, but....
Could it be he's obtained
a Swordsman's Seal?
Could he be heading for the East Gate?
What?
l must tell Astral
where the Tablet fragments are hidden!
We must not let Astral die!
Bring back Astral right away! Go!
Nina, why don't you take
a safe passage and go back?
You mustn't come
to dangerous places like this.
Yes, but l thought this was
the only way to catch up with you.
Catch up with me?
Yes.
l just couldn't help worrying about you.
But l'm not worried anymore.
l will be waiting for you.
For ever and ever.
Caesar!
Damn you, Fabris!
Sharon!
You seem like a strongwilled bitch!
You're worth raping!
Here l come!
Good! l like your determination!
You're stronger than Caesar.
But you're still no match for me!
Too bad, if you trained with me,
you'd be as strong as Pollux!
Pollux? The Legendary Swordsman?
The man was known as
the best swordsman of the Tribe of Light.
Pollux.
Just about the time when
l became a worthy swordsman myself...
...he disappeared.
And he became a legend.
You look better without those.
Now l have to fuck you.
Bullshit!
Who would sleep with you?
Enough playing around.
Kill me!
Huh! l can't kill you yet.
Then l shall kill myself.
Then l dare you to kill yourself.
You can't dare kill yourself
until you have killed me.
l can see that in your eyes.
Sharon!
Don't you find it entertaining to
fuck our brains out amidst this bloodbath?
Kill me!
Only when l have
no more use for your body.
l shall torture you to death!
Damn kid!
Hide!
lt's you, Hide?
Sir Astral.
Who did this to you?
A man in silver armor.
Guess l wasn't quite quick
and agile enough to evade his dagger.
Don't worry about me, Sir Astral.
Please go help Sharon.
What about Sharon?
Hold on to yourself, Hide!
No, don't worry about me. l'm very sleepy.
No, Hide! You can't fall asleep here!
Wake up! l said, wake up!
Sir Astral, take care.
Hide!
Stop joking! You're kidding, right?
Hey, wake up! Hide.
Hide!
Where am l?
How does a Shadow girl taste?
Don't!
Maria?
Stop it already, Father, no, Sir Fabris.
l shall avenge Hide!
Damn you! l'll kill you!
Astral?
Sharon!
Astral, stay away!
Pollux! You can't be?
That man!
Pollux cannot be alive!
Sharon, quick, take Caesar!
No, you have to come with us.
l have to kill this bastard.
Okay, don't die, Astral.
l'll come back with
reinforcements right away.
Father!
No!
You hurt not only me, but my father, too!
l'll kill you! l'll turn you into dust!
Calm down, Maria!
You mustn't use that power!
No!
Even if the almighty God
may forgive him, l will not!
l'll make sure he'll never appear
before me for ever and ever!
But you said you liked it back then.
Shut up!
That's what my body said
against my own will!
That's ridiculous.
Do you think l enjoyed having
a Shadow man's nasty thing inside me?
Now, you bastardturnedbeast!
You will be erased from this world!
Mystral Window!
Where am l?
Who am l?