Must be this way.
The passage is sealed. This must be it.
The crystal key.
What's going on?
Mystral Window!
Who was that girl? She looked like Mew.
What happened in my past?
Who's there?
l've been waiting for you, Pollux.
Who are you?
Your guide to the Land of Darkness.
The Land of Darkness?
What are you doing?
Don't be afraid.
Cutie boy.
No, don't....
Pollux.
Come over. Here, inside me.
That's it.
You're so good.
Right there.
lncredible.
What the heck...?
l can't wait anymore.
So good. More, more.
Amazing. What is it, why here?
So good. Harder, harder.
Do it hard, tear me apart.
More, more, pump harder.
So good. Much harder.
So good. Pollux's sword
is powerful and incredible.
l'm coming.
Good, so good, Pollux.
Damn! l was so close!
Damn this monster!
l won't let you get away!
Damn!
l can't think clearly. Thank you.
That was a close call.
ls that monster
from the Tribe of Shadows?
No. She said something about
the Land of Darkness.
The Land of Darkness? What is that?
Hey! Put on some clothes!
Sorry.
lt doesn't make sense.
Could there be a land
other than Light and Shadows?
Well, anyway.
l'm Rita. Are you the famous Pollux?
Now that you mention it,
you do look like that statue.
By the way, what are you doing here?
What?
l'm a Swordswoman of Light.
l figure, if l follow you,
l might win some fame.
What was that earthquake?
There will be a war again.
What?
That child can't be
a mix of Light and Shadows.
Either way, we have to do something.
ls this it?
ls this the Passage that connects
the Lands of Light and Shadows?
Looks like it.
Shall we?
Hold on a sec. l'll report this to Sir Fabris.
Let's go.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
l'm trembling with excitement.
A war again.
Sir Pollux.
What? The passage is cleared?
Yes, sir! Miss Rita
has just sent us a report.
She says Sir Pollux
broke the Seal of the Passage.
Pollux did....
This is the time for a showdown!
Round up the entire army!
We will attack the Land of Shadows
once and for all!
Who's there? A swordsman of Light?
We won't let you step
into the Land of Shadows!
Have l fought in this place before?
Finally, they're here!
Damn the Tribe of Light!
l shall kill them all once and for all!
Everybody, we shall attack them!
Sharon! l have to talk to you.
l can't wait anymore.
When this battle is over, l will
talk to Sir Wartoshika about you and me.
Caesar, you are a good man.
But l still don't feel it.
Are you still in love with Astral?
That bastard died 20 years ago!
Caesar.
l just can't forget that day when...
...that weak and indecisive Astral
came to save my life.
Sharon!
Astral! Stay away!
l don't want to believe he's dead.
l'm sorry, Caesar.
Astral died. Forget him, Sharon.
Attack!
Fire!
Damn, they have sentinels.
l think that hole will lead us
into the Underground Castle.
This way we won't waste our time
in battle to sneak into their headquarters.
You're not only a great swordsman,
but smart, too.
But how come you knew about this?
l have a vague memory of
wandering around here a long time ago.
That's weird.
Nobody could get in here for 20 years.
l know that.
But l don't remember anything
about 20 years ago.
That's such a long time ago
even l don't remember anything.
Let's go!
Sharon, this is bad.
Let's fall back to the West Gate
and regroup.
Agreed! We know the geography better.
We can fight back once we get back there.
Listen, everybody!
We'll need to buy time to regroup.
Once we've all crossed the chasm,
we'll blow up the bridge!
Yes, ma'am!
How long is this air duct?
l have no idea.
This is so tiring. Hey, is that the exit?
lt looks bright.
l don't think that's it.
Oops! Shit!
Pervert! What are you doing?
l'm sorry. You just stopped so suddenly.
What's wrong?
Look.
This is bad. Let's go back.
The explosives are ready.
Good. Let's blow it up now!
Yes, sir!
Soldier of Light!
The air duct!
They're coming in through the air duct!
Fire into it!
Oh, no!
This way! This way!
He's fleeing! Capture him!
We'll get you!
He can't be....
l see.
So they've pushed us back
to the West Gate.
Yes, sir.
Sir Wartoshika, where to?
Don't follow me. l want to be alone.
You're done reporting,
go back to the battlefield!
Yes, sir!
Dimwit.
l lose him around here every time.
Now l see.
Oh, no!
Well done.
Damn Wartoshika, how far is he going?
This is bad.
Soon he'll complete
the Words Worth Tablet.
This is bad.
l have to call back Menza right away.
Oh, my, l got separated from Pollux.
What can l do now?
Who are you?
Are you of the Tribe of Shadows?
l'm Wartoshika,
the King of the Tribe of Shadows.
Oh, that's....
That means l'm lucky.
l'll defeat you and l'll be a hero.
How brave of you.
But would it be so easy?
Come on!
What happened to your earlier bravery?
l'm coming to you now!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Shit!
What's up? ls that it?
Go ahead! Kill me now!
No regrets now to be killed
by the King of Shadows!
What a noble woman.
Too bad you are a Swordswoman of Light.
What're you doing?
You are so brave.
You will bear fine children.
What?
Now that Astral has disappeared...
...l have no choice but to mate with you...
...and produce
the One Who Mixes Light and Shadows...
...since you're from the Tribe of Light.
What are you mumbling about?
Don't! Just because l'm a woman....
Stop!
Don't!
l am a Swordswoman of Light!
l have no use for a man!
Stop. l don't....
Not there....
No....
lt feels good.
Stop it.
l'm going crazy.
Good. lt feels so good.
l'm scared. lt's so big.
You'll tear me apart.
You'll be fine.
Now that you're this wet.
lt hurts!
No, it hurts!
Bear with me. Relax a little.
lt hurts! No! Please stop!
You are hurting me!
lf you do this to me...
...l can't go back to the Land of Light.
Then you can stay here forever.
lt hurts, please stop!
Do we have to do more?
More and more, until you bear the child,
a mix of Light and Shadows.
You're tearing me apart.
l'm hot.
So hot.
Hot.
lt hurts.
l'm so hot.
lt feels good.
My body's going weird.
So good.
l'm coming, Sir Wartoshika!
Look at the Words Worth Tablet.
ls this it? l heard
it was smashed into pieces.
l have picked up the fragments
and reconstructed it this far.
The tradition says this:
''lf you read this Tablet,
you will understand everything.
''But it can be read only by
One Who Mixes Light and Shadows.
''And this one shall bring on a New World.''
Exactly! Therefore....
We can't allow that to happen.
Tessio?
Menza?
How come the Commander
of the Tribe of Light is here?
What?
l'll show you why!
Damn monster!
Die, Wartoshika!
l never imagined there'd be one
so skilled among the Swordsmen of Light.
But this is it!
That sword....
Sharon!