The I am the voice of God.
The people of the world of Light
and Shadow, listen to my words...
I've created light as well as darkness,
but that's not the final state.
One day, you will finally get
to a complete state.
Before the day comes...
I have built it in steel.
This is the story of Persia and April.
They are the swordswomen
from the Race of Light.
Another adventure of light and shadow.
Full of love and courage.
WORDS WORTH
Norman, are you all right?
My shoulder seems to be hurt.
But it's no big deal, really.
If we win this war, April,
then I'll marry you.
I am so happy, Norman.
Damn!
Those dudes from the Race of Light.
How can they do this on the battlefield?
I will go and get some water.
Please.
Damn, I must do this.
I must succeed. I will.
I am dying.
What?
April!
I'm so bored.
I sure wish there was something
interesting going on here.
I think I heard someone's voice.
I guess it's around here somewhere.
Stop it!
Is it around here?
Yes, I definitely heard it!
A girl.
What it is?
No one's watching.
I'm going in.
Come on, Say it!
Say it quickly.
Wow, she's a cute girl.
Miss Sabrina!
Stop it! What do you want?
Here we go.
Stop it! Why are you doing this?
Say it! Say it quickly!
So what are you trying to
make me say anyway?
What should we ask?
Lets have a look, shall we!
What do you want me to do to anyway?
We want like Lord Stallion,
to have happy memories.
Or should I say mammaries?
It's good to have happy mammaries.
I mean memories.
How do I get this damn armor off?
It's bloody hell.
The one who caused this war
is your Race of Shadow.
We don't want to leave you in the dark.
Stop it!
Honestly, you just got to love
the perks of this job!
What?
Stop it!
That screaming!
That strong Miss Sabrina.
It's hard to imagine how she suffers
from that painful torture.
Miss Sabrina.
What an admirable girl she is!
There's a voice coming from there too.
There.
Stop!
Look! She's so wet.
I'd say from here that
her titties are pretty great.
You're torturing me!
I can't hold it any more!
I'm going to give you 50 lashes
with my tongue!
Titties!
So good!
Love those titties.
Save some for me.
I'm getting in now.
Come on, hurry up!
Yeah, really good.
It hurts!
Harder!
You suck! Too weak! Come on!
Harder! Push harder!
She isn't here.
Where did April go anyway?
There's the smell of blood, Gua!
Gua! That's the swordsman
of The Race of Light.
How come he is here?
Here goes!
I can't give up,
I have to find April.
I swear I'll find you.
What do you want?
I can tell you are the swordsman
from Race of Light.
So what?
I have more important matters
to tend to.
I don't have time to play
kid's game with you.
A kid's game? Why, I ought to...
Now who's playing around?
Want me to compete with a monster?
I don't have time.
You've got plenty of time.
What's your hurry, boy?
I spy a fly.
Wow! It's a woman. Yeah!
Norman?
That wasn't very nice!
You're a female swordsman
from the Race of Light.
So what?
What are you going to do about it?
I'll tell you,
I'm going to molest you good!
No! Stop!
Let me go!
No!
- Take a look at that.
- No!
She looks like...
She looks very satisfied.
It's impossible!
Because she had just been
cruelly tortured, by all these...
Just to save the immature me...
who almost got caught
by the cruel enemy.
Then...
No! Stay away from me!
You're the type of girl I like.
Where are you going to go now?
Get off, I can't breathe!
Get off!
This one hasn't got mature yet.
Not quite ripe and we like it.
It's painful!
No, help!
Stop!
Let me go!
Tastes like a virgin to me!
No, not there!
He's doing it one more time.
But this Stallion dude,
in a wartime like this...
he can still take that so easy,
I really admire him.
Is there anyone much stronger here?
Persia!
Help me. No! Stop!
Hey! Leave her alone!
You asshole horse!
Your words arouse me,
come and get it baby!
Miss Sabrina!
Look at me!
Yeah, baby.
The scent of a woman.
All right! I'm coming!
- You ignorant guy!
- Miss Sabrina, no!
Persia. Are you okay?
Thank goodness!
Persia!
Miss Sabrina!
Stop! Stop it!
Allow me to keep you
abreast of the situation.
Have you ever heard of toad in the hole?
Yeah, baby!
No one would want to marry me!
How about this?
What?
No! Stop it!
No!
Stop!
Please, no!
Norman! Help me!
Simmer down.
No!
You're getting wet.
So why do you think you'd be caught
by that kind of an enemy?
I'm sorry!
For that kind of thing.
For being a swordsman in our Ray of Light.
Even for just being women.
If we get frustrated
with being a swordsman...
we have to overcome it.
It hurts!
Only this level,
no need to scream so loud.
This is called the love
of teacher and student, right?
Or perhaps my dear,
there is a deeper reason?
What do you want,
you peeping freakazoid?
I've come here for the little girl.
Stallion likes mature women,
But he prefers the little ones better.
My God, you're a stupid asshole!
Don't stare at me with such a terrible face!
- Shut up!
- My bones are breaking apart!
Come on girl, let's escape now!
Yes!
Wow! That's so cool!
Yeah, getting froggy with it.
I can't take it any more!
You'll want me to do it to you again!
It feels so strange.
But it's a good strange.
It's the first time I feel it this way!
- I'll bet.
- I can't take it any more.
It feels so good!
No!
So good!
Norman!
Who am I going to
horse around with today?
What?
Stallion, you're just in time.
I've got a splitting headache.
You stupid bone head!
How can you let them escape?
Quickly.
Yes!
I've got to climb up there, anyway.
But will Norman take me,
after my body has been tortured like that?
So, all is going well.
Obviously, it's because human beings
are a warlike race.
Why would Swordsman from the
Race of Light would come here?
I'm unsure as to whether
she heard us or not.
I don't know, either.
But the war is so serious.
It's only a step to let them
destroy each other...
we've got to be very careful,
It's a bit tricky.
Being a staff officer
in the Race of Light...
I'm not sure it's appropriate
for me to be here.
I will leave the rest up to you.
Miss, How do you feel?
Another monster!
Won't let you go!
What a tough guy to deal with!
Wait! My engines revving, baby.
Want to feel some horse power?
This way!
Looks like he got the same brain
like a horse or a donkey.
If we both run away together
it would be too easy to be seen.
They can see me first okay.
Understand me?
Good girl!
Two swordswomen and a horse head
man are out there.
Has anyone seen them?
No, I haven't seen them.
I didn't see anyone.
If you did, then you should leave them alone.
You want to try some new stuff?
New stuff?
What are you talking about?
That means the two of us.
Wow!
What?
You bad thing!
You make us act crazy like this.
Hey, what are you...
Haven't touched a good guy like this
for a long time.
Feeling horny, honey?
Hey, where did that saucy little virgin go?
Don't they like to ride ponies?
No!
Yeah, that one's really my type.
No.
No!
No, it's the Stallion. This is trouble!
Well, hello dolly!
No!
After the frog and the snake.
Here comes the horse monster!
If you hadn't have said that I was going
to be more tender to you.
No! I don't want it!
What kind of country is this?
No!
There are creatures in this place as well.
If you had more space,
your life would be better.
It's true!
On that side around the bog.
That's really a shame.
No!
No! Stop!
How dare you deny the Stallion.
Now I'm going to graze your pasture.
No!
Stop! Stop!
Yeah?
You're resistance is futile,
your just making me more horny.
No!
Pretty little titties.
How come all these monsters...
No!
It becomes so strange down there.
Nobody is ever going to marry me now.
Norman! Norman!
I'm sorry, Norman!
Feels so good!
It feels so good.
No, stop. Stop it!
Please, it feel so good!
Push harder.
Harder. Push.
I'm coming!
Are you feeling all right?
Cheer up!
It's all right!
I thought you were going to die.
This is...
It's not a big deal.
You were that girl, thank you.
Because of you, I feel so much better.
Are you leaving?
Yes!
You are the swordsman
from the Race of Light.
And I am from the Race of Shadow.
Please don't say so.
I don't know what to do, either.
You are so tender.
My name is Esterla.
What's yours?
Mr. Esterla.
My name is Persia.
Persia, you say?
What are you doing, Persia?
Miss Sabrina?
The sister on the wooden horse.
What?
He is from the Race of Shadow, right?
He was hurt.
Don't feel sorry for our enemy!
Drop dead, you Race of Shadow!