l never imagined there'd be one
so skilled among the Swordsmen of Light.
But this is it!
That sword....
Sharon!
Die, Wartoshika!
Damn monster!
Come on, Black Fog!
Dark Wind!
Mother?
Darkness has returned.
Sir Pollux. Mother!
l'm going.
Go then, Mew.
Your ring shall protect you.
Mother.
The sand must have absorbed the impact.
This girl....
l can almost remember....
Could that be?
Where does he think he's going?
What is this?
What's this? This view. I've seen it before.
l'm....
Damn, what're you doing here?
This room belongs to Astral!
Astral?
Damn you!
Sharon?
Sharon, it's me.
l'm Astral.
Astral?
Liar. You're lying.
l'm not lying. lt's me.
You really are Astral.
Tell me l'm not dreaming.
Tell me you are Astral.
Yes.
Damn bastards of Shadows!
ls there any other way in?
Find one! Find a way to their territory!
Must be this way. l sense evil.
Oh, Astral.
You are alive. Oh, Astral.
l'm so glad l've lived.
l lost my memory and l was
wandering through the Land of Light.
This is like a dream, Astral.
How l wished to see you again.
l've been praying every day.
Sharon. l've so wanted to see you.
Please. Come.
Sharon.
l'm sorry.
lt's okay, don't worry about me.
Come to me.
Sharon.
Astral.
lncredible. l've been waiting
for this for 20 years.
Tell me this is not a dream.
When have you become
this powerful and strong?
Sharon, l love you.
Oh, Astral.
l'm going crazy. More, more, stroke me.
So good. When did you become this wild?
Sharon.
So good, Astral, more, more.
Astral, l'm coming.
l'm coming.
Astral, please come with me.
Yeah.
How pathetic you are, Wartoshika!
Enough playing around.
Get ready to die.
We'll kill you both...
...and shatter the Words Worth Tablet
to smithereens again.
lt'll never be rebuilt again!
Who the hell are you two?
We're the Rulers of Darkness!
Sir Wartoshika!
Look at the lovebirds!
We shall taste that girl as well!
Damn you.
That must be the Underground Castle.
An Agent of Darkness?
When you were lost
in that battle 20 years ago...
...l realized for the first time
l was in love with you.
l've searched for your mirage.
l came to this room every day.
Sharon.
Let's go meet everyone.
Astral!
Who is it?
Delta.
l'm not taking a roundabout approach
this time.
Astral!
l've got you!
That was Delta,
but she wasn't acting like Delta.
Freeze, Pollux!
l've got you!
Prepare to die!
Sir Pollux!
Astral!
Evil of Darkness, leave this place!
Mystral Window!
Astral!
Sir Pollux!
Astral, are you all right?
Sir Pollux, come back to us!
Astral.
Pollux.
Ouch.
Mew, Sharon....
This is bad!
What are you guys doing over there?
Delta?
Ouch. What have l been doing?
Oh no! lt's an emergency!
Tessio was meeting
the Commander of the Land of Light...
...to discuss how to destroy
both the Lands of Light and Shadows.
What?
Those two are probably the source of evil...
...that destroyed the Words Worth Tablet
to bring Darkness to this world!
Delta, take us to where you saw them.
Sir Fabris!
We've found what looks like an air duct.
We suspect it may lead to their territory.
What? Tell that to the whole army!
We'll seize their headquarters at once!
Stop it!
How tight she is.
Produce the One Who Mixes
Light and Shadows? Don't make us laugh.
We shall scrape out your seed in here.
Stop it!
No!
Nobody's here.
Shush, l hear voices.
Sir Astral!
Nina?
Am l dreaming?
You're not dreaming.
l'm getting you out of there now.
Sir Astral.
Do they know each other?
Looks like it. Looks like more than that.
Sir Astral! How l've longed to see you!
She's hugging him!
Now he's holding her tight!
Mother, who is this?
Ariadonne, this is your father.
Daddy?
What did she say?
His daughter?
Mystral
Watch out for the water!
Sir Astral!
Mother!
No. Stop!
We've had Light and Shadows
fighting each other for years...
...and everything was going as we planned.
But thanks to you,
we have to speed up our plans.
Shut up!
l won't let you get away with this!
What can you do now?
Damn you!
The Words Worth Tablet!
l knew it was you, the Tribe of Shadows!
Damn monster!
They are the ones that destroyed
the Words Worth Tablet!
The Rulers of Darkness!
What?
We have the Kings
of Light and Shadows together.
We shall kill them all once and for all!
Damn you!
Die!
That man!
Astral!
Pollux!
Damn!
Mystral Window!
Damn you, how dare you?
We'll blow everything away
and turn this into a Land of Nothing!
Mew, give me your power.
Dark Wind!
Finally it's over.
Sir Astral!
l never imagined
l was from the Land of Light.
lf it is true, he should be much older.
No. That ring you are wearing....
lt gives you the same ''Time'' as we have.
l kidnapped you from
the Tribe of Light when you were a baby...
...to produce
the One Who Mixes Light and Shadows.
I was determined to find out
the secret of Words Worth Tablet.
Pollux....
Astral's father, was his name Pollux?
l don't know that.
His features, his swordsmanship...
...Pollux's mysterious
and sudden disappearance....
lf so, then all of this makes sense.
Had we known about
the presence of Darkness...
...we could have
spared ourselves of meaningless wars.
Sir Wartoshika!
Meaningless wars....
One more piece.
Can l have this?
Yeah.
Look at the Tablet inscription.
What does it say?
l've never seen this language.
''l am God. Tribes of Light and Shadows.''
l see! This is child is
the One Who Mixes Light and Shadows.
''Listen to me.''
You mustn't read it!
How could we lose to a mere child?
lf only Wartoshika had not kidnapped
a baby from the Tribe of Light.
lf only he had not tried to have
him read the Words Worth Tablet.
We were so close to destroying all of you.
Our bodies are going.
''l created Light.
''And l created the Darkness
at the same time.
''But these are not your final forms.''
What is that blue ceiling up there?
''One day...
''...you two shall be complete.''