Mystral Window!
Where am l?
Who am l?
Once again, Light and Shadow were
divided, and 20 years have passed.
Wow, he looks like Sir Pollux!
He sure does!
Pollux?
Hurry, hurry.
He's smiling! Sir Pollux is smiling!
He sure is! He is smiling!
I can't remember. Who am I?
Beautiful.
I never knew I was
such an incredible swordsman.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Were you hurt?
Oh, yes, no, please....
Please, do not get any closer.
l haven't even thanked him.
This is no place
for a dirty vagrant like you!
Go away! Go!
Ouch. You're awfully cruel.
Oh, do you want to fight?
Let's do it!
We have nothing better to do!
No, l never meant to....
So he struck down
that violent bear with great ease?
Yes. l also saw bright light,
as if there was lightning.
Mew, maybe you shouldn't
take strolls alone in that forest.
Grandpa, you sound just like Mother.
Maria said the same thing?
But, Grandpa, it's important to have
many experiences while l'm young.
Otherwise l'll have a tough adult life.
You got me there.
Stop, what are you doing?
What a pathetic fellow.
That man.... Grandpa, it's him!
What?
That man?
Guards, listen to me!
That's Sir Fabris. What does he want?
Kill that man!
Surround him now and kill him!
Sir Fabris? Sir Fabris gave us an order!
Let's kill him!
Grandpa!
What're you doing, Grandpa?
He saved my life!
Just watch.
l see. You have no memory.
But your face, your build,
and the way you moved...
...you're a dead ringer for the man
known amongst the Tribe of Light...
...as the best swordsman ever: Pollux!
Pollux?
Well, then, until you regain
your lost memories...
...why not stay with us at this castle
as Pollux, the Swordsman of Light?
After all, you saved the life
of my granddaughter, Mew.
Look, Mother, how cute.
lndeed.
That man....
Oh, Sir Pollux!
l have to hurry.
l hate this so much.
Without a doubt,
a fragment of the Words Worth Tablet!
Very good of you to have found it.
Sir Wartoshika, will
the Tribe of Light attack us again?
They will. They surely will.
To take back
this Words Worth Tablet fragment!
lt's 20 years since the passage
was sealed between Light and Shadows.
They have not made a move.
We must not lower our guard!
The fact is, we are so close
to completing the Words Worth Tablet.
What's wrong, Tessio?
No, no.
Dear Sir Wartoshika.
Finally our wish is coming true.
Sir Astral would be so glad
if he were still alive.
Astral isn't....
l mean, Sir Astral
has never been confirmed dead.
You can't talk like that.
Sharon. lt's all right.
Yes, sir.
Listen, all of you!
Stay on tactical alert
so we're ready whenever they attack us!
You hear me?
Yes, sir!
l'm so bored.
Can't there be some excitement?
l have to hurry.
Or the Words Worth Tablet
may get resurrected.
That's Tessio. What's the hurry?
Could that be damn Menza?
What was that light?
l hope nobody saw that.
Sounds interesting.
l think l'll check it out.
What brought you here, Menza?
Nice way to welcome your partner!
l've suffered so much to come over here.
You're making me sick, too.
Well, you did save me
the trouble of going over there...
...so l shouldn't complain.
You've got business to discuss with me?
Why would l bother to come over
here if l didn't have a business to discuss?
That is so true.
Who would imagine a secret
rendezvous between the two of us?
The Commanders of Light and Shadows.
The Commander of the Tribe of Light?
You.
Thank you so much for before.
You're welcome.
My grandfather told me...
...you were going to the Gold Mine
to find the passage to the Shadow World...
...and find out about
the Words Worth Tablet fragments.
l found this in the forest.
A tablet fragment.
What? ls it true?
l have a similar piece. Look, here it is.
Really? Sir Pollux, where did you find it?
l don't know. l've always had it.
Probably since
even before l lost my memory.
The two pieces became one!
Damn!
How bizarre!
Watch out!
l guess it's over now.
l'm scared.
There may be terrifying force
we know nothing about....
Please help me stop trembling.
Mew.
l'm afraid.
Please hold me so l can forget this horror.
Miss Mew.
What's wrong, Menza?
l've sent out my double
to locate the Tablet fragments, but...
...it seems someone destroyed it!
What? Who could do that?
lt must be him.
The very reason why l came over.
The Legendary Swordsman?
Probably.
We have to get rid of him quickly.
Sir Pollux. l'm so embarrassed.
Miss Mew, you're beautiful.
No, don't look at me like that.
l'm hot, l'm going crazy.
Sir Pollux. l need it.
But l'm a vagrant with no past,
are you okay with that?
Sir Pollux.
Here it is.
Oh, something is in here.
lt's a crystal key.
My mother wants you to take it.
lt will surely be of use.
Thank you. Then....
Oh, yes.
See you later.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
Please, come back!
The Legendary Swordsman Pollux.
Somehow we have to kill him.
And locate the tablet Wartoshika
has been secretly rebuilding.
And destroy it again.
Otherwise we won't survive.
Destroy the Words Worth Tablet again?
What's with them?
This looks bad, l should get out.
Who's there?
Damn!
Menza!
l made it
No!
The passage between Light and Shadows
is somewhere in that mountain.
The crystal key?
There?
No!
What a nice view.
Let me go! What're you
going to do to me, you monsters?
You have no business calling us monsters!
This is what we're going to do to you!
You will pant and moan
in the valley of pleasure and be our slave!
Say, will there be a war?
Why, Ariadonne?
l saw many swordsmen gathering
at the castle early this morning.
Did you?
A war again....
Sir Astral....
Look, that lady over there
looks like she's sick.
Are you all right?
Lady, are you all right?
l can't remember anything.
l just can't remember.
Lady, look out!
You have crossed Light and Shadows?
She flew away.
She was mumbling something.
She looked fine. Good for her.
That mother and her daughter?
So this is the cave that leads to
the passage between Light and Shadows...
...that was sealed
during the war 20 years ago.
Must be this way.
The passage is sealed. This must be it.
The crystal key.
What's going on?
Who was that girl? She looked like Mew.
What happened in my past?
Who's there?