Oh, yes.
Doctor, I'd like to go to the bathroom.
Not now.
The best part's about to begin.
I'll take you later, so just hold it in.
Okay. I'll try my best.
Good girl.
You all right, Ren?
Y-Yes.
- Take this.
- Th-Thank you.
Enjoy.
You're so mean to me, Doctor.
How was it? Being seen like that
in such an embarrassing situation?
It felt like a hot flash.
Oh? That means you really
must've been getting off on it.
Yes.
Indeed, your love juices
are sticky and wet.
Yes.
You seem to especially enjoy
being seen by others.
What? Do you really think so?
I mean, look at how wet you are.
Yes.
I bet you wanted that waitress
to keep watching you.
Hm? Isn't that right?
You were embarrassed, weren't you?
You were hot, weren't you?
And you felt good.
You enjoy people watching you
in compromising positions.
Ren, didn't you want to
go to the bathroom?
Yes, Doctor. I don't think
I can hold it in anymore.
I see. You did very well
holding it in this long.
Yes.
Maybe it's time you have a pee then.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Then it's time for you to go.
But, before that,
I want you to get me off.
Not yet!
You pee just as I cum.
Now, Ren! Show the people of
this town the sight of you peeing!
Who is that?
What're you trying to do?
Good morning.
D-Doctor H-Hirasaka.
It's been a while, hasn't it, Miss Shinjyo?
I thought that maybe
you were missing me...
so I sent you a special video.
Did you like it?
You're soaking wet!
Did you get all wet from
watching that video?
What kind of nonsense is that?
You threw water on me!
No. I'm sure you got wet
from watching the video.
That's not so!
You got all wet from watching me
have my way with you.
I didn't get wet.
Don't lie!
It's not a lie!
By the way, have you talked
to the police about me?
Not yet.
You seem to have a problem
with speaking the truth.
In actuality, you were getting off
watching yourself spew shit everywhere.
You got all sticky and wet.
I think I hit the mark.
Maybe you should be a little
more honest with yourself.
You probably just can't
wait to do it again.
Here, I've got a wonderful
present for you.
You can do whatever you want with it.
Come on. You know what to do.
Stop it!
Come on. We're good friends.
What's the problem?
Like this!
It's time for your meeting soon.
You'd better get this over with and
get out of those dripping clothes.
The head nurse mustn't be absent.
Keep going.
I'm about to cum!
We'll continue this
when you're off work.
Come to the examination room
tonight. We'll have some fun.
Good morning.
You can start sending
in the patients.
Thank you very much.
There. You take care, now.
Who is it? This late at night...
Remi Shinjyo!
Shit! I forgot!
Wh-What's that?
M-My stomach!
What's going on here?
What is this?
I can't believe you'd go
after such a young girl!
You sure have a fetish
for the young ones!
She's jealous.
Well, this is perfect.
Let me introduce you.
She's Hikaru Kodama of
the cardiac department.
Hang on!
I'm going to untie you right now!
No, I'm almost there.
I think you're misunderstanding
something.
Like you, Hikaru is doing this
because she wants to.
I don't want such a thing!
Of course you do!
Then, why did you come here?
Well...
Never mind. Let's just
hold that thought...
while we watch Hikaru do her thing.
See? Look at this?
The sight of Hikaru in ecstasy...
reminded you of back then.
And you got off on it.
No. From before you came
to this examination room...
you were probably already
getting wet thinking about me.
No way.
You've got to become more honest
with yourself, like Hikaru here.
You actually love these dirty acts.
You love to do it with me.
Look. Hikaru can see it too, right?
The sticky, wet love juices.
Yes.
No!
It seems like you're going to need
some special treatment...
to deal with that problem
you have with honesty.
Hikaru can help me, too.
No! No! Please, no!
What do you plan on doing?
Squat down on her, Hikaru.
Yes, sir.
I want you to shit all over her face.
- What?
- Stop this!
But the shitting is done.
I've shit all that a girl could shit.
You'd better hurry, or I'll get
your sister to take your place.
Please, no.
I'll do my best.
You've got to be kidding!
No, don't!
Come on! Open your mouth!
No shit, but in all that pushing,
we got a whole load of piss.
Come on! Drink all of it!
That's very good, Miss Shinjyo.
Already showing the results
from the treatment.
An incredible torrent of love!
As a reward, I'll shove this
vibrator into your ass.
Also, I want you to lick
Hikaru's asshole clean...
for helping with your treatment.
There.
I bet it feels good,
even just among girls.
And Hikaru, I want you to lick
Miss Shinjyo's pussy nice and clean!
Come on, Hikaru.
Keep that mouth working!
Yes, sir.
I want some, too.
That's the attitude, Remi!
Oh, that feels so good!
It feels so deep!
I'm going to cum!
Ren Nanase...
Ako Fujisawa...
Hikaru Kodama...
Remi Shinjyo...
These four sex slaves
will make excellent...
nurses for the new department.
Now that I have succeeded...
Hey, I've got mail.
I want to talk about the next phase.
Please come to the chief medical
officer's room tomorrow. Narumi.
By the way, how are things going
with Naoya Ohkawa lately?
I haven't been seeing him.
All that effort you made,
and he dumped you?
What a terrible man.
When I first came here, I thought
this was some ridiculous idea...
but now I'm starting to think
that there's something to it.
Shit. He's a big shot.
I'm not going to let Narumi
take advantage of me anymore.
It's open.
She set it up nicely.
This'll make it easier.
Come here.
You've more than met my expectations.
I want to thank you for all your work.
Well, you're welcome.
I hope you haven't forgotten
about my reward.
Not to worry.
We'll talk about the details later.
By the way, is that the
new special ward?
Yes.
Thanks to you, we were able to
develop the slave nurses.
So we got the go-ahead
from the president.
Glad to hear that.
How about a toast?
Well, to you and all your hard work.
And to the future.
Cheers!
That's good wine!
I would hope so.
To you, anyway.
This is the last drink
you'll ever have, after all.
How could this be happening?
I saw you pour the drugs into the wine.
I've never seen anything so stupid.
Ten years ago, I drank your
drugged wine and you molested me.
And here I was waiting for you
with a bottle of wine.
Didn't it seem strange to you?
There were drugs in both glasses
from the beginning.
Now, Hirasaka...
I want you to die.
To relieve my hatred and to compensate
for how you messed up my life.
That will be your reward.
H-How can you be so cruel about it?
Why didn't you just
kill me at the start?
No way.
I've never even once forgotten
about you these past ten years.
I was going to find you
and kill you with my own hands.
That's all I have lived for.
I've lived only to claim revenge.
But all I saw was a pathetic man,
sinking fast.
That's when I came up with a plan.
To restore you to what
you were in the past...
and to give you a purpose to live.
And only then would I kill you.
I didn't care about sacrificing the
nurses in order to carry this out.
I became a demon.
A demon hell-bent on revenge!
Doctor?
Doctor!
Narumi!
Wh-What are you...
Thank goodness! You've been
in a coma for a week.
You were worried about me?
Yes.
By the way, where's the chief
medical officer?
She passed away.
What?
She slit her throat with a scalpel.
I'll do the rest.
Doctor, we have duties to perform.
We'll be back later.
I'll leave the rest to you, Miss Nanase.
Okay.
Doctor, we're finally together.
Just the two of us.
Right.