This animation is only fiction and has no relation to real people, organizations or groups.
This place...
Eh? What? Why?
Where am I?
Why do I look like this?
It couldn't be...
I don't get it.
There seem to be no hints.
What happened to me?
I can't remember.
It's wet...
Well, for now I'll get out of here.
Mirror? That scared me...
Who is that? Me? Is this me?
Unknown face. Somehow it doesn't look like me.
Where is the exit?
There is no knob!
That means I can't open it...
Anyone! Isn't anyone there?!
It won't open, it's obstructed.
Why? Why?
Why? Why did this happened?
Why can't I remember anything?
At this state, if anyone opens the door...
Who are you? No! Don't come near!
No! Stop!
Please, stop!
No, not like that, that's wrong.
I surely ended already, I just can't remember.
That rope!
No! No!
Stop it!
Please... forgive me... already....
No!
I hate this!
I...
I'm sure this...
This...
I!m sure this...
Surely... like this...
I'm wet... It's more and more overflowing...
Somehow... this makes me really happy...
Feels good...
Why am I doing this? Such lewd thing?
But a bit more and maybe I could remember what happened to me.
With this...
I can't remember...
That's right, this thing, like this, it's not enough.
It was something more, more awful.
Why am I doing something like this?
And it suits you so much.
It really suits you.
It's flowing...
Flowing inside me...
Yes, that's how I was abused!
More, more!
Somebody come, quickly!
This way, this way...
I can remember!
Anybody is okay.
Mess... mess with me...
I... I...
Tch, that was so-so.
But it's not exactly right.
One more time.
One more time. One more time with a different way.
That way, I'll surely remember this time.