Put it on screen.
Situation?
Yes, ma'am. These floating
objects are of an unknown nature...
and they seem to be interfering
with our systems, somehow.
Life support hasn't been affected,
but Navi-Control is being disrupted.
Right. Understood.
Evacuating to the core shelter.
Level 3 emergency!
System flow! System flow!
O, here. I've moved to the core shelter.
Situation is worse than first thought.
Put the entire colony on Level 5 alert!
- Trouble!
- What's wrong?
A dimensional warp is forming.
Please get out of there!
I can't during a Level 5 alert!
Stand by and observe.
We can't! At this rate, the entire colony
will be sucked into the warp!
Hold on!
That voice!
Wander in the void between
time and space for all eternity!
The Demon Beast!
You who dared to interfere
with my resurrection...
shall be doomed to wander for all
eternity, orphans of the dimensions!
Now entering atmosphere.
Hello? Mailman.
Nobody's there.
Oh, thanks.
- Who is it?
- Mailman, with a special deliver.
Oh...
Sorry, this is a special deliver.
Can you stamp it?
Something wrong?
Oh, no. Nothing.
Let's see, the seal. The seal.
That's okay. You look like
you're busy at the moment.
Oh? Do I?
See you.
Thanks a lot.
- Who's it from?
- Let's see.
Air tickets?
Who could have...
Muneto, did you have to come so quickly?
Oh, uh. Sorry.
There's a real non-apology.
So, who's it from?
Muneto?
Muneto, who's the letter from?
Look, I only came over here because
you said you wanted to have some fun.
Am I supposed to blend into the
woodwork now that it's all over?
No, that's not what l...
Look, this is from my uncle.
It's some sort of an emergency.
What?
It looks like the Demon Beast
has appeared again.
My uncle saved us that other time,
and now it's my turn to return the favor.
But, Muneto...
It's okay. Don't worry.
My uncle will be there with me.
But we'll be apart for
a while. So, before we are...
Yeah?
Before we are, I'm gonna get
you for coming too quick!
OW! Kayo, cut it out! That hurts!
See you, Muneto. And be careful.
Great, I get left behind.
Shit! I'm gonna miss the plane!
I smell it.
I smell semen. You have the scent
of sperm on your breath.
Did you put it in your mouth?
Did you stick his dick in that
little mouth of yours and suck it?
I didn't do anything!
Now, now. You mustn't lie. I can
smell it from your lovely little mouth.
Stop it! Let me go!
If you struggle,
I'll spread the word.
About you and the smell
of sperm on your breath!
If you don't want me to tell...
then you'd better whisper
exactly what you did into my ear.
But... But, l...
Ah, and you have the smell of semen
on the nape of your neck as well.
All right. I took Muneto's...
Muneto's what?
Muneto's... and sucked it.
Good girl. I want to check out
a few other parts now as well.
I imagine you smell like
sperm down THERE as well!
MUNETO!
Shit! I'll never make it!
Uncle? When did you get here?
Muneto, why are you racing around?
Good timing! I'm going away
for a little while.
Can you watch the place for me?
- Where are you going?
- Hokkaido!
North. This bodes ill.
I don't want Kayo to think
I'm cheating on her.
It wasn't true that
my uncle wrote to me.
But I couldn't tell her that
it came from Miyuki!
And besides that, how she invited
me up to visit her in Hokkaido.
It might have been better
if she'd invited Kayo, too...
considering they're cousins.
But then, Miyuki and I
share that strange...
karmic link to each other
from our past lives.
So, you're Muneto, huh?
Hmm, not bad at all.
You landed a nice one, Kayo.
I didn't tell Kayo.
I feel like this isn't the
first time we've met.
So, I... I...
Please!
Miyuki, don't! Kayo and I are...
Have you forgotten me?
Even a thousand years apart
hasn't lessened my love for you.
Your Yukino still burns
for you, body and soul.
Sohnen, my love!
Miyuki, I'm not Sohnen!
I'm Muneto Ungyosai!
Don't say such things to me.
Have you forgotten the warmth of my skin
I promised to you a thousand years ago?
- Stop it Miyuki! SOH!
- You mustn't, Yukino!
Sohnen, my love...
You mustn't... You mustn't... No woman
may enter the sacred grounds of Oyama.
I must remain celibate for my training!
No... No... Love me... Love me!
As hard as you can!
Give me a passion that will
burn for a thousand years!
Yu... Yukino!
Sohnen, my love!
Yukino!
Oh, shit!
Karma.
The karmic debt of Yukino's love
for Sohnen a thousand years ago.
But, Miyuki and I are...
Ladies and gentlemen, we've begun
our decent into Furano Airport.
The captain has now turned on
the fasten seat belts sign.
I wonder how she is?
Okay. Huh?
It's in the mountains? Great.
Lord Muneto!
I've come for you, sir!
Huh?
Lord Muneto Ungyosai?
Yeah?
The Lady Miyuki sent me
to get you, my lord.
The LADY Miyuki?
Huh?
She's a priestess?
Yes.
Miyuki really. I never thought
she was into that.
Our Great Leader. No, the Lady Miyuki,
I mean, possesses fantastic power.
Fantastic power?
Yes. She's given us a new life.
A new life, huh?
Yes. With the father
of the black forest...
who is pregnant with the
seed of a thousand beasts.
The Great Savior of all creation
granted her this power.
When the Lady Miyuki
grants you her affection...
you will understand her power.
Uh, anyway, how much further?
About four hours.
Fo... FOUR HOURS? It's that far?
At this rate, we should be
there by daybreak.
Wow, it sure is cold here.
It is. 20 degrees below freezing.
Yow! I heard it got cold here, but...
This won't do at all.
Let's get a bit warmer.
Oh, it's morning.
We should see the palace soon.
We are two hours behind
schedule, though.
Oh, there you go again.
Well, I'm still young.
Look, you can see it now.
It's like something
from another world.
The Great Savior used his power
to create heaven on earth.
What's that disc?
It gives this place the power of life.
Allowing green fields to bloom
in the midst of winter.
Wow, pretty impressive power.
Wait a sec, you said Miyuki
started this sect?
Yes. Lady Miyuki is the sole incarnation of
the Great Savior's power upon this world.
I'm getting nervous
about meeting her.
Holy...
And it's the middle of winter.
Lord Muneto...
shall we go to Lady Miyuki now?
Come here, please.
What, on this?
Yes. Let's go.
Whoa!
Hang onto me.
We'll be at the shrine soon.
Lord Muneto has arrived.
Go in.
If you see a girl you like, we could
have her brought to your chambers.
Thanks, but...
Hi!
Muneto, welcome!
Huh? Miyuki?
I've been so looking forward
to seeing you again.
You look like a goddess.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Thank you.
- Now then, why don't you sleep till dusk?
- Sure.
The sect is having a feast tonight.
I'm glad you were able to make it.
Though you seem to have done
a few dark deeds on the way here.
No matter. We'll purify you.
Purify me?
Yes. I called you out here to save you
from when the earth is destroyed.
When the earth is destroyed?
Come, show Muneto where to go.
This way, please.
Sure.
Rest until nightfall.
Thank you for all your trouble.
Have no fear, you will be justly rewarded.
As will you.
My lady!
I told you to bring Muneto here,
not to do with him as you wished.
Forgive me.
Lord Muneto was cold,
so I thought I'd warm him.
Enough excuses.
You will get your reward.
Although I may have to teach
you to choose with more care.
Come. Don't you want it?
I do!
Grant me your power, Lady Miyuki!
I beg you. Grant it to me.
Oh, thank you!
There, all set.
- Now clean me.
- Yes, my lady.
Now it's your turn.
- Do as you like with her!
- Yes!
Ah, the smell! The smell!
The smell of a bitch in heat!
And now we can prepare for
the feast without any regrets.
Miyuki?
Good morning.
Time to rise and shine.
What are...
Purifying you.
I'm going to cleanse you
of the filth of the lower world.
But...
Just forget about everthing else and let
the two of us have fun with each other.
Don't move.
I'll do all the work for you.
This is Soma,
the holy fruit of our sect.
Soma?
Yes. The juice of this fruit will heighten
the passion between two people.
How exactly?
It'll take effect soon.
Oh, yes!
I can't take it!
Ready? Will you come into me?
I can't wait anymore.
Yes! Oh, yes!
Muneto! Muneto! Fill me!
Fill me up inside!
It's incredible! So warm!
I feel it! I feel you thrusting
into me, filling me!
More! Oh, God!
I'm going to come!
With me! With me!
Come with me, please!
Yes! Yes!
Muneto...
Don't stop! Here! Here! Here!
And don't you guys slack off, either!
MUNETO!!!
Outta the way!
I could've sworn I just heard Kayo.
Listen to me, all of you!
We now begin the holy feast
in honor of the Great Savior!
This foul world will
soon be destroyed.
We alone, the worshippers of
the Great Savior, shall be spared.
We must lift up our voices
in joy to the Great Savior!
We have brought his Holy Mother
to guide him here to us!
Bring the Holy Mother forth!
No! No!
Let me go!
Kayo? What's she doing here?
No! Stop it!
Miyuki! Help me, please!
I'm afraid you misunderstand.
You have to bring our
Great Savior here to us!
Miyuki! Miyuki, come to your senses!
It's me, Kayo! Your cousin!
I'm not this "Holy Mother!"
The Great Savior will soon
manifest from that golden orb.
And then he will surely
seek the Holy Mother.
He so longs to return
to his beloved home.
No! Stop it!
Miyuki, please!
What are you doing?
Stop it.
A sign for the gods
from the blessed Holy Mother!
Stop it! I'm so ashamed!
Prepare! For the Ceremony
of Ultimate Bliss!
No! No! MUNETO!!!
Dammit!
Kayo!
Miyuki?
We'll lead him here together.
The Great Savior.
What... What are you saying?
Here's something nice to rub on it.
How long can you resist?
Stop it, please.
Kayo.
My, see how it drips?
These love juices.
Stop it.
Oh, yes! The Blessed Love
juices for the Great Savior!
Now that I've smeared you with the
holy fruit, the flow will never stop.
No. Stop it. Please!
Oh? Not enough for you?
What if I were to stuff
ALL of this inside of you?
Stop it. Please, stop it.
STOP IT!
STOP!
Somebody out there?
No. Must've been our imagination.
Well, then get back in here.
Right. Time to punish you, little missy!
Muneto, now would not be
a good time to start yelling!
You know my name. Who are you?
Captain O. Interplanetar
Mutual Observation Agency.
You're who?
"To be continued..."