This is the night circuit where
Miki last disappeared, but...
We've seen generally what
her riding patterns are.
She wouldn't take a route
she's already taken before.
Yeah. Just like Sis wouldn't.
But, if she really is Sis...
then she'll have to
pass by this toll plaza.
Sis!
Weirder than usual.
Wait!
Stop, please!
What the...
What was that?
- Ash...
- That was our sister.
Huh?
Don't you think you look
a lot like her, Miki?
I don't have any sisters.
We were more than sisters.
We three were once a team.
Are you pulling my leg?
No, but explaining would
take a long time.
We need your power now!
You aren't like those girls who usually
follow me around. Come on!
Drink.
What's with you?
I was thinking about Sis.
I don't think we ever saw her smile.
Now, how about that explanation?
Where's Mari and the rest?
They still aren't back
from picking up Emi.
Mari?
Mari? Guys?
What are you doing?
Mother! Mother!
Where are you?
Where is my Mother?
Kayo! Where are you going?
I'm here with you, Kayo! Kayo!
It's me! Don't you recognize me, Kayo?
Is the Demon Beast calling her again?
Kayo...
That's a pretty unbelievable story.
But when I look into your eyes,
I can see you're not lying to me.
Miki!
Can you show me the image of
the Ash you remember again?
She does look like me.
Do you remember what her
final moments were like?
Miki!
I want to see how she died.
Not so bad. She went beyond
the wind and became light.
I don't think I'll live another year.
Miki!
I don't really have any ties
to life anymore.
Only when I'm riding my machine and
become like the wind do I feel truly alive.
Miki...
My parents died when they were flying
to Mexico to see my big brother race...
when a supersonic test jet
collided with their plane.
I hated the jet that killed them.
But I love speed
as much as my brother did.
Only in that instant when I feel like
the wind itself do I feel happiness.
Like I'm with them again.
But now...
Now I only live in my memories.
My body may be alive,
but my heart died a long time ago!
You chose a good moment
to show up, BB, Dee.
You mean...
I've been dreaming about a blazing end
for this life of mine.
I'd like to die by becoming light.
So I guess I'd be glad to
become your sister.
Miki!
Thank you.
BB here.
This is Muneto!
The Demon Beast's appeared!
And Kayo's getting even worse.
Get back here, please!
Roger!
Demon Beast carriers!
Miki!
None of you will get
even one step past me!
That's the Demon Beast?
Mother-r-r-r-r-r!
BB! Where's Dee?
She's fighting Demon Beast carriers.
Ash... No, Cat's Eye...
I am Ash. I feel that I am.
When I heard about Ash and you,
I got a strange feeling inside.
Help us, Muneto! Our ship's in
that grove of trees out back.
Gotcha!
Miki, are you sure about this?
Don't make me start
having second thoughts.
I'm not into self-sacrifice.
I chose to become Ash so that I can live!
You can ask BB and Dee about it later.
Miki, undress and get in.
I'd better go.
Stay here! You have to be here
when Ash revives.
Miki...
Ash loved only one man.
When she revives, the first
thing she should see is you.
All set over here!
It's Dee!
They're chasing her!
Muneto, take care of this!
Miki... Thank you.
Thank you. For being the first
and last man I'll ever love.
Miki...
Dee!
- Where's Miki?
- In the capsule.
Ash... Come back to us.
Ash. Do you hear me?
You are the greatest warrior
the I MOA ever produced.
Ash, we need your
powers once more.
Oh, God, no! Rejection?
Miki!
They're both dying!
Big brother!
Ash, warrior above all others.
Awaken! Your power
is needed! Ash!
Ash!
Ash...
Ash? Why? Why aren't you moving?
Ash? What's wrong? Ash!
Mune... to... Help me...
Ash?
Show me joy, like when we first met.
When you and Kayo become one...
The power of Maitreya can...
Ash!
Muneto!
Ash...
To the heights of ecstasy...
Ash!
Muneto!
Ash...
Mother!
Muneto!
Muneto...
Dee...
Sis...
We won. All the carriers are dead.
What about Miki?
Mu... Muneto...
Sis!
BB! Dee!
Sis...
Where's the Demon Beast?
She slept through it, totally oblivious.
That's for the best. All she needs
to see when she awakens is you.
Ash...
Sis! The Demon Beast!
We've looked everywhere...
but it's just disappeared.
Don't worry. It'll come back here, attracted
by the scent of Kayo's pheromones.
He'll have to show.
Move out!
Ash!
Muneto, I'll never forget you.
Take care of Kayo.
All citizens in the area, please
evacuate in an orderly fashion.
Mother. Mother, where are you?
It entered onto this course
when you began to revive.
Ash, I'm glad you're back.
How do you feel?
The terminals in your helmet are
set to tap into your body's powers.
In the event you have to initiate
your Final Mission option...
the armor you're wearing will
automatically merge with your body.
The armor is also equipped to give
off pheromones identical to Kayo's.
It should be enough to
confuse the Demon Beast.
When he's overwhelmed with desire,
you'll have your best chance.
Failure is not an option. Good luck.
Mother! Mother's scent!
A scent so thick it chokes me!
I can't stand it! Where is she?
Mother, where are you?
Mother?
No, not Mother. But the scent!
The scent drives me mad!
It has to be her!
The smell of Mother's warm juices!
Who are you?
Ash!
Sis!
Dee, no! You'll only get in her way!
Sis...
Where is she?
Where have you taken Mother?
Where is my Mother?
This scent... This scent...
Is it not Mother's?
Yes, this. Is this warmth
I feel not Mother's warmth?
I can't take it.
I can't take it anymore!
Mother! Become one with me!
Give me your power for all time!
Give me the energy of your joy!
Sis!
Ash!
Miki!
Beyond the wind...
To become light itself!
Become one with me!
I've won.
Ash...
Mother...
Oh, the heights of ecstasy!
MOTHER!
Sis!
Miki!
ASH!
Sis...
Miki...
Ash...
BB and Dee have returned.
Captain O...
Mission accomplished.
Eternal glory to Ash and Miki.
So, it all ended while I was sound asleep?
It's better that way.
I'll always be at your side.
Mm...
Ash. I don't believe you're dead.
I think I may see you again,
someday. And you, too, Miki.
Namae mo Shiranai mama
I may not have known your name
Koi o Shiteita
but loved you anyway
Unmei ii da Nante
Even at those times
Kanjita Toki mo
I thought fate was against me
Yokan sae mo nakatta
I had no warning of it
Deatteita no ne
but I met you anyway
Sou ne Mirai Nakureta
Maybe it's that feeling of calm
Yasuragi ka mo ne
from knowing there's no tomorrow
Chiizen ni Meguru
If I should wander the earth
Odayakana Deai nara
and calmly meet you again
Itsuka Mamuretai
I know I'll see your
Sugao no Hohoemi
smile again
Chizuka ni Tsuzumikomu
Nukumori ni Setsunakute
Ima Hanareru wake
Sagasumo wa Imi mo nai
Kotome Atarashii Kaze
ga Hakonda Kaori
Kiramaeki no Jooku
Yowinde Warai Sora
Arubamu