Go back!
We have to save Kayo!
- Just calm down!
- But, Kayo will be...
What do you think you
can do in that situation?
But...
If they're just interested in acting
like an average sex cult...
then we may be all right.
What?
But we have to worry
if the god they were...
worshipping turns out
to be the Demon Beast.
What? The Demon Beast?
What are you doing?
To be expected, Holy Mother.
You have no idea of the limits
of your love spring.
But, you see, it's still not quite enough.
We'll need a great deal more
to call forth the Great Savior.
Stop it!
"Do it!" she said, and in it slipped.
Now, how many more
can we fit in there?
But we have to save Kayo!
They're waiting for the moon.
Huh?
Kayo should be safe until
the moon crosses the meridian.
Until then, we have to prepare.
Prepare?
I only came down here
to Earth by chance.
You mean...
Yes. It was only by chance
that I was there to save you.
I'd broken into the shrine...
while tracing a weak
Demon Beast life signal.
The fact they were worshipping
the Demon Beast there...
my meeting you
and losing all my agents...
and having to face the Demon Beast
alone; all of it was by chance.
Though I certainly wish I could take
credit for a well thought out plan.
This may be my karma.
Well, I guess you're not alone.
You have me.
Oh?
Yes, you're right.
Sorry! I forgot how cold it was
to a regular human body.
Come in here.
Huh? Whoa!
You'll be perfectly warm in here.
Just don't get any funny ideas.
Oh?
That'll be kinda hard,
seeing as how I'm hanging onto...
a beautiful woman like you, Captain.
Muneto! What are you doing?
Stop it!
Huh?
You're awake?
What am I?
Oh, God! I'm sorry! I...
Yes, I know. This was to blame.
Look.
What is it?
I found something mixed in
with the fluids from your penis.
An unknown substance...
along with the secretions of
several normal human women.
DNA?
Yes, but not from any Earthly organism.
The Demon Beast's?
The things you've been fighting
up until now have just been tools...
made by the Demon Beast by joining
its DNA with Earth life forms.
Then, you mean?
That ceremony is calling
the real Demon Beast down...
from the Sea of Dimensions.
To do what?
Destroy everything.
Its vengeance against all life.
And Kayo is?
Just another tool it needs to reach
the next level of its existence.
Even Miyuki?
Yet another tool.
Although she seems very easily
possessed by the Demon Beast.
There may be a deeper connection there.
Wait, that's the Soma fruit
I ate before.
I see.
Huh?
Tha- That's the Demon
Beast's DNA again!
This species of plant supposedly
became extinct long ago.
- I didn't think it still existed.
- Huh? But...
The Interplanetary
Mutual Observation Agency...
managed to save a small
number of people from...
the so-called continent of Mu
before it sank 12,000 years ago.
What?
But, considering that the Mu
queen's bloodline survived...
her descendents must have
preserved the fruit as well.
Our records show that
the queen resettled in Japan.
Stop it, please!
I can't take anymore!
Good! Let's try to put in
as many as we can.
No! They won't fit!
Oh, I doubt that.
No.
Please.
We've only gotten 16 in.
I expected you'd be able
to hold at least 50!
We won't stop until
we've put all these inside.
Stop it!
You're going to rip it apart!
Look! I got another one in!
No use.
Can't hold it anymore.
They're coming out!
No!
No! No! No!
Oh, Kayo, whatever shall
we do with you?
To think the Holy Mother
would be built so small.
We'll just have to do something
about squeezing the ones inside you.
Please, stop it!
Turn back to normal.
Miyuki, please!
Miyuki?
Miyuki, you're...
The Demon Beast has you again?
Toh, the Great Savior has made it clear
that he needs me.
Now, he wants me to squeeze
the Soma fruit inside of you.
With this.
Stop it! Miyuki, please!
Can't you see that you are being totally
controlled by the Demon Beast?
Not at all. I work for the
Great Savior because I want to.
I have spent my whole life
working with the great savior...
to achieve what I have
desired because I wanted to.
Here we go, Kayo.
No! No!
Stop it!
Oh, Kayo! You're wonderful!
Even tighter than I thought you were.
My tool's getting numb!
The Soma fruit is being
properly crushed inside of you.
Soon, Kayo. Soon,
you will know the Soma fruit's power.
How does it feel, Kayo? Doesn't the
Soma fruit make you feel wonderful?
Oh! Yes! Wonderful! Wonderful!
It feels incredible! Oh, yes!
Well then, I'll make you
feel even better.
This is the power of the Great Savior.
He loves your womb so much...
that he has given us the power
to love each other.
Look, Kayo. Your love juices
are flowing nicely, now.
You're soaking. And your little
clit's gotten so big, too.
What a dirty little slut you are!
No, not there!
Oh, God!
No. Oh, God!
It's incredible! Oh! Oh!
Oh, God! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm going to...
We have enough
of the holy juices!
The Holy Mother's love juices are
calling out to the Great Savior!
Igu-na-ii! Igu-na-ii!
Sufuru-skuun!
He who was, still is.
He who is, shall be.
The master of the world,
the Great Savior!
Travel no more in the sea
of primeval dimensions!
Come to this dimension we know!
To the dimension of the lost continent,
sealed beneath the ocean.
Let the dimensional doorway
be opened and answer my prayers!
Lord Beast, arise once more!
I am reborn!
You've done it, La Ru!
I am made manifest!
When he destroys the Earth,
only my bloodline will survive.
And then my long dreamed
of ambitions will be realized.
And now, revive our lost continent!
Revive the glory we lost!
Cr out, all of you!
Let the Lord Beast hear
your cries of ecstasy!
The moans of joy!
Seek out your happiness!
Cr out loud!
Let all your carnal happiness be
carried up to the Lord Beast!
Oh, Lord Beast!
Answer our calls to you!
That should work against the
effects of the Soma material.
You should have no more flashbacks.
Whew! Great!
Wouldn't want to try
and jump you again, Captain.
What the hell?
The Demon Beast has appeared!
- What?
- Don't panic.
We still have some time
before he reaches Earth.
Now, let's go save Kayo.
- Let's go!
- Roger.
Mother! Mother!
Wait for me! Mother!
Now, let the final ceremony begin!
It's all over for you, Kayo.
Between the smell of your
womb and the love juices...
we've released with the Soma fruit,
we know the Great Savior will come.
Come for you.
And then Muneto will be mine alone.
Kayo!
Muneto!
Huh... Muneto?
Is Miyuki...
Yes. Forget about her.
But it looks like we've stopped
the Demon Beast's resurrection.
Look!
The moon's back to normal.
Damn it all! Damn it all!
Everything's been burned to ashes.
It would have worked.
I know in my heart,
it really would have worked!
Damn it! But I won't give up!
I still have some
of Kayo's love juice.
With this... With this, I will
call the Great Savior once more!
My 12,000-year dream...
it will come true with me!
What's happening?
The dimensional portal
is obviously open again!
Somehow we didn't stop
its rebirth after all!
Dammit! And after we
managed to save her...
He'll come after her again!
We won't let him have her.
Help me, Muneto.
What are you...
I'm going to transplant
her secretion gland into me.
The Demon Beast chases her
because of the pheromones she emits.
If I transplant the gland,
we'll be able to hide her from it.
But then you...
I don't think you understand, Muneto.
It's my duty.
I have to do this, if only for all
the friends it took away from me!
Please, help me.
All right.
Lord!
Lord Beast...
Lord, I've been waiting for you!
Ah, La Ru. My corrupt queen.
Think back! To that day,
12,000 years ago.
Am I La Ru?
Father?
You remember. With that dagger
you killed your father, King La Mu.
You were a shrine maiden,
forbidden contact with men.
And for that you hated your father!
And then your destiny was foretold.
The man you were fated to
carnally know was your own brother!
I have decided to grant you your wish.
It's no use!
My father has unjustly
imprisoned my brother...
in the turbulent Sea of Dimensions!
I'll never see him again!
Nothing is impossible for me!
I will search the thousands of
alternate dimensions to find him.
Will you do that for me?
I swear. However, you must give me
your mother in exchange!
My mother?
Eons ago, your mother was
once my mother as well.
She gave me life.
A holy karmic duty for her.
Very well! And in return
you will give me my brother!
Now, give him to me!
Have you forgotten?
What?
Think back!
You never gave me the queen
because she killed herself!
Give me my reborn mother!
What is?
So long as I don't have my mother,
you will never see your brother!
- Are you all right, Captain O?
- Yes.
We have to finish off
the Demon Beast...
while he still can't find Kayo.
But, before that, you must
give me all your true power.
But, in order to fight the Demon Beast,
I must be allowed to make love to you.
But... I mean...
Please don't worry. She won't
be waking up for a little while.
All right, Captain O.
Please, that's such an impersonal name.
Call me Olga.
Olga?
A real woman's name.
Olga, what I tried to do to you before
was because of the Soma fruit.
This time I'll do it to you
from my heart.
Don't be silly, Muneto!
What about Kayo?
Just...
Just make love to me
the way you should.
Sorry.
It's all right. Do it.
Here we go.
Olga...
Muneto...
Mu... ne... to!
MUNETO!
No! No! They aren't
like Mother's juices!
The scent, the flow...
All wrong! I need Mother!
Without Mother, it won't work!
That smell!
What is this? It's her scent.
My body trembles.
Such delicious captivation!
Mother! The scent of Mother!
This time! This time!
I will have my way!
Mother! Where are you going?
Mother!
Olga.
Brother!
Miyuki?
What the...
Brother!
Miyuki!
Brother! Brother! Take me!
Take me, my brother!
I've waited so long to have you again.
I'm not your brother!
Have you forgotten, my brother?
When you learned of my corruption...
you refused to love me...
despite how much my body
burned for your loving touch.
Again? Karma from
ANOTHER past life?
I can see it in your eyes.
Since you refused to love me
that time before...
if you don't love me now...
then I will die!
Stop it! Don't let your karma
from a past life control you!
I killed my father,
and knowingly doomed my mother...
by promising her to another.
I may as well die!
Stop this!
Brother!
La Ru... I will return your love.
We must stop this
endless cycle of hatred!
Brother!
Are you ready, La Ru?
Yes.
The moon's back to normal.
The cycle has been broken.
Om Ma Ire-yasu Sowaka!
Mother!
Now I will have my way!
Is this really my karma?
Come, let us both return
to the ends of space and time.
No!
This bodes ill.
I tried to use the mystic arts...
to peer across the galaxy, but failed.
Have the Demon Beast and Captain O...
both vanished into
the Sea of Dimensions?
Or else?
Muneto!
Muneto! Muneto!
Muneto, speak to me! Muneto!
Muneto!
Kayo.
You're all right. Thank God.
It's over. Everything.
Just as long as you're okay.
Where's Miyuki?
I can't find her.
I see.