You usually don't see a storm this
concentrated at this time of the year.
It's strange.
It's been going on for ten days now.
I get the feeling something
terrible is brewing.
Don't scare me like that, Muneto.
It's like the end of the world.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Kayo...
I don't want to go home, Muneto.
Captain O.
Analysis results?
The world-wide climatic disturbances
should be improving in the next 24 hours.
However...
However?
We're detecting substances in the rain...
which indicate the growth
of a Demon Beast life form.
What?
Look at the data we gathered from the
last time the Demon Beast appeared.
Probability of a new appearance?
72%. We believe there's the strong
possibility that proto-Demon Beast matter...
found in the asteroid belt was
somehow diverted to the Earth.
How long will it take to grow from its child
form into a full-grown Demon Beast?
From the start of life functions,
we estimate 69 hours.
I'm initiating a search
and destroy mission.
Select a strike team at once!
Yes, ma'am!
Mother... My life... Mother!
Whew! It's so steamy!
That rain finally cleared up
and now we get this heat!
You just can't win either way!
Ash...
ASH!
Wait, please!
That was Ash! But it couldn't be!
Am I seeing things now?
Muneto?
What's wrong?
Didn't you buy anything?
Come on, what's wrong?
Could you please leave
me alone for a while?
Silly Muneto.
I can't do anything
to fight the Demon Beast!
I don't have what it
takes to be an I MO agent!
I can't even protect Kayo, the girl I love.
I don't have the power
to do anything at all.
Enough of that!
Ash!
Nothing ever comes of despair.
Everything my sisters and I know comes from
our training to destroy the Demon Beast.
But what we need... is the power that
comes from protecting the one you love!
My sisters don't know what
that sort of power is like.
Ash!
Just once. Show me the joy
you give Kayo when you love her!
As though she were here
with you instead of me!
That's all I wanted from you.
Ash!
BB! Dee! Move out!
Sis!
Ash...
Muneto...
Muneto!
Sis!
ASH!
M... Mother!
Mother-r-r-r...
A-A-A-A-A-ASH!
Sis!
Ash! You can't die!
But Ash was... She was...
Sis...
Captain O.
Agents BB and Dee, reporting for duty.
Sis?
Ash was the greatest warrior...
the Interplanetary Mutual
Observation Agency ever had.
That remains true even now.
And now we need her once again.
But... She's... She's...
She was killed along
with the Demon Beast!
Which means we have to resurrect her.
Captain O!
There's a strong probability that a new
Demon Beast has come to life on Earth.
No. I should say we're certain of it.
A new... Demon Beast?
I have come to the conclusion
that Ash is the only warrior...
who would have any chance against it.
You can't bring somebody back
from the dead!
We have a duty to avenge her!
Please, send us out after it!
You two would have
no chance against it.
What's that?
Spermia, which we recovered
from Ash's body after she died.
"Spermia"?
A sort of embryonic cell nucleus.
The genetic sequences containing
Ash's individual personality and memories...
which we cultured from her cells.
Ash's?
It contains all of
Ash's combat memories.
While we were studying the secrets
of the Demon Beast's life functions...
after we killed it before, we removed
Ash's body from inside it...
and learned enough to create this
proto-nucleus: The spermia cell.
What do you mean?
Rudolf Steiner, a famous Earth scientist
active during the early 20th century...
theorized the existence of the spermia
of space creatures which might survive...
while encased in dead organic cells,
which would fall to Earth.
He believed that people who were
born and died on other worlds...
might leave behind spermia which
would then drift through space...
fall to Earth, and be reborn.
You mean people could be reborn from
meteor material or something like that?
Most people who carry these
sleeping memory sequences...
within their brains will never
awaken their old memories.
However, these memory sequences
can be concentrated by certain life forms...
allowing the possibility to
resurrect the old personality.
You mean the Demon Beast?
Exactly. And there's also the possibility
that the activation of the old personality...
in the mind of a human
could produce a new being...
with power nearly as great as
the Demon Beast's.
Then you mean Sis really
can be resurrected?
Someone on Earth has
the same spermia root as Ash.
If you implant this memory spermia into
them, and assuming no rejection occurs...
the old and new personalities
within them may merge...
to produce a being with
extraordinary abilities.
But, that person...
We'd never be able to find her!
Listen.
I saw her! I saw Ash!
I thought she was dead!
Has she been sent down here again
without you telling me?
Muneto?
Explain this to me!
What's going on?
She acted like she didn't
even recognize me!
I can't stand not knowing!
What's going on?
BB, Dee. Do you understand?
That person he saw carries
Ash's spermia root.
Ash, the I MOA's greatest
and most highly trained warrior.
This, along with her old memories,
should be enough to revive her.
Sis!
Your mission is to resurrect something
more than this holographic image of her.
However, the person Muneto saw knows
nothing of the spermia she's carrying.
She has her own memories,
of her own experiences on Earth.
We're only one step away from the
complete rebirth of the Demon Beast.
However, you cannot forcibly destroy
this woman's current personality.
It could very well kill her!
I know this is hard for you, but there's
no other way to fight the Demon Beast.
Once she's resurrected,
give this equipment to Ash.
It will tap into her body's
power to help protect her.
Remember, this will only work for Ash.
If either of you tries to use it, it'll drain
your life energy in less than a minute.
BB, moving out!
Dee, moving out!
May your mission be successful.
Mother... Mother...
Man, this run tonight was a wash-out!
We had the home-court advantage
and she still made mincemeat out of us!
Dammit! I haven't seen
Cat's Eye race in three days...
and I'm starting to get
withdrawal symptoms!
Ohhhh!
I guess we need turbochargers, too.
Three minutes was all we needed!
Oh, God! Oh, Miki!
Oh, Great Cat's Eye!
Bless us with your presence!
Hm?
What's this? Oh, it's cute!
What is it?
Ew, it's gross!
It's so cute!
It's still just a baby!
Emi, drop it.
It's a dirty little bug!
Tsugiko? Oh, you don't understand.
Butterflies start out as caterpillars
when they're babies.
Never mind.
Just chuck the damned thing!
Hello? What? Cat's Eye?
Just be a good boy. You might get
run over if you crawl around here.
What, again? And I was
enjoying myself tonight, too!
I get tingly just seeing her!
Faster! Fast as the wind!
And once again I only get
a quick glimpse of her.
Definitely gotta save up for a turbo.
Ohhh, if I could see her
up close just once...
If I could joyride with
Miki, I could die happy!
I just don't get how she can go so fast...
Wha... What the...
Hey! Stop it!
What's...
Mother! Mother, where are you?
Mother! Mother!
BB... Dee...
It's been a while, Muneto.
Where's Kayo?
She said she felt sick and went
in the next room to lie down.
I couldn't quite get what
the Agency told me before.
Can you really bring Ash back to life?
We have to bring her back.
That's why we came.
Anyway, can you tell us anything else
about that girl you saw who looks like Ash?
Just that her name's Miki,
though she goes by...
the name Cat's Eye to all
the bikers around here.
She's got a huge following of girl bikers.
That's all the guys at the bike shop knew.
A lone wolf, huh?
Sis would have been like that if she
was born and grew up on Earth.
I've been looking for that Miki girl
at that bike shop ever since I saw her...
but she hasn't come back there.
I see. The guys at the bike
shop may be hiding her.
Hm. She's apparently been attracting more
and more girl riders as groupies lately.
They said it was getting
to be a real pain for her.
I hope we're in time.
Dee?
The Demon Beast...
may have been reborn.
What? Captain O never said
anything about that to me!
Shh! You weren't to be briefed
on it until we both got down here.
Headquarters doesn't want Kayo under
any more pressure than necessary.
Kayo!
No. No!
Kayo, what's wrong?
Get away from me!
Kayo...
Mother!
No! I hear it! I hear it!
Dee! Tranquilize her!
Mm!
Kayo!
The Demon Beast has been reborn.
What did you say?
It's a voice only Kayo can hear.
The horrible birth cries which are carried
back to the womb which first bore it!
Kayo!
It's been secretly reborn somewhere.
HQ estimates that we have a little time
before it reaches full maturity.
But it's still just an estimate!
The news! If anything unusual happens,
it's bound to show up on the news!
And now for the final news for today.
The rapid surge in the activities
of girl cycle gangs in the city...
and out to the suburbs has
become a real problem.
They all wear a yellow cat's eye insignia
on the backs of their riding suits.
This is the mark of Cat's Eye, the lone wolf
rider these girls seem to worship like a god.
At the least sight of her,
these self-proclaimed followers...
will ride after her to try and join
Cat's Eye, causing accidents as they do.
And this mania seems to be spreading.
We managed to capture some
footage of the elusive rider.
Her name is Miki.
Outside of that, this mysterious
highway star remains an enigma.
Sis!
The girls' frenzied racing
in and out of the city...
is ruining the sleep of
the local community.
40 of these so-called "teams"
have been confirmed...
although the actual number of them
may be much higher.
Authorities are calling on
Cat's Eye to end the noise...
and say they are close to
taking her into custody.
BB! Dee!
We have to try and catch her.
Now that the Demon Beast has been
reborn, we don't have a moment to lose!
BB! Dee! Take me with you!
Stay with Kayo. That's your duty!
BB... Dee...
Looks like Emi's home.
Emi!
Emi?
Help!
Help me!
Mother!
Mother! Where are you? MOTHER!
MOTHER!
Give me strength! MOTHER!
Namae mo Shiranai mama
I may not have known your name
Koi o Shiteita
but loved you anyway
Unmei ii da Nante
Even at those times
Kanjita Toki mo
I thought fate was against me
Yokan sae mo nakatta
I had no warning of it
Deatteita no ne
but I met you anyway
Sou ne Mirai Nakureta
Maybe it's that feeling of calm
Yasuragi ka mo ne
from knowing there's no tomorrow
Chiizen ni Meguru
If I should wander the earth
Odayakana Deai nara
and calmly meet you again
Itsuka Mamuretai
I know I'll see your
Sugao no Hohoemi
smile again
Chizuka ni Tsuzumikomu
Nukumori ni Setsunakute
Ima Hanareru wake
Sagasumo wa Imi mo nai
Kotome Atarashii Kaze
ga Hakonda Kaori
Kiramaeki no Jooku
Yowinde Warai Sora
Arubamu