I see it!
It's the seal of the Blue Dragon!
This isn't good.
Who's there?
It's you again?
Yeah...
Damn you!
Stay right there!
I'm sorry!
It's Takarada.
You're always causing
the creepiest trouble, kid!
Oh, it's him again.
You're always causing
the creepiest trouble, kid!
I bet he was looking for junk again.
There's a reason for the trouble!
I won't let you walk away today!
That kid cut my class again
for some stupid treasure hunt.
Please listen!
That kid cut my class again
for some stupid treasure hunt.
Please listen to me!
That kid cut my class again
for some stupid treasure hunt.
Go!
Shut up!
Oh, Mari!
What are you doing here?
What do you mean, by saying that?
Aren't we on an art class field trip?
Sorry. Hold this a sec.
Wait, Go!
Hey, hey!
Look at this!
There's a great treasure in this shrine!
Shut up!
According to the booklet
in this treasure magazine...
In this shrine...
...there's a secret door to
the treasure of Saramandara!
What?
Salamander?
Guardian Priestess,
I'm counting on you!
Gramps, watch out.
Idiots!
Someone, help me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Go!
Sis!
Leave this to me.
Run.
Sis...
Go?
Ms. Mizuki, teach him to
never mess with this shrine again!
He's still holding it up?
Go!
Thank you, Sis.
Go, don't!
Not good.
This is a thirty story building!
I knew that, but...
As you can see, I
always have a paraglider handy!
I knew that would happen!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Looks like it.
What's he up to?
Calm down.
Danger comes with any adventure.
L-In this case, I'd better...
I feel it...
Very strongly...
You were waiting for me, weren't you?
I am Rane.
Rane Che Pani Coras.
A taxi runs in my tummy
delivering sheets with that look.
This weed is cooked round and chewy.
On a hungry lake sometimes.
Excuse me?
Do you understand me?
A monkey's sock.
Looking back occasionally and rest...
Scallion?
Beef scallion?
It's an elf!
Hey, he fell.
An elf!
Figures.
I see!
There's an elf!
Figures.
Go!
It's an elf! It's an elf!
Is something wrong?
Can't you fly?
My socks are falling off!
Go!
Yeah?
Sis!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm falling!
Want some help?
P-Please!
No problem!
Activate mecha Senju!
Salvation mode on!
Elfie!
Cigar store!
Wow, looks like he's saved.
I'm so relieved.
Dummy.
Elfie! Elfie! Elfie!
Take me to the world
of dreams and adventure!
Cap.
We've detected an
anomaly in District D.
There seems to be a spacial gap in the
northwest area of the operation center.
Also, I don't like the Fire
Department's special task force.
They brought in Senju to District D
eighteen seconds after the incident.
They're investigating on their own.
Hell, big surprise.
I'll report it to the president...
Fi er'uoy gnidaer siht sdrawkcab,
uoy evah oot hcum emit no ruoy sdnah.
I see.
You already had the data.
So, you'll report it to the president?
I understand.
Then I'll file an official
complaint with the Fire Department.
Gotchabaguse!
It's an elf! It's an elf! It's an elf!
Go! Go!
Wait! What do you have?
What about an elf?
Is that it in your bag?
Show me! Show me!
Sure, sure. Take a look.
It's an elf, right?
Isn't it cute?
L-It's really true!
How? Why?
This encounter between
Go Takarada and an elf...
...seems like it was a coincidence,
but it feels like it was fated to happen!
Where the hidden treasure of
Saramandara sleeps, there is a passage to...
...another dimension, and this
city and the elf's world is connected.
This proves that the door to
the treasure exists as I theorized...
The only surprise was the
connection with an elf which is my biggest...
...and only oversight.
It makes me laugh!
In other words...
The accurate guide to the
treasure was not the magazine...
...but the Scriptures of Tazurai!
It's Tazurai!
Wait a minute!
This is it!
Ta... zu...
The Scriptures of Tazurai.
In this book...
Right here! Read it right here!
Let's see...
A long, long time ago, a tiny person
fell from the sky above Kurakama Village.
What a surprise...
What is this?
Just read on!
The little person was called the One
Inch Priest, and dug the treasure mountain...
Here. Dig, dig...
What the hell is this?
Get it?
I don't get it!
In other words, the key to
the hidden treasure is the elf.
It says so in that book.
Hold it.
An elf?
This book is all
about the One Inch Priest!
Dummy, it's the same thing!
I don't think so.
I can't argue with an amateur!
This book was
written in the Kamakura era.
Back then, people
called elves One Inch Priests!
No way!
There's no mystery about it.
There is!
Sorry, Elfie. I forgot about you.
But...
You look really good in those clothes!
Please take me to the treasure!
My hard work will pay off soon!
That's my elf!
She's so dependable!
Dad! Mom!
I bet you've discovered some
great artifact in Europe by now.
Having been raised by archaeologist
parents and taught everything...
...from insect collecting to
survival skills to ancient civilization...
...I turned out to be such a healthy guy.
Maybe I'm really the reincarnation
of some great, legendary warrior...
Go.
Wait...
That would mean that
I'm not a human being.
Go...
So who are my real parents?
Hey, Go!
What?
What about this nymph?
Nymph?
Here.
The boy who met the One
Inch Priest also encountered...
...a nymph who controlled a dragon.
A nymph who controlled a dragon?
The disgraced apple!
Thanks for the taxi and tea...
The caterpillar dropped from the stool...
I came in search of the
treasure called the Four Hearts...
...which is the symbol
that protects our land.
I was guided by the legend that
was passed down the royal family.
I was led to this land.
You must be the clever
servants that my master predicted...
...would aid me upon
my arrival, aren't you?
I feel it.
I feel the power
between you and this land.
The Four Hearts must be in this land!
Please trust my feelings!
As the legend says...
It's still soaking in the dress
from yesterday and mushy, mushy...
I guess we really do
have a language barrier.
I got it!
The nymph who controls the dragon!
The dragon is the
fire dragon, Salamander!
It's not Saramandara!
It's Salamander!
And that nymph!
Damn it!
So, that priest is the nymph!
Let's go, Elfie!
Lend me some money?
Hey, Go!
What about the door?
Take care of it!
Go...
You left me behind again.
You're always like this.
What's all this "Elfie, Elfie" stuff?
Yeah!
I'm the only one who
played your treasure hunt games...
...and survival games
ever since we were children.
Hey, you over there!
I was always, always your only friend.
It's not just because we're neighbors...
Hey, Lady!
And you were
always leaving me behind.
Lady!
What is it?
Shut up with the "Lady, Lady" stuff!
O-Oh...
I'm sorry for surprising you.
Um, let me ask you something...
Did you see an elf?
She's about my size
and age but may look more...
Are you also an elf?
Why can I understand you?
Why are you floating?
Who is that elf with Go?
Why did you come to me?
Destiny?
What's gonna happen to me and Go?
Why are you wearing clothes?
Welcome home, Madam.
Would you like some dinner?
I'll pass!
Fi uoy kniht siht si looc,
yrt gnihctaw eht latsaoc bud.
Woh hcum doow dluow a kcuhcdoow
kcuhc fi a kcuhcdoow dlouc kcuhc doow.
Mr. Takuma.
You know...
I understand you just fine, but
could you make your report in writing?
Etik?
That's it, right?
I know that the Fire
Department is making a mess, right?
I know. I'm worried, too.
Make your report in writing...
No rush. Take your time.
Therefore, any trespassing during
the project is strictly prohibited...
The Yumenokata Foundation?
What is this letter?
It's so obnoxious!
Calm down, Ms. Natsuki.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I just...
...happened to be flying in
the area with my machine...
...when my surveillance system
detected a spacial gap in District D!
I know. I know.
That damn Yumenokata...
How dare they make it sound like
I was trespassing on their property!
You're taking it too hard...
Those bastards even
announced that their own task force...
...will take care of all the
emergencies on their property from now on!
You're getting worse.
What is it, anyway?
That Yumenokata Project?
They include almost the entire city!
I wonder...
You don't know, Manager?
That's right.
All I got was a notice from
the Ministry of Development.
And?
They say it's a fabulous plan.
That's all?
That's all.
That's all...
Ms. Natsuki.
What is it?
The Fire Department
isn't a bunch of morons.
The important thing is to protect
the city and its citizens from danger...
Right?
We have ways of monitoring
outrageous corporate activity.
So, they approved
the investigation team?
Bingo!
This is the permission.
Please, can I be in charge?
Please?
Is it okay?
Me! Me!
Oh...
But that's...
No!
Say yes! Say yes! Say yes!
Say yes!
Yah!
Thank you!
Oh, my.
Did I say yes?
Elfie!
Don't you smell some hidden treasure?
Let's go treasure hunting!
Kimchee, namuru!
Um...
Excuse me, Ms. Elf?
What'll I do if she's dead?
Yub ajnin stedac
splendid report ti skcor.
Yrt cigam s'resu bulc!
L-I'm sorry, Mr. Zenshuin.
Ekaf, no problem.
Mari...
I love you.
Master Zenshuin, dinner is served.
Uknin.
You idiot!
Stop it!
L-I'm sorry!
How dare you!
Do you know who I am?
Look!
My clothes melted!
You pervert!
Um... Um...
Where's my harken?
You mean this?
Give that back!
Oh, I feel sick!
That's amazing!
You're like a witch!
I am a witch!
I'm Mari.
Mari Yumenokata.
Oh, Mari?
I'm Leen Kyami Coonyo.
Just call me Leen.
Leen, is it?
Say, by the way...
Say, by the way... Hey, the story is...
My old friend Go
met an elf like you...
My old friend Go met an elf like you...
By making a gap in Panymora...
By making a
gap in Panyora...
...and took off By making a
to some treasure. Gap in Panyora...
...and took off
to some treasure.
...and took off... I was able to find
to some treasure. Elf Princess Rane.
...and took off
to some treasure.
...and took off I can sense
to some treasure. That she's nearby.
I can sense
that she's nearby.
Is she one of you? That she's nearby.
Is she one of you?
Her scent
is strong on you.
But you aren't Her scent
exactly the same. Is strong on you.
But you aren't
exactly the same.
But you aren't exactly the same.
Did you know that?
What?
What? What?
Anyway, Salamander's
treasure must be hidden in this shrine.
The problem is finding
the door to the treasure.
According to the
Scriptures of Tazurai...
Elfie, you're the key to this door!
I'm counting on you, Elfie!
A hint... I need a hint!
Waiting for rain and padding.
Pretty alligator, stolen pond and sweet
bean bread definitely come down, yes...
This young man is
trying to show me the way...
I can feel a strong power
guiding me to the Four Hearts...
I feel a great power...
A strange feeling...
What?
You're glowing, Elfie!
In one of the first
giants you encounter...
What is that?
It's an old saying in Panyora.
I can understand you, Elfie!
What's going on?
I've never experienced this before.
You've got a nice voice, Elfie.
Elfie?
My name is Rane.
Rane Che Pani Coras.
Rane?
Rane, huh?
I'm Go Takarada.
Go?
Say it!
Say it again, Elfie!
That old saying!
All right.
In one of the first
giants you encounter...
A large stone not in people's eyes?
Um, it doesn't go like that.
I got it!
I knew this had to be the one!
A big stone.
This has to be it!
The stone has to be
exposed to people's eyes!
It needs to be moved!
Here!
You can see this spot from anywhere!
In other words!
It's in this garden!
Control.
This is Dark Bunny.
We're on the
foundation's private property.
Roger!
Redeye Bunny, stay
in the west quadrant!
Longyear Bunny, proceed eastward!
Yes, ma'am!
Find out what they're hiding!
Chief!
Go ahead.
There are some
strange people in District D.
Altogether, there's...
...a lot.
They're emitting some
sort of communication signal.
It must be the the Fire
Department's investigation team.
They're getting in our way.
Well done, Mr. Takuma.
Using examples from
ancient ruins and Feng Sui...
This hi-tech project
is the work of a genius.
I really like this report
with a how-to-read manual.
Thank you.
So, what you're saying is...
...this spacial gap in District D is
interfering with the Salamander project.
Is that what your
concern is, Mr. Takuma?
Nihs aidan.
Nihs aidan?
Cap!
The Fire Department
is in District D again.
Hctaw egairram fi er'uoy
gnikool rof gnihtemos tnereffid.
But the Salamander is in District D...
And with that earlier incident...
Can we tease them a little?
Salamander, t'nsi that
gnihtemos morf tlatseg ekil a gib drazil.
Yes, I think it's a good idea.
Tahw eht Ileh ma I gniyas.
Gotchabaguse!
Gniyalp a kcirt no eht erif tnemtraped
Iliw eb doog entertainment ekil nihsnek.
Order the
Salamander Unit to District D!
Stand by with presentation level 7!
Our target is the Fire Department.
Gotchabaguse!
Careful... Careful...
Careful, big stone.
Elfie, this is kind of
boring for an adventure, but...
...I'm getting nervous just
thinking about the treasure!
Tummy belt going down?
Good work.
What?
Ms. Mizuki, you may go home now.
I don't have to.
Something's happening, right?
So, you're staying?
For overtime pay, of course.
I see.
This is how you spell your ABC's...
This and that and so on...
Surprised, Ms. Mizuki?
You're the first to see this room.
It's part of the Yumenokata
Foundation's City Amusement Plan.
The Yumenokata Foundation?
That infamous city
development project?
Yes.
Actually...
...it's an outrageous plan to turn
the whole city into an amusement park.
This is one of the
chosen areas of the theme park.
I guess the system will be
activated now on the president's whim.
Activated?
The state-of-the-art roller
coaster, Salamander Mountain!
Salamander?
Program standby okay!
Gotchabaguse!
Haruki.
Mizuki, what are you doing there?
I'm a part-time priestess.
I see.
Haruki, sorry for such sort notice...
...but could you lend me
that purple suit tomorrow?
Why?
A date?
Really?
But not that one.
Why not?
It won't look good on you.
They're twins...
We look the same!
All right!
I moved the big stone to the
garden to be exposed to people's eyes.
Finally, something will happen...
Something...
Right?
Big fat!
W-What is that?
Fur ball is rolling and pants...
What's that?
What's wrong?
A rumbling sound
like a beast's roar!
What?
A beast's roar?
Salamander
A beast's roar? Activation okay!
Only raccoons and
wild pigs are up there!
Open all gates!
Only raccoons and wild pigs are up there!
All entrance
gates open!
All entrance It doesn't sound
gates open! Like a raccoon!
All entrance
gates open!
Could it be
a monster?
Open exit gates! A monster?
Open exit gates!
Open exit gates! Give me a break!
Give me a break!
All exit gates opened! Give me a break!
All exit gates opened!
Don't you guys have any balls!?
Don't you guys
have any balls?
Start count down! Have any balls?
Start count down!
Start count down! Yes!
You didn't have
to answer that!
Five! To answer that!
You didn't have
to answer that!
How's the big stone?
No reaction yet?
What?
What's going on?
It's here!
What's there?
A monster!
Asshole!
Salamander!
The fire dragon and
guardian of the hidden treasure!
This is Salamander Mountain...
Beautiful...
M-My body...
Elfie, are you okay?
Elfie!
My body is getting hot!
It's like I'm burning!
Hang in there!
You're my...
My very important Elfie!
Important?
That's right!
Very important treasure...
I felt it again...
Strongly...
Go is guiding me.
It's coming!
T-These letters...
I saw them in the Scriptures of Tazurai!
This is my land's...
Panyora's language.
Here it is!
It's these symbols!
To the clever adventurer who
will solve Salamander's mystery...
This is the heart
stone of the Salamander.
Follow the guidance of Tazurai
and move on to the next treasure...
Wow! I knew it!
This stone itself is the hidden treasure!
No, it says, "Sorry,
you didn't win. Go east."
So it's just a signpost.
You did it, Go!
That's my boy, Go!
Please listen to me...
The treasure is rolling away!
The signpost is rolling away!
It's wonderful.
It's dangerous!
Ms. Mizuki, let's get out of here!
T-The monster was
actually a roller coaster!
But it exploded!
There are fires on the mountain!
Damn that Yumenokata!
Making such a dangerous thing!
Those Fire Department bozos!
What did they do?
Hey, is the Salamander broken already?
Azwoy! My project
si enog htiw eht dniw!
Look, Elfie...
Salamander's treasure is
vanishing with its guardian dragon...
The dragon protected
the treasure by destroying it.
Wasn't that just an accident?
This is the prologue to our adventure.
It's only just begun, Elfie!
The true adventure!
Let's go!
Treasure!
Go! Go!
Um...
You're looking for the
Four Hearts, aren't you?
Good bath...
Isn't it?
It's making my body so soft...
Why did I come here anyway?
You came looking for the elf
that Go took with him, didn't you?
Yeah...
That's right!
I'm going to kill Rane!
Hey, what are you doing?
Phoenix!
Leen!
Go's elf!
What are you talking about?
Stay tuned for the next episode!