Maruki, give me a status report.
Yes. He died about a week ago,
and Proto Machine number four...
was administered two hours ago.
Mother!
How sad that they become such things
when pulled from death's grasp.
Kaidoh.
Yes.
There's no time. l only have
a limited amount of power left.
l understand.
L-Lady Mother, please wait a bit longer!
l'm counting on you.
l see. Well then let me
tell your fortune with this.
What?
Go! Kick her ass! Yeah!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much!
Take that!
This isn't even a challenge.
What the... He's not getting hurt
even if l shoot him.
Damn.
Uh oh!
Ladies, l hope you enjoyed your time off.
Now, here's your next mission...
There are reports of dead bodies...
Episode 1: Suspicion
Rumor has it that the Lady Mother
is several hundred years old.
That's a story that you
hear a lot in modern cults.
The founder of Charisma, Kaidoh Ochi, is
backed by a lady mother of unknown age.
Sounds more interesting than
checking out some hospital!
Hello.
Oh Shiori, l hear that cast
is going to come off soon.
Doctor Maruki said he'd
take the cast off tomorrow.
What's the matter? You seem sad.
When you get out, we should hang out.
l still have my rehab.
l see, so you still have more to go.
You can do it, Shiori.
l hope you get to walk again soon.
Yeah. See you later.
Shiori's entire family died in a bad
accident, and she's the only survivor.
Any relatives?
She has no siblings, and her
grandparents are already deceased.
That's a bleak future.
Even when she gets out,
she doesn't have anywhere to go.
Doctor Giin, please try to relax.
We will now begin the ceremony.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Now is the time for you to rise.
You will gather a flock
that will rise above all others.
You will be the one to lead
these weak and lost lambs.
The word of God shall protect you.
Do what you believe,
what your soul tells you to do.
lt is done.
Thank you for your work.
That man will stand at the apex.
He had the power to change the world.
''Had,'' you say?
He will eventually die.
He is taking the long
route to regaining his time.
lf we treated him now we could
extend his life, but he would not wish it.
130 years ago, his great grandfather
sacrificed himself for me and fell.
Their dispositions are very similar.
lt feels almost like yesterday.
Having lived since the era of Heian,
l have seen the whole of humanity.
l'm sorry, Mother. lf l had inherited
even a little of your power...
lt is better that you did not.
To make someone relive the pain
of death even after their life ends...
Mother, please don't say such things.
Kaidoh, my last son, with those hands...
Mother...
Let me sleep for a little while.
l will send over the directions
for the teachings to your terminal.
Call for Maruki!
Hey, you really did your research.
lt passes the time. l snuck in
my laptop and tried a bunch of hacks.
But there's something weird
with this place's security.
That tells me a lot. Thanks!
Hey, l bet you're pent up.
Ah, nurse, you really don't...
You came already?
Figures it wouldn't work.
They keep getting ahead of me.
Bingo! How'd l get in suddenly? Huh?
They have Shiori's data too.
But why? What reason do they
have to keep this data separate?
Y-Yes, Kiriku General.
What? They're on the verge of dying?
lt wasn't that bad this morning!
Strange. And the other hospitals?
Then you don't have to send them here!
Our beds are full, dammit!
You! Quit fooling around!
There are important calls around here!
Y-Yes sir! l'm sorry.
Christ. And you! Where were you?
Did you check on Mr. Harada?
Doctor Maruki, please check
on Mr. Harada in room 303!
Patients with no relatives?
Shiori
Yes, everyone who
was in that separate data...
Yeah... They even bring in patients
from other hospitals who all...
for some reason or another,
share that one common thing.
Being backed by a large parent
company, they're supposed to be...
known for accepting any
patient who comes in, but...
there's a patient whose
very existence was erased.
lf we think about the reason,
then the information the boss got...
that dead bodies vanish from
this hospital, becomes more credible.
That's right.
What's it mean?
We don't know yet. We can be sure
that the hospital is definitely...
neck deep in some
highly illegal activity.
Shiori, you poor thing.
Hey you monks! What did you
do with the patient who died today?
Dirty trick.
l guess it's just about
time to make our rounds.
Hey, what are those guys for?
Oh l thought they might
cheer up Shiori a bit. See?
Sure, but you're not allowed
to bring animals into the hospital.
Oh l see, they were your Shikigami.
Hey, what happened to Yuka?
You know, she went to go check
on how Shiori was doing a while ago...
Oh crap!
Yuka, where are you?
Come on! Where are you?
Yuka!
Those damned monks!
No good. l can't access
the company's main computer!
l've never seen such
complex protection before.
lt's not the hospital planning
something. lt's the parent company!
Hey, what the hell are they
using the dead bodies of patients for?
Dogs.
Come on Doctor Maruki...
Sakura, did you have a reason for
pulling me in here?
l want to have sex with you.
Oh, Doctor Maruki, you're so big!
l can die happy right now! l never
thought a woman would do this to me!
l'm in heaven!
Sakura, l'm cumming.
Can l cum in your mouth?
Yes, as much as you'd like.
Owww oww! What are you doing?
Where did the patients
who were taken out of here go?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
Snake!
Tell me now!
Why don't you stop right there.
Kaidoh Ochi.
Well now, l was wondering
what kind of stray dog wandered in,
but you're quite a lovely nurse.
Beautiful. You're just my type.
Damn it, l lost. The company main
computer has to be alive or something!
We got trouble!
Sakura's gone!