Things seem to happen at random
but it actually follows a planned route.
That becomes cause and effect.
The power of the ring.
Allows you to...
bend that rule to your will.
Blue light leads the way,
black leads to destruction.
The polarity of the soul.
Who are you?
Just like you.
We are both related to my father.
We are related?
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
You don't like being with women?
Open up to me.
I want to know more about you.
Episode 2:
"The concerto of strange incontinuity"
There's been a lot of protest
by the local residents...
against the construction going on
around the Ken point, at the lake.
They're protesting daily.
And your mother is apparently responsible
for all the construction there.
This is apparently what she found.
I didn't know you knew her ID password.
Made things much easier for me.
Thank you.
So, Takuya...
I wasn't necessarily trying to help you.
So, what is this stone?
An old legend from this city
always warned people...
to stay away from the Ken point,
at the lake.
The fire of life.
What are you doing?
Something like this!
I can't, Mitsuki!
I can't do this anymore.
When we're alone by ourselves,
just the two of us...
you can be a woman, not a mother.
No!
Please, Mitsuki, we can't do this anymore.
We can't turn back now.
I know you want to see him, right?
Him? Who are you talking about?
Well...
What are you hiding from me, Mitsuki!
All the money spend to excavate this rock...
I suppose most of us can't understand
how rich people think.
It's a real puzzle.
What are you talking about?
What are you two doing in there?
They came faster than I expected.
Let's go!
Hold it!
This is going to be a serious problem.
Ayumi.
You can tell me, Takuya.
Who is she?
What does she want with the stone?
I swear I don't know.
I know you're not going to believe me!
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry Ayumi!
Wait, Takuya!
Leaving?
How about one more time?
I have to go now.
You are coming tomorrow?
If you want.
I'll be waiting.
Meow!
So where is it?
Don't rush me.
I need to shower.
I gave you the pin code last week.
Use it as you like.
Do you trust me?
I'd like you to think so.
The locker I showed you.
It will be in there.
After I get what I asked for, of course.
You're careful!
I'm a pro.
All right, just be sure to take care of it.
Be especially careful around water.
I know.
Take your time.
Before I forget.
The uniform I borrowed.
It's way too short.
I was practically flashing everyone.
Some women like to be seen, you know.
Shit, where did she go?
I should have at least asked for her name.
I'm feeling very weak.
You are...
Canna Hatano.
Who are you?
That's something daddy's
going to find out for himself.
All I can do is wait for you.
Hold on!
I'll be waiting, papa.
I'll fix both of us some breakfast.
I think it's almost ready.
Sure.
I passed out after that.
You used up too much power too quickly,
so your body couldn't adjust.
Do you know what's going on?
What's going on around me?
There's nothing I can really do for you.
That's all I can say.
Is it good?
I want to ask you something.
I live alone.
I'm by myself.
My mother passed away.
My father.
He lives near here, but I don't think
he knows anything about me.
What is it?
I have to go.
Just return my keys in the mailbox.
Are you leaving?
Now?
It's important.
What the hell.
I don't understand what's happening to me.
That girl.
Wow!
See?
The older guys really go for that look.
Don't you think?
You'd look good in a paper bag, Canna.
She's the number one,
most requested girl here.
Hiya!
That's Sakaimachi Academy's uniform.
I'm a student there.
Do you know Miyo Shimizu?
The daughter of the treasurer.
No wonder she's so wealthy.
Canna, you have a customer.
Wait!
You're leaving like that?
I'll be wearing my skirt.
With your bloomers?
They like this kind of stuff.
Okay.
She's not coming out.
What's she doing?
I'll find out.
What is Canna doing here?
Canna Hatano.
You know there's rumors about her.
Do you want to eat first?
I don't think this is right.
Do you know what you're doing?
I do this so I can survive.
Stop it, and put on some clothes.
The only people that really need me
here are my clients.
This is the only reason I continue
to remain in this world.
Remain in this world?
You scared off my client for the day.
Sleep with me.
What a shame.
It's not a ring.
With our technology...
this is the best we can do.
How sad.
Miyo, is that you?
I didn't know Canna was
in possession of one.
You're acting weird today.
What's wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with me.
Right, Canna?
Give me the pendant.
I can't, I'll die without it.
I'll have to force you.
Stop it, Miyo!
Get out of my way!
This is...
Why am I?
What am I?
Takuya, the asshole!
Where could he possibly be
so late at night?
Hey Ayumi!
He acts like he really cares about me.
So why isn't he here to pick me up?
Ayumi, I'm here.
What is this?
I should have had Toyotomi take me home.
What are you saying?
Did I hear something?
Teleportation.
Without the key?
Run, Takuya, right now!
Give it to me!
Miyo is not herself right now!
I'm totally lost here.
Again?
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Are you okay, papa?
You again.
You teleported too many times,
so things are starting to destabilize, papa.
Are you saying I'm your father?
Papa is papa, right?
I think you can get up now,
but how do you feel?
I can see your underwear, Ms. Eriko.
You're doing fine.
Where is Canna, Miyo?
How should I know?
I'm going to continue my walk.
You should be home
doing your homework, kid.
Don't be hanging out, wasting your time!
I thought I heard something.
Do you have to get drunk to hit on a guy?
That's just so uncool.
I can see your underwear, ma'am.
I don't really have any interest
in you as a person...
but I do want to know more about
what you're studying in your lab.
No!
Stop!
Please!
Tell me your ID code.
No, let me go!
Do you like fooling around in the car?
Get off me!
Why are you doing this?
She looks pretty damn good for her age.
She's not just a mature woman.
Widow, she's a widow.
That sounds like something special!
I can make you forget...
about your dead husband tonight!
Why are you doing this?
Money, and we're very bored.
These girls are really good at what they do.
I can make them stop right away...
if you tell me your ID code.
No!
I can't!
What's going on there!
Is there something wrong with me?
Hey, little punk!
Hi Mitsuki!
You might want to go home
and console your mother.
Unless you're waiting for your date
here or something.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling better?
Yes.
Thank you, Toyotomi.
This will make you feel better.
How did you find me?
I know everything abut my boss.
I need to go change.
Toyotomi!
I didn't know you wore lingerie.
I would love to see you in one.
This makes me feel
like I'm very close to you.
Out!
Out, this isn't fair.
Things between a man and a woman
is never fair.
No!
Stop!
You should just forget about everything.
About tonight.
About your late husband.
I can't.
Now, spread your legs.
I can't!
Just do as I say!
That's right!
I'll help you forget those bad memories.
Toyotomi.
I'm home!
I'm coming!
Takuy, you...
He rescued you from getting raped?
This sounds really fishy.
He's tricking you, Ayumi.
Even if you're right...
Sometimes ignorance is bliss.
I'm not...
I'm not strong, I don't like to be alone.
But, I'm here.
I am your mother.
I need a lover.
It's not like I can talk to you
about a lot of things.
But...
Why?
You see, kid?
She doesn't need your help anymore.
Is that true, Ayumi?
You don't need me?
I don't need you.
I don't need you to help me!
Don't let them fool you!
Canna?
She waiting for you, in a world far away.
Need papa's help.
Nobody's waiting for you.
She likes being with me, and you know it.
Just forget about her and leave her to me.
Don't forget anyone, papa!
Otherwise, you'll never see them!
You'll never see mama...
or Yu-no.
Yu-no.
Just give me the damned pendant!
I can't.
You.
Damn it!
Miyo, stop it!
Mr. Teleportation is with us again!
- You can't.
- What?
Right now, Miyo is not
the person you know.
What can I do?
What happened to her?
None of your business!
Without the key, and if we get rid
of the pendant.
You won't be able to teleport anymore at all.
Everything will be back to normal.
No one will suffer again!
Don't you agree, Canna?
You're wrong.
That's not true.
Don't Canna, it's dangerous!
I know of a way to bring Miyo back
to her true self.
It's okay.
I will take your spell away.
Miyo?
Takuya, you...
I don't think it worked.
Who the hell are you?
Takuya?
After.
Take care of her, papa.
Canna!
Canna, what's wrong!
She can't live without
her pendant, she's dying.
Takuya, please.
Are you okay?
You can't?
This is the first time I felt afraid
of dying in my entire life.
Did you know I always hated you?
But I think I lived this long
so I could meet you.
Stop it, Canna!
Don't!
Answer me!
Canna, Canna!
To Be Continued