I want to see you see you again, Father.
Did I hear something?
Damn it, I can't find them.
Where could they possibly be?
It's 10:00 already.
What could they talking about this late?
This is so nostalgic.
Do you remember how the three of us
used to come here with Kodai, Mitsuki?
Ayumi, you know I did not come here
to reminisce about old times.
If it's about the stone,
I can't tell you anything right now.
You should trust me, Ayumi.
Mitsuki!
Stop!
We are best friends, right?
What are you?
What's going on?
What is this ring?
I never would have thought...
I would find the key like this.
Mitsuki, Ayumi!
Takuya, what are you doing here?
Hand the ring over to me.
Mitsuki?
You have no need for it.
What is this about, Mitsuki?
Stop, Mitsuki, you're not like yourself
at all today, stop this!
Hurry up!
Go, Takuya!
Hurry Ayumi!
Takuya, wait!
Run Ayumi!
Takuya wait!
Wait, Takuya!
First episode: The spectacle of seduction
Would you like to borrow any underwear?
I'm all right.
It's no problem, really.
Well, I'll leave the bath towel here, okay?
Thank you.
Hey Ayumi!
Who is it?
Ayumi!
Yes I'm Ayumi.
Who are you?
Are you okay, you're not hurt?
You, get out, you sick pervert!
What are you talking about,
it's me, Takuya.
Takuya?
I'm going to catch a cold!
Stop, wait!
Ayumi, please wait!
Miyo, what are you doing here?
Mitsuki did what?
Yeah, and she was going to shoot me!
I'm flattered that you would be willing
to protect me even in your dreams.
But Mitsuki is my very, best friend.
I couldn't have been dreaming, really!
My god!
That was what this whole mess was about?
You're just such a troublemaker.
So Miyo, what are you doing here?
It's none of your business, Takuya.
Is having her here a problem?
Ayumi, I didn't know you two were friends.
Do you guys not like each other?
We were both walking back home...
when a sudden rainstorm soaked us.
You really have no reason to be
jealous or anything.
Ayumi, you have it all wrong, because
I have no interest whatsoever in Miyo.
Same to you.
It's hard to believe that a barbarian
like you is Ayumi's stepson!
Ten o'clock again.
Takuya, please walk Miyo back to her house.
That's all right!
But, it's not safe to walk alone at night!
It's not my fault that she's been
hanging out here until it's late!
Wait, I was investigating the lake.
What I do is really none of your business!
I'm leaving now!
What was that?
Why can't you be nicer?
Are you listening? Hey, Takuya?
Was that only a dream?
But this ring is proof.
It always seems like Miyo always
looks perfect, don't you think?
I don't understand why someone with her
grades is here for a review session.
Hey Takuya!
So, you're here for the review?
If I recall, Canna's her name, I think.
You know there's rumours about her.
Rumours, like what kind?
I thought you might know more about that.
What makes you think that?
I just thought, never mind!
Wow, fighting so early already?
Miss Eriko!
I would be happy to give you
relationship counseling.
What relationship?
Yeah, she's not my girlfriend!
Right, I would never pick you!
Whatever.
Miss Mitsuki!
Don't stare at me so much!
The usual place, after class, okay?
I'm really sorry!
What's wrong?
No worries, no one will find us here.
I can't believe I'm carrying on with
my best friend's stepson.
But this secretive,
kinky stuff really turns me on.
Where were you last night, Mitsuki?
I thought I was in bed with you.
Did you go down to the lake?
We'll talk about that later.
Hi Miyo.
What's going on?
This is the staff changing room.
Why, would I be in the way
of anything here?
Then, I hope you don't mind
if I change here.
I really need to change, so if you
don't mind, please leave, Takuya.
That's not convenient.
We were having an important
conversation right now.
Then, please go ahead.
Go ahead, I'll promise I won't be listen.
Will you excuse us?
Sure.
I am presuming that you have something
you want to tell me?
It's a disgrace to seduce Takuya
for your entertainment.
You're just out to corrupt him!
It's only been a year since Kodai died.
Takuya's still somewhat stand-offish
and won't call me mom.
No, I can't be getting depressed liked this!
Yes, I have so much to do!
What are you doing Takuya?
I was about to say the same thing.
What are you doing here at school?
I wanted to converse with Mitsuki today.
Yeah, Mitsuki's.
Something going on with Mitsuki?
No, nothing.
Are you sure?
You're not hiding something
from me, are you?
What makes you think that?
You're sure?
Sure.
If you say so.
I've been looking for you.
Mr. Toyotomi!
We're having problems.
We're back to our original plan.
The local group?
We need to go back to the headquarters.
Yes.
I'm going to be late tonight,
so don't wait for me for dinner.
Will you be okay?
Be careful.
I didn't mean to interrupt this morning.
Shit, there's nothing going on,
for god's sake.
You're embarrassed.
Wait, let me give you a word of advice
for all it's worth.
Remember that things happening right now,
as well as your past, is not absolute.
There are many outcomes to any situation,
and the reality will morph accordingly.
Situation?
Reality?
What are you talking about?
You'll eventually see what I'm talking about.
And my advice might prove to be
very useful, but just keep it in your head.
Just remember what I said.
Did I tell you that I called him last night?
So tell me what happened!
Miyo?
Come to pick another fight?
Come with me!
What, all of a sudden?
Just come with me!
Hey, slow down!
So Miyo, do you like Takuya or something?
Well, I don't think this situation
is healthy for anyone.
Well, I like him.
Well.
What?
Miss Mitsuki?
That was your first kiss?
Stop!
So, do you think you have something
to offer as a woman?
What?
I know there are lots of things I can do
to make him very happy.
So what's your point?
Remember that women love men
using their entire body.
You can't even tell him
how you feel...
much less do anything that could
possibly please him.
I can.
Hey, Takuya.
Hey, are you reading?
My dad had the very same book, too.
God, go put some clothes on!
Wait. Can you really read it?
I finally found it and bought it,
but I haven't been able to read it at all.
So how is it?
I can only read a bit.
Great. What does it say?
It says something about being
a path between the lake...
and the old well here.
Go on.
Will you get dressed?
Will you come to the well with me?
Why me?
I don't have much time left here.
So, what's your fascination with this?
I read one of the books your father wrote
about the lake...
and was really intrigued.
Yeah, about the old legend here...
something about the remains of an ancient,
advanced, culture.
I think it's great that the city I was born in
has such a great legend.
My father had strange ideas,
wrote some really kooky stuff.
That's not true...
he wasn't a kook.
He was your father.
So, are you going to listen to me?
Something about you traveling?
No, I'll be studying overseas!
Overseas, that's cool!
It was my father's decision.
I'll be leaving after this school break.
I thought before I leave.
Hey, is that the well?
Wait, let me finish first!
No rush, that's plenty of time.
Lots of time to make great memories.
Takuya.
What's it like down there?
Come on, tell me!
Well, this well is quite deep.
What's wrong?
What the hell is this?
Catch it, I'll throw it up there.
What is it?
It was stuck on the well wall here,
did you catch it?
Are you okay, Takuya?
What is going on?
Get back.
What is going on here?
What are you?
I'll be waiting for you, father.
Are my lectures really so boring?
No, absolutely.
I'm in the classroom?
Hey, wait up, Miyo.
What the hell do you want with me?
Don't ever talk to me!
This is all I can do.
This is all the data regarding that stone.
Where is it located?
This really is the best I can.
You will take me there?
What's up with Miyo's weird attitude today?
What did I do?
Takuya!
Ayumi, are you all right?
Nothing's wrong, but I really need
to get going right now. Bye!
I'm sorry I wasn't able to come back
home last night.
I couldn't leave work.
Don't worry about that.
Last night?
Wait a minute, you were at home
with Miyo the other night!
Me, with Miyo?
If you're dreaming about her why
don't you ask her out?
That was a dream?
Takuya!
Go home, stay out of trouble, and...
return this...
to Ayumi, please.
Wait. Those breasts.
You would only notice the breasts.
I already told you nothing's absolute.
You can't see the truth
unless you open your mind.
You must be Takuya, right?
Yeah, so?
I want you to forward a message
to your mother.
You mean Ayumi?
Tell her that further research is dangerous.
The "fire of life" is not for people
of this world.
Wait a minute, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Please, just tell her exactly what I said.
The rock should be returned
to its original location.
I need to get going now.
Hey, wait a minute!
Give her the message, please.
What is going on?
I'm getting more confused by the minute.
Want to know?
Do you want to know
what your mother's researching...
and hiding from the world?
Let me tell you a secret.
To be continued