Almost...
two months...
already.
I don't think...
I can...
make it...
anymore.
Strange...
no guards posted tonight.
I don't think...
I can escape...
anyway.
I didn't think you would be
the one to save me.
But is it all right?
Shouldn't we be on the run?
I'm sorry...
you've been...
treated very badly.
That's all right.
Just answer my question.
You should clean up first.
What do you mean?
This coming ceremony
is a very sacred event.
Everyone else except the head
priestess and her priestess...
is not allowed to stay in the castle.
That explains the absence of the guards.
This is the last stage here.
Main characters are limited in any play.
Who?
I might only have a small role
if everyone forgets me so easily!
Ms. Eriko?
Who.
Is somebody here?
That can't be.
Mama said we were the only ones
in the castle.
I thought there wasn't anybody here...
except for the two priestesses.
That must be the priestess.
Where's my underwear?
There!
Hiya!
You must be punished for your trespass.
Who are you?
Takuya?
Yu-No Episode 4
I'm sorry mama.
No, as long as you're all right.
But, I let all of them go!
Don't worry, just worry about
the upcoming ceremony.
Yes, mama.
That's really strange.
This area is protected by magic...
they shouldn't be able to move
freely around the castle.
It can't be him.
Who can he be?
Here, at Della Grand...
everything is considered very sacred...
and decisions made by the high priestess
is considered the word of god.
This is actually the real answer.
Everything in this world is...
controlled by this computer
network right here.
This place is like a diorama large scale.
I understand that.
But can somebody get me down?
I told you to just wear only your underwear.
Here, those with too much desire
will be restrained by it.
Your physical body is the only thing
that's really free.
Then you shouldn't be able
to wear underwear!
That's something I brought.
That's not of this world.
A bra?
Don't have one.
Takuya said it's not a good idea
to restrain breasts.
Wait, where did he go?
He wants to be alone now.
What?
He needs to concentrate his energy
on facing his fate.
You are so obsessed with the idea of fate.
I think it's comforting.
There's something of a bond
with the idea of fate.
Like you're not alone.
Stop that!
I think you will understand someday.
My life is in your hands, after all!
What's wrong?
I told you.
Here, those with too much desire...
are restrained by it in some way.
It's not much, but...
I'm a related to the priestess in this world.
Papa!
No, stop that!
Stop, help me!
No!
Stop, don't!
Papa, Papa!
No!
We'll see each other again.
Must get revenge.
Very soon...
we will meet again!
Kaytia!
I think I'm all right.
Don't worry about me.
I'm glad.
A coin from this world.
When I was a little girl...
I found the same exact coin.
I don't know where I got it.
I carried it as a lucky charm.
I lost it when I dropped it in a well
in my back yard.
It's a bond with this world.
A bond?
Then you've come here
for a very good reason.
Takuya.
Wait!
I have to go!
It's a bad idea.
He's not himself right now.
You'll see him soon enough.
I need to see him now!
I have so much I have to say!
You're going to be one with Grandia.
Just concentrate on that.
I know, that's why I was born,
and it's my fate!
I was born so I could save the world!
Him!
Why can't I stop thinking about him?
Watch out!
You are...
here again!
Takuya. Really.
Takuya.
Right?
Mama!
You've finally come here!
But how?
It can't be.
Ayumi.
You're late!
I was waiting a long time for you.
Mama, you know this man?
Who is he?
Sorry to interrupt this reunion.
Leave, I know you have
other things to do.
I don't need you to tell me.
Mama, tell me who he is!
His identity is not important
to you right now.
Now, come with me!
Yes, I know.
Wait!
Go, out of my way!
I'm your only opponent right now, Takuya.
So, you don't remember me anymore, I see.
You're Toyotomi!
I'll tell you something interesting.
You know Selles?
She's my sister.
Takuya!
We're not related by blood!
We were both orphans back then.
A priestess named Kaytia adopted us.
We were brought up as a family.
Stop it!
Mi yo?
Get out of my way!
The idea of a priestess saving the world
is just a fable!
You don't have to sacrifice yourself!
We'll meet again.
We have a special bond
between us called family.
But I don't want you to go!
You're all I have in the world!
Kaytia!
I wanted to see her again.
So I wandered all over the world.
Even wandered different dimensions, but...
When I finally found her at last,
she was already dead...
She died, to give birth to you!
Do you see?
Keiko Arima!
Your dead mother is Kaytia, my mother!
You aren't here at random,
you're here because of a connection.
You have had everything
I ever wanted out of life!
A mother's love.
A mother's warmth!
And my mother's blood!
Please, stop now!
I have reason to hate you!
I have every reason to take
everything you have!
Give No back!
Kaytia's blood!
I have it! I finally have it!
More, I want more!
I want to feel her presence!
More!
I'm coming to see you Kaytia...
right now...
The head priestess.
Can you feel Grandia?
I think I'm almost there!
We need to hurry, we don't have time!
We have to finish this very soon!
Takuya?
Stop Ayumi!
Please explain what's going on here!
Tell me where Yu-No is, first!
I know you know.
How does he know about me?
She isn't...
She's no longer your daughter.
Not anymore.
You're too late, you see.
You didn't arrive here until too late.
Just answer me!
Where the hell is Yu-No?
Don't hurt my mother!
Get out of the way!
Wait!
Takuya, that girl in front of you is Yu-No!
Are you...
really...
Yu-No?
Who are you?
I don't know who you are at all.
Yu-No!
I really don't know!
Takuya!
Takuya, are you okay.
This man is your father.
My father?
Papa?
This...
could be!
This event trigger something?
We must continue the ceremony!
Grandia!
But...
Hurry, now!
Right now, you have to stay
by your father's side!
You said you loved him more
than anybody else!
You have to hurry, No!
The fate of the world is in your hands.
Yes, I have to go.
Stop, wait a minute!
Just leave us alone!
Canna!
You can't leave us, Canna!
It's okay.
It's my fate, you see!
Just stop it with this fate thing!
I'll see you again!
I'm sure of it!
I'm sure we're bound together by fate!
No, Canna!
Canna!
Hurry, No, now!
Can't you see!
Evoking Grandia's presence
won't change anything.
And how do you know this?
Grandia, the creator
of this planet, Della Grand.
The tragic fate of this world is part
of her ultimate plan.
But that can't be!
The fate you are facing
is not from natural causes.
Let go!
Hurry, you need to be by your father's side!
No, I was born to save this world!
Please, listen!
Unfortunately, I know that
he wasn't looking for me!
What?
You're the only one that can save him!
Please!
See, there!
A strange scientist just moved
into that house.
It's really weird.
As soon as he saw my face...
he said "I wasn't from this world"
like he's some kind of psychic.
But, I saw his wife,
and she's really beautiful!
They said their expecting their baby soon.
What was my father like?
I want to know just a little bit.
Tell me please!
Why didn't Canna.
Why didn't she tell me anything about this?
I'm waiting.
Mom in the future.
I promise to be a good mother.
I'll raise you right!
No.
You are Takuya.
I'm papa.
Papa?
Here!
A lucky charm.
For when we meet once again.
Selles!
Yes, I understand!
Grandia's leaving now!
Ayumi.
She might be the biggest victim
out of anybody here.
Ayumi.
No, this can't be!
Things weren't supposed to go
like this at all!
I was going to be able
to fix everything!
It's okay.
It's really okay now.
I'm the one at fault here.
I was just looking out for me.
Instead of those important to me.
I didn't mean to leave you.
Takuya, don't!
Run, Ayumi!
Wait, Takuya!
I waited!
Takuya!
You're going?
It's my fate.
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
I held you responsible for so much!
What you do now will not
change the fate of this world...
or anything else.
Grandia...
she's calling me...
to her.
Besides.
You remember now?
That's impossible, she can't bring back
any of her memories.
In order to be a priestess,
you have to forget everything.
I promised already.
I really can't remember who he is.
I have to go.
I don't want regrets.
No!
I hear her.
I hear Grandia's voice,
she's calling me!
Please take responsibility.
Hi Mitsuki!
I thought you'd be here.
This is my favorite, special spot!
How about here?
It's reserved just for you.
I'm late!
I'll help you out, then!
Wait, that's my food!
Have fun!
Did you sleep?
Let's leave for school.
You're sure?
Of course.
Hey, Miyo!
Is there somebody in there with you?
No, you have to go!
But how do I get out of here?
Hurry, out the window!
This is the 2nd floor!
I'll introduce you to my dad soon.
He said we'll meet again!
Maybe this charm didn't work.
I can't stay in this world.
How are you?
You are...
Sorry I'm late!
Can I ask a question?
Sure.
I tried hard, but I really can't
remember who you are.
Do I have to be your daughter?
I think...
I'm falling in love with you.
Can... I... Can I love you as a woman
and not a daughter?
With mom's blessing.
I never used to like predictable
happy endings.
But this is all right.
I hope to see them again.
No, I'm sure I will.