One, two, three, four...
...five, six, seven, eight...
Yuka!
I'm coming!
Hurry up!
Fruits Cup, Episode One
There...
P-Please let me go!
Is this...
Could this be a hidden camera?
We're finally here!
You think you can quit after all this?
In your dreams!
You two...
Decide which of you will be next.
Oh, I certainly don't mind doing
both of you at the same time!
This is great.
Rich chicks like you
becoming my sex slaves!
Great job for Seika Academy, huh?
I'll come and pick
you all up in two weeks.
Thank you very much.
What are we doing for fun?
We're here for training
camp, don't forget that!
Everybody expects the Seika Academy
swimming team to win big this year.
Yoshino...
Excuse me!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Hello, the Seika Academy
swim team has now arrived.
Where's the caretaker?
I'm the caretaker.
I'm sorry, I was expecting
someone much older.
The original caretaker has been
hospitalized due to an accident...
...so, I was assigned to take
over his place in a hurry.
I see.
I'm Nagisa Kasuga, the swim
team advisor for Seika Academy...
...as well as the leader of the squad.
I'm Riku Omi.
When you say you're an advisor,
you mean a teacher right?
I thought you were also a student.
You won't get any rewards
for your compliments.
You seem very happy, Ms. Nagisa.
You changed your clothes already?
But...
Yep, Yoshino is very excited.
Oh, all right.
Just introduce yourself.
I'm Yoshino Kanmi!
I wanna eat and swim a lot and try
to get in shape during our stay!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Matsuri Nanashima.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Caretaker.
Shiori, go introduce yourself.
Shiori Sena.
I'm sorry, she doesn't talk much.
No, they are all fine students.
Well for the next two weeks, I hope you
can take care of us, Mr. Caretaker.
Of course.
What a bummer!
I have to get home quick and change!
Hey, you all right?
So this is how he plays...
Holy cow!
I'm gonna call an ambulance!
This much?
What is this large sum of
money? For saving that guy?
I can't...
Please, take the money, it's for
saving one of our important employees.
Actually, I do have
a favor to ask of you.
Okay...
I know it's sudden...
...and rude but...
...how would you like to be in charge
of a dormitory in the southern island...
...to be a replacement for
that man you just saved?
Substitute?
Caretaker of a dormitory?
Yes. Will you just listen
to what I have to say?
It's really not that bad.
He convinced me well enough
and I took the job...
...replacing that guy
who was hospitalized.
But I found something terrible.
This guy in the video...
...he must be the guy that I saved.
He was the one who took these videos.
His face is not visible, but
I know it's definitely him.
Plus, there's so many...
"My rape diary"...
...by Nero Dokujima?
August 10th, Clear day.
After all my hard work, I have finally
obtained the secrets of my prey.
It's good to have hidden cameras to
capture them in the bath or the toilet...
...but it's better to have a secret
that they don't want anyone to know.
I didn't know she was
an exhibitionist, but...
...my data collecting skills
have paid off big time.
August 11th, Cloudy.
She came to my office before
bedtime with some snacks and said...
..."Thank you for all your
services, Mr. Caretaker"
They don't even realize I taped them
real good when they were taking a bath.
What a nice group of girls.
They show their trust even though
I'm only pretending to do my job.
They were very cautious at first...
...now they are under my control.
August 12th, I finally got my prey
named Natsumi to come to the office...
...and I violated her to the limit.
After showing the material
that I got of her...
...her facial expression changed
from cheerful to despair.
The feeling I get
from that is fantastic.
Once you get the material and
threaten them, they become your slave.
Obtain the material and
threaten them with it, huh?
Now I'll violate you while
you wear your team swimsuit.
Team swimsuit...
Team swimsuit!
Team swimsuit?
Team swimsuit is the best eh?
Team swimsuit is the best.
No, no! What am I saying?
I'm gonna be very busy
with work starting tomorrow!
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
Darn.
Let's start with this room.
I'm gonna get in shape...
Weird taste.
I can't...
I don't wanna be like that guy.
But it's really her
fault for oversleeping.
Plus she didn't even lock her room.
Does she trust me, or
is she just playing with me?
Team swimsuits...
This one has a skirt!
The seam is from the underarm
to the crotch area.
This must be the mother
of all team swimsuits.
It's the prototype of swimsuits.
How lucky...
Um...
Are the swimsuits dry?
I would like to take them inside.
Ah, eh, yeah, sure, y-yeah...
Okay, okay...
What an ugly poster to
be placed on the wall.
I'll replace it with a
poster of my favorite idol.
No! Stop it.
Wait!
Is this...
This hole, could it be?
Hurry up everyone!
I'm ready!
Hey, just wait a minute!
Watch it!
I'm not gonna drop you!
It's dangerous if you fool around!
Help! Someone!
Stop it, Yoshino!
What happened?
The water!
Hurry up and fix it!
But...
Come on!
Hurry!
Oh, they were wearing their swimsuits.
Oh man...
You're disappointed that
we weren't naked right?
What are you saying?
Aha, you got mad! How scary!
Hey! Stop making fun of people!
Ha-ha, you got mad again!
Come back here!
Ouch!
The caretaker's a pervert!
It's true!
Perv, perv, perv, perv!
Damn it!
Are they toying with me?
Bastards!
We'll see who's the boss!
Transformation complete!
It's great to be in a
swimsuit on a hot day like this.
But the caretaker is a guy so...
It's all right. He seemed
pretty harmless to me.
Plus it said in my magazine
that women become beautiful...
...when a guy looks at them.
The prototype is the best.
The water needs to drain from the chest
area down through the crotch area...
...so the skirt and the crotch
section are dual structured.
The top part of the crotch
section is not sewn and left open.
That way, you can put your
hand deep into the body.
It makes every guy's fantasy come true.
That is what the
prototype swimsuit does.
Now, let's use the secret device.
What transparency!
Bath time, bath time!
Thanks for waiting, Yoshino!
Have you had any sexual
experience, Matsuri?
W-Why do you ask?
Well, in the magazine that
I'm reading right now...
...it said girls become
women after experiencing sex.
So what about you, Matsuri?
What do you mean...
Ah, so you're not in that kind of a
relationship with your half-brother?
Of course not.
Then Matsuri, have
you masturbated before?
Um, l...
So you have.
B-But I'm sure everyone has.
Everyone?
Wait, you haven't done it Yoshino?
Me?
Well of course I've done it.
I'm not so immature.
Even Matsuri is masturbating...
Since Matsuri isn't here right now...
Let's see...
...place my fingers...
I guess I need to
caress my breasts too...
W-What is this?
Right here...
It feels really weird...
This...
I see...
This must be self-satisfaction!
It feels good!
But I'm kinda scared...
I wonder when I can
become a real woman...
T-That's me!
It was pretty interesting, wasn't it?
Wasn't it worth coming
here to the office?
W-When did you take this?
You want to be made a real woman,
right Yoshino?
I-I'm going back to my room now...
Wait a minute!
L-Let me go!
I won't tell anybody about this!
Isn't it the other way around?
If you don't want to have this
broadcast over the internet...
...you're gonna do exactly what I say.
N-No! Stop it!
I'll turn you into a real woman!
No, stop it!
Don't you want to?
No, don't come any closer!
No! No!
There...
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop it!
It's not even in that deep yet!
It's time for you to become a real
woman!
It's gonna hurt at first, but
you'll get through it, right?
No! Stop it!
No!
Look at that, it's in real deep!
Now you are ready to become a real
woman!
Please don't move!
I'll be done in no time!
Please, take it out! Take it out!
I'll shoot plenty of it inside!
Stop it!
Here! Take this!
So, how does it feel to become a
woman?
You wanted to be a real woman right?
This is wrong.
I didn't ask for this.
This is a very important
step to becoming mature.
I helped you become a woman, and I'll
keep on doing so, and so much more.
You won't just look like a real
woman, but also feel like one.
So we have to keep this
a secret between us...
...and not let the other girls know.
Got it?
If they do find out for some reason,
you're the one who will be embarrassed.
I violated Yoshino today.
If you can get the material,
they become easy targets.
I'll violate her wearing
her swimsuit next time.
Wait, it's no fun
playing with just Yoshino.
I'll deal with the others as well.
Prepare yourselves.