Wait for me!
Brother...
Even though it's just two weeks...
I feel so lonely living without you.
I shouldn't have come to this camp.
Fruits Cup, Episode Two
Hey.
Should we end it?
I...
I got engaged to my boyfriend.
Can you forget...
...everything we had between us?
Brother, I love you.
This feels good too.
My breasts feel good...
Brother, can you see?
I want to marry you, brother!
We're not related by blood,
so we can marry, right?
What if...
...he finds out that
I'm doing such a thing...
...but I can't help it!
I wish these fingers
were my brother's...
...I'd want them to fondle me some
more!
There!
Fondle some more, more!
That's it, right there...
It sure feels good!
Squeeze my nipples too!
It feels great!
Brother!
I love you, Brother!
Simply wonderful!
Thank you for putting on a great show!
It's a shame to keep
this footage to yourself.
I'll send a copy to your half-brother.
I know, let's have more
people take a look at this.
How about this?
Let's broadcast this over the internet!
We can also make this into
a DVD and make a huge profit!
So, what exactly do I have to do?
I really like a girl
with brains like you.
Girls like you know exactly what
to do in this kind of situation.
But this is all possible due
to your great data collecting.
I really appreciate all
that you've done, Yoshino.
Are you convinced now?
Y-Yoshino!
So sorry, Matsuri.
Now that you know, Matsuri,
take off your clothes.
Stop!
You're my friend, right, Yoshino?
Do it now!
DVD! DVD!
Hey DVD!
No!
That's right, you two have to play
nice since you're both friends.
No!
Help me, Brother!
Stop it! Yoshino!
Unfortunately, your knight
in shining armor isn't here.
Stop! Please let me go!
I promised that my first
time would be with my brother.
Then I definitely gotta do you!
Stop! Please let me go!
Well, there's no point in waiting...
Well...
It hurts!
Look, your friend
Matsuri is in great pain.
Go help her out.
No! Please take it out!
I see. You really are a virgin.
Please! I'll do
anything, so take it out!
Great job on keeping your virginity
all this time, I'm very proud of you!
No!
Brother!
It's too late now.
This is your very
first sexual experience.
It hurts!
Help me, Brother!
Brother!
I'm ready to cum!
No, not inside!
Now that your friend
has lost her virginity...
...Let's get on with round two, shall we?
Yoshino, how does it feel to
be violated in your swimsuit?
I don't like this.
What are you saying?
Your body is looking more
attractive than before.
If you take in a large
amount of semen...
your tits are gonna get bigger.
No!
Barbarian!
You have a big mouth.
Clean it up gently with
that mouth of yours.
Things are going very well.
With this steady pace...
...starting tomorrow, I'll
entertain the remaining two...
Nagisa and Shiori.
Now, focus on the muscle right here...
That's good.
Bad material.
Camp is gonna end soon.
I can't work with this material.
Have you got any useful
material like I asked you to?
Well, I got Ms. Nagisa's.
Ms. Nagisa's swimsuit.
Smell of Ms. Nagisa's bed sheets.
Ms. Nagisa's fingers,
feeling my nipples...
Ms. Nagisa, please more...
Ms. Nagisa!
Shiori, what are you doing in here?
I'm sorry.
But I just can't take it anymore!
Shiori...
You and I broke up already, and
I wanted to forget about you.
But I just can't!
If I keep going like
this, I'll go crazy!
I can't live without you!
Shiori...
I know I can't be with you.
That's why I want you make
love to me one last time!
I want you to hold me very tight!
This is the last time, okay?
Yes!
Ms. Nagisa!
Pretty girl.
Ms. Nagisa...
Ms. Nagisa!
So good...
I'm starting to feel it too.
Ah, my pussy feels
great from the friction!
Ms. Nagisa!
It feels good, Ms. Nagisa!
Me too!
Matsuri.
Great job.
Now I have both Nagisa
and Shiori in my hands.
Let's have them join us.
I understand.
But will you promise to
give me back the tape?
Ms. Nagisa...
It's great.
Shiori, it feels great.
Your pussy juice, it's
a bit salty but tasty.
Consider it your reward!
It's good to know you girls understand.
This is terrible.
This is perversion.
You think I can go on
after watching that?
Now do it like I told you to.
Like this?
That's right, two of you
combined make one fine lay.
That's not fair!
It's not true!
It feels weird.
Yoshino!
Matsuri!
Ms. Nagisa, I think I'm gonna climax!
Let's climax together.
You're going to let us go
like you promised, right?
I don't think you understand.
What?
You just had a simple exercise.
The night is long, you know.
No! I don't like this!
No!
Hey everybody!
I came to pick you up!
Huh?
It's strange, where is everyone?
Is the caretaker around?
Hello?
Is anybody home?
W-What is this?
38th National Swimming Competition
That concludes the interview
with the winning team.
But this time around, the fan
favorite for this tournament...
...Seika Academy, has lost in
the preliminary rounds...
...and caused quite a controversy.
We tried to interview
coach Nagisa Kasuga...
...but she declined to comment
on the loss of their team.
One rumor has it that members
of Seika Academy...
...were involved in a
scandalous activity...
...but we don't know if
that has been confirmed.
What really
happened to the--
On to the next topic.
Earlier in the morning,
24-year-old Riku Omi...
...wanted for sexually
assaulting several women...
...has been found drifting offshore
by a fishing boat that passed by.
They contacted the marine police,
and Mr. Omi was arrested on sight.
According to the police, Mr. Omi
was a caretaker at a resort nearby..
...and treated the women that came...
Foolish...
How foolish...