Shit! I'm late again!
Seihoku University
So, it's split into business inventions,
employee inventions and free inventions.
In the case of any one of these,
the employee is compensated...
and the rights go to the company.
What a boring class, for crying out loud.
You keep looking at me, don't you?
No, I'm not.
Man, this is one boring class.
Can't wait until this one's over.
Hey Professor,
your lecture sucks shit!
Can't you talk about something
more interesting?
Feel good?
Feels good, doesn't it?
That's cool. You can start moaning.
You're already wet.
Don't hold back. Moan if you want to.
There are many problems...
with the distributing
of profits with patents...
and they are taken on
a case-by-case basis...
each handled in its own unique way.
Man, you're already getting
into this, aren't you?
You want to join in?
You don't have to say no.
Dumb little coward.
Then I'll give them some extra service.
No. Don't look at me.
Nice view, isn't it?
Take a good look at it.
Please don't look.
You say not to look, but look at this.
I'm not convinced at all.
What the hell?
Ignoring all the excitement?
I'd appreciate it if you'd at least smile.
Everybody, look here!
Fuck, man. A guy's going
out of his way to please everyone.
They could at least turn around.
Fine. I'll enjoy the fun by myself.
This don't feel good at all.
Why is this chick getting off like this?
It's pissing me off!
Look up here!
What the fuck?
They're all ignoring me.
It was all a dream?
And the idiot wakes up.
Excuse me. Do you
have a question, young man?
Damn it!
I'm stuck in an infinite loop of paradoxes.
Zero no Mono
Collection 1
Waning Moon
Good evening.
What the heck are you doing?
I'm just looking. Okay?
Excuse me, security!
What are you doing?
Hey, stop that! Someone, help!
Hey, what are you doing?
This sucks ass.
This blows big time.
What will I do now?
Shit, man. I'm bored out of my mind.
A sheltered rich girl.
This'll be fun.
I think I'll play with her.
I want to see this preppie girl
cry and scream.
That shit's my come, bitch!
Gross, isn't it? Go ahead and scream,
why don't you!
What the fuck?
You know what that shit is you're licking?
What was that cold stare she had?
She was smiling, that bitch.
She's hitting on me.
It'll be fun fucking a weirdo like her.
That chick.
This is getting good.
I was bored out of my mind today.
What's that voice?
Come some more, you bitch!
More!
Who the hell are the guys
in the masks?
Where's that chick?
Is that her being fucked?
Thank goodness that you were
interested in me.
You're my type of guy.
You're good.
I was worried that you might not have come.
Hey, what the hell is that?
That?
Don't worry about it, anyway.
Hey, wait!
That was all the explanation I get?
Don't worry about stupid things.
I'm beginning to think
that you're a picky man!
What?
Forget that, would you hit me with this?
Hit you? Why?
Entering without asking...
you didn't expect something normal
to be going on, did you?
Or maybe you just can't do it?
What did you say?
Of course you couldn't,
you yellow-bellied pervert stalker!
Don't be acting up on me, bitch!
Look who's talking, whore!
The pain.
What? You're the one who asked for it,
you fucking bitch!
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting for this.
You whore. What the fuck
are you planning?
What are you thinking, you bitch!
I've been waiting.
All this time for you. My master.
Your Riko has been a naughty girl.
What's going on?
Is this really that stuck up bitch I saw?
Please punish me until everything
breaks, master.
What's up with her body?
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm the master. I like that.
Please punish me, now.
This is an interesting game.
Cut all the crap and show me
your pussy, whore!
Yes, master. Anything you say.
Please don't look.
Your pussy's dirty as fuck.
You're already fucking wet!
Look at this!
Riko can't do anything without her master.
What's up with this dirty thing?
Maybe it's already rotted!
Say more bad things, please say them.
This bitch is fun. This is fun!
It doesn't matter who she is. She's mine!
She's my pet!
I'm no good. No good.
Your pussy really is dirty.
More! Please, punish me even more!
Punish me, please!
She's getting off on her own.
You're going so far in,
it'll go up to your wrist!
So you want me to shove it
in all the way?
You slutty whore!
It's about time to show off my stuff.
All right, now, suck on it.
It smells.
It smells, you say?
Don't talk back to me!
Clean it with your mouth!
I'm going to stick this in your cunt!
How's the taste of my cock?
Make sure to clean it good,
you dirty little trollop!
Yes...
What's up with her mouth?
Shit! I've never felt it so good!
This is the shit!
Master, you feel good, don't you?
I'll make you feel even better.
Shut up! Stop licking it, skank!
Master, punish your Riko
even more. More.
Shut up! Don't you dare
give orders to your master.
I'll fuck you now!
You better make me come
with that pussy, got it?
Please, master.
Spread your ass more.
I'm putting my fat dick into your dirty
pussy, right now!
You're going to like it!
How's the taste of my cock?
It feels good, master, it's wonderful!
Your cock is so big, I'm going crazy!
Go crazy! Get all fucked up!
You want me to stop now?
Or have you already gone crazy?
More! I don't want it to end!
You really want to lose it?
I won't lose it. I want more, please!
I won't!
I won't lose it!
Give me more, please!
Don't be a smart ass.
You're a pet! You're a fucking bitch!
I'll fucking destroy you,
all the way to the bone!
Do you want even more, bitch?
Answer me, do you want more?
Punish me more!
More, punish me even more!
Master, more.
I like it.
Hey, wait. Don't move so much,
dumb ass bitch!
Harder, faster, Riko's pussy, please!
There's something different about her.
She's not the same as before.
She's not my pet.
More, master, more.
She's not the one being owned, I am!
What's wrong?
Who the hell are you guys?
I told you not to worry.
Get away from me!
Master must stay my master.
What'd you just inject into me?
What did you do to me?
Love Potion destroys the rationality...
you were tired of
and turns you into a pure master.
I'm not your master, I'm not! I'm not!
Yes, you are. Or you will be.
My lovely master.
Master, fill my body with pleasure.
That is the fate of my master,
for both of us.
Yes, don't you see?
Stop it!
I'm begging you!
Stop it, please!
My very own master.
Soon, you'll be my real master.
More!
Get a bigger erection, dear master!
I'm sinking into the sea of ecstasy.
Down to the bottom.
Now fill my body with ecstasy
until I go crazy!
More, more, grind your body faster!
That is my real master.
My body is disappearing.
Am I going to exist just for this?
Please punish me until
you burn out like a candle.
I'm being sucked into the darkness.
More, master. More!
Harder! Fuck me even harder!
I'm the master! The master! The master!
Master!