At last I have finally returned.
I thought I had lost my way.
You did a good job getting here.
Even though I grew up in this village, this is the first time I've been back.
It's been 15 years.
Yeah...
But I feel like I was last here earlier than that. No that can't be.
Musashi-chan!
Musashi-chan, I missed you!
I wanted to hug you for so long.
Ah, you were my childhood friend...
Oh, you remember me?
Your name was...
An...
An?
It's not?
Then... um.. Na?
Na?
Su?
Su?!
Ma?
Ma?!
It's Tamamo.
Right, right. It's Tamamo. Long time no see.
What are you doing?
What was I doing...?
Do you really remember me?
Well, actually...
Sorry, I don't remember you at all.
That's all right.
Since you have come back
I'm so happy
You are such good friends.
Just like when you were young.
Yeah...
I'm too old to be up.
Please clean up the fire okay?
Okay.
Good Night.
What's wrong?
Nothing is wrong. Good night.
Good night.
Something smells good.
Musashi-chan. Can I spend the night with you?
I've been waiting so long for you.
For me?
Yeah.
I decided a long time ago I wanted you to be my first.
Tamamo-chan...
Do you really feel that way towards me?
Yeah...
What should? Now that you are here I feel a little shy.
She's so cute!
I can't believe she waited for me this long! It's like a dream.
Wait a minute, this is too good to be true. She
wants to but I don't remember her at all.
Everybody may be in on it and are trying to trick me.
That's it, it's a trap. It has to be!
I'll have a stupid look after I *#%@!* with her when
the guy with a camera appears and then
That smell... my mind's going blank.
I can't think properly.
Tamamo-chan.
Musashi-chan.
Please hold me!
I can't stop shaking even though I'm not cold.
Like this?
Hold me tighter.
She's shaking so much. Is this really her first time?
Does it matter if this is a trap?
Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
Musashi-chan. Thank you.
Tamomo-chan, are you scared?
Not at all. You're so gentle.
Really?
Yeah.
Musashi-chan, I love you.
That tickles.
It feels so good.
Do it gently.
Yes, like that.
That feels good.
No, if you do that they'll get bigger.
Not there!
S-Stop...
No, not there!
You're oil wet...
Because it feels good.
You're so sensitive.
Tamamo-chan, move your hips a bit.
If you don't, I can't take them off.
No.
We can't move on until they come off.
We don't have to keep going.
Are you sure?
We don't.
Tamamo-chan.
I said we don't.
No...
Musashi-chan, you pervert.
Tamamo-chan, can you spread your legs?
No.
Don't.
That tickles.
No, not there
Wow, it feels weird.
No...
It feels good...
Stop...
Don't lick there.
It's delicious, Tomamo-chan.
Don't tease me.
It feels so good... Musashi-chan...
You're not afraid anymore, are you Tamamo-chan?
No.
Okay, then here I come.
It's in.
A man's... Musashi-chan's...
Good...
Oh my god, it's inside me. Moving in and out.
That's it. It feels good.
It feels good. Really dirty.
I can feel it. Unbelievable.
Musashi-chan, I love it.
It's so good! This is the first time something's
felt this good.  Musashi-chan...
I had no idea it'd feel this good.
Harder, harder.
Harder..
Tamamo-chan, I can't take it anymore.
Musashi-chan, it's okay.  Do it.
Tamamo.
Cum inside me!
What's wrong? Calling me all of a sudden.
Wasn't last night a failure?
Yeah, but I'm sure I saw Musashi-san last night.
What?
Really? So it's true that if we pray into this mirror.
we can see the person we want to see.
Yes, but something wrong.
Wrong?
What?!
Onii-chan!
He looks good. But where is this? Our village?
It looks similar but it's not.
There's no way he could return here.
But it looks like it.
That's why I said it's strange.
No way.
What's happen?
This places hasn't changed since I was a child.
That's right, this shrine collapsed.
I often played here.
Who was I playing with?
That's right, probably with Tamamo-chan.
Forgive me Suzaku-san!
Who is Suzaku?
Here too...
Something is wrong.
The village I remember was more innocent, sexy, violent
and tidy.
What the hell was that? A dead village!
It's snowing. I'll have to hurry back.
Musashi-sama! Musashi-soma!
That voice. I've heard it before.
Snow?
Musashi-chan!
You left without telling me.
Sorry. I was getting a little nostalgic.
It's snowing so let's hurry home.
Musashi-sama! Musashi-sama! Musashi-sama!
It's impossible Yuki.
He can't hear you.
I'm sure he heard me just now.
Musashi-sama! Musashi-sama!
Hurry and get Tengu-sama.
But I've kept this a secret from him.
I hove a bad feeling.
Musashi will be in danger if we don't do anything.
Danger?
We must go.
To help Musashi-sama.
I can't seem to relax.
Onii-chan.
That girl.
Damn, I can't remember. I feel like
I've forgotten something important.
Damn it. Damn it! Damn it!!
Musashi-chan, is something wrong?
No... I'm probably just thinking too much.
Yeah, that's it. That has to be it.
I can't live if you hate me.
There's no way I can hate you.
But...
That's what he says.
That's true.
Lick me more. Clean me up good.
That bastard!
Onii-chan, that's so mean! Doing it with her!
Please stop.
I can't watch anymore.
I'm going to tell Tengu-sama.
Right there feels great.
So good.
Lick me there.
I'm going to...
Did you enjoy it?
My minds blank.
Hey, Musashi-chan. Could you promise me?
Kiss me here.
Tomamo-chan?
This will be proof of our eternal vow.
Vow?
Quickly.
Okay.
Musashi!
Onii-chan!
You will be mine forever.
Musashi!
W-What's that?
- Musashi!
Why do you know my name?
Those girls were banished from
our village because of evil acts.
What? Isn't that a play?
Save me!
Stop holding onto him!
They don't seem so evil especially since they're cute.
He said we're cute.
You dumbass. This isn't the time.
Musashi, let's run! They're going to use violence and steal all our things.
Let me get my clothes first.
Forget about that and hurry.
Damn you! Do I look like a barbarian to you?
You do. Like a savage barbarian.
This way!
Hold on.
Wait!
This feels like sauna. I didn't know that
there was a cave at that open air bath.
We should be safe now. They
shouldn't be able to follow us this far.
Yeah.
I'm so scared.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
You're so energetic.
Well, I am young.
What now?
Musashi-sama, you're human.
You must not interfer.
You too.
Get away from Musashi or else.
I don't remember you being
able to order me around.
I have no choice.
Tamamo.
You shielded me... why?
Isn't it obvious? We're not strangers anymore.
Musashi-chan..
Musashi-sama, you love her than me.
This is bad.
Musashi-chan, hurry.
No!
I hate to run away but I can't fight against ice.
Why did it get so cold all of a suddenly?
Tamamo-chan?
I'm at my limit.
My body's too hot. I'm going to melt.
What's wrong with her? No matter how hot
it is would you normally start stripping?
Um, are you all right?
Well, of course you're not.
I'll take you somewhere cool.
No, you can't. Leave me alone.
Don't be nice to me.
What ore you saying? Come on.
Stop.
Musashi-sama.
I can't take it anymore!
I can't hold back any longer.
Fuck me and cool my body down.
If you don't I will melt.
I'm such a bad girl.
I swore that. I would never be with Musashi-sama again.
I don't know what's going on but if she needs my help then...
Sorry, Tamamo-chan.
Musashi-sama, hurry and put it in me.
Musashi-sama, I can feel you in me.
I thought I'd never be able to do this again.
This is like a dream.
Musashi-sama... Musashi-sama! I'm so happy that you're fucking me.
Good!
You idiots! What the hell did you do?
I'm sorry.
This mirror doesn't reflect what you are thinking.
What's happened to them then?
I can only imagine the worst.
I can't imagine what terrible things are happening to Musashi.
This feels so good.
Musashi-sama, do you like it?
Harder, fuck me harder.
Musashi-sama.
Musashi-sama, faster.
What is this weird but familiar feeling?
I remember this girl...
Who is she? Who?
Damn it. I can't remember.
I'm cumming.
Musashi!
Con you hear me?
W-Who are you?
Musashi, you aren't in the
village you grew up in.
You are in an imitation of that village.
Who are you? Show yourself.
Musashi-sama, that voice...
Did you hear that too?
Who was that?
No, forget about the voice.
You, who are you?
Don't ask me that. You and I
aren't from the same world.
Then why do you know me?
That is...
Musashi, you mustn't be deceived.
That girl is evil.
You can relax, we caught
her evil companions.
Damnit!
Onii-chan!
Suzaku-chan! Anju-chan!
Hey, who are you?
What are you saying? It's me.
Don't lie to me.
My grandmother has no tail!
Damn...
That dolt.
Musashi, good eyes.
Again.
The truth is she is monster called an Enra.
Enra?
That's right.
I am the chief of the Enra Fire village.
Tamamo is my only daughter.
T - T - Tamamno - chan?
Homurabe.
(People who treats fire like a magician)
How can such a cute girl come
from such ugly parents?
I commend you on seeing through our seal.
We shall withdraw today but this
doesn't meant we have given up.
I shall destroy you.
I won't give up Musashi to you.
What was that...
Musashi, try to remember!
Not again.
If you can remember the truth, you
will break the seal on the village.
What do you mean the truth?
Did I completely erase his memory?
Is it impossible for him to remember?
Musashi-san, please remember.
Musashi, did you really forget everything?
Onii-chan, try to remember about me and everyone.
Onii-chan... you mean me?
Onii-chan... you jerk!
Where am I?
What was I...? Anju-chan? Suzaku-san?
And even Mayuki-chan.
Musashi-sama...
Why are you naked?
What's wrong, you two?
Is there something on my face?
Oh right, I don't see Nami-san.
What are you doing?
Ouch!
Hey, let go.
Musashi-san.
My seal has broken like that?
You old geezer! Playing around in
my head and erasing my memories!
My head's not a video tape!
Shut up boy.
I have to go a meeting of village chiefs to explain about this incident.
So shut up for while.
Meeting of village chiefs?
We need to discuss the Enra.
Take me with you.
What?
It's because your village chief heads
are so hard that this happens.
I feel sorry for these girls.
I'll go and tell them directly.