Finally, I have returned.
I've waited so long for you, Musashi-chan.
For me?
Ah.. This is a man's.. ah.. Musashi-chan.
You're wrong. This isn't a mirror
that reflects your thoughts.
Exactly, I'm the banishing chief of Homurabe.
and this is my beautiful only daughter.
Chief meeting?
We must decide how to deal with the Enra.
Take me with you.
What?
I will speak with them directly.
Love Princess 2
Let me meet the chiefs.
You just don't understand, do you? You
shouldn't be involved with us anymore.
What?
I'm telling you to forget everything.
Forget? You old geezer!
Musashi-chan!
Onii-chan!
Stop resisting. It will only be more painful.
No... I... I'll...
I'll...
won't forget!
Erase it from your mind.
Resistance is futile!
Musashi...
Onii-chan, you're going to die.
Musashi-san.
Musashi...
That's enough.
Musashi, stop!
Onii-chan! Stop!
Musashi-sama!
Musashi, give it up!
Shut up you old fart.
I'll never forget!!
Where...?
Musashi-san.
Musashi-san, have you regained conciousness? Thank god.
Nami-san. Where is this?
The prison in my father's castle.
The dragon-king's castle?
Tengu-sama used too much
magic and is sleeping.
So other chiefs decided to keep you here.
But why are you here, Nami-san?
They could not forgive me for
removing the solving seal.
I'm paying for my own mistake.
Then other girls too?
Yes. They are under house arrest.
No way.
Don't worry about us.
We are all impressed.
Because you won against Tengu's powerful magic.
I'll never forget!!
Your feelings for saving that person...
We are ready to accept any punishment.
Even if we really are to be separated...
I will continue to live and
support that person's heart.
Thank you, Musashi-san.
Nami-san, it's too early to give up
I will talk to the dragon king
so don't cry so much.
Don't touch there!
Why not?
Oh no...
What's wrong Nami-san?
For girls... our horns .. are the
most sensitive parts of our body.
Like a G-spot?
No, not like that...
Ah, that feels good.
Looks good.
Musashi-san... that...
Not here... It's indiscrete.
Isn't that what makes this place
a good place? Right Nami-san?
No, we can't.
More... I mean... Stop it. Musashi-san...
We cant.
How about here?
Harder... no, please stop.
Please let me go. If we keep going...
I'm all ready half dead...
Come with me Sasaki Musashi.
You're going to meet the Dragon Master.
So you like it like this?
W-what the hell are you doing?!
I have never seen a human like you.
Coming to se me like this.
I'm really angry at you.
First off, everything that's happened
is because of the demons in your clan.
I'm just some outsider that got involved.
You just go around erasing peoples
memories and tearing things up.
Furthermore, aren't you a parent?
Release Nami-san now.
You're tiny but you've got
balls to talk to me like that.
In consideration for your courage...
You're going to release her?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm saying I'll giving you a chance.
A chance?
If you beat me or one of other chiefs,
I'll listen to you.
Let's do it!
I won't let you easy just because
you're Nami's father.
Well said. Now bring it on!
Now?
W-Wait a second... I'm not ready yet.
Go easy on me a bit.
That damn chief. I'll make him beg for mercy.
Papa, are we really going to do this?
Of course. Why do you think we went
through all that trouble to get here?
I don't really care for revenge though.
There's no point if we get caught again.
We won't. We have to clear
our names of that humiliation.
That brat has the right of
succession in for four tribes.
If he married you then we'd
have power over them.
I wonder if this will really work out.
Well I don't care about the rest if I get Musashi.
Tamamo.
Sorry for using you like this.
Someday I'll introduce you to a man
who'll be a better match for you.
I know already. No need to repeat yourself.
You're a good girl.
So this is Kakibe tribes' castle.
Anzu-chan's home.
There's no way I can beat that Dragon King.
Maybe Anzu-chan's mother might help.
Welcome. I'm the Kakibe chief, Namiki.
I've already heard from the Dragon King.
Feel free to come forward at any time.
I'm not in a hurry.
Why don't we talk for a bit?
Would you like me to massage your back?
No, thank you.
What's this? Finished already? How boring.
Ouch.
Musashi!
Onii-chan!
Are you awake?
Anzu-chan? And Suzaku-san?
Are you hurt? I feel so sorry for you.
Seez, mother should have held back a bit.
Where is this?
Prison under the Namiki's castle.
Prison!? Then... Ah, we're locked in.
But why are you here?
My grandfather has been asleep for
a while so I've been confined here.
I've heard from my mother..
Onii-chan...
You must beat all tribes chief right?
Did you say all?
You're weak and always run away
but you're a man after all.
I've changed my opinion of you.
Umm...
Go for it, Onii-chan. But don't die.
When did it come to this?
Suzaku-san.
This is our clans way of expressing love.
Good luck.
I guess I'll do it too.
What are these two doing getting
it on like that. If that's the case...
Suzaku-san... It tickles.
Hey Anzu! VVhat are you doing?
Anzu-chan, I'm impressed
by your expression of love.
There's no way...
Musashi?
Hey Anzu, stop it!
But onii-chan looks like
he's enjoying himself.
Is it really okay?
Anzu, let me do it too.
Let me borrow it.
Hey, you have to be more gentle.
I feel sorry for him.
My turn.
If you do it like that...
Here's my chance.
That's not fair, Anzu.
Well I do love him more.
I love him more than you.
Idot.
No, I do!
I love both of you.
You!!
More, that feels great, Onii-chan!
Lick me more!
Right there! More! Harder!
You're so beautiful.
Wow, it looks so intense!
I'm getting excited.
Anzu.
It's embarrassing but it feels good.
Onii-chan, hurry! Hurry!
Onii-chan's in me...
That feels great!
Fucking great!
Anzu, I can feel it.
I'm going to come.
I'm coming.
Me too. I'm coming too.
Coming...
I came so many times.
Me too. But I love him more than you.
I love him more!
Onii-chan, do it with me again.
No, do it with me.
With me?
Pretend I'm sleeping... pretend...
He's going to risk his life and fight...
Please be safe.
Mayuki is too strong a girl that gets the wrong
impressions. I don't know what to do with her.
She might burden you but
please try and tolerate her.
You are the only one I can count on.
Oh, I hope I won't be a burder to her either.
Thank god Shizuhi-san's a nice person
and she's listening to what I'm saying.
Well, shall we do this now?
What?
I think I have the lowest
powers of all four chiefs but...
Please don't hold back.
Give me your best shot.
My best?!
Oh, what should I do?
I didn't do anything yet.
Um, are you still alive?
Uh, yeah... somehow.
I should have expected this
from Mayuki-san's mother.
Calling me at this hour.
I wonder if something is happened.
This must be the place.
Musashi-sama? Are you in there?
Musashi-sama?
Mayuki-chan?
Yes.
You did good escaping from the castle.
Because my mother's how she is,
it's easy to distract her and escape.
But why are you here Musashi-sama?
I have been beaten by the chiefs.
What?
I wanted to at least hear
your voice before I died.
No way! Musashi-sama!
Hold on! Open this door! If I don't
treat your wounds immediately...
No, I can't do that.
No, don't say that.
I'll open this door.
Musashi-sama?
Musashi-sama, where are you?
No, you mustn't get close to me.
Why, Musashi-sama?
Because if we touch each other, we'll disappear.
Anzu.
Suzume-chan.
Wake up.
Nami-onee-chan?
Don't speak too loudly.
What's going on at this time of day?
I got a message from Musashi-san
so I escaped from the castle.
From Musashi?
Did something happen to Onii-chan?
I don't know the details but...
Anyways, he says he needs to meet us.
Where is Musashi?
Come with me and quietly so
that Namiki doesn't notice.
That old man is supposed to be sleeping.
What are you doing?
Old man!!! When did you?
Are you the real Musashi?
Of course I am. Are there
any handsome guys here?
Why are you loitering around here?
I snuck in to beat you up while you slept!
Even if you are sick, a win is a win!
You better not complain.
Hmm... it seems you are the real Musashi.
Why are you floating there when
you're supposed to be sleeping?
Like I have time to be sleeping
during this serious matter.
Serious matter?
So Enra has kidnapped Suzaku and everyone else and
won't release them unless I exchange myself?
Right.
Geez...
Are you going?
Well, if I don't they'll be killed right?
So I have to go.
If it involves the Enra, this has to be a trap.
Do you intend to slip through their trap?
A trap, eh?
Well, either way, it's better than being killed
by the Dragon King and the other chiefs.
Musashi.
Sorry, that's the way it is.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Please rescue all four of them.
If you can beat the Enra,
I'll grant you anything you want.
Really?
Yeah, I won't trick you.
Remember that promise old man!
Yahoo!
That dumbass. He thinks he's already won.
That damn stupid fox... Imprisoning my precious
girls place in such place. Prepare yourself!
Where am?
Musashi-san!
It's been so long!
T-Tamomo-chan.
You came to see me, right? I'm so happy.
Er.. no, I come to talk to Enra.
Forget about daddy.
I can't do that.
By the way where is this?
This is the former site of Momurabe royal palace.
This is what became of it
after we were exiled.
Hey, just forget about that.
We haven't seen each other in such
a long time. Let's fuck. Okay?
I want to have a lot of babies
and re-build Homurabe.
Come on, it's alright right? Come on, Musashi-chan?
That'd be nice.
I mean, no, no!
No, I didn't come here for this.
You know where Mayuki-chan, Anzu-chan,
Nami-san and Suzaku-san are, don't you?
Musashi-chan...
Tell me where they are.
Who is more important to you? Them or me?
Didn't you say you were going to marry me?
Did I?
You did!
Hmm... did I?
That's mean! You tricked me!
Do I look like someone
who should get married?
Answer me!
Who would you choose?
What would you do if I
said I liked them better?
Well, maybe daddy will get angry and kill them.
That's too bad, I never wanted
to see this side of you.
We might have been able to be friends...
Musashi-chan.
Don't touch me!
Any enemy of those girls
are my enemies as well.
Could you take me to where they are?
Musashi-san.
Onii-chan!
Musashi-sama.
Are all of youill right?
We're all right but we feel
sorry for Miyuki-chan.
Enra!! You bastard!
This idiot has finally showed up.
I come as promised.
Now let those four go!
First you must make a blood oath with Tamamo.
Swear to be Tamamo's in front of us.
If I do that will you release them?
Yes.
Don't do it! Onii-chan!
Don't swear to her!
Stop!
Don't do it, Musashi! Stop!
No, Musashi!
No, no... I won't do this.
It feels so stupid.
I'm out of this agreement.
What are you saying?
I'd rather be dead than be
with this worthless scum.
It feels gross just being touched by him.
That's so mean.
You selfish girl!
My revenge plan is all
messed up because of you!
Well then, all that's left...
Is to kill all of you!!!
Brat, you're the first to die!
Tamamo!
Tamamo-chan...
Don't worry...
I may not look like it but
I'm a Homurabe princess.
Hang on!
Impossible! Why did my
daughter protect a human?1
Damnit! Why are all you
demons such crappy parents?
What did you say?
You're a big dumbass who can't even understand
the true feelings of his daughter!!
Her... true feelings?
It can't be.. it can't mean..
You chose this brat over
your father? Tamamo?!
Daddy...
What is it? I'm right here.
Daddy, please don't kill Musashi-chan's
precious princesses.
Tamamo...
Please, forget about your
revenge. Okay? Daddy...
Tamamo! Tamamo!
Tamamo..!!
I've lost.
I won!
What's with that stupid expression.
Look more like a groom.
But.. it's just..
I can't believe they consented to this.
It was the decision of the chiefs
but is this really all right?
Well I did beat Enra.
By the way, what's happened
to Enra and Tamamo-chan?
We couldn't give them capital punishment.
So we seal their magic and sentenced
them to eternal banishment.
Eternal banishment?
They're probably living somewhere
as a human family.
Wow... that's so nice. You've got
some good points after all.
Hey, don't get any ideas.
The bride preparations
have been completed.
So, it's finally time.
Hey, so who did you decide
would be my wife?
Well...
Here they come.
What?!
I may be inexperienced but
please let me be your wife.
Is this ethically allowed?
This is what we decided. We thought
we'd leave you to be the chief.
If someday Enra or someone like him comes
we expect you to take care of them.
Please take care of your wives, son-in-law.
Please have an balanced
number of boys and girls.
Balanced number?
Don't tell me I'm just supposed to breed.
Onii-chan.
I really became you're wife didn't I?
Yeah, I hope we're happy together.
I love you!!
I can't wait, hurry and strip.
Okay, okay.
That's the spot.
Wow, it's so big.
Anju-chan as well.
You're so wet.
No, not there. I said no.
It sounds squishy.
I can't have all the fun.
W-Wait a second.
This girl always takes the lead so...
This is too embarassing.
I can see your cutest body part.
It feels so good.
No...
No, I'm coming.
Stop it.
Please stop it.
Please, hurry and put it in.
No, not yet.
You're so mean.
Onii-chan...
I'm coming...
I'm coming. I'm coming!
Greetings again...
Have you been waiting for me naked?
In ancient times, wives of samurais were
well mannered and waited like this.
It was to prove that they
weren't hiding any weapons.
Lets finish this up quick.
Hurry up Musashi and strip.
I'm tired of waiting.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I'm not going to run away.
Please, no foreplay. Fuck me now.
This is in exchange for
always tormenting me.
That's... stop it...
No more, I'm getting horny.
That's...
Please stop.
I'm going to die.
This should be enough...
There... there...
Unbelievable!
No, what are you doing?
I can't hold it anymore.
F-F-F-Freczing room.
Are we going to do it here?
Yes. If not I'll melt.
But if it's this cold, he cant feel anything
This is secret medicine  from
my mother. Here you go.
Is it safe for me to drink this?
Don't worry.
My body is burning!
Yay!
Mayuki-chan!!
Unbelievable.
Not like that. I'll burst.
Finished already?
I got all excited quickly but
it only lasted for a moment.
That's all right but we
did just get married...
Sorry but my body's just...
We still have a lot of medicine.
Wonderful!
This is so good.
I can't take it anymore.
This feels great! This
position is the best.
I'm coming!
You seem very tired.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Please relax.
I'll do all the work.
Nami-san, you're so beautiful.
Don't say that...
Now lay on the bed...
Sure, sure.
I'm going to start now.
That's great, Nami-san.
Now how about this.
Nami-san, I'm so happy you're
letting me fuck your breasts.
I'm your wife. This is the least I can do.
You're such a nice person.
So in exchange, I'll...
Um, Nami-san? You don't have to...
Sorry, I was just lost in ecstasy.
It's not your fault.
But your sperm.
Don' t worry. Let' s do it again. Okay?
Musashi-san... Okay.
That's great.
I can feel you in me.
So good.
Musashi-san.
The sun's so bright.
I didn't know the guy's dream of a
harem would be this dead-tiring.
I brought a lot of snacks.
I told you this is not a picnic.
But I wonder what the city is like.
I'm looking forward to it.
Musashi-san, we'll be right beside
you until you graduate high school.
I'm so happy I'm crying...
Don't forget to make babies
while you're studying.
Make 5, no 6 babies!
If it's Musashi, I'm sure
he'll make at least 10.
I'm looking forward to it.
Leave it to us!
Oh father
We'll do our best!
My Iife's too hard!
Hey' wait!!
Give me a break!
We'll see you when we get back!