Umm...
W-Will you really let me go if I do whatever you tell me?
Of course.
If you do as I say, Mina-chan,
then I'll refrain from telling anyone about your shoplifting spree.
Doing this in front of another person is really...
But if I say no,
Mom, Dad, and even the entire school will find out.
It's just for a little bit.
I have to endure this.
I can't see where it's coming out very well.
Hey, can't you use your fingers to open it wide for me to see?
D-Do I have to?
Yep, you'll have to open it wide.
There, now I can see it better.
That lovely opening.
Hurry, I want to finish already.
You're peeing a lot, Mina-chan.
Now you've got me aroused.
I-It stopped.
Now, can you let me...?
Do you think you can go home already?
We're just getting started.
You said you'd let me go...
See? It's become like this after allowing me to see it.
No, oh no...
Don't come near!
Oh, it's still quite wet from when you peed earlier.
I think I can push it in easily now.
No, let me...
You'll have to put up with this, if you
don't want anyone to find out.
No...
I'm scared.
Is this your first time, Mina-chan?
I'm scared...
You had the guts to shoplift,
so I assumed you were used to this kind of thing.
You really are a virgin.
This is even better.
No, I was...
I was just invited by a friend to do it.
I wasn't able to say no...
Bad luck for you, then.
But don't worry, I won't tell a soul.
Your virgin pussy is really tight.
I can cum inside, right?
N-No!
Pull it...
You wrapped around it really well.
Here, clean it with your mouth.
No...!
It tastes like blood, sweat, and a man's scent.
It stinks.
I don't want this...
Oh yeah, you actually have another admirer.
He's waiting at my place.
We still have to think about what to do next.
You're coming, right?
I heard about it over the phone.
Oh, so this cute girl is a shoplifter.
Well, I have an acquaintance who can
ask for your details at your school.
You don't need to worry as long as you do what I say.
I knew it, this person...
He just wants my body.
Young girls' bodies sure develop quite early these days.
Th-This feels gross.
It feels gross, and yet,
why...?
My body is starting to get aroused.
Your nipples have gotten stiff.
Here, you already know what to do, right?
Will my dick fit into your small mouth?
This big thing, another guy's dick...
Is going inside my mouth!
There, that's good, just keep licking.
The way your small mouth sucks it feels very nice.
We're not done yet.
It's twitching a lot, deep inside my throat.
This man's smell is also going deep inside my nose.
Oh no, I'm so aroused now, I'm about to...!
Man, you sure love young girls, senpai.
Can I join too?
Yeah, of course.
Huh? The inside of your panties is already this wet.
Maybe you got horny after sucking a dick?
N-No, that's not...
Whoa, it's soaking wet.
Your bodily fluids are sticking to my thing.
Don't look.
No need to be embarrassed.
But this is embarrassing.
No!
Don't say that now.
No, I don't want this!
My body, please don't get aroused.
What a horny face.
Looks like you're already turned on.
What a naughty girl you are, Mina-chan.
With your slutty body...
If you're already this wet,
then I guess it'll go right in.
I'm being violated again.
Why is this happening to me?
Your body really is very erotic, inside and out.
You just lost your virginity earlier,
but you're now sucking me in really hard.
No way, she was virgin a while ago.
Damn, you've beaten me to it.
They're playing with my body, as if I'm some sort of toy.
But, if you were a virgin earlier,
then that means this part hasn't been taken.
No, that's my...!
Any more and... I'll realty go crazy...
I'll now take away your anal virginity!
Her ass is really tight!
She's starting to grip me even tighter.
My whole body is being stirred inside.
They're completely violating me.
My head, is going blank...
I don't know anything anymore.
Mina-chan, you're the best.
Oh? It's been twitching down there for quite a while now.
Are you about to cum?
So you re going to cum with our dicks?
I've already gone crazy...
I'm not supposed to cum, yet...
My body just moves on its own.
Then, in order to match your pace, I'm going to cum too.
I'm going to let it all out inside you, Mina-chan.
I can't pull it out.
Mina-chan, you're slicking it too much.
It's twitching, and it feels very great.
Now then,
you can go home now.
I'll call you again via phone.
Hey, Mina-chan?
She just passed out.
Oh well.
Anyway, we've now got ourselves a pet.
After that,
when school ends,
I continue this "extracurricular lesson ".
Whenever I go to their apartment,
they teach me lots of new things.
At first, it hurt, and I was scared.
But then I slowly...
Nowadays, I even lie to mom,
and spend the entire night with them.
Whenever I stay with them,
they don't let me take a bath until my body is covered in cum.
U-Umm... excuse me, can you...
Please, look at me.
During my free days,
we go out to town,
and they order me to ask strangers to do it with me.
I even had sex in places where we could clearly be seen by others.
Even if I ask them to cum outside,
they'll say it feels too good,
and simply cum inside.
Since that day, when I first met those two,
men's scents never wore off, no matter
how hard I tried to clean it off.
Mina-chan.
Shall we head off then?
You're going to stay for the night again,
so you'll be learning lots of things from me.
Okay...
Oh yeah, did you wear the present I gave you during class?
Yes...
Good girl, Mina-chan.
But this is no longer enough for you, right?
I'm going to give you a good treat later.
It might be a new day, but I'm still becoming
more and more naughty.