Alright, be quiet now.
Don't loiter around too much on the way home.
Mina has been acting weird lately.
She started coming home late,
and she always seem a bit gloomy.
Where is she going to every day?
In this place...?
It's not locked?
You've gotten really good at this, Mina-chan.
Your pussy is hot and tight as always.
Mina!
Nena-nee.
Y-You two, what are you doing to my Mina?
Who are you? Just busting in like that.
Her sist-, I mean her school advisor.
Oh, then this is perfect.
This is...?
Shoplifting.
Compensation dating.
She's been doing these kinds of things.
It'd be bad if the school ever finds out about it, right?
Mina...
No, I was just forced to...!
If these pics ever got leaked, it'll sure ruin her reputation.
As well as your position as a teacher, Miss.
I will do it in her stead.
So release her already.
This will do, right?
Oh, I see you perfectly understand us.
You sure are well-endowed too, Miss.
I've always wanted to be taught by this kind of teacher.
I have to endure this.
If I don't...
Is this one of your soft spots?
Your nipples seem to have suddenly hardened.
You're also drenched here...
Making sloppy sounds like this,
you're a teacher and yet you're getting aroused?
O-Of course not...
I-I'm just being forced to do so...
As expected of our teacher.
I see you're quite the stubborn one.
Then,
if I put this in,
I wonder what will happen.
I guess you're bound to moan because of this, huh?
And it's tight too.
Has it been that long since you had sex?
N-No, that's not true.
M-Mina...!
Give her back to me already!
Miss,
Mina-chan you see,
she says she doesn't want to go home.
Eh?
Mina...
Nena-nee...
Now, Miss,
why don't you become as perverted as Mina already?
No need to hold back.
Ne-Nena-nee,
Oh no...
I'm about to...!
N-No, you mustn't, Mina!
Just endure it...
Hey, you're already totally exposed.
It feels good being fucked by a bad man's dick, right?
No...
I don't want to...
I don't...!
I will never...
I'm, I'm about to... cum!
So are we, we're about to cum.
Alright, here is a present for you, Miss.
Be sure to wear this when going to school, okay?
Oh, and you also can't wear any panties.
We're going to make sure you do this everyday.
Sensei.
Hayakawa-sensei.
Is there something wrong?
You look like you're dizzy.
W-Well, yes...
I'm not feeling well at the moment.
Then, how about resting at the infirmary for a while?
Th-Thank you very much.
Well then.
Infirmary
What happened yesterday...
I have to do something about it.
Couldn't I just report it to the school?
But then Mina will...
But,
at this rate, Mina and I will continue to be...
Hayakawa-sensei.
How are you feeling?
Sensei, what is the meaning of this?
Th-That's...
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Wearing an innocent expression like that,
all while doing something lewd like this!
That's...
I've always liked the pure and flawless you!
And you've just...
Sensei!
You slutty bitch!
I'll do this to you!
Hayakawa-sensei,
what's with that expression?
You're... also a teacher at this school, right?
Doing something like this...
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You came to school wearing this,
so you're not convincing anyone.
It seems like your true nature finally surfaced.
Hayakawa-sensei.
N-No, it's not...
Th-This is...
Then, did you plan on making your pussy
wet during the entire class period?
I-I can't tell him.
Why don't we put something inside it already.
You'll be the one to do it.
I couldn't possibly...
Shall I tell everyone about the vibrator?
See, I'm already completely wet down there.
As expected,
it's really slippery from all those love juices.
Oh, you smell really nice.
No...
Wait, did you just cum earlier?
Not yet.
I've been working here a while as a teacher,
but I've never seen another teacher with a body as erotic as yours.
Also, you put on a proper facade in front of your students,
to think that a teacher is this lewd...
See over there? If you moan too loudly,
the students will notice.
It tried to suck me in again.
So you really get aroused while having sex,
while barely hiding the truth in front of your students.
Whoa, if you keep on tightly gripping me like that...
I can be your partner anytime, Hayakawa-sensei.
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
Nena-nee, are you about to cum?
I'm going to cum.
O-Oh no...
Not there, Mina... no...!
Miss, you came first again.
Don't you feel sorry for Mina-chan?
Our next lesson is blowjobs, sensei.
And this is for you, Mina-chan.
We regularly came to this place afterwards.
Here, and even at school,
we always have to answer to their desires.
We're not allowed to leave.
This is something we can never talk about.