You piece of shit!
Oh no, you're far too kind!
Hey, can I get another beer?
Oh, me too!
What? Hayakawa-sensei, aren't you gonna drink?
Huh? No, I'm done...
No need to be shy just because you're new.
We're all on this trip to the hot springs together!
This isn't school!
You sure can handle your stuff.
Not bad, Hayakawa...
Huh?
Huh? Sensei?
You okay? Hayakawa-sensei?
Hello?
Hayakawa-sensei?
Are you okay?
Unspeakable Things: ~2nd Scene~
Unspeakable Things: 2nd Scene.
V-Vice Principal?!
Oh, how shameful, Hayakawa-kun.
Wh-What are you...
No! Don't!
You were hiding this inside you this whole time?
Let's have a taste.
If you're this wet,
I'm betting you had it in you all day at school.
Did Hara-sensei put you up to it?
H-How do you know about that?
Sorry, it kinda slipped when we were all drunk.
I can't believe everyone knew and kept it a secret from me.
Don't you understand your position as an educator?
This is happening because you are always so lenient.
Try to keep it down, Hayakawa-sehsei.
If you don't, you're going to wake everybody up.
N-No...
Your pussy is soaking wet right now.
Look how easily I can slide it all in!
You can feel me getting even bigger inside you, right?
I've had my eye on you for quite a while now.
Not just Harada, but the Vice Principal too?
Of all the places to...
If anybody wakes up now...
Younger girls are so amazing!
Not only do you play with toys,
but you also have a nice body!
This suppleness... This tightness!
Please hurry up and...
You're making too much noise, sensei.
Suck on this.
You need to take it in deeper.
Every time I move, your pussy gets tighter!
I think it likes me more than the toy, Hayakawa-kun!
Hayakawa-kun...
Hayakawa-kun!
You did a good job of keeping it down.
I haven't done a girl as nice as you in a long time!
I couldn't help cumming inside you!
I can feel it going deeper and deeper inside me!
Bath
My body's all sticky now.
I need to hurry and wash myself.
The Vice Principal's cum is still inside me...
Hayakawa-sensei?
H-Hara-sensei?
Taking a bath at this hour?
You must be tired. Let's relax together.
You're pretty good at this, sensei.
Have experience doing this elsewhere?
I just blew my load, but I'm still as hard as a diamond.
S-Someone will see us!
We're just having some good one-on-one time.
Don't hold yourself back on my account, sensei.
You've had a long day, haven't you?
You're trying to wash the dirt off, right?
Lemme give you a hand.
The Vice Principal...
He pumped quite the load into you.
You'll need to dig deep to get it all out.
N-No!
P-Please...
If the others find out about this, I'll...
Please don't tell anyone.
Yeah, you've got a point.
It'd be really bad if this spread around the school.
Well then, what is it exactly that you
don't want them to know about?
I-I'm a dirty slut that will do anything.
Please ram your mighty, meat rod...
in my filthy, sopping wet hole.
I'm begging you! Please hurry!
It's really slippery, but it's not because of the soap, is it?
Yeah...
Is it just me, or are you tighter
than the time we did it in the office?
If anyone came in right now,
they'd see everything!
This hole is already pretty loose.
I can fit my finger in it.
How's it feel, Hayakawa-sensei?
Does it feel good?
I-It doesn't feel good at all...
Be honest now.
Or do you want the entire school to know?
Yes, it feels good!
Aw, you pissed yourself?
What a shameful teacher.
Looks like you're still not satisfied.
What is it that you want?
I can't tell him!
More... I want more...
Don't say it!
Please mess my pussy up!
You really are a slut, aren't you?
Forgive me, Mina.
Your big sister can't just resist it!
You came your brains out when the
Vice Principal fucked you, didn't you?
Y-Yes! I'm sorry!
You're a teacher, aren't you?
I kept getting hotter and hotter
when he was having his way with me!
Even the slightest touch
would make my mind go blank!
You really are a dirty slut.
Y-Yes!
If you keep stirring my insides like that, I'm gonna cum!
Already cumming again?
You're a teacher, but you're making such a perverted face.
Hey, can you even hear me?
I'm going to fuck your brains out!
That feels good!
Please release it all inside me!
All of it!
You're all dirty again.
You need to wash yourself off before someone comes.
Faculty Room
Hey, guys!
The pictures from our trip are here!
Ah, did you get your pictures, Hayakawa-sensei?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I gave them to her a while ago.
Isn't that right, sensei?
Y-Yes.
Let's go to the hot springs again.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: cockslider
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: fyurie
I'll never forgot that brilliant scenery with you in it
I was there
You were there
I couldn't wish for anything more
Please never leave my side
There's something I've wished for
Something I've been trying to grasp
What will your last words to me for?
"Good bye"
"We'll never see each other again"
I don't want to hear that
Tell me
See your love
Notice me crying
From the diamond, I could tell you were into me
Tell me
See your love
Give me wings
Calling you
Cry for you
Are you real?
What were you doing?
Oh, the seasons are changing
I feel like I'm being swept away
But I'm still in love with you