15 Beautiful Girls Adrift OVA is about to start!
If
it's with
Kazu-chan, then...
♥
A normal, independent childhood friend who loves to
take care of people
If it's with Kazu-chan, then...
Huh? Kazu-chan, what's that?
I picked it up just now.
It seems like the waterproofing system broke, so I wanted to see if I could still use it.
I see. You suddenly took out a video camera,
so I thought you wanted to play director and actress.
How rude!
I want to film art, not porno!
It's all the same, since all you want to film are naked bodies, right?
You know me really well...
But being completely naked is a bit...
Then how about non-nude erotica?
You're suddenly starting to stray from art...
Ero-scenes are important to art, too.
Geez, you really are perverted, Kazu-chan. I guess it can't be helped.
Good, good! Ah, this is the best!
Beauty to the extreme! It's art!
This is an important place that will someday carry the product of our love,
So I can't show everything to you that easily.
You're already this far in, so that shouldn't matter anymore, right?
You're only filming perverted places.
You're so dirty, Kazu-chan.
It's not dirty at all! It's art!
But Kazu-chan, you've got a hard on.
Ah, this is, um...
I knew it was impossible for you to understand art.
You're perverted to the core, after all.
That's a bit irritating, but I can't deny it.
But it's my fault for making you so hard, right?
So I'll take responsibility.
Ko-Koto?
You're getting harder and harder.
Ah, some pre-cum came out.
Kotoko, I'm... already...
Kazu-chan, do you want me to use my hands to make you cum?
Or do you want to do something that feels even better?
I wanna do it!
Then...
Come here, Kazu-chan.
Koto!
Kazu-chan! Kazu-chan!
My beloved Kazu-chan is hugging me; I'm so happy!
It feels so good, Kazu-chan!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come, Kazu-chan!
Kazu-chan, let's come together.
C-Coming!
I can't hold on anymore! I'm coming!
My stomach is full of Kazu-chan's love for me...
Bloomer
Photo Shoot
!!
A classmate who is fast at everything
Bloomer Photo Shoot!!
Saori-cchi!
What is it, Kazuma?
I want you to model for me...
Model... for that video?
That's right!
Your body is energetic and healthy; truly a work of art.
I want to pass it on to future generations.
Geez, if you call me a work of art, I'll get embarrased!
So, Saori-cchi... for the sake of art...!
I'll strip for the sake of art!
You sure made up your mind quickly.
That's my selling point.
Ah! Wait! You're stripping too fast.
You can't take everything off yet.
Why not?
Because bloomers are a man's romance!
Bloomers are a woman's romance, too!
In other words, bloomers are the treasures of all humanity?
Exactly!
Well then, let the bloomer photo shoot begin!
Saori-cchi, what kind of exercise is that?
What exercise? I'm masturbating.
I can tell just by looking...
For art, it has to be masturbating while wearing bloomers.
Ah! Ah! I'm coming!
As expected, you're pretty fast at that, too...
It's your turn next.
It's hard, just like I thought.
It's a given, since you've been filming bloomers for so long.
Saori-cchi!
What?
You came already?
I'm sorry.
Well, I don't particularly hate premature ejaculation...
...but only on the condition that the recovery is quick, too!
I have confidence in that!
This recovery speed...
Nice going, Kazuma!
I've prepared everything with high speed, so I'm gonna put it in.
Kazuma is pulsing inside me...
It's going all the way to the end of my pussy.
Saori-cchi, I'm already...
Fast again, eh?
That's fine, let's synchronize our speed and climax together.
Kazuma's sperm is coming in so fast!
Sorry, I came inside.
It's fine, my egg runs fast, too!
It's impossible to get me pregnant without becoming a man who's even faster!
The
feeling
of
being
tangled
up
A really spoiled daughter of the head of the mafia
The feeling of being tangled up.
Why do I have to get water?
I've never lifted anything heavier than a pair of shoes.
I broke my record.
Coffee speaks to herself in Japanese... Is she really Italian?
TL Note: Kazuma changed espresso into coffee here, her real name is Espresso.
When I was at home, I drank delicious water shipped by air from Rokkou every day.
You make that big of a deal over water?
But it seems like she really isn't from Japan.
Here I go!
Not even Papa has made me this wet before.
If I were seen by someone like this...
...it would be a disgrace to the Sabatini family.
She hasn't changed at all. She's still a person who can't do anything.
This seems interesting... I'll observe her for a bit.
If I have this...
I won't need any ropes,
and I can say goodbye to mediocre bondage that only binds my hand and feet!
What is she doing?
Why did I get all tangled up?
If someone like me...
If I'm seen here like this...
It'll be embarrasing!
I'll be laughed at. I'll be looked down upon.
If I get made fun of and treated as a pig,
I won't deserve to be called a human!
And then everyone will gather together and take turns playing with me...
Then they'll bully me one by one and abandon me.
A bunch of men continuously...
Ah, no! Don't look!
Well, I get to see Coffee's solo S&M play, so I guess this can be considered lucky.
Ah! Kazuma!
You! Why do you have a camera?
Stop! Don't film my embarrassing moment anymore!
Being filmed in a high definition video...
...and then shown on a big screen TV for everyone to see...
Do you want me to save you?
Y-Yeah, if you want to save me, fine.
But it'll be hard to do by yourself, right?
No, not really.
No, no, feel free to call the others!
Actually, go do that.
Then everyone can take their time and save me roughly...
I can do it myself.
Didn't I say not to do that?!
Don't you want me to save you?
That is... of course... um...
Ah! I'm sorry! Wait!
But you don't have to be in a rush about it...
Which is it!?
Wait a second, you... Stop!
What are you doing?!
Just...
Hey, you! What are you doing?
This evil thing... has to go!
Stop it, you...
This will do.
Stop!
Don't tell me that a piece of trash like you whose level of existence is lower than a maggot's...
...wants to do that with me?
Not even Papa has put it inside me before!
Don't worry, I'm putting it in here.
Hey, wait! That place is...
Ah! My butt! Stop it... No!
This stimulation... this is the first time I've...
Ah, it's so intense inside...
You look happy, so I'll give you an extra service.
I was originally planning on using this for tonight's dinner...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
This was... my very first time...
Well... let's follow Coffee's wishes and abandon her here.
How much
is
my modeling
fee?
A beautiful sadistic Chinese woman who is only
interested in money
How much is my modeling fee?
Kazuma!
I hear about you filming adult video.
I'll be model.
Really?!
Really.
Of course, I need charge you.
Just as I thought.
But... level of service depend on how much you pay.
I understand!
I'm happy!
Yahoo! How cute! This is the best!
That's great! The area around the butt is silky smooth!
Mon-MonMon-shi is the best! I can't stop!
This is great! That rack is so round and plump! And so soft!
Where you shooting? You pervert!
You only film weird place.
This is a man's romance!
Now is the main course!
The main course, huh?
Yes!
Any more... cost extra!
What?!
Damn... uh...
What you want to do?
Can't be helped, we do it another time.
I'll pay!
Thank you for business!
After this, you write I.O.U. for me.
It's fine! Okay! I-I'll write it!
Here comes service!
Wah! Spread eagle!
Panties are the best!
Just as I thought, girls the same age as me give off a different kind of charm.
Kazuma, you hard?
Yeah, of course!
Amazing! It stick out this much.
If you pay extra now, I give you special titty fuck service.
Yes! Please!
I'm happy!
Titty fuck, here we go!
Yahoo! It is wonderful to be alive!
How is titty fuck?
It's the best!
I'm happy!
Ah! It's the best! It's the best!
You coming? Say when you almost come.
C-China-san! China-san!
I'm coming!
Why?! Why?!
Service stop here.
You want to come, pay extra.
Are you a demon!?
I won't force.
What kind of hell is this?
By the way, there is much better place than titty for you to come! How about it?
What will you do, Kazuma?
Since I've already spent this much money, I'll just have to go all the way!
I love men who give!
Now, come!
I'm going in.
So this is... inside of China-san?
Kazuma not bad either.
No worry about me, just move.
It going all the way to end of stomach!
Good! Feels so good! Rub breasts harder!
Good, good! Push in more!
China-san! This time... for real...
I understand. You come inside me!
Ah! It's tight! I can't hold on anymore!
Ah! It coming!
Long awaited climax! I'm coming! I'm coming!
For everything... this much!
Tax charged separately.
This is service fee.
Wha- No way!
Ah, the video camera! My video camera!
Kazu-chan, what's wrong?
Huh? Not here. Uh... Ugh...
Geez, Kazu-chan. Have you been holding it in?
No! This is...
Don't tell me that was all a dream? Damn it!
Ah! Kazu-chan! Geez...
Since Kazu-chan's favorite gadget got washed ashore,
I wanted him to teach me how to use it...