Miss Sasaki, the anchor
woman of the 9 O'clock Wide Show...
...has just entered the press
conference for the new News Nine.
For the spring season,
News Nine has designated...
...Miss Miki
Katsuragi as the new anchor.
Miss Katsuragi became a freelance
reporter upon her resignation...
...from NH TV this past February.
Miss Katsuragi is known nationally...
...from NH TV's National News
as well as her role as the MC for...
...the New Year's Eve Red
versus White Battle of the Bands.
A woman of great style and
intelligence, she is a household name.
It looks as though Miss
Katsuragi is about to speak.
I am honored to have been given...
...the responsibility of being the
anchor of Tokyo TV's News Nine.
My name is Miki Kastsuragi.
This is a new challenge for me,
and I am sure I have a lot to learn.
I look forward to starting from the
beginning once again, and giving my all...
...to fulfill my role.
I thank you for your support.
Miki Katsuragi, what a gal.
Not only is she pretty, she's smart too.
They won't have any
problems with their ratings.
I understand why Tokyo TV
convinced her to leave NH TV...
...and gave her the
anchor's chair on News Nine.
Miki Katsuragi...
I've got to stop doing this...
If someone found out about this...
No...
...just doing this isn't
good enough anymore.
I'm tempted to make my
dangerous fantasies into reality...
I have to stop...
Nine O'clock
Woman
No...
I can't put my
vibrator in during the show.
I can't...
...but...
...just this once...
If I don't turn it on, no one will know.
It's so...
...good...
Miss Katsuragi...
Please stand by.
Fifteen minutes to live.
Y-Yes.
And go...
Good Evening.
It's time for News Nine.
I will be your host from today on.
My name is Miki Kastsuragi.
First, this news just in...
Earlier this evening, at around 8pm...
...a truck collided with a car,
causing a ten car pile up on Route 4.
A number or
fatalities have been reported.
We will update you
as we receive further details.
Route 4 may be closed
until tomorrow morning.
Miki Katsuragi...
She's great...
She's beautiful and seems so innocent.
She speaks well,
and she seems intelligent.
Our ratings are sure to go up.
Okay, thank you very much!
Thank you.
Thank you!
I'll take your mic.
Thank you.
Okay.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, are you okay?
I'm sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
No, it's my fault, I'm sorry.
That was close.
I can't...
This has...
...to be the last time...
It feels so good!
I have to stop this...
This is getting worse.
If they found out
what a bad girl I really am...
...getting off with my
vibrator during the show.
Floor!
We're at commercial now.
Ready to go live...
And in ten, nine, eight...
– Camera three, on Miss Katsuragi.
– Seven, six, five...
...four, three, two, one!
Roll opening song!
Good evening.
It's time for News Nine.
First, news just in...
...on the recurring earthquakes
centered at the Izu Peninsula.
This evening at 08:13 pm...
...the highest magnitudes since
the quakes began were recorded.
The following were documented...
Mikaye Island, magnitude 7, Kozushima,
magnitude 7.5, Oshima, magnitude 5.
Cue.
Prime Minister Morimura
has ordered the offices of...
...Emergency Management to
set up offices on the Ito Peninsula.
Cue.
And now, today's headline news.
Congress passed a bill
today in a special session...
...limiting social
security benefits for the elderly.
Cue.
Congressman Kimura, will
this new bill benefit the people?
There are many
benefits in the short run...
...but long term, it will
increase costs for taxpayers.
This is great.
Miki Katsuragi is great.
Our ratings have gone way up
since Katsuragi became an anchor.
She's got great style.
Great, thank you very much!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Good work!
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
That piece was
really easy to understand.
Thank you.
Good work!
Hey, Satake, hurry up.
Yes, sorry!
I have to...
...stop this.
If anyone knew I had my
vibrator in during the show...
...that I was such a bad girl...
If anyone found out...
I really have to stop this...
Miss Kasturagi.
Yes?
I have tomorrow's script for you.
T-Thank you.
I think this will change a little.
Okay, thanks.
Thank you.
Oh, by the way, Miss Katsuragi.
Yes?
Is your vibrator in right now, too?
He knows.
W-What are you talking about?
Oh come on, don't play dumb.
You had a big fat
vibrator you-know-where...
I saw it.
Who would have thought that the
smart and innocent Miki Katsuragi...
...has something like that in
her while she reads the news.
W-What do you want?
Money?
If it's money you want,
I can make arrangements, so...
That sounds good, but first...
I want you to take
It all off and show me...
It's in there right now, right?
Your vibrator...
Oh no, I'm finished!
I can't see anything like that.
Spread your legs.
Yeah, like that.
I can see it.
Wow, Miss Katsuragi, you're all messy.
How can you read the news like this?
Isn't this enough already?
Promise me you won't tell anyone.
Please!
How many times did you come?
Stop...
How many times did you
come during the broadcast?
I don't know...
No, stop!
No!
Answer me honestly.
How many times did you come?
Twice.
You're going to have
this in tomorrow too, right?
Then we should
rehearse so you don't mess up.
What?
But...
...with something else.
Come on, Miss
Katsuragi, read the script.
If you don't read the
script, I'm going to tell everyone.
G-Good evening...
...it's...
...t-time...
...f-for News Nine.
O-Our top story...
Does it really say it
like that in the script?
I think I'm going to come.
No, don't!
Please forgive me!
Okay then...
...we'll finish this tomorrow.
No...
I...
Miss Katsuragi, I'll
operate this by remote control...
...during tomorrow's broadcast.
Good luck.
You should get dressed, you
never know who might stop by.
And ten...
...nine, eight, seven.
six, five, four, three, two...
Five Seconds
Turning it
on high
...one, and go!
Good Evening.
It's time for News Nine.
As we brought to you in the
headline news, the final count for the...
...House of Representatives'
election was completed at 7 this morning.
Despite the massive
campaign efforts by the Democrats...
...the Conservative Party secured...
...the majority of the
votes, ensuring their victory.
In light of this breaking news,
I, Miki Katsuragi will bring to you...
...a special program, Post Election...
...Conversations with the
Representatives, beginning at two.
And that's it for
Wednesday's edition of News Nine.
We look forward to
seeing you again tomorrow.
Okay, thank you very much!
Thank you!
Miss Kasturagi, you
were great again today.
I look forward to your midnight show.
Y-Yes.
Thank you very much, Miss Katsuragi.
I hear you're going to
stay here and rest for a while.
Thank you for your hard work.
Uh, yeah, that's right.
I guess it looks like I'll
be spending the night here.
Miss Kasturagi.
Tomorrow's script.
Please take a look at it.
Yes, I understand.
Miki Katsuragi
Wait in studio two.
I will come by later.
It's dark in here.
I don't like this place.
Miss Katsuragi, please come to
work with this on in the morning.
It will turn on every 30 minutes.
If you take it out...
...I will tell everyone that...
...Miki Katsuragi has a vibrator in
her whenever she reads the news.
No, no more...
Wow, Miss Katsuragi...
...it looks like you've wet yourself.
P-Please take it out.
It's getting so...
Please hurry!
Please give me the key...
Oh come now, Miss Katsuragi.
If you're going to ask
for a favor, ask properly.
You're good, Miss Katsuragi.
That's it, use your tongue more.
That's great, very good.
I'm going to come now,
and I want you to swallow it all.
If you don't, it will go all over your face,
and you'll be in trouble for the next show.
Oh, you got all dirty.
Oh, well.
And now, I will take
it out, as you asked.
No...
No, don't look.
Wow, you're all messy.
And you're wide open, and
I can see all the way inside.
N-No...
So, all day today, you came over and
over with everyone watching, didn't you?
How was it?
Was it good?
Look at you, I guess
that was a stupid question...
Look at your face on the monitor.
You're blushing, you don't
look like yourself, do you?
N-No!
No!
Look.
Come on, look.
No!
Look at yourself.
No, stop!
Look at that close up.
It's amazing.
Oh, you're all wet again.
No, it's not true.
It's true...
Now, look.
No, no...
Miss Katsuragi, you like being watched.
No...
It can't be.
Look, you're on...
...look at the monitor.
My dick is going in...
...and out of you, Miss Katsuragi.
No...
I want to show everyone...
...this bad side of you.
No, not this...
Miss Katsuragi, you have a
midnight special after this, right?
Put this underwear on for the show.
I can hear my inner voice
begging for this pleasure.
Good Evening.
It's time for News Nine.