Good evening, this is the
nine o'clock news.
First up is the murder of a female
student in Matsudo.
They have discovered the weapon
used for the murder.
The weapon and what is believed
to be the suspect's
cell phone were both discovered
close to the body.
The weapon discovered
is a kitchen knife that is
about 15 cm in length.
Stained on it is the same O-type
blood as the victim.
Yes.
It's going well.
Yes, next month.
It's almost done.
Miki Katsuragi will be corrupted.
Satake-kun?
Satake-kun, are you not there?
I arrived at this company two
years ago as a part-timer,
but since then I have become
a technician for News9.
I met you for the very first
time at this studio.
You were pure, elegant, and beautiful.
Not someone I could pursue.
Satake-kun.
I have always admired you.
Maybe now, I can tell you my feelings.
I'm beginning to like you.
Satake-kun, I...
But now, I've got you.
From the moment I first laid my eyes
on you, I'd already decided
the last training is...
I can't do it anymore, I can't
express myself to him...
Katsuragi-san.
Please do it the usual way,
strip off your clothes,
pull out the vibrator,
and open your legs.
I can't express anything to him...
Nine O'Clock Woman. Episode 3.
Katsuragi-san, you always wear this
outfit, you must be used to it by now.
Before you know it, you'll
never forget this feeling.
The sensitivity of your
breasts isn't too bad.
Then, what about here?
How is it? Does it feel good?
Even so, my fingers satisfy
you, don't they?
Okay, go for it, Katsuragi-san.
It's always like this.
No...
No? You're so wet already.
Wetter and wetter.
You still like it like this better.
Then I'll do it like this.
Katsuragi-san, I'll show you a
brand new happiness today.
It's the first time here, right?
No.
That place...
It's okay, it'll be fine in a moment.
If it's Katsuragi-san...
Don't come until they're all the way in.
One.
Two.
Three.
No, Satake-kun, that place...
Four.
Five.
Do you only feel pain?
Six.
Are there any other feelings?
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
You sure can hold it in, Katsuragi-san.
You're already so wet.
You're about to come, aren't you?
Now, let's see how much
more you can withstand.
No, I can't...
Too bad, you couldn't
stand it and came.
In other words, you also feel
it from the hole in behind.
You're like a female dog.
You are tight after all.
Does it make you uncomfortable
if it's too sudden?
But, it's all right.
Doesn't it feel good, Katsuragi-san?
Don't hold back.
Just feel it naturally.
Feels good, doesn't it Katsuragi-san?
You're about to come, that's good.
Even ejaculating from behind is...
It's so scary, even though my body
belongs to me, I have no control...
Satake-kun.
What should I do?
You got me this far, what... are
you going to do with me now?
From now on, you will serve me
as Miki Katsuragi, my sex slave.
I listen quietly to his hidden feelings
and heart-depth voice.
Yes, hello?
Ah, hi.
Now? Not a problem.
Is that so?
I'm flattered.
that the first customer would be me.
Yeah, that's great.
I look forward to it
I know, I won't tell anyone else
Bye
Miki Katsuragi.
That's great (is great?)
Great... I'm about to hit
orgasm... I'm coming!
See you tomorrow night.
All right, thank you for the hard work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Katsuragi-san.
Sataki-kun. What is it?
This is a new project
from the producers.
They're beginning shooting for
Nozaki Marlins's interview
arranged for tomorrow.
Please head to room 3002 of the
Marriott Hotel at eleven-thirty.
I'll go pick you up once I finish
up the work around here.
Any questions?
No, I don't have any.
There are still things that I must
go take care of, see you later.
Another bad premonition.
As always, I'm wondering
what he'll do to me.
Work, work.
It's here.
Welcome, I've been waiting.
Please come in.
Thank you, sorry for disturbing you.
Thank you so much for taking time out
to meet me on such a busy day.
No, no, you're welcome.
Are you by yourself?
Where is the substitution for the
professional baseball player?
It's just me.
Even though it's like this,
I'm still very happy.
You've always been my
idol, Katsuragi-san.
Thank you.
Here.
Alcohol? Because we're
in the middle of work...
It's like a dream. To have
you before my eyes...
Um, let's go through the
interview contents.
Ah, excuse me.
Before that, I have something
that I would like to show you.
After I got my hands on this, I don't
know how many times I watched it.
This is... that time... with Satake-kun...
Even though the price to buy
you is somewhat expensive,
if it is to buy Miki Katsuragi
I'd pay double the price.
From now on, you will serve me
as Miki Katsuragi, my sex slave.
The night is long.
Let's enjoy this slowly, Katsuragi-san.
Is... is this your wish?
Satake-kun?
Oh yes, Katsuragi-san, please
change into this outfit.
Satake-kun, no!
Yes.
It fits you very well, Katsuragi-san.
Come, move your hand.
Hurry up.
You're beautiful.
What a lascivious body.
You can't move on your will
without my directions,
Katsuragi-san.
Yes, open your legs.
Put your hand behind you. That's good.
No...
You're already this wet.
I'm speechless.
Next, how does it taste?
No...
There's more.
Why... are you doing this...?
How lascivious is this body!?
How come I'm feeling this, I...
You're so wet, it's unstoppable.
Now, Katsuragi-san
you will serve me.
For the whole day today,
you are my slave.
Come, serve me, your master.
Keep doing this...
No... I can't...
No... no...
I'm going to come.
Am I... going to continue
being corrupted...?
Good evening, this is News9.