Nine O'clock
Woman
Good Evening.
It's time for News Nine.
First, the situation on the Izu...
...Peninsula, where there have
been repeated quakes, is very serious.
This afternoon at 06:26,
Mt. Mihara in Oshima had...
...its first eruption.
The ashes from the
volcano have rained...
...down upon the
town, limiting viability.
There is about 30
centimeters of ash covering the city...
...and all traffic has ground to a halt.
She's smart...
...and unpretentious...
I hold close to myself...
...my secret feelings...
...of such a beautiful woman...
Hey, Shimizu!
There aren't enough
lunches in studio four.
Get off your ass and
take some over there.
Y-Yes!
I better hurry.
I'm gonna get yelled at again...
Ouch...
I-I'm sorry, I...
Uh...
Miss Katsuragi...
Shimizu, what the hell are you doing?
I'm sorry Miss Kasturagi, are you okay?
Yes.
I'm fine...
Here.
Use this.
I was looking at my
script while I was walking.
I'm sorry.
Miss Katsuragi...
She's so nice...
She's so beautiful...
The repercussions
of Prime Minister Gori's...
...recent comments are still rippling.
Reporting from the Capitol.
And that was our Capitol
Correspondent, Miss Maya.
Prime Minister Gori's recent comments
have escalated the ongoing battle...
...with his opposition.
It appears that there is no end in sight
to the budget committee's investigation.
When we come back, sports.
And commercial rolling...
The sports news
starts with baseball, right?
Shimizu!
Mr. Satake!
I heard you got yelled
at by Mr. Yamada again.
Yeah.
I dropped all the
lunches this afternoon...
I see!
But Miss Katsuragi stood up for me...
She's such a nice person.
Miss Miki Katsuragi...
Mr. Shimizu, you have
a thing for Miss Katsuragi...
Uh, no!
I...
To be friends with
Miss Katsuragi like you...
...there's no way...
I'll help.
What...
I will help you become
friends with Miss Katsuragi.
You interested?
Mr. Satake...
After work, come to Miss
Katsuragi's dressing room.
It's okay.
I'll tell her.
Coming out of commercial.
But we have to think
about her reputation so...
Places...
Try not to let anyone see you.
Three, two...
And go, live!
And now for sports.
First, here are the results
from today's baseball games.
Reporting on the S
league's championship game...
...between Hiroshima and
Hanshin, is Hiroshima TV's Mr. Tsuda.
Apologize for this afternoon...
...and thank her for the handkerchief...
Miki Katsuragi
Okay!
It's completely dark.
I guess Mr. Satake and
Miss Katsuragi aren't here yet.
Who is it?
Miss Katsuragi...
Mr. Satake, is that you?
That's right, Miss Katsuragi...
You want to be friends
with Miss Katsuragi, right?
Then keep quiet.
Mr. Satake, this is enough, isn't it?
Please...
...take it out...
How many times did you come
while you were waiting for me?
Twice...
You're that wet and
you only came twice?
You really came more, didn't you?
No...
And before we started this...
And what about when you used to
have your vibrator in during the show?
And what about when your
vibrator was on all day at work?
Stop, please.
And when you filmed
yourself getting off on camera...
No!
And when you wore those
panties soaked in my come...
It looks like you just had a
little orgasm, Miss Katsuragi.
You get off just thinking
about other people seeing you...
...like this, don't you?
No way...
If you want the real thing, ask
for it properly like you always do.
Please...
Please put it in.
Miss Katsuragi...
Mr. Shimizu, she's asking you...
Stop!
It's so rough...
Mr. Satake...
This is different...
...than normal...
I'm sure it's because of
the blindfold, Miss Katsuragi...
No, no, I...
Mr. Shimizu, if you wish to continue
being friends with Miss Katsuragi...
You understand, right?
I won't tell anyone.
Miss Katsuragi, are you okay?
Yes.
I wonder why I feel
better seeing his face...
Well, I'm staying here
tonight, so I'll see you later.
This...
Wait, wait a minute Mr. Satake!
Why is this handkerchief here?
There's no way...
I've come too far...
I can't turn back anymore...
And that's the
weather report for tomorrow.
If you're going out tomorrow,
don't forget to take your umbrella.
Good night, and I look forward
to seeing you again tomorrow.
Commercial rolling.
Okay, thank you very much!
Thanks!
Thank you!
Miss Katsuragi, thank you.
Thank you.
Miss Katsuragi.
Thank you, Miss Katsuragi.
Uh, thank you...
Mr. Satake.
Would you like to go to dinner?
My treat.
Mr. Satake?
I saw an outfit that I
thought would look great on you.
So I bought it for tonight.
It's in a paper bag
in your dressing room.
It's a present from me to
you, so make sure you wear it.
I will call you on your cell phone
later to tell you where to meet me.
I'll see you later.
B-But...
Oh, come on...
...it'll be a nice change.
I'll be waiting for you.
What should I do?
I'm kind of happy...
This must be the outfit...
I should have known
what he wants from me.
How stupid can I be...
Hello.
Did you like my present?
Miss Katsuragi,
let's enjoy your present.
Don't wear anything
but your coat over it.
Put the switch to the
vibrator in your coat pocket.
We'll meet at an Italian
restaurant called CoCo.
It's around the
corner from 109 in Shibuya.
Miss Katsuragi, I'm
looking forward to our date tonight.
Hey, it's Miki Katsuragi.
Hey, look...
Wow, it's Miki Katsuragi.
It's too much...
Every time I move the vibrator rubs me.
I can't anymore...
Um...
You're Miki Katsuragi
from News Nine, right?
Uh, yes...
I'm a huge fan of yours,
can I have your autograph?
I'm sorry, just one second.
You're late, Miss Katsuragi.
I'm almost there...
You must be punished.
Turn the vibrator on right away.
I can't!
I'll know if you turned in on
or not if I check the battery.
Goodbye.
Um...
May I have your autograph?
Of course.
Miss Katsuragi, you're late.
I made reservations and everything...
...but you were so late, we lost them.
Can I turn this off?
Please...
There's a park near here.
Would you like to go for a walk?
M-Mr. Satake, please forgive me!
Please turn this thing off now.
Keep your voice down or
people will notice, Miss Katsuragi.
Unbutton your coat.
If you do as I say, I'll turn it off.
Go on...
Open it up and let me see.
It looks good on you, Miss Katsuragi.
Okay then...
...as you wish...
Pretty amazing, as always.
Don't...
What would you like
me to do to you now?
Please...
Put it in, please.
Miss Katsuragi, if you
don't keep your voice down...
...people will notice.
No!
Or do you want to be seen?
No, I don't...
No more...
Are you coming?
Go ahead.
I'll watch you come.
No, don't!
Mr. Satake, why...
...do you do this?
You're almost there...
You're almost...
...the perfect sex slave...
What does...
...he mean?
Good Evening.
It's time for News Nine.