You know...
I was planning on studying with Kaho, and just Kaho.
Well, you see, I ran into Mr. Kanie...
...and when I told him about today, he said he'd help us study.
If you're serious about studying, it ought to be better with a teacher, right?
Oh, you know, I was having trouble with math,
so I brought a workbook and stuff.
I sure was hoping Kaho would be the one to teach me...
What?
Mathematics: Starting with the Essentials
Ow!
Teach you math, right?
Get a clue already, man.
Anyway, you shouldn't be asking this girl about math.
She only barely scraped by the last exam.
Hey!
Moreover, Aida did quite well on the supplementary exam.
If he would just attend class,
he wouldn't get such bad grades.
Huh?
I-Is that true, Aida?
W-Wait...
Could it be that... you thought I was just stupid?
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 10: Is That Jealousy?
It's true. You got them all right.
That's amazing, Aida!
You could say that.
OK, now try these practice exercises.
I Understand Mathematics
Problem Workbook
Seriously, there's more?
Don't you want to impress Miyoshi?
Ahh, right. Guess there's nothing for it, then.
I wonder if this side of Aida is a bit like the way Kanie used to be.
H-Hey!
Why is he...
What could he be thinking?
K-Kanie...
You can't! You have to stop or someone will notice!
N-No, not inside...
N-No way, you're going to put your finger in
in p-public like this?
Oh no, I'm going to moan.
Kanie, just how far to you plan on going?
Could it be... Could he be planning on going all the way?
P-Please, let me go!
If you keep going that hard, I'll...
You're making all kinds of lewd noises down there again.
You're actually turned on by this, aren't you?
N-No! Don't say things like that!
H-He's wrong!
It's just that this is so embarrassing!
It's no good, I can't... hold it back.
I'm going to—I'm about to cum
in public where anyone can see.
Kaho, is something wrong?
Oh, umm... s-sorry.
You OK?
I-I'm going to the ladies room. Be right back.
Don't push yourself too hard, Miyoshi.
Your face is all flushed.
Unbelievable.
After doing all that, whose fault does he think that is, exactly?
Wait, could it be that he was jealous of Aida?
No, no, I need to stop making excuses for him.
At this rate, I'm never going to get any studying done.
Kanie is actually taking his tutoring seriously.
That's right, Kanie is already a fully-fledged teacher.
And what am I doing with my life, exactly?
Who could have predicted this reunion?
Welcome back!
Aida, I feel bad leaving, but I remembered I had plans.
I've got to leave now. Sorry.
Seriously? Then I'm done too.
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Try to see this as an opportunity and keep studying with Mr. Kanie a bit longer, OK?
Why are you all pushy one minute,
Seriously?
And Mr. Kanie, I'm sorry for leaving after asking you to go out of your way like this.
If you'll excuse me, then.
and then gentle the next?
Right.
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Yamada Shiro