Tonight is Kanie and my first class reunion since graduating high school.
Graduating Class of 1989, ***** Academy Class Reunion
That so? Kanie does seem different somehow.
It took me off guard.
Right, Hana?
Y-Yeah.
This girl was so rude.
She didn't remember me at all.
I-I mean...
I recognized her on sight, too...
I-It's because he recognized me on sight that I went though all that...
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 4: On the Night of the Class Reunion
This is so embarrassing. Why does Kanie have follow me around?
Your feet.
My feet?
Are you still having cramps?
Oh, no. They're fine.
I see. That's good.
Yeah.
Could it be that he was worried about me?
Huh?
What are you doing, Kanie?
If you act strangely, people will suspect something's going on.
Huh?
That can't be right—this guy's just the worst.
B-But Kanie, if we're together like this,
people will know something's going on.
This is no fun.
W-Where are we going?
Wait, Kanie! Don't...
Not here...
Today you aren't a student, so I won't stop halfway.
Plea—
Man, everyone's changed too much.
I couldn't even recognize any of the girls.
No way, someone's coming in?
K-Kanie, you can't. We'll be found out.
If you make any noise, we might be.
Oh yeah, that guy Kanie was with Natori. Were they ever close?
They're dating, surprisingly enough.
For real?
I guess that's what it looks like, huh?
N-No way...
That's right, Kanie had a crush on Natori back then, didn't he?
W-What did he just say?
Kanie had a crush on me?
That time, Kanie was especially intense
as if he were trying to distract me from what I had just heard.
What? No way!
Wait, that's...!
We can't, not in a place like this!
Why is this happening? I can't keep quiet!
K-Kanie—
I-It's so deep!
Hold on to me.
No, K-Kanie... No more!
You can finish.
I-I can't move.
People might be suspicious after we were gone for so long.
S-Say, Kanie...
Hmm?
About, umm... what they were saying back there...
Yeah?
N-Never mind.
S-Sorry! Thank you.
I'll make up a suitable excuse, so take it easy and come with me.
I can never understand what Kanie is thinking.
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Artist: Utsugi Yua
Be sure to watch next time!