This isn't going too far, is it?
I mean, he helped me study and everything.
Doing this for him, though...
It's almost like... I'm his girlfriend.
Watcha making?
Fried eggs?
Omelets?
If it's fried eggs, I like mine well done.
U-Understood! Now put some clothes on!
It's so early, but you're wide awake.
H-Hey!
That's because I don't want you to be late for school!
School is such a pain in the ass.
What?
Here I was thinking, "gee, Kanie's really changed since we were in school..."
...but you haven't really, have you?
Nope, I'm going for it.
K-Kanie, no...
Like I was saying, l-look at the time!
It'll be fine if we're quick.
W-What do you mean, "quick"?
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 9: That Morning, Just the Two of Them
It's like these are asking me to touch them.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Just look how hard they are.
Oh no.
If he keeps that up, I won't be able to stand.
Not... there...
You mean here?
I-I said stop!
No!
D-Don't put your finger in! Stop!
My finger just went right in.
You sure this isn't what you wanted?
You haven't been resisting as much lately.
Y-You're wrong!
Stop that!
Sorry, but it's too late for that.
You really are hot inside.
S-Stop it, I said stop!
Kanie!
"Stop?" Don't you mean, "This feels so good!"
M-My mind is all fuzzy.
I-It feels so good!
This is how I always end up being caught in the flow as Kanie does whatever he likes.
At some point along the way, though, I stopped having so many reservations about it.
What's the matter?
If you don't eat quickly, we really will be late.
Oh, right.
It must have felt really good for you to be so out of it, huh?
W-What about you?
Me?
Nothing! I didn't say anything. Forget it!
Don't worry.
It felt really good for me, too.
This is the worst. Why did I have to go and say something like that?
Mom (Mobile)
Mom's calling me?
Yeah, it's fine. I'm on my lunch break.
I know. I'm not just working part-time.
I'm still looking for a full-time job, too.
Yeah, that's right.
Finding work mid-career isn't so easy these days.
I have to go.
Bye. I'll call again soon.
Yeah, OK.
What am I even doing?
I'm 25 years old, and I haven't even been able to find a new job yet.
Instead I'm playing at being a student again.
I'm a real failure, huh?
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Michinoku Atami