I wonder how long it's been since I seriously exercised...
I feel so heavy...
Mr. Kanie, I'm dying out here.
It's better than embarrassing yourself at the athletic festival.
You've gotta get your practice in while you can.
Don't compare my stamina to these kids'.
Also, wear something under that next time.
Your bra is showing through.
N-No way!
That's it for today.
Come with me.
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 3: Private After-School Lesson
If you don't stretch properly after exercise, you'll never get over the fatigue.
I'm sure you know how bad muscle pain can be at 25.
Sit down here.
Y-Yes, sir.
Something doesn't feel right.
Hey, what's got you all nervous?
Ouch!
Huh?
No, that was just...
So I was right, even sitting is hard for you.
Lay back.
Y-Yes, sir.
It hurts!
You're really stiff.
T-That's not true—
I-I can handle this much on my own, Mr. Kanie.
Just hold still.
Something's not right about this.
No, I mean it—I'm fine. Since you started doing that, I...
Well, I hadn't planned on doing anything...
Then why, Kanie?
If you're going to get my attention like that, I can't help it if I get any strange ideas.
I'm not trying to get—
No, at this rate we'll...
N-No! I really... have to be... getting home.
You're going home dressed like this?
K-Kanie, don't.
That's Mr. Kanie to you.
You're already so wet.
Y-You're wrong!
You're also drenched with sweat.
W-What is this? At this rate, I'll...!
You're into it even more than last time.
N-No!
Please!
Ow!
What's wrong?
Ow, ow, ow! My foot, it's cramped!
Huh?
It's not funny!
You're right, I'm sorry.
Be sure to keep working on your flexibility.
If you're this stiff, you're bound to get hurt some day.
R-Right...
Yes, sir!
Good.
By the way, the day after tomorrow is the class reunion, huh?
You're coming, right?
Huh? Yeah...
Our class reunion...
I won't be going as Kaho Miyoshi, but as the 25-year-old Hana Natori...
Who could have predicted this reunion?
...with Kanie.
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Artist: Meg
Be sure to watch next time!
Kanie, you demon!
You're a monster!!!
After school during
supplementary lessons!