So Kaho, what do you say to going on a date?
A d-date?
Like I said the other day, I've always thought you were good looking.
What do I do?
I can't be dealing with this right now.
I'm not currently wearing any underwear!
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 6: I'm Going to be Found Out!
It could even be right now.
We could just skip fifth period.
I think... we should probably just go to class.
Really?
You might think it's a waste of time now,
but when you think about the future...
You know, Kaho...
I was thinking this the other day too.
You've changed.
Y-You think so?
It's like you're... more mature somehow.
T-This is bad.
It's a little suspicious.
You know what? I changed my mind!
Let's skip class together!
That's what I thought you'd say.
Wait, where are we going, Aida?
Say, Kaho...
...wanna do it with me again?
W-What? "Again"?
Oh come on, it was just the day before
yesterday on my way home from work...
We went to a hotel together.
Don't you remember?
U-Umm...
No way, how long has Kaho been doing that kind of thing?
Just kidding!
I was just pulling your leg.
What?!
But seriously, though...
Why didn't you deny it just then?
I knew something seemed suspicious...
If you don't tell me what it is, maybe I'll just do something even more lewd.
W-What do I do?
If he gropes my butt, he'll know I'm not wearing panties!
I can't let that happen—I just can't!
That's enough of that.
Dammit, Kanie again?
I could say the same about you.
Didn't I tell you to address me properly?
K-Kanie? How did you...
I hope you understand how serious this is.
You could be suspended.
It's not what you think—there was just something I wanted to confirm.
Right?
That's enough for today.
See you later, Kaho!
U-Umm, I...
Come with me.
I-Is he mad?
AV Room
What did you think you were doing?
I, umm... Well, it's not like my cover's completely blown.
I wasn't talking about that.
Huh?
Anyway, are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
I'm fine. I little surprised, though.
I'm sorry. I told you I'd protect you, then this happened.
I-It's alright.
As long as you're okay.
S-So I've been wondering since the class reunion...
Kanie, do you...?
D-Don't, Kanie...
Are you wet because of him?
N-No, of course not!
Really? Is it because of me, then?
W-Wait!
This is in the way.
Don't cover them.
N-No...
Kanie!
No!
No, no! Wait...
No...
Stop, what are you...?
N-No!
Not there, that's...
S-Stop!
I...
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Koshino