That's right, Kanie had a crush on Natori back then, didn't he?
W-What did he just say?
Let's go do karaoke!
Kanie felt that way about me?
That can't be true.
Hey, Miyoshi.
Yes, sir!
Are you still half-asleep?
W-What's going on?
Why is he staring at me?
Skirt length, makeup, hair...
...all against code.
What?
Oh, I see. This must be a dress code inspection.
Come to the sociology prep room during your lunch break.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Seriously, what was I even thinking...
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 5: How Could I Have Lost Those?!
Sociology Prep Room
I've been thinking about this since that first day...
What's with that getup?
And your makeup—you were hardly wearing any at the class reunion.
T-That's because Kaho is a really showy girl.
I-I don't like it any more than you do.
And here I thought you just liked dressing up that way.
A-As if!
But as your teacher, I need to discipline you.
Wha—Kanie!
Are you going to disobey a teacher?
Huh? W-What are you...?
Stop!
You're light as a feather.
W-Wait, you can't!
Behave, now.
N-No!
W-Wait, don't just...
Why? You don't need them.
That reminds me, don't we have a test coming up?
Oh, yeah.
No, Kanie! I mean it!
A-At this rate, we'll be...
You're right. It's just like last time.
Oh, shit, I didn't do my homework!
No!
No, this might be worse.
There's no telling when someone will come in, or who it will be.
No way...
Shall we give them something even better to look at?
N-No, you can't! I'm begging you, Kanie...
Stop, please stop!
There's the bell. I guess that's as far as we go.
What?
Oh, are you saying you wish we could have kept going?
O-Of course not!
I-I have to get back to class.
Don't trip over yourself getting there.
I'll be perfectly fine, thank you!
Huh? Why is it locked?
There's no way I'd do that without locking the door.
Sociology Prep Room
I-If you'll excuse me, then.
I'll never get tired of watching her.
Hmm?
Oh.
Damnit, I just know Kanie is enjoying himself.
Wait...
My butt feels kind of cold...
I-I forgot my panties!
Oh, hey Kaho.
Who could have predicted this reunion?
What's the matter? Class is about to start.
W-W-What do I do now?!
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Be sure to watch next time!
Artist: Takada