This was a terrible idea!
Does this skirt have to be so short?
I'm 25 years old, dammit!
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 1: An Unexpected Reunion
You want me to go to school for Kaho?
That girl does nothing but go out with friends.
She hasn't attended classes since she enrolled.
At this rate, she'll have to repeat a year.
No way! Not happening!
You'll be fine!
You and Kaho are practically twins!
You can do it!
Hana, I know you haven't found a new job yet.
I'll be sure to make it worth your time!
I ended up giving in...
Mathematics: New Edition
...but I don't think I can keep this up.
Kaho. Kaho Miyoshi!
Y-Yes!
What's the matter? Are you not feeling well?
Yes. I umm... I have a headache.
Nurse's Office
I'm beat...
He told me to take a break and lie down.
Oh, hey Kaho. Skipping class again?
Why'd you leave karaoke early the other day?
W-What do I say?
Is he a friend of Kaho's? He couldn't be her boyfriend...
You know, I've always thought you were pretty.
That's really close!
Next time, come as my trophy girl.
You've done that for other guys, right?
What's going on in here?
Shit, it's Kanie.
You've got a lot of energy for someone with such a terrible a fever, huh Aida?
W-Well, you see...
He's a teacher?
If you're feeling better, go to class.
Yeah, yeah.
"Yes sir."
Got it.
U-Umm, sir, I wasn't feeling well and so...
It is you! You're Hana Natori.
Y-You're mistaken. I'm...!
Huh?
Have I been found out?
So you really don't remember?
Well, it has been quite a while since graduation.
I'm Akito Kanie. We were in the same class.
You're that Kanie?
What's that mean?
Please, Kanie.
I need you to keep quiet about me.
You see, there's a very good reason for this...
I see. I understand the situation, but I can't support such foolish behavior.
W-Wait, Kanie!
I told you, at this rate Kaho is going to be held back.
We reap what we sow.
Besides, how do you feel about it?
I don't think it's right, but she worked so hard to get into this school.
You're still as softhearted as ever.
Kanie?
Do you know what to do to keep a man quiet?
A kiss?! But why? N-No...!
Kanie, no!
You're trembling after a simple kiss.
You can't possibly be a real high school girl.
That's because you didn't give me any warning.
And here I was thinking I'd just tease you a little...
but if you're going to make that face...
N-No way!
N-No! Stop it, Kanie!
You want me to keep quiet, don't you?
Y-You can't. We're still in the nurse's office.
Just for you...
I'll give you a special lesson I can't give to children.
This can't be happening. What do I do?
M-My body's not listening to me.
You're not struggling very much now.
N-Not there...!
No!
How did it turn out like this?
What's going to happen to me after this?
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
What's going on here?
Dark Loli Warrior Costume Set
Be sure to watch next time!
Artist: Esaki Bisuko