N-No more...
I'm so embarrassed, I could die.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
No, Kanie! We can't go any further!
S-Stop! Why are you...
How can I take you seriously,
when you're clearly enjoying it?
No...!
W-Wait, I-I...
You're not getting away from me.
No, oww—
Y-You can't, no more or I'll...
No, no more!
Sounds like you're getting close to finishing.
Stop, no...!
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 7: Private Study Session
You're actually going straight to class, Natori?
If I don't, there's no point in my being here.
Besides, we have exams soon.
That reminds me, you did terribly on that quiz the other day.
W-What did you expect?
It's not like I've had to study since graduating.
Alright, alright.
Leave your schedule open tomorrow after school.
I'll teach you how to study.
What?
How did this happen? How did I end up in Kanie's apartment?
Here. You're good with coffee, yeah?
Wha—
Oh,  t-thank you.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing...
Oh, did you think I was going to do something to you again?
Could it be that a part of you was hoping I would?
Y-You're wrong!
Your face is bright red.
I said it's not like that...
No, Kanie...
Don't worry,
I won't do anything.
Huh?
Oww!
Now get to work already.
R-Right...
To begin with, I want to know your abilities, so start with this bit here.
This is so difficult...
Could I really work out stuff like this back then?
Well, you won't master the subject overnight,
but I can at least teach you the fundamentals.
Be sure to ask if you don't understand anything.
Yeah...
Say, Kanie, do you wear those because you have poor eyesight?
You wear them during class, too.
It's not all that bad.
But it's easier with them, sure.
Do you like me better this way?
That's... That's not why I asked...
It's backwards from when we were in school.
Huh?
I'm going to wash up.
You keep working.
Did something happen when we were students?
This may be a more serious problem than I thought.
I really tried my best...
Well, that's alright.
We've got plenty of time, after all.
B-But, if it gets too late, I won't get home on time.
****day **/**
Just stay over.
Wha...What?!
I said I'd help you, didn't I?
What?
So listen to me.
Y-Yes, sir.
I can't tell if Kanie is being nice, or just pushy!
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Hatokonro