I guess I just made things awkward.
I started feeling sorry for myself, and
now I'm causing trouble for everyone.
Natori!
Kanie? Why are you...?
You were lying about running errands, weren't you?
N-No, I wasn't!
Is it that you really just wanted to be alone with Aida?
What?
Am I wrong?
You weren't able to turn him
down when he asked you out.
You certainly didn't seem very upset when he did.
I told you, that's because he already suspects that... that I'm not Kaho.
If I avoid him too much, he'll get even more suspicious!
Suspicious?
It's not like he has any proof, so what difference does that make?
I mean, I guess...
Just how long do you plan to keep up this ridiculous charade when you're scared of your own shadow?
"Ridiculous charade," huh?
That hit the nail on the head.
I have no comeback.
Sorry, I didn't mean to come at you like that.
I'm done.
What's that mean?
Done with what?
What do you think you're going to do now?
That's none of your business.
"None of my business," is it?
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 11: The Absolute Worst Day
It's alright, K-Kanie.
I can get home by myself.
So you don't really have any errands, do you?
Huh? W-What are you doing?
I'll be the one to decide that it's "none of my business."
K-Kanie...
N-No, Kanie... S-Stop, I mean it...
Is he upset about what I said?
You can say it's "none of my business" all you want, but I can tell how much you're enjoying this.
N-No...
No more!
You're soaking wet.
No...
I-I thought that, bit-by-bit, I was starting to really understand him...
...but all it takes is one remark hitting home
to set him off like this.
I can't take it anymore!
That's none of your business.
I-I'm going to...
N-Natori, I'm sorry. I went too far—
What the hell am I doing?
Hasegawa.
Here!
Fuse.
Manaka.
Here!
Miyoshi.
Kaho Miyoshi.
Mr. Kanie.
Miyoshi isn't coming in today.
I see.
I can't say I'm surprised.
Miyoshi
Huh, I guess auntie is out.
I even told her I was vising today.
I really wanted to have a serious conversation about Kaho.
I ended up skipping school.
What am I even doing?
Call History
Kanie
I have so many calls from Kanie...
I wonder if he's worried about me after all.
I need to have a real talk with him.
I said some things I regret too.
Kanie
Mobile
A-Another call?
Who could have predicted this reunion?
Natori...
K-Kanie...
Got a minute?
Y-Yeah...
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to be optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Makana