As I recall, back when we were in school, Kanie acted something like this...
Hey Kanie, you've got supplementary lessons today!
Oh, shoot. Sorry, I've got plans today, so I'm leaving early.
Back then, I could never in a thousand years have imagined that Kanie of all people
would become a teacher, or that things would turn out like this.
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 2: In the Nurse's Office Bed
Nurse's Office
Just for you...
I'll give you a special lesson I can't give to children.
No!
Not that!
No more!
You're already so wet, though.
You actually want it, don't you?
Y-You're wrong.
No! Don't, Kanie. Any more and I'll...
They'll hear you outside.
That's a good girl.
Wow, it's really sloshing around.
Stop it already!
What's that? Are you OK with being found out, then?
That's right, if my secret is exposed it won't be just me that gets in trouble, but also Kaho.
But doing something like this...
Natori.
Huh?
Nurse's Office
In the end, Kanie didn't go any further.
I suppose I can keep your secret.
Your personality is the polar opposite of Kaho Miyoshi.
If you keep acting all timid like that, you'll be found out in no time.
Are you really going to keep my secret, Kanie?
And if you don't want to be assaulted by punks like Aida, you'd better try and stay close to me.
It was you who assaulted me just now...
I'm a teacher here, you understand?
So while we're at school, address me properly if you don't want to be found out.
Y-Yes, sir.
This whole thing is off to a terrible start.
Let's see... Boys in Class B...
Akito Kanie
Kanie used to look like this?
It's no wonder I didn't recognize him.
Wait, now that I think about it, how was it that he recognized me so quickly?
Natori
I guess I really haven't changed much.
W-Who could that be?
Dreams
Hello, is this Natori?
Yes. Umm...
It's me, Kanie.
K-Kanie?
How did you know my number?
I got it from Konishi, he's the coordinator
for the alumni association.
So, umm... Why are you calling?
Did you know the athletic festival is next week?
A-Athletic festival?
You had best get some exercise.
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I'll train with you.
I-I'm fine, I don't need you to.
"Fine," you say? Do you really think you have that kind of stamina, Miss 25-year-old?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
W-Well...
OK, we'll start tomorrow, then.
Don't forget your gym uniform.
Why are you all pushy one minute,
H-Hold on!
and then gentle the next?
An athletic festival, huh?
How is that going to work out for me?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
You still have a
hickey from
the other day,
you know.
What?!
Where did
you make it?!
Be sure to watch next time!
At 25, marks
like that take
a long time
to heal!
Artist: Nayuka Mine