The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 12: I Love You!
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I ignored your feelings...
...and hurt you.
I'm sorry too.
You followed me because you were worried.
I'm sorry for saying it was none of your business.
When I see how you've become such a wonderful teacher,
it makes me angry and depressed about my current situation,
and I ended up taking it out on you.
Natori...
Do you remember when you would tutor me back in high school?
Oh, yeah, but...
Well, I wasn't exactly the best tutor.
Even though it was for a stranger, you took it more seriously than I did.
I couldn't believe it.
W-What?
But seeing you like that...
...I thought "that doesn't seem so bad."
Huh?
You're a big part of the reason I am where I am today.
That's why I don't want you badmouthing yourself like that in front of me.
Kanie...
By the way, do you... really not remember?
About that one time...
Which time was this?
It's just, I...
...confessed to you.
Huh?
Library
Hey Natori, do you like, have a boyfriend?
No way.
I'm not exactly popular with the boys.
I like you pretty well, though.
Oh, you're so funny, Kanie.
Wha—
Wow, that's amazing Kanie!
You've finished all the review problems!
R-Right...
I-I'm so sorry!
Back then I was sure you didn't feel that way about me,
so when you told me so casually, I was sure you were teasing me.
It was a long time ago.
U-Umm, could it be that you... still feel that way?
I-I thought this conversation was past tense.
Kanie's so embarrassed...
Crap, he's just too cute.
What?
I... want you to say it.
I love you even more now.
You're crying. What's wrong?
Am I? Sorry, I just...
Never say it's none of my business again.
I won't.
Also, I want you to come to me next time something happens.
I will.
Crap, I really want to do it.
Huh?
Don't want to?
I didn't say that...
You look really into it today.
T-That's because...
Because it feels better than usual?
Y-You're such a tease!
You only just realized that?
N-No, don't! Not... there!
W-Wait...
N-No!
No, stop...
If you do that now, I'm going to...
Natori?
S-Sorry...
I...
I'm sorry, Natori.
I can't take it any longer.
I'm going to put it in.
O-Okay.
H-He's being so rough.
If Kanie wants to do it that way, I'll show him I can keep up.
We shouldn't be doing this here.
This is so embarrassing!
I love you, Natori.
I expect to see you in school tomorrow.
Save that kind of talk for your students.
See you tomorrow, then.
Umm, K-Kanie?
Yeah?
It made me really happy to hear how you feel.
I... love you too.
What took you so long, dummy?
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to be optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Makana