Thanks to Kanie's tutoring,
I'm done studying for my test.
Well, that's alright.
We've got plenty of time, after all.
N-No!
He meant plenty of time to study... right?
The 25 Year Old High School Girl
Episode 8: On That Day, At That Time, In That Place
What's this?
He fell asleep.
If he was that tired, he shouldn't have stayed up with me.
It's backwards from when we were in school.
What could he have meant by that?
Back then, Kanie had longer hair...
...he even dyed it.
He was even less approachable than he is now.
What's up?
S-Sorry!
I didn't mean to wake you.
Thanks for letting me take a bath.
And these cloths... I promise I'll wash and return them.
Are you trying to turn me on?
What?
K-Kanie, are you sure not still half asleep?
No!
Stop! Y-You said we wouldn't do this kind of thing today.
I never promised anything.
T-That's playing dirty!
You always mislead me when it comes to the most important details.
Then I'll ask.
What do you want me to say to you?
W-What? He's asking me?
What do I want him to say?
Well, I...
Too bad, your time's up.
It's no use.
I can't think clearly anymore.
What, embarrassed?
N-No!
K-Kanie, wait!
I won't.
You're already soaking wet.
Does it feel that good?
Th-That's not...
No!
Look at me, Natori.
I can feel how hot you are inside.
No!
N-No, Kanie...
A-Any more and I'll...
That night, I had a dream.
Oh, hi.
Natori. Did you forgot something?
Oh, no. Why are you...?
Me?
Being forced to do makeup lessons until just now.
Apparently I have a make-up text next week.
S-Sounds rough.
Not like this crap will do me any good.
B-But you never know what
might be useful in the future.
I'm sure it will come in useful, somehow.
Do you find people like me hard to deal with?
N-Not at all!
Useful in the future, huh?
Do you have any plans for your future?
Well, I used to, but I think it's a little late for that...
It's never too late!
I think just having a dream is really amazing.
Especially since I haven't been able to find one for myself, even after all this time.
Sorry, we weren't talking about me.
Then what do you say to helping me study?
What? B-But I'm really not all that smart...
You're smarter than me.
Umm, so what is it you want to be in the future?
Not telling.
That's right...
I completely forgot.
Could it be that Kanie had feelings for me back then?
Well?
What about now?
Then I'll ask.
What do you want me to say to you?
It was really underhanded of him to put me on the spot like that.
Who could have predicted this reunion?
I reel in this thread of memory, and use it to spin my tale
Why are you all pushy one minute,
and then gentle the next?
As long as the two of us share this secret
it will be the light that guides you
to somewhere in the yet-unknowable future
I'm telling you, it's okay to optimistic
I want to know everything about you
hidden deep within those eyes
I can't control these feelings
Piece by piece, my heart is being snatched away
Translated by IBN_5100
Miwashiba