Looks like she's really having trouble choosing.
She's kinda petite too.
So cute.
stare
Wait? What the?
It's as if she's staring at me really hard.
Y-You've been looking at this way for a while.
Do you need something?
I'm envious. You get to buy lots of sweets, onii-chan.
I want that too.
Shall I buy you something, then?
Oh, really?
Yay!
Whoa, I can totally see her tiny nipples.
Not a single bit of meat at all.
Lessee...
Well.
Petite girls are cute!
I want this!
I love this candy.
She's just super cute!
I'm going to buy that, then.
'Kay.
Hey, onii-chan.
Since we're at it, why don't we eat
those together by the rooftop?
Whoa!
I'm so happy.
It's really good.
Sweet!
Hey, umm... what's your name?
Manami.
Manami-chan, huh.
Such a cute name.
What school year are you now?
Hm? I'm a third year.
Which means, umm.
About twenty.
She's rather small for a college student.
Nope. I'm ***.
Oh, it's gone.
Eight, you say? Ah forget it, then.
I can see her tiny nipples again!
That's nice. Yours looks kinda delicious too.
Do you want to eat these?
Eh? Can I?
Yeah!
What?!
Snacks.
Wow... she's on my lap!
This petite girl is on my lap right now!
Looks tasty.
This tastes delicious.
She smells nice.
Her tummy feels soft too.
It's tender all over.
Maybe I should have gotten this one instead.
Her legs also feel smooth.
This is the best.
Manami-chan.
Let's eat snacks here again tomorrow.
I'll buy you something again.
Yay!
I can't wait!
I might be able to touch her even more tomorrow!
Next Day
Picked one yet?
Which are you going to choose?
I want this,
but it's kinda expensive.
Which one?
It's cheap!
Guess it's normal for her to think that. How cute.
She really is a kid.
Oh yeah.
300 yen, huh.
It's a bit expensive, but...
Alright, I'll buy it for you.
Really?
Alright!
In exchange,
can you listen to one single request from me?
Okay! I'll grant anything!
So good.
Y-Yeah.
So, Manami-chan,
well, about the request I mentioned earlier.
Your body feels soft and smooth.
Could you please let me touch it a bit?
Huh? That's all?
Okay then. I'm used to being petted, anyway.
Whoopsie.
Here, onii-chan, go ahead.
Wow, the scent of soap wafting from her is nice.
Onii-chan, that tickles!
Her sweat makes it even softer to touch,
and since she's so slender, her petite body feels great.
Onii... chan...
I really wonder why it feels this tender.
Her slender body still hasn't matured.
Her navel is petite as well.
Such tiny nipples!
They're not even ample, but they feel surprisingly soft.
I might just get addicted to this.
Huh? It felt like her nipples kinda got hard.
They're starting to bulge.
Onii-chan,
something... feels weird.
What's wrong, Manami-chan?
Is she getting a bit aroused?
My body... feels kinda hot.
If I continue to play with this.
Alright.
Thanks. It really felt great touching
your soft body, Manami-chan.
Are you...
done already?
Yup. Let's wrap this up for today.
Onii-chan.
Oh? What's wrong?
Do you want to continue?
It felt good, I see.
Yeah.
I want to do it more,
but it's getting late already, so let's just do it tomorrow, okay?
After that,
in exchange for buying something for about 300 yen,
I got to play with Manami-chan's soft body.
My breasts feel tingly.
Please don't touch me down there!
Manami-chan, this spot is called "pussy".
Pussy?
While I try to learn more and more about her body,
I also get to discover more and more of her tender spots.
This body, that's still ignorant of sexual matters,
is molded... ever so slowly.
Her mouth is small.
She's licking with her tongue.
Even sucking the tip.
I'm about to...
That spot is!
Your pussy really is petite.
It's so erotic.
Even this very young body,
given enough time,
eventually reacts like an adult woman's body.
Please don't... put your finger in my pussy.
It's still tight even with a pinky, huh.
In the span of a week, she was finally
able to cum with her clit and nipples.
The juices start to flow as I continue to lick it.
Onii-chan...
Oh no, not that spot.
It's starting to overflow.
Hey now, I need to be able to lick it properly.
Looks like you came again.
She's completely dazed.
She's breathing heavily too.
I've waited for a week already.
I can do it already, right?
Looks like it's loosened up a lot, anyway.
Manami-chan, try to relax.
Onii-chan, what are you going to do with your dick?
Are you going to rub it again?
This time,
I'm going to.
Rub into your pussy while inviting your clit in.
The tip's in.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt, but...
My insides,
they, they feel tight.
If it doesn't hurt,
I guess it's okay?
It's quite wet already, anyway.
I'm going to push a bit deeper.
Mine's so wet now with your pussy, Manami-chan.
O-Onii-chan...
So tight.
Even this small pussy can widen this much.
So it's right around here, huh.
I never really thought it'd fit in.
So you can but it in if you loosen it enough.
Your hand tickles.
I'm trying to tell where the tip is exactly.
I'm going to push it in further.
It went deeper inside!
Dead end already.
Her vagina is only up to this point, after all.
It feels like my dick's about to be squeezed off.
I'm going to move, Manami-chan.
Slowly.
Onii-chan...
It's going in even deeper than earlier.
I'm actually touching her cervix!
Onii-chan... my pussy.
It feels hot.
Her insides stimulate me at every move.
It makes my back feel all tingly.
Every time her insides twitch,
it contracts, and then.
This... kind of feels nice.
Her insides also feel so tight.
It feels very, very good.
Such a petite ass.
I wasn't able to push further than the tip,
so I used to just fuck with the tip of my dick.
Onii-chan...
It's coming out.
Many Days Later
After that...
Onii-chan!
– I kept meeting with her every single day.
– Over here!
– It looks like she's gotten used to having sex as well.
– What do you want today?
– Actually, I already have my choice for today!
– She even started to moan pleasurably while doing it.
– Is that so?
Here, onii-chan.
I want this one today. It's a new product!
– I want to eat it already.
– Looks like our 300 yen relationship.
– There's lots for both of us!
– won't end anytime soon.