Everyone is familiar with these kinds of games.
The Hero, Tomochiro has been summoned.
Together, they have formed the
Invincible Buddy Party.
In one such game, I was the hero and had started a journey...
Here, begin the journey of the 6 cute warrior.
A journey with 6 cute warriors.
Enemy gargoyle has appeared!
Gargoyle attacks!!
Gargoyle has split itself.
Everyone is probably familiar with
the RPG experience shown so far.
Tomochiro,
the Hero
But what's in front of me is...
I've actually been summoned into a real RPG world.
This isn't a game at all.
I wondered, "Why me?"
Alice!
Frey!
It was all for the sake of doing something only I could do.
We can't lose. We have the power
of Tomohiro-sama with us.
What's that?
By my command, magic within me, infuse
thyself into my blade!
Welcome to the World of Polygamy!
This is a tale that precedes the time of this realm.
A tale from a month ago.
We swear before God.
We offer ourselves as Tomohiro-sama's brides.
We swear that we will live together, sharing our
happiness and sadness, protecting one another.
My name is Alice Erzan.
My name is Frey Ringitt.
Alice... Frey...
My name is Tomohiro Kutsuki.
Until recently, I was just a feudal history
otaku with no luck with the ladies.
That is, until I was enveloped by an eerie white light...
And summoned from my world to this one,
a world called Euniphonia.
And now I'm here... with two beautiful women...
Tomohiro Kutsuki-sama?
Y-Yes?
Will you take us as your wives, swearing to live
with us and overcome all hardships together?
I... I swear it!
What an unexpected development!
You two are so beautiful...
Are you really okay doing this with a guy like me?
E-Even though I'm your wife,
don't stare too much. Idiot!
S-sorry.
Geez, have some confidence in yourself. You're the
hero we've summoned from another world!
That's right. Your semen will significantly
boost our magical powers.
Please, Tomohiro-sama. Shoot all of
your cum inside our bodies.
We will do anything to make that happen.
Alice... Frey!
That's right! My semen has the ability
to increase people's magic levels.
This is all for the sake of taking back the kingdom of
Euphonia from the Heavenly Four and protecting it.
A-Alice...
Tomohiro-sama, I'm sorry for being so dirty.
I just ready like your dick.
And how do I put it... I just can't resist
the strong smell coming from it!
Princess, in the legends, they say the hero's
dick is coated in a strong aphrodisiac.
A-Aphrodisiac?
Well then, I'll help you out.
Frey, you too?
You two... are just amazing!
The aphrodisiac feels stronger, now that his
pre-cum and sweat are mixing together.
Come on, shoot it out! Spray your cum
all over us! Holding back is futile!
For our first night together, this is rather intense!
The source of our power, your semen, is stored in these balls.
It feels good. It feels really good!
That makes me happy! I'll do my best!
We'll become wives you can be proud of!
I'm gonna cum!
His meat stick is twitching.
Princess, quick! Take it all in!
Sorry, I'll be going first, Frey.
Tomohiro-sama! Give us that love juice!
Shoot it out!
Cum... cum!
It's so hot!
So, this is the power of his semen?
Just by having his semen touch me,
my body is getting hot!
It's hot...
It's so hot! My lower half is...
What is this sensation?
I want it... I want it inside!
Inside! Stick it inside!
It's so big!
If it's only this size, I can bear with it.
I'm sorry, Frey! I just can't stop!
I'm your wife! Just stick it in as far as you want!
I never knew doing it for the first time would feel so good...
Frey, does it hurt?
No, the semen from his meat stick is
being absorbed by my pussy, so...
It's gonna explode!
Wow... so intense!
Don't worry, Princess! It'll quickly...
Tomohiro, cum! Hurry up and cum!
I'm going crazy!
I'm gonna cum!
That's right! Cum!
If you don't, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Your semen is pumping into my womb!
Frey?
Don't look at me!
It's coming in! With my womb filled
with his power... I'm cumming!
To-Tomohiro, I'm fine.
Please tend to the Princess...
To-Tomohiro-sama!
A-Alice...
This is my first time.
I'm offering it to you.
Tomohiro-sama!
Tomohiro-sama's dick is going
deeper and deeper inside.
Deep inside the pussy of one of his wives!
Tomohiro-sama!
Alice!
I'm sorry for letting out such a lewd voice!
Tomohiro-sama! Sorry! I'm sorry!
Alice, your insides feel amazing!
I wanna go in deeper!
T-Tomohiro, be more gentle!
It's fine, Frey.
Every time his dick moves, magic is
being pumped into me.
I feel it reaching to my core!
It feels too good, I'm gonna cum!
I can feel your dick bulging inside me!
You're going to cum, right?
It's fine. Cum whenever you want
and as much as you want!
Princess!
F-Frey?
I'll help you out.
Come on, Tomohiro. Cum inside her.
Cum all over her!
Tomohiro-sama's dick is... it's...
My pussy's getting so wet, I can't get enough!
Alice... Alice!
It's coming out!!
Tomohiro-sama! My body won't stop throbbing.
Your semen just keeps coming and coming!
I just keep cumming. I can't stop! It feels so good!
That's right. Give all of your
cum to the Princess!
Cum! Cum!
It's coming out!!
I'm so happy that I can take in all of his semen.
– Alice!
– T-Tomohiro!
– Tomohiro-sama!
I love you!
And so, I became their husband and ultimately, the
hero who would save this world with semen.
Take this!
Alice and co. have taken a huge blow.
It seems that she can change her body's structure with magic.
Eh?? What are we going to do?
Damn it!
Frey and I have the magic we've
acquired from Tomohiro-sama.
We'll use that..
Alice, Frey...
Can you increase the magic in your weapons?
If you release the magic stored in your bodies
through to your weapons all at once, then...
Your attack power will drastically increase!
Understood. There aren't any other options.
Everyone else, back them up.
Right!
Heaven and Earth, all the divine spirits,
please give us your strength!
End of the line!
I won't let you! Oh wind, blow it away!
Lightning, rip it apart!
Meddling pests!
Now!
Magic, gather at my sword's tip!
And cast out the darkness!
What!?
We did it!
B-By mere humans...
Impossible! I've been...
This is all because of Tomo-kun's semen.
Alright!
Lord Hero...
Alice, what's wrong?
W-W-What's this!?
That way Open Air Bath
Reserved By: Party of Alice
This is heaven!
After beating one of the Heavenly Four, Nemone,
the gargoyles ran away.
I wonder if this area will finally become peaceful again.
All's well that ends well.
Yeah, yeah!
It's not all well!
She's right. Nothing has been solved.
Alice-sama?
Isn't it a good thing your boobs have gotten bigger?
I wish you could share some of that with me.
If that was possible, I would've done it already!
I-I'm embarrassed to think what would happen if I
showed Tomohiro-sama this dirty chest of mine...
Rachel, what do you think caused, this?
I think something similar happened to the Heavenly Four.
There was probably too much magic involved and
the leftover magic remained in your bodies.
For them, their muscles were enhanced, but...
For you two, it looks like your boobs got enhanced.
Th-Their boobs were...
But... you know...
Isn't this a good thing?
It would've been worse if your
stomach or face got bigger.
Bounce, bounce!
Th-that's true...
Besides...
Tomo is a boob lover...
So shouldn't you be happy about this?
– Wa-wait!
Stop! Don't rub them! No! Stop!
Huh? What's this? Your nipples are getting
hard. Are you getting off on this?
No, I'm not! Stop lying!
So when they get this big,
they become more sensitive, huh?
Tatiya, stop!
Stop doing this! We're both girls!
Stop rubbing them!
What are they doing over there?
Really?
Is there really a way to turn them back to normal?
Tell us, Rachel!
For that, you'll need the help of your husband.
Tomohiro-sama?
So, truth is...
We have to do that?
Yes.
Actually, while we're at it, how about we all do it together?
Together?
Huh? What's going on?
We've decided to borrow the men's bath today.
Hey, there.
Please, my love.
Do you want to be cut?
I'm so excited.
Tomohiro-san, please stay still.
It'll be over soon.
Eh? W-wait!
You're me? And you're me?
Wow, you really split Tomohiro into 3!
Looks like the clone magic worked.
C-Clone magic?
Yes!
It might be strange to share sight and other sensations
across the 3 of you, but you'll get used to it in no time!
Okay, now Tomohiro-san, come this way.
H-Hey!
You're over here.
You're going to be our husband for today!
W-Wait, this is...
You're a clone, so this doesn't count as cheating, right?
Ch-cheating?
Forget it. Just do as you're told.
Didn't you know? Southern girls are a lot
more aggressive than you'd think.
Wow. Even though he's a clone,
this part of him feels like the real thing!
Real one
Um... I still don't really get what's going on...
So... in order to get our normal breasts back, seems
like we have to do a lot of perverted stuff.
I have no pleasure in sh-showing you this lewd sight, but
I've no choice. I'll be borrowing your power, Tomohiro!
But what about the clones?
After today's battle, you understood that your semen
greatly amplifies Freya and Alice's powers, right?
Y-Yeah...
Considering that we're going to continue fightnig the Heavenly
Four, we'll need to raise our magic levels further.
Can we?
But doing this...
You say that, but you're already this hard. Idiot!
Wow. So this is a man's cock, huh?
Is this your first time seeing one?
It's everyone's first time.
So Tomohiro-kun, please make us feel good!
If it makes you happy, we'll do anything!
Are we doing okay? If we do it right, can we
make these lewd breasts smaller again?
P-Princess, if you keep rubbing against me like that,
my nipples are going to get hard. I'll get turned on!
Rub harder you two! Make sure you squeeze out every last drop!
Tomohiro-sama, my boobs are getting
real hot. Why is that?
M-Me too. The hotness is taking over,
it feels like it's gonna burst!
No! It's coming out!
Hot stuff is coming out!
Why is breast milk gushing out?
N-No! This is probably the excess magic!
This is too amazing. The breast milk
feels like lotion, it's so good!
I'm glad to see you're pleased!
My breast milk's coming out! If it
doesn't come out, they'll burst!
No!!
Me too! Any more of this and I... squeezing this perverted
dick with my huge tits, squirting out all its milk!
I'm gonna!
Okay then...
Yeah!
On your marks...
My insides are being torn open by Tomohiro-san's dick!
It's so big! Your dick is just so damn big!
Oh wow! A girl's pussy can spread open this wide?
S-Sorry that I'm... taking him all for myself.
No, not there!!
Rachel, your pussy is gripping me so tight!
I can feel it, I'm really feeling it! I can feel
your stiff dick stirring up my insides...
Your dick is just amazing! It feels like
my pussy's going to melt!
Even though it's just rubbing against my womb's
entrace, I can feel the magic flowing into me!
It's going to pour in!
This way, we can all do it together.
My pussy is dripping wet,
it's making really lewd noises!
I can feel the tip of your dick
twitching and getting bigger!
Come on, thrust it in harder!
You're not just kissing my mouth,
your dick is kissing my insides too!
My sensitive nipples are rubbing against yours.
No! I can't hold back!
Don't be embarrassed you two. Just let it all out!
Y-Yes!
It's just gushing out and covering our bodies!
It feels so good, my mind's going blank!
P-Princess... please, please don't
look at my unseemly figure.
My breast milk is being squeezed out!
Frey, your pussy is really hot and wet!
Don't say that!
N-No, my body is... don't put
your fingers in! Don't stir it up like that!
Tomohiro-sama, your dick is twitching and
it's going wild in my pussy!
I'm going to cum soon, you two!
Yes! Cum, please do! I want it all!
I want the stuff that squirts out!
Please inject all of your dick juice into our pussies!
Cum inside, just shoot it in!
N-No! There's so much coming out!
There's so much magic pumping in!
Both my boobs and pussy feel divine,
I'm starting to lose it!
No, no more! There's so much
hot stuff inside... I just can't!
Rachel, Tatiya, I'm going to cum!
N-No!
Frey!
Tomohiro-sama, let's all... together now!
Yeah!
Everyone, let's go!
Yeah!!
T-Tomohiro-sama!!
No!!
– No!!
It's squirting so much!
Women's bath
This is a good bath!
Really, humans are such repulsive creatures.
Well, I guess it's about time I leave.
Thank goodness! Our breasts are back to normal.
Now we can, once again, fight unrestrained!
But I feel like this is kind of a waste...
I'll cut it off!
W-Where?
Let's calm down!
How splendid!
The magic is overflowing!
It's hot, so hot!
So this is semen and its power?
Having my semen praised so much
makes me feel kinda embarrassed.
W-Wait, this presence...
We're surrounded by gargoyles!
Crap, there were still some that survived?
Or maybe... a new enemy?
Alice, Frey?
You need not worry, Tomohiro-sama!
We'll protect you!
You're an important husband to all of us!
Okay everyone, let's go!
Translator: Hikarucon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4real
So... what's going to happen to us?
Well it'd be a waste to change you back.
Yep, yep.
Alice and co. have gained
new allies and powers!!!!!
End