Deputy!
Yes?
Mt. Baekdu?
Or River Han?
Mt. Baekdu...
How cruel!
Did you do what I asked?
Sure. Upon your order,
we've been working...
Cut to the chase!
Okay.
How embarrassing!
Executive Producer :
Park Min-ho, Choi Moon-soo
Concept & Character Designer:
Lee In-ho
Storyboard: Oh Yoo-nam
Produced by: Kim ll-bae, Oh Yoo-nam
Photography: Park Ji-won
Directed by: Kim ll-bae
Tarzan
Get some sleep.
Nah, I need to read this
for the medical seminar.
Captain
we've got a plane tailing us.
Because we have Baron
and his family on board.
Being wealthy doesn't necessarily
mean happiness.
I wish I owned a plane
as nice as this one.
Show me your ass.
Okay.
It's ready.
- Go ahead
- Not you!
The future of our country
is on his shoulders.
This is the sign of a successor!
My baby!
Today in the jungles...
It's that George again!
Stop it!
Be a good girl!
- Stop it!
- Stay still!
George, leave her alone.
She doesn't like you.
Look who's talking, orphan!
What?!
Did you just called me an orphan?!
Well, can you untie me?
Hey, Tarzan.
What's wrong?
Mom, am I your son?
What are you talking about?
Let me show you.
See?
We're the same,
aren't we?
George told me that
you'd found me in the bushes.
Ignore what he said.
You're my cute baby.
You think we can find it?
You never know what could happen
in the jungles.
Keep your eyes on the road!
We're in the jungles.
Sure. We're professionals.
Take your time.
Yeah, I'll get back to you
as soon as we find it.
I know you won't.
I will tell him that
we found the dead body.
You naughty boy!
Drive carefully!
What do you expect?
Can we find him?
Definitely.
We'll find him, father.
I'm sure we will.
Thanks.
He must be good-looking.
Jim...
You think he'll fall for this?
I'm sorry,
but you have to die, Jim.
Jim?
Is that my name?
That's right.
Your farther is my brother.
You'd be declared missing,
so I couldn't be the heir.
You have to die for me.
This is poisoned.
Starve him and give it to him.
Yes, sir!
Yeah, he's safe.
Thanks.
Don't be scared.
I'm on your side.
They'll sleep throughout
the night.
Why?
Baron Toton is my sponsor.
Huge!
You're making me horny!
You're like a real snake!
We should hide somewhere
until Baron gets here.
I'm afraid you can't.
I knew you'd betray me.
You could've done better.
We didn't drink what you gave us.
You scum!
We'll have to tie you up.
Go get him!
Don't let him get away!
Let's split up!
I blew it!
You must be Jim.
Jim...
Jim, you're all grown-up now.
She must've raised Jim.
Sir!
Thank God I'm a doctor.
Jim, don't worry about her.
I'm not Jim.
I'm Tarzan!
I don't care.
I'm just happy to be with you.
I'll always be with you.
How do you feel?
You wouldn't know.
You're nothing but a toad.
Mom, I'm home!
You still think of me as your mom?!
You're my only mom!
Oh, boy!
Was I too strong?
- Hey.
- Yes?
This set looks familiar.
- Due to the tight budget...
- Shut up!
Mt. Baekdu or River Han?
Choose one!
Mt. Baekdu...
Let's get it started.
It's fun torturing a beauty
passing off as a guy.
We need stronger sex power.
I'll give it some thought.
What's with the super jellicon
that's been developed?
It's being produced.
Going as planned.
008, what are you doing?
The world needs you.
Don't give me that.
Everybody can see you.
You're making me hornier.
I think she's cut out for the job.
If so,
there's no need to wait.
Why is the lab separated
from the HQ?
To monitor the whole world.
After that picture,
we lost touch of 0069.
It looks like a hole.
0069 gathered this information,
risking his life.
The name, Gold Chinga
and those pictures.
So cute!
It's not just a cat.
It's their HQ.
Why don't you launch
an investigation?
Since there was no evidence...
...we had 0069 undercover
to avoid international conflicts.
That is called Golden Vibe.
We think it has a special function.
What special function?
What?
That's not funny at all.
Find out about the function
that Golden Vibe does.
Just information?
That's our mission.
Don't be too stiff.
008!
What?
Stop it.
That's enough.
I heard it's better than Viagra.
It's for my wife.
What a loving hubby!
Contact Pupa there.
Video shop?
008.
You can enjoy yourself there.
I'd prefer a real man, though.
It's believed to be a front
for their lab.
Your panties show!
Do I have to fly a fighter
to go to a video shop?
What a perfect cryptogram!
Meet me in Rose Room.
The password is 69.
This should do.
Hi there.
Rose Room.
What movies...
"She's wet"
"Sex Report"
"Power of Viagra"
"I Think I'm Coming"
"Happiness in the wet land"
and "Pink Riders"!
You don't have to name them.
Pick anything from the shelves.
He didn't know I was a girl.
6!
9!
What happened?
You're Pupa, right?
Yeah, you must be.
The director had this on, too.
Wow, this is unbelievable.
Using the neurons,
it stimulates the cerebrum.
It also amplifies the frequency
in the cognitive network.
What the hell does that mean?
It controls human beings
as ecstasy does.
Is that why it attacked me?
Well, it's good for guys.
It keeps the penis hard,
enabling guys to come repeatedly.
It's better than Viagra.
Everybody's crazy about it.
Rumor has it that
all the public officials have it.
It's not just a rumor.
Shame on men,
falling for something like this.
This amplifying data.
Influences cognitive control.
The stronger the date is,
the powerful this thing becomes.
Please, speak English.
What Gold Chinga wants is
your sex power.
Golden Vibe controls women.
Chinga wants the data.
He's controlling the director
to involve you into this thing.
You're saying I'm a sex machine?
Look!
At the Presidential summit,
the unbelievable is happening.
We're in favor of Chinga.
The people of our nation
support Chinga a great deal.
They passed the Bill of Chinga.
Love live, Chinga!
Also...
What's that?
Once you reach ecstasy,
Golden Vive takes over.
That's how the brain
and their system is hooked up.
That's your chance.
You have to get into their system
and destroy it.
If you make it,
It'll be nothing but a dildo.
How do I do that?
This amplifies ecstasy.
Into the widened tunnel,
you've got to infuse your senses.
Then?
Let your body do the job.
What do you mean?
Making this gesture is enough.
It isn't that easy, though.
Once you get into the system
using your senses...
Gee, you put your fingers
way too deep in your throat.
Fill me in with your energy
before I go.
Why don't I...?
Make it back alive.
Do me a favor.
What?
- It's.
- What?
They're controlling you.
I don't want to fight you,
but I guess I'll have to.
We finally got you.
No, I came on my own free will.
Everybody was talking about it,
and I wanted to see it myself.
If you become my slave,
you'll know how it feels.
With her power,
I'll rule the world soon!
Feel it, 008!
Let your body shake!
This is...
No, it's not enough yet.
Now I understand
what that researcher said.
This can't stop me!
I'm the best!
Gosh!
Our system's been hacked!
It's 008's senses!
We've got a problem!
What?!
She's going to the main computer!
What's going on?!
Where am I?
Oh, you've come to.
You did a great job,
destroying the system.
Oh, you've come to.
I got you out of there.
Don't worry about a thing.
I just did what I was told.
Congratulations, anyway.
It's better than I expected.
I suppose your sex power is
quite strong.
Whatever.
My mission is over, right?
You can't run this time.
Come here!
Wait, wait!
Do you copy, 008?
I've got a mission for you.
Do you read me?!
Cyber Love
Love is like playing games,
and I'm not good at it.
Don't ask me whom I liked most
among all the girls I dated...
...because I did my best
for every single girl.
They say that's why I'm not good
at playing games.
Only if I could go back
to the day we met...
...I'd console your loneliness
with my tears.
Only if I could go back...
Hamburger, please.
Yes!
Mind if I sit here?
Sure, go ahead.
What do I look like?
You're gorgeous.
What's wrong?
I'm so happy.
Nobody said that before!
Really?
Please, help me.
Sorry. I've got to run.
Though she's beautiful,
I don't' feel right about her.
You're the only one
who can help me!
Please!
I don't know what You're saying.
Maybe you should see a doctor.
Stop crying.
Let's get out of here.
I'm an alien.
Sorry, but I've got to go.
Our race is dying out.
The sun will disappear
500 years from now...
...and we've got nowhere to go.
Then, the God of the universe will
give us a chance.
If we pass his test,
he'll give us a new planet.
It's bizarre.
- What kind of God is he?
- We don't know.
You trust this mysterious God?
When I came to senses,
I was here.
I'm going insane.
Let me take you to our spaceship.
You can play a game for me there.
It's the test that he gave us.
You should talk to an expert
like a shrink.
That's our spaceship.
Isn't that the game center?
It's a spaceship!
What a spaceship!
It looks like a game room.
I've never seen this one before.
Who makes it?
It's the test machine.
I see.
It's free, right?
Of course, it's free.
I love you.
How many girls have you
said that to?
You're the only one.
What are these dots for?
What's she upset about?
Well, the horoscope says
I'll find love this month.
Hamburger, please.
Mind if I sit here?
Sure, go ahead.
What do I look like?
Like a cute bunny.
I knew you'd say that!
In fact, I'm an alien.
Sorry, but I've got to go.
What a nutcase!
Sung-ki!
Did you find the person
you were looking for?
No.
Where do you live?
It's chilly tonight.
You want to go to my place?
No, sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
Can I?
That's how we moved in together.
She said that
her planet was facing extinction.
Following the order of the God...
...she had to find a man who
would look at her as a human...
...and marry him
to keep her race from dying out.
But she couldn't do anything
with the bunny mask on.
It wasn't what I expected.
She'd go out everyday
looking for the right guy...
...and come home
looking pitiful and depressed.
And I was getting used to
waiting for her to come home.
Where is she?
I was worried about you.
Sorry.
What if I can't find him?
Don't say that.
you'll find the man.
What if I don't?
The God of the universe said
there was one, right?
Let's go to the theme park.
You haven't been there, right?
Just for a change.
Aren't you hot?
Just a second.
Excuse me?
- You didn't get your change.
- Thanks.
She's beautiful.
What did you just say?
I said she's beautiful.
They had a wedding
at a beautiful church.
We never miss anybody
that we see all the time.
But when that person is gone...
...we realize how attached
you were to that person.
When you realize loneliness,
It's too late.
If this were a game...
...I could reset the machine
and start all over.
Love is like playing games,
and I'm not good at it.
Don't ask me whom I liked the most
among all the girls I dated...
...because I did my best
for every single girl.
They say that's why I'm not good
at playing games.
If I could only go back
to the day we met...
I don't care if this is a game.
I love Bunny!
Is it possible for us to have sex?
The God of the universe said
physical intercourse was ok...
...as long as
We're one by heart.
Bunny and I will be living
on a new planet.
I don't know what it'll be like,
but I trust the God of the universe.
At this very moment,
I'm happy beyond words.
- Doctor?
- Yes?
Mt. Baekdu or River Han?
River Han!