Damn, that guy really likes his adult books.
'Borrow them and learn a few things?'
This is the same one...
"When Domineering Fails"
"The days of anguish when you're 25 and can't be dominant are over."
I should use it before I send it back.
Let's see, I think it was on page nine or so...
I'd better finish while I can.
Hey! Let's go play!
Uh huh...
Hey...
I caught ya.
Hey, let's go play outside.
You know, there's a place called Belgium in France...
I know it.
I thought I'd hang around there for a bit.
Then you're going to leave Japan?
No, my rightful place is here.
With everyone.
I see.
Come with me.
Huh?
I'd be so bored otherwise.
I can't do that.
Why?
Is it that weird?
I never would've brought it up otherwise.
Ah, well...
Maybe it was too much to ask.
As things stand, if you told me that you weren't interested in me at all...
I may just kill you.
Did she really mean that?
In broad daylight?
Kuuya!
Tomo-nee, get out of here.
Run!
I'm not afraid of him.
Let your sister protect you.
What are you saying, Tomo-nee?
Trans...
...form!
Mega... Jiga...?
You're awake.
Thank goodness.
Where is this?
Tomo-nee's room.
Hey, my wound's gone.
I healed it.
It's one of my powers after I change.
Huh, I never figured you for much of a fighter.
I actually feel great.
What are you doing?
Sorry!
Um... Take your hand off.
My god, she's cute...
Which hand?
Well, your...
Uhm... The one that's on my breast.
Weird... I'm getting really turned on.
I might just lose it!
S-Sorry...
That I didn't get there sooner to protect you.
If you really want to with me, then, go ahead.
Tomo-nee.
But I'm sure you don't want to, with the way I am.
Tomo-nee, what's wrong?
Let's start with... kissing.
Is this alright?
Isn't there anything weird about my body?
Can I ask you... to...
...be gentle...
I will.
Relax yourself.
Looks dirty.
Don't look!
It's embarassing.
Here goes.
Will you be alright if you're that sensitive?
It only gets more intense from here.
And I'm being serious.
It's so tight.
It feels really good... inside you.
I'm moving.
It hurts, huh?
Try to keep going.
I'm trying!
I can't stop myself.
No, don't move like that!
I'm feeling a rush, Tomo-nee.
You're feeling something too, aren't you?
It's coming!
I'm...!
Why I am I...?
It's like you're feeling it the more we do this.
No, it's not...
Here.
Tomo-nee.
Tomo-nee...
Tomo-nee!
Meat! Beer! Meat! Beer!
Foundation of the meal!
This yakisoba isn't fried enough!
45 points.
This salad tastes quite pleasant.
Kuuya can cook so well...
I'm really proud!
What's wrong?
Hey, look at the TV!
This is our part!
Here's a look at the various sights this beach has to offer.
And here's a cute little girl playing in the sand.
Hinano nee-san...
Kuuya?
Don't be so formal.
Come in.
Oh, you need not worry.
I am not that upset anymore.
Here, drink up.
Don't worry about your manners.
Thank you.
My apologies.
Perhaps it was a bit too hot.
Hand me the tea.
Leave.
Take that!
Now we don't have any distractions.
This is good.
Is it?
That's good to hear.
We have one hectic family, don't we?
Well then...
Since you must find it in your heart to choose someone...
Is there someone here that you like?
Nee-san, are you alright?
Sorry, may I ask you to bring me some cold water?
Wait here.
She's still hurting a lot after all.
Welcome home.
Bring a mint ice cream to my room.
Finished the order.
Looks good...
That white furball...
Well, who cares about that lowly creature.
I have to go.
Thank you.
W-What's wrong?
No wait, onee-sama, it wasn't me!
Get out of my sight!
Much better.
You're a good man, Kuuya.
Yes! I'm very pleased to have helped the family head.
Speaking of which...
I found all kinds of these books scattered in your room.
You're not in trouble.
I expect men of your age to like these books.
Or at least Serori tells me...
But some of these things are quite amazing.
To touch someone here...
I can't grasp the concept.
What makes this feel so good?
Just what are you planning with these books?
Wha -- Now what are you doing!?
Kuuya, could you possibly help me?
By help, you mean...
Touch you?
Right.
Well, I guess no one can get upset with me now.
What I do!?
No...
It's just that I imagined it differently from what you did.
Well, I suppose it would be.
I didn't tell you to stop!
Keep going!
All right...
That tickles a bit.
Well? How's it feel?
What is this?
I can't explain this.
What's happening?
Here, try this.
What are you doing?
Huh... How strange.
I never noticed her sweet smell.
Nee-san, you're being sensitive.
This is just so weird.
My body is trembling...
This is so odd...
I'm the leader of the Hiiragi family, but I'm getting so worked up just being touched.
Hinano nee-san's so pretty...
Hinano nee-san.
H-Hey!
No underwear?
Who gave you permission to do that?
Hey! Stop doing that --
Nee-san...
Well...
Are you too ill?
Can you have sex like this?
I believe that I can...
I've never really done it, so I don't know.
And besides, why are you asking me such a thing?
Sorry, you're just such a cute -- beautiful woman.
I can't really help it.
You're such a helpless guy.
But, since it's you, I'm actually quite happy.
Nee-san...
You're already that big?
Actually, that's a little impressive.
Phew, I thought it was going to force itself out.
Please take care of me.
Then let's get started, nee-san.
First...
Kissing?
All right, do it.
Hinano nee-san, stick out your tongue.
Like this?
She smells so sweet.
It's pretty embarassing, to be in this position.
Nee-san...
What's taking you?
Nee-san, you have to relax.
It's be easier that way.
Even like this, I can't really do that.
Nee-san, does anything hurt?
Are you alright?
And who do you think you're talking to!?
I'm Hinano... of the Hiiragi family.
I don't need any of your sympathies!
Now get on with it!
Hm, all right.
Nee-san, it might get stuck, or not go in at all, but...
Here I go, though it might hurt.
I don't mind, do it!
Nee-san, are you alright?
Don't!
Don't worry about me!
I'm doing just fine with this!
No one has the right to tell me I can't do things like this!
Now get moving already!
This is to make me a complete woman, so I at least want to finish this.
Hinano nee-san...
Kuuya!
What is it, Hinano nee-san?
Nee-san... Is it getting better?
Kuuya! Kuuya!
Nee-san!
Kuuya, it's so hot.
Hinano nee-san...
What's this thing?
How relaxing.
How are you, Tomoe?
Is there anything that you'd like to talk about with me?
Yeah, my breasts got bigger again.
*twitch*
But, I think they're actually a bit too big.
Maybe it'd be better if they were a little smaller.
*twitch*
Hey Hinano nee-san, since Tomoe-nee always a hard time, shouldn't we help her out?
Huh? Right here in the bath?
You're always so darn big, Tomoe...
To the point where I'm really jealous.
Is this what they do when they say they tease her?
Does it hurt?
Hey, since you're trembling so much, does it really feel that good, Tomoe nee-san?
Her breasts got hard.
They're really getting hard.
Nee-san, please stop.
We could, but this is to make things all better.
I remember someone saying: "My breasts are getting too big."
For goodness sake, don't stop!
Huh? Thanks.
Please, Hinano nee-san...
Don't suck on them!
You were very cute, Tomoe...
Nee-san...
All right, now let's wash your back, shall we?
OK.
Do they always do things like that?
Wait, where did this...?
You have a bulge in your pants.
Shh!
Hey, why don't you want to be with me?
It isn't really fair...
And I even said that I love you and everything.
I'm suffocating. I can't breathe.
Just stay there a while. I'll let you go in a minute.
This is something I have to hold on to.
Just for a while.
Pissed-Off Sister Punch!
I know that Serori onee-chan is expressing her affection for you wholeheartedly...
But the way she does it is just scary.
It's just that Kuuya looks at Kaname-nee with such loving eyes.
Is there really no room for me?
And I thought my heart would finally be happy...
Kuuya.
The Hiiragi family has adopted a son.
His name is Kuuya.
I thought I liked that name.
That was when Hinano nee-san was very ill.
So I had to become the most responsible sister.
However...
Onee-chan!
Why was it that he always smiled...
Well, it was probably because he was so kind.
I waited one night until Kuuya was asleep, and I went to kiss him.
It was a woman's secret.
Right... That would mean I loved Kuuya.
At the time, I didn't want Kuuya to leave me.
And then he left to live in another relative's house.
And I was going to tell him at the next festival...
My dear mother died.
Kuuya left.
My love broke up with me.
And even my cute dog died.
Everything precious to me disappeared.
It was absolutely unfair!
I didn't want to be hurt anymore.
My legal career started.
And the more people I saw, the more I hated them.
With all the injustice that I saw, I decided that no one deserves forgiveness.
Even now, when Kuuya came back I thought I would be happy...
But the hate I bore against everyone didn't disappear.
And all the pain that I endured, was mostly caused by Kuuya.
Kuuya!
What are you doing? Stop at once!
Wait...
I can't move!?
I see...
You drugged the wine.
Yeah.
This is a drug for Kuuya to make people go numb.
Kaname-nee always drinks a lot of wine after coming back from work.
You little shit!
You did the same thing to me, didn't you?
Like I care.
Wait, Kuuya!
This looks really familiar.
Release me from these right now.
If you do, I might not press any heavy charges.
Now release me!
Obey my orders.
You're not going to listen to your sister?
I'm... I'm just getting back at you!
I see. That's too bad.
I liked you as a little brother.
But, to be such a bastard...
I have no sympathies for you!
You've really reached rock bottom.
I love you regardless.
So just let me do this for you.
If I make you feel good, you won't say a thing.
Make me feel good?
No chance in hell.
And you should be more worried about yourself.
All you have to do is release me.
I know that.
Hey!
Hey, is that sweat I'm tasting?
Not a chance!
Are you the degenerate type?
Huh? Did I just hear a shriek of excitement?
Don't get cute! How dare you touch me!
That's not what these are saying.
Nee-sama...
No, leave it alone.
Okay, that's enough.
I apologize for what I did that night.
I'm sorry!
Nee-sama, does it hurt?
Let me out of these, so I can hold you.
Nee-sama, I'm sorry.
I didn't know what I was doing.
I can't hate you Kuuya.
You're such a cute little brother.
Nee-sama, I...
I want you to suck on this.
Don't put me on your level!
But before that, here, put this on.
Looks good on you, nee-sama.
Get it deeper in your throat.
What's wrong, nee-sama?
I'm not finished yet.
You damn masochist...
Wait!
How can you act like this?
I'll never forgive you!
Your asshole looks so frail.
Shut the hell up!
Then, shall I see for myself?
Stop it, you freak!
If you touch that, I'll kill you!
S-Stop it!
I've been waiting for this, so it'll be better to not use a condom.
No...
I'm coming!
Hm, you sure come quickly.
You have a lot of pride, so I'm going to return the favor with interest.
Wait, don't do it from underneath!
Sorry, I already put it in.
Come on, move it.
It's feels great inside you, nee-sama.
Please, don't move so violently.
Please, stop.
Leave me be!
A change in attitude?
No can do.
I'm in charge now, so shut up.
This isn't happening!
I... I... I can't take it!
To find out it was this painful...
I had no idea!
After you made me do it with my mouth, I thought you'd gladly stop.
Nee-sama, that's the real you.
The real you isn't so cold.
You're simply a regular girl.
You just needed a little help.
I feel fantastic after getting better.
From now on, Kuuya and I will create a beautiful and graceful family.
One that no one can match. Won't it?
I took all the money I could and went for it.
I had to bet Kuuya after all my gambling in Vegas, but...
If I lose here, then Kuuya will just get away from me.
But, a life like this is fun too, right?
I love Kuuya.
As a brother.
And as a man as well.
My fight with the Claw hasn't ended...
I'll endure it.
To protect my precious family.
To protect my beloved Kuuya...
From here on out, me and Kuuya are just starting things...
We haven't reached an ideal relationship yet, I think.
He can do better, right?
After all, Kuuya is my dorky servant...
And one and only little brother.
Kuuya is attending the same campus as I am.
In exchange, I've asked the other sisters let me have him all to myself during that time.
Thank you, Kuuya.
From now on, we'll be together forever.
From now on, I will be splitting the responsibilities of the Hiiragi family with Kuuya.
We've now put aside our egos.
I hope to protect him as both a sister and a woman would.
Whenever I'm on TV, I always remember Kuuya's face.
And it always gives me a sense of peace.