Morning, Peron.
Morning, everyone.
Wait here for a second.
All right, I have to go out.
Good morning, Hinano nee-san.
You're up early as usual, Tomoe.
Since you're up this early, for your reward...
You get a hard candy!
Thank you very much!
The woman with the beautiful voice, singing while she prepares everyone's meal...
Everyone's mother -- Tomo-nee.
Tomo-nee, your singing's really pretty.
Is it?
Kuuya, why don't I help you?
You shouldn't, Umi.
*wither*
Hey dork.
Make some yakisoba for breakfast.
Meat and beer are the foundations of any meal.
Serori nee-nee, and Takane Aneki too -- don't complain.
Tomo-nee made this with everyone in mind!
That was blunt.
That's now how you're supposed to answer.
I just leveled up.
Damn this sucks.
Oh, Kuuya.
If you stay here, you'll fry.
Nee-nee.
Here, come on, come on.
Check this place out!
It's cool in here!
Gah, another person's here now.
Come on in.
We all had the same idea.
Umi onee-chan, Tomo-nee.
Hey there, dork...
Isn't it on hot days like this when you should be making yourself useful?
Even if you say that, I'm done for the day.
Please, just let me stay here.
You sound just like Hinano nee-san. Shouldn't you just go to her room?
Well, I'd just be bothering her.
And you think you aren't bothering me!?
Yup.
Because you're the younger sister.
Because of your pigtails.
I don't even get the last reason!
Speaking of which, this room is pretty tasteless, don't you think?
It looks like a twelve-year-old girl's room.
Seriously, nothing but girls' manga and stuff.
No stuffed animals...
Damn you all...
Actually, it is a bit sad.
Your room's very comforting, Kaname-nee.
This soft bed has your smell in it.
It's a tender and comforting smell.
Nee-san...
Huh, but this bed makes it so easy.
Not only can you lay down here...
But fall asleep... too.
Looks like you fell asleep.
I heard from Kuuya that if you don't keep covered, you'll catch a cold, nee-san.
You always look so cute when you break down, nee-san.
You're an eyesore.
Get out of my sight.
The A/C shut down.
Crap, the breaker must've come undone.
Kuuya, get down there right now and fix it.
It's all right, Umi onee-chan.
I've got this.
Uh, please listen for an announcement.
Unfortunately, we've had a power failure...
You're kidding!
It had to happen now of all times...
So hot. I'm gonna die.
Aneki, your underwear's completely exposed.
Shut up, just don't look.
Agh! I can't take this!
Kuuya, come with me!
Huh? Me?
Hey! Where are you going?
Shut it!
Sumo!
Volcano!
Hot pot!
Sun!
I give...
What's with all the heat-related words!?
To make you suffer as much as possible.
Kaname nee-sama!
Are you alright? You aren't that hot?
I am called the "Icy Lawyer."
I can't have simple heat bother me.
This heat can't handle me.
Up!
"Icy" Lawyer...
Hey, wait!
The ice is going to melt and warp the floor, Kaname nee-sama!
Sometimes you really can't leave Kaname-nee to do anything.
Ah! That's cold!
Summer really calls for bathing in cold water.
We should have everyone do this.
*meow*
Let's get more comfortable.
In the house, it's always nice to bathe with others.
I want a good wash down myself.
Hey -- Don't touch that.
Nope! You're not getting away!
It's getting bigger.
Umi, wanna have some fun with 'lil Kuuya?
Play...?
You wouldn't do that would you? Umi onee-chan?
But Kuuya, you're getting awfully big here.
Really big.
This... Uh... Wait...
Hot!
That cat girl and four eyes...
Where did they go after ditching me?
I can't take it...
I should start making dinner soon.
What's wrong?
Savor more of the taste in your mouth.
If you don't make me scream, you'll get punished.
You're so cute, Kuuya.
Here, lick this.
Here.
Good!
Good, Kuuya!
Let it all out!
Give it to me!
You're still hard, Kuuya.
This feels good, doesn't it?
How do you like my breasts, Kuuya?
Nee-nee...
Don't spoil your appetite by snacking.
It's insulting to me.
What is?
Me, snacking?
You sure?
Gah! Why the hell do you just eat everything indescriminately!
Yakisoba is basically stir-fried wheat flour noodles, but is usually mixed with vegetables and Japanese Worcestershire sauce.
That's my yakisoba!
Come on, don't be so stingy.
Here, let's split it.
I don't want that now!
Kuuya! Go out and buy some yakisoba right now!
Huh? But I'm not finished cooking...
Listen, twerp!
Just how much of your disobedience do you think I'm going to let go?
The next time that happens, I'll beat you senseless!
You think I'll let you off with an excuse like that?
Hah! I hope that makes things clear.
Worm! Little bug!
I'm going out shopping.
Kuuya, let's go together.
Hey, Tomo-nee...
Don't you find Takane aneki to be a major drag on things?
Not especially.
Really?
Then what do you think about Serori nee-nee's snacking without any disregard for anything?
If you put it that way, don't you kind of feel sorry for her?
Serori nee-san and Takane both worry about you.
That's why they both let you go.
How do you figure that?
Don't be angry at them.
Hey Tomoe-chan!
We have some good prawns today!
It's really good with boiled salt water!
Oh my, welcome Tomoe-chan.
Here, doesn't this look good?
Come on and buy it!
Tomoe-chan! Wouldn't my favorite customer love to buy this meat from me?
Hey, good day, Tomoe-chan!
Make sure to take lots to your house.
Whelcome, Tomoe-chan!
Here wit' your 'lil brother?
All right! Take this tomato!
Eat it wit' your brother!
You're really popular around here, Tomo-nee.
Tomo-nee, is that what I think it is?
Yeah, it's here. A Claw!
Don't make any sudden moves.
Just stay back and support me for now.
OK.
Trans...
...form!
Tomo-nee... Tomo-nee.
Tomo-nee!
Is it safe to move her?
I'd better carry her anyway.
Heavy...
180 cm = ~5' 11"
For us Americans still behind in the world.
So this is what someone 180 cm weighs.
I... May not be able to make it.
She seems blissfully unaware at least.
When holding a princess in his arms,
the knight has to make it all the way.
And that goes for everyone...
My back's giving out.
Work is a pain in the ass.
I want a vacation...
My arms are shaking.
Damn sisters...
Almost there...
Kuuya, come on and sleep next to me.
I can't believe I made it!
My DNA's making me want to touch her!
Ugh... Where are you, you dork?
Yakisoba...
Thank you... for carrying me here.
Though I had a hell of time doing it.
Actually, I was partially concious when you were carrying me.
Sorry for faking it.
It's been a dream of mine.
Dream? You mean being carried like a princess?
Yeah... I must've been heavy.
You were.
Anyway...
Thank you.
Kuuya, I love you.
As a brother?
No, both ways.
I see.
Then, go on here.
Your chest got a lot broader.
Tomo-nee.
No, seeing Tomo-nee like this...
Tomo-nee, I'm really thirsty.
No, that's not what I mean.
I want a drink from your body.
Your body fluids.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Are you too embarrassed?
Y-Yeah.
Oh the pain! I can't go on!
My conscience is getting to me now.
Don't look at me like that.
Hurry! It hurts!
Hang on!
Tomo-nee...
All right, Tomo-nee. I'll get under you.
I can't do anything that bold!
Please help me!
This feels really weird...
No...
Sor -- Sorry... Sorry, I...
You climaxed, didn't you, Tomo-nee?
Tomo-nee, my face is all dripping wet now.
I don't want to do this anymore!
Tomo-nee! In front of you!
You're such a clumsy person...
There's a surprise.
They're sensitive.
She really has a smaller opening that I would have thought.
I can't.
I can't do it to her while she's unconscious.
Kuuya...
I'm sorry!
Go ahead...
You sure? I thought you'd be furious.
I love you, Kuuya...
And...
I want you to feel pleased.
J-Just leave it to me.
It's like it's alive.
I think, this should make you feel good.
Tomo-nee, try licking it.
It tastes weird.
Try sucking on it.
Good.
Sorry, Tomo-nee. I'm coming!
Tomo-nee, let me see your ass.
I've wanted to try you from behind at least once.
This position's so embarassing.
Here I go...
It still hurts, huh...?
Keep with it.
I'll try...
Make more of those sounds.
You sound like a slut.
Come on.
I want it louder.
Come on, come on!
One round isn't really enough.
No!
No, we already went through a weird position already.
All right then, Tomo-nee.
T-Then -- !
Only once more.
Wait, no!
Here goes...
Don't!
Tomo-nee, your breasts are trembling!
Don't look at those!
Maybe that's a good thing.
It shows you're enjoying this.
All your stuffed animals can watch.
They're all your friends, right?
No!
Come on, give them something good to hear!
Look, they're all watching!
D-Don't say that!
N-No...
I'm... What did I ever do?
I wonder if your ass would like something in it.
Not there!
Come on, in here.
It's going inside me!
Tomo-nee, sorry for all the teasing...
You were just too cute.
Don't worry.
You did good today.
I'll do the same tomorrow.
Don't overdo it though.
I'll be fine as long as you're right there with me.
Tomo-nee...
There, there...