Encoded by Seyrri @A-h-E
Credit to HEroAP for subs
Kaname nee-sama, wake up.
It's time.
I'm alreadies awake.
What do you mean "alreadies'?
Nee-sama! You're going to be late!
If you want me awake that badly, then you wake up.
Ugh, that makes no sense at all.
Oh, right...
Work.
What a pain...
I want a vacation.
All right, let's get going then.
Wait!
Kaname nee-sama!
P-please don't freeze in that position...
Awesome Hentai Encodes
HEroAP subs
Shoot, we're out of Kaname nee-sama's favorite coffee beans.
Kaname nee-sama's going to be pissed.
If it's Kaname-nee, this'll be fine.
The real stuff is something else.
Yes, hello?
You got the meeting time wrong so you can only do it in an hour?
Can we make it if we take the car?
Ah, we can't.
I heard there was an accident, so we'll be stuck in traffic.
I see, then we'll have to take the train then.
I didn't expect to take the train, but i guess we don't have a choice.
Kuuya, I'm going to sleep for a bit, so guard me from other people.
OK, how's this?
Off to sleep then.
So you don't mind if i see your sleeping face?
It doesn't matter that my younger brother can see it.
Younger brother...?
It's just, I love you more than that, Kaname nee-sama.
It looks like she's been really tiring herself out.
Something's really off... What's going on?
Serori nee-nee!
You can't eat that before dinner!
And it's supposed to be for everyone! Don't you dare eat it!
No matter what i say, you never do it.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Huh?
Don't interrupt me.
Kuuya, whenever Kaname-nee says something, you always do it.
The sister that i remember wasn't like how she is now.
I want the former version of her to come back.
Fine then.
Even back then you'd always end up with Kaname-nee.
Do you know something I don't?
My cake!!
I wanted Kuuya to eat that delicious cake, so I've slaved over it since yesterday!
My poor Kuuya!
I'll make another one for you!
She'd always put me to her chest.
Without our mother, my sister was a good substitute, and it'd always put a smile on my face, but...
I'm not a kid anymore.
Sorry, I have something to say to all of you.
I just want to declare something in front of you.
If things keep going like this, the same thing will happen as before.
I don't need Umi or any of you to dote over me.
It doesn't matter if you like me or not.
Live the way that you decide.
Just do whatever you feel like.
Do what we want...
A harsh onee-san.
For Kuuya's sake.
I can do that!
Do what we want...
Play everyday.
Share his feelings with me.
Love, love.
Do what we want...
Hold him affectionately.
A problem-free place.
Everyone will be happy and carefree.
Do what we want...
Use him any way that i want.
On my every whim.
All to myself.
All right, let's do it!
It's all for our sweet little brother.
We'll help him out.
Just leave it all to onee-san.
I'll do my best.
Be thankful that I'm doing it.
Thank you everyone.
What nice sisters I have.
Umi onee-chan, I'm going to do this.
I'm not sure what you want to accomplish by all this.
It's so that I won't have to do every single thing with all of you anymore.
Now I understand what you mean.
Then kissing's still fine, right?
Well, not really.
Then what about hugs?
That... too.
Then what about cuddling?
None of that, either.
*whiter*
What am i going to do?!
I can't even tough Kuuya now!
I've been a good girl!
I've done everything for him!
I'm heartbroken!
Umi, think about Kuuya's feelings for once -
Quiet, you!
This isn't the time for you to act conceited like you usually are.
You have some nerve to say that out loud.
W-what'll we do?
Hinano nee-san, there's such a violent mood in here now.
Wait now, you two!
You're out of line.
Don't you realize how immature you two look?
I suppose.
I let my tongue slip.
Very good.
Umi will just have to get used to not being around Kuuya.
Kaname, you did a very mature thing.
Here's some candy.
Thank you very much.
Umi onee-chan...
This is for me, so please don't fight.
I'm sorry, it's just that I can't fathom being away from you.
You're my cute little brother so...
Onee-chan!
Don't do that. You'll just encourage her to do the same things to you.
You're right, it's for the best.
We need to tell him about this.
Nee-sama, you mean to Dad, right?
Then does that mean...?
Yes.
When he finds out, he may very well take Kuuya away again.
So, what are we to do?
Well, I'm not letting this opportunity go to waste.
Tomoe nee-san, let me have this.
You could care less, right, nee-san?
W-What? Are you angry?
I'm going out!
I'm sure you know I'm concerned...
It doesn't matter to me wether you're here or not.
Just what are you thinking?
Onee-sama, why'd you get so cold all of a sudden?
I just thought I needed to act grown up.
How stubborn...
Think about the consequences before you act.
It's just that I love you.
He doesn't give up...
Looks like you're not going to give up no matter what I say...
I'm racking my brain trying to settle this.
Hey, don't sell me short.
Get out of here.
Looks like trying to talk to her would be useless now.
Kuuya...
What's she doing?
All she's been doing is calling out Kuuya's name.
Kuuya...Kuuya..
She looks awful...
What about just touching her?
I just think she needs to feel you.
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
Kuuya.
Yeah, it's me.
Kuuya! It's the real Kuuya!
Kuuya!
Onee-chan!
Those two... Was that really all they had to do?
Hey look, Kuuya's already getting excite.
Great isn't it? I knew he was getting a hard-on.
Get yourself ready...
Head first into everything, as always.
So why are you already taking off you obi?
No need to be critical.
It won't be a problem for there to be three of us.
Good idea, Hinano nee-chan. Then I'll be on the bottom.
Wait, Umi!
Besides, I want to see.
The face you make when you're going at it.
Takane onee-chan? Are you scared or something?
Hell no!
Whoa, you two make a great small pair.
I wouldn't call us a small pair.
We're here to support each other in any way we can.
N-Nee-sama.
Takane, just relax.
What?
Turned on, aren't you, nee-chan?
Her tongue feels so good...
Your skin's getting flushed.
Hina nee-san, it's not right that I'm the only one having a good time, so let me do something for the both of us.
You're a little wet, Takane.
I'll have you just as wet in no time.
Scissoring is boring...
I'll make your heart race.
Whoa, this is the first time I've seen a woman threesome.
Takane onee-chan, how about I tickle you here?
N-Not there!
How are you feeling, Hinano nee-chan?
I can't take this!
Kuuya!
Hina nee-sama...
Hinao onee-chan! Takane onee-chan!
T-Takane!
Umi!
Great, this is all great.
Hinano! Taka! Umi!
Why are you only leaving me out?!
Nee-nee!
Uhm, Kaname nee-san...
About telling Father about Kuuya...
About telling Father...
Let's keep it a secret between us.
Nee-san!
Thank you.
Well then...
Wouldn't it be better if we just talked about it?
It shouldn't be a problem if no one objects.
Isn't that a little cold?
Everyone's pretty open-minded, so I think we can get through this.
Kaname nee-sama looked a little upset after going through some book.
Books? What books?
I don't know.
She went through them pretty fast.
Well, she is rather introverted about such things.
So no one knows...
Another win for the "ice-cold" lawyer.
Congratulations. You look pretty confident.
I knew it from the beginning, so I'm not especially glad about it.
Your next case looks tough too. What do you think about it?
It will most certainly be a full-scale legal battle...
I say this as an address to my competition.
Wow, Kaname nee-sama's really good.
But I'm not so sure how this is different from back then.
Hey Kuuya!
You're raiding the fridge again...
It's just a little, so don't worry.
"A man's gloominess reflects his heart."
Anyway, what did you call me for?
Kuuya, you've pretty much decided on Kaname-nee, right?
Nee-nee, do you know something?
Just what makes Kaname-nee so attractive?
Now I've got you right where I want you.
What? Hey, what are -
Let's get it on!
That's good, nee-nee.
Hey, I told you not to play with those. I can't stand it.
What? What can't I play with?
I can't concentrate when you're doing that!
You're cute like that, nee-nee.
Hey, stop stealing my lines.
Did I make you forget your troubles?
Huh? You mean about Kaname nee-sama?
Are you sure I can't change your mind?
Hey...
Now that's a lot.
Speaking of which...
whenever I felt down about having a different mother than the others...
You were always there for me.
It wasn't that big of a deal.
It's just that I'm older and I'm supposed to take care of my little brother.
Well, right now you shouldn't really worry about those things.
But then, you were always so sure that Kaname-nee would do anything and everything to help you.
Right...
Well, we can't very well do anything now.
Serori was always always sensitive to it, at least around me.
It really took me by surprise.
Why Kaname nee-sama was so angry.
Like she also broke up with her lover.
And her cute dog passed on too.
Serori had a reason to keep quiet.
Now we have all our stories straight.
So now what?
Now that you've heard from everyone, have you found anyone interesting to you?
It was you, so I couldn't accept what I saw.
Because it was too harsh, too cruel.
Really now... Do you really love me that much?
If that's the case, then I can do anything to you, am I right?
I wonder what your breaking point is?
No matter what you do, I won't break.
Look at yourself, you can't do a thing now.
That's something. You just keep getting harder and hotter.
Do not close your eyes!
Keep them open and look!
Here...
And here.
How about i turn it up some?
Onee-sama...
Some on, listen to your own perverted sounds.
All right that's enough You aren't getting anything out of this.
Then how about I do this?!
What's wrong, onee-sama?
You aren't making me come.
Then how about I do this?
Why do you always have to put on this act?
Shut up!
Then how about...
Get ready...
This is tough. I can't break in front of her!
It just keeps getting more intense.
I can only look, but I can't help myself.
This'll make it the second time that I'll completely break you.
I can't even look anymore.
Onee-sama, you look like you're going to cry.
Don't try to mess with me!
You stubborn brat!
Shut up! Shut up!
This is really getting to me.
But I'm going to outlast her if it's the last thing I do.
I can't take this!
Coming!
Hey, what's this nice feeling I'm having...?
Kaname nee-sama...
you really went too far.
You toughed it out all the way until I came.
Stop that! Don't touch me!
You really have turned into a horrible person.
No wonder you soul's drowning in its own pity.
W-What are you...?
Your attitude is still too much like a schoolgirl's...
Hey, do you even know what you're saying?
Leave me alone!
Fine, give me the cold shoulder.
I'll turn you back...
No matter what it takes!
Wait a minute...
I...Don't touch me!
Sorry, I know I've been a dissapointment to you.
But now it'll all be fine.
Don't say that. You'll just disappear again.
Kuuya, Mother, and him...
Everyone dear to me disappeared.
I won't disappear.
I'll always be here with you.
Believe in me.
I've been...
I've always been...
Back then, whenever I was asleep, you'd always come to give me a kiss?
Kuuya, I really do love you.
I'm rather surprised myself.
I've been in denial.
How did I even become so bitter?
Alright then.
I'm going to start.
Go ahead.
I love you.
I love you too.
Nice.
Don't say that...I'm embarrassed as it is.
I can't find the right hole.
Come on.
Sorry.
It's right here.
I'm an idiot. sorry.
I'm still your big sister...
So don't worry about it.
Relax yourself.
It's inside me.
Kuuya, you're cock is really big.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Go ahead and fuck me.
Take me any way you want to.
Here i go then.
If you keep moving like that. I'll...
I'm going to come! Right now.
So much...
You came so hard.
You're still coming inside me so much.
Hold me close...
Stroke my head...
Kaname nee-san, trust me, I'm not letting you go.
I thought you were acting strangely.
I'm impressed that you can take this responsibility head-on.
Don't worry, I'm not letting you escape.
Thank you. Don't worry, I'm fine now.
As long as I have you around.