Let me hear your voice.
It looks like you can still move after the drugs...
But this is more exciting.
You're getting turned on by your ears?
Hey, you'd better not be at your peak yet...
Nee-sama, that's my...
If it's getting this big...
Isn't it getting tight in there?
Nee-sama, wait!
You're still fine, aren't you?
Oh, is that all?
Why am I being felt up by Kaname nee-sama?
What ever happened to my kind older sister?
Kuuya...
What are you thinking about?
Looking back on it...
The reason why may be where I don't want to remember.
My parents died, and I was adopted by the Hiiragi family.
And with six elder sisters, I'm the only guy.
I remember many times that they treated me as a toy, but also very lovingly.
But my favorite out of all of them... was always Kaname nee-san.
I suddenly realized it one day...
But their father noticed and was worried about what it could become.
So, I expressed my true feelings to her for the first time.
I... I love you Kaname nee-san.
Kuuya, let yourself grow up a little more.
Then I'll answer you.
Then, she gently kissed my cheek, as if to seal our agreement with it.
My heart felt like it was tied up...
And now, here I am...
I returned to my home town where my sisters were.
The heat makes it so exhausting.
Everyday it feels like a sauna outside.
Maybe I came a bit too early.
I'm bored.
Hey!
Welcome back, Kuuya.
Nice to see you, Serori nee-nee.
Well then, catch you later.
Huh?
You aren't here to pick me up?
Why did she come here then?
Guess who?
It's been so long, Umi onee-chan.
You're back, right, Kuuya?
I'm back.
You're supposed to say "onee-chan" too.
Welcome back, Kuuya.
Oh, yeah...
I'm back, Tomo-nee.
There, there.
Honestly...
So you're finally here.
Hm, the crybaby Kuuya grew up a little bit.
Sup, Takane-aneki.
I see you still have that little fang.
Stop acting all high and mighty!
I'm still better than you, you know!
So, where's Kaname nee-sama?
Kuuya...
It's been so long.
I've just come back.
You've really grown up.
What was with that reaction?
It was... weird...
Oh, it seems that you've grown a bit.
Hinano nee-san!
Long time, Kuuya.
Maru, this is my younger brother, Kuuya.
Hi there.
Who would've guessed Hinano nee-san was the oldest.
Kuuya, come here a sec.
Yes?
I've wanted to see you for so long...
Aw, no fair.
That night we had my welcoming party.
I was glad to be back home...
...or rather I should have been, but...
Why am I the one doing the cooking?
It's great that Tomo-nee is helping me, but...
Why are those two only watching?
Because it's too bothersome...
Make sure not to burn the yakisoba.
Kaname nee-san has become a popular lawyer on TV.
And this town has become a source of spirits and strange disappearances.
But since everyone ate so happily at the table, it put me at ease.
Think of these as little fireflies.
Serori nee-nee was born from a different mother than the other sisters.
Kuuya, your face is a little red.
It must've been that cola that Kaname nee-san gave me.
Why is Tomo-nee going out this late?
You know, I really love you Kuuya.
Huh?
I love you too.
Not "like", I mean "love".
Do you know the difference?
My head's spinning.
Did I drink too much?
And, that's when I found myself in my room, like that.
I have to get out of these.
Just keep laying there.
Nee-sama?
Your heart's beating so fast.
Are you that turned on?
No!
I'm not like that!
It's because of nee-sama.
It's because of you, Kaname nee-sama.
You say such cute things.
You got hard again.
You're so easy...
Don't... don't be like this.
What? Do you have any objections?
Such a cute dick.
It's so hard...
So hot...
And smells so sensuous.
And so big too.
How many women has this been inside, I wonder?
Premature ejaculator...
I knew it...
You're acting really weird, nee-san.
What happened to you?
Snap out of it!
I want my sister who always smiled at me.
You don't get it, do you?
No more!
I don't want it like this!
No way. You'll come as many times as I see fit.
Good boy, good boy.
Now you can't come even if you wanted to.
Come on, let me hear you scream.
You're really a good boy, aren't you?
If I had something like this done to me, my heart would be broken.
But...
This was just too much fun.
Take that!
You were at your limits, huh?
Oh yes, I forgot to tell you something.
Welcome back, my dear little brother.
♪ One day, in the afternoon ♪
♪ The older sister, finally came ♪
Kuuya, I'm coming in.
Kuuya, I couldn't sleep...
Let's sleep together now...
Kuuya..?
I'll... I'll do anything...
Kuuya's gotten all shriveled up!
What's with all the noise this morning...?
What happened?
What's with the dork this time?
Kuuya, hang in there!
I'm not a dog.
I'm human...
A quick dip should get him going.
It worked! Kuuya came back!
It's all right.
Just tell your big sister what happened.
Nee-sama did something horrible to me!
Shut the hell up you damn prick!
I'll be washing your underwear for you.
Thanks...
How humiliating...
All that milk isn't working at all!
Are you curious about the little princess?
Just what am I doing?
Here, you can look in Takane's room from here.
Wouldn't this normally be considered a crime?
I feel kind of sick.
Maybe I drank too much.
Here it comes!
What is she doing?
But, with this I can have a bigger bust out of all three of us.
I'll be more woman than they can handle!
Just you watch, you cat girl and four-eyes!
Is her head not on straight or something?
Well?
Didn't that little sneaking around excite you?
Compared to her I'm perfectly healthy, and have tons more confidence too.
Right?
Huh?
She may call me a cat a lot, but that may not be such a bad thing.
Meow!!
Meow! Meow!
Hey wait, nee-nee.
Come on, take it all off!
Hmm, it looks a lot bigger than it did in the bath.
Hey, hey wait.
It looks so good... Good enough to eat.
Be nicer, nee-nee.
You're freaking me out!
Let's get together, little cutie.
Such a healthy boy we are.
And you even moan too.
You're so cute...
Hey, will a hand job be enough for you?
Nee-nee...
I'm gonna...
Don't you want me?
But —
Come on, give me what you've got!
Look at it go!
Now then...
Do your best not to come, okay?
Okay...
Okay, here we go...
I didn't think you'd keep making noise when I haven't even put it in yet.
Here, can you see?
It's going in.
Okay, here goes...
It's really tight after all!
What did you do? What is this?
I'll make you come in only half a minute.
It's all squishy and smooth inside.
Hey, get yourself moving already!
I can't move!
If I do, I'll come!
The whole point of this is for us to come!
It's all right.
You taste so good, Kuuya.
Nee-nee!
Don't do that!
Then how about this?
Kuuya!
I'm going to come!
Kuuya, I can't keep going!
I'm coming!
I'm coming right now!
That was wonderful...
But this doesn't end here...
Ah man...
What a pain...
My yakisoba snack!
Hey, dork!
Go out and buy some! Right now!
Oh well...
I bought the book that my friend said to get.
"When Domineering Fails"
"The days of anguish when you're 25 and can't be dominant are over."
Sounds like something I could relate to.
That's a little creepy...
Those don't sound like normal footsteps...
Is it just me?
What the —
Late night cosplaying?
No wait, is that one of those spirit things?
Crap!
Go away!
Run for it!
Away...
Just how many things must I go through?
It's almost like my sisters are toying with me!
But then, that voice...
Run for it!
I swear it sounded familiar.
Sup, aneki.
This is quite the sexy costume, isn't it?
But bear with it. It's all to make me into an adult.
Oh crap, the crazy girl's into bondage!
I'll give you the time of your life.
Ow!
You little dork...
Don't think that because you're my little brother that I'm going to be soft on you!
Now do as I say!
Look me in the eye!
Seems like you got hard.
Since you seem to like being hit...
Now get on your knees and start licking my legs.
What's with that look?
Is there a problem?
I'm sorry.
Damn...
I thought you were a freak...
...but this?
Well, how does it taste?
Your legs taste good.
You dork.
Such an obedient worm...
You've always been like that.
You'll do anything that I order you to do.
That's enough.
Get on the bed.
Why?
Quiet!
Just shut up and get on the bed!
Very good.
I'll unzip this for you.
This is the proof that I'm an adult.
What, getting aroused?
Just thinking about what's in front of me.
Let's....
...put this in.
You all right, aneki?
Hmph, this is nothing... I can't do.
This feels good.
It went in...
Aneki...
Kuuya...
Aneki, I can't...
It's inside...
♪ Hungry, hungry... ♪
♪ Hungry... I'm so hungry... ♪
This yakisoba tastes like the cheap stuff.
♪ Carbs! Meat! ♪
Tomo-nee, where'd that injury come from?
Oh, it's nothing really.
What is this?
Looks pretty extravagant...
Oh, that...
Kuuya's the only one who can really cook, so I've been studying how.
Could you try it for me, Kuuya?
Umi's cooking...
What'll we do?
It's been known to kill.
Ugh...
Oh no, she's gonna cry.
It's fine.
If it'll give you some confidence...
Maybe I should make it —
Hey, not half bad...
Huh?
I can't... focus...
Oh, what a bad night...
Time for a bath.
I thought the bath was empty.
Onee-sama...
You shouldn't sleep in the bath.
I'll just go ahead —
Hey!
I told you no more.
Kaname nee-sama...
I hope she really hasn't changed that much.
What the?
Kuuya...
Not there...
This is my room, right?
So why is she...?
Kuuya...
Onee-chan...
She's masturbating in my room!
Onee-chan!
Kuuya!
Don't!
Wait!
Onee-chan...
It's your fault, onee-chan...
Doing such a thing in my room.
But, I thought you wouldn't be out of the bath so quickly.
No, Kuuya!
Onee-chan, you're so pretty.
Wait a second!
I can't do this now!
Kuuya, don't be so mean.
Onee-chan...
There's no way I can't look at your body now.
Let me see.
No, it's embarrassing!
Onee-san, you have such a soft backside.
Pervert...
Kuuya, it's fine if you touch my breasts all you want.
But that place is just too embarrassing!
No, no...
I want to see you embarrassed.
It's really cute down here.
Is it really not that good down here?
No, this is just too embarrassing.
We should be hugging or kissing first.
Then I'll kiss you.
But I'll be kissing this mouth.
No, don't!
Why do you have to do that?
Kuuya, don't you understand?
A woman's place isn't there! It's in front!
I know that.
Relax yourself more.
Right, that's it.
Your ass seems to like it.
You're a real letch, aren't you, onee-chan?
Kuuya, what are you...
Yeah, your getting turned on enough as it is.
Sorry, onee-chan.
But I want to do it now.
I want to be inside you.
I want to have sex with you.
Onee-chan...
Do what you will with me.
I'll give my whole body to you.
It doesn't hurt?
I'll be fine.
You know what to do now, don't you?
Can you do it?
I know.
From here, it goes in.
Onee-chan!
You're thing... so hot!
I'm gonna move now.
Onee-chan!
Kuuya! Kuuya!
No, not this position!
I'm going to come inside, onee-chan!
Kuuya, you came, right?
Yeah, it felt really good. I'm dizzy...
Kuuya...
We both came, didn't we?
Yeah...
So now, our hearts and souls are bound together...