It's great to have you out with us, Hiiragi-senpai.
You look as great as ever, like you're still growing up.
I must say, you two look cuter too.
Oh, I don't think so.
Damn, now I'm stuck with these two.
Uhm, would you like to go to my place for some tea?
Huh? Oh, sounds good.
Hey, look at that couple.
They're even kissing in public.
Those assholes!
Hiiragi-senpai, what was that about?
Oh, nothing at all.
Come on, let's go.
I love the way you smell , Kuuya.
You missed some ice cream.
Life with my sisters has settled down.
Nothing very loud or exciting happens anymore, but everyday is still enjoyable.
It's great to live life with my wonderful and beautiful sisters.
Or so I thought...
Maybe I drank too much water.
I don't feel so great.
Hurry up and close the door, you retard!
S-Sorry!
What are you doing in here!?
Ah, Sorry!
Don't look over here!
Why are you back in here!?
Kaname nee-sama is out there.
I can't go out there!
If she saw us both in here...
Aneki, you don't have anything on down there...
That's why i said not to look, you retard!
So now what?
'Now what'?
You...
Fucking prick!
My punishment...
Watering the front in the afternoon.
Why does she have to pick on me?
It's freaking hot...
Why am i even doing this?
Uh, can i help you?
Your are?
I'm a member of this house.
I see. Then that would make you Kuuya, right?
Ah, Mibu-san!
Come on in! I've been expecting you!
If it isn't Takane-san...
It's been forever.
Mibu-san is an old friend of Dad's.
He's a marine biologist, and has even studied a few unknown areas.
He originally came to survey the area...
But his true intention...
May really have something to do with Takane.
All right, I'll take my leave then.
Yes. Please come over and time you'd like.
The next time that i go to survey, i might a little free time.
I might be able to come back to this town.
Do you mean that?
I may come over to visit.
Would you mind?
Of course not. I'd be pleased to have you over again.
All right. Tell Kuuya to come along too.
All right! Now i have the perfect chance!
A chance? You don't mean...
To go out with Mibu-san?
Yup.
How can Mibu-san resist going out with me?
You're not serious?
Aren't you aiming a little high?
It is Taka after all...
No chance at all, I'm sure.
Got that right.
She'd be the worst to pick.
Such a spoiled brat.
Highly strung.
And with pigtails.
What does that have to do with anything?
Small breasts.
Chicken legs.
Pigtails.
Shut yer mouths!
That old guy may flatter you...
...but his pheromones only follow adult women.
Taka's still a little girl, right?
Really little.
Shut up!
After that...
Mibu-san viisited quite frequently.
During which, Takane took it as a challenge to impress him.
Takane's serious about it...
But what does Mibu-san think of her?
Tomo-nee, you really like gardening, don't you?
Yeah, I love the smell of the soil.
What's wrong, Aneki?
Loves me not.
Loves me.
Taka! don't do that to the poor flowers!
They got to be so pretty.
Aren't you being hypocritical, nee-san?
Well...
Well, what!?
They go through rain and wind, trying to live out their lives. But don't you notice you're at fault?
You killed a lot of weeds.
You butcher all those plants and you dare say that you want things to live? Huh - Huh!?
Aneki!
Takane-Aneki...
...got invited to the beach by Mibu-san.
When word got out...
Everyone tagged along.
Mibu-san invited you here...
So what?
"I'd go, but i can't swim!"
Couldn't you have just lied about it?
This is just practice for the real thing.
Aneki, how well can you swim?
I can't swim at all! Is that such a bad thing?
So I'm giving you the honor of teaching me.
It's the least a slave of mine can do.
Be thankful for that.
Yeah, sure.
Then let's start by getting into the water.
Hey! Are you trying to kill me?
I didn't do a thing.
That's a good start.
Let's try it without holding hands.
You'll get this eventually, Aneki.
Kaname nee-sama's being hit on by those three guys!
Kaname nee-sama, are you alright?
Yeah, I just told them that i didn't care who they were. And that they were annoying the hell out of me.
Oh, thank goodness...
What happened to Takane?
Oh, Aneki's - Oh, crap!
Aneki turned into a fish!
Have not!
Moving along then, you're going to teach me how to cook.
Now we're on cooking?
Why go through all this trouble?
So i don't fall behind the other sisters.
Hey, do you know why Mibu-san's coming over?
Beats me.
He wants Kaname-nee!
Aren't you thinking a bit too -
Think about it! it's the perfect place to get her!
He comes here, but it's really nee-sama that he likes.
Mibu-san, does that mean I'm nothing to you?
He'll ask: "Is Kaname-san here?" or something.
Ch-ch-choking!
If nee-sama steals him from me, I'll never forgive her.
I'll definitely get him to like me.
But to do that I'll -
Kuuya? Hey, Kuuya?
This guy isn't responding to his name...
You say it makes a popping sound...
But you can't because today is for...
Kuuya, want to take a bath with me?
Huh? Kuuya?
All I can remember is Aneki bullying me.
You're in the way. Move it!
What's with that look? You got a problem?
This guy's funny when he's in pain!
Hey! Get moving. You're my ride.
This is fun isn't it? if it is, then laugh!
Crying again? If you're going to be that way, I'll just leave you behind.
I'm going to eat this, so get on your knees and watch.
Despite all that, someone actually likes her.
That guy has strange taste in women.
Mibu-san is so cool, don't you think?
So refined...
So gallant...
That's why we keep saying you're too different for him!
A person's upbringing has nothing to do with love!
But a four-eyed nerd like you wouldn't understand that.
Oh, Mibu-san...
I don't get what you see in that old guy.
By the time you grow old, he'll be nothing but dust.
Exactly. There's a point where age is the deciding factor.
It's fine as long as the heart's in the right place!
What do you think, Kaname nee-sama?
Of that type of guy?
Let's see... It is true that part of me likes his type.
But you're the type that I'd stay with forever.
I'm perfectly fine with being naked with you.
An old man's body can't compare with yours.
I'm finished!
Yes. I understand.
What happened? Taka-nee?
Mibu-san - Mibu-san...
Underneath the glittering shooting stars, under the moonlight, on the beach...
This has to be a confession!
But who'd have thought that he would call me out late at night.
Well that's good for you..
If it really is a confession, this is quite a way to do it.
You're right.
What did she say?
She's obsessed over it.
That idiot...
How could it be a confession?
It'll probably be for surveying.
Well, I piked around a few things.
These days they call it "steady".
More like "study".
After she gets back and we all say: "Too bad", why don't we have a party?
Exactly.
With plenty of yakisoba.
Um, if it happens to be a real confession...
and we make all those things...
I wonder what we should do.
Go ahead and lock up.
Aneki, whatever happens, don't let anything get to you.
You know, in cases like these, you're supposed to say: "Don't go!" or something.
Why would i say anything like that to you?
You really just don't get it, do you?
Why is this getting to me?
Just to be on the sake side, I'll follow her.
Good evening.
Thank you for coming so late.
O-of course.
What are they talking about?
I'm on it.
It's a hybrid listening system. Let's see what happens.
Then I'll dub what they're saying.
And just how would you do that?
This thing here.
Mibu-san, do you remember the first time we met?
Yes, it was when you were learning how to get on the train.
The moonlight really makes you think.
And that is the truth.
Huh?
I see you as a beautiful woman. Do you understand what i'm saying, Takane-san?
I am expressing my feelings to you.
Um...Uh...Well...
Were you prepared for what i said?
Unless you think I'm being to pretentious...
N-Not at all! You're not being pretentious...
But...
This is the way that i do things.
To have us travel to this vast sea...
And this is the one place that i had to do it.
That is why i could not answer your plea for my affection.
Oh, i-it's all right.
I'm sure you didn't mean any ill thoughts.
But then...
If you wish to have one memory of this summer...
I shall be the first to respond to your feelings.
Uh, uh, Mibu-san?
M-Mibu-san, wait a minute...
This is a little much...
Aneki!
No...
Wait just a damn minute!
Mibu-san, regardless if you love her...
I can't just let you have your way with my sister like that.
For you to say that...
That would mean you yourself love your sister Takane, am I right?
Isn't it, Kuuya?
That doesn't matter!
Looks like i hit the nail on the head...
Very well then...
Shall we settle this like men?
Fine! I'll take you on!
Ah, you're awake.
What am I doing... in your room?
Kaname onee-sama fought for me, but i simply refused that she do it.
Oh, so that's what happened...
Well, a lot happened out there, but, well...
You won.
I won?
Congrats... and, thank you.
You were... really something...
It made me rethink my opinion of you...
So...
W-wait now!
Aneki...
I won the fight, so I'm sure you know what I'm entitled to...
Aren't you supposed to take some revenge?
Not when you're like this I won't.
N-No!
Come on, Aneki.
Fine...
You're so wet.
Don't!
Please, let me suck your cock.
A-Aneki... that feels so good.
Let me suck you harder.
Sorry...
It tastes delicious, Kuuya.
Kuuya...
Aneki...
You're pussy feels so good...
...please fuck me more, can you, right?
I'm all yours, fuck me more.
Yes!..
Fuck me harder.
Finally awake?
This is the first time...I've heard you on the piano.
Well, of course.
My playing isn't to be heard by just anyone.
It's only to be heard by the one man that I truly love.
Huh?
I'm a perfect woman though, and it'd be awful of me not to, so I'll let you listen.
Be thankful for this, retard.
Perfect, huh?
I definitely agree with the "awful" part.
Hmph, trying to make fun of me.
Just shut up and listen, retard...