Based on the encoding of Sakaato.
Translation: Ale1ster
QC: KingOfTheBongo
This...
Professor Sagdal, what are all these mummies?
Ah, it is wonderful.
These are without doubt the mummies
that are said to be accompanying the Great Emperor after his death!
That means that... under that tent...
Th- this ...
What the...
Genghis Khan!
H-He looks like he is still alive.
For 760 years,
what is he trying to do in this position,
ready to shoot?
And with 3 arrows nonetheless!
A-At last, I discovered him.
My lifetime dream has come true!
Surpassing even professor Hedin's discovery of Loulan,
this is a breakthrough for the archeological society!
What are those three lights?
Wh-What happened?
T-The Great Emperor has come back to life!
What?
What do you mean?
E-earthquake.
It's an earthquake.
Earthquake?
You, who have awoken me from my sleep,
hear my words carefully.
One thousand days from now,
a large calamity will befall your world.
The air will become foul, the earth poisoned,
and you will abandon your cities and head towards the lands of the setting sun...
With arrows of fire and whips of steel,
you will raise mountains of corpses,
and the blue-eyed people will fear you
and call you "Yellow Peril"!
/*Yellow Peril (黄禍論) in contrast to While Peril (白禍)
Yellow Peril was introduced from Kaiser Wilhelm II in 1895 as a demeaning metaphor for race, referring to the skin color of East Asians.
White Peril is a term introduced from Okakura Tenshin as a corresponding counterconcept.*/
As a released arrow does not return back to the bow,
an awoken cicada will not return under the ground.
But listen!
Three children bearing the scar of an arrow will appear.
If they join forces and kill the three Great Emperors,
my prophecy will not come to pass...
Remember!
Three children bearing arrow marks
will be the ones to send me back to a thousand year sleep...
Children bearing arrow marks?...
Professor Sagdal, hurry.
My lifelong dream!
Three...
Great Emperors...
Is that so?
I understand.
Inform Tokyo.
A child bearing an arrow mark
was spotted in Beijing.
Yes Sir.
Children with arrow marks?
Wolf cubs and dog pups may look alike,
but their nature is completely different.
It is best to kill the wolf cubs before their fangs grow.
Good morning.
Are you the instructor of the Majestic Fist school,
Master Yen Pao Lin?
Good morning.
Indeed I am Yen Pao Lin,
but if you came looking for a challenge, I must decline.
I have grown old and my eyes weak,
and I find it difficult to rise up to a fit opponent.
A challenge?
That would be absurd!
Having defeated your opponents single-handedly,
in numerous battles in the past,
we couldn't possibly be a match for you,
the famed Master Yen Pao Lin.
All things considered,
what an unusual blood thirst you have!
I take it you two are from the Kung Fu Iron Chain Fist style.
Using Cantonese
and having the smell of rust on your hands...
It is as if you introduced yourselves.
And when smelling steel,
the first thing that comes to mind is concealed weapons.
What a geezer!
It was about time you showed up...
I take it you are emissaries of the Great Emperors.
What the...?
You are late, Shin.
I'm sorry, Master.
I overslept again.
Stupid, both teacher and student.
Having only a few more seconds to live...
M-my arm!
Wh-what happened?
The effects of my fist, kick in afterwards, internally.
I don't know what's your end to this,
but I won't show mercy to anyone
who targets Master Yen's life.
You little...
With these fists, forged by training on iron bags,
I 'll reduce your skull to dust!
That hurt.
What the hell?
The human body is not made of wood or rock.
A little movement change, shifts the impact point,
and with a soft body, you can absorb the shock.
No way! That scar...
So, you are...
Die!
Master Yen is not the type of person that incurs enmity.
Why did you target his life?
This smell...
It must be a suicide capsule of potassium cyanide.
He must have hid it inside a molar.
Speak!
Who the hell are you?
What?
What happened?
An eye-shaped death spot...
This one has one too, Master.
So they were emissaries of the Great Emperors after all.
The Great Emperors?
Master, what do you mean by that?
Master!
Who was that?
Master.
Find your two companions.
You will know them,
for they bear the same scar as you...
Master, don't die.
Don't die!
An obstacle got in the way.
Master, I will avenge your death.
I swear by Heaven's name!
The Hong Lang is in Beijing?
That was close.
Hey, coward!
Sir?
It is OK,
I will call for an ambulance right away.
T-Take this...
Hold on , Mister.
Don't give up!
/*Great Emperors (大王)
Forehead Scar (額傷)
Sworn Friend (盟友)*/
A newcomer.
This scar on your forehead...
Scar?
So, you are a Hon Ran.
You too are the Great Emperors'...
Under the Great Emperors' orders,
I am going to send you to the next world!
Oh! My eyes...
Nobody has seen this spider
and lived long enough to tell about it!
Until I have avenged Master Yen,
there is no way I am going to forfeit this life!
For a  blind wolf, hunting is impossible!
Where is he?
Where will he come from?
Even a Hon Ran
is like a moth caught on the spider's web!
Calm down.
Concentrate on his blood thirst.
Here it comes!
Even though unable to see,
you see through my fist!
Even with both my eyes crushed,
my mind's eye is still able to see.
Shin, cast aside your fears and doubts.
Picture yourself crushing your opponent with your fist,
and it shall come to pass.
That's right, there is nothing to be afraid of.
I am the one who has inherited Yen Pao Lin's teachings!
What are you mumbling about?
Like hell I'm gonna let you
take the suicide pill in your fake tooth!
Speak up!
Who is the Great Emperor?
Hon Ran!
You stupid...!
Is this the end?
That damn Arisa!
Even today she sleeps over...
You would think she would come home at a day like this...
Give me that.
The one you got from Ezawa!
Where is it?
Ezawa?
I could always ask your body...
An arrow mark!
Hon... Ran...
Hon Ran?
This summer,
the months following our return from Mongolia,
I feel a presence threatening me.
Professor Sagdal, apart from depression
he suffered during the excavation,
he developed cancer, and is on the brink of death
in a hospital in Ulan Bator.
Professor Shinoda,
part of the same team,
last month commited suicide
under mysterious circumstances.
Before the same things happen to me,
I feel obliged to pass down the incredible events
that took place in Mongolia.
That is in order to avoid the great calamities
that will eventually befall
first Asia, and then the whole world.
I hope with all my heart, for the need not to rise
when a just and brave man will have
to witness this record.
Is this true?
They was nothing on TV or the newspapers...
Hear, thee! After a thousand days pass,
a great calamity will befall your world.
The air will become foul,
the earth poisoned,
and you will abandon your hometowns
and head towards the setting sun.
With arrows of fire and whips of steel,
you will raise mountains of corpses,
and the blue-eyed people will fear you
and call you "Yellow Peril".
Trouble, huh?
But were it to occur today,
World War III will break out
and the mankind will perish.
But bear in mind!
Three children bearing an arrow scar will appear.
If they join forces and kill the three Great Emperors,
my prophecy will not be realized.
A Hon Ran bearing an arrow scar
lives in Beijing.
/* Chinese Dictionary*/
Hong as in Crimson...
Lang as in Wolf...
/*Hon Ran (紅狼): Crimson Wolf*/
Hon Ran.
An arrow scar.
Who is it?
A policeman!
But how could he come here so fast?
And why did he pick the lock
without even ringing the bell?
I take it you are Mashio Mizuho...
I can't stay here anymore.
Anyway, it doesn't hurt to go have a look at Beijing.
Where are you taking me this late at night?
I see.
That is the case.
You are planning on killing me
at some deserted place, huh?
Are you too one of the Great Emperors' pawns?
That's right!
I have sold my soul to the Great Emperors.
And it's not just me.
Half the influential men on this country,
are already under the Great Emperors' control.
Pretty soon China is about to be taken over.
After seizing control of the army,
the Great Emperors will rule the country.
In order for that to happen,
every threat must be taken care of.
What the hell are the Great Emperors, anyway?
Shin, do you wanna know who took care of you master?
It was me!
You bastard!
And with you, anyone posing a threat
to the Great Emperors disappears.
But what a surprise!
Who would had thought that the Hon Ran
would once more reappear in this world?
Again with this Hon Ran!
What the hell is it?
The Hon Ran can't fight alone.
And before all three can get together...
I still have 5 more bullets left.
Shin, we came to pick you up!
Chang,
Ma!
Mong,
Xiao-Shu!
You guys...
Damn thugs!
I owe my life to Master Yen,
for he raised me when I was an orphan,
and taught me martial arts.
I loathe you so much
that I could tear you apart for killing him.
But if you tell me what a Hon Ran is,
I could spare your life.
Do you really think that a servant
of the Great Emperors is afraid of death?
A grenade?
I will drag you along to the next world!
Before that happens,
I will take my revenge for Master's death.
The scar flashed...
in shape of a wolf...
Shin, jump out!
Hey, whose car is that?
Come to think of it,
we don't know anyone who drives a beamer.
So who is he?
Leave it to me.
Yang, be careful!
Are you OK, boy?
Don't worry.
I am an outcast, like you, too.
After all, both me and you,
cannot live in the surface of Socialist China's society.
And who are you?
I am Ryūko.
R-Ryūko?
If you mean that black marketer,
I thought that his execution by firing squad
was on TV last year.
That's true.
I was sent to the firing squad.
But the shots were blanks.
The truth is that,
a certain International Conglomerate
made a deal with the goverment
and got me out of it.
And now I am working as a local consultant
for that certain company.
And what does that Ryūko want with me?
I want to use you in the Underground Society.
Yang!
Shin, who is this guy?
What are you going to do?
What are you doing?
I have no interest in small-timers.
Shin, you have the potential to become boss
of a big organization.
Do you feel like letting me make you
Number One in the Underground Society?
I don't expect you to decide right now.
Come to my office at the Wang Fu building in 5 days.
I 'll be waiting for the right answer, boy.
An airplane?
The Wang Fu building.
The entrance to Beijing's Underground Society, huh?
Hold on... I am finishing here.
Have you reached a decision about entering
the Underground Society?
We outcasts can either oppose the authority or prey on it.
There is no other way.
Of course, I chose the latter one.
I have no interest in the Underground Society.
More importantly, I wanted to give you this.
The eyeball of your friend
on the Japanese motorcycle?
Yang needs 2 more months in the hospital.
He got fired from his job
and doesn't have any fall-back.
And what's more,
he cannot work like before.
So you are telling me to compensate him?
Very well.
What currency do you prefer?
Chinese Yuan,
convertible banknotes?
Or would you prefer Hong Kong dollars?
Or maybe Japanese Yen?
If you come with me, you can make
that kind of money in half a month.
That takes care of my debt.
And now, don't you think it is your turn
to repay me for saving your life?
What do you want me to do?
It's easy.
And that takes care of it.
It is not because of my friend
that I contacted you.
I thought that if i asked you,
who lives in the Underground Society,
about the Great Emperors and the Hon Ran,
I might get an answer.
Shin, I have something to show you.
Isn't that used in PCs and word processors?
That's right.
It's a floppy disk.
Despite this magnetic disc's size,
it contains a horrible prophecy that would
make the whole world turn blue with fear.
Prophecy?
Hon Ran!
What is documented here
is the prophecy of Genghis Khan,
witnessed by experts from the joint expedition
of Japan and Mongolia.
The prophecy of Genghis Khan?
In short, it states that a great Asian army out of China
will occupy Europe
and slaughter and pillage until hell freezes over.
However,
if three children bearing arrow scars appear
and kill the three Great Emperors,
the prophecy will not be fulfilled.
Three children bearing arrow scars?
You might not believe it,
but this floppy came here on a corpse.
It is in here.
In this cellar?
She has the same scar as me.
What?
You mean that this girl
is a legendary Hon Ran too?
She woke up!
Wasn't she dead?
It seems that due to the shock from the plane crash,
she was just unconscious.
Plane crash?
Didn't you hear it on the news?
Five days ago, a Japanese airliner disappeared
on its way from Narita to Beijing.
From the 400 passengers that were pronounced dead,
she is the only survivor.
But why Beijing?
It was fate.
Fate?
She was floating at the sea,
when she was picked up
by one of my Korean smuggling ships,
disguised as a fishing boat.
Normally, they would hand the victim over
to the authorities,
but that would expose the smuggling.
And there,
when the captain laid eyes on her,
he thought that I would enjoy her,
and sent her to Beijing,
to me, as a present.
But what this girl
had hidden in her panties,
was a secret that would make
the whole world turn blue in fear.
I don't think that all this happened by chance.
It must be divine intervention.
I didn't expect to hear you talk about the divine.
I might not agree with Marxism or family,
but I believe that we are all subject to the divine's will.
Even me being here now,
is merely a result of heavenly guidance.
As long as the heavens don't abandon me,
I will never stop rising.
Like a dragon.
And this trump card
serves towards that purpose.
Having only a tiny floppy disk in your hands,
don't you think you talk a little big?
It is not just that.
I also obtained two Hon Ran.
Hon Ran?
Are you talking about this scar?
Who is there?
How long till Beijing?
Her senses are still confused and
she doesn't understand where she is.
Eh?
Noo...!
Where is this?
Who are you?
This isn't a dream, right?
What the hell was that jet fighter?
Jet fighter?
That means that the airliner
was shot down by the Great Emperors...
Shot down?
Nooo!...
Mother!
Brace yourself!
It is only natural.
Having a sudden death-like experience,
only to wake up
totally naked
in an unfamiliar basement...
I've seen this face before.
But I can't remember who it is.
A very long time ago,
I was supposed to have held
this girl in my arms.
When could that be?
The Great Emperors
fearing Hon Ran that much...
That only goes to say that
I am holding a trump card against them.
Ryu, what are the Great Emperors
that are trying to ocuppy China?
They are demons born by the capitalism,
who believe that they can buy
the next world with money.
Buy the next world?
They don't fear death the least bit.
For them,
money is more valuable than life.
What's more,
for them to manipulate the future China at will,
they are not humans.
Not human?
That's right.
It's name is Gokū.
Gokū?
We can't let this girl
stay like this forever...
I will prepare a change of clothes for her.
Wait here, Shin.
Good timing, Mon.
You saved us.
Just in case,
I was keeping an eye at the back door.
More importantly, Shin,
won't introduce me to the beauty next to you?
That's right.
I don't even know her name yet.
Hey, Shin, that beamer
is following us for some time now.
Here it comes again.
This is bad!
Don't tell me,
that damn Ryūko...
Quickly, run!
You...
It can't be,
the previous Head of State's,
Wu Yan Pin's son,
Wu Tai Lon?
What the hell do you plan to do with us?
Everything is for Gokū to decide.
Gokū you say?
Behave yourselves for a while.
Where...?
Shin!
His body warmth is faint...
I'm so glad.
It's cold,
what should I do?
If this goes on,
Shin will die here...
This way the body heat won't escape.
But why am I in such a place,
in such an shameful outfit?
Up to just a week before,
my concerns were only school and work,
but now that seems like a distant dream.
Shin's birth mark and mine,
surely must be because our fates interwine.
Being with Shin,
I am not afraid of anything.
So, please God,
don't let him die.
What should I do to share my warmth with him?
Shin!
But the only thing I can do for him is this.
Mizuho.
Shin.
I'm sorry.
There is nothing else I can do for you...
Although it is supposed to be the first time,
I 've had this feeling again,
a long time ago.
This is not the first time
I hold Mizuho in my arms.
When was that, I wonder.
Shin, who are you?
Where did you come from?
Mizuho, who are you?
Where could you have come from?
Hon Ran,
kill the Conqueror.
Our art is not fit for the Path of Destruction,
but for the Path of Righteousness!
You saw that?
Yes.
If these were our previous lives...
The mark of the third Hon Ran
is an arrow scar in the neck.
If the legend is true,
we three joining forces,
will kill the Great Emperors.
But, how will we get out of here like this?
A chance is bound to appear.
You see?
Here's your meal.
And how do you propose we eat that?
Huh? Get your muzzle down there
like a dog and eat it.
Such a poor service around here...
You would think that a Croesus
like Wu Tai Lon
would have piles of gold plates...
Don't expect luxuries!
Come on,
we have to get out of here.
H-here?
Hey, outcast.
Ryūko!
You are supposed to be a martial artist,
and yet, coming under the sun
before your eyes get used to the light...
You need more training.
Ryūko!
You bastard!
Don't get me wrong.
I came to help you.
Why?
The underlings of Wu Tai Lon in there,
killed all my men.
I have something to show you.
Come on, follow me,
both of you.
To where?
Come and you 'll see...
This is Gokū.
This?
This monstrous computer?
Yes.
This Gokū is the one ruling China now.
And also, this monster
is the Great Emperors themselves.
What is that?
Wu Tai Lon?
Ryūko!
What did you do?
He is the one who was contracted to buy Gokū,
and as a NBM delegate,
he got high on his horse
/*Heihaizu (黒核子): "black children": children in China, born outside the One-child policy, and not registered in the family register.
Here I think the best translation is outcasts.*/
and insulted us, outcasts.
From then on
it was just a matter of time
before it came to this.
What about Gokū?
Soon,
my men are gonna blow up this place.
That should take care of it.
Gokū huh?
Like we would let a monstrous machine like this
control our fate.
Ryūko!
Tao Lee!
You are so stupid, Ryūko!
Not even realizing that one of your own men
switched sides...
Sorry, aniki.
You are not my boss anymore.
You bastard!
What did you get for your soul?
I didn't trade for money.
I traded your life,
for happiness into the next realm.
Shin.
Shin!
I-I won't forgive anyone
who betrays his friends.
Nonsense!
What can you do with that body?
Shin!
That's Hon Ran for you..
But, you still don't know
the Great Emperors' true power.
Aniki is the one who is responsible
for his men's mistakes.
Ryūko,
you couldn't be...
You are the third Hon Ran?
Me?
Hon Ran?
Yeah.
That's absurd.
I-I couldn't possibly be...
There is no doubt about it.
Don't you feel it?
This warmth and this yearning...
Even if all three Hon Ran gathered,
it's too late now.
Before long,
the virus I sent
to the control system of the army,
will make the People's liberation Army
move according to my wishes.
With my one command,
I can fire each and every one of their missiles
at the biggest Chinese cities.
And then the Great Emperors will resurrect
and China will invade Europe!
Impossible!
Gokū, what the hell are you?
/*秦始皇帝: Qín Shǐ Huángdì : the first Emperor of a unified China in 221 BC.
Genghis Khan : the founder and Emperor of the Mongolian empire in 1206.
毛泽东: Mao Zedong : dictator and 1st Chairman on PRC in 1949.*/
The spirits of Qín Shi Huáng, Genghis Khan, and Mao Zedong,
the three Great Emperors, exist within me,
the great computer Gokū!
We remember you.
You are the ones who tried to assassinate us
and failed,
the three Hon Ran!
What's going on?
Th-This place...
We have been drawn
in Gokū's Dream Realm.
Take those three Hon Ran's lives!
This is the Master's cloth.
What?
Impossible!
Our Master's art in not fit for the Conqueror,
but rather for the Path of Righteousness.
We three have come
to suppress the Conqueror's lineage.
Greenhorns,
don't get cocky!
Shin!
There might be limits in a clubroom,
but not in the dream realm...
These fists are empowered by the spirits
of the people killed at Tian'anmen Square.
You...
Impudent Hon Ran!
The Great Wall?
Oh Dragon, my child, awaken!
From the Great Wall,
three dragons...
Stupid Hon Ran!
You think you are a match for us?
Fall quietly into our hands and perish!
The three of us, this time
will sever the Conqueror's bloodline!
Fools!
Mizuho!
Are you OK, Mizuho?
Thanks, Shin.
And for the finishing blow.
Take this!
What happened, Ryūko?
You, who sent China's youth
to the Cultural Revolution,
cannot even touch me, for I was deified.
It is pointless!
I can't kill Mao Zedong!
Why?
Have you forgotten, Ryūko?
We were branded as 'black children',
excluded from schools and power...
Who do you think is the originator of that system?
Ryūko!
It seems that together with this blood,
the myth of the communist ideals
is also being washed away.
Are you alright, Ryūko?
Don't mind me!
You think only about taking them down!
I'll settle it with the next blow!
Concentrate all your power on me.
Got it.
Hey, look!
What the hell is that?
Are you ready?
You evil Great Emperors,
sleep in the next world for all eternity!
You damn humans!
Someday
we will without doubt be revived
at a distant place,
and bring about destruction and chaos!
This settles it, right?
No, this is just the beginning...
China is reborn anew.