Why? I should have powered up when I ate those meat buns.
It looks like my meat bun bomb is working effectively.
Now then, shall we enjoy tonight's punishment?
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
\Kanbu
Kanbu
Aku no Onna
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
Kanbu
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
Kanbu
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
Kanbu
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
Kanbu
Presented by
Anim8S
Aku no Onna
Kanbu
Presented by
Anim8S
2nd
「Licentious Beast's Discipline」
This time, punishment involves echelon unit position.
Hey!
It's punishment time.
Open your eyes right away!
Katsuma?
Where are we?
As you can see, we're inside the garden.
What am I doing here...
Eh?
My neck is...
Na... Na... Na... Naked!?
I thought it would look nicer while walking a perverted dog like you.
I'm not a pervert!
Take a walk? That's not...
Is it okay?
If you talk so loud, there'll be more people coming over here.
I'm not-
your-
dog.
Why are you doing something like this?
It's embarrassing...
I won't let you get away with this!
Hey... hey... don't bark at me like that.
This is your punishment, you know?
Then what should I do?
There's a tree over there, right?
Act just like a dog...
There! You know what to do, right?
Wha... What is it?
Make a mark.
Just like you mark your own territory.
Don't fuck with me!
There's no way I would do something like that!
Right now you're a dog.
No one would care if a dog took a piss there.
I... I'm telling you, I'm not a dog!
I don't want to be seen like this.
Hey, why don't you do it already?
Even though you say it like that,
I couldn't do that right away!
Is that so?
Then shall we take a walk until you want to do it?
Take a walk where there'll be a lot of people around you.
I'll do it, I'll do it here right away!
Just a little bit...
My pee is warm...
There's a lot of it coming out...
It's embarrassing...
Why it won't stop already?
I can already feel it, it makes me feel sick.
You're actually doing it.
But what a lot of pee you're making.
Don't look... Don't look at it!
Stop it, please let me go already!
Hey, suck it!
I want you to lick it until my thing is clean.
Then I shall make you remember my scent.
It's strong and sturdy...
You're doing great,
Is it possible that you like to suck it?
It's not-
I can't stop doing it...
I don't know why I'm able to do it,
but I'm doing it right now.
It's great, so this is what they call a man's thing.
It's getting big like this.
I feel good when I keep licking it like this.
It's really hot and it's making me shiver...
That's means it's about to cum.
Cum? You mean sperm?
The stuff that would make me pregnant?
That's right, It'll make you pregnant if I cum inside of your mouth.
What should I do?
You should let me cum onto your face,
then you won't have to worry about getting pregnant.
But...
I shall make you remember my scent.
Let's do it.
It's hot... and it's really sticky...
No...!
It stinks.
I want you to clean it up thoroughly.
This is what you call punishment.
But...
There's no but!
By the time you suck all of this up,
it'll be the end of your punishment.
Is it possible...
You're joking about that, right?
Katsuma.
Sto... Stop it, don't do it!
I can't let that thing...
inside of my body!
It... It hurts!!
So this is what your virgin pussy feels like.
There's nothing great about it.
Don't say that, could you just say that it feels good...
It hurts-
Slow down...
It hurts...
It also feels weird...
It looks like it's not just your blood flowing out of there.
You also feel it, right?
There's no way I would know about that.
Sto... Stop it...
When I keep fucking it,
your pussy gets tighter & tighter than before.
I don't mean to do that.
No... don't do it that hard!
I'll cum and fill your womb with a lot of sperm.
No... No!
You know that my kind get pregnant easily!
That's why I've never done something like this before.
I might get pregnant right away after this.
Please... I beg you.
I'll do anything, but don't cum inside of me!
Then I'll cum a lot,
I'll make you remember what kind of scent a male has.
That's... I don't want it!
I don't want that kind of sticky sperm...
No!
With your hips moving like this, what are you saying?
It's going to cum... cum inside of me...
Emblem steal!
It really stinks...
It stinks, but somehow...
You dare do something like this to me!?
I'll do something horrible like this in return to you!
You shouldn't do something like that.
Wait... wait a minute, that crest emblem!?
I just stole your crest from you before.
That's not...
You know what will happen to an executive who has lost their crest, right?
I'll return your crest when the right time comes.
Until that time has come,
I want you to be my watchdog!
Now then, I shall give you your first mission.
I want you to find out Oboro's weakness.
Then?
What am I doing looking like this?
That's for sure, It'll be the punishment style this time.
Even though you say that,
what bad taste you have if I look like this.
I've covered your important thing,
so you won't have any problems, right?
There's no way I would be okay with that!
Hey, don't you dare to look there!
What a great looks you have, Oboro.
I told you, don't look at it!
Do you want to get killed?
Shut up!
Don't act so highly after you failed your mission!
That must be some kind of mistake!
When I thought about it before, there was no way that my troops would be defeated like that!
Don't you have any shame, Oboro!?
You filthy rabbit!
How dare you to call me that!?
I won't let you get away with this!
What are you doing!?
What is this!?
You can feel it shocking inside of you, right?
These shocks will suck away your spirit of life.
That's-
You dare-
do something like this!?
Don't you have any shame!?
Doing something perverted like this to me!
It's an unforgivable act-
Just stop it!
It's going to...
Hey... hey... Oboro-sama the Crescent Moon is actually enjoying this kind of maniacal play?
That's not true.
You're the one who's making me do this.
I'm not going to feel it!
Stop it!
Just stop it!
Please stop it!
Please... I beg of you.
Please... please stop it right away!
Quick... quickly!
No way, It's gonna come out!
No!
Don't look, don't look at it!
I'm actually going pee like this...
A lot of it is coming out...
Aku no Onna Kanbu
That's why I told you not to do it...
It makes me want to die when I think about it...
You're satisfied, right?
Your punishment is over!
Just let me go already!
Huh?!
It's not over yet.
Just when I'm about to feel your noble thing.
You... You want to make me do something like that?
It's filthy, you know?!
What are you doing?
No way...
No, you can't!
I'll do anything but that!
No-
No...
It hurts.
You were acting so high and mighty before this,
but it's your first time when it come to this.
I won't forgive you!
You dare take away my first time being this rough.
There's no way I would accept this kind of punishment.
I'll tell our queen everything about this later.
Do as you'd like, if you can do it.
It hurts!
Don't start moving it!
What a noisy girl, I'll do it slowly then.
What are you talking-
It's thrusting into me.
It's starting to feel weird.
How is it, do you feel good?
There's no way I would feel good from Katsuma's thing-
This can only make me feel pain...
That big thing is moving inside of me.
You actually like it this big, huh?
I could tell from your lecherous face.
There's no way that my face-
would look like that.
But, it makes me crazy!
I'll make you cum for sure.
Forcing me like this...
There's no way I would cum-
Why?
Even though it's my first time,
what should I do?
I'm about to cum.
I can't hold it, my head is about to lose consciousness.
I... I'm... cumming!
Great... It's too great.
I can't stop cumming!
It's cumming inside of me.
That... that's...
No-
Even though I don't want it...
Even though I don't want it, that sticky thing is...
inside of me!
There's hot stuff within me...
I... I'm... cumming!
Emblem steal!
Doing something like this...
Making me dirty like this.
If you get pregnant from this,
would the children have rabbit ears as well?
Don't make fun of me...
how dare you say something like that?!
How dare...
How dare you take my virginity!
I can't simply accept this kind of shame.
I will let the queen know about this,
and you'll be killed because of this!
Wait, that's going to be a problem.
That's...
Your crest shouldn't be a crescent moon...
But what's that...
What does that mean?
I just took away your crest.
You're nothing without your crest.
That's not possible...
You know what it means to live within this nation without any crest?
That's...
What are you going to do with me?
It would be just fine if you follow what I'm saying.
Right now, I have no choice but to say yes, right?
As I expected of Oboro, you're understanding.
I'll leave it to you tomorrow.
Katsuma-san.
You're not here?
That idiot, calling me here like that.
What does he mean by disappearing like this?
After he makes me do a lot of perverted thing like that.
This is that man's clothes...
What dirty clothes he has,
there's a weird scent all over it.
This is the scent of Katsuma-san's sweat...
It makes me want to do it...
No...
I shouldn't do something immoral like this.
Bu... But.
I can't hold it.
I can't hold back against this scent.
This scent makes me feel excited.
My body is getting hot and I can't stop it.
Katsuma-san's scent is making me crazy.
This feels good.
No-
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming because of this sweaty scent.
Looks like you're enjoying yourself, Oboro.
Wha... Wha... What... eh?
This is...
Oboro the woman executive is actually a scent pervert.
Let me go!
It's already this wet.
Did my sweat make you feel this excited?
That's not it!
Katsuma-san's thing-
feels good.
It smells great.
This kind of penis scent makes me feel...
It stinks but-
This penis is so tasty.
It stinks but,
it's Katsuma-san's scent...
It makes me feel calm.
I'll thrust this stinky thing inside of your pussy.
Yes... of course.
I couldn't think of anything else.
It's inside! Your penis is thrusting-
Doing something perverted like this...
Penis... your penis...
It's getting hard!
It doesn't feel painful anymore.
It feels weird...
No!
Katsuma-san's scent is making me feel crazy.
Great.
Katsuma-san penis is thrusting into the deepest parts of me.
That stinky penis is inside,
that's going to make my thing stink as well.
My thing would smell like Katsuma-san scent.
I want you gave me more of your scent in there!
You're making that lecherous face again,
I didn't know that you were always this perverted!
It's... It's not true, I've been like this since you took away my crest.
I only belong to Katsuma-san!
I wonder how many you've done something like this, you scent pervert!
Don't say something like that...
No, It'll make me even more crazy.
It's great... please give me more.
It feels good.
No!
I'm about to cum... cumming... it's cumming!
I'm going to cum inside of you a lot, okay?
You can't let it out inside.
I'm about to... cum... cum... cum...
Cum... Cumming!
Ah, I let too much out at you.
This will make you pregnant for sure.
I'm...
How dare... how dare... how dare you!
How dare you play with my body and my heart like this!
I'll make you pay for this!
It's not over yet, Oboro.
Oboro.
I never knew that Oboro would be that perverted...
No!
Why... Why would,
Serena is in here as well?!
I also lost my crest to Katsuma.
I'm sorry, Oboro.
Is it possible, the one who broke apart my troops was Serena?
What... What have you done to us?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Besides that Oboro, Serena,
I want you to get along as my slaves!
Serena, you smell like sweat.
That's because before I met Oboro,
Katsuma was doing it a lot with me.
You're like that as well, I can smell your sweat so much.
No...
Does it smell that much?
What soft and bouncy breasts you have.
Your body feels like steel,
but why is this place is so soft.
You're really cute, aren't you?
I'll make you even cuter like this.
Sto... Stop it.
If you keep doing that...
I just licked it a bit, and your nipples are already that hard, you slutty girl.
Serena, It feels really great.
Oboro... Oboro!
You're so cheeky, putting on that kind of face even though you're younger than me.
No!
But, when I look at Serena's face like this...
it makes me feel that too.
It's driving me crazy...
That's not fair if it's just Oboro.
Then I'll do the same thing to you.
Don't pinch them that hard, you idiot dog!
Driving you crazy, huh? There!
No... you can't do that. If you do that so hard my nipples won't be the same anymore!
I'm feeling it too much!
Me too, Serena feels so good.
Serena's asshole smells so sweet.
Stop it, please don't smell that thing.
Oboro, I'm already this wet and can't I hold it anymore.
Me too, let's feel good together.
Oboro, that's too much! I can feel you rubbing my clitoris with your tongue.
It's going to come out!
My clitoris is going to come out!
Oboro... Oboro.
It feels good.
Serena.
Oboro... Oboro.
Serena... Serena.
I can't hold it anymore...
I'm gonna cum... I'm gonna cum...
Cum... cumming...
Aku no Onna Kanbu
Katsuma, I feel...
I feel my body getting hot and driving me crazy.
The others are busy fighting,
there's nothing to be worried about, right?
But you know, It's not my intention to do something like this with you up here.
Penis... I want more of your penis.
Is it okay for you to suck that penis?
It'll make you pregnant, you know.
I can't stop that feeling after you already gave it to me once.
As I thought, my pussy wouldn't feel this good if you weren't doing this.
It's okay for you to go deep... that's why you should give me... more of it.
Good... It feels too good.
More... I want you to do it even more intensely.
You're such a slutty bitch dog!
Stop it...
Don't call me a bitch dog... I'm actually a proper wolf being, you know...
No, I don't want you to call me a dog...
but you won't thrust your penis into me without it.
It's making me-
want to cum!
You idiot dog!
Where are you and what're you doing?!
This... This is Serena, I'm a bit busy at the moment!
Is it that bad for you, are you okay?
No... no... I can handle it.
It's big... It's big!
Big, what's big?
It's nothing to be worried about.
Hurry up and help us over here, Serena.
I got it, I'll come soon... I'll be coming soon.
Wait, Serena-
Hurry up and cum, I've got to go to Oboro's place right away.
Just get it done quickly!
I've got no idea when it'll cum, you know...
I'll let you return to the battle after this.
I've got it, but please be quick.
Shall I let it out inside of you?
But that'll make me pregnant, so no.
Then like usual I'll pull it out and and spread all of it onto your body.
More... more... my pussy.
Make my pussy cum.
I'm sucking your penis in.
It's hitting deep inside of me.
Cumming... I'm cumming!
I don't care if it'll make me pregnant,
just let that hot stuff out inside of me.
It's cumming... that hot and sticky stuff... that hot thing!
There's a lot of your sperm inside of my pussy-
It feels warm...
Happy... I'm happy... to get pregnant from Katsuma's...
You two! How dare you leave your mission like this?!
What is it? Do you want it as well?
I'll make love with you right now as well.
Just come down here.
What is it?
What, you don't want to do it?
No, you're putting it inside like that!
Huh?
What? Aren't you already this wet?
That's because I can feel Katsuma in there.
I can smell Katsuma's scent from here!
Then doing it outside...
like this-
It'll make me go crazy!
What a great pussy you have, Oboro...
I can hear its echoing from here.
It's embarrassing, having such a noisy pussy.
To let Serena see me like this.
What're you saying? I can see all of your perverted things like this.
Don't say that.
Why should I do something shameful like this-
Eh?
That's because Oboro is too cute, right?
Don't... call me cute like that...
Katsuma, what about me?
Serena is cute as well.
Katsuma!
You're such idiot, Katsuma-san!
I'm about to cum.
It's cumming... let it cum inside of me!
No!
No... No... why have I become such a perverted girl?!
The hot stuff is inside of me... a lot of it inside of me.
It's going to cum again.
Cumming!
How... How many times has he cummed inside of me...
Surely I'll get pregnant from this.
If you're pregnant, let's give birth together, Oboro.
What are you saying, you idiot dog.
From now on, I'll make you listen to what I'm saying.
Yes.
My master.