Arrow Two, I've arrived at the destination.
All clear from up here.
Can you hear the helicopter sounds?
No.
Is that the newest machine?
I just can hear these cricket sounds from here.
Are you really in there?
Then, would you like to play a game with me?
Scissors.
As usual, you're not afraid of anything, are you?
You should try it once, Munei-san.
You'll get used of it.
I'll have to refuse that.
Arrow One, preparation is OK.
Understood.
Rei, follow my instructions carefully.
Don't do any grandstanding today.
I'll do my best.
Arrow One, proceed!
Understood.
REI
Let's capture the special agents!
The power going to back on soon, you have ten seconds.
Understood.
This is Arrow One, I've confirm the power has turned back on again.
Arrow Two, infiltration is a success.
OK. Arrow Three, you can move in right now.
I'm sorry, It seems we've triggered something
within the building electricity.
Hey, that's causing trouble in here...
As we planned before, there isn't any security on the 35th floor right now.
If we just move in right now, we'll be successful.
If there are more than three people guarding that place,
step away from there.
All right, I'll step away if there's more than five people.
I'll cut off the communications for now.
Rei? Rei?!
It's in here.
This is?
The power has down back there.
That's right, but we got a back-up power supply in here
so there won't be any problems.
Five people, huh?
Like I care.
Hey, where do you think you're go-
Damn it!
It seems you don't have much time to finish your conversation.
The boss of North Cartel, Joachim Night?
Who are you?
I'm asking the questions here.
Joachim Night, right?
That's right.
You dare make me bleed like this-
I won't allow you to threaten me.
It seems this place isn't really a narcotics storage place.
What's that thing?
It's the money resources.
You're one of those narcotics special agent, huh?
Just answer what I'm asking you!
What's your name?
I'll make sure to kill you!
I'll rape you... rape you... all over again,
so you'll regret being born in this world.
That's right, I'll make your family, your friends, and everyone,
I'll make them suffer to death!
Is that so?
Let's talk again slowly after this.
This is Arrow Two, I've captured the target.
You can pick me up.
You're not going to pass out on me, now?
Joachim Night.
International crime syndicate boss, North Cartell.
Nickname: General.
Birthplace unknown.
Japanese descent.
He's also one of the most wanted guerrilla terrorists of the 20th century,
known as the Red General.
He also has several secret headquarters in South America,
which create the new generation of narcotics.
His syndicate relies on violent crimes,
and after many years he's been able to create the world's most powerful crime syndicate.
Last year, he began planning to make another headquarters in Japan.
Within half year, he's already conquered all syndicates
in the Kanto area.
We've tracked and captured him in one of the hotel within those areas,
and have found out there are a lot of unknown things in the other rooms of the hotel.
One of his subordinates who's working in goverment has already noticed,
and now he's planning to look for his missing boss.
We have a maximum 48 hours to lock him in here.
Before the time is over, I want you to find out what he's planning
with all those materials back there.
You're talking like that's possible to do, Chief.
Though it's not impossible to do.
Rei!
Don't you think it's better for us to act like a soldier,
since he used to be a soldier?
Formerly one of the biggest guerrilla terrorists,
who's now working as narcotics boss.
Don't you think you've lost your authority in there,
Mister Red General?
12 times.
You've hit me 12 times.
It's 12 times since you hit me back there in the hotel.
Now it's 13 times.
It's good for us if you have good memory in your head.
Then I'm sure that you'll be able to answer my questions easily.
What's that thing?
Back there, I saw those creepy things in the tubes.
Though I couldn't take all of your material data at that time,
I was able to take some of your data last night.
Our specialist is already working on that data right now.
We'll know what it is soon.
It's better for you to talk to us without hiding anything.
I'm not sure about that.
It's 30 hours...
No, maybe you have about 40 hours left to lock me up like this.
I'm sure there's a friend of mine who's already prepared
to release me from here.
Then your data which you stole from me earlier,
will be useless within the next few days.
Do you understand right now?
It's 13 times, Miss Special Agent.
Stop your interogation.
What?
There's an informant who wants to talk with us about
the thing that happened yesterday.
Informant?
I'm sure you already know Uematsu the informant, right?
Yeah, that rat with the bad taste
and the golden watch.
Of course I couldn't forget that man.
Also he always took a lot of money for his informations.
It's the first time I've seen an informant such as him.
I suppose that proves his information is trustworthy.
But, don't you think it's strange for Uematsu
to contact us like this?
I assume it's going to be dangerous information after all.
He wants to give it directly to us.
He also demands that we pay him in cash.
Don't you think that the timing is too coincidental?
Although it's going to be a trap, it will be useful
if we can find something to pressure Night.
We'll decide it after thinking about the dangerous part first.
Yes, of course.
He's also thinking of safety within these crowded trains.
Be quiet.
He's coming.
Understood.
Oh... No-
W-What is this...
You're able to hold against one shot.
Usually, it only takes one shot to turn someone into a limp doll.
St-top... it-
It'll be a pain if you call someone.
Re... Rei...
It can't be...
All of these passengers are...
What a clever woman, aren't you?
Your insight is correct.
And then, this is the thing you've all been searching for.
It's called the Brain Control Nano Machine.
It's a serum to control someone's brains with one word.
Even for vulgar uses.
It's not going to be fun if you don't react.
I'll let you scream your pleasure as much as you want.
Re... Rei.
Then, shall we enjoy ourselves in here?
Stop... it...
No! Stop... pinching... my nipples...
No...
If you pinch my nipples like that...
No... you can't do that!
My tongue is moving by itself...
My breasts and my pussy are totally drenched...
I've made contact. I'm proceeding with the transaction.
I'm sure you've already know Uematsu the informant, right?
Yeah, that rat with the bad taste
and the golden watch.
Of course I couldn't forget that man.
Rei, what's the matter?
Rei, respond!
Say there's nothing going on.
Why... should... I...
Say it: no problems here. Now.
There... are... no... problems... here...
Is that so? Then proceed with the transaction.
Wait, that wasn't me just now!
It... it can't be...
Today, I'll show you how we fight
arrogant woman like you.
I'll let you scream with your voice.
You can let out your screams of pleasure.
Hm... so this is how your body looks like underneath.
It makes me surprisingly excited.
You jerk, let me go...!
My, my, that wasn't enough for you?
I'll let you release a lot of your feminine liquids with this serum,
then you're going to take care of them.
What's the matter?
It's perfectly fine for you to let your luscious voice go.
Let me hear you cry out like an animal in heat.
Though I can't guarantee that your friends going to hear it.
Who-who would-
Who's going... to moan-
No-
You...
Stop... doing that...
Stop... that-
Your mouth is saying that, but down here is completely honest.
I can't endure something like this.
But,
I'll make sure this won't-
Hm... even though we're doing like this, you're able
to keep your voice in there.
Splendid, splendid.
As a reward for what you're doing, I'll let you see your precious
friends from the special agents.
No... stop it...
Let me rest a bit...
I'm going to cum...
Going to cum...
Cum... cumming... cumming-
Rei...
No... stop it...
Don't look at me... Don't look at me with your face like that-
There... there, why don't you tell her how you're being raped.
Explain to her!
Though I don't want my pussy being raped, my pussy is filled with it...
there's a lot of penis coming inside my pussy...
Though I don't want it, but I couldn't do anything!
That's good, I'll reward you for explaining properly.
Looking at me... I'm going to cum while Rei is looking at me-
Going to cum... going to cum again...
I'm going to cum with my slutty pussy while everyone is looking at me...
Cum... cumming...!
Munei-san is being shot with that serum,
my fault... It's my fault!
It's... it's feels good... being seen like this...
I'm going to cum while you look at me...
The next hole will be yours.
You've already screaming with one thrust?
But it's only the beginning, you know?
There you go! I'll make you pregnant with this, old hag!
There's a lot of sperm coming out...
There's a lot of sticky thing come out from your penis,
It's coming inside my pussy...
It's coming... It's still coming inside of me...
Make me cum with it...
Make me cum again!
It's coming through... in my womb.
Don't push it in... don't push it into my womb-
Go on, cum! Cum! I'll make you cum!
Who's going to-
Who's going... to cum-
It's coming out... It's really coming out... inside of me...
His sticky sperm is coming into my womb...
Damn... damn it!
Let me go!
In-inside of my womb is being stirred up...
I can't think of anything else-
No... not that hard!
If... if you're doing it that hard, I'm going to-
Admit it. Say it, that you're feeling all of it.
Who do you think... would feel... feel something... like this-
There you go, bitch!
Cum-cum-cum-cum-cum! I'm cumming!!
There's a lot of sperm coming inside my pussy,
the semen's going to make me pregnant...
Don't even think to bite it, okay?
Politely...
That's right, suck it politely with your mouth.
Let me go...
Don't cover me with your sperm... stop it!
You've let it out inside me again...
I'll... kill... you... I'm going to... kill you...
Then, shall we let you out at the next station?
I'll take care of your pal.
If you want to save her, you know what to do.
Hey, it's time for you to go.
Hey... hey... what the matter with her? Are they filming a porno?
What's wrong with her?
It's digusting...
There... is-
The last serum is?
It's the release serum.
It's pity that we're not able to watch what'll happen after this.
I can't... hold it-
My body...
is being...
freed.
Toilet.
Right now...
I can't...
If you're not...
Let me get... to the toilet-
Hey, you!
It's going!
It's... going out-
My urine...
is come out...
I'm cumming... while I'm... peeing...
I'm cumming... while peeing...
I'll... kill... you.
If I drifted away, I can always go back
to the days where I belong
Even I lose something important
There's a way to remember it
If I just attach to those lost days
I might be able to remember something
But I never feel any regret in my mind
With those eyes once again
I want you to look at me
With this feeling once again
I want to reach for you
Never again
o
t