If we're talking about his way back home from working at the DVD rental shop.
Hosaka Ippei often used this park as his shortcut to come back home.
But his reason wasn't because he needed some good and slow night walking.
Good, more.
What? It's just some couple.
That's right, what I want is some kind of rape!
Even though he said that, he never raped anyone,
or even saw any rapes happen.
It makes me bored seeing sex between couples.
Let me go!
This way?
Please, someone help me!
I said shut your mouth!
Okay, I can thrust it into you right away.
It's like a dream come true for Ippei.
Now he can let his fantasies about rape fly away.
This time,
I'll let my big thing thrust into your pussy!
There!
That's good.
That's the kind of face I want to see.
I'll cum a lot inside of you.
Your nipples are getting hard on their own.
Your pussy is also dripping wet.
Right, it's about time for me to cum.
It-It's out!
It's not over... yet.
How is it? I shot a lot inside of you.
When he watched the scene with his hand still holding that hard penis,
Ippei started to lose patience against his imagination.
This is... This is it!
Wh-Who is that!?
Oh shit!
Good bye!
I want to experience that too.
It couldn't be...
I heard a woman's voice just now...
Hey... hey... this can't be happening.
Hey!
Are you alive?
I-I can see her panties!
Panties... It's virgin panties!
This virgin,
I'll rape her for sure!
I'll just attack her blindly,
it looks like she's asleep right now.
She doesn't seem like she'll wake up soon.
Her lips look soft and sweet.
I'll make her suck my thing,
I'll take it out when I'm about to cum,
then I'll shoot my sperm onto her pretty face!
Then I'll forcefully put my penis into her pussy.
Inside of her pussy three times, and into her mouth twice,
that's how I want to cum!
I'll use her asshole as well, and I'll keep cumming inside her over and over!
Just a bit... Just a little bit more.
It's coming out-
Where should I release it? Inside of her?
On her breasts?
Or on her face!? Eh... wait... wait... I can't stop-
It's going to cum again-
This isn't what you think... this is just...
What were you thinking about?
Original Animation Video
~Chidori Yuuma's P! On P? Making P!? Chapter~
This is my room.
What an unpleasant room for a pervert like you,
I can even smell your pervert juice from here.
My... My pervert juice...
This is what you like?
Don't touch it on your own!
This is all about rape isn't it?
You filthy cherry boy.
That's not even your business.
I'm hungry.
Didn't you hear me?
I said my stomach is empty.
Just prepare dinner quickly.
Self Control
Calm down, all of this is for keeping that secret.
Live with me... in my room?
That's what I told you before.
Wait a minute, you're-
Call me Sari-sama.
Um... Sari-sama, there's no way girls like you would want to do it.
Then could you tell me what you just did,
to this defenseless girl in front of you.
That's...
Is it possible that this girl was running away from home?
Don't think about unnecessary things.
Just listen to me and let me live in your room.
Wait a minute...
Didn't I read an internet post about someone that let a girl live in his room,
and she would do anything to return the favor?
This is...
just my chance for easy sex!
What do you say? Can I live with you...
or not?
Of-Of course you can live with me, Sari-sama.
Well, that's fine with me.
I won't say anything since you already said it like that.
Where's the bathroom?
Inside that door.
I'll take a shower while you prepare dinner,
got it?
Ye... Yes.
It's almost time for my chance!
When did I fall asleep?
This woman...
____________
_____________
______________________
Famous Idol
Kujou Sakura
New Maxi Single release!
Kujou Sakura?
Do you like this kind of idol?
This woman just wants to be raped.
Um... did you bring your medicine?
When you're done with your breakfast, you should take it.
You're just...
Very well,
I'll show you my specialty.
I can see what kind of woman desires to be raped.
No doubt that this woman has the desire to be raped,
which means she want to be attacked.
Desire to be raped?
Welcome.
As I expected, this shop is too narrow.
Um... Customer-sama?
I'm not a customer.
Please don't mind me.
Is that so...
That place is our adult corner, so kids like you-
Who are you calling a kid, huh!?
I-I'm so sorry, Manager.
Oh, Ippei-kun.
Hey!
What're you doing here?
I-Ippei-kun, you know that little girl?
Is she your girlfriend!?
It's not like that, she's just...
Hey, manager.
Ye-Yes.
What a nice collection you have back there.
I can see you've been collecting a lot of famous stuff.
Did... you recognize it?
Of course.
I can see some of them are limited edition releases,
and even some famous local releases were there.
Are you the one who picked those titles?
What good taste you have.
I should praise you for that.
Thank you so much.
Did you really know those titles?
Of course.
By the way, what's your relationship with Ippei-kun?
Do you want to know?
If that's possible.
When I lost consciousness in the park,
this guy was suddenly using my face as his-
Sh-She's my cousin.
Cousin?
Tha-That's true.
She just arrived yesterday from her village.
Who are you calling your village cousin?
Just let me handle this for now.
'Kay... Okay?
Well, as you please.
Then you should introduce yourself to my manager.
I'm his cousin, Sari.
Sari-chan, eh? What a cute name you have.
"Moe" isn't it?
Hey, are you sure this guy is okay?
I'm this shop's manager, my name is Iwao Kojiro.
Pleased to meet you, Sari-chan.
Take care of me, okay.
Don't say that so highly.
Then, I'll be in the back room.
I'll leave the rest to you Ippei-kun.
I've got it.
Sari-chan as well, please enjoy yourself here.
You're so cute.
Now I get it.
So you're interested in little girls like me, huh?
I'm not interested in lolicon, okay!?
What's the difference for the pervert I met last night?
Pervert, eh?
Ah, welcome.
Um... I want register as a member here.
Ye-Yes.
Now would you fill out this registration form
with your name, address, and your phone number as well.
I understand.
She's very much like her.
Hey.
Huh!?
Is there something wrong with that woman?
Idiot, don't talk to me right now!
I just think that she looks like someone I know.
Who is it?
My old classmate.
Excuse me...
Yes.
I'm sorry if I was mistaken.
Weren't we in the same class in High School?
You're Hosaka Ippei-kun, right?
Chidori...san?
That's right, I'm happy that you remember me.
Of course I remember you.
What a coincidence,
this must be some kind of fate, right?
Is that so?
Ah, sorry.
Right now, I'm about to meet with my friend.
I've got to go right now.
Can I introduce you to my friend as well?
Of course.
Thanks, then I'll be back later.
Sure.
Here.
Your member card.
Thank you.
If you'd like,
shall we get something to eat together?
Just call me when you've got time, okay?
See you then.
See you...
Now's your chance.
For what?
I'm sure that was just a normal invitation for me.
That's not it.
It's your chance to rape someone like her.
I-Is it possible that-
That's right, she has the desire to be raped by a guy like you.
Even a popular girl in my class like her?
Let me tell you something good right now.
That woman,
she's still a virgin, you know.
What is it?
Hey, what do you call this snack?
Unmai stick.
Unmai stick, you say?
That snack was around since I was a little kid.
That's tasty, isn't it?
I can't believe this would be tasty.
The price is cheap and it also comes in many various types.
It also comes in various types?
Did you like it?
I like it.
From now I declare that I shall only eat this Unmai and Pudding,
for the rest of my life.
No, you should eat proper meals as well.
Welcome.
Good day, Hosaka-kun.
Chidori, welcome.
As I promised, I brought my friend.
Eh? Promised?
Didn't I tell you that I'd suggest this store to my friend?
You really brought her here.
Of course.
I brought you a special person right now.
Good day.
Welcome.
Did you figure it out?
Your voice is too loud.
Kujou... Sakura!?
Ding dong, you're right.
Let me introduce you.
This lady used to be a beautiful idol, you know.
She's also a famous idol singer,
Kujou Sakura.
I'm Kujou Sakura.
Pleased to meet you.
Is this... some kind of dream?
What is it?
It's the second girl.
Didn't I tell you before?
That idol girls...
desire to be raped.
He... Hey...
Who exactly are you?
Do you want to know?
I-I'll just stop right here.
Hm, is that so?
I just can let go about Sari's identity for now.
Besides that, I've got something I must do right now.
The girl who I admired since High School, Chidori Yuuma.
And then,
The girl who I recently met, that famous idol,
Kujou Sakura.
I should choose which one will be my first rape.
Their looks don't appear to desire that,
but inside their hearts, they want me to do it.
They want to be raped roughly by a guy,
they desire to be raped.
I'll... I'll make their desire come true.
I'll make them say that desire with their mouths.
They'll say "Please Rape Me"!!!
I'm sorry to make you wait, Chidori.
You're late!
I'm sorry, something happened.
Since you're the one who's late, today you'll treat me.
Um... Of course.
I was joking.
No, but-
I'm the one who invited you yesterday,
that's why it'll be my treat.
Sure... I got it.
Good then, shall we?
You remember that one time,
Restourant Totosu
when Ritsuko pretended to be a ghost and showed up at the window,
then Maeda-sensei screamed at her,
"Who is that, show yourself right away!?"
I'm the only one who talked about myself from a while ago.
Ah... I'm sorry, I was just nervous.
Chidori... is beautiful and was pretty famous in class back then.
No way, is it possible that you're already drunk?
Ah, my cellphone. Sorry, I'll be back soon.
Sure.
Alright, it's my chance.
This much I guess?
No, It should be more-
No way!
I-Is she going to be okay?
I hope she won't know about this.
The rest would be after Chidori drinks this wine.
She'll go to the restaurant's toilet.
After she goes in there,
I'll wear this mask.
Then I'll come inside her toilet space.
I'll force her to undress,
I'll thrust her into pussy with my penis as I'd like,
then I'll cum inside her a lot!
Then our relationship would be better after leaving this restaurant.
It's a really great plan after all!
I'm just a genius.
I'm sorry.
Then, let's have a toast.
Sure.
Cheers!
Please Rape Me.
Then drink it, with the potion Sari gave me before.
Then after you go to to toilet... I'll rape you for sure, Chidori Yuuma!
Hosaka-kun.
Why? Why?
She wouldn't go to the toilet even once?
Ho-sa-ka-kun!
Are you okay, can you go home by yourself?
Ah, what about you?
I recall that Chidori lives on her own.
Then shall I accompany her to her home? After that-
Shall I accompany you home?
No, I'll be fine by myself.
But...
Don't you think it's too dangerous for girls like you when it's this late?
I thought it would be more dangerous if I stayed with you.
Did-Did she know!?
I was joking, okay.
Don't forget to call me back.
Eh, seriously?
Don't joke with me!
What? She doesn't wait for a taxi?
Is it possible that she's about to-
This shortcut through park was silent and dark, so no one would use this way.
Even though it's a shortcut,
it's not a good way for girls like her to use.
It's another chance for me.
Then,
shall we go?
I made it.
Did I lose myself and drink too much?
Wha-What was that noise just now?
Le-Lecherous?
No, It's not like you-
Oh shit.
Huh?
Hey, Chido-
Wait, I shouldn't call her by her name.
Hey, are you okay?
Inside a toilet stall like this, there's a defenseless woman like her.
There's no way I would give up on this chance.
This is...
The virgin pussy of Chidori Yuuma!
Wh-What is this?
Are you already awake?
What is this about!?
Someone please help me! Someone-
Shut your mouth...!
Would you shut up?
Do you want something horrible to happen?
Wh-Who are you?
Me... I'm just... Um...
By the time you wear that mask,
you'll be a mysterious rape-man,
rape's devil or just a plain rapist.
I should called you Masque de Rape.
Masque
de
Rape
I'm mysterious rape-man,
Masque
Masque de Rape.
de
Rape
You're just a lecherous pervert, huh?
Silence, don't call me a pervert!
You went into the girls toilet looking like that, isn't that some kind of pervert thing!?
I-I know the truth, you know...
I know that you desire to be raped.
Desire to be raped?
There's no way I would have-
This is Chidori Yuuma's pussy.
You're not going to-
This is it! This is how Chidori tastes!
Wa-Wait... please listen to what I said-
This taste,
I can't hold back!
It's salty.
No, that's because I just peed.
That's why... stop it.
Then,
Shall I make you lick mine?
What did you say?
Don't let that filthy thing get any closer to me.
Open your mouth, huh!
No... stop it-
If you won't listen to me, do you want something to happen to your best friend?
This girl is that famous idol, Kujou.
Why do you know that? This doesn't have anything to do with Sakura.
Don't lay a hand on her.
That would be your choice.
You cheater, I'll do as you say.
I don't want my body to get defiled, that's why... please...
That's if you could satisfy me with your mouth, okay?
What's wrong? Just do it quickly.
I-I got it.
This...
This feels good!
What is this?
As I thought, it was supposed to be like this.
It's too big, stop it!
I don't get what you're saying.
I can't just hold back with all this heat.
Damn-
You'll have to drink a lot of my sperm.
Is she angry?
Um...
Just as you promised,
now you'll let me go.
What is it?
You're... this thing is...
You're...
dripping wet like this, is it possible that-
Th-That's not-
St-Stop it-
Stop it!
If you want to be raped, why don't you be honest about it.
Don't joke with me, who would want to do it with you!?
There!
No!
Then as you desire, I'll forcefully thrust it inside of you.
What's the matter?
What is that?
That can't be... It got bigger than before.
Tha-That thing will thrust inside of me?
Sure it will.
If I'm getting raped with that kind of thing...
I-It's nothing.
Wa-Wait a minute, that thing-
Be happy, your virginity-
How do you know that I'm a virgin?
I'll take your virginity right now!
It hurts... more than that-
It's impossible-
It hurts!
As I thought, you were a virgin.
It's the same thing Sari told me.
This is what you wanted, right?
I don't want it-
This isn't what I wanted-
Eh, It's kind of strange...
Is it true that Chidori had the desire to be raped?
Then I'll just wait until I'm cum inside of her.
Quickly... just quickly release it.
Shall I do it then?
It'll a bit painful inside of you.
What will you do?
Do as you please.
Then I'll do what I wanted!
Not yet... It's not over yet is it?
I can't... hold it-
Quickly, just let it end.
Just hurry!
Do you really want it that badly?
I'll cum a lot inside of you!
I-Inside-
Not inside-
Please don't do that!
It's already too late!
Please, not inside.
I beg of you, please release it outside.
Not inside!
It's cumming inside... there's hot stuff inside my of stomach.
It's not over yet.
That a lot of cum inside of me...
You're cumming a lot!
Wait... you're-
It's horrible...
Even Chidori would cry about it.
Just now, you said Chidori?
A
.
I said something wrong again!
No, I just looked at your student card, alright?
I don't remember that!
You're...
Is it possible that-
I-I'm just mysterious rape-man, Masque de Rape!
I'll be back to rape you again.
I'll see you again, farewell.
You know... I think I just did something amazing back there.
Ignoring me, huh?
Someday I'll rape you,
rape you,
rape you...
What's this?
There's something touching my thing down there...
Um...
Why is this girl touching my penis like this!?
This girl is the most difficult woman to handle in this world.
If I wake her up the wrong way, she won't let me go that easily.
I just noticed, I can see this girl's breasts!
Those... Those are Sari's breasts.
This means that-
I'll let my breasts make your penis cum.
She wants me to do that!?
I want you to return that Unmai stick
What? What do you want me to return?
Give me,
I want you to return that stick thing to me.
What's wrong with her?
I can't open it.
That's because it's not a Unmai stick, but it's my pen-
I got it.
She's still dreaming about that.
Thanks for the meal.
Don't stretch it out!
I-It hurts, but it feels good!
Wait-
Hey Sari, would you put your face closer to it?
You want to eat it, right? There, you've almost got it.
Unmai stick.
I want to eat you.
This is bad...
This is becoming too intense, I'm going to cum before she could even start sucking it.
Sari move your face closer.
There, open your mouth.
I can't hold it-
I-It's going to come out!
Unmai stick, It's hot...
But it feels good.
Then before she wakes up-
U... Um...
Eh?
Hey.
Ye-Yes.
Explain to me what happened here!
This is... a really difficult situation to explain... and the result would be-
Anyways, what happened!?
It's about...
I'll just die.
I approve of it, kill yourself!
Yes, sir!
Goodbye, my life...
Today inside of Hosaka Ippei's peaceful apartment,
there's a loud screaming voice from some hopeless man...
In my ass...
Please don't put a Unmai stick into my ass~!