Seichi has the potential to use magic.
That means this story is about one lonely virgin, it happened a month ago.
Something happened in the middle of the night.
That night, Seichi was working hard as usual.
I can't go on like this, I'll take a rest for now.
Spring was almost over, but you could still feel
the coldness of the wind that night.
But that kind of wind was a good fit for Seichi.
What a nice wind.
So, what should I do now?
I've run out of time to complete the assignment.
What's that?
Is it coming from the neighbor's place?
In this place... I'm-
As I thought, it came from the neighbor's veranda.
I'm such a dirty girl,
rubbing my clit in a place like this.
Wha-?!
He saw the girl's naked body in the moonlight.
She sat at the floor and opened her legs wide.
Her finger touched her private place.
As her body got hotter,
she couldn't even notice that someone was watching her.
I... I can't stop.
Is... this a dream?
No... No... it can't be, but as an eroge writer I can't stop watching.
Even my nipples are already so hard.
I just can't...
The girl followed her instincts,
then groped her own breasts
and they started to sway.
That's just awesome, big breasts?
Even the shape is great.
Beautifully shaped, big breasts,
slender hips,
not much fat on her butt,
her proportions are all just right.
The name of this dirty little girl is...
But why would Sanjou-san masturbate on her own veranda?
Seichi had known her for a long time,
but he only knew Sanjou Maki as his neighbor.
Her mother is a professional ex-model,
who modeled for famous brands, so she's very rich.
He knew that she also was also enrolled in a prestigious all girls school in his neighborhood, Outo Academy...
Everyone knows that Outo Academy
is like a school for princesses, so it's very hard to qualify for a place in it.
Of all the students there, her grades is are at the top.
She's also took the position of school council president, and is sometimes called a 'madonna'.
My nipples-
I can feel them.
They're shivering...
I can feel the shiver all the way through me, and it's making me drenched.
My panties...
are already this wet.
Her long sigh and the sound of her breathing,
started to come out from her mouth.
She ignored everything that wasn't there to give her pleasure.
All she wanted was more stimulation.
I... I can't.
I want more.
Rubbing my panties isn't that bad.
But-
It feels more exciting when I touch it directly.
Just a little bit more, her pussy will be...
Touching my own clit in a place like this...
If someone saw me like this...
I'm sure-
He'd take my embarrassing moment.
Then even more than that,
he'd force me to do everything.
Even make me his body slave.
I'd be some dirty masochistic girl!
What a great imagination she has.
He'd rape my pussy, my ass, even my mouth.
He'll fill it with his sticky and smelly sperm.
What a lovely moment.
Is it really that lovely?
He'd rape me every day.
He'd fill and break my virgin pussy with his smelly penis.
She's still a virgin?
With his penis,
he'd thrust and cum into my womb,
and make me pregnant!
Th-That would happen!?
He'd fill my pussy with his penis whenever he wanted.
He'd thrust it into me over and over.
Then nothing could beat the pleasure of that moment.
H-How much longer will this fantasy continue?
No... No way, I can feel it when I keep fantasizing like this.
My clitoris is feeling it-
I'm... I'm about to cum... cumming!
If I'm cumming on this small veranda-
I'm going to grow up like this.
It's great... she's actually there.
Seichi, who saw the girl's beautiful body,
started to feel the coldness of the wind,
and his body reacted to it.
It's bad.
The time which was frozen before, started to move again.
Maki-chan
to Nau
Maki-chan to Nau
Lecherous girls fainting in agony
～ Lecherous girls fainting in agony - Sanjou Maki chapter ～
Sanjou Maki chapter
Um... for now, let me say sorry.
The night wind was blowing,
swaying Maki-chan's long hair.
Behind her fallen veranda wall,
and in the middle of the sound of the wind, she heard him begging for forgiveness.
Eh, why are you apologizing?
Eh, that's because... I was just peeping on you.
I wanted to have the thrill from the possibility that someone might see me,
so I was doing it on my own veranda.
There's no need for you to apologize.
I... I'm sorry.
I told you, you don't have to apologize.
Then, what do you plan to do with me?
What should I do...
You've already discovered what a dirty girl I am, after all.
If you're going to threaten me with something like that,
I don't have any other choice than to do as you say, right?
Um... I'm just a failed novel writer.
For my day job I just work as an eroge scenario writer.
Eroge?
You could said they're games for adults.
You know nothing about them?
Know nothing? They're my favorite after all.
Heh...
But now we know each other's secrets,
which no one else should know.
You can be assured that I won't tell anyone about it.
You're so weird.
Hm... I can't deny that I'm weird.
That's not what I mean.
You even said your own secret just to make sure we're even.
You're such an honest guy.
You can say something like that so easily-
Wait, did she said something different before?
But yes, now I know that you're a good person.
Thanks for that.
Hey, since you know my secret, I've got a request for you.
I want to exchange my virginity with your 'cherry'.
Yes!?
By that time, Seichi's hard penis had showed up,
and Maki started to stare at it.
After that, both of Maki hands took off Seichi's pants.
Maki has discovered something behind them.
Seichi's penis, which was ready to explode.
Maki-chan to Nau
My penis is in contact with her pussy.
It's really hot,
soft,
and slippery.
If there wasn't someone who understood my dirty fetish,
there's no way I would give my virginity to anyone.
You're talking about me?
That's right, I just knew that I should do it when I talked to you.
Would you gladly... accept me?
That's... of course.
I'm so happy, thank you.
But I never thought that my ideal partner would be my neighbor,
what a coincidence.
A penis which gets big like this, isn't just hard.
It's also pretty elastic.
It's really hot and kind of grotesque.
The girl started to lead that sturdy penis
into the entrance of her pussy.
The angle...
Um... it should be here, right?
Then I'll put it in.
No, this big and hot penis is going to-
At the same time it felt like something had been torn apart,
Seichi's penis penetrated her pussy.
Just now... I can feel my virginity has been torn apart!
A-Are you okay, Maki-chan?
Is it painful?
No, it's a necessary moment of my first time... that I need to endure.
It's really great.
I feel so suffocated when it gets tight down there.
You... You sure it's okay?
Okay... it's okay.
This is it, the feeling of my insides...
Being rubbed by a penis like this.
Maki-chan, I can't honestly take all of this.
Without any experience of something like this,
Seichi is
about to reach his limit of endurance.
That's right.
I can't hold it anymore-
My pussy is slowly feeling good.
I'm going to go crazy from this.
No!
Me too.
No, I'm about to cum-
I'm really going to cum!
I can feel something hot inside of me.
Give me a lot of it.
Fill my dirty womb with all of your hot cum!
Cum inside!
C-Cum inside?!
It's okay.
Today... should be my safe day, after all.
It... should be... eh!?
Sperm...
I just want to try cumming inside once.
That's... what I've been thinking about all the time!
That's why you can thrust it in.
I want you to fill my womb with your hot sperm.
Just hurry-
Yes, you can even make me pregnant with this!
Please turn my pussy into your cum dumpster!
Make you pregnant... that's not-
I can't, I'm at my limit... It's coming-
My pussy is full!
It's still coming... cumming... I'm cumming!
It's the first time... I've cum from my pussy.
Even though it's my first time, I can feel that I've grown up!
In that bewitching time in the middle of the night,
Maki received so much stimulation over and over,
her sounds of pleasure echoing around the veranda.
Ah, it's terrible.
I forgot to ask you something important.
Something important?
Your name.
I still don't know your name.
Ah, It's Seichi... Sakonji Seichi.
Hm... It's Seichi-san.
I'm Sanjou Maki.
Well, of course you already know that.
I hope we can get along from now on.
My future husband.
Um... yes.
I hope I'll be getting along with you too... wait, husband?!
Then it was your plan to get pregnant-
The sweetness between their lips as they met,
then Maki's tongue started to penetrate his mouth,
that's
the first kiss between this otaku and the beautiful girl.
Seichi-san.
Seichi-san was working in his room,
while Maki was doing her homework in the living room.
Those needed to be done during this summer holiday.
You're putting on a difficult face right now.
I can even hear your voice from the living room.
Um... yes, this new project is kinda taking a lot out of me.
Really? Then it would be a good idea for you to take a break.
Take a break?
That's right, why don't you put your butt over here?
If you're relieved of all the pain in your penis,
you'd be able to think more clearly.
Right?
M-Maki-chan...
It's okay, Seichi-san, just continue working.
I'll enjoy your thing down here.
Nyan!
Seichi-san's penis is already this big.
I really like it.
Really?
I haven't even touched it yet and it's already twitching like this.
Shall I start then?
This naughty penis...
I really like how it feels.
It suddenly feels good.
I'll reveal all of Seichi-san's
good parts.
Does it feel good, Seichi-san?
I feel so happy.
Seichi-san's penis
is bigger, longer and harder than the other day.
It's really tasty when I lick it.
Th-That's-
Your twitching penis is getting hard and sturdy inside my mouth.
Maki-chan, I can't hold...
That's okay.
You can cum in my mouth, on my face, or even somewhere else.
I can't hold it, I'm going to cum, Maki-chan.
It's out.
A lot of cum.
Seichi-san's sperm
is hot and slightly smelly.
Nyan! It's tasty.
With her face covered in sperm,
Maki wore a suspicious smile.
I'm sure that was a good break for you.
It's getting bigger than before.
I can tell that it wants more.
Shortly after they took one break, Maki started another round.
With Seichi-san lying on her bed,
she gave him a titfuck with her breasts.
I'm sure it'll be enough for your big penis.
Shall I ride on top of you, Seichi-san?
Um... shouldn't we do some foreplay, Maki-chan?
You shouldn't underestimate my erotic pussy, you know?
Here, look at this.
I didn't underestimate it.
Oh, what a great view.
That's why I'll take Seichi-san's penis instantly,
I'll suck it up with my perverted pussy.
Your cellphone is ringing, Maki-chan.
Hmph, what a bad time to call.
Who is it anyway?
Hey, isn't it from Yuki?!
Misono Yuki
Yuki-chan?
Maki parents divorced a long time ago,
and Maki went to live with her mother while her little sister went with her father.
The bond of these sisters,
up to now, against their will
has been broken because they had to live separate lives.
Yes, hello.
Yuki, what's the matter all of a sudden?
You ran away from father's house?
You won't go back?
Yuki, where are you right now?
We're just going to pick up Yuki-chan,
but what's with having to dress up in this suit?
Wait-and-see.
They went out to the station in the neighboring city,
so that they could pick up Maki's little sister.
It was already noon, but there were plenty of people on the train.
I wanted to experience something like this once in my life.
Molester play with a salaryman.
I want you to attack me.
My body feels more sensitive than before.
Even though I'm just touching your thing through your trousers,
is it possible that you already came?
Um... yes... maybe.
But, Maki-chan is already this wet as well?
As I thought.
Maki-chan is such a perverted girl, right?
True.
I like being molested in front of people,
I'm just a perverted girl.
I can feel that behind Seichi-san's trousers
there's some hot, sticky juice.
Eh, is that true?
I don't really want to make my trousers dirty.
Is that so?
Then.
How about this?
There, what a healthy penis you have.
Seichi-san's naughty penis.
I'm being molested on the train by Seichi-san.
I'm being molested...
No!
I'm getting excited!
It's so thrilling...
No... if you touch my clit like that, I'll...
I'm gonna feel it already!
You don't want me to touch it?
Then, I'll just put it in.
No!
Seichi-san's finger is inside my perverted hole.
Please touch me more in there.
Cum... Cumming!
There's a lot of sticky juice coming out from the tip of Seichi-san's penis.
That's right, Maki-chan, do it like that.
No way, your finger feels so good.
Hey... My breasts, I want you to touch my breasts too.
That's really bold of you, Maki-chan.
Hm... that's because...
The bold Maki,
didn't even realize that the other passengers had already noticed what they were doing.
She just easily let them see,
took off that much of her dress,
letting the other passengers enjoy the view.
It's good, if you grope my breasts like that...
My breasts can't bear this feeling.
If you pinch my nipples like that...
I'm shivering all the way inside.
No, it's embarrassing!
This feels really good,
my pussy, my breasts too.
My nipples feel like they'll melt as well.
I'm gonna melt!
Seichi-san naughty penis,
is as hard as steel.
I can feel it shivering.
No, it's really sturdy.
Because Maki-chan hands are really good with it.
Then it's okay to let it out anytime you want.
You too, Maki-chan, it's okay to cum anytime you want.
Yes.
No!
You've even put two fingers inside.
You're stirring up my pussy.
My hole is getting wider.
You can't!
No... I can't hold it-
Your voice is too loud, Maki-chan.
Even if you say that...
I can't hold it when my pussy and my nipples feel this good!
No!
But, I'm almost at my limit.
If I cum right now,
I'll make your dress dirty.
No!
It's okay, just cum on my dress.
I... I can't hold it anymore!
Your penis is shaking and there's lots of sperm on my hands,
it's cumming now.
The train slowed down,
but in a situation like this those two didn't even realize it.
That Maki's little sister, Mizono Yuki, was already waiting for them at the exit door of the train.
The door is already open when their bodies still approach each other like that.
Seichi and Maki, who were still covered in sperm, finally realized their situation right then.
The moment they enjoyed before stopped.
On the other side of them, there was already someone standing there.
Collaboration Works, next project preview.
The protagonist, Hosaka Ippei,
has a strange desire to be raped, but she doesn't have the bravery to follow through.
She went to be raped at the park, but instead she found a beautiful girl lying there.
Being threatened by Sally, she brought her into her own house.
The other day, Sally saw some idols in television broadcast,
and she murmured, 'this girl also wants to be raped, huh?"
Eh!? Isn't this girl the famous idol, Kujou Sakura?!
The desire to be raped, do I have something like that too...?
Original video animation, "Please Rape Me".
Chidori Yuuma, making P, doing P, becoming P.
On sale April 27th 2012.
It's still in our planned release window.
～Should be exclusively TL projects for Ingrid00 (0.0)～