Hey how long are you gonna sleep for?
Let me sleep some more...
No!
I was up late last night...huh?!
ohhaahuuuuu
Hey...come on wake...up!
Just three more minutes...
What the heck!  You're always like this every morning...
You promised to help me with the shop on your days off from school didn't you?
Hurry up and get some breakfast!
I have to do this everyday too you know.
So come on!
Geez...why'd she have to roll me around looking like that?
I'm all hard now...
My Sister-in-law is Obstinate #01
Coochie coochie coo...you're such a good boy~
Bye bye Shino-chan.  Mommy's gotta go to work now okay~?
So you finally woke up.
I'll make some toast.
Mai-san, have you heard anything from my brother?
No...
What the heck is wrong with him.  He could've turned down the job transfer.
There's nothing he can do about it, since it looks like they're pretty busy over there...
But you guys just had a baby!
Doesn't he care about that?
He just left the shop and the baby to you.
What kind of guy does that?  ...That's just me anyway.
You know, if you got a job you'd understand what Shigeki-san is going through too.
So you're gonna work hard for me today right?
Not "today."  Don't you mean "today again?"
Don't get smart with me!
Enough about that.
Come on, hurry up and eat!
You'll help with cleaning up the store right?
At least let me enjoy my breakfast!
No can do, since our part-timer is coming today.
We'll have to clean up nicer than usual, don't you think?
Alright, this looks pretty nice.
Tsutomu-kun, what might you be looking at?
Your technique is perfect as usual.
Why of course, I'm a pro at this don'cha know?
Well I'm gonna go deliver this.  Watch the store for me ok?
Oh yea...if the part-timer shows up have her wait for me.
Watch over Shino-chan for me too.
Thanks!
Alright alright.
I'm so bored.
Eh?  A customer?
Hmm...this flower is...
...definitely an Iris!
That's...actually a lavender.
Lavender?
Oh...of course!  A lavender!
I got it wrong.
I've got to study my flowers some more.
You work here right?  Is Mai-chan here?
No, actually she's out on a delivery right now.
Ah...are you the the new part-timer that's starting today?
Yup!  My name's Takama Kozue.  Nice to meet you.
Ah, likewise.  I'm...uh...Katsuragi Tsutomu.  Nice to meet you too.
Ah, Mai-san's back.
Mai-san!
Ah, senpai!  You made it!
It's been awhile, Mai-chan.
It'll be great working with you starting today!
Same here I'm happy to help out!
Hello?  Shigeki-san?
Well then Kozue-san, please come inside.
(Yea...I just got back from a delivery.)
(Yea...Shino-chan's doing great.)
It smells so nice in here!
(Uh-huh...what, really...?)
Ah...Kozue-san.  You don't have to be so formal with me since I'm younger.
Nope, I have to be!
You're my senior at this shop after all.
I have to follow the rules.
Are you serious...
(Hey hey!)
Shigeki-san just said he'll be coming home tomorrow!
That's great, Mai-chan!
Then Tsutomu-kun.  We'll be fine out here, so go clean the house up.
What, right now?
Well of course!
Shigeki-san's coming home you know.
Guess nothing I can do about that.
Kozue-san, Mai-san's great at using people so watch yourself.
Oh just go!
Alright alright.
Once is enough!
Allllriiiiight.
Geez...he's a cheeky bastard isn't he?
Huh?  My brother didn't come back?
I'm home!  Ah...as I thought.
Welcome back.  Have you eaten?
I ate with everybody else.
Drinking the night away?
That's right...
Seriously what the hell is my brother thinking?
Seriously...
You've had enough.
What are you doing...
Give it...hey, give it ba...!
I said you've had enough...
Who asked you to look out for me?
Mai-san...you're always working too hard.
If I don't then who will??  Shigeki-san's not here...I'm so lone...
Sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
That uh...well...sorry I just suddenly...
Wait Mai-san!  I...uh...I love you...I've always loved y...
Uh...wait...
This is because you said you loved me.
How do you want me to do it?
U...uhh...
You shouldn't be indecisive about these things.
Ah...wait...stop...I can't...!
You can't what?
I'm gonna...!
Sorry...
Geez stop apologizing already.
Well it's because I...I was too quick...
But...it looks like you're still ready to go.
This time...it's your turn.
Wait...if you suck on it so hard...it'll come out!
Ah...it's coming out!
I drank some of your milk.
Isn't it gross?  It's not exactly for adults...
Your milk is really good.
It feels good...
Wait...be gentle...
Please...be...more gen...tle...
Do me...
That tickles!
Let's stay like this for a little while longer.
What happened last night...it wasn't a dream.
No!
Mai-san?
Let's leave it at that.
We...really shouldn't do this.
What happened last night was a dream.  I think so too.
aw :(
Thank you very much!
Ah...Tsutomu-kun.  Time for class?
Yea.
When...are you gonna be back?
I dunno...
I see...have a nice day...
Mai-chan...did something happen?
With Tsutomu-kun?
Oh nothing's wrong!
Did you two have a fight?
You've been kind of weird since this morning.
R...really?  It feels the same as always I think...
Well that's good if nothing's wrong...
If you've got something on your mind, don't hesitate to talk to me ok?
Thanks senpai!
No...I can't go to him...
What's wrong with me...
I can't stop!
Tsutomu-kun...I love you!  I love you!
Tsutomu-kun!!
Tsutomu-kun is all I can think of...
Hello?  Shigeki-san?
Yea...I know you're busy.
You don't have to push yourself.
Yea...we're doing ok over here.
Shino-chan's doing good too.
Ah, Tsutomu-kun?  Yea, he's doing good too.
Sorry...I'm just...a little...
No, it's nothing.
Yea, the shop's...doing good too.
Sorry...honey...good luck...with work!
I love you too.
Did it feel good?
Idiot!  That was cruel!
What'll we do if Shigeki-san found out?
My brother's the one that's cruel!
Leaving such a cute woman all alone!
If I were him...I'd never leave you alone!
I'd always be by your side!
So...don't do this by yourself.
You knew?
It's too lonely doing it by yourself!
I've also always wanted to do this...together with you.
I can't...I've been holding myself back this whole time.
If I don't, I'll be depending on you too much.
That's fine.  You can come to me whenever you want.
So what's up with that?
Shigeki-san...he got it a long time ago...
Serious?  That brother of mine did?
So you're into that sort of thing...
Wonder if I can use it on you too?
I was thinking of you.
You called out my name.
You were listening?
I heard you.
No...this is so embarassing!
But you were doing this earlier.
Don't tease me...
I can't...!
I'm gonna...
Ah...I'm gonna cum already!
I'll make you feel even better.
Do it...do it hard!
Ah...I'm gonna cum!
I can't take it...Tsutomu-kun!
It feels good!
I love you Tsutomu-kun!
Good morning!
Good morning senpai!
You're all smiles today!
What's wrong?  Are you feeling sick?
N...no.  I'll be fine...
Aaand we'll do this...
Mai-chan?
I'm fine...I'm fine, really.
Umm...where's Tsutomu-kun?
He's got a break from classes today so he said he'd help around.
Good morning, Kozue-san.
Good morning.
Well uh...I'll take care of things over here.
Alright, thanks.
Well I dunno what happened, but it seems like things have gone back to normal with you two.
Hmm...though maybe it feels a little different...
R...really?
Yup!
Well anyway, thanks again for helping out.
Sure!  Let's work hard together Mai-chan!
I'll go do some cleaning.
Thanks.
I've set the flowers up out in front.
Wait!  This is too embarassing!
Senpai's gonna find out!
Did my brother do stuff like this for you?
No...
Then...we'll have to enjoy this.
This is really not a good idea!
I'm about to go do some work.
W...wait!
Please, Tsutomu-kun...
Wait...Senpai's...gonna find...
Show me what's going on down there.
Are you serious...?
You're so cute, Mai-san.
This is so embarassing...
People will hear me!
No one will hear you if I do this.
Done!
However I may have been hurt,
I was always soothed by your words in an instant.
The city seemed a blur as I ran through the streets
because my tears just wouldn't stop.
Those days I wanted to see you but couldn't
it felt as if my feelings were trying to test me.
Why didn't I realize
what was important to me sooner?
When I was with you, I was able to be myself.
It's frustrating, but that's what I was able to think.
If I could turn back time,
I would without a doubt be with you.
Translated, timed, & edited by feiX
Hope you enjoyed!