My Sister-in-law is Obstinate #02
I'm gonna...right there...
I'm gonna cum...I'm cumming!
You've become pretty sensitive haven't you, Mai-san?
It's your fault.
You make me feel it all day long.
You've been wanting it all day long.
I'm going to cum again!
Tsutomu-ku...
I'm cumming!
You were really cute.
Don't look at me like that.
It's embarassing...
Mm...wait!  I'm gonna feel it again.
Tsutomu-kun...wait.
What's up?
It's something about Senpai...
About Kozue-san?
Recently, there've been times...when I think that she's been kind of cold to us lately...
Now...that you mention it...
I wondered why she's become like that so suddenly...so I asked her.
And?
She saw us!
Eh??
It's because of you!
Fooling around in the store...
Well you've been enjoying it too, right?
Wait...please!
Listen to me!
I am listening.
Tsutomu-kun...please.
Senpai...she's saying...she's jealous of us.
Jealous?
Yea...
I'm so jealous.
By the way Mai-chan, since Tsutomu-kun's been around, you've been looking really happy.
Really happy you say...
Being alone...is a terrible feeling isn't it?
Did something happen?
No it's not that, but...
My husband...he's so busy with work
that even when he comes home, I often find myself alone.
I was just thinking it's kind of lonely...
Working here, I feel that I can get my mind off of my loneliness.
So that's what's going on...
Tsutomu-kun is a nice one, isn't he?
Yea...
That's so great, Mai-chan.
Lonely, huh?
Are all the husbands in the world this worthless?
And you know...I've got something to discuss with you.
Something to discuss?
Since...you said you loved me, I feel so full of happiness right now.
So that's why...
What is it?  You can say whatever it is.
Will you...go on a date with her?
Huh?  You mean...with Kozue-san?
Ho...hohoho...
Geez!  What are you thinking of?
I don't mean like that!  I'm saying to go out and have a fun time with her.
Geez...what are you getting hard for?!
All right!  I'll go on a date with her.
...so, that's the story.
Thank you Tsutomu-kun!
Please take good care of me today.
S...same here..ah, wait...you don't have to be so formal today you know.
But, when I'm talking with Tsutomu-kun, I feel more comfortable like this.
I see...you're an interesting one, you know that?
You think so?
oogiiiiie
Stop it Tsutomu-kun!  Where are you looking at?
It's embarassing...
It's not just me!
All the guys here, they're all looking at you, Kozue-san.
Is this swimsuit too tight you think?
Not at all!
It's cute!
But what should I do?  I'm so embarassed all of a sudden!
I can't face anybody.
Well, just look at me then.
Even though I said that...
It feels kind of weird.
I'm jealous.
What's wrong?
I was just thinking that you're a different person at the pool than the one I normally see at the store.
Since I don't really know you outside of work.
I feel like the you that was at the pool seemed like a girl and was really cute.
But the you right now really gives off the feeling of a mature woman.
You're very beautiful.
You're a nice person yourself, aren't you?
I'm so happy to hear you say that.
I'm really grateful to Mai-chan for setting me up on a date with you all day today.
But, I was worried.
Worried?
Because I thought you might have looked down on the thing with me and uh...Mai-san.
I really didn't know how to deal with it.
So I pushed you two away.
I'm so sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
Looks like I got carried away myself.
If Mai-chan is happy, then that's all that matters to me.
Tsutomu-kun, please be good to Mai-chan from now on ok?
Kozue-san, we should get back...
Can we be together...just a little bit longer?
Do you want to go drinking somewhere again?
Or...
Or?
What's wrong?  You look so curious.
This is the first time I've come to a place like this.
Really?
Yea...
So I'm a bit nervous.
Ah...Tsutomu-kun!
So soft...
Oh I've got it...I want you to do something for me...
What is it?
I want to be surrounded by these breasts...
down here.
It got big.
Will you do it for me?
But...
Um...could you teach me...please?
You've...never done it before?
I'll show you how.
Amazing...it's so hard.
Try doing it like I showed you earlier.
Ok.
Does it feel good?
Yea, it feels good.
Try it with your breasts now.
Ok...
It's...so hot..
Like this?
You're really good, Kozue-san.
It feels good.
Kozue-san...I'm gonna...
Go ahead...please go ahead and cum.
Cum all you want!
I made a mess.
It's ok.
It makes me happy to see that it felt good for you.
It's warm...
Kozue-san, take a look at the mirror.
You've got such a slutty look on your face.
This is embarassing...
You're so wet.
My body's been feeling so hot for awhile.
Please!  On the bed...
Try putting it in like this.
T...this is embarassing.
I...I want to make love so much...
with you!
I'm cumming!  It's...so good...!
I...I'm home...
You're quite late, aren't you?
Late...or rather...I'm pretty early today...
I called you so many times.
Did you know?
I saw that I got some calls this morning.
But I thought you'd be sleeping, so I didn't call back, that's all.
If you were going to be late, you could have at least called to let me know!
I was so worried this whole time.
Sorry, if you're going to lecture me I'll listen to it later.
Hold it!
I'm sleepy.
I waited for you...
...all night.
Mai-san.
Did you sleep with her?
That's not it...
Liar.  I can tell something's fishy.
Hey!
Mai-san!
I have to punish you...
Answer me truthfully.
You slept with her didn't you?
What are you going to do if I answer honestly?
With an answer like that, it doesn't matter what you say anymore.
That's...
Tsutomu-kun...you're too nice.
Mai-san...
Mai...san...I'm about to cum.\!
Hey?!
You're punishment...
I'm not gonna let you cum.
We'll see about that.
Wait!
No waiting!
I said hold on!
This isn't fair...
I can't let you go anymore!
No...that's...!
I'm going to punish you too.
Wait...I'm scared...stop...
You're the one who told me to go on a date with Kozue-san you know?
So you don't have any right to feel jealous.
Don't move it!
Don't do anything weird!
But...you're so excited.
Does my brother play with this hole here?
So...this makes me the first.
For your first time down here, it's amazing how excited you're getting.
D...don't say that...
It's embarassing!
You should be more honest with yourself.
No...not like this!
Then, you want me to stop?
It's weird...it feels good...
I'm scared!
Plea...uhn!  You're going to rip me apa...ahh!
Good morning, Mai-chan.
Ah, Senpai!  Good morning.
Thank you very much for yesterday.
Ah...it's ok...
Kozue-san!
Tsutomu-kun, good morning.
Are you heading to school right now?
Yea.  Well, I'm off.
Have a nice day.
Tsutomu-kun!
Thank you so much for yesterday.
You're welcome.
See you later!
Senpai...
What's wrong?
Mai-chan...I'm so sorry!  I...
I know.
I heard from Tsutomu-kun.
Since...well, you made him come back in the morning.
Anybody could have guessed what happened.
I'm so sorry!
You don't have to apologize.
If you had fun,
then that's all that matters to me.
Mai-chan...I um...
What is it?
I'm thinking...I should stop working here.
Eh??
Because, if I keep staying here, I feel like I'm really going to fall in love with Tsutomu-kun.
Yesterday, he was incredibly nice.
He was so gentle with me.  I had so much fun.
I thought, "how long has it been since I had so much fun?"
When we went our separate ways it felt like my heart was broken, it hurt so much.
I want to be with him more!  I wanted to fall more in love with him!
Wait a minute, Senpai.
Just because of that, you don't have to quit working here do you?
If I were close to him, I really would fall more and more in love with him.
You wouldn't want that either, right?
That's...not true.
Yes it is...
Mai-chan, you really love Tsutomu-kun.
I can tell.
Tsutomu-kun is yours.
Senpai, please don't quit!  I'm begging you!
But...
If...that's what you're saying
this might be kind of awkward but...
What?
Would you mind if...we shared Tsutomu-kun?
Ehhhhh???
It's from Mai-san.
Hurry home today, ok?
I've got a surprise ready for you.
Surprise?  What's that?
I'm home!
Welcome back, Tsutomu-kun.
Kozue-san!
Just in time!
I just finished cooking dinner.
This is...the surprise?
Not just this.
Kozue-san??
S...top...so sudden...Mai-chan...
Senpai said that she's never used one of these before.
I played around with her a little.
I can't...I'm going crazy!
Are you ok, Kozue-san?
I want you Tsutomu-kun!
W...whoa wait a minute!
But...
You're so cute, Senpai.
Mai-san!  Why are you doing this?
Why??
It's because you're too nice.
I'm...not really...
That's why you're going to belong to both of us from now on.
Belong to...?  What are you talking about?
We talked about it and decided.
I knew that I couldn't keep you just to myself.
Me too!
I haven't been able to think about anything else since we spent that night together!
Eh??  Even you, Kozue-san??
My breasts...it feels so good!
Sen...Senpai...don't...not there!
Tsutomu-kun!
Tsutomu-kun...do me too...please...
No!  Give me more!
Oh Senpai...you're so dirty.
But...I want it!
I didn't know you were such an indecent person, Senpai.
Tsutomu-kun awakened me.
There we go.
Here I go, Mai-san.
Tsutomu...!
My breasts...
I'm cumming!
Morning.
Good morning.
Morning, Kozue-san.
Good morning, Senpai.
It's getting big.
Oh Tsutomu-kun...you're so perverted.
You two are the perverted ones!
Hey.
Let's do it again right now.
Right now??
Your friend down here...is saying he wants to do it.
OHH MAAI GAWWWWWWD!
We'll close the store today, ok?
However I may have been hurt,
I was always soothed by your words in an instant.
The city seemed a blur as I ran through the streets
because my tears just wouldn't stop.
Those days I wanted to see you but couldn't
it felt as if my feelings were trying to test me.
Why didn't I realize
what was important to me sooner?
The days I spent with you, I was able to be myself.
It's frustrating, but that's what I was able to think.
If I could turn back time,
I would without a doubt be with you.
Translated, timed, and edited by feiX
Hope you enjoyed!