Give it back!
Give it back to me!
Don't you want to be
with your papa and mama?
Kill him.
This guy's one of the most
wanted, murdering, perverted bastards.
He's been kidnapping
young girls, raping them...
...and killing them by
chopping their bodies into pieces.
Who cares if one or
two guys like him die?
Find whoever killed my papa and mama.
Yeah, I swear I will.
Just die already!
Manager, someone may catch us!
Yes, but it's so exciting!
If we're lucky, we'll find
something left behind by the suspect.
Search every square inch of the room!
You think we can find
anything in this mess?
That's what a professional does, right?
If you fell from this height, it'd
be impossible to identify the body .
Lucky girl.
Must've grown wings or something.
Mr. Akai, can we come in now?
Yeah, go ahead.
There aren't that many
press people here today.
They're all at the police station.
Did they find out about the
chief's Lolita complex or something?
Huh? You didn't know?
There's a witness!
What?
Did he say anything?
No.
He's still in shock, but...
...it's a woman.
A woman?
The killer was a woman.
A young one.
Mr. Akai...
...how long
have you been there?
Kanie, your woman
may have to wait a while.
I'm going to go look for it.
You were spotted at the scene, too.
Why didn't you find it for me?
The place was completely destroyed.
That tiny earring must
have been destroyed too.
That earring was important to me.
You should know that best of all.
One should be enough.
Anyway, you should
realize the situation.
You killed the client.
Mr. Kanie gave me the wrong target.
It's not my fault.
The result is all that counts!
Then do it yourself!
Don't stay out for too long!
Sawa!
What's up?
Are you okay?
Of course not.
It still hurts.
I have a bald spot and everything.
I'm exhausted.
Come in.
I'll make some coffee.
I prefer tea.
Really strong green tea.
I don't have any.
I brought some.
It's bitter...
It's good!
Sawa...
What?
What will we be
doing ten years from now?
What kind of question is that?
There's only one target.
It's an easy job for you.
You got that, Oburi?
Be on time tonight.
Sawa...
Ten years...
Five years...
Even tomorrow
may never come for us.
All I can do for now
is live life to the fullest.
Your life or even tomorrow's lunch...
No one knows what it'll be.
Akai?
That's right.
...to kill you.
That's why you came here?
You knew that, right?
Get ready.
Your parents were killed by...
...Akai and Kanie.
I know.
...for a long time now.
Promise to come back here.
This guy's a
prosecutor for the DA's office.
He was bribed to ignore the
illegal activities of a big corporation.
He'll be in the last train car in three
minutes, so take care of him there.
He doesn't look like a
government suit type.
Be careful.
I don't want Mr. Akai to fire me just yet.
Who the hell are you?
Don't you know?
Just an ordinary citizen.
Die.
You shitty punk!
You punk!
I'm gonna chop you into pieces!
The one in pieces...
...is you!
Sorry, Mr. Akai.
Oburi, what are you doing?
Don't even try it!
Calm down, okay?
Who the hell was that prosecutor?
A cop from the SWAT team.
Didn't Kanie tell you that?
That guy had a gun...
He tried to kill me!
What do I have to do with that?
I'm going to disappear from your sight.
If you follow me, I'll kill you.
Hold it, hold it.
You promised to do
two more jobs, didn't you?
Do it yourself.
Is Sawa with you?
I'm taking her with me.
I see...
You punk, you caused
me some serious trouble...
What happened?
You!
I thought you died already!
Get away!
Get away from him!
Sawa...
Oburi, hang on!
Hang on!
S-Sawa...
Why are you here?
Can you stand?
I guess...
I'm losing feeling in my left arm...
We'd better take care of you quickly.
Don't move!
Sawa...
Oburi, I won't kill you.
Sawa, thank me.
No, let me go!
No! No!
Stop it!
Kanie, you want to shoot him?
Yeah, I really want to shoot this
punk and splatter his blood all over.
You hear that?
What are you going to do, Sawa?
Oburi, a dog is better
off chained to its master.
Don't...
No...
You didn't have to do
all this just to kill him.
Just killing him isn't enough for me.
You hate him that much?
It's not just that.
It's my hobby.
Hobby?
I really take pleasure in
watching other people's pain.
Nothing else makes me feel like that.
Gross hobby.
Your act really scared me.
I almost thought you'd
betray me for a second...
So, I'll be on my own from now on.
Don't worry.
We already found a
replacement for Oburi.
Where are you going to kill him?
The place where we
made you kill for the first time.
I'm looking forward
to tomorrow's autopsy.
I'm going back.
Why don't you stay tonight?
I have an exam tomorrow.
Why don't you drop out of college?
I look better with
pencils than with guns.
Death caused by massive blood loss.
There are several bullets.
I don't appreciate doing this kind
of stuff first thing in the morning.
We've done most of the
checking before you came in.
Good work.
What's wrong?
This isn't like you...
Did you notice?
What?
I just realized, Mr. Akai...
This place.
It's a parking lot now...
...but this is where that family
got slaughtered a few years ago.
A few years ago...
We did the investigation, you know.
I remember they had a daughter.
She was adopted by somebody.
It was a really sexy girl.
Oburi...
Oburi, I didn't think you
had the balls to kill Kanie.
But in your condition, I
don't think you can beat me.
Right?
This time, I'll nail you myself!
Right now, you don't even
have the strength to pull that trigger!
...not with your left hand.
Sawa?
What's going on, Sawa?
My hand!
You and Oburi...
The one who killed Kanie was me.
Oburi is fine.
The two of you tricked me...
Why?
Do you know how long
I've waited for this moment?
This is for Papa and Mama...
...and for me.
Sawa!
Let's go!
Where the hell were you?
Shut up!
I'm gonna win today!
Go get everybody!
Wait just a little longer...
Pretty soon...
Oburi will be back.