How do you like this building?
Is this a cool place or what?
Yeah...
You're special, you know.
Those ugly dogs in my fan
club don't know about this place.
You're disgusting, you vulgar,
arrogant, retarded celebrity punk...
Just because you have some TV show.
Give me a break.
Who do you think you are?
Shame--
You bitch!
How do you like being kicked
by a retarded celebrity punk?
You old bitch!
Your stinking perfume makes me sick!
You're the disgusting one, bitch!
I'm going to sue you for this...
M-My son is an excellent lawyer.
A punk like you will
be squashed like a bug.
Do you hear me, punk?
We found traces of two bullets...
in the chest and in the head.
I see signs of blood under the skin.
He must have died instantly.
Mr. Akai...
It must have been a very special gun...
The bullets exploded inside his body.
Better check those bullet fragments.
Is the medical team here yet?
They're all in the hospital
because of food poisoning.
Those assholes.
What a waste of our tax money.
What's with granny?
Probably shocked to death.
Looks like it was a heart attack.
Get an autopsy just in case.
So, this guy's a celebrity?
He has seven TV shows a week.
He's a popular comedian.
What a joke.
His usual material is about corpses.
Nobody's gonna laugh at this.
What a tearjerker.
H-He was such a nice guy.
W-Why would anyone kill him?
He was the nicest guy I ever knew.
I can't stand breaking
up our team like this...
Mr. Ogata at the studio?
His outraged fans are
rushing to the location.
We can see how popular he was...
Also, according to our sources,
this case may involve organized crime...
Well done.
I feel sorry for that old lady.
People die everyday.
Come here.
I'm not in the mood today.
Give it to me.
I know...
But...
Sawa...
I have enough problems already.
Anything wrong?
Can't you feel it?
Get on top.
Be more punctual, Oburi.
Who are we doing?
Which one?
All of them.
We've called someone else in.
You take care of the one in front.
The other one will take care of the rest.
What did they do?
The three of them are child molesters.
They're going to pay for what they did.
There's another one besides me...
How about this weekend again?
Call me when you can.
You know our usual activity...
My wife just isn't
good enough, you know?
Surprised?
You did it?
Right.
The reward for each
adult is the same as always.
Take it from Kanie later.
You stink, Mr. Akai.
Oburi, I don't have
an easy job, you know.
The stink from the corpses
makes my eyes water all the time.
And that rotten smell is so strong...
It's no wonder I always stink.
Mr. Akai...
Did you think about what I asked you?
Sure.
I don't want to hold you back.
Wow...
Your generosity makes me feel weird.
However...
...you have to take
care of three more jobs.
I knew you'd say that.
It's between you and me, isn't it?
We've got to be fair to each other.
Right, Kanie?
Isn't that right?
Mr. Kanie, I'll do my best to be on time.
What are you doing?
You suck!
You're so slow!
You retard!
Give it to me!
Hey, buddy, give us the ball!
You got my jacket dirty.
It wasn't that nice, anyway.
Go home and wash it yourself, okay?
He's pretty good.
That's why I need you.
1 05 yen is your change.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
You look good in that uniform.
You...
Tastes good.
This must be a new flavor.
Want some?
You asked Kanie
where I worked part-time?
So...
What?
Tell me your name.
Sawa.
As in ''the sand you can't hold''
and ''the feather blown by the wind.''
Remember that.
Is that your real name?
Of course.
I'm...
Oburi.
You're Oburi, right?
How much do you know about me?
Are you mad?
No, I'm just...
Kanie told me your name, that's all.
Is Oburi your real name?
Yeah, it is.
It's a very unusual name.
Everyone says that.
Do you have a family?
Nope.
You?
Me neither.
We're alike, aren't we?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Anything.
I'll tell you.
What is Akai to you?
He's...
...my guardian.
Same as me, huh?
What a strange coincidence...
...we have here.
Those earrings
must be very special to you.
Why's that?
You were wearing
them the last time, too.
They look weird, yet really beautiful.
They're...
...made from the
blood of my papa and mama.
It's kind of my lucky charm.
Let's go!
Where is it?
Your place.
Shit...
That's...
You know him?
He's a Hollywood movie star, isn't he?
Some of my classmates are fans.
But I didn't know that
he had a twin brother.
They'll be here in a few minutes.
This is the third celebrity.
Kill...
...the right one.
If I get the wrong one, I'm sorry.
He has three bodyguards, so be careful.
Where do I get him?