One day, the incident began, after school.
It was when I was late because of my after school duties.
Sheesh, she uses us like slaves.
I wonder if Fujino went home without me.
Huh?
What in the world is that Fujino doing in a place like this?
She's doing such a thing on my desk...
Could it be that... She's imagining me while she's masturbating.
No, this isn't what it looks like. This is, umm...
No no no. Like I said, I wasn't trying to peep.
Uh... Sorry Fujino.
I'm sorry.
Now that I think about it, this was but a prelude to the incident.
The Animation
TL Note - The yellow sign says The Convenience Store for a Man and a Woman".
TL Note - The green sign says "Handle the items delicately please".
But man,
this sure is amazing.
Wha... you want this one?
I still can't quite grasp Fujino's tastes...
Why are those two in a place like this?
It makes it harder for me to shop.
Alright, I'll go buy this.
Could it be that...you want to buy more?
Fujino, that...
are you really going to buy that?
If you take a picture in it before purchase, it will be 30% Off...
Don't tell me you're going to try this.
Wow, this is kinda weird.
Amazing... it's all see-through.
You can't do that, then we can see "it" very clearly too.
That is... kinda off-season yet kind of...
Fujino, I can't hold it any...
So you were feeling it too, Fujino.
It's all wet down here already.
Sheesh, those damned fools.
They don't even care where they do it.
Umm... Excuse me...
Huh?
Is somebody using the dressing room right now?
I've been waiting you know.
(The comics, Hatsu Inu 2 and Hatsu Inu 3 are out right now!)
No!!! You can't, it's still in use at the moment!!!
Pardon me.
Is that right..?
Sheesh, why do I have to do this for them.
Crap, I'm about to...
You're pretty convenient at times like these, Fujino.
I mean, you don't really have to lower your voice or anything right?
Alright. Lets go now.
Hm? What are those DVDs?
After that day, Fujino started acting in a very strange way.
Fujino.
You know...
Wha... Fujino?
Fu-Fujino.
So Fujino went home.
I cant agree with this.
I'm glad if you're breaking up with Fukaya but
this sort of confusing thing makes me uneasy.
I believe I at least have the right to ask.
Huh. Wha-what is this?
I see, so that's what it's about.
If that's the case, I can cooperate with you.
Sheesh, every time you come here it's this.
This isn't a love councling office you know.
I-I'm sorry.
But I really don't know what the hell is going on.
Why did Fujino suddenly distance herself.
Well, I suppose it was right for you to come here in this particular case.
You were looking at stuff like this in front of Fujino weren't you?
Thi-this is...
Fujino probably thought that she wouldn't be
able to satisfying you with her quiet self.
But that's not true at all.
That part about Fujino sure is strange.
I-I'm going to go look for Fujino.
By the way, how do you know about this teach?
Shu-shut up... Just go find Fujino already.
Uh, right.
But man... If Fujino's started to worry about how Fukaya feels...
I guess it means they're getting pretty serious.
Dirty words huh? I suppose they are important.
Alright, then lets have you remove your clothes first.
Oh? Isn't it that you want to be able to talk more during sex?
If that's the case, we have to do some training.
Come on, hurry hurry.
You came to me because you couldn't solve it yourself right?
Then you have to listen to what I tell you.
This is getting interesting.
I'm going to have a lot of fun playing with Fujino today.
That won't do. You have to strip every last piece off.
Show me all of it.
Yes, I'm going to embarass you more and more.
Fujino, you are so cute.
How do you feel?
I bet it's oddly embarassing to be the only naked one.
Spread your legs more.
Oh my. You're this hot already.
Did you get wet, just by being watched?
It's alright, just feel the pleasure.
If it starts to feel good make sure you let your voice out.
You got that?
You let your nipples get so hard. How should I play with you next?
Well then. How about you show me your masturbation next?
So you're fine with the way you are. What if Fukaya gets bored of you?
Hey, wait!
Hatsu inu 2
Where in the world has that Fujino gone off to?
I bet it's really embarrassing to masturbate while another girl is watching.
Come on, you can be louder than that.
Say stuff like, "It feels so good" or " More, more".
You're starting to feel pretty good aren't you?
Are you telling me to put this vibrator in?
Fine, I get it. Sheesh.
You're a really perverted girl you know.
I'll totally mess you up.
There, doesn't that feel good?
I can hear the dirty noises coming from done there.
Fujino.
A-amazing. If you did such a thing right in front of me I...
I'm starting to get excited too.
Did you just cum?
Wha, where did you get that?
Are you telling me to join in too?
You've got to be kidding me!
Why do I have to do such an embarassing thing?
Fine, I get it.
I'll just have to show you the kind of dirties noises that I can make.
She doesn't seem to be home and there doesn't
seem to be anywhere else that she might be at.
There, I'm pu-puting it in.
Wha-what is this? It's so big.
It's coming deep inside of me.
I-I'm gonna... I cant....
I wonder if it's because you're watching me.
It feels so much better than when I usually masturbate.
Wha-what are you doing?
It would be pointless if I was the only one who felt good.
Here, I'm coming Fujino-san.
How does it feel to be fucked by a girl, Fujino?
I bet ifs your first time.
Hey, don't be so rough. No...
Oh no, it feels so good.
It's rubbing my clitoris...
Doesn't it feel good for you too?
You should just let your voice out...
My hips keep moving by themselves.
I'm gonna cum... I'm about to cum.
Why do did I have to go too.
Hey, wa-wait a second.
You're such a fool, like something like that would
change how Fukaya feels about you.
You're the only one who doesn't understand.
Fujino!
I'm sorry, I...I guess I made you feel horrible.
I don't think that you have to say dirty things to me.
Since the first time I met you... you had this weird thing about you...
But with all those thing together... I was able to get to like you.
Come on, let's go home. I'll walk you back.
Fu-Fujino... could it be...
Fu-Fujino...
You're wearing...
Could this be... this is the way she wants it to play it out today?
Fu-fujino...
Where do you learn such a thing?
Fujino was trying so hard to show her feelings through actions...
As if she was trying to make up for her lack of words.
The-the lotion is so slippery and...
I regreted from the bottom of my heart, that I let Fuji no worry so much.
Even though she deals with me so admirably.
Fu-Fujino, I'm going to...
So-sorry, I got it all over your face.
Fu-Fujino.
We haven't done it for a while so I'm still ready.
Fujino, your pussy is a lot more warm than usual.
It's almost as if you were just having sex.
I can't hold it...
Fujino...
I'll be the one making you feel good at the end.
Here I go Fujino.
Fujino... Fujino... Fujino.
Fujino.
Fuji no, I'm going to.
I guess Fujino had quite a tiring day.
Th-That sound is.
Co-could it be?
I-I knew it.
Fujino, what in the world were you doing today?