KENNEL
TOKOROZAWA
KENNEL TOKOROZAWA
I'm a dog. My name is Rin Tin Tin.
They say Rin Tin Tin is a fine name for a dog,
but in Japanese it sounds like "penis."
Th-This is Kamonegi Chikako, the daughter of this shop's owners, but I call her Chika.
I'm head over heels for Chika,
but in a platonic way.
Who am I kidding, platonic?
Come here, Rin Tin Tin.
Ouch!
What are you doing in here?!
Wh-When we get married, I'll scrub your back each morning, Chika.
Did Rin Tin Tin wake you?
He never leaves me alone!
That's a man in love for you.
You make such a nice couple.
That's what happens when you live together.
Nature may well take its course.
What are you talking about?!
Don't follow me!
Are you here again, Rin Tin Tin?
One, two, one, two, one, two...
All right! Stretches!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five...
I-I haven't done anything...
Rin Tin Tin's really fond of you!
I almost feel pity for him.
What do you mean?
He's so devoted that it'd be nice to give him a chance.
Stop it, Tsuruta!
Don't give up!
Have you heard that she and the dog are an item?
What do you mean, "an item"?
They live together and everything!
Wow! Incredible!
What are they whispering about?
Kamonegi?
Can I talk to you?
Are you a dog lover?
My parents have a pet store, so for me he's like a human.
Like a human?
Think about your future.
You can't legally marry a dog.
Even if you love each other, you'd have to worry about other people's opinion.
Huh?
In addition, you're still only in high school.
Do you understand what I mean?
Why are you spreading rumors about me, Tsuruta?
What are you talking about?
Don't follow me all the time!
Just my luck. It seems a lot of strange rumors are circulating about me.
Pretty soon I'll be unable to attend school.
Are you Kamonegi from the second year?
Humans are far better than dogs, girl.
What? Stop it!
I'll show you how good a man is in bed. You'll love it!
Rin Tin Tin!
We'll get you for this!
I guess you can be dependable.
Thanks. I'll repay you later.
W-Wait a minute!
Hump, hump!
Have I said that you're allowed to do something like that?!
I-Is this the thanks I get?
Hump, hump, hump...
Chika wants to become a dog groomer.
Dog grooming seems like a difficult job.
I'm not very good at crafts.
Don't worry. You just have to practice!
You can just practice at home, can't you?
Good idea! Let's get back
to Chika's and practice!
Huh? Where is Rin Tin Tin?
He was here a minute ago.
Maybe he saw what's coming.
Rin Tin Tin!
Hump, hump...
This is the best way to summon Rin Tin Tin.
Chika's future as a dog groomer depends on you, Rin Tin Tin.
Are you up for it?
But I don't want to be a guinea pig.
Is this how you treat your sweetheart?
Can't you do such a small favor for Chika?
Look, what about this?
But that's a poodle.
Poodle clipping is part of the basics, after all.
I-I find it hard to say no.
There's not that much of a difference. Go for it!
Don't worry about failing. You're only practicing.
Stay still, Rin Tin Tin.
You already caused irrecoverable damage!
A-As I thought...
We'll pretend like nothing happened. Just continue.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Just shave off more so it looks balanced.
How's that?
Look at him now!
What should I do?
I know.
There's only one way to fix this!
We'll need to be much
more daring. Like this!
A punk dog?
A punk dog? That sounds tough.
Don't laugh at him. He's very sensitive.
You look great, Rin Tin Tin.
You look so handsome now that Chika might be up for it tonight!
He must be Japan's most sexually perverted dog.
Just look at him!
I-I don't think I'll ever get up again.
I-It's not always easy growing up, but don't give up, people!
Chika, decide. It's your fault that Rin Tin Tin lost faith in his manhood.
He's still so young.
What do you mean?
You know what we mean.
Rin Tin Tin needs your love now.
Not as an owner, but as a woman.
What are you talking about?
Here.
What's that?
It's a gift certificate for a hotel.
We won it in a lottery at the mall.
You'll need the right environment.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it? You're the only one who can help Rin Tin Tin!
Look there!
I'm so d-depressed that I want to die.
I wanted to m-marry Chika
and have lots of puppies.
But it was a hopeless dream.
Rin Tin Tin!
Don't do anything stupid!
I wasn't serious.
Chikako, you need to take responsibility.
It looks as if he bit his paws.
It's your fault!
Oh no...
Now, the two of you must go!
Nekobouzaki
I-Is this what you call a sentimental journey?
What am I doing here?
What am I doing here with a stupid dog?
Akakura
B&B
There sure are a lot of couples.
Why do you have a sea
cucumber on your head?
I-It's my friend!
It's half melted.
I just want to die.
She wants to die?
Yes.
She's here alone and seems tired of life.
It sounds serious.
Don't let her out of your sight.
G-Got it.
I-It's my friend!
Throw out that disgusting sea cucumber!
TESTAMENT
N-No way!
Rin Tin Tin!
Sh-She ran out towards the cape!
Damn! Follow her and stop her!
O-Okay!
Rin Tin Tin! Where did you go?
Rin Tin Tin!
Hey there!
What a coincidence meeting you here.
Are you taking a walk?
Huh?
The sea is nice, isn't it?
When you look at the ocean, it seems problems just fall away, don't they?
My problem is much bigger than the sea.
U-Um, feel free to open your heart to me.
I can't tell you about Rin Tin Tin's and my problem.
If you fall down from here,
you won't survive, will you?
Hey, hey, how about talking it over with a cup of tea?
Well, um...
He's hitting on me.
This is better than I expected!
I'm alive again!
This is going well. Tonight, maybe...
This is going well. I can probably prevent her from killing herself.
Hm? What's he doing?
Rin Tin Tin!
Wh-Why do you have an
octopus on your head?
I-It's my friend?
Geez!
Is it gone now?
Yes, you look fine again.
Why would such a pretty girl
want to kill herself?
Finally! I've been waiting
for this for 17 years!
What now?
It's my friend!
Are you all right?
Right, can we meet here tonight?
I want to show you something.
Huh? What is it?
A turtle!
A turtle? Do you mean your...
When you get to see it, you'll realize how precious life is!
See you later!
He's moving so fast!
Maybe we should wait a bit, though.
It gets pitch dark when the clouds hide the moon.
Someone's coming. Are you there?
You're breathing so heavily.
Not so fast...
Not there!
When you get to see a sea turtle lay her eggs, you'll realize how precious life is.
Be quiet now.
They seem to be certainly here already.
Hump, hump, hump, hump, hump...
Hump, hump... Hump, hump, hump!
Hump, hump... Hump!
Hump?
...ump.
Now I understand why she
wanted to kill herself!
Wait! It's not what you think!
Wait! Hey, wait!
I-It was probably better this way. Yeah.
L-Love grows through
adversity. Hump, hump.
Yokoyama Kakugen, 43.
Father of two and a math teacher at Tokorozawa Academy.
M-Moreover, he is my, um archenemy.
Shinzanji Temple
Right now, h-he leads a school c-camp.
Then we eat watermelon.
I'm getting bad vibes.
Shinzanji Temple
Good morning!
We've waited a long time, Sensei.
Now, now.
So you're here as well, Kamonegi?
Yes. I don't think dog grooming is right for me, so I figured I'd study further.
I see. Well then, let's start!
Hump, hump!
What are you doing, Rin Tin Tin?
Kamonegi's looking at me intently.
She's normally so lifeless.
How about a little break?
After lunch, we'll continue with English.
Sensei, can I ask you something?
How exactly do you calculate the derivative here?
She's blushing!
Hump... Hump...
Has she fallen in love with me?
This morning, she threw herself into my arms.
What should I do now?
Has something happened?
You could say that.
Out with it, then.
Oh, I think one of my students has fallen in love with me.
Is that really true?
Yeah, what a pickle!
Take me, Sensei!
Do you see that?
Why isn't he at his own place?
Did you see how he sat and helped her when we had homework?
Uh, e-eat more meat, meat!
Don't you want it yourself?
I have to watch how much meat I consume, because of my cholesterol.
Eat some more, so that you can keep up with the lessons.
Someone could hurt himself, Rin Tin Tin!
No mutt will come between Chika and me!
Look, sparks are flying between them!
What a stupid love triangle.
Let's start the test of courage, okay?
A boy and a girl will form a pair to find the sign and write down the symbol on it.
We'll pick them using this list.
This wasn't mentioned in the description of the camp.
I want the English teacher.
Of course!
This will be fun!
Let's see. Wakabashi and Harukawa.
No way!
And the couple you all wanted to see, Master Kakugen and Kamonegi!
Success!
Let's go, Kamonegi. You're safe with me.
O-Okay.
Th-This isn't good.
Come!
We're off.
Do you see that? They're holding hands!
The old man knows what he wants.
Disgusting!
I'm easily frightened!
Help!
Do you know what happened here ten years ago?
Do you have to talk in such a scary voice?
It was a moonless night just like this.
It was just a cat.
God, I was so scared!
Stupid of me!
Come, Kamonegi.
H-Hold on to me too!
I'm not going to be upstaged by a dog!
I'm not going to be upstaged by an old man!
They have murder in their eyes!
Never mind the test of courage.
This is more fun.
As long as the dog is with her,
I haven't a chance.
Luckily I came prepared.
Here you go, Rin Tin Tin.
Fetch.
He's just a dog.
He's probably lost our trail by now.
Bone, bone... Bone!
Where's the sign?
It should be here somewhere.
What idiot placed the sign here so that everyone could find it?!
Did you find it?
N-No, there's nothing here.
He'll stop at nothing!
It's very scary.
Maybe it's further in here.
Are you sure?
I can't do this! Let's go back!
A snake!
Did it bite you?
It may have been a viper.
Huh? What should we do now?
I'll get help.
No! Don't leave me here!
Right, go get some help!
I'll wait here with Kamonegi.
Are you sure about this, Kamonegi?
Sensei, don't!
G-Go by yourself, old man!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean? Are you saying I should go?
Hump, hump!
Rin Tin Tin!
I can't leave her alone with that dog!
Shouldn't we we do something?
Wait, this could be fun.
A perverted dog against a lecherous teacher!
Stop arguing! Just call
an ambulance, all right?
Help me!
Kamonegi!
Don't move. The poison could be spreading.
Then why are you dragging me?
Well, you know, out here, no one will see us. Wait, forget it.
First and foremost, we have to suck out the poison before we can get help.
Huh? But the snake bit me in the butt.
Is this the time to be worried about that?
Don't be afraid. After all, I'm your teacher.
And after all, I'm your faithful dog.
Are you going to gang up on me?
You don't want to die, do you?
Of course not, but...
Oh, I know!
It's embarrassing, so one of you has to look away,
while the other one sucks out the poison.
Who's going to turn around?
They went for it! Now I can sneak away.
Okay, let's settle the matter with rock-paper-scissors.
The dog seems very clever,
but a clever dog is still just a dog.
His paws are only fit for paper.
Rock, paper, sci...
Love always finds a way!
No way.
Why did I have to say anything?
But I guess I'd rather it be him.
He sees me naked all the time anyway.
Okay, then! Wait a minute!
Turn around, Sensei.
How's it look?
Hurry up!
What are you really licking?
Wh-Where did the dog lick you?
That's not important!
Where did you lick her, you mongrel?
Now it bit me!
Help!
What kind of teacher are you,
leaving me here?
Can I lean on you, Rin Tin Tin?
What, have you been bitten too?!
Ouch. It does hurt a lot.
Rin Tin Tin!
Chika!
Can you walk, Chika?
You won.
You're the best, Rin Tin Tin!
Now you only need to get better.
Rin Tin Tin!
It wasn't a viper, fortunately.
So I-I'm ready for lots more new adventures.
English Translation
Timing
Editing
Special Thanks
M74
Collectr
Studio Paizuri
AFTER A MANGA BY
MAKI ŌTSUBO
(YOUNG SUNDAY)
Rin Tin Tin
JIMMY ŌNISHI
CHIKAKO
MIINA TOMINAGA
CHIKAKOS MOTHER
MARIKO MUKAI
KAKUGEN YOKOYAMA
TOSHIYA UEDA
OTHER VOICES:
HIDEYUKI UMETSU
DAIKI NAKAMURA
KIYOYUKI YANADA
YUMI TAKADA
SANAE MIYUKI
SATOKO KITŌ
MAYUMI KONDŌ
CASTING
81 PRODUCE
SCRIPT
YUKIYOSHI ŌHASHI
DIRECTION/STORYBOARD
SEITARŌ HARA
CHARACTER DESIGN
KATSUMI HASHIMOTO
ANIMATION DIRECTOR
TOSHIHARU SATO
KATSUMI HASHIMOTO
BACKGROUNDS
MOMONORI TANIGUCHI
SOUND PRODUCTION
MIWA IWANAMI
MUSIC
KUNITOSHI TOJIMA
SOUND EFFECTS
YUTAKA INOUE
(ANIME SOUND)
ED SONG
"KOI KAMO SHIRENAI"
MUSIC: TAIMARU FUKUDA
PERFORMER: MARIKO
ANIMATION STUDIO
ANIMATION 21
DIRECTOR
HIROSHI SASAGAWA
A FUJI TV-PRODUCTION
AT HOME WITH AKIKO
Dear 120 million viewers, welcome. I am Akiko Yagi from Fuji TV.
What did you think of "Kennel Tokorozawa"?
For those of you who have seen the whole movie,
we present this special program, "At home with Akiko."
If you don't want to see more, just turn your TV off.
And now, here's our guest, Rin Tin Tin.
Come in, Rin Tin Tin!
Here I am! Over here. Here!
No, what are you doing! Not there!
Rin Tin Tin! Stop it, Rin Tin Tin!
Calm down, Rin Tin Tin!
Sit down!
How are you doing?
Have you calmed down?
I thought Rin Tin Tin was a German Shepherd.
You look more like some sort of movie monster than a German Shepherd.
Look, you're totally filthy.
Down, down, down!
Upon reflection, you must be Rin Tin Tin. How nice you are!
I've heard that you have a really good sense of smell.
Now we get a sample of Rin Tin Tin's fantastic flair.
Rin Tin Tin Smell-Along!
Here we have three shoes.
Let's see if Rin Tin Tin can guess which one belongs to one of Fuji TV's announcers.
Rin Tin Tin can barely contain himself.
Here we have a pair of shoes from the same owner.
When you smell them, you'll know what to look for.
Here you are.
Are you ready?
He smells his way up one shoe at a time.
He liked that shoe. Now he goes to the black one.
It also smelled good.
What? No, no, no, no, no!
He can't decide.
The red shoe?
Is that the right shoe?
How fast you are!
Now, here's the other shoe. Let's see if you were right, okay?
It was the red shoe! How clever you are!
But of course, all dogs have a  good sense of smell.
You must have smelled something familiar?
The shoe belongs to a certain Jimmy Onishi's manager.
How are you?
Now you've seen an example of Rin Tin Tin's amazing sense of smell.
Rin Tin Tin seems to be feeling a bit off right now, so we'll take a break.
Next, we'll talk with Kennel Tokorozawa's animator, Otsubo Maki.
Excuse me, can't I say something? My only line was "Hump, hump."
You're a dog.
- Dogs might well think otherwise.
Want to say something? Here you go.
Thanks so much!
And here we have our guest, Jimmy Onishi!
Thank you for coming here.
How did it feel when you got this role as a voice actor?
I was just happy to get a job.
So you were happy?
Absolutely.
Really...
You bet.
Did you get any advice for this part?
Not to do anything I couldn't handle.
How did it feel to act the part, then?
I couldn't handle it.
Oh? I thought you did well.
Indeed.
Not really. The staff said they had to administer a lot of beatings.
There was no real acting involved.
I mostly made a lot of humping sounds.
So were you reading dialog lines?
Yes, there was a lot of dialog.
Did it all go well, then?
You saw for yourself.
Indirectly. Was it fun to be a voice actor in this show?
No, it was difficult.
What was so difficult about it?
I found it hard to read the script and the lines with all the words.
It sounds like a real ordeal.
So you wouldn't want to do this again?
I don't think I'll get the chance.
I heard that you'd be involved with the sequel if one gets made.
I'll see if I can do it.
It's bad to be so pessimistic.
Well, do you have any advice for aspiring voice actors?
Do it if you think you can.
That sounded a bit arrogant.
Is there anything that you think you did right when playing Rin Tin Tin?
We both talk very vaguely...
but I think I can convey his feelings.
She says so, and I think so.
It wasn't easy.
But you managed it anyway?
I did, in fact.
No, it was difficult.
Here's a contest where
you can win great prizes!
SPOT THE DIFFERENCES!
Would you explain the rules, Jimmy?
W-Watch the video!
I'm alive again!
W-Watch this, please!
Explain the rules now, Jimmy.
I h-have to finish this!
Then I'll explain the rules.
Did you see the two film clips?
Write down the points where they differ and note down the exact times.
Those who guess correctly will be eligible...
for one of a hundred beautiful Kennel Tokorozawa mugs.
Don't you agree, Jimmy?
Answers here.
Send your answers here.
Pony Canyon, postal code 102, Chiyoda-ku Kudankita 4-4-31.
Mark the letter with  "Kennel Tokorozawa."
Submit your answers no later than April 30, 1992.
Winners will be notified by letter.
Thank you for being here, Jimmy.
What are your plans for the near future?
I'm thinking of becoming a pimp.
A pimp?
Right.
One of those people who go on the street and...
Yeah.
Good luck then.
Good luck to you to, ho.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for watching "At home with Akiko."
I hope we see you again in
Kennel Tokorozawa 2.
Thanks from us!
Hump, hump!
God, I'm hot.
Swedish translation: Iggy Drougge, 2013
Dedicated to Alice Engström, a great dog lover.