Xpress Train
Part II
This can't be...
What's going on?
I don't know...
If you do it that fast,
I'm going to cum.
It's okay. Don't hold back.
Hurry.
I want you to cum a lot.
Cum!
I can't hold it anymore!
It's like soap.
It doesn't taste like anything.
Did you cum recently?
Are you a pervert?
I thought you and I were
the same type of person.
No! I'm not like you!
What do you mean?
We both like groping people.
I...I...
I don't lick cum!
- Hey!
- What's with him?
I did it again.
My body acts on its own.
Since that day...
Back when I was
a college student...
I used to take the local train
from the suburbs to get to college.
And on that fateful day...
No! Stop!
Stop! If you don't stop,
I'll call for help!
Go ahead, call for help. Go on.
Come on, call for help.
Do as I say!
No!
If you don't listen,
I'll show everyone. Look.
That's a good woman.
Good. Use your tongue more.
That's right. Lick my balls, too.
Why isn't your hand moving?
Yes...Yes...
I bet you want
something in your pussy.
What's wrong?
I didn't tell you to stop.
I'm going to cum!
Swallow all of it!
Naughty bitch.
You dirtied public property.
A naughty bitch
needs private lessons.
From that day on,
he continued to violate me.
Come on. Stop staring at it
and do what I told you to do.
Yes...
Yes...That's good.
All right. Moving on!
Stop acting dumb.
Do it before I have to say it!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Are you talking about sex?
No, I don't fuck virgins.
I don't like seeing blood.
That feels good.
Spit on my cock
to make it more slippery.
Jiggle your tits more.
Yes...
That's right.
Spit on it. Make it more slippery
and give me a better titty fuck.
Yes... That's good... Yes...
You're fucking me so hard...
You're going to make me cum.
I'm gonna cum!
That's enough for today.
Hey, what are you doing?
That's enough. Stop!
Today's lesson is over!
I'm going to cum!
Isn't that enough?
Again? You've sucked me dry!
And so, I mastered the art
of making a guy cum.
Now my body reacts on its own and
I grope them back when I get groped.
H-Help! I'm getting raped!
It was one terrible
incident after another.
I dated a guy for the first time
the second semester of that year.
When we were going
to have sex for the first time...
I can't...
What's wrong?
Why not?
Because...My body has been spoiled.
He had his way with me, and...
You were raped?
But he didn't make me have sex
with him, so I'm still a virgin.
Reiko...
It doesn't bother me.
I'm sorry you had to go through
something like that.
Yasu.
What are you doing?
Give it to me.
Please?
Come inside.
Okay. I'm coming in.
It hurts!
Wait, Reiko!
It hurts! It hurts!
What's wrong?
Reiko? What's wrong?
Get a hold of yourself!
Hey!
Huh? What's going on?
I can't pull out!
Prepare the mats!
Let's get this out.
Yeah.
It's so heavy.
Tell me about it!
That was heavy.
Took you long enough.
You should've helped us, then!
I was suspended for two weeks,
but that wasn't the only punishment.
I had to spend my days wondering
how people saw me at college.
I couldn't make any friends
or another boyfriend.
When I met him... I thought
he was my missing half, but...
I know you're in there,
Number 500! Open up!
Apprentice
Number 500!
I know you're home. Open up!
You haven't practiced in a week.
Your gold finger
is going to be useless!
Plus, you haven't passed
the final groping graduation test!
I'll be waiting!
I can't grope anymore.
But I sincerely think
it's for the best.
Hi, I'm calling
about the job opening.
Yes, the appointment is at two?
I was sick. I couldn't stop even
if I wanted to. I was a gropeaholic.
Make up your mind!
Do it or don't do it!
You suck!
Um...
If you're going to do it,
do like you mean it!
The one getting groped
is serious too, you know!
Mister!
Mister, please.
Hey! Watch how
this guy does it, okay?
Me?
It's all you.
I'm gonna do it! If I put
my mind to it, I can do it!
Okay!
What's wrong?
Come on! Like this!
What's happened to you?
I'm sorry. I can't anymore.
But you have to! I can't get excited
unless I get groped!
You're the one who made me
like this! It's your responsibility!
What's wrong? You seem down.
You're not as enthusiastic.
I guess I have no choice.
I'll do it to you.
My son...
What the hell
are you saying, old man?
I've treated you
as if you were my own son.
So what?
What are you trying to say?
Are you sure?
Are you sure about this?
You have found your true self.
Are you sure you want to
deny that and live this way?
Leave me alone!
It's fine. This is the way
it's supposed to be.
Are you sure?
You have found your true self.
Are you sure you want to
deny that and live this way?
Leave me alone!
I've had enough!
What's wrong?
Mister!
Old man!
Old man! Hang in there!
What happened?
This old man
was groping me, but...
the minute he started
to fuck me, he passed out!
Old Man?
Old man! Hang in there!
Old man!
What about her?
Old Man.
The rest is up to you.
I've taught you everything.
I have no regrets.
Farewell, my son.
Old man! Old man!
His heart's stopped!
- What?
- Don't give up yet!
That's amazing! He's dead,
but he's hard as a rock!
I can help, too.
Old Man, hang in there!
It's too late, he's...
Just a little more...
Yes! Cum!
Ewww!
That was amazing!
Old man... You're amazing...
At least he died
while he was groping.
I'm sure you felt his passion.
His passion is
too much for me. It's a burden.
You've received everything
from him. You need to do it.
You need to regain
your former self.
Mister!
Come!
Let's go!
My son... My son...
Old man...
Follow my instructions.
Keep your arm
at a 45 degree angle.
Stick your middle finger
out a little.
Hand at a 45 degree angle.
Sticking the middle finger
out a little...
Touch it gently,
as if you're touching...
a piece of fragile glassware.
Gently, as if I'm touching
a piece of fragile glassware...
Slowly at first,
then picking up the pace...
Your other hand
caresses her breasts.
My other hand
Lower the panties, make your way
through the bush... all the way in.
Lastly, the insertion.
If you master this, you've passed
the groping final exam.
The insertion... Let's do it.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to pee!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum inside!
Cum! Cum in me!
Old man!
Do not forget.
May the Groping be with you!
Farewell!
He's better than ever,
thanks to the God of Groping!