Sis, what's really on your mind?
Please, let go.
Why? You came here now because you want it, right?
Stop...
Stop it now!
First you seduce me, and now you reject me?
Well...
It wouldn't be nice to stop when you're this wet.
No!
Bad girl. I have to teach you a lesson.
It hurts!
It went in. Sis, your ass feels just as great.
Please stop this!
I just wanted to save this resort!
So that's why you let Domon and I have sex with you?
It feels so good that you're speechless?
I-I...
Sis, your ass is great.
I-I can't take it anymore. My butt... I'm cumming soon!
Sis. You don't really care about this place, do you?
Th-That's not t-true.
B-But, don't stop. Screw me harder.
M-My mind is going blank.
Sis, customers are watching.
They can see everything.
No, please don't look at me like this. Don't watch!
They're watching. My vagina, my butt being penetrated, all of it...
Sis, your grip has tightened.
It's great, it's great.
My butt feels great.
I'm going to cum while others are watching!
It's all right Sis, cum!
I'm going to cum from anal sex!
People are watching but...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Spa of Love
- Volume 2 -
Welcome back.
Um, is something wrong?
I went to try out the local sake,
but I'm a bit disappointed.
Oh, if that's the case, I'll go grab one.
A delicious one.
You sure?
Not a problem. Until I come back,
please drink the ones we have.
All right, I'll do that.
Excuse me! Yu... oh?
Wakana?
I-I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it. Well, see you later. I'll be waiting.
Please.
Wakana, it looks like I need your help.
When Yuki comes out of the spa,
please serve her alcohol.
Okay.
U-Um...
What is it?
Why do you treat the customers so perversely?
You really want to know?
But don't you know already?
It's what they desire. They all like sex so much.
I-Is that really true?
Of course. I'm counting on you.
Okay!
But what about me?
Here.
Thanks. By the way, he's very caring.
You two have some as well.
Why don't you drink a few with us?
I-I'm working right now, so...
You're a hard worker.
Well, can you at least stay here and talk with us?
All right, but...
Oh, don't worry. We've known each other for a long time.
We want to talk with you, don't we?
I agree.
So do I.
Um, okay...
Oh yeah, tell us about "him."
Him? You mean Yuji?
Yuji? I see, so you guys know each other's name.
I-It's not like that.
H-He's a relative.
We played together when we were young.
And he was the first boy you fell in love with?
Huh?
I see.
Looks like you two have a rival.
Yuki, what are you...
You think I didn't know?
When he's around, you two look uneasy.
W-Well...
Well, only you have my vote, Wakana.
Do your best.
Ah... Ah...
You two are married, so don't take him seriously.
I-I guess you're right.
Don't tell me you two really...
Yes?
It's me. May I come in?
Speak of the devil.
Yes, please come in.
Pardon me.
What perfect timing.
Hey...
If you had to choose one of us, who would it be?
Let's see. It would be you, Yuki.
D-Don't kid me.
I'm not kidding. You're the only one left, Yuki.
You scream cutely.
Wait, both of you. Stop!
Yuki, I can't resist.
He said he'll make me feel good if I obey.
Ryoko, what...
I'm sorry too.
But I also can't hold out any longer.
D-Don't touch me there!
What did you do to them!?
I just had them open up.
You'll feel the same way soon.
If you resist too much, you might hurt them.
You pathetic fool. How can you do this to them!
They became my slaves of their own free will.
Ryoko, can you strip her to make my job easier?
All right, come on Yuki.
I'll help.
Your skin is so rich and smooth.
Stop, please!
I'm sorry, but...
But...
How's the situation, Wakana?
She's wet, although only a little.
Wh-What are you talking about!
How can I get wet from being raped!
Fine, trade places with me.
Okay.
Hey, wait, don't look!
Yuki, which side do you prefer, front or back?
I like neither!
I see.
Open up. It'll feel very good.
Ryoko, Ryoko, let go!
Oh, don't tell me you like it in the ass better?
All this juice pours out when I touch it.
She's wet. It seems she likes it.
That's not... not my butt.
Well, here I go.
S-Stop!
It went in more smoothly than I expected.
Spreading... D-Don't grind inside my butt!
This isn't normal.
Looks good.
See, people are watching.
Don't watch. Don't watch me getting poked in the butt!
She's so wet.
Yuji, me too.
Not yet, not until I satisfy Yuki.
Cumming soon? All right.
No!
Wow.
I-I can't hold out much longer, please!
Ryoko, what are you...
I can't wait any longer.
Please fuck me with that big thing!
All right, I understand.
What about me. My body craves attention as well.
Wakana, please take care of Saori.
You can stick your finger inside her and make her cum.
Okay
Well, I'll...
When you pull out so quickly...
Hurry, please stick it in!
I know.
Inside, it's inside! This is what I wanted.
Ryoko, you're too honest.
It's because, it's because I like this! It feels good!
Oh, what's wrong?
If you want it, be honest and say you want it.
I-I won't!
I want... I want it deeper inside me!
Once you open up, I'll make you feel good.
Wonderful! I'm going to...
cum, I'm going to cum!
Ryoko's cumming.
Yuji, I want to be pleasured more.
Yuki.
Why are you acting so strangely?
Please...
Please... stick it inside me and make me cum too!
But just a little while ago you were refusing.
How can I resist after all that.
I'll do anything. Please fuck me!
All right then.
Yuki is... so cute.
I can't hold back much longer!
All right, go ahead.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Me too!
I feel it inside. I'm going to have a baby.
But doesn't it feel good
when there's a huge load inside?
Yes, it does.
But we can't... My husband...
Well, it's your choice to do what you want, Yuki.
If you don't like it, you don't need to come back.
Don't say that.
I'll be here as often as I can.
So please, give me more pleasure.
I don't want to go home either.
Yuji, please take me next.
I can't be fully satisfied by myself.
Me too.
Just as I planned, they're all mine now.
And they crave nothing but sex.
No, don't!
What you say is all talk.
See, you won't let go of my thing.
That's not...
You just couldn't forget the fun we had.
That's why you came back, right?
Your nipples are always sensitive.
How was Yuji?
Was he better?
Forgive me. Right there, it's... it's driving me.... Don't rub!
Milk for my baby...
What baby? The one you left at home, eh!?
Come on...
No, you're going to make me squirt milk!
My nipples, my nipples...
First Okami couldn't pay me my salary,
so instead she gave me her body.
Then I came up with the idea of making
rich housewives like you into sex slaves.
That way, you girls will keep coming back to this resort for more.
However, Okami fell in love with me.
She said she couldn't stand
watching me fuck other girls.
So I called Yuji to do the dirty work.
Come on, let go of yourself!
Cumming, I'm... going to cum!
Cumming!
So... cum. Shoot lots of it inside.
It was great, ma'am.
Just as I expected, you're a total slut.
D-Don't say that please.
But you like being fucked, right?
Please touch my breasts again.
Right there, too.
What am I going to do with you?
I just want to be pleased.
Well, the plan backfired a bit,
and now Okami is Yuji's slave.
Oh well, not a problem as long as this place gets more customers.
It's so big! Stick it in much deeper!
I'm going to cum!
Cum. Shoot all your load inside me!
Come on, how much longer are you going to stare?
You said you wanted me in the ass.
Um, right.
So big!
It's so tight!
There are more surprises.
What the...
I'm sorry, I...
It's all right. You're still hard.
I think we can do it at least five more times.
Being able to screw a beautiful young
lady like you is a dream come true.
S-So rough!
I've always had my eyes on you.
I've always lusted for you when I stayed here.
I think you've been very lonely since your husband passed away.
You won't even let go of my thing.
D-Don't talk about my husband please.
Not while we're...
We?
You're the one who invited us.
Don't stop, or else I'll go crazy!
To be honest, I wanted to fuck you in front of your husband.
Same here.
But, but... I'm sorry, dear!
I'll be sure to visit this place, and you, more often.
Everyone here is happy.
If everyone is happy, I can't ask for more.
After all, I'm having fun.
A great bath. Another great day.
Everyone was just as... no, more than I expected.
I think I can have fun a bit longer.
Um, excuse me, may I join you?
Oh, it's you,  Wakana. Of course.
Pardon me.
I want to...ask you something.
Let me guess. You're fed up?
If you can't take it, you can quit.
Oh wait, you needed the money, so you can't, right?
No, it's nothing like that. But...
But?
When will it be my turn?
Please have sex with me like the others.
No, I want it to be more wild than that.
Wakana, all right. Then, stick this in yourself.
Ok.
It's so tight. Are you still a virgin, Wakana?
Y-Yes.
It hurts! But it's going in.
Well, how does it feel to be in control on your first time?
Well, it hurts a bit, but also feels good.
I can't stand it.
I can't bear to watch you have sex with other women.
It's great. Wh-Why does it feel so good?
It's your first time, and you already like it.
Yes, it gets better with each thrust.
You're so wet, you pervert.
All right, I'll make things easier for you.
It's rubbing against me inside.
It's great!
I can feel you tightening up. You'll cum soon.
Yes, I'm going to...
Not finished.
I-I need rest!
I'll make you cum more.
This isn't fair. Please, me too.
Huh, Ryoko? I thought you were taking care of a customer.
Well, it wasn't enough.
I need sex that's more wild, so...
Ryoko, you're so mean. It was my turn next.
But...
Um, may we join in as well?
We need more too.
Please, stick it in my butt and make me squirm.
Me too, please.
Saori, Yuki, and Sis?
I'm sorry.
But none of us can wait any longer.
We need more.
What she said.
You made us realize what we like.
Now you have to take responsibility.
I don't mind.
But I can't take care of you all at once.
If that's the case, let me be first today.
But...
Oh, he didn't cum inside?
You must be dissatisfied.
Wakana, you're cute.
Lets have fun with her.
Please stick it in.
All right.
So hard! I like this cock!
The penetration alone makes me cum.
Well, I've been on the edge for a while, so...
Cum! Keep unloading inside me!
Please keep fucking us over and over, forever.
Hey, I'm next right?
My breasts needs attention. Please milk them.
Let me rest for a bit.
Not yet. You're still good to go.
Fine then.
Don't forget me!
I haven't.
Volume 2
- The End -