Wh-What are you doing?
See, you're already wet.
You probably wanted it.
Th-That's not true...
You don't need to lie. I know you want it.
Here I go.
Sorry... I'm sorry, dear.
Spa of Love
- First Bath -
Don't be so rough.
It's great! You're really wet!
It's in deep too!
No, not so deep.
You're really turned on.
I wonder what your husband would think?
No, this is... Honey, honey!
Your juices won't stop flowing!
Let me make it better!
Well...
Doesn't this feel better?
Stop.
What if someone sees?
That's even better!
See, you got tighter.
Don't! Stop this now!
Since we've gone this far, I'll cum inside.
No, not inside!
Even my husband hasn't...
But don't you want kids?
I'll help you!
No, don't...
Not inside!
I'll cum when you cum, Ryoko.
Great...
Th-This isn't right, but it feels...
great.
I'll let you have it.
This is... so cruel...
Your pussy was just great.
Pregnant... babies inside...
Th-This is just too...
But you liked it.
Anyway, this isn't over yet.
Sis!
Wh-hy are you...
I'll make sure you won't forget this.
Ryoko, it's your fault for being so beautiful.
It's not my fault for wanting to explore
that beautiful body of yours.
Azusa.
Stop...
No...
It's big.
It's deep inside.
I-If this goes on! No!
It's driving me crazy. It's driving me crazy!
Such a tight grip!
I-I never...
So, it's your first time having an orgasm.
Well, I need to release soon too, inside!
Please, give, give it to me!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
I feel warm... inside...
Looks like it's going to be another great day.
I came to this resort to help out my sister.
To be honest, it doesn't pay well,
and it's hard work. But...
Seeing all these beautiful women,
I know I'm lucky.
I'm surrounded by beautiful housewives.
Then, I came up with a plan.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Working so early?
It's part of my job.
Saori, you're up early as well.
Yes, I just woke up.
I was taking a walk around the shores.
If you can't sleep, I recommend
you do some kind of workout.
I'm not good at that.
Well, I'm going back to my room.
Okay, get some rest before breakfast.
I'll give you a good workout later.
This traditional resort surely needs some changes.
Well, I'd better finish up before night falls.
This resort doesn't have many customers.
This inn used to be big,
but that's a thing of the past.
Because of the money spent on advertising,
it's barely in business.
Well, I guess that's why I'm here to help.
Looks clean now.
Yuji, may I have a moment?
Who is she?
She started working here today, Ms. Sumiyoshi.
I'm Wakana Sumiyoshi.
I've known Asuza for a long time. Nice to meet you.
Sister Azusa, how much did you tell her?
Not a thing.
Please help her out.
Of course I will.
Wh-What's wrong?
Come here for a sec.
Um, what are we...
It's really simple.
Since we're working together,
we should get to know each other.
S-Stop this now!
Azusa!
Azusa, you knew?
Sis likes to watch.
Ain't I right?
Yes...
Wakana, you're a virgin?
This is your first time?
Ouch!
So, you've never done it.
Y-Yes!
Fine, I won't have sex with you today.
Oh, thank you! Thank you very much!
Instead, use your mouth.
Wow, your tits are pretty big.
Don't worry. I know you have no experience,
so Azusa will show you.
Wakana, look closely.
Yes...
Once you try it, you can't go back.
Wakana, try it.
Hurry, don't be afraid.
Come on.
One more time.
This time, lick the whole shaft.
Don't forget the sack.
Now you should suck on the tip, hard.
Suck on it harder!
Yes, that's it!
I see your sack tightening.
Shit, cumming!
Wakana, make sure you drink it all.
Good girl. Great job.
Well, I'm getting back to work.
Sister Azusa, clean up the mess.
Hello.
Hello, you look relaxed.
You look relaxed. Enjoying the spa?
Of course, that's why I always come here.
I see. I can tell you really do like it.
Well, not as much as Saori.
Really?
She stays in for a long time. She'll probably
be there for at least two more hours.
I see.
Oh, but you better not peek.
I'm not like that!
Just kidding. Later.
See you.
I see, so Saori is by herself.
It's time to make use of Wakana.
Hello, excuse me.
Are you a new guest?
I haven't seen you around.
No, I'm Wakana Sumiyoshi, and I started working here as of today.
Nice to meet you.
My, nice to meet you too.
You're really energetic.
Friends tell me the same thing.
Well, I think it's a great thing.
Thank you very much!
W-Well, can I wash your back?
Are you sure?
I-I'd love too!
Really?
Well, I guess I do want one.
Have a seat.
I'll begin.
Please do.
Wow, your skin is smooth.
Must be because of the spa.
That tickles.
Ouch!
Wh-Why are you here?!
Wakana, please!
Y-Yes...
L-Let go, Ms. Sumiyoshi!
I'm sorry, there's nothing I can do.
She's helping me out in order to
give you better service, Saori.
Service? How is this a better service?
Well, this will service your needs better,
since your husband and child are away.
What!?
You'll like it.
I promise.
Ready, Wakana.
No, d-don't!
It's very soft...
yet firm.
This is embarrassing...
Saori, you're sensitive.
What about here?
N-No, don't touch...
You're so wet already?
No, that's from the spa.
Our spa's water isn't sticky like this.
Her nipples are getting harder.
Hard, and perky.
No, don't squeeze it.
Wakana, looks like she wants to be squeezed more.
Wow, so much!
It feels good.
Milk, lots of it. S-Still, stop. Stop,
or else I'll go crazy!
The milk is going to waste.
Wakana, you can drink some.
S-Stop, this is for the baby.
D-Don't drink it!
No, don't suck.
Well, here I come!
Why? Stop... don't...
I'll make you feel better,
until you admit it.
Here I go!
Wow, it's making a slurping sound as it goes in!
Oh, don't say such things.
Look, more milk!
N-No, it's sensitive there.
Well, you seem to be enjoying it.
It's getting wetter inside!
See, if I do this...
N-No, don't push in so deep.
Saori, you're such a naughty housewife.
You even have a kid.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Saori, you're moving your hips by yourself.
How erotic.
N-No, that's not true.
It's true, but I like it when you're like this!
So much milk.
Great... releasing milk feels great...
Looks like you came.
But we're not done yet!
N-No, I just came!
This is... driving me crazy.
It feels so good to release!
Luckily for you, this is a bathing area.
Come on, show me your kinky side, Saori!
Something is coming... Cumming, cumming!
Me too. I'll give it all to you inside!
No. No, anything but inside!
I'll do anything!
You just said you'll do anything!
I-Is she really all right?
Yes, she is. She passed out because it was so good.
Please clean up.
Make sure Saori doesn't catch a cold.
Y-Yes.
Hey! Are you doing your job?
Y-Yes, I'm getting used to it.
Hmm, I see.
Yes, thanks to you.
Well, you need to be a bit faster.
He's Domon Onihei, the chef.
An employee of the resort.
Being a male, he's in the way, but we do need a chef.
Hmm, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing. I still have work left to do.
All right, later.
Excuse me.
Ryoko, I'm coming in.
Saori, you're here too.
Oh, you two don't look well.
Was it that shocking? Doing it with another man?
What?!
I can't believe this.
A mere service for your satisfaction.
Does thinking about it make you feel hot?
Wow, already. You really are perverted, Ryoko.
Stop, don't do this.
But your hips are pressing against my hands.
Was it that good yesterday?
Saori, dont look. Please don't look.
Saori, you want it too?
If you do, take off your clothes and come here.
Y-Yes.
You're bold.
I can't take it. I need it.
I like honest people.
Me too, please.
Then you use your mouth, Ryoko.
You know what I mean.
I've never done this with my husband.
Ryoko, you're doing great.
Please keep going.
Great! I can tell you really do like sex, Ryoko.
You too, Saori.
It's great! My nipples feel so good!!
More, please touch them more!
Delicious...
Ryoko, it feels really great.
Your husband would've loved this!
Please don't talk about him. I don't...
All right, get on top then.
It's rubbing inside.
I can feel the warmth deep inside!
Ryoko, this is so kinky!
It's wonderful.
Me too, me too, please!
Just watching is driving me crazy!
Then play with your nipples.
And pretend that it's me.
W-With your hands...
Please suck. Suck on them!
It feels good. It feels good when you suck them!
More, suck more!
There, suck harder, right there!
Deep. It's in so deep!
It's all the way inside, and it's big!
It feels good! It feels like I'm being milked!
I'm cumming, and I can't stop!
Me too. I'm going to cum!
The way you touch my chest is making me cum too!
D-Don't cum until I cum!
I'm just going to cum inside!
No,n ot inside!
Looks like you're satisfied.
Um, I want sex too.
Saori, you want it inside as well?
My vagina is aching for it.
Yuji, please give me your big, hard thing deep inside!
All right.
You have to suck on it to make it big.
After all, I did just cum.
You dirty slut.
Looks like you just can't get enough.
Come...
Please, give it to me all the way inside...
As many times as you want.
I wonder how long they've been doing this.
Come in.
Huh.
What's wrong, Wakana?
Umm...
Wh-What's this?
Don't you think it's good quality,
for a hidden cam?
I've placed them everywhere.
Yes. Good quality.
When did you...
Camera's today are amazing.
They're too small to notice,
yet they provide great quality.
I-Is this okay to do?
Who knows? It depends on how you see it.
You saw those two women enjoying it.
But my plan isn't...
I need your help again, Wakana.
She's my next target.
I saved the hardest challenge for last.