By BD & irrOn
Ryohko...wait
Ryohko...no...
Even if there is no relation by blood, we shouldn't be doing this.
There's no need to hold back.
When you're feeling good just let it out.
But...
Don't be like that Yu.
It's not only for your sake.
We also want to have a good time.
You too, Kyohko...
My, aren't you lucky Yu? Having two such wonderful sisters taking care of you all nude.
Yu's face feels pretty good.
Kyohko, can't bre...
Wait a second. Just what are you two doing?
What...Giving Yu a handjob it seems.
That's not what I'm asking.
Siblings in law doing something perverse like that.
What are you saying, Anzu?
Now that we all are going to live together again...
...there's no need to hide anything from each other.
But...everyone naked like this...
Anzu, are you going to take bath dressed like that?
Kyohko...no. You're making me all wet.
Don't worry about that.
Just have a peek at how Yu has grown in some areas.
I'm really not that interested in...
Kyohko...
Kyohko...no.
You just stay put.
Don't look away while I'm doing this for you.
Ryohko...
Let's feel good together.
Kyohko...please...
Don't you feel bad wearing clothes?
There's something called "spending time together nude", right?
No...not there!
Oh, it's already pouring out of you, Anzu.
No..that's not true.
Ryohko...I'm...
It's alright. Just let it all out, I'll clean you up.
Ryohko...can't...
The reason why I let this strange relation with my three sisters continue
is all because of this mysterious bottle.
What do you mean?
Don't be quiet like that - Say something!
Why did you do these shameful things to us?
Yu, if you don't tell us why, you're going to get life time
You're going to get a reeeally rough time
Well...
So you finally understand...
It seems like we'll have to return the favour.
Spill it all out.
Just relax.
Yu, just say it.
Please Yu, tell us why.
Yu？
Yu?
Yu, are you alright?
This strange bottle is the "Vial of Inanna".
My uncle brought it with him from one of his trips.
In this room that was given to me when i first moved in...
...I soon discovered this bottle and when i picked it up, everything started.
Somehow there seemed to be a curse contained inside it.
If I just left it alone "The worst horror" would somehow come upon me.
To lift the curse one would have to collect a great amount of female bodyfluids..
...or in other words "juice".
But the worst part is that the target would have to be unaware of the curse's excistance.
What's wrong with those two?
Showing themselves to Yu like that.
It's not like I don't have a bad conscious for collecting "juices" from my sisters without them knowing.
The one who fills the bottle with "juice" and lifts the curse will also get one wish granted.
Did you want to play with Yu too?
I'll have to get it by turning them on.
This is the story about how I came to spend my holiday here...
...trying to collect the "juices" from my three sisters in law.
It's really not that difficult.
At these moments the flask send out a signal.
Kyohko, are you there?
Could she have gone out?
Did she pass out after drinking to much？
But this appearance...
It's the signal from the bottle!
If her "juices" start pouring out now, the bottle will fill up.
Molesting a sleeping girl isn't really my style...
I guess she won't wake up from this...
Let's go.
This...?
Is this...
I'll use this right away.
I guess I'll better start collecting her juices.
This underwear cuts in...
Wow... Even when sleeping she gets this wet.
To collect her juices it comes down to this, I guess.
She's so sensitive.
Alright!
Don't...
Did she come...?
Are you awake Kyohko?
Yu?
What are you doing here?
I..erm.. came to return a book i borrowed.
And then...you see...
And just were is this book that you borrowed?
Well...that is...
Bad little boys who lie needs to be punished, don't they?
It's twitching under my hi-heels.
It...hurts...
Hey! Don't try to get up!
Oh, could it be that it actually feels good?
Then I better get really serious.
Please wait. I'll apologize so please give me a break.
How pitiful...
I was really hoping that you would be a bit more manly.
Even if you say that...
What's wrong with you Yu?
Are you alright? Are you in pain?
Don't worry, I'm alright. It was just suddenly...
What's going on here?
Awesome!
I don't have a clue either.
"I was really hoping that you would be a bit more manly."
Could it be that bottle fulfilling her wish?
If thats the case, then this is way different from how I remember it
Did you just remember something?
It just looks so much bigger than before.
Not really, I'm just thinking about how you look in your underwear.
Yu, can't you take your clothes off?
Do you think I'll miss an opportunity to see a dick this huge?
Awesome. Even my breasts won't reach around.
You don't have to overdo it Kyohko.
Don't worry. I want to calm down this dick...
So big... my jaw is almost dislocating.
There is no point unless you come.
It's so soft.
It feels so good twiching between my breasts.
Can't hold...!
There.
That's all for today.
You're not letting me put it in?
No way.
If you put something this big in me, my poor little pussy will break.
Let them have a look at it in the hospital tomorrow.
But...
Just joking. There is no way we can stop now, right?
You still haven't come yet.
Let my pussy taste it too.
Well then Kyohko...
It might be to much for me, but put that big thing in me.
You're awfully tight. Are you really alright?
I'm...I'm really fine.
Yu, move as fast as you wish.
A..awesome. It's stirring around inside me.
I've never felt like this before.
Kyohko...it's awfully tight. Should we stop?
No! Don't stop. Move harder.
But...
Don't worry... Please.
If you say so.
Kyohko... I can't...
Hold on. Let me do the last...
It's reaching all the way in.
My...my hips move by themselves.
I'm losing it.
Wonderful.
I'm really about to come now, Kyohko.
I'm almost there too.
Inside or outside - wherever you want.
Yu...Come!
Sorry about coming inside of you, Kyohko.
There is still some left in here.
This time, put it in my butt.
Er...that's a little bit...
The following day my huge dick was back to it's normal size again.
At that time I also thought the curse from the bottle was lifted.
However...
R...Ryohko.
Oh, you were on this bus too?
Yeah, I wanted to do some shopping.
It's really crowded in here.
The train had some kind of accident. It's not always like this.
Yu, what's wrong ? What happened?
It's nothing. Are you alright?
I'm fine. What about you?
I'm just fine.
Like I'm fine with her breats touching me like this.
Collect her juices. Otherwise the curse won't be lifted.
Why isn't this over already?
Did you say something?
Not really. Just talking to myself.
I guess under these circumstances I'm just an ordinary grooper.
I've got no choice. You don't know unless you try.
No!
Yu, stop it! Not in a place like this...
Shh! Keep your voice down or the others will take notice.
But you just...
That's it. Stay put and it will soon be over.
Don't! It's emberassing
No way...I'm getting wet...
Please don't...
No...if you...more than this...
I'm feeling hot...
Ryohko...she's getting into this.
That's it.
Can't hold it anymore.
Ryohko...
Ryohko...I'm...
...about to come?
Really... Having a naughty brother causing me trouble like that.
Sorry about that Ryohko...
I would have been up for it any time. All you had to do was to ask.
That's not the problem here...
Wouldn't it be nice if it was like back then again.
Back then you were much more reasonable and cute.
If we could go back to that time right away I would give you a really good treatment.
Ryohko...
Let's get back home.
Walking around with wet underwear will only make you catch a cold.
But the next morning something really big was about to happen.
Yu, get up. It's already morning.
Aaa..Good morning...
Come on now, if you can't get up by yourself your friends will make fun of you.
Ryohko, what are you talking about? Is this some kind of game?
Game? What is?
What's going on here?
This is like when I was a kid.
"Wouldn't it be nice if it was like back then again."
What? What is it?
Ryohko...do you remember ten years ago when my mother died
and I was adopted by grandma?
What are you saying?
Your mother passed away last year, didn't she?
Yes...that's right.
There is no doubt about it. Ryohko thinks it's back when we were kids.
That stupid bottle is doing it again.
Yu, what's wrong? Aren't you feeling well?
No, I'm fine.
Really?
Oh well. If it's the same as with Kyohko, everything should be back to normal by tomorrow.
Actually...
Huh?
This might be fine for a while too.
I...
I want to know more...
...about the female body.
Yu...
Do you...Do you really want to look?
Uhm...Because I'm really interested.
I see...
Look, these are breasts...
and this is...
...the vagina.
So this is what it looks like.
It's so hot. I really need a shower.
Is Yu taking a bath at this time?
This is where you can insert the penis.
I can't really see the inside very well.
Ha... have a closer look.
Ryohko...Can I touch it?
Yes...but gently.
Is this where you insert the penis?
No that's wrong. That's where the pee comes out.
Really. Some pee just came out.
Do... don't talk like that. It's emberassing.
Then, what about here?
Yes...that's where the penis goes in.
Ryohko, you're really twiching down here
That's because it feels really good...
Ryohko, something is starting to flowing out
That is...because you're touching me...
When a boy touches a girl down here, it feels good.
And then body fluids come out.
Ryohko...
Do you want to touch it more?
What is that Yu up to again？
But considering how the talk goes they'll likely end up having sex.
Ah, enough!
Ryohko, you're nipples are getting hard. Does it feel good?
Yes, just the same way as a penis.
Do anything you want.
But playing with your nude body...
...made me like this.
This time, can you make me feel good, Ryohko?
Okay then.
No way, my body is getting hot too...
Yu, you're so big.
And here I still thought that you were a kid.
Ryohko, you're really wet.
You're good, Yu.
Your tongue is in my pussy.
I'll do something even better.
No...don't suck on my clitoris.
Ryohko, I want to put it in you.
I understand. Then I'll be your first.
Yu...look.
Yu's penis is sliding in.
Yu's penis, it's in.
So big and hot.
I'll start moving now and make you feel good.
Yu, does it feel good inside of me?
It feels really good...
That makes me happy. I'll try to do even better.
Ryohko...
You're so good, Yu. Touch them harder.
That will make me even more turned on.
Now it's my turn.
Amazing...he's inside of her.
I...I'm...
Good. Yu..it feels really good.
I'll make you feel even better.
I'm so happy. Do as you please with my body.
I'm being messed up inside!
N...no. I'm seeing it all.
Yu is sliding in and out of my pussy.
Ryohko, I'm about to come.
Me too...let's come together.
It feels like you're about to burst
Just let it all out inside of me.
Ryohko, I'm coming!
My belly is full of your...
Sorry, I just couldn't stop...
Don't be. It felt really great.
That time I had no idea of what took place in my room.
Uhm...
Huh?
You two are really horny.
What are you saying Anzu?
It's your turn next time.
Wait...no! That's just too emberassing.