Mochizuki, your dick's all stiff.
Okay, that's the 20th.
Time to switch Momo.
Hey, it's my turn again now.
Just get horny all you want, okay?
Tomoya-san, you feel really hot.
It feels good.
It feels good, but how did it end up like this again?
Oh yeah.
This is not the time for me to completely
submit to my carnal instincts!
Why am I in this situation?
Why is our artist Kisara-san and our scenario writer Momoka-chan,
doing this very sweet and delicious thing to me?
This is like a scene from an H-game.
Why did it turn out like this?
H-game?
H-game...
Okay, let's think.
Think.
Original Animation Disc
Eroge! The joy of sex and game development
The Battle of Conquest for the Adored Cum?! Gotta
catch some white and sticky milk! Chapter
Mochizuki Tomoya is the newly hired member of Flower,
our H-game company that is about to go bankrupt.
It's all good that someone who loves H-games
was able to work for such a company,
but the games that Flower made, according
to this self-proclaimed H-games master,
was way below what one would be able to call as acceptable.
I, the company's president, Sonono Nene.
Her 3rd Came in the Making
oujinishi's are quite
Artwork, Himeno Kisara.
Scenario writer, Fujiwara Momoka.
Graphics Artist, Kousaka lori.
All of them are yet to play an actual H-game,
and do not even have a single experience with actual sex.
We do have the technical skills to actually create them,
but without any knowledge of sex,
we wouldn't be able to properly complete one.
Kisara and Momoka,
had this fact revealed to them by Tomoya.
And were eventually taught sex with their bodies improving on it.
It's all wet.
This is gross!
Will it really eventually come out?
Hey, I said hey!
Is it coming out? Is this it?
It's still coming out.
Wait, just how much can it squirt out?
I have to properly draw a sketch of a dick,
as it cums from a footjob.
Here, if you want to cum, just do so.
You want to try and make my knee
socks wet with your sperm, right?
Oh, that Cowper liquid's finally coming out.
The tip feels like it's trembling.
It feels hot!
It's hot!
This much cum on my feet?
No, you can't just drive it deep inside me and cum like an animal!
I can't concentrate on my work anymore.
There's going to be cum in my pussy...
Your cum is going to...!
Cum is pouring inside me.
Is this a vibrator?
What are you trying to do?
That part is...
No, that's not...
That's not what an ass is used for!
It's deep!
My ass, my asshole!
Dressing me up like this while making me suck your dick...
Never thought blowjobs felt like this.
This feels strangely great, I think.
I want it...
I want your cum.
Pour out all your cum inside my mouth!
What's this? No...
Don't thrust it in now.
No thrusting right now.
Mot my boobs.
Stop sucking it strongly.
I'm cumming...
My nipples...
I'm going to cum by my nipples!
As a result,
Kisara's illustrations became far more accurate.
Momoka's scenarios are also now good enough
that you can fap to them while reading.
However, under those circumstances,
Kisara and Momoka lost their virginity to Tomoya,
and they entered a sex only relationship with him.
Needless to say, he likes both of them.
However, unable to choose between them,
he constantly gets lured into a "sex study session" with Kisara.
Usually, this "study" is conducted after work, when
everyone has gone home already, but...
Okay, I'm going out for some field work.
I'm leaving everything else to you, Mochizuki-kun.
Understood.
The four who were left,
had no choice but to continue their work
in this aircon-less, steamy room.
Hey, Mochizuki, we need to talk.
Come with me.
Can't it be done here?
Of course it can't, that's why I'm telling you
to come to the meeting room with me.
Just come already.
No way, with them still around?
Shut up, and just bring that digital camera!
Tomoya, dragged by her,
went holding a digital camera as instructed.
Pull it out.
What should I pull out?
Your dick, of course!
I'm going to give you a blowjob.
Be grateful.
Okay.
Kisara-san, if you keep making such loud noises,
we'll be heard from the other room.
It's okay, it's just a bit.
Anyway, you're the one who shouldn't act too strangely.
O-okay, I understand.
Okay, let's go for the main course.
Main course?
We're really doing it here?
No! Why do you think I made you bring that camera for?
Hurry up and assume a piledriver position already.
I brought that camera specifically for that purpose!
Does it feel good?
I Bet you're getting all aroused in that embarrassing position.
Umm...
It feels good.
Here, make yourself hornier.
Okay, I'm going for your asshole now.
That part is...!
What's it?
Does it feel good in your ass too?
Oh, it does feel good.
Now, I'm going to squeeze it all out of you.
Hey, don't make such loud noises!
We'll be heard from the other room.
Alright, now for some pictures.
These embarrassing shots even reveal your asshole.
Okay, now lie down over there.
Hey, umm...
Don't worry, I'm going to make you cum.
You want me to give you a blowjob like this, right?
I'll take it for you.
I'm going to suck your die.
There, release your cum milk into me already.
Let it all out into my mouth.
Hey you two, what are you doing?!
Momo?
Momoka-chan?
You're terrible, Tomoya-san.
Even though I'm serious about you...
Serious? But Mochizuki is mine.
What are you saying?
He's mine.
Umm, calm down you two.
A good talk would surely...
Shut up!!!
Anyway, all the time you had me do this, and that...
You were actually also into Momo?
Is it only sex that's on your mind, you beast dick!
So you were playing with my feelings all this time?
I did lots of embarrassing things with you.
Were you not going out with me?
That's why I said that officially dating is a bit...
Jeez, just tell us who you're going to choose between us already!
I already said, that I want to focus on completing
the game's development.
So I tried teaching you two a thing or two about sex.
So the issue of whom I will choose to date is...
What indecisive things are you blabbering about?
You just trampled upon the purity of a young girl!
So all those things you taught me about sex was all just for work?
Just so you know, my body now can't live without you!
Okay then.
If it has come to this, then why don't we settle it once and for all?
Momo, I challenge you to a duel!
I accept!
Tomoya-san's body is all mine!
H-hey...
Okay, let's make him cum then.
And here, I thought this was just some sort of ruckus.
Now it has become a bloody battlefield.
Listen up.
I'll be taking Mochizuki's left side.
You take the right.
We'll stroke his dick, make skin contact with our boobs,
and we'll also lick parts of his body.
The one who makes him cum first is the winner.
Okay then.
tomoya-san, please choose me, okay?
Eh?!
Wow, your dick is all stiff and lively now.
Does my handjob and licking feel good?
I'm going to remove my bra and stick my breasts directly on you.
Even I can do that.
Here, Mochizuki, this is the boobs that you love so much.
Hey, that's the 20th stroke already.
It's my turn now.
Okay, I know.
Here, switch with me.
What's that?
Don't just get too aroused from her handjob!
Here, give me your hand.
This is what it should touch.
There, can you tell?
My pussy is already this wet.
Mochizuki, does it feel good?
Hey, it's switching time already.
Tomoya-san, isn't your dick at its limit already?
Be sure to cum with my hand, okay?
Okay, now fondle my breasts next.
Hey, what are you doing, Momo?
Oh, I want you to fondle it as if you're trying to milk it.
Ok, forget it.
Licking the ears is still the best for you, right?
Just say it already.
Oh wow, Tomoya's hand is fondling me vigorously.
Oh no, oh no!
if you try to squeeze my breasts that strongly,
I will cum...
I'm going to cum...!
I'm cumming!
Jeez, you're not the one supposed to cum here.
Now switch with me.
There now, cum already.
You want to cum with my hand, right? Look.
I want you to continue...
I want to cum... to cum with your hand.
Did you say something? I didn't hear it.
You said something about wanting to cum with my hand?
About wanting to squeeze all the cum milk out from it?
Here, just cum already.
I'm going to make it even faster.
Release it.
I'm going to cum.
Cum, cum already!
With this it's my win!
This means Mochizuki is truly mine!
No, I can't have that!
It just happened that he was about to cum when it was your turn!
What's that? Are you trying to nitpick now?
I just can't accept it!
Let's flight with our pussies then.
Let's see who can make him cum buckets!
Hmph, okay then.
I'm the one who's going to win anyway.
Challenge accepted!
Huh, you two are still at it?!
Eroge! The joy of sex and game development.
Okay, now we're ready.
Hey, Mochizuki.
Choose who you will do it with first.
Eh?!
I'm still not mentally prepared for this.
And I just came earlier.
Oh, his dick is already limp.
Okay, we'll commence our battle to seduce his dick first.
We're going to masturbate in front of him,
and let him decide who he will fuck first.
Okay, I accept those conditions.
Tomoya-san, I want you to watch how I masturbate
and make yourself aroused, okay?
Now then...
I'm going to wear the camisole that you love, so cum with me.
Tomoya-san, make your dick big by watching
how I play with myself, okay?
First, from the boobs, like how I always do it.
Mochizuki, are you watching?
I already tit fucked you lots of times, right?
Look.
I'm ﻿starting from the breasts as well.
It's like this right, Tomoya-san?
Just like how you always fondle them.
Mochizuki, look at this.
It's the pussy that you always love.
This feels good.
Whenever I think that you're the one doing this, I...
Look closely at my pussy.
It's already wet and twitchy.
My clitoris is already bulging out.
Look, I'm pinching my own clitoris.
Even I can also do that...
Look, Tomoya-san.
The area around my clitoris feels great!
Oh no, my body is starting to get aroused as well.
My clitoris...
This feels good.
Me too, I'm...
Look at this, I'm about to insert the dildo that you gave me.
It's going inside my pussy.
Look, it's going inside.
It's gone in.
It's going in and out like it's your dick.
It feels good!
This feels great!
Tomoya-san, I'm about to insert this too.
The vibrator that you once inserted into me.
It's now going inside my pussy!
This is amazing, this is really amazing!
It's moving inside my pussy!
Tomoya-san, are you watching?
The vibrator is now filling the insides of my pussy.
The nipples which you have fondled also feels great.
That thick thing is...
I'm envious.
It looks really bulky.
Also, does it really feel good to fondle the breasts?
Mochizuki, don't just stand there and insert it inside me already.
No, here Tomoya-san, you have to insert it into my pussy.
So you came for me after all, huh?
Put it inside already.
This dildo isn't enough for me.
I want your huge dick.
Kisara-san,
I'm going in.
It's in!
This is the dick that made my pussy crazy.
Wow, this really feels great.
There, it's hitting my womb.
I want you to violate my pussy more with your big dick.
Oh wow, it's really inside.
Wow, something like that can really fit.
Oh no, I think I want some too.
I want a dick too.
I'm getting horny.
But what I really want is to be fucked by a real dick.
My love fluids squirt out whenever you go in and out of my pussy!
This is bad.
Your dick is just too big!
Oh no, if you thrust too fast like that,
my mind might go completely blank!
My pussy would feel too good!
I'm cumming!
Mochizuki, you haven't cum yet...
Just me...
Give it to me too.
I want your entire dick inside me.
I'm going in.
It's in!
Your dick is finally in!
It feels really great!
Much better than a vibrator!
Thrust it deeper inside, please!
Your dick is my pussy's!
It's exclusive to me!
That's why I want you to make my pussy your personal pussy too!
Oh, yes!
That's right, thrust it in more!
Momoka, your pussy feels really tight and wet.
It feels really good.
I'm happy about that.
Your lively dick hitting me deep inside.
I'm going to make it feel even better, Momoka-chan.
That's right, I really love my breasts being fondled by you.
Because you're the one who made them this way.
You're the one who made them this sensitive.
So play with it more, pinch my nipples more!
I'm getting really horny.
I'm about to cum again.
I'm going to cum with my breasts!
it's coming out from my nipples!
Now, my pussy too...
I want you to release it too.
I want you to release your milk in me!
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Tomoya-san, I just came.
I came with your dick.
Hey, move over now.
Momo, he hasn't cum yet.
This a battle on who will make him cum with our pussies, right?
Mochizuki, it's my turn again.
Lie down over there.
Here, I'll be on top,
so you can just stay still.
I'm definitely going to make you cum with my pussy.
It's in.
It's at my deepest point.
Listen up.
I'm the one who'll move.
So don't move an inch there, okay?
I'm going to move it forward and back, like this...
This feels good.
Of course, this is my pussy we're talking about.
Your dick is my slave.
If you don't understand that, then I'm going to make you!
Okay, now I'm doing circles.
Well? Does it feel good?
Just say that it feels good.
Your pussy feels good.
That's right.
You just need to openly feel aroused.
I'll be the one to move my hips so don't worry.
Here, how is this?
Does this feel good?
Look here.
Say that you want to cum inside me!
I can't hold myself anymore, Kisara-san.
I'm going to move too.
Sex.
No, just wait...!
What are you going to do?
You knew this kind of embarrassing position?
That's our H-game master for you.
Okay then, let's show it to Momo.
What is this?
This is amazing!
It's hitting me at my soft spots!
Oh no, don't!
It feels too good.
Wow, what's that?
Does that feel good?
Oh no, if I continue watching...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Oh no, oh no...
Stop, wait...!
Are you about to cum?
Then release all of your cum already.
Fill me up with your cum now!
Oh no...
Kisara-san, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming.
Then cum.
Cum.
And I'll...
Cum too!
Let's cum...
Together!
I'm cumming!
See? Looks like I won.
Is that so?
Momoka-chan, I'm still...
I'm still not done, so...
I'm happy, really happy.
I just came earlier,
and I'm getting aroused again.
Oh no...
This is amazing.
You just came not long ago,
and yet it's already this big again.
More...
No, my head's starting to feel fuzzy.
It feels too good.
Momoka-chan, here I cum.
Okay, please cum.
I want you to pour all of your white
and sticky cum inside my womb!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
It's coming out.
It's pulsating...
This feels good.
The sensations of your dick twitching inside feels great.
It feels good to be cummed inside.
And so...
Hey, so this is...
Who won in the end?
Mochizuki?
Tomoya-san?
I'm sorry, I really can't choose between you two!
You already confessed that you liked me!
You really are an indecisive good-for-nothing.
I totally agree.
But I like him.
Wait.. Even I also like him too, you know!
Then why don't we do this?
Until the game is completed, we'll both have him.
Can't be helped then.
That's all good with me.
But after that, you need to properly choose between us, okay?
O-okay.
I'm back!
Huh? What are you all doing in the nude?
Well, this is...
You see, it's really hot today, so...
Oh, it really is quite hot today, isn't it?
Y-yeah, it is!
Now, back to work!
Let's complete our first would-be successful game,
and then we'll be able to move into an office with an aircon, okay?
You're right, we need to work hard for it.
Right, Kisara-san?
0-of course.
It's just about a week before the final completion deadline.
Will I be able to choose between them during that time?
Alright!
Let's do our best until the final completion date!
Yeah!
Yeah...