Orifushi
I'm finally here.
My name is Shiki Haruomi.
For various reasons,
I've returned to the home of the
Orifushi sisters, where use to play.
Huh? But I called ahead.
I wonder if they had to leave home suddenly?
Hello!
It's Shiki!
Is anyone home?
Natsumi-san? Are you here?
Sorry Mafuyu, can you bring me a bath towel?
Mafuyu?
Exciting Life With Three Sisters
Complete Edition
You can use this room, Haru-kun.
Wasn't this your Dad's room? Is
it really okay for me to use it?
Yeah, Dad and Mom are long gone.
I see.
Onee-chan's inherited the shop and is giving it her best.
Natsumi-san has?
Haru-kun, you've grown big, haven't you?
Well, if you compare me to last time, I must look bigger.
Even you...
...became beautiful?
To be honest, Akina was cute, but she's
become even cuter than before.
Yippie, you blushed!
Somehow... she wrecked the mood.
And now to do it properly... Welcome, Haru-kun.
You're late, Haruomi.
Long time no see, Haru-chan
Umm...
Thank you for your hospitality.
Thank you for the food.
It's incredible.
Haru-chan, you're a man, so you have to eat more.
Uh, yes, thank you for the food.
Umm, Natsumi-san...
Your way of calling me is a little embarrassing.
Oh my, why do you think that?
We're not at that age anymore.
But, "Haru-chan" is cute.
I don't like it being cute.
But "Haru-chan" is easy to say.
That "chan" is a little...
But "Haru-chan" is more friendly.
But!
Yeah, it's okay that way.
Are you sure?
And I had around ten more reasons.
Here, Haru-chan, say "Ah".
No, Natsumi-san, wait...
Hey, onee-chan, you're getting too close to Haru-kun!
Oh my, Akina-chan, are you jealous?
Haru-chan, among the three of us, who's your type?
Eh? Umm, it's...
I know!
I'll guess it.
Aww, I knew it would be Akina-chan.
Wait a minute...
And I thought that as your elder,
I'd be able to lead you gently.
Stop that!
Natsumi only wins because of her breasts.
That's not true.
Onee-chan!
I might be a really lucky man, getting to live under
the same roof as these three beautiful girls.
Eruptions of a volcano... I didn't think that
was in the cards for my lifetime, but...
It's possible that it might actually happen.
You wouldn't expect that... normally.
Do you have a minute?
I heard everything from Akina.
I'm Byakudan Midori, and this is Himenohara Suzuran.
Suzu and I are Akina's childhood friends.
If you don't know something, please ask me.
Th-Thanks for your concern.
Haru-kun, here's your lunch.
This is the first time I've made lunch for
Haru-kun, so I really tried my best.
You're really close, huh?
But be careful.
Akina is the school idol, so it's better
if you don't make any enemies.
I told Akina that I'd accompany
her to her club activities, but...
Where's the pool?
Anyway, Akina has great style.
Or so I wish.
There's no way she'd have a swimsuit like that.
What the hell was that about?
Akina really works hard as well.
I need to go to the bathroom.
This is what rush hour in the city is like, huh?
Never mind what happened yesterday.
I'm really glad I came here.
Hey, Haru-kun. In that place...
I-It's hitting my butt.
Haru-kun, that should I do about that?
S-Sorry.
I'm moving back already!
Sorry, I was pushed.
Haru-kun, don't move it.
If you go on like this...
When guys grow there, they won't settle
down until they cum, will they?
I'll make you cum, so...
Huh!?
Shh, if you're too loud, we'll be exposed.
Is that right?
Akina, where did you learn that?
N-No, your penis got caught.
A-Akina, this is bad.
It feels good.
Haru-kun, you can't!
Don't rub it there.
Haru-kun, it's incredible. It's showing from under my skirt.
I'm going to cum.
W-Wait, Haru-kun!
I did that.
I'm sorry, Akina. It wasn't on purpose.
Haru-kun, this...
Don't I have to drink it?
What?
I wonder if Akina is mad about
what happened this morning?
It ended up like that, but it was just
an accidental emission, wasn't it?
Either way, who knew that Haru-kun was so big.
What am I thinking about!?
A-Akina, I'm sorry about this morning.
That's right!
If my uniform got stained, clearing it would be really hard!
Haru-kun's an idiot!
Hey, it's dangerous!
Akina!
Ah, Akina-chan is late.
Good grief.
Be careful.
H-Haru-kun, thank you.
So much happened today that I'm really tired.
I know it's dangerous, but I think
just a little more would be okay.
You were watching again, weren't you?
M-Mafuyu...
Come in.
Th-This is... Umm...
Don't move, you peeping Tom.
You got aroused from watching me masturbate, right?
If you want me to keep it secret from Akina and the rest,
show me where you cum from, Haruomi.
H-Hey, Mafuyu...
Where I cum from? You mean...
You've become like this.
I'll help you.
H-Hey, Mafuyu!
Shut up.
I'm good, aren't I?
I read about this in a book.
Haruomi is a pervert.
It's so aroused and stiff.
You want more stimulation, right?
Cold...
How's my foot?
Does it feel good?
This is bad. I'm not a masochist,
but it does feels good.
You're a man, and yet you're feeling pleasure
from the touch of a woman's foot.
You're so disgusting.
You want to cum already, don't you?
You want to release all that pent-up semen.
You're so cute, Haruomi.
You've become all red.
Your dick's become so big.
All right, cum. Release it. Spurt it on my leg.
I'm cumming...
This is semen.
Th-That Mafuyu...
But it felt good.
Natsumi-san?
Since tomorrow's the end of semester ceremony,
maybe I should go and help Natsumi-san?
Th-This is...
Natsumi-san's shop?
Thank you, Haru-chan.
No need. I'm always glad to do you a favor.
But there aren't any customers.
That's it.
Since I took over the shop, the number
of customers has decreased.
N-Natsumi-san, it's overflowing.
But this shop is one of the things
that Dad left, so it's all right.
You don't have to worry, Haru-chan.
Natsumi-san has a strange charm.
She's really childish, but oddly enough,
at times she's really erotic.
Whatever you say, she has big, beautiful breasts.
Yeah, yeah. They're soft just like that.
Haru-chan, if you love breasts so much,
why don't you fondle them?
Natsumi-san!?
Haru-chan, you're so cute.
Natsumi-san, wait a sec...
Haru-chan, do you have an erection already?
Look, it's become so stiff. You don't have to be embarrassed.
Since I made you like that, I have
to take responsibility, don't I?
Haru-chan, please use my breasts to feel good.
N-Natsumi-san, this is dangerous.
My, my. Haru-chan's penis has become really big.
You really love breasts, Haru-chan.
It's incredible.
Natsumi-san's breasts are so soft.
I became excited as well from
seeing Haru-chan's sturdy penis.
I'll cum. I'm cumming, Natsumi-san!
It's okay. Spurt a lot of semen!
This is Haru-chan's...
I've become live this because of you, Haru-chan.
Please take responsibility.
You mean...
Please have sex with me.
Natsumi-san, we shouldn't do this!
I-It's incredible. This is Haru-chan.
Natsumi-san, is this your first time?
Don't worry about the small stuff, Haru-chan.
But...
Haru-chan is so cute.
You can move now.
Natsumi-san!
H-Haru-chan's big penis is burning inside me!
Natsumi-san, are you going to cum?
Yes. Haru-chan's penis is hitting
deep inside me. It feels so good!
Incredible...
Excuse me...
Oh damn, it's a customer!
Natsumi-san?
Whoa, Natsumi-san, you reek of alcohol!
Wait a minute. There's a customer.
Hey, Natsumi-san!
A few days later...
It seems like Natsumi-san hasn't changed at all.
I don't think she remembers anything.
You're going to Natsumi's shop a lot lately, Haruomi.
Do you like her that much?
My!
It's okay with me. I don't care that Haru-kun does.
No, look. You're always taking care
of me, so I'm just helping out.
It's the middle of the summer, but we
don't have big sales or anything.
That's right. You have a car, don't you, Natsumi-san?
How about making it into a mobile stand?
For example, you could move it to the
beach, where there are more people.
That's a good idea.
You have your moments, Haruomi.
Incredible, Haru-kun. You're really trying your best.
Don't treat me like a kid all the time, Akina.
I-I'm sorry.
I'm home.
Didn't Akina have club activities today?
I'll look for her.
What kid sleeps like that?
Dammit.
A-Akina.
Huh? H-Haru-kun!?
Y-Yo.
Why are you here!?
Why? Akina pulled... Umm... No,
sorry. I'm leaving right now.
Wait!
Stay like that a little longer.
S-Stupid, that's enough.
I'm going to get dangerous feelings.
It's all right.
If you're really attracted to me...
You're the sort of splendid man I could sleep with.
If you say that...
I really won't be able to hold back.
Yeah, don't hold back.
You're not a boy anymore, and I'm not a girl either.
Akina.
H-Haru-kun!
No!
Haru-kun, my uniform will smell because of this.
Uh... yeah.
Akina.
Akina, lick it.
Okay.
When I look this closely, it seems really difficult.
Don't force yourself if it's impossible.
I'm not forcing myself.
I'm just wondering if I can do it right.
I'll be happy with anything if you're doing it.
Good, there. It's really good there.
Really? I'm glad.
I'll do it more.
I'm amazed that Akina would do this for me.
Akina, it's incredibly good there.
This is bad!
Sorry. I came in your mouth.
I'm all right. You felt good, didn't you?
Yeah, really.
Now it's your turn.
Haru-kun!
N-No, Haru-kun!
Akina, you're so wet.
But...
Akina, I want to put it inside you.
All right.
Come, Haru-kun.
It's in.
Did it hurt, Akina?
Y-Yeah, for a second. Now it's faded.
I'm going to move, Akina.
O-Okay.
No!
Akina, it feels awesome!
I'm going to cum already!
Haru-kun, it's still hard.
You want to cum more, don't you?
It's okay. I'm really happy that I can
make you feel good, Haru-kun.
Akina.
Akina, you're tightening up so much.
Haru-kun! Haru-kun!
Akina! Akina!
Haru-kun, I'm going to cum!
Let's cum together, Akina!
Akina, you're treating him too well.
Haru-chan, did something happen
between you and Akina-chan?
N-Nothing...
That's right! Haru-kun is still going
to help you with your shop.
Haru-kun, hurry, we'll be late!
Friendly Akina...
Tolerant Natsumi-san...
Devilish Mafuyu...
Come on, we're going!
Ah, okay.
Life's gonna become even more interesting from now on.
Haru-kun, not in a place like this...
Akina...
My sisters will notice.
Haru-kun...
If you do it like that, I'm gonna...
Haru-kun.
Like this?
Yeah, stroke it like that.
It's so long that the tip pokes out.
Your breasts are big,
so it feels great, Akina.
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Haru-kun, did that feel good?
Yeah. Akina, keep doing it like that.
My breasts are wet with your cum.
Akina, I just came, so if you lick that spot...
Exciting Life With Three Sisters
Complete Edition
Why did you come here, Honnouji...
His name is Honnouji Tsukasa.
He's the type that gets carried away easily,
or should I say that he's the class troublemaker.
I have no idea why he's always clinging on to me.
It's not that. This is really bad, Haruomi.
That 101 ice cream is finally coming to this neighborhood.
I'm talking about the 101!
The 101? What's that?
Hello, Honnouji-kun.
Akina-hime!
What brings the three of you here?
We heard that a 101 is opening nearby,
so we wanted to take a look while we were out shopping.
And to check out how you're doing, too.
So, that's a 101?
It's incredible! It's the biggest company in Japan.
Its reputation and sales were the finishing blow to my shop!
Your family runs an ice cream chain as well, right?
All gone now...
My social status and fame as the
number one man in Tanabata
and the son of the president of Hagge Dazs.
You don't have either social status or fame.
You've just been a clown all along.
So, where's that 101 going to open?
There.
You've gotta be kidding.
Bye, Haru-kun. We're going to take a look.
Let's go, Suzu.
Rain?
I'm already busy just studying for exams.
And now it's gotten even worse.
I-I'm gonna leak!
Shit! Toilet!
I-I'm sorry, Himenohara. Are you all right...
What!?
Himenohara, wait, what!?
Hey, Honnouji,
do you think you're allowed to bring that to school!?
An angry class rep would be second best after Akina-hime.
You jerk!
H-Himenohara...
Stop that.
Hey, did you have that on during class?
And that last time as well?
It feels good,
but even if you don't do it, I'm not gonna tell anyone.
So do this with someone you like!
Penstemon.
Penste... what?
Stop that, Himenohara! Anything more will turn out badly!
There's no way around it. I have to get her to finish quickly.
H-Himenohara, you're too loud.
I can't take it! This is bad, I'm gonna cum inside!
Haru-kun, what happened? You're spacing out.
No, it's nothing.
Haru-chan, are you tired?
N-No.
By the way, it seems like there's a 101 opening nearby.
Their ice cream is really tasty, right?
Wait, onee-chan, they're our rival.
It's a very big shop.
Is it? I have to think of something, don't I?
Mafuyu, you think a little as well.
Don't rely on Natsumi-san all the time.
Haru-kun!
You're just a peeping...
"Peeping?"
No, it's nothing!
Mafuyu is thinking with us, right?
Shit, that damned Mafuyu!
What's with this?
That's all of them.
I'm not having and luck today.
That girl...
Natsumi-san, I'm gonna take out the trash.
Oh my, Haru-chan, that's...
Natsumi gave me this job.
Is that so?
But if I help, you're gonna have an easier time as well.
You're disgusting.
I'll be right back.
Great.
Akina-hime is just the best!
You...
As I'd expect, I'm safe because of your large body.
Hey, give it a rest!
By the way, Himenohara's not here.
What are you recording!?
You reap what you sow.
Boys are such jerks.
Haru-kun, it hurts.
What a gorgeous smile.
I'm going to the infirmary,
so I'll leave the rest to you.
Infirmary
I'm sorry, can I have some band-aids?
Huh?
The Doctor's out.
Is someone here?
Himenohara, huh?
Wait, what's she holding!?
If somebody finds that here, it's gonna be bad.
Wait a minute, Shiki-kun.
What are you doing?
"What?"
Th-This is... Wait, don't misunderstand!
I can explain everything!
It's okay. I understand.
I know...
that you and Suzu were...
at school...
But you have Akina, don't you!?
Himenohara and I...
Please, break up with Suzu!
Of course, I'm not asking you to do that for nothing.
I'll let you do whatever you want to me.
D-Do whatever I want?
You just want to have sex.
Sex? Byakudan, you're...
Don't run away, Shiki-kun.
I'll prove it to you.
Wait!
See? Your dick's gotten so big.
W-Wait a second! This is...
You get aroused even if I'm not Suzu.
A-Any girl will do.
Could you be...
Wh-What? I know how to do it!
This is a man's dick.
It's so big and warm.
My body feels hot!
No, my mind is going blank!
Byakudan?
Byakudan, I'm gonna cum! Watch out!
Y-You came so much, but you're still not satisfied, are you?
Byakudan?
Come, Shiki-kun.
I'll make you forget all about Suzu.
What's with you? Jeez.
Shiki-kun, you're a brute. D-Doing something like this.
Not there!
You're soaked.
Here I come.
Come, I'm gonna satisfy that big dick.
Byakudan, as I thought, you're...
This much is nothing.
I know.
I'm gonna start moving.
Incredible, I can't get enough!
Is this what sex is like?
I-It feels good...
Su...
I-It's not like that!
This is...
Is it possible that she heard everything?
Wait a second, Shiki-kun?
Don't do that, Suzu!
No, no!
Suzu!
Himenohara, not there!
I'm cumming!
Suzu!
I'm home.
You're home as well?
It's your mating season, huh?
What's with her?
Hey, what is this?
Is it interesting?
Ma... fuyu...
Did you get aroused?
N-No.
Punishment time.
Eh?
Hey, Mafuyu, what's the meaning of this?
Resistance is futile.
Resist? What do you mean?
Haruomi, you're interested in those
sorts of things, aren't you?
Do you want to try them with me?
L-Like I would.
Are you scared?
N-No, that's not what I mean.
So, Haruomi, what's this?
Th-That's because earlier...
If you listen to me, I'll make you feel better.
Where did you...
Your body has high endurance.
Your dick is so stiff.
It feels good, right?
How about this?
This slender sensation is dangerous.
Haruomi, your dick is all red, and you look desperate.
You're making such a cute expression.
Are you about to cum already?
Mafuyu, wait!
You came already? You're so cute, Haruomi.
You're such a beast. You're still so stiff.
It tastes strange.
M-Mafuyu, could you untie me?
Don't mind it. Stay still.
Incredible...
What is this? She's sucking it whole-heartedly.
Here.
Ma-Mafuyu...
Can you put up with it?
I'm gonna make you feel even better now.
It's your first time, right? Don't force yourself.
It's okay. You be quiet and...
show me the expression you make when
you're feeling good, Haruomi.
Mafuyu!
It's all right. Don't move.
Jeez, it's because you're always so rash.
Wait, I'll make you feel good.
Haruomi...
You're wet. Are you feeling it?
Not really.
You're not cute at all.
You're too cheeky.
Wh-What?
In that case, I'll ask your body directly, Mafuyu.
How is it, Haruomi? You're about to cum, aren't you?
You're still saying things like that?
I have to punish such a cheeky girl.
Haruomi... Inside me... It's so hot inside me!
You're finally being honest.
Just a little bit more!
Mafuyu, here I come!
Haruomi, more, more!
I'll cum. I'm gonna cum, Mafuyu!
Jeez, she pushed herself too hard.
I think you're cute when you're more honest.
Good morning.
You woke up really early today.
Did something happen?
Lunch.
Lunch?
I'm gonna make lunch for Haruomi.
Huh?
What!?
Oh right, I haven't thought of anything to counter the 101.
Haruomi, what's this about?
What do you mean?
You bastard, you went to the beach with this glorious trio?
"Bastard", you say?
Why didn't you invite me!?
Akina-hime was there in a swimsuit
with Natsumi-san and Mafuyu-tan!
Honnouji...
you're creating a serious misunderstanding here.
So, that's the problem?
What do you think about these?
They look like maid uniforms, but.
I've never seen them before.
I mean, aren't they too high quality?
To be honest, I made these.
Haruomi, this is my once m a lifetime wish.
You can have my camera
but I want you to let me photograph
Natsumi-san and the rest wearing.
First of all, you're.
Wait a second.
We have a deal.
U-Umm.
We're going to sell ice cream wearing these outfits?
Wow, it's cute.
Why are they just the right size?
I think our shop is lacking a theme.
That's h, with the impact these
will make, we're sure to succeed!
But don't they look like clothes for a sex shop?
Not at all.
They're really cute.
You wear this, Haruomi.
Huh?
Then, let's use it on the next holiday.
Eh? Onee-chan!
Welcome!
It's promotion day at MinMin-Ice!
MinMin-Ice gives service now!
Please take a look.
Today, you get twice the vanilla for your money.
Then I'd like a double scoop of vanilla.
Okay, one double vanilla.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Close for the Day
We did it, onee-chan!
We sure did, Akina-chan!
Haruomi is dead.
Akina, I'm coming in.
You liked it that much?
H-Haru-kun, knock!
You don't have to cover yourself.
It really suits you, Akina.
Haru-kun...
Haru-kun, you worked really hard.
So today, I'm just your maid.
Haru-kun, it's embarrassing.
Today, maid Akina is going to give me some service, right?
Y-Yeah.
It's so warm, Haru-kun.
Your technique is incredible, Akina.
Your tongue is entwining around me. It feels awesome.
Can you make me cum, Akina?
Yes, my mouth will make you feel even better.
I'm gonna cum, Akina!
Akina...
N-No, that's...
The way you do it is so lewd.
They've swelled so much.
When did you become such a perverted girl?
It's not like that.
Akina, it's incredible. You're so wet.
Here, can you hear that sound?
No, Haru-kun, don't do that!
Put it in already!
Here I come.
You're so warm inside, Akina.
I feel like I'm melting.
I'm cumming, Akina!
Haru-kun!
It's hitting me!
Your big dick is hitting my womb!
Akina, one more time!
You can't! You just came inside me!
Haru-kun, you're cumming inside me too often!
It's too much!
Akina! I'm cumming again!
Your sperm is brimming over!
Incredible! It's so slippery with my sperm!
I can't take it!
No! Haru-kun, me too! I'm going to cum again as well!
Akina! Akina!
Incredible, I didn't know I could cum this much.
Jeez, Haru-kun. You overdid it.
Akina, that's enough.
Haru-chan's dick is as sturdy as always.
I'm going after Natsumi.
N-Natsumi-san, huh? You remember...
Oh my, Haru-chan, it's a secret.
Haruomi, I'm next.
Haru-kus is mine.
It's punishment for keeping it from us.
You won't get ahead of us.
Jeez!
Well then, Haru-chan...
...we're starting the service.
Akina...
Thank goodness, Haru-kun is back to normal.
Akina-chan, we're...
...getting married.
Thank you, Akina.
What!?
And so, the hero regained his true form and
lived happily ever after with his lovers.
Ma-Mafuyu?
Did you get wet?
Akina-hime...
All over my homework...
Exciting Life With Three Sisters
Complete Edition
Shiki-kun's lunch looks splendid, doesn't it?
Did something happen, Akina?
N-Not really.
F-For once, Haru-kun and I are...
Did Haru-chan say that?
Well, about that...
Haruomi is just being horny.
He's not...
Haru-chan belongs to everyone.
Well, Haru-chan is a boy, so when there are
such charming women close to him...
I don't believe anyone could blame
him if he changed his mind.
W-Wait a minute, you two!
Natsumi-san, I'm going now.
Wait, Haru-kun, your lunch!
Here.
Thank you.
Huh?
I'm off.
Huh? It's quite edible.
Actually, it's delicious.
Yo, Haruomi.
Do you think MinMin-Ice can win this year?
The competition: Tanabata Distnct's
Ice Cream Products Fair.
The summer festival starts next week, right?
On its last day, the local bigshots run it.
Didn't you know that?
Your shop received first prize three years in a row,
and my company took third place last year.
Well, MinMin-Ice is delicious, so it's only natural.
To begin with, putting aside national
brands like Golden Stone and 101,
there's no way Hagge-Dazs could win
against the tastiness of MinMin-Ice.
I know that! But I want a match!
A match?
That's right. This isn't a favor, it's a proposal.
Contract
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Give me one of your recommended ice creams.
Done.
All right! If my company wins first prize,
I'll make you do whatever I want!
And you'll really do a commercial for MinMm-Ice for free.
And no peeping photos for the rest of your life!
I got it!
Oh, I forgot to mention, my company joined
the 101 Group, so if 101 wins, I win too.
What!?
Akina, Akina, Akina-hime...
I'm home.
For goodness sake, there's no way
Natsumi-san's ice cream could lose.
Well, if we can get more exposure for the shop
this way, and stop Honnouji's devilish acts,
we'll kill two birds with one stone.
Welcome home.
Wha...
Did I surprise you?
Of course you did!
He he he.
What's wrong with her?
Natsumi-san, there's something I want to...
It's not enough after all, right?
I knew that. With this...
At this rate...
It's not good enough.
Natsumi-san...
What's wrong, Shiki-kun?
Byakudan, can you read this?
It's about herbs.
Herbs?
Yup, herbs. You use them to make ice cream.
I see, ice cream.
I could translate it for you.
Really? That would be a big help.
All right then, but eill you come to the rooftop for a minute?
It can get this big?
You sure are in high spirits, Shiki-kun.
Well, it seems like I have too much energy lately...
But if it's yours, it actually looks kind of cute to me.
Huh?
Byakudan, you're actually pretty perverted.
This is just for practice.
If you don't like it, I can just stop, okay?
Okay, I get it.
Sheesh.
It's gotten so hard...
You're the perverted one here, Shiki-kun.
Let me hear your cute voice, Shiki-kun.
I didn't expect Byakudan to be this good at it...
Oh, no... I'm...
I'm... cumming...
Wow, there's this much...
Now, just as you promised...
Huh?
Wait a...
Byakudan!?
That's enough.
Stop! Byakudan! Wait!
Haru-chan, thank you for finding that notebook.
No, it's nothing.
That notebook has herb ice cream recipes that my dad used.
When I received it from you, I was really happy!
You saved me again.
Don't mention it. I'm happy that I could help.
Huh? Natsumi-san?
Haru-chan, you're so cool.
Thanks. Wait, not that.
Natsumi-san, look behind us! Hurry up!
We need lavender that grows only on that island.
You like this place quite a lot, don't you?
Yes. Dad used to take a boat out,
and we often went to pick them.
Ah, but we don't have a boat anymore.
Still, as Akina-chan would say,
we have hard-working Haru-chan.
Come again?
You're both late.
Jeez, onee-chan, you're too fast.
Using the car was against the rules.
Huh? Where's Haru-kun?
He's working hard.
Shit! I'm not getting closer at all!
I can't move.
Haru-chan, you're awesome!
My pleasure.
Take a break, Haru-kun. I'll help out in your place.
Here, Haru-kun. Good work.
Yeah, thanks.
Huh? Where's Mafuyu?
Mafuyu-chan's upstairs selling fortunes.
Ah, there you are.
Looks like you took your work seriously.
That's rude.
Is it tasty?
Yeah.
Haruomi, draw your fortune.
Fortune? All right.
Another clichéd result.
Bad Luck
One more!
Your everyday deeds have surfaced, huh?
It's not like "Bad Luck" is so bad.
Are you trying to cheer me up?
The Person You're Waiting For
There's already a blond, long-haired girl near you. You should choose small things over big ones.
Haru-chan, thank you for the lavender.
It's a cheap price to pay if this helps
your ice cream become even tastier.
MinMin-Ice's gonna take first prize this year again.
We won't lose to some 101 shop, right?
Ah, I'll pack up.
It's fine.
S-Sorry.
Haru-chan, thank you.
I have a feeling that ever since you came to our home,
everyone's been a lot livelier.
It's the other way around, Natsumi-san.
I'm grateful to all of you.
Though there are times you really wear me out.
That's the Haru-chan I love.
N-Natsumi-san?
Please stand still.
Natsumi-san, wh-what is this?
I'll make you cum a lot and relieve your fatigue.
Natsumi-san, it feels great.
Your nipples have gotten so hard.
And your dick's standing so straight.
Natsumi-san...
What is it, Haru-chan?
Haru-chan?
Haru-chan, you really love breasts, don't you?
Your breasts are too wonderful, Natsumi-san.
Feel them some more.
Natsumi-san.
Your breasts are so soft.
Oh, Haru-chan, you're silly.
Haru-chan, how do you like this?
Th-They're so soft, and they feel great.
Natsumi-san...
Your dick is going in and out. It's kind of lewd.
Are you about to cum, Haru-chan?
The pressure of your breasts is awesome.
I'm gonna cum already.
I'm cumming, Natsumi-san!
Natsumi-san...
Haru-chan...
Your butt is so big and soft.
Haru-chan, you can't do something like that.
It went inside you so easily, Natsumi-san.
Haru-chan, do it already.
Natsumi-san, here I come.
It's great! Your dick is hitting me inside.
Haru-chan, please fondle my breasts more, much more!
It's so warm deep inside you.
I feel good too.
Your dick's reaching deeper and deeper.
I'm gonna cum, Natsumi-san.
Cum inside me, Haru-chan!
Plenty or your thick cum!
It's certainly tasty, but...
How is it?
It's tasty, but isn't it the same as always?
It's better this way.
Huh? Why?
There are three more days before the contest.
Somehow, I'm getting worried.
I'm home.
I-Is this a dream?
Umm, y-you know...
We're really gonna get dizzy.
Damn Mafuyu, she came in out of
the blue and won't say a word.
What's going on?
Haruomi, you're horny again.
W-Well, I can't help it, because I'm in
a situation like this with a cute girl.
I'm cute?
Well...
...that's when you're being a little more honest.
You're the only one who says that.
Mafuyu, we really have to get out soon.
You like girls with bigger breasts more, Haruomi?
That doesn't matter.
It moved again.
Y-Yeah, well...
As I thought, you're a beast.
Sit still.
M-Mafuyu, where did you learn this?
Your dick grew even bigger.
Haruomi, turn this way.
Even my breasts can make you feel good.
I don't think it's possible.
I can't win against those two like this.
Like this.
If you do it like this, it's pleasant too.
I-I knew that!
Your dick's gotten big and red.
It feels so good that you're about to cum, right?
Yeah, it feels good, Mafuyu.
You can cum, Haruomi.
I'm gonna cum!
Here it comes!
What are you doing, Haruomi?
Look...
You're soaked, Mafuyu.
Haruomi, don't. It feels too good.
You're about to cum, right?
N-Not there...
Was it good?
Y-Yeah.
And you're still this hard.
If you want to, I can let you put it in.
You "can let me"?
Put it in!
Fill me up with your huge dick!
How is it, Mafuyu? Do you feel good?
It feels good!
Your dick is hitting me inside. I'm gonna cum!
Your dick's gonna make me cum!
I'm gonna cum too! I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Pour lots of cum inside me, Haruomi!
It's going in... A lot of your cum...
Tomorrow's the competition, huh?
I have a feeling that I wasn't any help after all.
What's left is to help Natsumi-san.
You forgot something.
Did you fall for me?
L-Like I would!
Have faith in Natsumi.
Huh?
It has a gentle taste.
The ice cream isn't excessively extravagant,
so the main focus is its taste.
I did something unforgivable the other day.
But you came to us again.
As I thought, you're just like him.
It was delicious. Thank you.
Thank you for your patronage.
42nd Tanabata District Ice Cream Competition
Main Conference Hall
Natsumi-san, what are the results!?
Not good. 101 snatched the first prize.
N-No way.
Onee-chan, it says here that our shop received first prize!
Huh?
For some reason, 101 is leaving the
Tanabata district tomorrow,
so they lost the right to participate in the competition.
Hey, isn't that the man who used to work at dad's shop?
Now that you mention it, I have a feeling
that I've seen him somewhere before.
I'm sure of that.
Oh my, welcome.
What's going on?
We've come to take Shiki-kun for a supplementary lesson.
Supplementary?
You're my enemy.
That's the way you introduce yourself?
It's what my intuition tells me.
Oh my, you're so popular, Haru-chan.
Akina, Natsumi, a temporary cease-fire.
Cease-fire?
It seems like this problem has no chance of getting solved.
Shiki-kun!
Haruomi ran away.
Wait a minute, Haru-kun!
Those are the most suitable clothes to make
the very best of Akina-hime's charm after all.
That's what you meant?
All right, next time, I'm gonna have her
wear the swimsuit I made and...
All right, here we go.
Three, two...
Welcome to the MinMin-Ice.
Presented by Erobeat & biribibi
http://www.erobeat.net
http://biribiri.techsuki.net
Translation: biribiri
Editing: Collectr, GeroGE, Len
Timing: PlasticYakuza, Nicolai
Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Quality Check: Chaosrains, Afro Thunda
softsub: торрент иваниваныч