Haru-kun.. Not in a place like this..
Akina..
My sisters will find out..
Haru-kun.. If you keep touching me like this, I..
Haru-kun..
Like this?
Yeah, keep moving like this.
Haru-kun's penis has grown so big.. You're almost coming, aren't you?
Akina's breasts are so big too.. Feels good.
Coming! I'm coming!
Haru-kun, did you enjoy it?
Yeah.. Akina, keep going like this.
Haru-kun's semen has made my breasts so wet..
Akina.. I just came, but if you lick me there, I'm gonna..
Huh?
Kanojo x Kanojo x Kanojo
~ Exciting Life With Three Sisters ~
Episode 2: Meetings In Bathroom, Infirmary, Maid Paradise
By perverts fans, for fans
neregate.wordpress.com
Bizounours Presents :
His name's Honnoji Tsukasa, the girls' number one enemy.
Or rather, the nuisance of the classroom.
I don't know why, but he's been following me around.
Anyway, the situation's bad, Haruomi.
Those One O One ice creams have finally arrived in this town!
Hmm?
This is One O One we're talking about!
One O One? Isn't that-
Good afternoon, Honnoji-kun.
Ah! Akina-Hime!
What's with the three of you together?
We heard that a One O One has opened nearby.
And since we had some shopping to do, we decided to come have a look.
We stopped to see how you were doing.
Hmm.
So, One O One is-
They're amazing!
They are very notorious in Japan.
Our shop is having a hard time because of them!
Oh, if I recall correctly, Honnoji-kun's parents own an ice cream chain, don't they?
It's all over..
Tanabata's number one sponsor is history now.
(Note: Tanabata is a Japanese festival)
As the son of the chain owners, I feel like I lost my pride and honor.
But you don't have any pride or honor, do you?
You're always having fun making us cry.
So, where is that "One O One" going to open?
Over there.
Heh?!
Are you kidding me..
Well then, see you Haru-kun. We'll go and have a look.
Let's go, Suzu.
Rain?
I already got my hands full studying for the exams;
things have turned out quite troublesome..
I-I'm gonna leak out!
This is bad! Bathroom! Bathroom!
S-Sorry, Himenohara!
Are you o.. kay?!
EEEEEEEEEEH?!
Hi-Himenohara! Wai-
Honnoji!
Do you really  think it's alright to bring this at school?
Angry Class Rep sends out a good aura, just like Akina-Hime.
You..!
Hi-Himenohara..
S-Stop it!
You..You've had this  the whole time during classes?!
Could it be that.. the other day too?
It does feel good but.. even without this, I won't tell anyone about it.
You should do these kind of things with someone you like.
It makes no difference.
No diff.. What?
S-Stop it Himenohara! We'll be in trouble if we go any further!
I've got no choice.. I have to end this fast.
H-Himenohara.. Your voice is too loud!
No use.. This is bad! I'm gonna cum insi-
Haru-kun, what's wrong? You're spacing out.
Heh? A-Ah, it's nothing.
Haru-chan, are you tired?
N-Not at all!
Ah, by the way, next time we'll be able to go to One O One.
Ah! Their ice creams are really delicious!
W-Wait a minute, Onee-chan! They're rivals, you know?
It's a really big shop.
Is that so? I guess I'll have to think of something.
Mafuyu, you should try to think a bit about it too.
Always blindly relying on Natsumi-san and all..
Haru-kun!
You peeping Tom, what's with you?
Peeping..?
Ah, nevermind!
Mafuyu will think about it for sure! Ha.. Ha! Ha!
Damn it.. That Mafuyu!
That hurts..
What the hell is that?
All right.
Sigh, I'm out of luck today.
She's..
Natsumi-san, I'll go put the garbage outside.
Oh, Haru-chan, that's-
That's the task Natsumi gave to me.
Is that so? But if I help out too, you can have it easy, no?
You make me sick.
Eh?
I'm off.
Nice!
Akina-Hime's the best, as usual!
You..
That's Haru-kyun for you. Your body's big, it's helps out pretty good!
Hey, you! Stop this at once, will you?
By the way Class Rep, Himenohara's not here today.
What do you think you're filming right now!
How shameless. Boys are really-
Ha-Haru-kyun, it hurts..
A priceless action.
Well then, I'm off to the infirmary. I leave the rest to you!
Excuse me, do you have some plasters or somethi.. Eh?
The Sensei's not here..
Is someone there?
Oh, it's Himenohara.
Geez, what the hell is she holding?!
If someone finds this here, things will turn out bad!
Wait a minute, Shiki-kun. What are you doing?
What I am doing?
Ah! Erm.. That's.. W-Wait, don't get it wrong! I'll explain everything!
It's okay. I know.
I know it all.
You and Suzu.. At school..
But you have Akina already.. Don't you?
M-Me and Himenohara are-
Please, break up with Suzu.
Eh?
Of course, I'm not asking you to do this for free.
The things Shiki-kun wants to do.. I'll do them to you.
T-The things I want to do..?
I'll have sex with you.
S-Sex?! Byakudan, you..
I won't let you run away, Shiki-kun.
I'll properly show you that I can do it.
W-Wai-
S-See? Your penis has grown so big.
W-Wait a minute, that's-
Be it Suzu or me, the excitement remains the same, doesn't it?
Shiki-kun is fine with any woman, isn't he?
Could it be that you..
W-What now? I'm doing it for you!
T-That's.. A man's cock..
So big.. and warm.
My body feels so hot.. This is bad, my mind's going blank!
B-Byakudan..
B-Byakudan, I-I'm coming!
S-So much came out.. But you're not satisfied yet, are you?
Byakudan, stop..
Come, Shiki-kun. I'll definitely make you give up on Suzu.
What's with all this.. Geez.
Sh-Shiki-kun, you're so gross.. Doing such-
T-That place..!
You're already dripping wet, aren't you?
Let's go.
C-Come. I'll statisfy that big penis of yours.
Byakudan.. As I thought, you're..
T-That much is nothing.
I get it..
I'll start moving.
So damn good.. I can't stop myself!
So this is what people call "having sex with a man"?
F-Feels so good..
Heh?!
Su..!
T-That's not what you think! This is-
Could it be that.. she heard everything?
W-Wait! Shiki-kun!
D-Don't do this, Suzu!
Don't! Don't! Suzu!
Himenohara, that spot is.. This is bad! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Suzu!
By perverts fans, for fans
neregate.wordpress.com
Bizounours Subz
I'm home.
Hmm?
So you're back already.
Teasing me?
Eeh?
What's with her?
Hmm?
Woah.. What's that..
Interesting?
Ma..fuyu?!
Excited?
N-Not really.
Punishment.
Eh?
H-Hey! Mafuyu! What's the meaning of this?!
Turning hostile is a no-no.
H-Hostile? What do you mean by that?
Haruomi, you're interested in that kind of things, aren't you?
Want me to show you?
L-Like I would!
Are you afraid?
N-No, that's not it.
So, Haruomi.. What's that?
T-This is.. From earlier..
If you do as I say, I'll make you feel even better.
You.. Where did you learn such..
Holding it in is bad for your health.
Haruomi's cock is throbbing.
Feels good, doesn't it?
How's that?
This smooth sensation.. This is bad!
Haruomi.. Your cock is enjoying it, right?
Such a cute face.. You're coming, aren't you?
Mafuyu, sto-
So you came already? How cute, Haruomi.
What a beast you are, Haruomi: Still so erected..
Strange taste..
Ma-Mafuyu.. Won't you untie my hands?
Enough. Just stay still.
Amazing.. What's this.. She's no amateur at sucking.
There..
Ma-Mafuyu..
Think you can bear it? It's going to feel much better now.
It's your first time, isn't it? Don't push yourself.
I'm fine. Just keep quiet, Haruomi.
Let me have a look at your pleasured face.
Mafuyu!
It's fine! Just don't move!
Geez, you're always so pushy.
Just wait up, I'll make you feel good.
Ha-Haruomi..
You're getting wet. Are you feeling it?
Not really..
You're not being cute at all.
It's just Haruomi.. Don't get too full of yourself.
I see.
Wh-What now?
Well then, I'll ask Mafuyu's body directly.
How's that, Haruomi? You feel like coming, don't you?
You're still saying such things?
Bad kids need to be punished.
Haruomi.. I'm feeling so hot.
You've finally become honest.
Just a little bit longer!
Mafuyu.. I-I'm coming!
Haruomi! More! More!!
Coming! I'm letting it out, Mafuyu!
Geez, pushing herself like that.
I'm sure you'd be cute if you were a little more honest.
G-Good morning! You're quite early today.
Is something the matter?
Bento.
Bento?
I'll make Haruomi's bento.
Eeh?
EEEEEEEEEEEEH??
Now that I think about it, I haven't thought of any counter plan against One O One.
Haruomi. What's the meaning of this?
What now..
Do you really had to go to the beach with the 3 of them?
"Had to go" you say..
Why didn't you call me too!
Akina-Hime was wearing a swimsuit! Natsumi-san too! Mafuyu-tan too!!
Honnoji.. Can you stop this before people misunderstand the situation?
Heh?
So, what did you want?
Here. What do you think of this?
They look like maid outfits but.. I've never seen that type before.
Anyway, don't you think they look a bit "bold"?
The truth is, I'm the one who made them.
Eeh?
Haruomi, this is my only wish.
You can even borrow my camera.
Make Natsumi-san and the others wear this, and film them for me-
Geez, you're always so..
Oh, wait a minute..
Alright, I'll do it.
Erm.. This is..
W-We must sell our ice creams wearing this?
Waah! So cute!
How come it's right size?
What our shop lacks right now is.. young waitresses!
But with so much impact, we'll succeed for sure!
But you know.. Won't it look like some perverted shop?
T-That's not true! It's really cute!
Haruomi will wear this.
Huh?
Well then, let's do the next shift without delay!
Eeeeh?! Onee-chan!
Welcome! BB Ice is currently having a service campaign!
Special service for MiMi ice creams!
Wait in line, please.
Today, we have a special reduction on vanilla flavor!
Well then, can I have a double vanilla, please.
Okay. Vanilla, was it? Here you are.
Thanks for your patronage.
We did it, Onee-chan!
Yes, Aki-nee-chan!
Haruomi.. is dead.
Akina, I'm coming in.
Do you like it that much?
Eh?! H-Haru-kun! At least knock!
There's no need to hide it, don't you think? It suits you very well, Akina.
Haru-kun..
Haru-kun, you really did your best today, didn't you? Today, I'll be Haru-kun's only maid.
Haru-kun.. That's embarrassing.
Today, Maid Akina will do what I want as a reward, no?
Y-Yeah..
Haru-kun's penis feels really hot..
Akina's fellatio is amazing. The way you suck it.. feels so good.
Will you let me cum, Akina?
Sure. My mouth will make you feel even better.
I'm coming, Akina!
Akina..
D-Don't! That's..
The way Haru-kun touches me.. feels really perverted.
To let me do all those things.. When did Akina become such a perverted girl?
That's not true..
Akina.. Amazing, you're so wet!
Can you hear it ?
Haru-kun, don't! Come now.
Let's go.
Akina's inside feels so hot.. like it's melting.
I'm coming, Akina!
It's hitting me.. Haru-kun's big penis is hitting me so deep!
Akina, I'm coming again!
Y-You can't do that! You just came inside a minute ago!
Ha-Haru-kun, you're coming inside too much.. Too much!
Akina, it's coming out again!
Haru-kun's semen.. is overflowing.
It's so wet because of the semen.. This is bad! I'm gonna-
Haru-kun, I'm coming too! I'm coming again!
Akina! Akina!
Incredible.. So much came out..
Geez.. Haru-kun, you're trying too hard.
Akina.. No more..
Heh?!
Haru-chan's penis.. is sturdy as usual.
I'm next after Natsumi.
What?!
Na-Natsumi-san, that's.. Remember!
My my, Haru-chan.. That's a secret.
Haruomi, I'm next.
I'm the one with Haru-kun!
That's punishment for keeping it from us!
You can't have him all for yourself.
Geez.
Well then, Haru-chan..
Let the reward begin.