PANTHEON as Sport Synthetic Facilities,
Many Japan's sport representaive,
hope to get their body trained in this facilities.
A ball game, skate, judo, & the other,
has been prepared in this latest facilities.
I just starting a part-time job at ORCUS office lately....
You have wonderful hand, aren't you?
Good hand it is.
Eh, Saibara-san....
[Saibara Fumiko - Sports Massager]
Among 100 people out there, your hand is golden hand.
What is that mean?
Your hand, let me check it for a moment.
Right~, as I thought!
You had a talent to spouting girls ulterior's skill.
Spouting?
You know isn't it?
Girls have a stimulation spot in that place, that is....
I know it, but that's not related to sport though....
He~, you don't understand aren't you?
You know that all representative in here is aiming for being the top three in here, right?
They don't have any time to think about love & sex right now.
But, we're all in here realizing that it's important to them.
If they're not releasing with properly,
it could make their body damage by oneself.
Is that really true....
Their valueable talent can't let it waste because of that.
That's why they need special massage for them.
Is that..spouting?
That's right, you have a talent to do it.
For the sake of Japan & for the girls, you must cooperate with it.
-Binkan Athlete-
~New Gene 00 H-Subs~
[One month later]
Ooyama Megumi,
I'll be in care with you for special massage.
[Volleyball - Ooyama Megumi]
Yes, pleased to meet you too.
Err.., as I'd been told that I come here without wearing underwear.
Right, then if you would like to lie down over there?
Yes.
All right, let's begin.
Yes....please.
It's fine, you're just have to relax like that.
Wha..what is this....
It's only massage, but why it's feeling like this?
Wa..wait!
Over there....
This is a treatment, for girls this spot is vital part of it.
That is..mm....
How is it, are you feeling good with this?
That is..have a whit more with "feeling good" mean.
Wait, stop it!
I'm trying to release Megumi-san's stress.
Please, leave it to me.
Is this really treatment, right?
Of course.
I can't....
No~!
See, over there is getting wet already.
That is..embarrassing..NO!
That hurts, wait!
No~!
This is the first time....
This is a treatment, please bear with it.
It feel's like till inside of my body, have been massaged.
Then this time, let's start doing breast massage.
Bre..breast?
Over there, it's wonderful.
What's important is Megumi-san feeling good.
That's why, please feel better with it.
Even you said like that, what should I do?
It's better you have pleasant feeling with this.
Don't hesitate & tell me what do you want to do.
I..I understand.
Please play more with my nipple.
My..my breast....
Are you okay with this, right?
I feel's like an awfully indecent girls.
If you think more enough about it,
there's nothing wrong being indecent.
Is..is that really true?
Right now, your just look's like indecent one it is.
Right now..I'm being indecent one, right.
Go..good!
What do you want to do for the next one?
That is..I want you to touch over there.
It's embarrassing~
Then let me loosen this, right.
Eh, that is....
No, till like that....
Over there~
How is it in here?
Over there, my clitoris it's hurt....
Ple..please, more gentle with it.
Is it possible, you're rarely masturbating?
I'm rarely doing masturbation.
Inside of me feel's good..coming out.
Something come out from inside of my body....
It's coming out!
That's the time for you to said "coming out".
Coming out, is this?
Something is coming out~
I'm coming out a lot of it, sorry about that.
Err, you're okay over there?
N..no, this is....
It's just fine, if you're feeling good I'm doing just fine with it.
Th..this time, why don't you let me do it?
That is....
Just because of me, you're thing being like that.
I don't want you hold on it.
I hadn't doing like this before,
doesn't it feel hurts?
Yes, it feel's good.
Please don't think that I would be doing like this to everyone, right.
Your thing is very hot.
Me..Megumi-san, you dont have to do like that....
It's fine, if it's with you,
I'm feeling good too, that's what make me happy.
A, Megumi-san.
Being eaten like this, it feel's good isn't it?
Me..Megumi-san..I can't hold....
It's coming out, right.
Please let it come out, in wherever place that you like.
A, the sperm.
This is..your sperm.
It's warm.
So..sorry, it came out on all over your face.
It's fine, a while ago you make me came a lot too.
-Binkan Athlete-
Can I slide too?
It's fine, today we're the only one left in here.
But, I don't use skate shoes though....
[Skate Figure - Yaginuma Nao]
Even with usual shoes you could slide without problem.
We'll be support you.
[Skate Figure - Yaginuma Shizuku]
Wait..wait a minute!
Right..right, just like that!
Unexpectedly, I could slide with it.
Right, just I told you before.
Then, next one just a little....
You're left behind~
Even you said like that.
If you're worried too much, it could be more dangerous.
It's fast..it's too fast!
Sorry about that~
But, don't you think it's feel interesting?
It hurts..that's too much from two of you.
This is need a little punishment for you two.
Is it really gonna do special massage over here?
Being seen like this, it's embarrassing.
If you're looking this hard....
Did you like looking at my thing?
Finger..your finger on a way in of my thing,
touching it..like it's gonna thrust in.
Being touched like this, it feel's strange,
It's indecent..Nao's thing it's indecent.
I feel's like turning into naugthy girl!
All the time on the skate circle,
when tournament too, I feel's indecent like this.
Shizuku-san, being erotic it's beautiful thing.
Erotic? I am erotic?
Right, over there had been opened like that.
Being soggy like this....
I like erotic girls, you know.
True..is it true?
Then more I'll become,
more erotic one it is.
I'm rapidly become dirty minded.
Wonderful..it's extremely wonderful!
Why..why it become like this?
Is it possible you want to do it yourself?
Don't want to..it look's like I become naughty girl....!
Right, you're the same..doing like this with us,
is it something in your imagination, right?
Rapidly it become..become more filled with it.
Good..it's good..I'm feeling your touch.
Over there & my butt is drenched already.
Your finger..the way your touching it,
I feel's like gonna coming out.
Coming out!!
No..no, it's coming out.
I'm feeling hot over there, still your finger stimulating my thing.
I just can't hold it....I can't..!!
If it's like that..me too..I can't....
Coming out..it's gonna flowing out inside of me.
It's coming out....
Me too..it's coming out....coming out~!
Put it..put it in,
over there..inside of my thing.
Give me your thing inside of me.
Please make my thing more drenched with it,
as my thing already oozing something already.
I'll..I'll put it in, okay.
It's in....
It's inside of it!
Inside of me!!
That big thing....right now,
it's inside of Onee-chan's thing..already.
Please don't see it like that, Nao.
The way you're licking it is wonderful.
I'm feeling it already.
Moving it, I'm moving it with myself.
Even Nao's watching at me~
You're licking at girls important's thing.
The place which I'm feeling it is drenched....
It's getting bigger,
your thing is getting bigger as I moving it.
Onee-chan's movement is getting faster onit.
Not..not on my breast, over there is....
Your nipple is getting this hard.
I know it, cause my nipple too is feeling it.
It's indecent~
Nao too..being licked like that, I'm feeling good too.
My thing..it's sopping wet~, did you feel it?
It's because..because being licked like this make me feel's good.
More..I want you more licked on me~
It's..it's hitting inside of me.
More..I want more....
I'm..I'm moving it myself~
No, I can't hold it anymore~
Coming..it's gonna coming out.
No~
Onee-chan, you're so indecent,
even it's Onee-chan....
Coming out..coming out..coming out!!
Let it out..let it coming out.
Your hot..your hot sperm, let it come inside of me.
Wait..wait Onee-sama, I'm gonna coming out too.
I'm coming out..coming out while Nao is watching at me.
Getting this drenched all over my body....
The smell of sperm....,
with Onee-chan, I got covered with the sperm.
-Binkan Athlete-
Fight, Asaka!
Fight!!
Score it, Asaka!
[Beach Volleyball - Miwa Asaka]
Chance!
That day, Asaka-san became one of Japan's representative.
After interview & victory celebration, one after another,
at last we had a moment to meet, but it's already midnight.
You look good in your swimsuit.
Is..is it true?
I feel's little uncomfortable with it though....
But if you said like that, it makes me happy.
Anyway, in the last day of valuation,
it's great that you'd got good result on it.
Right, but now I couldn't go to Pantheon everyday.
That is....
Ee~, can you do it once again?
Ah, right, if massage's thing we could do it,
when we get back at the hotel.
Not like that, I want to do it right here.
Today it's not only massage, but I want to do sex with you.
No..you're touching over there....
Only a way in of my thing?
It's little out of what I want
Asaka-san, why you want to do it?
Do I have to tell about it? No, it's embarrassing.
Do you really want to hear about it, right?
Yes, I want to hear it.
No..I don't want to, but if you insist of it....
Over there, on my shyly hole..I want your finger put in it,
inside of it....
I want you to stir up inside of it!
I..I said it....
You're coming, give me a lot of it.
Cause today is special favor from me....
There..over there..the way you're touching inside of it,
it feel's good....
Wait..it's about to come out....
Coming..coming out.
It's out..it's coming out!!
It..it came..it came out..it came out....
You've completely had become indecent body it is.
Cause..because you're always doing it....
Even like that, I surprised that you had this far.
No..not like this....
Did you don't want me more like this,
or do you want me to be more "indecent one"?
If I've gotta choose, I prefer indecent girls it is.
I'm..glad to hear it.
Asaka-san?
This time..let me make you feel's good, okay?
Your thing is coming in & out between my breast.
It feel's good.
It's okay to move it.
If you're feeling..if my breast feeling it too,
my breast & your thing rubbing each other.
Can I move little hard on it?
Do as you like, feel free for using my breast on it.
Your thing is getting bigger, you know.
My breast..my breast is getting pliantly.
My breast & my thing is sizzling over your thing.
Your..your hot & hard thing, it's gonna coming out.
It's tickling enough & coming out, right.
Asaka-san, I'm....
Yes, right..it's fine.
Let it..let it out, let your sprem come a lot.
All..let it all out....
Let my breast get drenched of it, let it out!
It came a lot....
your sperm it is....
It feel's like I'm completely being one of your thing.
You're gonna loose it?
Do you feel shy about it?
Be..because it look's strange, right?
A trace of sunburn is remain on it.
That's not a problem.
It's hot..your hot thing is bumping it.
It's in, inside of mine is full of it.
It's clearly stand out, your thing & even your butt hole.
No, I don't want it.
Thing over there..I don't want you to look at my butt.
It's embarrassing.
The way my thing insert of Asaka-san's thing,
it's hanging sealskin on over it.
Be..because..it's hard & overflowed like this....
Everything is seen~
Asaka-san, I'll start it.
Come..come in....
Want this..I really want this.
It's hard..being hitting in & out like this..getting big....
Your spurt is overflowed & your thing is unbreakable,
even your nipple is getting like this, it's so indecent.
Be..cause you keep stir it up,
my nipple get's crunchy & overthere is drenched full of it.
It feel's good, right?
It's fine..it's okay even it's overflowed everywhere,
More..more of it, I want you to squish my deepest thing....
Want it~
You want to get more squish of it?
Yes, I want you smashed it.
I..I really love it, love it!
It's good..it's good..it's good..it's good~
Asaka-san, I'm coming!
Coming out!
I really thank you.
Eh?
Thanks to you, I can get over my slump,
I can be Japan representative too.
Not like that, I just....
No, because of your support,
I can't be ever think of embarrassing.
Today, that's how I feel in my match.
Asaka-san....
That's why today's winning, it's all thanks to you.
For that, I want you to accept it with pleased.
Your thing is stand up again,
do you want to do it one again?
-Binkan Athlete-
-New Gene 00 H-Subs Team-
Translator: Ingrid00
Timer: Moe-chan
Editor: Lily
RAW Provider: Fredericklim
Torrent Uploader: Aardy
Please keep support us by downloading our release!!!!
Thanks for watching hentai movies with our subs^^;!