I'm really sorry for earlier on.
I borrowed your uniform unreasonably.
And I made it dirty.
You don't have to worry.
There are many uniforms around.
But, matters of the heart are different.
As long as both your hearts are connected, nothing else matters.
You're still a child, aren't you?
So this is me?
Compared to her, I'm still so immature.
That's impure. How shameless.
What exactly am I thinking on my own.
Good morning, Sylvie.
You're up early today.
I have morning practice.
Well then, I should be going.
Shameless... Shameless... Shameless...
Doing things like that in broad daylight...
What's wrong with me?
There's no way I can face him properly.
Good morning, Teppei-sama.
Did something happen?
You don't look too well.
No, it's nothing.
You don't seem to be fine.
Alright, this way.
Original Video Animation
Vol. 2: "Unwilling to Spend the Night Alone"
What are you doing?!
This is why you called me here?
Because... you wanted both of us to be alone.
I only wanted to ask how you were doing.
You looked embarrassed.
You too.
You must have been holding it in, right?
Your smell is seducing me.
Arima-dono too.
Haven't you been holding it in?
Yuu-san?
Van Hossen is ignoring you.
It must feel very bad.
That's...
Ever since she moved in here, I haven't had the chance to relieve myself.
J-Just now, that was a lie!
All the porn inside the luggage has been disposed of.
Since it has become this, I thought you didn't have the chance to do it either.
Let me take care of that.
At least have a bit of shame.
It's only been two days since we last did it.
Yet you became like this.
B-Besides, this isn't something that can be done openly.
It's all your fault for ignoring me.
Okay. Let's do it. Do it as you please.
I won't let you blame me unreasonably.
Now...
...swear. Just like a knight would.
I, Sylvia Van Hossen,
...for one day, will become Arima Teppei's...
You can lie, or you can say for eternity.
The promise is only for today.
I swear to be Arima Teppei's subordinate... subordinate for a day.
Well said. You can climax now.
U-Unfortunately, I won't climax with just that.
That place... you can't!
Arima-dono... that's... no!
I got it. I admit.
Please Teppei, can you stop doing that?
I remember this feeling, so please stop.
I beg you, Teppei!
Toilet, let me use the toilet.
I don't want you to see my shameful side.
I want to see everything about you.
Stop this already.
Are you mocking me?
This will make me suffer a humiliation worst than death.
You're my subordinate right? So you don't have the right to decide.
This and that are...
No! Don't!
If you insert it inside, I won't be able to hold it.
I'm reaching my limit.
Teppei.
I'm already begging you this much.
You're such a...
Don't be like this.
I want to see your face when you're feeling good.
I won't let you, I...
I-It's coming...
I can't hold it anymore.
I don't have any strength left.
No, no, don't!
At a place where every student in the school will use.
I left such a filthy smell.
Just clean it up later on and it'll be fine.
You only have to find a cloth or something.
Now we've to.. .
You're such an indignant guy.
Despite how unreasonable you are, you insist on entering my heart.
Not only did you make a lady incontinent,
but you also stood by and watched.
In my eyes, a guy like that is not respectable.
A guy who instantly desires my body as well.
Precisely because I have such desires,
that's why I'm afraid that you'll hate me.
But whenever I am around you, I can't help but want to do it.
If I could, I would have hated you long ago.
Besides, I'm supposed to be a woman at your mercy today.
But, something like today will never...
Don't be so rough right from the start.
I'm starting to feel hot.
My insides!
The shape has been changed.
It's about to break.
I'm inside Sylvie.
You don't need to say things like that.
It's enough if you know it.
I've already become such a woman.
Someone like me who has already lost her etiquette and chastity.
I'm in a mess.
Be it my values, or my dignity.
All of them are gone.
I can't turn back anymore.
You turned me into this.
You have to be responsible for it.
Take responsibility for taking away my heart and my rationale.
You're so mean.
You made me gradually unable to hide my own humiliation.
You only need one shameless slut in me.
From today on, do it with me whenever you feel lonely.
Empty everything inside me!
It's coming soon.
I can feel it getting bigger. It's also throbbing inside me.
Just ejaculate inside me.
It's better than dirtying the uniform.
Also, we don't have to clean up after that.
Hurry! Hurry!
Shoot inside me, my waist is running out of strength.
Climax like we always do... together.
If it's Teppei, I'm about to come...
I'm coming!
Did you settle some of your private issues?
That's true, but she's still so stubborn.
I think she really hates me this time.
In the socialising world, it's not enough just to be able to sweet-talk.
As for Teppei-sama, you still need to learn how to treat a lady.
You could always think of this as good experience.
Experience of getting caught cheating?
This isn't something a maid can teach.
It's great that you can think that way.
Discipline?
This is discipline; that is also discipline.
I see. You intend to continue being wrong.
You can reject it if you dislike it.
For people born into a family of knights, breaking a vow is unacceptable.
That's all.
Now you're my slave.
I have also changed.
I know very well that I'm uncomfortable in a dress.
I'll become a weak woman.
But now I seem to have grown used to it.
How lewd.
You came so much inside me from behind earlier on.
Now you're so hard.
Don't think you can always have your way.
Seriously... It's so hard to the extent that it's embarrassing.
Getting bullied by this hot thing...
Wouldn't it make someone want to change the vow to last for an eternity?
You're beautiful, Sylvie.
More so than anyone else.
You're sweet-talking again.
You're such a shameless person, no matter where you are.
I'm also shameless.
Furthermore, my body has already remembered it.
The fact that I have become your woman.
Gradually pushing it in, it's clearly impossible.
Your thing inside me, it feels extremely good.
Blame me. Blame me for being such a mess.
What used to be a body only for the country...
It's been... By a guy.
Please, Teppei.
At least... Let's at least climax together.
Incredible. I'm coming! I'm coming!
Don't let me do it alone.
I'm coming!
If I simply become pregnant...
I'll finally understand that I'm yours...
N-No, it's nothing.
Just ignore what I just said.
Listening and not speaking is despicable.
I love you.
That's all I want to say.
Saying things like that at a time like this is even more cunning.
But I have also thought about it.
Using staying over as a method to bind you isn't too bad.
Women are very cunning creatures.
Remember this.
Stop being so spoilt, Maria!
Sit at your own place when eating.
Wouldn't that make Teppei feel bad?
If it tastes bad, Maria will say "Ah" and feed you.
Are you alright being abused by my sister?
A guy should never spoil a woman too much.
That was what Papa used to say.
I'm sorry for disrupting the meal.
Teppei-sama, there's something urgent to report.
It's fantastic, even dazzling.
Uniforms are good.
Though for functions, dresses are equally attractive.
This appearance is the Sylvie that I respect the most.
Such thoughtless words will make a person feel flustered at times.
If I haven't met you then, I would never have lost my way.
I won't hesitate to offer my life either.
It's different now.
I'm extremely afraid.
My country has become a battlefield.
What can a mere girl like me do?
Lives might be lost.
We might be imprisoned by other countries.
You never know, I might not be able to return to this country to see you.
Just the thought of that...
I've indeed become your woman.
Even so, you still want to go?
I know that I am a woman who can easily get jealous.
When I'm not around, there will be many others by your side.
Just thinking about things like that,
my resolve is crumbling.
It seems like saying that I'll wait for you is not enough.
I'll let you see my resolve.
Then the one who needs to understand is you, Sylvie.
Show me all your shamelessness.
I understand fully.
I've already been tied to you ever since we first met.
I offer every part of me, as a woman, to you.
I carve myself as a woman onto your man's body.
Carve my lewd and shame into your eyes.
O-Only for you alone to see.
It's hot.
Your fingers are making me melt.
No, I can't take it anymore.
No, I'm coming, I'm coming!
Don't you forget...
Only you...
You're the only person who can see this side of me.
There's only you.
You can laugh at me for being so shameless.
It seems like I am getting immersed into this pleasure.
What's wrong? You're looking down on me for being so shameless?
Didn't you say that I'm dirty tonight?
Not that place!
No way, that filthy place, you can't!
I really can't?
Alright, you can.
My asshole, my asshole...
Is it okay like this?
Yeah. I don't want to leave any parts of your body undiscovered.
I would have felt better if you didn't look directly.
Right now, I feel so embarrassed that I want to die.
But on the other hand, I feel slightly happy.
Because I can finally get my reward.
You can't be serious. This thing is coming in. No way.
Teppei, it feels good!
It feels much better than before.
The size is just right.
That's quite a huge shock to me.
No, I love being one with you.
I want to feel you deep inside me, always.
Master, I can feel where we are connected.
This is the woman whom you promised your eternity to.
I won't let you regret.
Don't you ever forget.
Don't you forget my smile.
We can only meet in dreams...
So it's harder than bearing with it.
How I wish to bring along this heat, this hardness, this shape together with me.
Feels good... It feels good, I'm almost...
So...
It's alright now, shoot it out, shoot all of them out.
Make my asshole know you more.
Empty everything and end this.
I feel it... Your thing.
What did Sylvie say to you?
She warned me not to let my guard down.
Teppei-sama will make use of his shamelessness to target women.
A woman like me will be replaced after one night.
Just what kind of evil man do you take me for?
Doki Fansubs
Translation: ZeroYuki
Everything else: Holo
Doki Fansubs
Translation: ZeroYuki
Everything else: Holo