That's...
You're not needed!
No, I'm coming!
Wow, this is bad...
Are guys from all over the country going to hear this?
I think I did something unbelievable.
Kogawa Yuika
Aoi Kanna
Ah, my name!
N-No one will find out, right?
Nice work, everyone!
Nice work!
This is all thanks to you, Kanna-chan!
That's for sure.
No way, I'm not that...
That's right!
Did you really come while you were acting that?!
Graphics -Harie Natsumi
W-W-What?!
That's so erotic!
Hey, she's already having a hard time, Natsumi.
Graphics -Hirobe Fuyumi
But, well, it's all thanks to you that we successfully completed this thing, Kanna.
Onee-chan...
Good morning!
Hi!
Sakanami-san.
Voice Actor -Shigeichi Sakanami
Sorry for being late!
Oh? Are you Kanna-chan? Yayoi-san's younger sister?
Ah, yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Aoyagi Kanna.
I see... you really are a high school student.
Nice uniform... and you're 16 years old.
That makes my di** hard!
Hey!
atsuku atsuku torokesou de mune ga mune ga kurushiku naru
My chest is feeling hotter and hotter, like it's melting. It's becoming more and more painful.
熱く熱くとろけそうで　胸が胸が苦しくなる
amaku nigai konna kimochi hajimete dayo
It's the first time I've ever had such a sweet and painful feeling.
甘く苦いこんな気持ち　初めてだよ
jugyouchuu demo yume no naka demo kimi no koto bakari
When I am in class or in my dreams, I always think about you...
受業中でも　夢の中でも　きみのことばかり
kamo?!
Perhaps?!
かも？！
basu no naka demo nani shiteite mo yada... kangaeteru
When I am in the bath and no matter what I do, no... I think about you.
バスの中でも　何していても　ヤダ…考えてる
hazukashikute dokidoki shite
I feel embarrassed and my heart is beating.
恥ずかしくて　ドキドキして
kimi ga yorokobu to kimochiyoku naru
It warms me up if you are happy.
キミが喜ぶと気持ち良くなる
motto mitai sonna egao
I want to see more of that smile.
もっとみたい　そんな笑顔
...kore ga koi no mahou?
...is this the magic of love?
…これが☆恋の魔法？
mawaru mawaru chikyuu no ue
On the round, round Earth,
まわるまわるちきゅうの上
kimi to deatta sono hi kara
ever since the day I met you,
きみと出逢ったその日から
dondon ookiku natteku koi sonzai
the existence of love has become bigger and bigger.
どんどん大きくなってく　恋　存在
mou kore ijou wa dame dayo
I can't take any more than this.
もうこれ以上はダメだよ
mou kore ijou wa muri dayo
I can't have any more than this.
もうこれ以上は無理だよ
kore ijou suki ni nattara dou nacchau no?
If I love you any more than this, what will happen?
これ以上好きになったら　ど～なっちゃうの？
My voice douka kotaete
My voice, please answer me.
My voice　どうか答えて
Your voice douka oshiete
Your voice, please tell me.
Your voice　どうか教えて
Doki-Chihiro
Being a Voice Actress in Secret!
Somebody's watching you.
Who is?
A certain guy is glancing passionately in this direction.
A certain guy?
He really did look this way just now.
Hazuki is really popular among guys.
That's what I thought at first,
but it seemed like he was looking at you, Kanna.
Why?
There are different types of glances.
Types of glances?
80% of the glances aimed at me are the ones you look at small animals with.
The other 20% are the ones who want me to call them "Onii-chan"...
I'm coming! I'm scared!
...or perverted glances that want to make pranks.
They're lolicon.
That's disgusting.
In Hazuki's case, almost 100% of them are glances of desire.
They want to squeeze that thing between her boobs, rub it and shoot it at her face.
Is that so?
I lost my appetite.
There are also people who look at you, Kanna,
but Kaizu-kun's glance is different from the others.
How has everyone been looking at me?
Like a cheerful girl.
Maybe Kaizu-kun likes you, Kanna.
He might have wanted to ask you whether you have a boyfriend.
That is possible.
No way!
Why not?
Because... I've never been popular among the boys.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Your glasses didn't break, did it?
Oh what? That's a rather good mood.
Be sure to tell me if you two make any progress.
Motoki, block him!
Could this...
...really be true?
But I like Hioki-oniichan...
...though that may not count as love.
If Kaizu-kun really does like me...
W-What am I thinking?
Seriously... this is all because Hazuki and Kotori were saying weird things!
K-Kaizu-kun.
Ah, Aoyagi-san, are you heading home now?
Yes, my club activities are over.
I see. I am about done with my class rep tasks.
Thanks for the hard work.
Thank you.
This feels awkward...
I can't stand it!
T-Then...
W-Wait!
Um... May I have a little of your time?
W-What is it?
It's hard to say, but there's something that I want to ask no matter what.
Um... I know it's strange for me to suddenly ask you this...
Could it really be?!
Aoyagi-san, you don't happen to be...
...an eroge voice actress, right?
W-Why do you know about that, Kaizu-kun?
So it really is you, Aoyagi-san.
I've always wanted to ask.
He found out. He found out...
Onee-chan!
Somebody found out! One of my classmates found out!
It'll spread around school.
That would be a problem.
I can't go to school! I can't face Kaizu-kun anymore!
Is that kid called Kaizu?
Yeah...
That kid's okay. He won't spread it.
Why?
Perfect timing. We have a meeting at work tomorrow after school.
Can you come to the office?
This is the president of the company working with us for our next job.
I'm Studio Kaiser's Kaizu.
Nice to meet you, I'm Aoyagi Kanna.
Kaizu?
President Kaizu has been taking care of me and Nagatoshi since we started working in this field.
Good morning.
Huh? H-He looks like Kaizu-kun.
H-Hey.
Anyway, he's President Kaizu's son, and just like you, he's here to help us with work.
I heard that you are in the same class as Motoki.
Y-Yes.
I see. Kaizu-kun heard about me from his father.
Yeah, and I've heard about you from your sister before.
She didn't tell me your name, but she said her sister is a voice actress, and to take care of her.
Since there's someone in my class with the same family name, I wondered if this really could be the case.
Onee-chan, you should tell me if you knew!
Sorry, I forgot.
I knew it!
I see. That's why Kaizu-kun has been staring at me all the time.
I'm sorry.
Nope. I just thought it was...
Thought it was...?
N-Nothing! It's nothing!
I'd forgotten this too, but you'll be practicing with Motoki from today until the actual recording starts. I'll leave that to you.
Onee-chan, you idiot!
**men really is delicious!
It's delicious! It's delicious!
Let me drink more. Let me drink lots of **men!
I-It's quite intense...
They make a lot of intense ones over at President Kaizu's place.
By the way, ***** means semen.
Do I have to say this? In front of Kaizu-kun?
Yeah.
I can't!
I feel sorry for her.
You can do it. Do it!
My d***'s gotten hard!
What about Onii-chan?!
Nagatoshi's confined himself to the library to work on the scenario.
He won't be coming for a while.
But it's too embarrassing for me to say the lines from an eroge in front of a guy classmate!
We'll see each other in school everyday!
It's not just at work!
For somebody like that to think of me as a perverted girl who says those lewd lines...
I don't want that to happen!
I can't take that.
H-Hey, Aoyagi-san.
I won't think of you as a lustful person.
Rather, I really look up to you as a voice actress who participates in making eroge.
You did your best to say such embarrassing lines after all.
Even though it's work, these lines aren't something you can say without courage.
You've been a voice actress since your first year of high school, Aoyagi-san.
I think that's splendid.
So don't worry about it. I'll be happy if we can do our best together.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'm touched, young man!
Shoot it out! Fill my mouth with it!
A lot of it came out! The **men tasted great!
Something like that.
How is it? Did you get the feeling already?
Well, I got the idea.
What is it? Ask if there's anything you don't know.
All right, there's something I want to ask...
The girls often lick the ****, right?
Oh, you mean fellatio?
Why do you lick it?
Are you seriously saying that?
High school students normally know that!
Well...
Listen up, Kanna-chan! When it comes to fellatio...
Using your mouth is much better than using a hand!
To tell the truth, I wish I could lick my own!
However, our body's structure doesn't allow us to do that!
That's why we need somebody else to lick it, but having guys to do it would be disgusting!
That's why we need girls to lick it!
Understand?
I understand it very well now.
Anything else you want to ask?
Okay, just one more thing.
Oh, ask me anything.
This game talks about things like licking *****, drinking semen and that it tastes very delicious, right?
That's right.
Then... does it really taste delicious?
That's a wonderful question!
It feels embarrassing, but it can't be helped!
Go ahead and lick my **ck!
Stop it!
That's right... in general, **** tastes salty.
It's no different than your finger.
I can only say that semen is the taste of semen.
Yayoi-san, that's too straight.
But there's nothing else I can say.
Yayoi-san, why don't you leave it to me here?
Wait... what are you planning to do?
Kanna-chan, semen actually...
...tastes like condensed milk!
The proof is that semen is white, isn't it?
Is it fine if you don't stop her?
That's right.
She's giving her wrong information!
Nah, that may be just right for Kanna.
She can fill in the rest by just imagining it.
If you tell her semen tastes great, she might just sound like it's delicious in her acting.
When did you start doing this job, Kaizu-kun?
My first year of middle school.
Eh?!
It feels rather complicated to think that I grew up with eroge.
I understand...
Everyone must be shocked to know that I am working on a job like this.
It's a secret between just the two of us!
Aoyagi-san.
I was actually quite happy when I found out about you, Aoyagi-san.
There hasn't been someone in the same year as me that I could discuss these things with.
If it's fine with you, can I discuss various things with you from now on?
No way! That goes for me too...
Speaking of which, I've never held hands with a guy...
Thank you. I'll be counting on you.
Same here. I'll be counting on you.
What do you think?
Something definitely happened.
If something happened, it has to be that, right?
Hazuki, Kotori, want to go buy juice?
Congratulations!
Sign: Congratulations! Leaving "History without boyfriend = Age"
W-What?
Spring has finally arrived for Kanna too!
How did he confess to you? Oh, you!
Confess?
Kaizu-kun confessed to you and you started dating him, right?
That's not it!
But just now, you two looked really intimate when you were talking to each other.
T-That was...
Today, we are practicing the scene where they do perverted things at the library, right?
That's right. Starting from page 52 of the script.
Sakanami-san told me we will also be doing a fellatio scene in a classroom after that.
O-Okay.
T-That was...
Something did happen after all.
Nothing happened!
But you've never talked to Kaizu-kun before.
Explain that if you two aren't dating.
I can't tell you about that...
There have been too many things you can't tell us lately.
It's just too suspicious when you pretend it's complicated.
But I really can't say it...
It's really great to drink it right off the ****.
I'm doing something like this after all.
I can't get enough...
A current high school girl is trying her best to hold in her embarrassment and say lewd lines.
My **ck just got hard!
Hey, stop it!
That's sexual harassment, Senpai!
You... really are an idiot.
What was that?
To say that my **ck got hard is the highest praise there is!
My **ck only got hard because I was made uneasy by Kanna-chan's essence!
That's...
Hey, Motoki, you got hard too, right?
I... didn't really...
You can't get hard at that age?
That's not it!
Then what is it?
That's not what I meant.
It feels disrespectful to the voice actresses who tried their best to say these lewd lines!
I can't get excited!
You really are earnest, Motoki-kun.
That's just thinking too much.
I debuted by voicing eroge, and even though I'm also doing anime now,
I've never considered to stop voicing eroge.
Why is that?
Eroge is my starting point. I want to keep doing it with pride.
I understand the principle...
All right, Fumika, Kanna-chan!
Try to give Motoki a hard-on with your acting skills!
Eroge voice actresses are there to give erections!
Put your pride on the line and make him hard!
That's stupid,
but since you dare to go that far...
It feels nice to ride on top of you.
More... more...!
Tickle my *****!
I'm coming! I'm coming!!
Um, I'm sorry. It's not really...
Sakanami-san, I'm annoyed!
Isn't that right?
I've always thought of you as an idiot for making me do things like this,
but thanks to you, I've realized something important.
Right? I'll be beating you up in a moment, though.
Next up is Kanna-chan.
Even though Fumika-san couldn't do it?
Leave it to me! I'll teach you a finishing move.
I can't say something like that!
What is he telling
her to say...?
It's fine! Just pretend it's from the script and you can say it!
Now, go!
U-Um...
Since I don't really have any actual experience,
I m-may not be able to do that f-fellatio scene that well.
That's why... I want to lick Kaizu-kun's **** as practice.
If you could, give your s-semen...
Huh? What is it?
Did it happen? You're hard, right?!
There's no way I wouldn't get one if she asked me that!
Motoki-kun, let's try it again! Give me another chance!
Spare me!
Oh, no...
Why was I so happy about it?!
We've been going back and forth between school and the office everyday for practice.
We need to take a break every so often. Here.
Thanks.
I'll go ahead.
What!!?
This is bad...
That's amazing.
What do you mean?
Actually, I was a bit embarrassed to work with you, Aoyagi-san,
but I don't feel that way anymore.
I will do my best to help you, even if it's a tiny bit.
Kaizu-kun...
I can smell the scent of youth.
No! It's not what you think!
It feels like a sweet poem.
All right. It's finally time to try that.
Do I really need to do it?
Who else is there to? Go, hurry up.
Then...
What should I do?
Are you ready, Kanna?
W-Wait a second.
How about you, Motoki?
Yes, I'm fine.
There's a lot of people in the gallery.
Don't worry about them.
We'll be fine if we do it like we practiced.
We practiced that much after all.
All that's left is imagination and concentration.
Blend myself into the character.
I'm ready!
Starting from line number WA0001.
I'll leave it to you.
Good morning, Momoka.
Hey you, stop touching Momoka!
I can see it all of a sudden.
Does that mean I'm focused?
A delinquent like you isn't fit for Momoka!
Me? I'm Fujisawa Wakana! I'm part of the disciplinary committee.
How is it?
Pretty good. The feeling is just right.
The problem starts here.
Can Motoki turn her trance mode on?
Why are you unzipping?
You can't be making me suck this.
A-Are you an idiot?!
It's finally here...
Do it!
Even if you say that...
Kaizu-kun can see me licking it.
This is embarrassing.
But somehow, this is different from sucking Onii-chan's.
I felt a little happy when that happened.
Right now, all I can feel is embarrassment!
It's no good. She didn't enter her Trance Mode after all.
What is that?
Kanna can enter an euphoric mode within her subconscious once a certain requirement is met.
For someone without experience like her to voice an ero scene,
she just can't make it without entering her Trance Mode.
It went well to have her suck Hioki's finger last time.
I see. There are other requirements when Motoki is her partner.
Yes.
Regardless, we'll have Kanna take a run.
The problem is how intimate and affectionate she is with Motoki.
Nagatoshi is her childhood friend, so both values were maxed out.
Even if he can't get there, if only we could raise these numbers by a little...
Um, Yayoi-san.
This isn't a galge.
I know that!
But even if you want to raise the numbers...
Your affection rate isn't bad. She sucked your finger without hesitation.
She just couldn't suck your **** because it was too embarrassing.
That has nothing to do with this.
In that case, use mine...!
I'm back!
Welcome back!
For now, why don't you try to touch Motoki's naked **ck?
What am I doing to what?
Then make a detailed observation of his **ck.
I can't!
Then why don't you try smelling his **ck?
Well, let's just go ahead and shove his **ck in.
No way!
Do you have any ideas, Fumika?
Um... Then how about a kiss?
I can't do that either!
You're being so childish.
How about a hug, then?
Well, that much is fine...
Eh? Is that fine?!
Then, Motoki, give Kanna a big hug before she changes her mind.
Right here?
Then, may I?
Y-Yeah...
This feels really intimate...
I can smell Kaizu-kun's scent.
Could I be smelling of sweat now?
Um, Kaizu-kun, I...
Motoki, you're too loose! Hug her tighter!
Ah, yes.
This feels different from the time with Onii-chan.
I can feel Kaizu-kun's heartbeat.
Both his breath and smell.
It feels this nice to be hugged...
Seems like she successfully entered her Trance Mode.
Is that so?
Yep. Let's restart the recording.
This is completely different!
A high school girl's fellatio!
It makes my **ck hard.
Motoki, what we talked about.
I didn't think I'd really use it.
Sign: Condensed milk
It's sweet...
This is the taste of condensed milk.
Condensed milk...
The taste of semen...
This is the taste of semen.
More!
It feels nice! Do my ****** more!
Your **** is doing a lot in my ******!
I'm doing this again...
I can't stop!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I came again... And what's more, it's in front of Kaizu-kun...
Aoyagi-san.
Hey, Kaizu-kun.
It's too embarrassing! I can't face him!
Kanna, do you have a moment?
What is it?
K-Kaizu-kun!
Huh?!
We'll be heading home, then.
Bye!
Um...
I'm sorry!
I've been... um... running away from you all this time.
It was my first time being hugged like that by a guy.
It felt too embarrassing.
You don't need to worry about that.
It's normal to feel embarrassed.
I should be the one apologizing for making you go so far for work.
You did really great, though. Aoyagi-san, you did your best after all.
I am the one who should be apologizing.
You must have hated someone like me hugging you...
T-That's not it!
My acting went well because of that!
I'll try my best to do even better!
I hope you can teach me about various things from now on.
This is bad. Stay away, Aoyagi-san.
We are being watched.
It was Kanna who started the hug, right?
She did quite well, taking the first step.
T-That's not it!
I wonder how it will turn out.
I'm looking forward to it!
It's not like that!
nakami wa miseran nai dare ni mo
中身は見せらんない　誰にも
I won't let anyone see inside me.
genkai tsuugaku bakku
限界　通学バック
The limit is my school bag.
sawarasenai wa zettai ryouiki
触らせないわ　絶対領域
Don't touch my absolute territory.
kimi no yubi ga abako utosuru saguro utosuru
君の指が　暴こうとする　探ろうとする
Your fingers are exposing and exploring me.
yada ! himitsu ga tsumatterundamon !
やだ！　秘密が詰まってるんだもん！
Nooo! Many secrets are in there!
koji ageru nara yasashi kushitene
こじあげるなら　優しくしてね
If you insist on prying, please be gentle with me.
sukima gurai wa yurushi chau kamo
スキマぐらいは許しちゃうかも
I might forgive you if it's only a small gap.
onedari mo suki suki mo donna koto mo ieru
おねだりも　好き好きも　どんなことも言える
Beg me or love me, spill everything out.
yume de nara serifu nara kokoro nara yoyuu de
夢でなら　セリフなら　心なら余裕で
Be it dreams or speech, as long as you have the heart, there will be surplus.
mousou ga bousou chuu chuuihou hatsurei dayo !
妄想が暴走中　注意報発令だよ！
Amidst your wild delusions, the alarm has already activated!
hazukashii koto ukkari kimi ni tsutae chau mae ni
恥ずかしいこと　うっかり君に　伝えちゃう前に
Before I accidentally tell you embarrassing things,
kuchibiru ni chakku
くちびるにチャック
Hurry and zip my lips.