It's there... It's big...
It's so hot...
Nice! It's in...
It's inside my p****!
Arihara-kun's is in!
Why?
Why can she say that so easily?
Harder! Harder! Pound me harder!
T-This...
No... I'm coming!
I can't say things like that!
atsuku atsuku torokesou de mune ga mune ga kurushiku naru
My chest is feeling hotter and hotter, like it's melting. It's becoming more and more painful.
熱く熱くとろけそうで　胸が胸が苦しくなる
amaku nigai konna kimochi hajimete dayo
It's the first time I've ever had such a sweet and painful feeling.
甘く苦いこんな気持ち　初めてだよ
jugyouchuu demo yume no naka demo kimi no koto bakari
When I am in class or in my dreams, I always think about you...
受業中でも　夢の中でも　きみのことばかり
kamo?!
Perhaps?!
かも？！
basu no naka demo nani shiteite mo yada... kangaeteru
When I am in the bath and no matter what I do, no... I think about you.
バスの中でも　何していても　ヤダ…考えてる
hazukashikute dokidoki shite
I feel embarrassed and my heart is beating.
恥ずかしくて　ドキドキして
kimi ga yorokobu to kimochiyoku naru
It warms me up if you are happy.
キミが喜ぶと気持ち良くなる
motto mitai sonna egao
I want to see more of that smile.
もっとみたい　そんな笑顔
...kore ga koi no mahou?
...is this the magic of love?
…これが☆恋の魔法？
mawaru mawaru chikyuu no ue
On the round, round Earth,
まわるまわるちきゅうの上
kimi to deatta sono hi kara
ever since the day I met you,
きみと出逢ったその日から
dondon ookiku natteku koi sonzai
the existence of love has become bigger and bigger.
どんどん大きくなってく　恋　存在
mou kore ijou wa dame dayo
I can't take any more than this.
もうこれ以上はダメだよ
mou kore ijou wa muri dayo
I can't have any more than this.
もうこれ以上は無理だよ
kore ijou suki ni nattara dou nacchau no?
If I love you any more than this, what will happen?
これ以上好きになったら　ど～なっちゃうの？
My voice douka kotaete
My voice, please answer me.
My voice　どうか答えて
Your voice douka oshiete
Your voice, please tell me.
Your voice　どうか教えて
Doki-Chihiro
A 16 Year Old's Secret Job
Kanna, become an eroge voice actress.
Huh?!
Here, this is the script.
Do I need to say perverted things?
Yes.
I need to say them?
No way!
What are you talking about, Onee-chan?!
There's no way I can do that!
It's fine. You can do it.
I'm still a high school student!
I know that.
I've been waiting until you turned sixteen.
I actually wanted you to start when you were in your second year of middle school.
A small company like mine isn't very rich.
It's too expensive to find professionals.
You understand, right?
Onee-chan is making eroge... I can't believe it.
I didn't really mean to hide it.
You didn't ask anyway.
T-Then... when you were playing eroge at home before...
Was that for work too?
Onee-chan?
Well, yeah.
Because of that, it's best that I raise someone around me to be an eroge voice actress.
Okay?
No way!
What's wrong? I'm not asking you to strip.
No way! You don't have to ask me!
Who else is there for me to ask?
No way! Anyway, no way!
Enough chatter...
Do it!
Absolutely no way!
Hey!
Seriously... Onee-chan is too forceful...
Kanna, welcome back.
Mom, are you working night shift?
That's right.
I'm sorry. I can't be there to celebrate, even though it's your birthday.
It's fine. I'm not a kid anymore.
I heard you went to Yayoi's company today.
Is she not with you?
Well... It's a little...
Yayoi really cares about you.
She must have prepared a surprise present for you.
Well, she wanted me to be an eroge voice actress after all...
Did you know? Yayoi is trying her best to save up for your college tuition.
Eh?
Although Dad passed away, and things have gotten a little tough,
she told me she doesn't want that to have an effect on your future.
Onee-chan did?
Her job also seems to be a lot of work, but she said that it's for your sake...
...even though I told her that letting me earn our living was enough.
I see... Onee-chan was thinking about me that much...
She's been thinking about me for a long time...
Compared to that,
this is only a little embarrassing.
I want to try it... to become an eroge voice actress!
I see.
Thank you. That'd be a great help, Kanna.
Well, let's hurry up and start practicing, then.
C*ck
P*ssy
All right, let's give it a try.
C*ck
P*ssy
Eh?
C*ck
P*ssy
These are just the basic ones.
You can't become an eroge voice actress if you can't say these.
H-Hold on a minute...
I want to prepare myself...
Pu...
Nobody's here. It's just the two of us.
T-Then...
P*ssy.
Say it clearly.
P*ssy...
You're too quiet!
Say it out clearly!
P*ssy...
I can't hear you!
Say each syllable out clearly!
Say it out like you're yelling!
P...
P*ssy!!
I'm back!
What was that scream just now?
Kanna, let's go home together.
Do you want to have some cake? It's our treat today.
We need to celebrate your birthday.
I'm sorry. I need to go to Onee-chan's studio.
Studio?
Oh, you're helping with your sister's work, right?
I remember it's a game company...
What kind of games? How are you helping them?
I-I'm sorry! I'm in a bit of a hurry!
I'm really sorry!
She seems quite busy.
Seems quite suspicious.
Let's begin, then.
Starting from page 4, line number SA0001.
Hey, hold on a minute, Arihara-kun!
You're the only one who didn't hand in your assignment!
What do you mean, I'm annoying?!
Amazing!
If you don't want me to talk to you...
It can't be helped... Then this time, let's...
It's as if she was pulled into the world of the story...
What? You don't want to?
It's more like she's in it!
Great!
It's kind of hard.
And it's... hot.
It's getting bigger...
I can see it!
I've never seen it before, but now it feels like I know what they're shaped like!
Should I rub it harder?
After all...
Does it feel good?
But...
What's the matter? Should we do a retake?
No, it's nothing.
Incredible!!!
It's inside me!
Do I need to say these things?
Can I say these things?
It's so deep inside me!
Somehow... Somehow I...
Arihara's cum… I want you to shoot a whole load of cum inside me!
No... I...
Nice work, Fumika.
That was great.
Really?
It's obvious once you see Kanna's face...
It seems like she really reacted to it.
O-Onee-chan!
I'm happy! You reacted to my acting!
That's to be expected of our top voice actress, Warasono Fumika.
Aoyagi-san, do you really want your sister to become an eroge voice actress?
Of course.
But it really doesn't seem right since she's in high school.
When it comes to it, just say she's told us she's eighteen.
We often get people lying about their age in this industry, no?
Please don't say something so dangerous.
Well, it's fine as long as we don't report her age,
and she doesn't have to show her face in public.
That's right. You're just too stiff-necked.
I was only being serious, so why am I getting yelled at?
Let's do our best together.
Y-Yes.
If I have to do it, I want to be as good as Fumika-san.
I want to become a voice actress who can make people visualize the scene by simply hearing my voice.
I don't know how long it'll take to get there,
but since I've decided to, I'll try my best!
C-C*ck!
D*ck
C*ck
P*ssy
It's great that you can finally say it out loud, but try to put more feeling into it.
But it's embarrassing!
We don't have time for you to improve slowly.
We only have one week until the recording.
One week?! That's ridiculous!
I can't do it!
The industry is full of tough schedules.
Even so...
...isn't that a bit cruel?!
I'm probably not the one to ask...
...although I do feel a little sympathetic.
That's why this isn't the time to get stuck at the beginning.
Next up... is this one.
This is the lewdest of the words, but it shows up most often in a game.
On the other hand, if you can say this out loud, you can probably say the others.
Often... how often is it?
That's right...
Well... about 90 percent.
Isn't that pretty much the whole game?
All right, give it a try.
D- D-
D***
Fumika, give her an example.
Then...
D*ck.
Got it? That's exactly it.
I-It's erotic!
That's your homework until next time.
It's fine! You just need to get used to it... I guess.
How can Fumika-san say that so easily?
Well, it's my job.
But isn't it embarrassing?
Well, it is embarrassing,
but you become the character when you're acting.
You become the character?
No matter what you say or what kind of erotic things happen,
they're both done by the character instead.
Once you can tell them apart, you'll be able to cope with it better.
The key is to use your imagination and concentration to become the game's character.
Imagination and concentration?
Have you played an eroge before?
Of course not.
Let's try this one first, then.
It's what they call a stripping game.
W-Why?! No way!
It's strange for you to become an eroge voice actress without having played one, right?
Playing eroge on a Sunday morning... seriously...
It started with an erotic scene out of nowhere!
Good morning, Master.
Your cum's so thick and delicious in the morning, Master!
She's licking it!
Why? Does the concentration change the taste?
Eh? It's going up her ass!
Why? How come?!
Besides... can it even fit up there?!
Ayano
Ah! Master's d*ck is so deep inside me!
The drawings are amazing, as are the lines.
More!
I can see it again.
A voice actress said this, right?
I can't possibly say these things...
The key is to use your imagination and concentration to become the game's character.
I mustn't say that I can't do it!
Imagination and concentration!
I am that girl... I am that girl...
It feels good.
She sounded like it was comfortable.
Is it really that comfortable?
I also want to have this done to me...
I want more...
I want your d*ck to make my p*ssy wet...
I... want your... d*ck to make... my p*ssy wet...
It went in! Your c*ck feels so good!
Your c*ck... feels so good... Oh!
Master, this is wonderful!
Master...
Harder, please! I can't hold it anymore! I-I'm coming!
N-No... why?
No... No, no way!
A message?
Tomorrow, come to the studio
after school.
It's from Onee-chan.
I got it.
No way! I didn't touch it, but it felt like I was about to come!
Seriously! I won't play eroge anymore!
Kanna-chan, it's been a long time!
Eeh? Hioki Onii-chan!
Why are you here?
Do they know each other?
Nagatoshi is my childhood friend after all.
I've known Kanna-chan since she was born!
She always said, "I want to be Onii-chan's wife" when she was a kid.
I wouldn't have thought that Kanna-chan would help with our games.
I'm glad!
The script for the stripping game I gave you was written by Nagatoshi.
Then... I was about to come reading Onii-chan's script!
Judging from your expression, it seems like you rather liked that game.
You idiot, Onee-chan!
Did I get it right?
It's nice that you get along well with the title.
I'll let you read Nagatoshi's scripts from now on.
All right, here.
Try to practice reading it aloud more.
How about you give it a try first?
I gave you homework, after all.
N-No way!
Oh, nice!
I'm looking forward to Kanna-chan's acting.
All right, here.
I-Isn't it a little hard?
You'll need to say it eventually though.
B-But...
All right? Say it like you feel really comfortable...
...with a smile.
Y-Yes.
Then let's give it a try.
Your d*ck is warm... and hard.
It feels so good.
My! That sounded really good!
It might be embarrassing, but keep doing your best!
Y-Yes.
Leaving that aside, that  might be a problem for Kanna.
Oh, that, is it?
That? What's that?
Sucking sounds.
Elephant... sounds?
Note: She misunderstood "sui" (suck) with "zou" (elephant)
The lines in erotic scenes are spoken as the character licks on a guy's thing.
Naturally, you can't speak like you would normally.
In general, Fumika.
Sucking sound
Okay.
It's delicious...
It's lewd!
Instead of using sound effects, these rely on the voice actress's own acting skills.
If you can't do this well, you can't be an eroge voice actress.
It's like this, right?
Doesn't seem to be.
There's more saliva on it...
...in... and out...
...licking both the front and the sides...
What are you doing?
Seems quite erotic...
Hey, what was that just now?
I-It's nothing! Don't worry about it!
It doesn't seem right. But what's wrong?
It's not lewd enough.
There was a sound, but it didn't sound like it was licking a d*ck.
That's because I've never licked one.
Do you want to lick one then? How about Nagatoshi's?
Well, it doesn't seem like that would work.
Come with me. I have another idea.
Here, lick it.
Eh?
I thought you would be able to grasp the feeling if you licked a part of your partner.
If a d*ck won't do, wouldn't a finger be fine?
Onii-chan, is it all right?
Your finger will get all sticky.
It's fine, as long as it's Kanna-chan.
T-Then...
Onii-chan's finger is warm, and it's thicker than it looks!
Hurry up and practice your sucking sounds!
Think of it as a d*ck.
O-Okay.
Somehow, it excites me a little.
Kanna, ask if he's feeling comfortable.
O-Onii-chan, do you feel comfortable?
Yup, it feels really nice.
I'm happy... that Onii-chan is feeling comfortable because of me!
I didn't think I'd be this happy...!
Even though it's so embarrassing...
I want to make Onii-chan feel even more comfortable!
Seems like she got the hang of it.
Kanna-chan is brilliant!
Once she focuses on something, she doesn't care about anything else.
I look forward to the recording.
Giving life to one character...
...can I really do it?
Anyway, calm yourself down.
It's fine as long as you do as you practiced.
Starting from line number YA0001.
Y-Yes!
Y-Yes, you wanted to check it out, right?
Then, please write your name down on this card-
All right, start over.
Add "Take two!" to the beginning, and continue.
Take two!
Y-Yes, you wanted to check it out, right?
T-The-
Y-Yes, you wanted to check it ou-
I'm sorry...
Take four!
What should I do? I can't do it right!
She sounds really nervous.
It's her first recording. It's only natural.
Kanna, you're too nervous. Relax your body.
After that, say "p*ssy" ten times.
Why?!
Enough, just say it. Hurry.
I-I got it...
P*ssy...
P*ssy... P*ssy...
You're too quiet!
P*ssy! P*ssy! P*ssy!
Louder!
P*ssy!
No way!!
All right, let's go on.
What was that just now? Was she just toying with me?
Umm...
Y-Yes, you wanted to check it out, right?
Then, please write down your name, year and class on this card.
Huh? I said it?!
It seems like she's calmed down...
It was tough for her to leave her worries aside.
All right! Let's keep it up!
Become the character using imagination and concentration!
W-What is it, Katayama-kun?
"Why," you asked?
It's because I'm a librarian.
I guess that's right.
Not only did I see the scene in front of me,
but it was like I could hear him!
Isn't she doing well?
Her acting is still far from perfect, but she's already doing her best.
The real problem has just started, though.
Oh, the s*x scene is coming up next.
Oh... M-My finger is moving on its own... It won't stop!
It didn't work after all.
Well, she didn't practice this part, after all.
It can't be helped. Let's try that tactic.
Kanna, let's stop here for now.
Y-Yes.
Umm... I'm done changing.
All right, run for thirty minutes and come back.
I don't really get it.
All right, I'm off!
What is this meant to do?
Once she's tired and out of breath from running, her acting should become a little more erotic.
Cheap...
I recall that Kanna-chan used to be on the track team, right?
Yup, she specialized in mid and long ranges.
No wonder. I was amazed that she was so enthused despite recording for this long.
Even though I've practiced so much, I still feel embarrassed.
Not to mention, it was really hard.
But...
I need to work hard!
I'm back.
Eh? Onii-chan?
I want Nagatoshi to sit there.
So just do it while you're looking at him.
Eh?!
Let's do our best.
O-Okay...
I-It feels good...
You can touch it more... My p*ssy.
For me to say something this embarrassing in front of Onii-chan...
Let me touch Katayama-kun's too.
I want to try touching your c*ck.
She's really starting to sound erotic.
It'd be perfect if we can have the finger-sucking atmosphere on top of this.
It's an erotic scene...
I get weird remembering what happened last time...
D-Does it feel good?
Katayama-kun's... big...
So this is what a d*ck tastes like.
It's delicious! It's really delicious!
She's doing really well all of a sudden.
That's because the finger-sucking turned her on.
Your c*ck is so warm! And it's so hard!
It feels good!
Wonderful... It's wonderful!
I've really become weird.
I used to think that these things were embarrassing to say!
More... Fuck me more!
Somehow, I feel nervous!
If you carry on, I'll lose my mind!
No! I can't anymore!
I'm going to... I'm going to come!
I... again! Besides, it's even stronger than last time...!
No... If I don't stop this... Even though I'm in front of everyone...!
No, I can't stop it!
No!!
You came a lot...
There's a lot of... cum... inside...
It feels... really wonderful...
Nice work!
Kanna, you really did great.
Even though this was your first recording, it was excellent.
Onee-chan...
Thanks. I'm counting on you next time as well.
Y-Yes!
By the way, you actually came in the scene just now, right?
W-What do you mean?
No, it was pretty obvious.
It really was amazing.
You didn't touch her, right, Hioki-san?
Hmm? I didn't.
Normally, it'd be impossible with only your imagination, right?
There's just no way.
But... It really was brilliant!
Yeah, I've met quite a lot of voice actresses,
but this is the first time I've met someone with so much skill.
You have a skill that even Fumika hasn't, Kanna.
Have more confidence in yourself.
You might be quite suitable to become an eroge voice actress.
nakami wa miseran nai dare ni mo
中身は見せらんない　誰にも
I won't let anyone see inside me.
genkai tsuugaku bakku
限界　通学バック
The limit is my school bag.
sawarasenai wa zettai ryouiki
触らせないわ　絶対領域
Don't touch my absolute territory.
kimi no yubi ga abako utosuru saguro utosuru
君の指が　暴こうとする　探ろうとする
Your fingers are exposing and exploring me.
yada ! himitsu ga tsumatterundamon !
やだ！　秘密が詰まってるんだもん！
Nooo! Many secrets are in there!
koji ageru nara yasashi kushitene
こじあげるなら　優しくしてね
If you insist on prying, please be gentle with me.
sukima gurai wa yurushi chau kamo
スキマぐらいは許しちゃうかも
I might forgive you if it's only a small gap.
onedari mo suki suki mo donna koto mo ieru
おねだりも　好き好きも　どんなことも言える
Beg me or love me, spill everything out.
yume de nara serifu nara kokoro nara yoyuu de
夢でなら　セリフなら　心なら余裕で
Be it dreams or speech, as long as you have the heart, there will be surplus.
mousou ga bousou chuu chuuihou hatsurei dayo !
妄想が暴走中　注意報発令だよ！
Amidst your wild delusions, the alarm has already activated!
hazukashii koto ukkari kimi ni tsutae chau mae ni
恥ずかしいこと　うっかり君に　伝えちゃう前に
Before I accidentally tell you embarrassing things,
kuchibiru ni chakku
くちびるにチャック
Hurry and zip my lips.