"I'm home..."
It's sure more quieter than usual around here.
Mom and Dad went to Yufuin for a hot springs trip.
Dad said they're doing it to celebrate his promotion to department manager or something.
My little sister was all excited, saying she was going to cook us dinner, but...
can she actually cook?
Hey, Onii-chan!
"Kaho, you're back? So what are you cooking for dinner?"
"Whoa, what's with that look?"
Come to my room for a minute.
Onii-chan, what's this?
COUNSELOR
RECOMMENDED
SEX COURSE
FOR VIRGINS
SEX COUNSELOR
NISHIKUSUNOKI SERA
"Uh, that book... Wait, you snuck into my room?!"
"I keep telling you to stay out of my..."
I'm asking you what's this?
I was thinking "Why is she pissed?" but her threatening look kept my mouth shut.
"Well, you can tell from the cover."
And you've hid this in your room?
I don't remember raising you up like that!
I don't remember you raising me up, period.
Onii-chan...
"H-Hey..."
Do you... have a girlfriend?
"Huh?"
So you have a girlfriend and are using this book for practice?
Is that true?
"N-No! I don't have a girlfriend! I just got it out of curiosity, you know, for social studies!"
Wait, why do I even have to explain myself to you?
Really?
"Really!"
Wow, what a relief!
So you don't have a girlfriend.
Those were crocodile tears?!
There's no way, since nobody other than me knows how great you are.
"Huh? Say what?"
Nothing, nothing at all!
Hmm... so social studies?
"Look, that's enough. Give it back."
Say, Onii-chan.
Maybe... I can help you study.
Eh?
I mean, you don't like studying that much.
And studying together is better than studying alone.
So I'm willing to... help you out.
Eh, what? Wait, that's what's she's been
getting at? No, wait, think logically here...
Onii-chan?
That's when I gulped. Before I knew it, I had closed the door to her room.
It's important to kiss before sex in order to calm down the girl
and in order to increase both of your sexual passions.
It doesn't matter if it's awkward or if you don't do it well.
Be sure your kisses convey the feelings you have for her.
When you kiss her, be sure to do it softly at first.
If you start off by kissing her intensely, you'll just make her nervous.
So it's important to relax the girl with soft kisses.
Once you're both in the mood,
you can try using your tongues while kissing.
Softly touch each other's tongues,
stroke the roof of her mouth,
and intertwine your tongues, in a way that is stimulating.
While kissing,
gently caressing the nape of her neck or her back can be effective.
Stimulating two or more places at the same time by caressing them
is a very important technique when you are having sex.
You will be using this technique in all sorts of positions, so be sure to keep this in mind.
You can spend time caressing her through her clothes.
The stimulation is softened this way compared to direct contact.
This way the girl will be tantalized
and become increasingly aroused.
Be sure not to pull at her clothes too much
or be too rough with her during this time.
Bra hooks may be difficult to unfasten for guys who are unused to them.
Structure of Bra Hooks
How To Unhook A Bra
What's Hooked
What It's Hooked Onto
But they are simple enough, so follow along.
When you first do it, use both hands and be careful.
You can unhook it while holding the girl with your hands behind her back.
Or you can do it from her back while stroking her ears or nape of her neck,
without spoiling the mood.
If you are unable to unhook it, then you can ask her to do it for you.
You may be skilled enough to remove the bra with one hand,
but it may give the impression that you fool around with a lot of girls, so be careful.
Caress her breasts by gently massaging them.
Gently massage the
very sensitive part that
is under her bust.
Carefully caress her under the bust, which is a highly sensitive area.
Since you are trying to get her entire body aroused,
at this stage, make sure not to touch her nipples yet.
Slowly work your way towards her nipples.
Stroke the areas around the areolae.
Maintain your patience,
stimulate her teasingly in a way that says you're not going to touch her there that soon.
When you take of her clothes, the girl will feel embarrassed
if you stare at her intently.
So pay attention to her needs
by taking off her clothes while gently hugging her, and by darkening the room.
By stimulating the inner thighs, the outer crotch, and the inguinal region
you will be able to arouse her entire body.
Just by teasing her in those areas,
you will see her wanting more, leading to the next level of your caressing.
You have finally reached the final step...
of your caressing.
The nipples are...
so sensitive that they are commonly referred to as the c... clitorises of the upper body.
Just by rubbing over them in circles,
and lightly pinching them...
you can give the girl considerable pleasure.
Depending on the girl, her left breast may not be as sensitive as her right breast, and vice versa.
Observe her reaction and stimulate the breast that seems to arouse her more.
Once you lie her down on a bed, you increase your range
of combination caressing.
You can use your tongue and your other hand
to caress different areas at the same time.
When you directly stroke the clitoris,
first wet your fingers with your saliva or her vaginal fluids.
When it gets fully lubricated, making it easier to move your fingers,
it will feel so good to her that it will double her state of arousal.
When the girl gets nice and wet,
if you insert your finger into her vagina,
it will give a girl a whole other pleasure than...
what she attains when you stimulate her clitoris.
Work your finger like a penis,
and slowly insert it in and out.
Once you put your finger...
G-Spot
Tap With Finger
all the way inside, and gently bend it...
you will find a rough area.
That is... the G-spot.
Just by...
pushing the G-spot instead of stroking it...
will give her even more pleasure.
So stimulate her by tapping the G-spot with your fingertip.
Just by doing that... it will make her...
feel incredible.
Once you've gotten in the rhythm, you can add that tapping movement
while inserting your finger in and out.
When you also use your thumb to softly rub the clitoris...
this combination of strokes done at the same time...
will feel really good.
If you continue to stimulate the G-spot...
She will secrete even more vaginal fluids,
and she may even engage in what is called "female ejaculation".
Just so you know, whether female ejaculation occurs or not
depends on the girl.
Since a girl might not ejaculate even if she experiences intense pleasure,
there's no need to worry about that, and just enjoy sex naturally.
Wow...
Your penis is so hard, and it's also twitching!
If the girl doesn't appear to be against it,
you can also have her perform fellatio during sex.
If you shower or take a bath before having her perform fellatio,
the girl will be even more willing.
The deeper your relationship is with the girl, the easier it is to ask her to perform fellatio.
So try to have her do that every time you have sex.
Once the girl is fully wet,
slowly insert your penis inside her.
If the two of you don't have much experience, there may be some difficulty with the insertion.
It's not uncommon for it to take two or three sexual encounters
before you're able to insert it inside her easily.
If that happens,
you can also flirt with her and talk to her while your both in bed.
The missionary position is the most basic posture you can take during sex.
Since you can see each other's faces,
you can make her feel at ease.
It's even popular among girls.
If you use your hands or mouth to caress the girl during copulation,
you can increase the pleasure the girl is feeling.
If you start to feel tired,
you can even just rest your fingers or hands on her,
and still give her a lot of pleasure.
You can lay on top of the girl while in the missionary position.
That way you can change up your sexual position.
While moving your hips...
you can pleasure the girl by kissing or caressing her.
You should use protection, for your sake and her sake.
Squeeze the
air out of
the tip (important)
Pull down the rubber
The most popular form of protection is the condom.
You're done.
Make sure the right surface is on the outside before putting it on the penis.
Squeeze the
air out of
the tip (important)
The tip of the condom that collects the semen will be filled with air,
Pull down the rubber
since it can cause breakage
You're done.
you press the tip with your finger to remove the air.
You then roll the ring down to the base of the penis.
Squeeze the
air out of
the tip (important)
Pull down the rubber
Since you can also get a kick by asking the girl to put it on for you,
You're done.
so don't complain, use protection.
You can sit up from the missionary position,
and have the girl sit on your lap while having intercourse.
This is called the "Lotus position".
You two can become more intimate.
You can kiss her and embrace her while engaging in intercourse.
The fact that you can easily become lovey-dovey with the girl...
is one of the good points.
You can freely use your hands...
and caress her breasts, her ears,
the nape of her neck, her back,
and even her rear.
You can try a whole lot of...
combination of caresses.
You can even try some variations of the Lotus position.
The girl can assume a position where she supports herself
by putting her hands behind her and thrust her hips at you.
Because a girl can feel a sense of shame doing this,
this sexual position can feel somewhat S&M-ish.
If the man lies back from the Lotus position...
the two will attain the cowgirl position.
From this position...
the girl can freely move her hips...
and she can make the proper adjustments she finds her sweet spot.
Instead of having her go up and down,
she can move her hips back and forth...
in a grinding motion,
she will tire out less easily, and you'll both enjoy this position even longer.
This position will limit the range of where you can perform your combination of caresses.
But you can still use your hand to...
stroke her nipples and her clitoris.
As a variation of the cowgirl position,
the girl can get into position where she lays on top of the guy.
From this position...
you two can kiss or stimulate the napes of your necks
and ears with your tongues...
and engage in other combination of caressing.
From this position, you will be able to penetrate very deeply.
Compared to the other positions...
it is easier to move your hips attain pleasure.
You can get the strong feeling that you are abusing the girl...
and from the guy's perspective,
this position give him a feeling of dominance and conquest over the girl.
But a girl might be bewildered by it.
On the other hand...
girls who are on the masochistic side will prefer this position.
Considering those extremes, when frequently engaging in sex with your partner,
test this position with her and see her reaction to it.
Through the use of a combination of caressing...
you can stimulate the breasts and the clitoris...
and get feeling that you are abusing her...
that much more.
While the girl will feel confused...
the man will attain the feeling of conquest over the girl.
As a variation of this position,
you can push the girl's upper body all the way to the surface.
You can also hold down her hips with your hands,
putting the girl in a... static position.
Since the girl cannot move while in this position...
she will really get the sense that she's being violated.
Onii-chan... I love you.