Hey, you'll stumble if you don't slow down!
Relax! You worry too much, Onii-chan!
Really?
I'm fine, honest!
See, I told you.
You were always this clumsy.
Thank you...
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, you perv!
You're such a perv!
Kasumi's sure gotten big.
W-Wait! That's not what I meant...
KASUMI
A dream?
Well, it's not like nobody's here.
*Home Delivery*
For Pete's sake, we're always getting these.
Onii-chan, that's mine.
Yeah, I know.
Onii-chan!
Thank you, Onii-chan!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep there.
I'm not sleeping.
You'll leave your job after taking too many sick days. That's a good way to become a NEET, you know.
That's not going to happen.
You know I've been reading a lot of books after what happened with Kasumi.
I know.
What's going on, for heaven's sake?
And I already have my hands full with Kasumi.
I said I know.
Say, Mom.
What?
Why did Kasumi become a hikikomori?
I don't know.
Didn't you read all those books?
Different people have different reasons, there's no way to know.
I wonder what's the real reason behind her case?
Say.
Do you have a boyfriend?
You want to know?
Um, not really.
Just kinda wondering, I guess.
What about you, Onii-chan?
Want to know?
Not really.
Well, I dunno.
That's when it began.
That's when she started acting strange.
What, you can't go? What happened? Is there an emergency?
Well, there's this drama I want to see tomorrow.
You didn't say anything about that yesterday when we made that date.
I forgot about it back then.
B-But...
I'm not sure if I like guys as pushy as you.
Uh, nah!
I hear you.
If there's a drama you have to see, what can you do?
I'm always up for another chance to go, okay?
Uh, yeah. Too bad about tomorrow.
I thought I finally got a date with her.
But it looks like it's dead on arrival.
And for a drama of all things?
Guess I have to cancel the restaurant reservation.
And canceling doesn't come cheap.
Kasumi?
I was going to meet with a friend at work.
But it looks like she's going to be busy.
I don't want the reservation I made to go to waste.
So I was wondering...
Can we make it a date, or something?
She's been cooped up in this room forever.
Her hair's all messed up.
Always wearing baggy sweats.
And... does she even take baths every day?
I was wondering if you want to have dinner with me?
I mean, we haven't been going out lately, right?
You might not like hanging around your Onii-chan,
but it doesn't hurt to go out once in a while.
R-Really?
We'll meet at the restaurant right after I get off from work tomorrow!
Um...
Uh...
You really surprised me, Kasumi.
Actually, it's been a while since I've had a good look at her face.
It's always covered by her bangs.
I've never noticed since she's always hunched over wearing baggy clothes...
but she's really grown, hasn't she?
Wait, wait. You're my sister.
Sorry, Kasumi.
I think I should rest...
What am I thinking?
I guess I must be drunk.
How did that happen?
She's my little sister!
K... Kasumi!
Wh-What are you doing?
Don't joke arou...
Hey, this is wrong!
Idiot! If this is a joke, I'm not laughing!
You're hard.
No, this is just... uh...
I want to thank you, Onii-chan.
Hey!
H-Hey, Kasumi...
C-Crap, I'm coming.
You came a lot. I'm glad.
Where did you....
Didn't it feel good?
No, it felt great.
Wait, hold on!
You're my sister! Do you know what that means?
It's because I love you.
It's because I've always, always loved you, Onii-chan.
You've always taken care of me.
You're so nice to me, you tell me I'm cute, so...
But I guess...
a girl like me, isn't good enough?
Kasumi, you're hunching over again.
You've opened up your heart to me.
I don't deserve to be your brother.
My sister...
No, I'm happy that Kasumi confessed her feelings to me.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan... I'm ready...
I'm putting it in.
Okay.
Pretty tight.
Kasumi, are you all right?
I'm filled with you.
I'm so happy.
O... Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
I-I'm sorry.
This will just be for today.
Tomorrow I'll go back to being your sister.
Kasumi, don't say a word.
Say.
Onii-chan, are you okay with this?
Don't worry about me.
Are you really okay with this?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, you'll stumble if you don't slow down!
Relax! You worry too much, Onii-chan!
Really?
I'm fine, honest!
See, I told you!
You were always this clumsy.
Th-Thanks you...
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, you perv!
You're such a perv!
I wanted to be touched by him.
By Onii-chan.
It's already evening.
Welcome back, Onii-chan.
Yeah, I'm home... huh?
Kasumi, you could always go back to that look you had back then.
Just kidding.
Kasumi?
I only made myself that way for you, Onii-chan.
That's not how I always looked.
That's only for when I'm with you.
Hey Kasumi, doesn't this inn look great?
The rooms each have open-air baths.
I luckily got us a reservation.
So, why not?
Look at this, Kasumi!
We have our own open-air bath, so this should be all right with you.
Do you want to go in now?
Or do you want to wait till after dinner...
I want to go in together, right now.
Can't believe I'm in here with you, Kasumi.
I didn't pay attention to you, especially here.
This time, I'll be the one pleasuring you.
Good...
Kasumi, you're good.
Kasumi!
Onii-chan...
Here goes.
I'm... about to...
M-Me too.
Let's do it together.
I... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
I'm filled with... all your...
Hot springs are really great.
Let's go in again after our meal.
Yes, let's go in 10 times before we leave.
I want to have sex in the futon, not just the bath.
Actually, I was saying I just wanted to relax in the bath, since we're at the hot springs and all.
I guess we're doing it 10 times as well?