Do not enter
W-Who is it?
It's time for me to finally take your virginity, Eri...
H-He is...
Have you forgotten about me?
I used to be the super for the
dorms of Seishuku Music Institute...
...Shusaku Kato...
Mr. Kato...
I vaguely remember your name.
Vaguely, huh?
I took a lot of effort to take pictures of you, Eri.
All the embarrassing moments...
How do you like it?
Isn't it beautiful?
What do you want from me?
Why did you ruin those masterpieces?
Nothing is more exciting than
these photos for young men.
Stop this!
It doesn't matter if you destroy the pictures.
I can print hundreds of them!
What's this?
You should've known already...
This is the world of never-ending desire that God created.
Never-ending desire?
Hell yeah.
We're nothing but characters in this two dimensional space created by God.
Give me a break!
Whatever you say, I know I'm real.
I'm not a character in anyone's game!
Are you sure?
I thought that a smart girl like you
had already figured it out...
What is this?
Come to this side.
You should see what is real, with your own eyes...
Is this the door to the other world?
What will I find there?
Shusaku
Chapter ll
The Freedom of Eri Takabe
What happened to the dorm?
Oh my goodness...
My dear Eri, thank you for coming.
I've been waiting for you.
Mr. Kato, what is this about?
What do you care about those bitches,
they're nothing but whores.
Stop talking about them like that!
They are my friends!
They look like they're having fun, though.
That's what you think!
Nobody wants to be treated like animals.
Release all of them, right now!
If I say no?
What?
If you are willing to be a substitute
for them, that's a different story, Eri.
Substitute?
What do you think?
I don't think it's such a bad idea...
But...
You're a smart girl, you must've heard about "self-sacrifice"...
Isn't it the ultimate pleasure for a narcissist...
...to sacrifice herself for others?
I couldn't do anything to you
even if I wanted to, until now...
But now...
I can do whatever I want...
I can even make you mine.
Cut it out!
It won't open!
That's because this is what God wants.
It looks like you don't need
to stay a virgin in this game, Eri...
So please give yourself to me, Eri.
No!
What are you doing?
The god of desire neither bothers us nor interferes with us...
He is saying that I should baptize you with my cum!
Oh no!
No!
It's strange, I can't resist him...
White panties look great on a virgin girl...
It's my job to take your sacred virginity
and let you grow as a woman...
I've never asked you such a thing!
Oh, you don't need to be humble!
No, please stop it.
You bitch!
It must be tough for you...
...to hide your real desire, longing for
the pleasures deep inside you...
I would never surrender to you!
You are such a strong-minded person...
However...
...what if I do this?
Can you keep your attitude up?
So? I'm not feeling anything!
Really? You don't feel anything?
You are such a liar...
I'm not lying!
I'm not the kind of person
who lets desire take control!
You are lying to yourself.
Be honest with yourself, and seek pleasures.
Eri, you're in denial.
In other words, you may look like
a human but you're really not human...
I'm not human?
I told you.
You're merely a character in this game.
Don't be so pretentious!
Come on, why don't you suck my dick...
...and please all the gentlemen
who are playing this game!
No...
Does it stink?
I hate taking a shower.
You have to clean it with your mouth!
If you don't do it, I'll torture your friends with this...
Would you really release them if I suck this?
Of course...
You're irritating!
Put it deep in your throat!
No!
Don't you want to help your friends?
Do it!
Okay.
Now the whole thing is in your mouth.
Move your head now...
...like this!
God, you're bad.
Don't just put it in your mouth, use your tongue.
Make me feel good!
That's right, and for the gentlemen
who are playing this game...
...look sexy, too. Okay?
Don't spill it, stupid!
Swallow it until the last drop!
What a waste!
I'll make your other mouth swallow my cum, then...
Let's move onto the next step!
But you promised!
You should regret that you ever trusted me.
No, please!
I can't move...
I can't move my body, not since I got here...
W-Why?
No!
Gentlemen, can you see?
Today, I am here to take Eri's virginity...
...right in front of your eyes.
I hope you enjoy the show!
It smells like a fresh, green meadow.
Ah, the scent of precious purity...
It looks like a rose bud...
She's never had a man before,
it still has the perfect shape.
No, please don't look!
Too bad...
I'm aware that you've lost the power to resist since you came here...
The reason is simple.
That's because the...
...energy of the audience's sexual desires is focused here.
That's why you cannot resist me.
Mr. Kato, please, don't do this...
You sound like you're begging for your life.
This is the last fort you're protecting, isn't it?
If I break it in, you might be able
to break down the wall of reason...
Ouch...
Please stop this...
I like that look...
I've been waiting to see you getting
dirty and overwhelmed by pleasure...
It's hot...
I'm feeling hot inside of me.
Why?
Why am I feeling like this?
Finally, your love juice is coming out.
It smells like honey!
Well then...
Please, someone help me!
You'd better give up, and accept it...
...my super-size dick!
Oh, I can feel it! My dick is going deep inside of you...
It hurts! It hurts!
It's so warm inside...
It feels incredible!
Your body's already started to feel good.
It's so wet inside.
This is much better than my fingers, huh?
Mr. Kato, please pull it out...
Pull it out!
No one can stop me now!
Walk, walk!
Walk like a dog!
I-I can't do this...
I don't even love you.
Love?
What the hell are you talking about?
If you feel good, that's all that matters.
The climax is approaching...
Oh no! Please no!
I'll come inside and overflow your womb!
No...
Here I go!
Please, no!
Here we go!
What are you doing?
Now I would like to take the virginity of this hole...
How does it feel to have a real dick in your ass?
It's better than an enema, isn't it?
Eri, your job hasn't finished yet.
I would like you to clean up my dick with your mouth...
N-No...
if you serve me from the bottom of your heart...
...maybe I might find "love" in my soul...
Love...
Yes...
If I could find out what it is, then we
could finally put an end to this game.
Mr. Kato...
No!
I haven't made love with Takabe yet!
I don't want to end this game without making my wish come true!
Maejima...
That's not fair!
You can't do that, Maejima!
She's right!
Please Eri, let me do it!
Please, make love with me...
Takabe!
Takabe, we all love you!
Kaori Maejima...
Maejima...
Please, do it with your mouth.
I want to see it.
If you could accept someone rotten like me...
Otherwise, I can't end this game.
Takabe, please use your tongue more.
We've all been waiting for the day
when you would love us beyond reason.
Love beyond reason?
Yes, for a really long time.
You've gotten better.
Maejima...
I could give you pointers if you want.
That's good, Takabe...
Oh, Takabe...
I want more...
More!
Maejima...
Please, call me Kaori...
No! I won't let you go!
Kaori...
I was raped by him, just like this!
Eri, do you feel good?
It feels so good.
Please use your tongue more!
Shiho Minaduki, Nagisa Kondo...
How does this feel, Takebe?
Nagisa, let all of us be together.
Yes, we can finally become one...
So Eri, get on top of Shiho.
No!
Nagisa, move a little more...
Like this?
Look, Takabe...
Finally, she was able to learn the
true happiness of being a woman.
Oh Asami, do it harder!
Yeah, I'll make you come, Chiaki!
Eri...
Fujima...
Eri, do you think you can do
any nasty thing you want?
I don't know...
But even if you violate my body,
you can't violate my heart.
You should say it if you feel good...
You should learn to accept somebody's affection...
It's rude to someone who loves you,
if you don't admit how you feel.
Eri!
What happened?
Takabe?
This is great.
I wish I could turn this moment into eternity.
What happened?
What's happening?
This world is collapsing!
Damn it!
I don't want to be erased again!
What the hell is wrong with you, gentlemen?
I thought this was what we all wanted, wasn't it?
Why are you betraying me now?
Betray him?
Who the hell betrayed me?
Please, don't erase me...
Mr. Kato...
I'll comfort you...
What?
I just realized that you are,
indeed, the god of this world.
You mean, you would love a terrible guy like me?
I've been waiting for this moment to meet you...
Please come to me...
Don't be afraid...
I may be just a character in the game...
But I feel that if you and I become one,
I could continue to live in this world.
Even though we all live in this game, everyone can continue to live on...
...if they are loved.
So please...
Please remember us,
even in the corner of your mind...
Please keep us with you, forever...
No! Don't go yet!
Good bye...
Good bye, Mr. Kato...
He allowed us to live in this world.
So we can all still live together.
Hey, it's tomorrow, right?
What about tomorrow?
You forgot already?
The new teacher will come to your class tomorrow!
Oh...
So what does he look like?
A young, good-looking guy...
Shiho went to school to take
a peek at him the other day...
Nagisa, I told you that's a secret!
Well, because you looked
so happy when you told me...
Are you jealous?
We are allowed to live in this world and go on with our own lives...
...until he erases us from his memory.
You dropped this...
Eri...
Thank you, you came here to see me.