No!
Part 2: The Sorrow of the Degenerated Demon-birthing Princess
Hime Dorei: The Twin Princesses Fallen From Grace
Well done, Captain.
I'd tell you to take a break, but there is still work to do.
What? Still?
N-No... That's...
No... No... No!
No, stop this right now!
No, stay away! Stop!
No, please stop!
I'll do it! I'll do it!
No!
It's still coming?
Th-That's...
No!
No more...
Very good.
Very good, Captain.
You did well.
Yes!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
My pussy is cumming!
Let's do it again!
You've got your hands full, don't you, Princess?
Waldo-sama!
What would your father think if he saw you behave like such a slut?
I'm sure Father would be happy, too!
That would be wonderful, wouldn't it?
Yes!
Well then, I shall give this slut of a princess a little present!
Um... Waldo-sama?
You'll be fucked silly in every hole possible.
Do you understand, slut princess?
Y-Yes!
Give it your all!
Yes!
That hurts!
Hey, please don't be so rough.
I won't run away or anything.
Be good, all right? Thank you.
There's no need to rush. I'll do anything you want.
So, how are we gonna do it?
My stomach... hurts!
No! No!
Don't release it here! No!
Stop, stop, stop!
My stomach!
Please! No!
Stop!
No! No!
It's coming out! It's coming out from my ass!
I... I squirted it out...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Stop! I'm going to burst!
Wh-What are you doing?
Don't!
You two! How are things going?
Do not worry,
Waldo-sama. As usual for the kingdom...
...the statesmen have taken care of everything.
"I'll be waiting in the Great Hall. -Waldo Crowley"
Who's there!?
Y-You two... What's with that look?
Waldo-sama is waiting.
Waldo... sama?
Now, if you will.
I understand.
Now, please enter.
How good of you to come, Liese.
What is your intention, calling me out to a place like this?
Don't tell me you're going to confess your love for me?
I thought I'd give you a chance to make a deal.
A deal? Do you even understand the position you're in?
Aren't you the one who doesn't understand their position, Princess?
I got this chance thanks to you. So I'll be compassionate.
All along, you did this to get your revenge for the destruction of Izuur.
A good conjecture. Just what I'd expected of you, Princess.
First, let me show you this...
Estelle, Mireyu!
Wh-What? What is this?
Just what are these things!?
I was going to make the King do battle with these monsters.
I'd slay the king, lay waste to the country
and return everything to the beginning.
But, if you wish to avoid battle,
then make me the new king. You should be able to do that.
In that case, I promise I'll protect the peace of this land,
and let you have your place as queen.
Then, you would claim the throne as my husband?
Sounds good.
My stomach is being filled up!
Now, please me.
Yes.
You know what happens if you disappoint me even a little.
Yes. I will give my all to service you.
What's the matter?
I'll do it.
I needed to take a leak.
Service me with your tits next.
Yes.
Like this?
Well, aren't you skilled...
My stomach is so full!
Cum! Cum inside me more!
It's about time, isn't it?
It feels good!
It's so good! More!
No!
It hurts! It hurts!
I can't believe how tight you are!
Onee-sama... I...
You look just like me!
What a pretty girl! Let's enjoy this together!
What... What have I done?
These irreversible things...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Foolish women!
With this, the country is mine!