It's already this late...
Kase-san might have already arrived.
Kase-san!
S-Sorry. Did I keep you waiting?
It's rare for you to be late, Mayu.
I-Is something weird on me?
I spent a lot of time preparing...
I see.
Now isn't the season for uniforms.
Geez, of course!
Do you remember how many years
it's been since we first met?
I'm already a college student.
I'm not a child anymore.
~ Do You Hate Horny Girls? ~
Episode 1
I'm really happy that you invited me out today.
I called and texted you multiple times, too...
I hope I wasn't being a bother.
No, don't worry.
It's not like I have a girlfriend now.
Really?
Thank goodness, I'm relieved now.
How should I put this...
If you and I go out...
Well, I kind of think of you as a little sister.
R-Really?
I guess it's impossible to hook up with a student.
I said I'm not a child!
No, I didn't mean that... Well...
I'm still a virgin...
That means you're still a child.
Then...
Please make me an adult!
M-Mayu?
Sorry for blurting that out...
But I've decided.
K-Kase-san? Could you give me an answer?
Be prepared to have an alibi for your curfew.
Was this your first kiss?
Well, with John...
John? Some foreigner?
N-No, he's my dog. A Siberian Husky.
What?
Don't laugh!
You're rather assertive.
That kiss was beautiful.
D-Don't say such things.
K-Kase san, please turn off the lights.
It's embarrassing.
No, that means I wouldn't be able to see you.
No... Stop being mean.
Can I take off your clothes?
That's a cute bra.
Kase-san...
No, if you do that...
You're pretty sensitive.
Could it be that you do this yourself?
No, don't say weird things...
I'm taking off your bra.
No, don't stare at me...
My body is shaking...
No, not there!
Don't do that!
If you react to this, that means you do masturbate.
N-No, I don t...
Stop...
There's no way it would be
so sensitive if you didn't.
Come on, be honest.
No, if you do that...
I'll feel weird.
So? You do masturbate, right?
No...
Stop...
Come on, tell me.
I do... I do masturbate a lot.
S-So...
That's what I thought.
Why don't you show me?
Show me how you masturbate, Mayu.
But I can't do that...
Then let's stop today.
T-That's just mean! You can't!
Just do it how you naturally would.
Only if you turn off the lights...
Nope.
So? Are you going to do it, or are we going home?
F-Fine.
I'll do it.
I'll start masturbating now...
No! I'm already...
Touching yourself now?
No... Please, don't stare.
It's embarrassing.
No, I can feel it...
It's so embarrassing but I just can't stop.
I can hear some lewd sounds from down there.
No, don't say it...
I'm a lot more...
...sensitive than usual.
What do you fantasize about
when you masturbate?
Y-Your penis...
I fantasize about your penis penetrating
me when I masturbate.
No... I'm gonna cum...
Good, show me how you cum.
No, no, no!
No...
I'm orgasming in front of someone else...
So this is your...
What's your first impressions about it?
I-It's big...
Hot and hard.
Do you think it'll fit?
I wonder... I don't know.
But...
Please go ahead.
No, it's coming in...
Just a little more...
It's in, Mayu.
Thank goodness it's in.
I'll start off slow.
W-What's this? I'm feeling weird...
My insides are all shaking.
Wow, it's all  the way in.
Amazing, I can hear the echoes...
I feel so weak.
No, not so hard...
My insides... Wow...
Are you turned on?
No...
I feel so turned on even though it's my first time...
I'm going to cum again...
Me too, I'm going to...
Cum... Cum inside me.
Co ahead. It's my first time, so cum inside me.
F-Fill me up...
All right then.
No... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
Your warm fluids feel so good.
Its weird for you to call me Kase-san.
Just call me whatever you want
you don't need honorifics
Can I really?
As long as its not something weird.
Ill call you Kunio then.
Sure, that's fine.
I've finally become lovers with Kase-san
No, I mean Kunio
My heart is filled with happiness.
The first time he invited me into his
room was the summer of that year
Come on in.
I'm sorry for intruding.
Hey.
I'm going to the store to get some drinks.
It's fine, it's hot outside.
I turned on the A/C, so just
watch TV or something.
Okay.
The room's pretty neat.
I never thought he'd be interested
in photography and filming.
Oh right, TV.
Video?
Hey, wait...
But...
Don't worry.
No, not here...
Is that Kunio?
No, please...
It's no different from inside.
No! Someone will see us.
Moreover, it'd be more exciting this way.
That's not...
No, you're too rough.
You want it harder, don't you? Then...
No, but...
This feels amazing.
Wow, your hard thing is penetrating me.
I hear some lewd noises. Your
love juices are flowing out.
It's not like I can help it.
I mean, you're being so rough...
They're pretty hard.
Are you cold?
No! They're turned on. My nipples are turned on.
But, down here is even better.
Oh my god...
Your penis is amazing.
What?
What's wrong?
Why did you stop? Tell me.
I want pictures of you.
Can I?
N-No... I don't want that.
No, you can't do that.
Then let's stop it here.
I-Idiot, why did you pull it out?
I want to feel even better.
That's cheap.
Then let's go home.
Fine, whatever you want.
Do it.
How could you make me do this...
She did it...
She's naked even'though she's outside.
Can I really?
Do whatever you want.
Just put it in!
You're really taking pictures of it...
This is amazing...
This really turns me on.
Start moving more then.
Since I'm letting you do so much already,
it's only fair you make me feel good!
My, my.
Wow... Your penis is amazing.
My pussy is going to break...
People will see us if you're so loud.
I don't care.
Just let them watch.
Oh god... I'm feeling so good, I don't even...
Me too, I'm about to...
Cum! Cum!
Just let it all out inside me...
Lets cum together...
I know how many girls Kunio
has been out with before me.
But I never thought...
he'd do such a thing.
But...
But I...
Well, it's weird. I'm not mad, nor am I shocked.
My body just started to feel weird.
And I...
Wow, it's so hot.
Not to mention it's throbbing. You're so perverted.
Tomomi, you're the last one
I'd like to hear that from.
Now you said it... Cosh...
Wow.
Don't tell me this is...
Hey, put it in.
That's really dirty.
Jeez, it's so stiff.
You're amazing...
My cleavage is feeling so hot.
My breasts are going to melt...
Amazing...
Lots of juices are coming out of it.
It's easier to move up and down.
Using breasts to do that...
They call that a titty luck, right?
Even though I know this might get recorded...
I'm going to...
Is this your weakness?
It's throbbing.
Your penis is so sticky and hot.
I can't hold it back..
It's so stiff.
My tits are...
Of course it'd get hard if you suck on it.
Tomomi, you're amazing.
Thanks.
I'll make you feel even better.
Wow...
Not yet.
This too...
Your nipples...
My nipples feel good, don't they?
Crap, I'm going to...
It's okay, just shoot it all on my face.
Okay...
My face is filled with your cum.
So much cum...
So much semen on her face...
Kunio, it's my turn now.
It's inside.
It's all in.
Yeah, it's deep inside me.
Sakamoto, take the pictures.
Seriously?
You're not refusing, right?
Her expression is so hot.
Don't take pictures of my face... Don't...
Hey, ignore the camera and start moving.
I am moving... slowly...
Doesn't it turn you on when
someone else takes pictures?
You too. Your penis is getting harder.
Really?
Take the pictures!
Oh god, I'm in heaven...
I feel so good when someone's watching
and taking pictures...
Even there? That's embarrassing!
Don't cover it.
Were all going to watch it later.
No!
It's twitching here too.
Don't! Stop... My butthole doesn't feel that good...
N-No!
Your fingers inside... It's tight.
Wow. My finger's inside a girl's asshole.
Don't say that.
Don't play with me like that...
Sakamoto, don't you want to put it in?
I'm all hard.
No!
Kunio's already filled me up... Please, no.
It's okay.
His finger already went in.
N-No, don't do that...
No, no, no!
W-Wow...
Both her pussy and asshole are penetrated...
There's a cock inside my ass...
No!
Don't move yet...
Why?
Aren't you happy?
N-No!
It's the first time I've got two inside me...
My body's really sensitive...
I must take pictures of this.
You pervert! How many are you going to take?
That's right. I can't just take pictures.
No! My body's moving by itself...
You're getting turned on, aren't you?
I don't know...
My insides are churning...
My butthole is on fire...
Her butt is moving.
Well, of course it is!
You're both screwing me at the same time...
I'm gonna melt!
Oh god... My butt feels good...
It's my first time, but my butt is so turned on!
It's really tight.
No, I can't stop...
Having two penises in me is the best feeling ever!
I'm about to cum.
Cum... Cum all you want inside me.
I'm going to cum soon too...
So please cum inside me.
Fine, I'll cum inside your butt.
All right, just let it all out!
I'm cumming too.
Okay, okay! Cum inside both my pussy and butt!
G-Give me all your cum!
I-I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
W-Why am I doing such perverted stuff?
But... But...
This is an amazing feeling.
So you really watched it.
K-Kunio?
W-Well...
Don't worry.
I was going to show you anyway.
So what did you think?
Well...
I-I want to do that too
Why did you call me over all of a sudden?
Nothing much. Just wanted
to show you something.
At that time, I didn't know...
what would become of me.