The battle maiden Hildegard was such a pushover.
They call her "Child of Odin."
She's naive to the ways of men.
That made her easy to trap.
What will you do with her now?
Corrupt her like the others?
That would be boring. She'll help me continue Aliya's brainwashing.
Aliya?
[Master, Please Forgive This Indecent Servant...]
Ikusa Otome Valkyrie 2: Part 2 [The Treacherous Slave Girl]
Why am I being embarrassed like this?
Stop lying to yourself and you'll be much more comfortable with your new life.
Freya-sama... why...?
"Comfortable?"
How could she say such a thing to me?
A good friend of yours is dying to see you.
Stop!
What the hell?
Lady Hildegard? What's she doing here?
Stop it!
Aliya-oneesama... I'm so glad you're here.
Bastards! What have you done to her?
I think you have the wrong idea.
This battle maiden is here voluntarily.
What!?
Hilde-sama spent most of last night being ravaged by dozens of soldiers.
She surrendered to us to give you a break.
You should have seen it.
She lost all innocence.
She was raped in every possible hole.
No... Ojou-sama...
Onee-sama... I did it for you.
I'll do anything to keep you safe.
But it'd be rude not to let Hilde be on the giving end for a while.
T-That's...
I'll plant this pod in your friend,
and the two of you can experience real intimacy.
Can we, really?
No! Do what you want with me,
but don't put that inside her!
Ojou-sama!
Something's... coming out...
I have a penis!?
How about that? Bet you'd like to fuck something with it.
Yes... my penis is hot!
I want pussy!
Ojou-sama... wait, stop!
Onee-sama, let's pleasure each other.
No! Ojou-sama, don't put that-
Your pussy feels wonderful.
No!
Take it out of me, please!
Wow. It turns out the "Child of Odin" is a nymphomaniac.
She'll fit right in around here.
Tell me about it.
She's like a fucking machine!
Stop watching! You mustn't see us Valkyries like this!
Onee-sama... So nice and wet...
No, don't!
You're fucking me too hard!
Aliya's starting to feel it now.
See how stiff her nipples are.
Ojou-sanui... why are you doing this?
Your pussy is sucking my cock.
I'm so happy that we're this close.
No, Hilde... please...
I want to cum on you. All over you!
Just not inside me, all right?
I can't... take it anymore! My cock is ready to cum!
They put on quite a show for us.
Just beneath the surface, the Child of Odin is as base as any of us.
What... What have I done?
It's alright.
You raped me as best you could.
Onee-sama, I'm sorry...
Our chastity is ruined.
Their corruption is inevitable.
Master will be pleased.
Leia, how does it feel to have another of your friends fall under my control?
Enough about that, Master. Just focus on the titties wrapped around your dick.
Your ample breasts are among the best I've felt.
I'm happy to hear it. Please enjoy my titties.
Your prick is so hot! Fuck my cleavage!
Almost time for me to cum.
Yes, please! Spray it all over me!
All over my tits!
I'm dripping with your yummy fuck milk! Good to the last drop!
But we're just getting started.
Dirty Leia wants Master to punish her with his fuckstick.
Your pussy is sopping wet.
That's because it's hungry for a good, hard fuck from Master's cock.
Talk about a goddess in heat.
I love it!
Take me from behind, like a filthy beast!
Hey now, move your hips against me.
But...
It's so good.
Your cock is amazing!
Your dirty beast cock makes me feel like a rutting animal.
Get ready. I'm going to pump you full of semen.
Do it!
Fill me with an ocean of hot cum!
Here it comes!
Oh, God! Right there! Fuck me numb!
I'm cumming! cumming!!
I can't... feel my legs...
The Eclipse is reaching totality
I can't wait to receive today's cum bath!
Oh no, the cum you just put in me... it's spilling out.
This is the day we've been waiting for, Aliya.
W-What do you want?
I think you know the answer to that.
I don't feel well today. I need a break.
I'm serious.
I'll... I'll be fine by tomorrow.
The Eclipse is tonight.
Yeah? What about it?
You draw your strength from the moon.
When the Eclipse reaches totality, you will be weakened.
If I cum inside you during that window,
you're certain to become pregnant.
You bastard!
Cool your temper. Your fate is in my hands.
Damn you.
You'd better be more polite.
Please, not today.
I'll... Ill do anything.
"Anything?" How interesting.
All right. Lick my foot, then.
Your foot?
You said "anything."
Or would you rather be pregnant?
You snake!
God, it stink It's filthy I can't..
What's wrong? Lick it now.
You know better than that. Keep going until I tell you to stop.
Put the whole toe in your mouth.
Leia, you know what to do.
Yes, Master.
What?
N-No, Leia! You can't put that inside me.
Wait! It won't fit!
Sorry, I'm just following orders.
It's going in!
Impressive, isn't it? Leia made it for you.
If you can keep it all in, I'll give you a break tonight.
You can't be serious!
Stop! I can't... I'm going to burst!
Ugh... I feel...
Too full? Shit it out, then.
It's coming out...
Go for it. You'll feel better.
Look away!
Oh, God!
Wow. Remarkable distance!
I've never seen you like this, Aliya. I like it!
A deal's a deal.
Prepare to get knocked up.
No... Don't...
Your breasts are swelling in anticipation.
What?
That can't be.
You're ovulating. And those eggs need to be fertilized.
That cock... is sure to impregnate me.
No!
A pussy in heat is a beautiful thing.
No... take it out... please! Take it out...
Stop, please! I can't today!
I don't have the strength!
No!
My cock is aching to impregnate you!
I don't want to...
be pregnant!
Aliya's so hot!
Are you ready for my seed?
No!
Stop! Stop!
Please don't! I'll become pregnant!
No!
No! No!
NO!!
It's inside me.
Eight Months Later
C-Can't breathe!
Oh... God!
Leia invented quite a device here. I like it.
Are you enjoying the tentacles? Your pussy is a mess.
Let me go! Get your fingers out of my cunt!
Hey, can I do it now? Can I fuck her?
Sure, why not? Get in there.
No! I don't want to be fucked by a girl.
Wait... didn't you fuck Aliya?
But... that was...
This is going to be sweet!
It's amazing! So hot... and tight!
No...
Fenrir, why don't you go to work on her ass?
No! Onee-sama, please... help me!
If you bitches want to fuck, come over here!
What an invitation.
I think I'll take you up on it.
You traitor!
What the fuck is that?
No tricks, no magic seeds. This is how I've always been.
Just as I am neither god nor demon, I'm neither man nor woman.
It's all in! Must be poking into your uterus.
Be careful! There's a baby in there. Please!
That's up to you. Can you satisfy me?
I can. I'll bring you to orgasm.
A battle maiden who so readily offers her cunt is a sight indeed!
Shut up! Just finish, quick.
You're going to be a good whore just like Aliya, aren't you?
Please, be gentle... you'll make me pee.
Hormones are making you irrational.
How's this?
No! The baby...
Don't worry about that. My demon baby is no weakling.
No! Please, that's too hard. The baby...
Since when do you care about my child?
The baby is all I care about!
Y-Yes!
Fuck me deep!
God... your big dick is ripping me apart!
No... I'm cummmg! I'm cimming!
Duke, are you satisfied with our services?
To be honest, playing with you has just been a way of killing time.
Actually, as fun as you Valkyries were at first,
I'm bored with you now.
So I'm handing you over to new ownership.
Duke...
is this what you wanted for us all along?
You brought this on yourselves.
The baby just kicked!