Aki-chan, what are you doing!
The coffee's gonna get cold.
This feels good.
N-No! Don't touch there!
You put tape there again?
It's gonna get peeled off.
But... Cedar pollen goes right through my panties.
What are you saying? You said
you didn't wear panties before.
I... I never said that.
...I think.
Whatever. You better get ready
or else you'll be late for school.
Oh no!
It's around that time of year for me, too...
Seasonal allergies...
The Pollinic Girls Attack!
I Can't Stop the Sticky Sliminess
Oh no, I'm late again.
Sugita-kun will see me again.
Excuse me! Let me in!
Excuse me!
Good morning, Hanazono-san.
G-Good morning, Sugita-kun.
Today's pollen seems bad again.
N-No!
I... I have to hold it in... or else Sugita-kun is going to see.
N-No...
I can't take it!
This is perverted and embarrassing...
...and Sugita-kun is watching.
B-But it feels good!
S-Stop!
If you press that hard, I'm gonna go crazy.
I can't take it!
I came again...
It must be a difficult time for you.
If you want you can use this.
Seasonal allergies are so embarrassing! I hate it!
It's okay, I'll be fine. Put it in my ass.
I'm going in, Miku.
O-Okay.
Are you really alright?
Don't worry, just go in and out.
You should make yourself feel good.
Okay.
I feel you! I feel your hotness inside my ass.
It's in! It's in deep!
How is it? Does it feel good?
It feels good!
No! My clitoris! I'm gonna come!
I can't hold it!
Come, Aki-kun!
In Miku's ass, Just come!
Hey, I got really wet today, so I might be able to do it.
So... can you put it in here too?
Don't push yourself. You need get bigger first.
I'm 21 already. There's no way I'm gonna get any bigger!
Oh, I'm sony.
I have to go to work now. Let's
talk again when I come back.
He and I can't have normal husband-and-wife sex.
It's because my pussy is too small.
Ow! Ow! I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
It's been 6 months since the failure at our honeymoon.
Fake orgasms and fake sex...
isn't what normal married couples do.
I'll buy something for dinner on
the way back. You like sweets?
Gosh, you're such an idiot!
M-Miku?
See you later.
I want to be one with Aki-kun.
No, no! I need to think! I'm supposed to be a good wife!
The Pollinic Girls Attack.
Koume Trading Company
Looks like I have to do something about it.
H-Hey, do you have a moment?
This is reference material for tomorrow's meeting.
C-Can you add something to it?
Sure. Hanazono-san, you have seasonal
allergies too? It must be harsh.
Yes, I do.
There's been a lot of pollen in the air since this morning.
Since this morning?
Don't stare at me like that!
I'm gonna leak!
Hanazono-san, are you all right?
I should go to the clinic.
My pussy is gonna get too big
if they keep putting dicks in it.
Pussy getting big!
W-What is this?
Is this what I think it is...
Yeah. I was thinking seriously.
Aki-kun?
It's better to take action than suffer.
Let's try it right now.
What's this?
It's a speculum.
I'll check the diameter of your vagina every day.
It's... a little intimidating.
Don't worry. Spread your legs.
It's cold!
Here we go.
Stay calm. You'll get used to it.
N-No... He's able to see my insides.
Ow! It hurts!!
This is as big as it could go.
Get ready.
You're gonna put that in?
This size should just barely fit.
Stop! It won't go in!
You'll be fine. Now, relax your muscles.
It's all the way in.
Until I measure your vagina again, keep it in.
What?
It's gonna keep getting bigger until my penis fits.
Okay.
From now on, this will be inside of me?
Will I be all right?
You have a delivery.
I'm sorry, I don't have a Hanko stamp, can I sign?
Oh no, it's hardening.
T-This is huge!
Oh no, I'm thinking dirty.
Good, it's 5mm wider!
Looks like I'm getting more flexible.
I can't take it! I'm having a hard time holding things!
It's cold and it feels good. I feel it widening.
This is amazing. It keeps widening.
M-More! Make it wider!
My pussy is getting wetter.
Stop it! Stop doing this!
Not my ass! Don't mess with it!
T-This is intense. I'm jealous of all
these kids with seasonal allergies.
B-But starting tonight, I'll...
I'm home.
Aki-kun, welcome homedick!
H-homedick?
Welcome home dick... put together it's homedick!
What's the special occasion?
It's because... I'm finally big enough.
Please? Can we get started. I can't wait
Fine.
I don't think we need to hold back.
Aki-kun, you're hotter than ever.
Tonight our practice will end.
I'm gonna measure you with myself this time.
Really?
Please, put it in.
Put it all the way in and measure me.
Here we go.
It's... It's in!
I feel you! Aki-kun, you're filling me up.
Amazing... you're so tight ifs almost hurting.
Aki-kun... Aki-kun, I'm finally one with you.
No need to call me Aki-kun anymore.
Honey, honey I love you!
Don't leave me! Stay with me forever!!
Miku, your breasts, your ass, your body, everything about you is mine now.
This feels good!
This is my first time but now I want more.
I'm about to come! I'm coming! A week's worth!
Let it out! Fill me up with your hot cum!
We're finally together as husband and wife.
You're right.
All right, now we have to make your dick bigger.
Here.
What?
What do you think?
The Pollinic Girls Attack.
This morning in the bus, Sugita-kun saw me orgasm again.
Yeah, I try not to go on the same bus as him, but...
But Aki, you're not very good at waking up early.
I'm no good! I came so many times in front of Sugita-kun.
Don't worry about it. There's nothing
you can do this time of year.
But, they make fun of me saying,
"Girls with seasonal allergies are dirty."
Maybe I should give up on him.
You can't blame it on the pollen, Aki.
What?
Aren't you blaming your cowardice on seasonal allergies?
l-l wouldn't...
Hmm, then I should go after Sugita-kun.
What? Yun...
D-Don't do it so hard.
My nipples are sensitive.
Uh, sony.
W-Wait!
Wait Sugita-kun!
I was waiting for you.
Me?
Do you know what the best medicine
for seasonal allergies is?
No, I don't know.
Um... they say it's the semen from a boy who
isn't suffering from seasonal allergies.
What?
Wait a second!
I'm seriously suffering from my seasonal allergies.
I want you to save me.
It's getting Dig.
Sugita-kun, your dick is so big and hot.
Don't say that.
Wait.
I can't do this.
Why? Doesn't my mouth feel good?
It's not about that.
Don't worry about me. Let it out in my mouth or my pussy.
Come all you want where you want.
Wait!
Wait, Yuri!
Aki!
Hanazono-san.
I'm sorry...
I can't give up after all.
I'm full of cum and perverted,
but Sugita-kun, I like you.
I'm sorry about making you cry on the bus.
I've been thinking about you since then, Hanazono-san.
S-Sugita-kun...
Well well, it's finally coming to an end.
Fine, I'll entertain you two.
I'm glad. I really wanted to do
this with someone I really like.
Sugita-kun...
G-Go ahead. My pussy is already
wet from the seasonal allergies.
You're beautiful when you have allergies.
It's inside of me! Sugita-kun, your dick is inside of me! It's in my pussy!
I'm gonna move.
It feels good! You're in deep! It feels
like you're kissing my womb.
Even I'm getting really aroused.
The pollen in the air is getting heavy.
You're getting even bigger.
Hanazono-san, you're slippery and it feels really good!
Don't! I'll...
Don't, it's my first time...
D-Don't! Don't put it in there.
Save me!
It won't fit!
Your dick... your dick's rubbing against...
My body's already hot.. I'm about to lose it!
I'm about to... too!
Do what you want! I want you to mess up my body!
Let it out! Just let it all, all out!
I didn't know... seasonal allergies felt so good.
Thank you, pollen-san.
I'll be on my way!
W-Wait, Aki-chan, you're gonna go out wearing that?
I'm gonna be getting,wet every
morning from now on anyway.
Shouldn't you at least wear a skirt?
No, there's gonna be a lot of pollen and
I don't need to hide the wetness.
Now then, III be off!