I want to become one with Onii-chan.
This isn't the time to do this, Kaede.
Onii-chan, look at my pussy.
It's already this wet.
Here, look inside me.
Oh, no... This feels too good!
No! My finger...
Even though this is really embarrassing,
I'm starting to overflow.
There's so much nasty juice flowing out of me.
This is amazing! It's tingling so much.
Onii-chan is watching me masturbate.
It's so wonderful!
Kagirohi: Shaku Kei
Vol 2: Tentacles From Hell
Onii-chan...
Let's do it...
Why...
is your face so sad?
If this will satisfy you...
All I do is cause you trouble, right?
Kaede...
I'm sorry, Sempai. But please, just this once, let
me be selfish and express myself completely.
All right.
I'm so glad, Sempai.
Sempai, please make love to me.
Sempai, this is really embarrassing.
Please don't tease me like that.
It's going inside! It's so hard and thick.
All of it went inside.
I'm so happy. Your entire penis is inside of me.
Sempai, don't worry about me.
Please move however you want.
All right.
Thank you, Sempai.
Your dick is moving.
It's thrashing around inside me.
No! My breasts feel so good, too.
It's amazing! Your dick is ramming me over and over again!
I'm going crazy!
It's hitting my womb. I'm going crazy!
It's so good! Sempai's cock is stirring up my insides!
It's too good!
It feels so good. It feels too good!
Amazing! I'm losing my mind!
I can hear nasty noises. They're so loud!
I can't take it anymore!
Kaede!
I'm at my limit...
You came so much.
Sempai... Are you serious about Ajisai?
Yes. I'll go even if you try to stop me.
You love her that much.
But...
Kae...
I can't let you put yourself in any more danger.
I'll take care of Ajisai.
I'll put and end to the feast for your sake.
Where do you think you're going?
Sumire-sama...
My, my, Kaede-chan. Does this mean that you're betraying me?
I made a promise with Sempai.
You're doing this for that man?
I think you need some harsh punishment to set you straight.
Ajisai!
No way... This isn't supposed to...
Why?! Why would Izanami-sama do this?!
What are you doing, Ajisai!?
What are you going to...
I won't forgive you.
Where did Kaede go? She couldn't have...
Dammit!
No! This is disgusting! Let me go! No! Sempai!
Someone save me! Release me at once!
Let me hear you cry louder. Amuse me.
Stop! That's too big!
Not my ass!
That's right. Savor this suffering.
It's going in... No!
It's reaching my womb... No, don't go that deep!
Gross, it's thrashing around inside of me.
No! It's too thick! Don't go in there!
Don't!
My ass! My ass is going to be ripped apart.
N-No!
If two of them move around like that...
It's going all the way in.
Please take them out!
Don't spread my asshole apart.
No! That's too wide. It's so thick.
If you do it that hard, I'll go crazy.
Not both of them...
I'm cumming from my ass.
Please stop! It's going in so deep!
My ass...
Don't slither around inside! No, not there!
Don't go in that deep!
My ass is starting to feel strange!
Stop it!
I want to cum.
Here's some more.
Don't! I'll cum! It's so big!
It hurts! I'm cumming!
I won't let it end yet.
You deserve more.
Ajisai!
A-o-i?
Stop this already! Ajisai!
I am now Izanami.
Izanami is now deeply intertwined with all that was this person.
I won't stop until I lay waste to this entire village.
Ajisai wouldn't do something like that!
Oh, she would.
And if you get in my way...
My beloved Ajisai couldn't do something like that!
Don't concern yourself with me anymore.
Aoi...
This light...
Izanami is disappearing.
It's beautiful.
Hey, do you remember?
The first time we met was in this classroom.
Yeah. A lot's happened since then.
Say...
Whoa...
I want to do it here - right where we first met.
Can we?
Okay, fine.
I'll take care of everything.
Even though we only kissed, it's already this hard?
Does it hurt? Don't worry. I'll let you cum soon.
Wow, it's already this big.
This perverted smell is amazing!
It's so hard and hot, and it's throbbing.
Well, how is it? Does my hand feel good?
I'll make you feel even better.
O-Oh... Something's coming out already.
Does it feel good? It's okay, you can cum.
Let it all out.
Amazing...
Come to me.
Oh no...
Yes!
There...
A finger's going in!
If you do that I'll...
I can't take it... Hey, hurry up and do it...
Please put it in.
It's touching me...
Stick it in! Stick it in!
Don't tease me.
It's inside!
It's hot and hard!
So big...
I feel like I'll melting!
No! I'm being too loud!
Oh no!
It's so good!
You can do it harder if you want.
No! It's amazing! I'm overflowing.
It's making weird noises. It's embarrassing!
Oh no, I'm getting even wetter!
M-My womb...
My insides are being pounded!
If you do that, I'll...
Don't be so rough!
No! It's amazing! I'm going to cum!
It's twitching inside of me!
It's okay to cum. You can shoot it all inside me!
Shoot lots of your hot stuff inside!
Oh no, I'm going to...
No, I'm going to... No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's coming inside. So much is flowing out.
I love you.
Translation:
KuriosAkantha
Translation Check:
Tamesuu
Edit:
Rika-sama
Timing:
Zetsuei
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Quality Check:
Chaosrains