THE TIME
COLORED
SCARLET
Hiiro no Koku
Episode 3
Die
SKLAVIN
der Lust
Business trip?
Yes, starting next week.
I'll be gone for a month or so.
A whole month?
Yes. Still, it's the shortest trip I could make.
But I just had a good idea.
Actually, my business trip is going to take
me to the neighborhood where I grew up.
Where your mom is?
Yes, so I thought perhaps we should
all go there as a family.
Emi has a break from school anyway.
And Etsuko, wouldn't this be a nice
opportunity for you to relax too?
What do you think?
Yes.
It's a good idea.
I'll go with you.
Hello? Aketa residence.
Hi, wifey.
Haven't talked to you in a while.
You sound well.
What do you want?
Aw, so cold.
I was hoping you'd give us a call by now.
Don't screw with me!
What's wrong?
Who is it?
No one.
Just a prank call.
A prank call?
Yes.
He sounded drunk.
He was really annoying.
Okay, move aside.
I'll answer this time.
N-No, don't!
Why not?
Um...
You need to be firm with people
like that, or they don't get it.
Hello?
What?
Oh, hi! Thanks.
Oh, is that so?
What a problem.
Okay, I'll put her on.
Wait just a minute.
Etsuko, it's for you.
An old friend of yours from high school.
Okay, I'm going to go brush my
teeth and go back to bed.
Okay...
Hello?
What's that?
You thought I'd actually call back myself?
I used one of our secretaries.
He probably trusted her because she was a woman.
I knew it.
Sounds like he's got a business trip coming up.
How do you know that?
We're aware of everything you two discuss.
Did you think we'd go through all this trouble with
you and not take some precautions for the future?
I hear you and your husband had a
pretty decent fuck last Saturday.
Your screams sounded so cute.
But they weren't as intense as the
screams when you were fucking us.
I'd sure like to give your husband a lesson.
He can't satisfy you, can he?
What do you want?
We'd like you to stay behind during the business trip.
What did you say?
Tell your husband you have to go to a class reunion.
I can't.
Tell him you'd like to stay behind.
We won't take no for an answer.
You can't say no anyway.
No! You can't!
You don't have to apologize.
If you have a reunion, there's no choice.
Actually, Emi was the one who took it badly.
But it's good that you'll be able to join us in a few days.
Y-Yes, it is.
I think she'll be lonely without her mommy.
Well, I'll take her while she's asleep.
Well, I'll see you later.
I'm so sorry.
I told you, you don't have to apologize.
Enjoy your freedom in the meantime.
Oh my, are you going out, Aketa-san?
Good morning.
My business trip is close to my childhood
home, so I'm taking the whole family.
Oh, the whole family, eh?
My wife has a class reunion,
so she'll be joining me later.
That also sounds like fun.
But you'd better hurry and join them
before your daughter gets too lonely.
I will.
Well, Etsuko, I'll miss you.
I'll miss you too.
Well, I'll be on my way as well.
Thanks for seeing me off!
Not a problem. Have a nice trip.
Have a nice trip, dear.
Where did you guys come from?
We're very resourceful men.
This thing has helped us out a lot.
When people are alone, they do such amusing things.
Wifey, we've brought a special colleague
of ours from the office today.
He'll make things more fun.
Man, with this body, it's tough hot to get aroused.
So she can't live without the attention
of a group of young gangbangers, eh?
No!
I'm not that kind of woman.
Really?
Then between your husband and these guys,
which experience has made you cum more?
I...
Looks like you've been branded pretty deep.
No! Not the rope.
Just stop it!
That's not what your eyes are telling me.
Hold her.
Don't!
You're actually scared, aren't you?
Scared of feeling the rope again.
You're scared you'll like it, huh.
Don't worry, you'll learn very soon.
What do you think, Shima-san?
No. Don't look at me.
Stop trying to tell us you don't like it.
If you get this wet just from being tied up...
You're hornier than a rabbit from sexual frustration.
You can't.
Why?
So sensitive.
I like that reaction.
Unless a woman really knows the flavor
of a man, she won't react in this way.
What?
This is different than usual.
This man scares me.
Even your butthole is wet.
When a woman is sexually aroused,
her body temperature rises,
and she becomes even more sensitive to pleasure.
You're turned on to the depths of your soul.
Whoa! What a reaction.
Nice spot.
The feeling from your asshole is
completely different from your pussy.
Awesome!
She's pissing herself.
Did she cum just from that?
Looks like she reacts much more
strongly than I thought she would.
Her flesh is good too.
She's even better than I'd imagined.
Okay, you guys can do what you want now.
Just what I wanted to hear!
You can count on us!
Do a good job, okay?
Fuck her until her hips fall off.
Just look at that.
She's a waterfall.
I can't stand it.
But, we get to fuck a MILF again.
This is awesome!
For sure, for sure!
Hey, don't you think the rope around her legs is loose?
Okay.
It's all tied tight.
We'd better make it so she can't move.
I agree.
From now on, we'll be together forever.
That's right. One happy family.
Come on, wifey, take a look.
It's your favorite d**k in the flesh.
You want it, don't you?
We'll cover you in our juice.
Watching us do that really makes you want it, huh?
Come on, put it in.
You don't wanna keep her waiting too long, do ya?
The anal beads are making her too tight.
I'm coming in now.
Come on, come on.
I'll make you feel better.
Awesome!
Yes!
Wifey, you sure are excited.
Look how firm you are.
Even when a man you don't like
enters you, you get turned on.
That's the kind of woman you are.
My butthole... No...
You don't really mean "no".
You really want it.
Come on, how does it feel?
Yes!
Man, this is hard work.
Let me have some too.
Sure. We've got plenty.
But doesn't this place just feel like our castle now?
Certainly.
Still, I hear that replacements have been lined
up in case we can't keep performing.
Our leader likes to have extra men around, I guess.
And who wouldn't want to take our place?
Our job is the best.
I agree.
Yeah, but I feel sorry for Kazu.
It seems he's been on Daigashi's shit list for a while.
I guess Kazu never thought the boss
would get that upset with him.
For real. That's scary shit.
What are you talking about?
Um, nothing. Boring stuff.
Well, I guess I'll have another go.
Okay.
I'm cumming.
What?
You're cumming again?
How many times does that make?
Oh, no!
Come on, come on.
Another guy's come back.
Let's do some double penetration.
But Shima-san, are you sure she'll
hold up if we use her so hard?
Just do as I say. Don't ask questions.
Please stop it!
I'm cumming!
And I don't want to cum.
That woman is a masochist at heart.
It's not a matter of her body.
It's her temperament.
Did you cum again?
The more you give her, the harder it
will be for her to be without a man.
She won't be able to live without a man fucking her.
Don't make me cum again.
I'll die!
Did you cum so much you threw your back out?
In that case, when I cum, I'll stop.
Really?
Yeah. I'm not a liar.
But you need to make all of us cum within three hours.
Can you do it?
Okay.
Not "Okay".
"Please let me do it".
Please let...
Please let me do it.
Yes, yes, that's pretty nice.
Come on, move your hips more,
like a slut.
Yeah, that's right.
See, now you know how to move your hips.
Right.
Use your tongue more.
Suck it down to the base.
Please... Please cum.
I can't...
If you want us to cum, provide the right mood.
Come on, be naughtier.
Please...
More... Do more.
More sexy things.
Show your feelings some more.
– You need to behave more lewdly, or we won't feel it.
– Yes!
Oh, yes!
It's amazing!
Yes.
I love this.
Your d**k is reaching all the way inside.
И правильно, это же могут увидеть дети :).
I really feel horrible.
I've become such a horrible woman.
But my pussy feels so good I can't stand it.
I'm gonna cum.
I can feel it.
I can feel it coming.
Do me. Do me.
Harder...
Oh, no.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Please...
She came again.
– Did she get too excited?
– Please...
Please cum!
– Don't make me cum all the time.
– Come on, come on.
Oh, no!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again.
Oh, no...
I'm cumming!
Okay.
Here's your reward.
Come on, what's wrong?
It's all my pent-up cum.
Awesome.
More...
More cum...
Give me more.
I love it.
Awesome.
Oh, you came here too?
Daigashi told me to come over and check things out.
Oh, Daigashi sent this along for you.
Hm, leave it over there.
But, has she fallen already?
Not yet.
Not even close.
But looking like that, she's almost...
She's almost...
Why am I acting so lewdly?
Why am I doing this?
With each passing minute, the sensation
becomes more addictive.
Sexual ecstasy.
Oh, it's coming.
Cum inside!
Yes!
The sense of disgrace is giving way to happiness.
Inside...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Her fall from grace...
is only beginning.
Right now...
I could run away.
Run away somewhere.
But how would I explain it to them?
While I'm dressed like this, I...
I didn't put on any underwear.
So, why is this happening?
Just the thought that someone might see me...
Good morning, Mrs. Aketa.
Good morning.
You're up rather early today.
Taking out the trash?
Y-Yes.
This little guy was noisy this morning.
He wanted his walk.
How was your reunion?
Um...
I...
Excuse me!
Um...
Goodness, that was a lot of fun.
You got turned on because that old man saw you, huh.
Look how wet she is.
If she got that wet just because someone
saw her without her underwear,
she really is a pervert!
N-No...
You're wrong.
No, you're wrong.
You're a slut.
Slutty odors emanate from your body.
And when a man comes within smelling
distance, you wiggle your hips,
and your pu**y juice spills down your thighs.
Why...
Why am I letting them do such horrible things to me?
What's wrong with me?
Looks like she can't get past it.
She wants a man all the time.
Her mouth tries to make excuses, but this
part of her body can't be silenced.
Every time we put something
in here, her fluids flow out.
Seriously.
You're a real whore, wifey.
No!
Come on, come on.
Yes, yes.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me the location is turning you off.
Eh?
I guess you're not that much of a slut after all, wifey.
That's right.
Sucking other men's dicks while your old man is away
doesn't excite you as much as we thought.
Or is it the opposite? You don't
think it's a bad thing at all?
You're... wrong.
Oh, really?
Look how loudly you're screaming.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You should just accept it and have fun.
Come on, come on.
I can't.
No, I can't think of anything else.
My body is quivering,
and I can't think of anything else.
That must be it.
They're right.
I don't care anymore.
Just keep doing this.
Keep doing this.
Sorry about that.
You want me to continue?
I...
You want this?
The size, the length, and the thickness...
This is perfect for you, right?
No! Don't go!
It will fulfill your every desire.
Just be honest with yourself.
Emi!
I'm sorry.
I...
You're about to melt, aren't you?
If you accept it, then I'll give you this toy.
I...
I'll give it to you so hard you'll forget everything else.
Now, what will you do?
You want me to stop?
No...
Don't...
Don't stop.
Please don't stop.
Please let me cum.
Please... Please let me cum.
I can't think of anything else.
I'm a sex slave.
If they'll help me cum, I'll do anything.