What do you think, Suki-san? Isn't this an ideal spot?
I can see it.
Yes, you can see it.
But do you suppose it's okay for us to do this?
It's not an offense punishable by seppuku.
Still, Mito is well known as the
most beautiful woman here:
the "Crimson Princess".
And we get to behold her beauty unadorned!
In secret, softly...
Ah! I can't hold myself back anymore!
Easy there, restrain yourself. Just a bit more.
Oh, her dark area...
Just a bit more and I'll get to see the whole thing!
Me too!
In just a bit more I'm gonna...
Ah, that felt good.
Yuck, stop it!
Ah, Princess...
What lovely weather we're having today.
Who are you intruders!?
You rude men!
Harenchi Koumon Manyuuki
Translation: Voldemort | Timing: commander`A | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Mito Castle
Mito West Mountain Chalet
My, Princess, but you do look dashing.
Suki-san, Kaki-san, you also look nice.
Well, Suki-san, Kaki-san, let's set forth!
Yes, Princess.
Don't call me "Princess" from now on.
Yes, danger might await us behind every corner.
That's why I'm dressed like a young male samurai.
I'm no longer a young princess
but the son of Saru Taishin.
And while on a quest for my samurai training,
I've enlisted you commoners to accompany me.
Well...
Yes! Let my new name be Kurenai Mitonosuke.
So, here's a little enlightenment for all you kiddies.
Chilled Tofu
The stories about this that you used
to watch on TV were all false.
After retirement, Koumon-sama lived
in the Seizansou Residence.
Tokugawa Mitsukuni
He didn't have time to travel and gather materials
for the compiling of "The Great History of Japan".
Instead, the person who went out on
a quest was his beloved daughter.
Princess Mito Kurenai
The very same Princess Mito Kurenai you see.
That is to say, a substitute for Mito Koumon!
Mito Koumon
And also, this pair is traveling with her.
Sasaki Saburo
Suki-san, aka Sasaki Sukisaburo, and
Kaki-san, aka Atsumi Kakinoshin.
Crimson Princess Bath Scene
They had their first meeting when the two
men peeked in while she was bathing.
Suki-san & Kaki-san Apology Scene
However, they were not asked to commit seppuku,
as they would have been If this
was historically accurate.
Instead, they were given positions to
guard the Princess on her quest.
Well then, kiddies, the wait is over.
The Party Sets Out on Their Quest Scene
Here is the tale of the Crimson Princess's
quest with that naughty and stupid pair.
Are there any further questions?
Harenchi Koumon Manyuuki
Then, it's Harenchi Koumon Manyuuki.
Let's begin, let's begin.
Castle Warden | Fujii Mansion
Mamushi, are you there?
Yes, sir.
Over here.
I hear that Princess Kurenai has set off on a quest.
Something about collecting historical
documents for her father.
Apparently, certain people would prefer
that Princess Kurenai not return home.
As you wish, sir.
Gokaro-sama!
Mondayu-sama!
Oh my, oh my.
Just visiting one house has been such a bother.
Map of Everything
How very tiring.
This area in particular is the dividing
line between Mito and Edo.
I don't really care about that.
More imporantly, what's the matter with this room?
It's old, small, and smelly,
and it only has three tatami mats!
Is your room like this as well?
What do you mean?
The three of us are sharing this room.
That's right.
This was the only vacant room they had.
What? We're sleeping together?
But I've never slept in a room with men before!
But you're a man now, right?
Kurenai Mitonosuke-san!
If I intend to go on a harsh journey as a man,
how can I do that if I'm
frightened of my subordinates?
Hey, you promise that you won't try any tricks?
Of course we won't!
We're your comrades!
That's right.
A comrade does not harm another comrade.
Sharing a room with the Princess...
She's as good as mine.
We'll discover our love for each other tonight,
and there will be ejaculation.
Not only ejaculation,
but also soft, smooth, pearly white skin!
Even though her face is young and
innocent, she's got rocking tits!
And they'll be mine.
Very well.
I'll sleep in here with you.
With that decided, Princess...
Um, I mean, Mitonosuke-san, have a drink.
But I've never had sake before.
Every experience is important.
He's right!
Yes! That was a nice gulp now!
One more cup.
Princess, um, Mitonosuke-sama?
Hello? Mitonosuke-sama?
Your face is bright red.
I wonder if she's already drunk.
Impossible! She only had one drink!
Oh my, oh my, Princess, your body is too much.
Rude beasts!
Is this what your intentions were when you
agreed to accompany me on my quest?
This is an important mission that
my father entrusted to you.
We're collecting vital historical
documents for the new Japan!
We're already in severe danger,
venturing into Tokugawa houses.
That is why I'm risking my life
and impersonating a man.
Do you understand?
You're exactly right.
Yes, m'lady, um, m'lord, I mean, Mitonosuke-sama.
Yes, but, yes, but... To tell you the truth...
I'm scared!
Just the mere thought of running into
something dangerous on the road...
It seems as though the Princess is drunk.
It seems so.
Now, now, Princess.
Don't cry.
We're here for you.
Yes, we are.
Really? Suki-san, Kaki-san...
Of course we are.
And we'll do our best to protect you!
Okay, Princess? So cheer up.
They say life is full of storm clouds and clear skies.
Yes, they do! Through your tears you'll see a rainbow!
You boys. Where do you think
you're putting your hands?
You speak soothingly to me, yet your real
intention is to see my naked body.
Oh, not something so indecent!
H-He's right! We subordinates are
not worthy of such splendor.
But you do want to see it, don't you?
Yes!
Well, you leave me with no choice.
Just a little bit.
Dinner time!
Me too!
I'm gonna suck on your delicious...
The Princess... is asleep.
Now's our chance!
Princess, sorry about this!
Ta-da!
There's a magic crest on her loincloth!
I can't open my eyes.
I can't do this. She's untouchable!
Princess Kurenai is in this
lodging, disguised as a man.
With her are two men.
We're going in.
What's this?
An enemy?
Where is he?
Over there!
It's a man!
You bastard, who are you!?
I won't allow you vile brutes to lay one finger
on the precious Princess Kurenai.
We won't go easy on you!
Did we kill him?
Not sure.
It's one of ours!
Shit, we killed the wrong man?
Shit! We're dealing with another ninja.
You bitch. Who are...
You failed?
Yes, and it's unforgivable, Master.
But someone interfered.
"Someone," you say?
What is this person's identity?
The mysterious ninja was carrying a sword.
And even though he was dressed as a man,
the face was unmistakably like Princess Kurenai.
What? Princess Kurenai?
I highly doubt that Princess Kurenai has
the skills to defeat a squad of ninjas.
I'm not even certain if we should
inform the Lord about this.
Chilled Tofu
Hello, kiddies, we meet again. Chilled Tofu speaking.
Tokugawa Tsunaya
The ugly man pictured here is the
"Lord" Fujii was speaking of.
He's Tokugawa Tsunaya, the
antagonist of this part of the story.
Even though he's not the rightful child of this man,
Tokugawa Kokoku
he still receives financial aid as needed.
Princess Mito Kurenai
But he does have a real daughter, Kurenai,
and if he trains her in his ways,
she'll prove to be a valuable heir to him!
That's why Tsunaya decided it would be a
good idea if Kurenai died on her quest.
Accordingly, he ordered Fujii
Mondayu to assassinate her.
Fujii Mondayu hired the mysterious ninja
squad that tried to assassinate Kurenai.
And the beautiful fighter who foiled the plot?
Well then, well then. This thrilling period drama
will lead you from mystery to mystery!
I must bid you all farewell for now!
Don't wait up for me!
We now continue with our story.
But Gokaro-sama...
Rest easy.
We've already set the next plan into motion.
If brute strength won't work,
then we'll enlist the help of the
women who use black magic.
They're already here.
Black magic, you say? Where are they?
Right before you, Gokaro.
What?
Wh-Who are you?
Gokaro-sama, pleased to make your acquaintance.
I am Hotaru of the Tsukuba ninja.
I am Tsubaki.
And I am Sakura.
Mamushi, who are these women?
Women of the Tsukuba clan: Hotaru, Tsubaki, Sakura.
But what kind of magic do these women use?
Wh-What's happening?
Ninpo Tsudzu-botaru.
If cast on a man, this spell gives the user
the ability to suck his manhood dry.
Ninpo Mandala-tsubaki.
This giant flower envelops my victim
and takes him to a world of illusion.
Ninpo Chichi-dakura.
The sweet fragrance of breasts from the wall of
cherry blossoms distracts the man's senses.
But these spells are intended for men.
Will they be effective against Princess Kurenai?
Don't worry.
These witches are still women.
They know a woman's body even
better than they know a man's,
and what women do best is
bend someone to their will.
Gokaro-sama, what do you think?
Oh yes, very nice.
I leave everything to these women.
Do me proud, ladies!
Book: How to Walk to Edo
Sir, we'll be in Edo soon.
Yes, yes. Edo is a very lively and nice place.
The sake is yummy, and the girls are pretty!
What?
That was a woman's scream!
It came from over there!
How dare ya try to run from us!
I think we'd better teach ya a little lesson.
– No! Don't!
– Hey, Bro...
You sure it's a good idea to spoil
the goods before we sell 'em?
W-W-Well, we've gotta test 'em, right?
I mean, with a little use, she'll be even better.
Guess you're right.
I guess it's good for us to try her out first.
That's right. Oh, very nice.
Not so fast, not so fast!
Who's there!?
You evil brutes, forcing such lewd
acts upon a defenseless lady!
Samurai of justice, Mitonosuke
the Crimson has arrived!
I'm with him! Sasaki Sukisaburo!
And I'm Atsumi Kakinoshin.
Suki-san, Kaki-san, restrain those brutes at once.
Yes, sir!
They're coming for us!
I don't give a shit, get 'em!
Suki-san! Kaki-san!
So, pretty boy, wanna be next?
We'll take good care of you!
Fall back, fall back, fall back!
Have you no idea who this person is?
Behold the royal crest of Koumon!
The true mark of his beloved princess!
You are face to face with Princess Mito Kurenai!
Can your vision not comprehend
this crested loincloth?
Oh, dear!
A thousand apologies!
Please have mercy on us!
Oh, did it work?
Operation successful!
Suki-san, Kaki-san, get me down from here!
It's embarrassing.
Hey, Bro, could that be...
Yeah, definitely a woman,
and what's more, Princess Mito.
I thought that face was too pretty to be a man.
Okay, everything's changed if she's a woman.
We'll take her for ourselves!
Yeah. A royal princess would fetch a very high price.
It didn't work!
We're in trouble!
Catch the Princess!
Yeah!
No! Get away, get away!
Bro!
Did ya learn your lesson, tough guys?
The power of the Mito royal family's
swordsmanship is frightening.
Did you get a good look at it?
Is that what happened?
You bitch!
This ain't over.
No, it ain't!
Princess, that was awesome!
So she thinks she can slash with
her sword from a distance.
Little did she know I was throwing
daggers the whole time.
However, you looked really brave, Princess Kurenai.
Thank you for saving me. I was almost a goner.
My name is Shino. Thank you
from the bottom of my heart.
What? You were being sold to pay off a debt?
So they were on the way to
Yoshiwara to sell you, I suppose.
That's right. I managed to escape at first,
but then those men captured me.
I almost gave up hope.
Those men are Inoji and Noroji, and
they're gangsters in Yoshiwara.
Oni-goro is their boss.
They lure young women in need of money,
or suffering under mountains of debt,
and carry them off to Yoshiwara.
Unscrupulous business like that
flourishes under this corrupt Shogunate.
As a member of the royal family, I cannot overlook it!
Suki-san, Kaki-san, we're going to
infiltrate this Yoshiwara place.
Yay!
By the way, Princess, do you know
what kind of place Yoshiwara is?
N-Not really, no.
Aw, well, that's too bad.
Kaki-san, let's accompany our inexperienced and
naive Princess to Yoshiwara, to protect her.
Yes, good idea, Suki-san.
Let's accompany the Princess and invade Yoshiwara!
Well, it's decided. So let's make haste!
Yes! Let's go!
Fools! You mean to say the
girl you captured escaped?
It is inexcusable, Oni-goro boss.
But we were ambushed by that Mito princess,
and she was a really strong fighter.
You fools!
I don't have time to listen to your pathetic excuses!
Then just capture the Princess!
She'll sell for a good price!
If you wish to capture this princess,
why not enlist our help?
What the hell are you bitches doing here?
Do you have any idea where you are?
You're in the room of the esteemed
Oni-goro, the boss of Yoshiwara!
That doesn't matter to us.
We also have business with that princess.
What?
If you do as we say, we'll take
care of everything for you.
You're no match for Princess Kurenai.
That's why you must enlist our services.
She's right.
And in exchange, we'll do your bidding.
Just do exactly as we say until then.
What should we do?
The Princess and her companions
will arrive in Yoshiwara soon.
Wait until then.
Will she really come?
Another from our group has seen to this.
There's another woman on your team?
Just don't think of anything else,
and do exactly as we say.
We'll do anything you say...
Yoshiwara
So this is Yoshiwara.
Correct.
This entire district is Yoshiwara.
I wonder where the aforementioned Oni-goro is...
Book: Nice Spots in Edo
Let's see.
There are about two hundred
buildings here in Yoshiwara.
I guess our only option is to go
through them one by one!
Yes, yes.
We'll search all of them.
But, two hundred places?
Excuse me, Samurai...
Ah! You're that guy from...
Hello.
Mr. Samurai, you're here for some fun today?
Shino-san told us everything.
Where is this Oni-goro? Tell us!
Now, now, there's no reason to fuss.
We're really sorry about what happened earlier today.
We'll help you out from now on.
That's right! To apologize, why don't we
take you to a nice place for free?
It's a very special place.
Come, come, this way.
Um, but I don't really...
Come, come, your comrades as well. Hurry! Hurry!
All right!
Censored
Fight!
Come come, this way.
Watch your step!
Yoshiwara is that kind of place?
Well...
Yes, it is.
Mr. samurai, his is your room.
Your comrades may go to this room.
Well, Princess, um, young lad, we'll see you later.
We're off to another room.
Just enjoy yourself. Take all the time you want.
Excuse me.
My name is Sakura Dayu.
Nice to meet you.
Whee! You're cute!
Let's get to it!
Dinner time!
You have such pretty skin.
It's white and smooth, like silk.
God, how I love the Edo period!
Someone like me gets to have
sex with someone like you!
I'm coming in!
Um, wait a minute!
On the way back, could you buy me a sash?
A Dayu sash?
That's right.
I want you to buy me a sash.
If you do, I'll do this for you!
Please?
Okay, I will!
I won't cut any corners. I'll buy
you a brand new Dayu sash!
I understand! I'll buy it!
That pleases me!
I'm in heaven, I'm in heaven!
Oh my, you already came?
You sure are fast, sir.
Don't worry. I can still go on.
Then do this part next.
I'll let you do anything to me.
That tickles!
What?
Are you saying I don't understand
the proper technique?
Then how 'bout this?
How's this?
See? How about this?
I'll make sure you never forget me.
Jeez. You're so bad at this!
I can't feel anything!
If you want to please a woman, you have to do this.
This is great!
Ninpo Kaijime!
Clunk.
Book: The 48 Positions of Sex
So I take her legs like this?
A mere woman will turn to mush in the
arms of the great Sasaki Sukisaburo!
Hey, woman! Come in anytime!
I'm coming in, man.
Sorry I'm late. I'm Tsubaki Dayu.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, welcome!
Why are you being so stiff?
Only one part of you needs to be stiff.
Fine. Let's start right away.
Come. Hurry up and lick it.
Hurry up already!
Uh, okay!
Th-Thats right.
You're much better than I expected.
I see.
I was a little scared at first, but she's weak after all.
Next, we'll use this.
Wh-What are you...
Come on, come on, come on!
Call me your queen!
Oh? How's this?
This feels really good, doesn't it?
No way does this feel good!
I'm not into this kind of thing!
Oh, really?
Then how about I punish you with this instead?
Wh-What are you doing!?
It'll feel good really soon.
Cut it out.
You made me go to such lengths for you!
You lucky bastard!
I'll send you to heaven!
That's strange. I don't see this anywhere in the book,
but it feels amazing!
Oh dear, you're so hard up here.
Aren't you ashamed?
N-N-No, I'm not, Tsubaki Dayu!
Call me Queen.
Queen...
I can't hold back anymore.
Please let me put it in.
"My Queen, I beg of you,
please let me put my **** in your ****."
Say that, please.
Okay.
My Queen, I beg of you, please
let me put my **** in your ****.
Good boy.
Ninpo Nure-tsubaki!
Yoshiwara sure has improved a lot
since the last time I was here.
I'm in heaven.
Young man, I'm coming in.
I am Hotaru Dayu.
May we share a dream together tonight.
But I didn't know that Yoshiwara was this sort of...
Young man, is this your first time in Yoshiwara?
Oh my, young man!
Your breasts are even more beautiful than mine.
Um, I'm...
Don't fret, dear.
No matter your position in life,
the bedroom here is in a different world.
Whether our customer is a noble
samurai or a dirty peasant,
showing him a wonderful dream
for the night is our job.
All you need to do is remain calm
and quiet and do exactly as I say.
No! Not down there.
No one's ever touched me down there.
But you've at least touched yourself, right?
I'll give you pleasure that's ten times better.
I can lead you down the path of ecstasy.
Young one, suck on mine next.
Oh, yes, you're very good.
Now this as well.
Oh, young one!
Yes! Yes!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Tsubaki. Sakura.
How are the other two?
Just as planned.
They're boring. Their technique sucks.
Sakura, that's not it.
Hotaru nee-chan meant something different.
Oops! I meant, "They're fast asleep"!
Good.
Then it's time.
Hotaru Dayu-sama?
Kurenai, um, I mean, young man!
Oh my, Hotaru Dayu-sama,
why are you dressed like that?
And why are there three of you?
Well, this isn't...
Never mind.
It's time for me to pleasure you now.
Let's go!
Um, wait!
Now! Take off these things!
You even changed your hairstyle.
But you're beautiful no matter what.
Well? Does this feel good?
I'll return all the pleasure you gave to me.
I'll return it tenfold, no, ten-thousandfold!
Lucky girl. That looks like fun!
It's starting to make me wet!
Why don't you two join us instead
of lingering in the doorway?
Yes! Yes!
Sakura, your duty...
Oh, well, whatever.
Yes!
This feels great!
I've never felt this good before!
Kaki-san, good morning.
Hey, Suki-san.
Did ya have fun last night?
Yeah. And you, Kaki-san?
That reminds me. Our companion...
I wonder how her night was.
Let's go!
Young man...
It's morning.
Princess Kurenai... Harder...
"Princess Kurenai?"
"Harder?"
That was a good sleep.
Oh, Suki-san, Kaki-san. Good morning.
Princess...
Good morning!
Princess, it seems as though you
enjoyed yourself a lot last night.
You must be more technically skilled than you look.
What are you talking about?
That reminds me. Suki-san! Kaki-san!
You both knew Yoshiwara was like this, didn't you!?
Um, we sort of heard rumors.
Just tell me the truth, you perverts!
Oh, never mind!
Princess!
You girls sure are lazy.
Come on. Wake up.
More, please...
Stop sleep-talking!
A-Azusa!
Azusa-chan!
Azusa nee-chan?
I didn't receive any reports by morning,
so I came here to investigate and found this.
What's going on?
But it felt so good!
That's not the answer she's looking for.
Still, it seems that Princess Kurenai
is no ordinary princess.
Her swordsmanship and sexual skills are first-rate.
She's a double threat!
You just stay quiet!
Never mind.
You girls always seem to have a hole in your plan.
And I went through all that trouble pretending to
escape from Yoshiwara to lure the Princess here.
Let me make the plan this time.
But Azusa-chan...
Don't call me "Azusa"!
I'm "Shino" here.
I'm the tragic heroine, trying to adjust to brothel life.
Shino, the peasant.
Princess!
Princess, please cheer up already!
I'm not speaking to you!
Perverts.
Shino-san?
What are you doing here?
I was worried because you hadn't returned yet.
However, it's dangerous for you to come here alone.
He's right!
Yes, but more importantly, I've discovered
where the kidnapped girls are being kept.
Really?
Okay, Suki-san, Kaki-san, we're
invading this time for sure!
Okay!
No!
Stop it!
Oh, how I love firm, young girls!
From today on, you girls will work hard for Yoshiwara.
Today I'll teach you what a man tastes like,
so that tomorrow you'll be able
to make us lots of money.
That's right. We'll teach you plenty about
how to make a man feel good.
What do you see, Princess?
I'm not even sure!
So disgusting...
It's probably too hardcore for a princess's eyes.
Let's get down there with our special ninja skills!
Suki-san, Kaki-san!
You peeked on my bath the same way, didn't you!?
Now, now, Princess.
Please be quiet.
They'll hear you downstairs.
Don't change the subject!
You pervert!
Ow, that smarts.
You'd think we'd have learned from last time.
I suppose that's a weakness in our ninja skills.
Suki-san, Kaki-san, you idiots!
Well, well, well. Welcome, Princess of Mito.
I'm Oni-goro, the esteemed manager
and boss of the Yoshiwara district.
And I'm Inoji!
I'm Noroji!
So you're Oni-goro!
How dare you take advantage of defenseless girls!
You'll pay dearly for this!
Oh? And how exactly will I "pay" for it?
With your blood!
You and your disgusting followers will be slashed to
ribbons with the special Mito ninja sword technique!
Boss, we're in trouble!
Her sword is no ordinary sword.
Just watch the dazzling dance of the sword of Mito!
Don't move.
Shino-san, but you...
Princess!
Shino-san, are you...
That's right. Shino is just an alter ego.
My real name is Azusa.
Yes. Everything was an act to
capture you, Princess Kurenai.
But you were...
Wh-What do you mean?
Anyway! There's an important man to whom
your continued existence is a problem.
It pains me to do this, but you must die.
No! Don't do it! Don't do it!
Wait! Don't do it yet!
It would be a waste to kill
something as high-quality as this!
What's more, with her Mito name,
she'll really pull in customers!
So please, let me take care of her.
We can just keep her shut up in here for
the rest of her life instead of killing her.
No way.
It's not like we want to kill this cute little princess,
but it's our duty.
Then at least let me do her once.
There's a beautiful young princess in my
room with breasts like hard-boiled eggs.
When will I get an opportunity like this again?
Hey, no fair!
Me too!
Yuck!
Oh well, fine.
Just once.
Lucky. I wanna join in.
Hey! You chauvinistic brutes!
He's right! The Princess doesn't like it!
She's really nice.
Hey, Princess, your crest has gotten soaked.
Let's get those wet clothes off of you.
No! No, don't look!
Oh my, look!
Don't say that.
She sure is a princess.
What a lovely color she has down here.
Her boobs aren't bad either.
Now I'm really horny!
You're always really horny.
Princess, you've come a long way.
Let me see about coming inside of you, okay?
I suppose you taste just as good on
the inside as you do on the outside.
No! Stop it!
Princess!
Here I go...
Wh-What?
What was that?
The Princess is gone!
What?
Where'd she go?
I didn't even get to fuck her once!
Princess.
Princess!
Suki-san, Kaki-san, here we go!
Yes!
Hey, hey, you, listen up!
The wrath of Mito Koumon shall fall upon you,
for forcing such brutality on his
precious Princess Kurenai!
Representatives of Mito Koumon
Recognize her in her changed
form and fear her power!
You perverted beasts,
luring poor, innocent women into your brothel
and forcing indecent acts upon them!
In the name of God, I, Princess Mito Kurenai,
will exact vengeance upon you!
What should we do, Boss?
I said we were in trouble.
I don't care! Just get them!
Let's go!
Without physically touching its opponent,
my blade slashes through from afar.
Do you respect and fear the sword of Mito now?
That sounded cool, huh!
You idiot.
You're having too much fun.
You will not escape!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, dear! Suki-san, Kaki-san, I'm sorry!
Princess Kurenai!
We won't hold back now.
You will fight us!
Ninpo Mugen-botaru!
An illusion spell...
I won't...
Ninpo Mandala-tsubaki.
Welcome to a world of illusion.
Ninpo Chichi-dakura.
Princess, how do my breasts smell?
Ninpo Inkamayu.
Princess, you won't escape from us now.
I have yet to know your body, but it's
even more beautiful than I imagined.
Does this feel good, Princess?
I'm sure it does feel good for her.
Drown in ecstasy.
Because when you release your
pent-up lust, you will die.
What the hell are you doing?
Never mind, never mind.
We can't just sit back and watch
with this hot scene in front of us!
Hey! Would you stop that?
Stop it, you brutes!
This isn't just a sex act!
This is our unique ninja skill!
Hey! You guys gotta let me join in!
I said, stop it!
Princess...
I love ya!
I'm so happy to be with you!
They really are unreliable comrades,
and you're a very accident-prone princess.
It's getting tougher and tougher to step in for you.
Do you appreciate that?
But you really are cute.
Still, you would be, of course!
We have the same face, after all!
Goroko.
It's a letter from Mitsuko.
I see. So that sort of thing has
been happening in Edo.
I wonder if Princess Kurenai
will be all right from now on.
Jubei Mitsuyoshi-dono.
You need not worry, sir.
My granddaughter Mitsuko is descended
from a line of Yagyu protectors.
Here is the mysterious, beautiful swordswoman,
who's been protecting Princess Kurenai
from the shadows the whole time!
Her name is Yagyu Jubei Mitsuko!
She's third in the Yagyu ninja succession line,
and she has the same mother as the Princess!
What's more, she has the same face as well!
She was charged with guarding
Princess Kurenai on her quest.
At the same time, she was also told to seek
out and expose wrongdoing in the country!
Harder!
Not yet. Don't cum yet!
I wanna stop...
You have no right to complain!
Because of you, our target escaped.
Princess Kurenai escaped!
She's right,
and you need to pay for your crimes with your bodies.
But it's no use. I've aged a hundred
years from this constant fucking.
Silence!
Even if it takes three or four days, you're
going to keep it up until we're satisfied!
That's enough.
Just kill me already!
Well, Princess, your actions during
this quest were very heroic.
He's right.
Your swordsmanship must be the best in Japan!
And your woman-killing techniques, too.
What are you talking about?
Book: Diary of Our Manyuuki Travels
Now, now, we're praising you.
I'd like you to teach me that technique, too.
I don't understand what you're talking about.
You're weird.
Japan has clear skies today!
This has been an account of Princess Kurenai's
travels through Yoshiwara with her hopeless duo,
but her quest has only just begun.
Three Days Later
Damn you, Princess Kurenai!
Next time, we'll get you for sure!
The End
Mercy!