Are you ready now?
Yeah. I suppose.
Here.
Ohashi-kun, I'm sorry. You came
to visit me and I'm really busy.
It's okay.
I like watching you work, anyway.
I'll be able to take a break in a little bit.
S-So wait for me, okay?
Sony for-
Dammit What's your problem!?
I-I'm really sorry!
Hey, what are you gonna do about this?
This stain ain't gonna come out easily.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
We were planning on going on a date.
Now we're in a fix.
Um, I'll get you a change of clothes at once!
Change of clothes, eh?
In that case, give me your clothes.
It's not fair that I'm the only
one who's gotta look like this.
You're gonna have to be embarrassed, too.
B-But, I cant...
H-Hey, wait a minute!
This is just too weird, you guys!
Ohashi-kun...
Oh? He your boyfriend?
He's annoying.
Accelerando
~ Whisper of the Fallen Angels ~
Sorry about this, but I need
ya to stay still for just a bit.
P-Please, don't do anything mean!
It's in your hands, girl.
If you do what we say, we wont hurt him.
I-I understand.
In that case, take off your clothes and get naked.
What?
Right here!?
Of course right here.
Come on. Get on with it.
O-Okay.
Tamaki!
Is this all right?
No, it's not
You have to take off-everything.
Even my panties are stained.
Oh no...
Oh? Were you lying when you said you'd do what we said?
No... I'll take them off.
Come on. That part too.
Look this way.
Don't hide yourself.
O-Okay.
I took off... everything...
Please... Will you leave me alone, now?
You're shivering.
How cute.
No... Don't! Please stop!
When you took off your clothes,
you knew this would happen, didn't you?
Be a good girl, now.
Looks like if s show time.
No...
S-Stop it!
D-Don't... No...
Well? How do you feel having your pussy all
squishy and wet in front of your boyfriend?
Oh no... Ohashi-kun, don't store at
me like that... It's embarrassing...
No, don't squeeze my boobs so hard...
Don't squeeze them...
I wonder... Does it turn you on
being watched like this?
No way. I'm not... turned on...
It's just because... you're touching me so much.
No!
Squishing around inside of me... No... Not this...
Well, it's really turning me on, being with the two of you.
Let's make things even better.
Wh-What are you doing!?
Haven't you ever done this with another woman?
N-No!
Don't lick me!
I'm losing my mind!
Come on. Lick me, too.
Okay...
Oh no.
No... Why am I doing this while Ohashi-kun is watching?
Why am I licking another woman's pussy?
This is... so embarrassing!
Why is... my body getting... hotter?
From my pussy... this perverted juice keeps... flowing!
And it won't stop!
See? You're about to cum, aren't you?
D-Don't! Don't!
I'm cumming!
D-Don't... be so rough... I'll...
I'll c-c-cum...
It's okay. Go ahead and cum.
No!!
Tamaki!
Amazing.
You came pretty hard, there.
Am I... done now?
Good question.
I guess I can let you off the hook,
but it doesn't look like he's satisfied.
Ohashi-kun?
This time, you're going to have to satisfy him.
Accelerando.
Hinoto
We're allowed to do more than kiss, now.
Hey, you two! Time for breakfast!
I'm really sorry, Kanue-chan.
I hope my son isn't giving you a hard time.
Don't be silly. I'm just happy to have a family again.
And I like my new, cute little brother.
And I'm really happy to have a
pretty girl like you for a daughter.
Oh, Mom, thank you.
Ka-Kanue-san?
If we don't hurry and eat we'll be late.
Call her "Onee-san," Hinoto.
Oh, it's okay.
I actually prefer being called by my name.
Ka-Kanue-san?
It's still goopy.
Didn't you change your underwear?
Yesterday, I got a call from Kimiha-chan.
I told her you wouldn't make it today.
That's mean! How could you?
Hinoto-kun, you're good at this!
Aren't you going home?
Hinoto. You wanna go home?
Yeah.
Because were now step-brother and sister,
we're not allowed to cross this line.
I wonder why that is?
Ka-Kanue-san.
If that's the case,
will you betray Kimiha-chan?
Will you cross that line?
S-Stop that.
But your dick is really hard.
Is it all right for me to go down on you?
Is fellatio permitted?
Can this line be crossed?
What about cumming in my mouth?
Is that allowed?
Very well.
You still haven't cum enough, have you?
Will rubbing against my clitoris be forgiven?
I don't think it's any different from putting it inside of me.
Ka-Kanue-san...
So, you're going to put it in, after all.
Do you understand what that means?
I called Kimiha-chan here.
Shell show up any second, now.
N-No way!
If you choose me, then just keep going like this.
That's not fair...
Nee-san!
It's in me!
No!
Your penis... It's so thick!
Hinoto-kun, are you about to cum?
I-It's okay.
Inside of me...
Shoot all of your sperm inside of me!
So much...
A-Amazing!
Hinoto-kun, you're...
You're still so hard!
It was the first time that
Hinoto called me "Nee-san".
At that moment,
we were no longer just "male and female".
Accelerando.
Right here? Really?
Of course.
Since you ruined our date, you'd
better give us some entertainment.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault you got caught up in this.
Don't worry. Besides, I'm already hard.
I'm glad. Then, let me make you feel good.
I wonder if they remember we're here?
Ta-Tamaki...
This time, I'll do you with my boobs.
Well?
Does it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
Really good.
I'm so glad!
Ohashi-kun, you're so hard.
They're closer and closer.
Her nipples cant stand it anymore.
My nipples... they're so hard.
They're itching!
How sweet..
Tamaki...
I-I'm...
It's okay.
You don't need to hold back.
Cum all over me!
Sorry, Tamaki.
Wow.
So much came out, but you're still so hard.
Ohashi-kun, I'm putting it in.
Tamaki!
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'll move for you.
What is this? I-It's amazing!
It's, so intense this time!
I guess she gets turned on by being watched, huh?
Don't say that!
I'm not... turned on by that...
What amazing intensity.
There's so many perverted things showing.
I can totally see her asshole, too.
D-Don't! Please...
D-Don't look at me close-up like that!
Tamaki.
I-I'm cumming...
It's okay! Cum inside of me!
Blow it all inside of me!
Again...
Hey, hey. How many times can you guys go at it?
It's fine...
Because,
it feels so good!
I really like it when you're watching us!
I'm gonna cum...
No!
I'm cumming!
I wonder if those kids are still going at it?
Who knows.
We've seen them so many times,
but they didn't notice it was us at all.
It's kinda funny.
Well...
What?
Why did you trick them again?
Good question.
Because I thought these clothes were cute
and always wanted to wear them, maybe?