I'm in a waking dream.
In this dream...
I sometimes realize it's actually a dream.
For example, when I'm spacing put,
it's like my feet are not on the ground.
It feels like... I'm not really here,
but somewhere else.
Moreover, my lust spills forth shamelessly.
In this dream...
This is my dream.
In a school reserved for the elite,
there are girls here who satisfy
the lust of all the students,
to prevent students with a bright
future from committing crimes.
Each of them have their reason for being here.
But there is one thing they share.
That is... they have no name.
This prevents students from knowing them later in life.
That's why they are called by number,
so their names remain unknown.
Hey, we're out of time.
I know.
Hey, take care of these guys too.
I shot a load.
Huh, was that the first bell?
One of the gills in this school...
She was... the very first love I ever had.
Even this scene is probably...
just a dream.
If I Call Your Name
Episode 1
Jeez, how gross.
Give it to me, and I'll stay quiet.
Let me have some too.
Say something.
What's wrong? You don't want to talk to me?
Eh, errr...
H-How do you do?
S-Sorry.
I'm fine.
So fine that I can take my time
drinking this delicious coffee.
How about you?
N-Nothing much
What?
Do you think we can tay in the toilet all day?
Err... No... Well...
Your job looks hard...
I got used to it in no time.
Well, the small bits of semen stay in my throat.
And since it's a fluid,
I feel bad having too much of it in my stomach.
That's the only thing I can't get used to.
And everything ends up tasting like semen.
Ah, was that too indecent?
I'm Sorry.
Ah, no.
Oh, it's lunch break.
Well, time for work.
Say...
Yes?
Can we meet here again?
Would I get coffee next time?
Err...
I-I'm Nakagawa.
She didn't remember me.
I see, Nakagawa-kun.
I'm sure you know my name.
I know.
My call sign is...
Your name is...
"Number Three."
After that, I went to the rooftop every day.
She's gushing! Hey, stick it in!
See? We can do both holes, it'll be faster this way.
Those guys...
Nakagawa-kun!?
Hey, listen to me.
They sandwiched me from both sides.
It really wore my hip out.
They have to be more careful.
It could feel good for me too,
if they just came at me one at a time.
S-So, it feels good?
Y-Yeah.
If I'm handled with care.
If I'm treated well, then... yeah.
I-I see.
You've never asked for me before.
What's wrong with you?
Damn it! Stop! Let go of me!
Aren't you Nakagawa from class B?
Who the hell is that?
Listen. It's not your place to tell us how to use her.
Don't act like you're calling the shots.
Aren't you having a strange dream?
To begin with, she's doing this because she wants to.
Hey, try begging for it.
Just beg for it.
Please.
Stick it in me, please.
Sure, I'll stick it in.
It's great! Your penis is great!
See, she likes it. She's here of her own will.
This is great.
My pussy...
You want sperm, right?
You want to drink it until you are full, right?
Please, give it to me.
Give me, please... give me more sperm.
Look at that! She's moving her hips.
This is what you call "reality."
Get ready, I'm going to shoot.
Deep inside.
Faster, faster. Shoot all your sperm inside me.
Ah, it's filling my pussy.
More, more...
More, give me more sperm!
Your penis... so good...
It feels good, both my pussy and my ass.
More, give me more.
Your penis is great.
More, more sperm please.
So deep, it's hitting me so deep.
Cum, cum all over me.
Semen, please.
You're so silly.
I had it harder when I was in training.
I'm fine with something of that level.
Well, err...
T-Thank you.
O-Oh yeah, I should do you a favor in return.
I don't have anything though.
In that case,
I want to call you by your real name.
H-How can I? That's just...
Why are you making that face?
Let's do it this way.
I'll give you three guesses.
Try guessing my name,
and if you're right, I will respond.
No hints, okay?
Go ahead.
Mitsuko... -chan.
Yes.
My father's factory went bankrupt as
soon as I finished middle school.
We lost our citizenship after that.
That's why, the only place left for me is here.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
W-Well...
Hey, don't get me wrong.
I'm totally fine with double penetration.
The food here is tasty,
the workplace is clean, and I like school too.
Well, if there was anything I wanted...
It's would be nice wearing the school
uniform once in a while.
I see.
With a uniform, you can play with your skirt.
I-It's my sister's. Her name is Mitsuko too.
Don't do something like that!
I-It's a real problem!
Jeez, you're making that face again.
I'm going to change. Don't peek.
H-How is it?
So cute.
W-Wait a minute!
What do you think?
Does it look strange?
Try turning around.
Like this?
Hey, did you peek just now?
You pervert.
It suits you, Mitsuko-chan.
I go to the rooftop at the same time every day.
Mitsuko is always waiting for me...
wearing that uniform.
It was the first time I had a good time at this school
It seems like a ream.
Nakagawa-kun.
Yes, sir.
Do you have a minute?
Yeah.
You're late.
Huh?
Who the hell gave her a school uniform?
No, no, no...
No, no! Let me go!
No, no, no!
No, no!
She's not quite wet enough.
She usually gushes out so much that it's unsightly.
She's running away, she's running away!
Don't try to get away.
You must really hate us...
You came already?
It's like a real rape.
The look on her face was just golden.
It's been a long time since I came so much using her.
That was good.
Even though she's just wearing a uniform...
Hey look, she's crying.
What's this?
Resist like you did just now.
What? You turned back to your usual self?
I liked how she resisted back there too.
What's this? A name tag?
There's a name written on it.
Mitsuko?
No.
Don't call my name.
Stop it.
Mitsuko.
Mitsuko-chan.
No, No!
No, don't.
Mitsu... ko.
No, don't call my name.
Hey, it looks like she really despises it.
Yeah, this really turns me on.
Let me do her too.
W-Wait a minute! I'm going to cum, Mitsuko-chan.
Inside, inside your pussy.
No!
No, no more.
Mitsuko-chan, I'm next.
No, no! Let me go!
Hey, take care of this too, Mitsuko-chan.
Hey, let's cum all over her uniform.
No no, please stop!
Stop!!!
Hey, switch with me.
You're still good to go?
Yeah, I'm really excited right now.
Come on, Mitsuko-chan.
Stop it.
Damn, held up by that useless junk.
Is Mitsuko-chan still waiting?
She cries when you call her Mitsuko.
What's that? Is it true?
Yeah, the uniform is a real turn on.
Seriously? A cosplay?
It looks just like real resistance.
Heh, it's that good?
Yeah, she resists when you call her name.
It's almost like a real rape.
No, don't call my name!
I just wanted to give her a dream.
But, that time, I...
...had an erection while sympathizing,
seeing her tears.
Don't call my name.