What I'm concerned about is what
these people behind this screen want...
No!
Stop it!
Standby
Shutdown
Restart
This story will never end until
I get down with this person...
Shusaku
Reason and Fetishism
Yes!
Good morning, Takabe.
Minazuki, Kondo, good morning.
You two are always together.
Would you like to go to school with us?
Of course...
...but why?
Actually, we always wanted to talk to you.
Takabe?
Maejima...
I'm sorry to interrupt you, but could
I have a word with you, Takabe?
Of course...
Let's go then, Nagisa...
Yes, let's go...
Excuse us...
See you later then.
You can't be too careful around them!
Takabe, would you mind washing these for me?
Sure.
You're so obedient, and cute too...
Your breasts must be the same size as mine.
I have some extra bras that I can give to you.
Well, um...
A-ha! I just captured the moment of truth!
Fujima...
Listen you two, if you don't do what I say...
...I'll spread this video clip all over the school!
Oh no...
Nah, I'm just kidding!
Watching you two made me want to tease you.
I don't care, do whatever you want.
Maejima...
I can't believe I'm hearing
such a comment from an...
...honor student of the famous
Shukusei Music Institute!
I don't care about rumors, as long
as they're about you and me...
Hey!
You'll be late for class!
Wow, Asami, you're good at flipping skirts!
I saw Eri's white panties!
That's because I've practiced flipping your skirts.
Please cut it out, you two.
Why are you so upset?
I don't like being teased.
We're not teasing you.
We're serious about taking your virginity, Eri.
My virginity?
Hey Eri, you're the only one
who's still a virgin in this dorm.
Why don't you leave it to us?
Girls.
What are you still doing here?
Hurry up and go to school.
Shoot!
Come on, let's go Chiaki!
Okay.
See you later, Eri.
Ms. Takabe!
I need to speak with you in private.
Ms. Minami?
I don't understand.
Why do you have to tie me in
such a place to check my uniform?
Because you tried to run from me.
No, I didn't.
Besides, I don't think I broke any school rules!
Ms. Takabe, are you trying to resist me?
No, I didn't mean to...
For that, I'll check your underwear, too.
No, please don't look!
What's wrong, Ms. Takabe?
We both are girls...
You have no reason to be embarrassed.
Oh no...
You'll get used to this soon...
...soon enough you'll wet your
pretty white underwear...
Is this really a uniform check?
Sure.
Your parents asked us to take good
care of their precious daughter.
By doing this, I'm going to find
out if you've been a good girl.
You're lying!
You are just playing with my body!
Oh, you knew.
Now I don't have to pretend anymore.
How do you feel being touched by a woman?
Why are you doing this to me?
I want to know how much a good,
smart girl like you can take...
No!
Please, stop this...
Ouch...
What a great view!
Why do you close your eyes?
You should look like this all the time.
I never liked your stuck-up attitude.
You're thinking that I'm nothing but
a foolish, horny teacher, aren't you?
No, that's not true.
Then why don't you open your heart to me?
Why don't you ask me to make love with you?
You are a woman too...
Show me how wet you can get!
No...
Even if you do this to me,
things can't be the way you want!
Why do you try to control
yourself and live in a boring life?
Is it really fun living like that?
No, that's not true.
I just respect you, Ms. Minami...
I don't want to hear bullshit!
As I thought, you are a virgin, aren't you?
I'll train you to be a mature and obedient woman.
What are you doing?
Does this feel tingly?
You must be excited, not being able to escape...
Women get aroused when
their freedom is taken away.
I don't get aroused by such things.
You are so stubborn...
I remember that I said the same thing
to him as I disobeyed his orders.
Him?
The person who taught us
what our real sexual desires are...
Who is he?
You want to know?
Then you have to accept him.
He will show up when you're ready to accept him..
Please stop this!
I need to make sure you can handle his dick...
And you have to please him.
Do you feel like accepting him now?
It looks like he's here.
This is my room...
But I'm sure that I was in the storage room...
Are you sleeping, Takabe?
I'm up!
My family sent me this tea, I hope you like it.
Thank you.
So, what brought you here?
I heard Ms. Minami had scolded at you.
Everybody in the dorm is talking about you.
I heard that you were punished in the storage room...
Are you the ones who rescued me?
No, I heard that you managed to escape by yourself...
By myself?
That's right.
That's strange, I don't remember...
Somebody must've helped me out...
Well...
I want you to tell us...
About what?
About the punishment.
No.
I don't want to talk about it.
Oh, it must have been so terrible!
So, did it involve one of these things?
Why do you have such a thing in your room?
You know, we might encounter
a similar situation in the future...
So, it might be good for us to be ready for it.
Excuse me, but I'd better go back to my room.
Takabe, what's wrong?
I just got dizzy all of a sudden...
What is this?
Kondo, Minazuki...
What's gotten into you?
We're sorry for doing this to you...
Takabe, please accept this!
Otherwise, I-I...
It makes me feel...
I get so excited when I see
beautiful girls relieve themselves.
I want to see you go...
...a big one...
Nagisa...
Takabe, I can't let you be embarrassed alone...
I'll do it too!
Kondo...
Nagisa...
When I hear dirty words, I get insanely horny...
I can't control myself!
Just watching you is making me feel strange...
Takabe, don't make Nagisa do it by herself.
I want you to be naughty, too!
Please stop! Minazuki!
Please be quiet.
Your anus is so lovely...
No...
Please, don't look at it!
Takabe, don't worry,
I'll save your virginity for him.
Who is this man you're talking about?
You'll find out soon.
Your lovely anus...
Your anus soon is going to be...
It might hurt a bit, but please bear it.
Please stop it!
Please!
No!
Okay, I'll put it in...
Good, it went smoothly...
Please, let me go...
It's just begun.
What are you..
You'll feel an urge to relieve yourself soon.
I'll make you feel more comfortable...
I'll make it easier for you.
Don't touch there, it's dirty!
I used to think like that before...
But "loving somebody means accepting
everything about that person"...
...that's what he taught me.
Who is he?
Oh no, it's going to come out...
Just hold it for a little longer.
Let's have fun.
What are you doing?
Are you in pain?
You must endure it.
Soon the pain turns into pleasure...
I know you want to relieve yourself...
Hold it in a little longer...
Do you feel good?
Please stop it!
It's strange...
Nothing's happening...
Did you put it in enough?
Yes, it should be enough.
Maybe Takabe is more patient than we thought...
Oh my god, I can't hold it anymore...
No!
She did it!
Wow!
That's a lot!
Thank you for helping me...
It's okay, I thought this
would happen to you someday...
Maejima...
By the way, Takabe, why didn't
you come to my room?
I told you that I would give you my bras...
Thank you for helping me.
I can walk on my own now.
Takabe!
My stomach hurts...
There's something wrong with the people here...
I have to find out what's going on.
I'm sorry!
Is that Chiaki's voice?
What happened?
Um, it's nothing...
She saw me peeing!
That's terrible!
I didn't mean to...
Eri, did you really see her peeing?
No, I was...
Oh my God, she saw me peeing!
Aw, there, there...
How dare you do that?
I-I'm sorry...
Sorry doesn't cut it!
You have to show me your peeing!
My peeing?
Yeah, then I'll forgive you.
Great idea! I want to see that too!
I can't do that...
Come inside now!
Please, stop! What are you doing?
Nagumo!
Please, let me go, Kurihara!
No way!
It doesn't hurt to show us your peeing, right?
You won't feel embarrassed if you take this off!
No...
Why are you doing this to me?
You are nothing but a toy for everyone!
Don't you get it yet?
All girls in this dorm are
already my slaves, except you.
W-Who are you?
You've forgotten about me already?
That's a little cold, don't you think?
It looks like it's warm inside...
And it's clean, too.
No...
I knew it...
Nobody makes you wet like I do, huh?
Even if you try to forget it and run away from me...
...we just can't be apart, baby...
What do you mean?
Have you ever been inside
the superintendent's room?
You'll find the secrets of your future there...
You'll know that you're just a
horny chick craving my dick...
That's the future of a slutty girl...
Don't you dare say such a thing to me!
Ow, that really hurt.
What's gotten into you?
Oh Kenji, you are wild today.
I know this is a bad habit, but it sure
is fun to watch somebody's affair...
Nagisa, since I saw Eri's...
Shiho, you too?
Nagisa, you're already wet down here.
Oh, don't do that...
Do it harder!
Don't pull it out!
Is this hard enough for you?
No!
Not inside! Don't come inside...
Well...
You'll find the secrets of your future
in the superintendent's room...
I remember him...
I remember him!
Do Not Enter
There is a saved file.
Would you like to open it?
Opening the file...
I love you!
You are the only one...
I've been waiting for you for a long time!
What is this?
Oh, please! Please come inside of me!
When was this taped?
How do you like the story?
Eri nude isn't something you can see everyday.
Just sit back and watch what happens next.
You will finally be mine next...
I have my pride as a pervert.
Shusaku Liberty: Reason and Struggle
I'm going to enjoy Eri's virginity!