Damn it! Stop!
Throw him out.
That's right, I should return the favor.
But I don't have anything to give you...
Then...
I want to call you by your real name.
W-What should I do? That's...
Now you're making that face?
Then, let's do this.
I'll give you three chances.
Why don't you guess my name?
If you're right, I'll, answer.
No hints, all right?
Mitsuko-chan.
Y-Yes.
Her facial expression that time...
...was so realistic that I forgot for
a moment that this is all a dream.
There was no pain.
I heard the sound of Mitsuko's moaning.
Just like always.
If I Call Your Name
Episode 2
This swimsuit is stimulating, too.
Say, whose is this?
Yoshino's sister?
You know, he tried to get in the way again.
That Nakagawa.
Ah, did you get him good?
Come to think of it, have you done it yet?
Oh, not yet.
Mitsuko-chan.
Mitsuko-chan, Mitsuko-chan.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
No more, don't call my name.
It's time to close.
Hey, I haven't had my turn yet.
Those who are still on school
grounds, please go home.
Don't get annoyed.
What should we do next?
The next cosplay?
How about waitress costume?
That's a good idea.
I'll go first next time.
I felt it just couldn't go on like this.
I had to destroy it.
Because this lewd dream...
...is my dream, after all.
Dream?
The present?
Y-Yeah, this world might be someone's dream.
Whose dream?
F-For example... mine.
Your dream...
If that's the case, I...
Have you read "Kocho no Yume"?
Nope, since I'm stupid.
If that were to be true...
Then Nakagawa-kun, take control of it,
and lead it to an happy ending.
No...
No!
It hurts!
No! Take it out! Take it out!
No!
My butt isn't wet yet.
It's painful!
It hurts!
The pain!
No, I don't want it!
No more...
No more!
No!
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
No!
I can't anymore!
Stop!!
Please stop...
On that day, I withdrew all my money.
The stun gun and handcuffs weren't
as heavy as I imagined.
On the next day, I went to search for the key.
Staff Room
Excuse me.
This way, Nakagawa.
Ah, yes sir.
I called you here for a reason.
I think you already know why.
Your grades have been going down.
Ah, yes.
If you came to this school as an elite,
you'll have to continue to a
university at the same level,
and make your parents proud...
My father's factory went bankrupt as
soon as I finished middle school.
I never knew.
Because, unlike everyone, I took
the exam for another school.
And we lost citizenship after that.
You see,
I can't remember much...
...about that time.
As you know, I'm pretty dumb.
I didn't understand how agencies really worked.
That girl... Mitsuko...
She's been trying to forget about me,
the same way I've forgotten
about her the past little while.
So, the only place left for me is here.
I had forgotten all about her.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Well... I'm sorry.
Nakagawa.
There's been a big commotion during
the school breaks recently.
Do you know anything about it?
As pathetic as it sounds...
It took me three days before
I was mentally ready to do it.
W-Where's Mitsuko?
Where's Mitsuko?
Where's number 3?
What are you doing at an hour like this?
Let's run way.
Together.
Run away?
Away from this place.
This place?
You mean the school?
Let's go to some town.
I prepared things in advance.
And I have the money.
Let's rent a small room for the two of us.
When things calm down, we'll get a part-time job.
The first home will be a cheap one.
When we saved up enough money, we'll go overseas.
Mitsuko?
Dream all you want, you silly virgin!
This has nothing to do with virginity!
I-I just...
Well then, impotent!
Go masturbate alone, you delusional idiot!
I'm part of this school's furniture.
The interest from my debts is
being paid by the country!
I-I knew that already.
Same thing with my school expenses,
my living expenses...
And my contraception expenses.
I'm getting everything through taxes.
I'm this country's property!
If Nakagawa-kun took me away,
Who is going to take my place?
Your mother?
Your sister?
No, I'll do it properly!
Damn it.
I knew it.
I'm just doing something unreasonable.
I just...
I just want to forget.
That this is all my...
My...
You're making that face again.
Are you really going to help me?
Are you going to make me see a dream too?
Be my lover tonight.
Make love to me.
That was my first kiss.
Lies.
Geez.
This is my dream, you know.
Lick it.
You don't want to lick mine?
Is it dirty?
No, it's not that.
It's because it's so pretty.
Mitsuko's pussy.
My pussy... so good...
Let me do you too.
Mitsuko...
Her juices...
Her voice...
Everything was so sweet.
It was as if everything were real.
Nakagawa-kun.
Say you love me.
Now I'm just lying more...
Mitsuko.
I love you.
Mitsuko was really happy about that.
See? Here, put it in.
Be my very first.
Wait...
Say that you love me more.
I love you, Mitsuko.
Dummy, not that way...
Well, you could put it there too...
Come on, you're such a tease.
It's going... all the way.
Mitsuko?
You made me cum.
And I wanted to play as virgin too.
So hot!
Nakagawa-kun!
More, give me more!
Amazing...
Inside me... so deep... sucked in....
Sorry, I keep cumming alone.
It's so embarrassing...
Nakagawa-kun, Nakagawa-kun!
Please call my name, Mitsuko!
Mitsuko, Mitsuko.
I'm so happy!
It's so good!
Harder!
Mitsuko is so real.
Even if the whole world is a dream.
Yes, more! Harder!
Yes, it feels so good!
Nakagawa-kun, please!
Say that you love Mitsuko.
Please!
I love you, Mitsuko.
Mitsuko!
More, say it more!
Call my name!
Say you love me!
I love you.
Mitsuko, I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you I
More, say it more!
Call my name!
Say you love me!
I love you, Mitsuko!
Mitsuko!!
I'm... I'm so happy.
Yes, it's feels so good.
Yes, it's so good!
Amazing...
So good...
Nakagawa-kun, Nakagawa-kun.
Inside, cum inside me.
I-I can't anymore...
Nakagawa-kun, stay like this for a while.
Hug me tight.
I ejaculated, like it was a dream.
Mitsuko wasn't there when I woke up.
It happened so naturally.
My actions regarding this matter
were never mentioned at all.
It's like there's always one idiot
who does this every year.
There was even a procedure for it.
I was able to get away with just a suspension.
Mitsuko was apparently transfered to another place.
The school went easy on me.
Of course, my parents had to pay for it.
In the end,
I wasn't able to wake up from my dream.
Still... I accidentally say her name from time to time.
During those moments, my body hits me with pain.
But the reality behind that pain...
...will wake me up from my dream one day.
Only then, will I actually see the dream.