vol.1
Find Momoko!
I have the same initials as Marilyn Monroe: M.M.
I'm Morita Momoko, age 22.
I'm an actress in training.
I've been to countless auditions so far,
but I haven't gotten a break yet.
So that's who I am.
I'm Momoko.
I'm working at my part-time job right now.
Jeez, look at all the people around here.
At least one of them could bother to look at me.
Cities really are unfriendly places.
What's that?
A potentially catchable salaryman!
But I wonder why he's been
waiting there for over an hour?
Did she stand you up?
Well, well, this mannequin looks almost human!
She can't move, can she?
Aw, shut up.
Idiots.
Damn, what a realistic mannequin!
She's really soft!
Whoa, she's real!
Wow, she's squishy. I'd like to do her.
S-Someone!
Stop these jerks!
Ow, that hurts!
Take it easy, guys. We're in public.
Who the fuck put you in charge, old man?
Oh, dear. They took him away.
Hey, you! Don't be so rough with us!
Old man! You have a lot of nerve,
latching onto us like a clam!
Hey, you! What school do you punks go to?
By intruding on the scene, you've totally
messed up the investigation!
Investigation?
She's an undercover cop?
Why don't I send you guys off to
juvie to make some friends?
Oh, shit!
Morita-kun! You shouldn't leave your post!
See? Now you've made my boss mad.
It's all your fault.
Oh, shit! Let's run for it!
Don't desert your post. I'm paying
you money to work for me.
Money?
I-I think I should explain.
Well, on second thought, you can go home.
I don't need a woman with a boyfriend.
Um, you don't mean I'm...
I do mean it. You're fired.
Pow.
I don't know who you're waiting for,
but nobody should make you wait three hours.
Why don't you just leave me alone?
I'll bet it's a girl you like.
She must be really sexy.
Are you sure you're not ill?
Stop fooling around.
So I'm right.
H-Hi!
Reiko-san!
Sorry I'm a bit late.
Un, well, it's not...
"A bit"?
Oh, dear. Why are you dressed like that?
I told you I wanted to go to a formal dinner.
Oh, crap.
I guess I'll stop off at home and...
We don't have time for that.
And I was really looking forward to this party.
S-Sorry.
You're late too, you hypocrite!
What a rotten personality.
I'll go alone tonight.
Bye.
I'll see you at work tomorrow.
What's wrong with this guy?
I'll make excuses for you there,
so don't worry about it.
Bye.
What a mean bitch.
Listen, listen, you should just
dump that stupid woman.
Where are you going?
Kentaro?
I never thanked you for
helping me out back there.
Don't thank me.
I made you lose your job.
Then, will you be my new job?
Be what?
I'll live with you and provide everything in
your life that doesn't relate to your job.
That way, my rent, employment, and
sexual needs will all be taken care of.
But what you just described is marriage.
Oh, it doesn't need to be so formal,
as long as we both agree to it.
You don't have any complaints
about my body, do you?
Flutter.
Well?
Would you like to live with Momoko,
the Japanese Marilyn Monroe?
You're really weird.
I was being serious, you know.
Oh, please spare me.
Kentaro, don't tell me you're
engaged to that bitchy woman?
Go easy on me.
She's my boss's daughter.
Just leave her, and you'll move on in time.
Don't tell me you actually like her?
Yeah, right.
I'm only with her to advance my career.
But I can't... anymore...
You're not being yourself, Kentaro.
Hongoh, eh?
You live in a pretty nice place, don't you?
I guess.
Sorry, I'm drunk.
You can touch me whenever you want.
I never wear a bra.
Okay, I'll claim this man.
Hey, don't fall asleep on me.
I'm carrying you, so you'd better make
love to me when we get home.
Minami Kentaro, Ochiai Haruo
Jeez, it's hard to sleep.
Why can't you sleep in your own bed, Haruo?
Hey, Haruo...
What the hell?
Senpai! Who the hell is that in your bed?
Who? Isn't it you?
Then are there two of me?
Come on. Stop sleepwalking and talk...
She's naked!
Senpai, I didn't know you
were that kind of person!
After spending years at prestigious
Tokvo U, I couldn't have imagined this.
It's Marilyn Monroe!
Monroe? And you say I'm sleepwalking?
Weren't you cuddling with her just now?
No way!
I-I wonder if we did it?
Capital Hongoh
Just to be safe, I think I should
accompany you from now on.
Even though she's a business
woman, she's still a woman.
I guess... I probably shouldn't have got drunk.
That's the least of your problems, man.
Ah, it's this late already.
Kentaro?
She's awake!
I really overslept.
Wh-Who is this man?
Uh, um, I-I'm Ochiai Haruo, a classmate of his.
I-I'm his roommate.
Kentaro, I thought you lived alone.
- Uh, um, well... I thought...
- Well, never mind.
I'm Morita Momoko!
I'll make us some breakfast, so sit tight.
Let's see. What do you have?
What would be good?
Uh, um, Momoko-san... a-a skirt...
Huh? If it bothers you, I'll put one on.
Oh, it doesn't bother me at all!
Do you like it?
It's delicious!
Um, Momoko-san?
What is it, Kentaro?
D-Did I promise that you could live with me?
Yes, you did.
Ah! Kentaro, shouldn't you be leaving for work?
Okay! Let's have a nice day today!
Ah, that's right, Kentaro.
Leave your laundry out for me.
I'll wash it later today.
Sales Business Department
She's gone!
Hi, sorry for the wait!
Wh-Who is it?
Ah, Kentaro?
I just finished tidying up, and
I'm about to take a shower.
Wh-Where's Haruo?
Him? He fainted.
- Kentaro-san?
- Y-Yes!
Oh, dear. He hung up.
Just a bit more...
Oh, well, whatever.
Hi!
I can't stand it.
If you wanna peep, then just go
ahead and peep shamelessly.
Otherwise, it's bad for your health.
I'm going to go collect my belongings,
so you take care of things here.
Hey, are you mad at me for going
to the party alone last night?
N-No.
That's a relief.
I'll treat you to dinner tonight, as an apology.
Um, well, it's my turn to cook tonight.
That's good timing then.
I'll ask my father's restaurant
to send food to your place.
Um, but this is so sudden.
I don't mind. You don't need
to hold back on my account.
Well, I'll meet you at 7:00 at your apartment.
Oh, no...
7 00...
Oh, no!
Momoko!
Oteru? I've got big news for you!
Oh dear, oh dear.
Yes, it is what it looks like.
Oteru!
Oh, yes...
Look at the big mess you've made.
No... Oh, yes.
Well, I guess this should do it.
Oteru?
What is it?
Oh, are we in the way?
Oh, I didn't know you'd be back today.
Hello.
What is it?
I've found someplace else to live.
So I'm moving.
Who is he?
A man even handsomer than George Marley.
His name is Kentaro.
What about being an actress?
She's gone.
She's gone!
I'm back!
I guess it was just a bad dream.
But Momoko-san is coming back.
She only left to fetch her belongings.
Th-Then... she's coming back here?
Yeah. Well, I guess so.
Listen, don't let her back in.
But she left her bag behind.
See?
Throw it out!
S-Something slithered out.
Wh-What is it?
S-Senpai!
It's moving!
It's... It's an iguana!
Let go of me, Haruo!
B-But it's coming this way, Senpai!
What's wrong, dear? Are you hungry?
It's my pet, Wilder, from the
Galapagos Islands. Hope ya like him.
Don't worry about him.
He's housebroken.
He's not the issue.
I don't want you here.
But you promised.
I was drunk. I made a mistake.
Yes, you did.
And engaged or not, you'd better take
responsibility for your actions.
Haruo, shut up.
Now you've made her cry.
A-Actually, the girl you met
in Ginza is coming at 7:00.
She's...
coming here.
And if you're here too, it will be awkward.
Don't you understand the position I'm in?
Please, Momoko-san,
I'll do anything to make this up to you.
Okay.
Okay, I'll leave.
Thanks!
I won't forget it!
Yes, he is.
Oh, Reiko-san? Yeah.
Hey, doesn't she want me?
D-Didn't she want me?
She says a friend from Paris is
visiting, so she can't come.
How many floors in this building?
Building!
W-Wait, that's not what a meant!
Never mind.
Just please cheer up.
My life is so pathetic!
Making a girl cry? What a jerk.
You don't need to cry anymore.
I guess I'll go to some more auditions.
Wh-Where should she sleep then?
If she's in here, she'll disrupt your studies.
What should we do?
Momoko-san is going to sleep
in bed with you, right?
I guess sh-she thinks so.
Well, I think I'll go sleep
downstairs under a sheet.
Why don't you just do what you want?
What are you doing?
Making a bed for myself.
Couldn't you just sleep with me?
Let me clarify a few things.
Even though we're living together,
let's keep some privacy.
Okay, I agree.
Good night.
You're going to sleep already?
Yes.
You're really sleeping?
Kentaro?
You're no fun, Kentaro.
One boring sheep.
Two boring sheep.
Three boring sheep.
Four boring sheep.
Five boring sheep.
Six boring sheep.
Seven boring sheep.
Eight boring sheep.
Nine boring...
I can't sleep with that racket!
Then...
let's do something fun!
We can't with you like that.
But I can't sleep unless I'm naked.
Like Coco Chanel, I guess.
Momoko looks like Marilyn Monroe, doesn't she?
Momoko!
Wh-What is it, Kentaro?
Time out.
Wilder.
Take care of that for me.
Ow, ow!
He's like the Secret Service.
He'll be our lookout.
Galapagos...
Momoko...
Kentaro.
Shouldn't I be able to watch at least
a little, for future reference?
Dammit.
Dammit!
I came. I came. I came. I came...
Hey, what if I get pregnant?
Answer me.
Should I keep it?
Don't worry. I'm on the pill.
Did I scare you?
Sorry about that.
Kentaro.
This is really surreal.
We used to be strangers,
but we met under the city lights,
and made love there too.
Where are you from?
So you're finally interested in me?
I'm from Onomichi in Hiroshima.
Do you know it?
I've heard of it.
It's surrounded by mountains and the ocean.
It's a very beautiful place.
I was born on a farm.
A farm?
Yep. We grew fruit.
I'm a middle child.
My big sister is Nashiko and
my little sister is Kuriko.
Note: "Nashiko" means pear.
Note: "Kuriko" means chesnut.
Note: "Momoko" means peach.
That's why I'm... Momoko.
My family is full of fruits.
That's a strange family.
Yup.
Lots of people say that.
That we're strange.
I bathed with my father until I
started going to high school.
He'd always scrub my chest and butt.
That's why I'm so well developed.
Listen, Momoko.
You're a woman too.
You're soft and supple on the outside,
but juicy on the inside.
That makes a perfect woman
and a perfect peach.
What a perverted thing for your father to do!
He's a pedophile!
Oh, dear.
Are you jealous?
He told me there is only one
peach in the entire world,
and that I should become that peach.
Like Marilyn Monroe.
Is that why you want to be an actress?
It is.
What if this is all a dream?
But I'm also your Momoko, Kentaro.
As proof of that...
let's go for another round.
The last time ended too quickly.
Haruo,
your eyes are pitch black.
What about you, Senpai?
You seem to be drained.
Almost like someone's tied you up.
Wilder, must you always be so greedy?
Jeez.
Unless you stop eating that, it'll all be gone.
What do you feed him anyway?
Cactus.
Cactus?
I don't see the problem.
I can always buy you another one.
Starting today, I'm gonna find
a job and get back to work.
I think I'm gonna try an adult video audition.
Adult videos?
Are you sure, Momoko-san?
Yeah.
I already practiced for it last night.
Just kidding.
I'm going to work.
Kentaro?
Are you set for the next 24 hours?
I wonder if it's natural for my lifestyle
to change drastically overnight,
and then learn so much about women so quickly?
Momoko...
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Hey, Chief, you're a woman, right?
And what about it?
...though an aged fruit is a different matter.
I wonder if it's only me?
I'm the only person who thinks you're not smart
enough to have graduated from Tokyo U.
Minami-kun, you're the chosen one!
Wait up!
And yet you fell into that woman's trap.
Hello.
You're such a fool!
Even if you weren't engaged
to your boss's daughter,
you'd still have a bright future ahead of you.
I got to my exalted position
by cutting men's throats.
Position...
Even I would love to have graduated from
Tokyo U and be married at age 32,
but I guess that an affair is
all I've got left right now.
Hey, Chief, you have a meeting today, don't you?
With the head of Personnel, yes.
And Kawakami Reiko, your fiancée,
says she wants to watch.
Good morning, ma'am.
Good morning.
Um, may I borrow Minami-san for a little bit?
Yes, yes, be my guest.
Idiot.
What's wrong, Reiko-san?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
My friend from Paris came back all of a sudden...
and brought me a beautiful present.
I wanted to show it to you.
What is it?
Chanel.
Ch-Chanel?
Here it is.
Well? Isn't it stylish?
What is it?
Ah, um, weren't you going to a video audition?
I was lying, hoping Kentaro would stop me.
Oh.
Hey, do you know of any good jobs?
Well, there's unskilled labor.
Yes! That would fit me perfectly.
What is it?
Um, well, it's a job where you need to wear a bra.
A boob-band, eh?
I don't own one.
I'll go buy you one!
Okay.
Here we go.
I promise you won't regret this job.
Can you really promise?
Personnel Department | User Interview Conference Room
Is that so.
Any other questions?
Are you finished?
Yes, we are.
Oh, boring.
Young people these days have no manners!
Next.
Excuse me.
Well then, let's start with your name.
I'm Morita Momoko.
How old are you?
I'm 21.
Why do you wish to join our company?
What's the matter?
In today's society, there's a question of what
role electronics will play in women's lives.
I believe this is an important issue,
and I believe that in order to make the most
efficient use of their time and money,
women must become
comfortable with electronics.
And so, I want to research ways to
increase efficiency in the workplace.
By the way, Morita-san, do you have a boyfriend?
Yes, I do.
He's just a humble salaryman, but...
Where did he graduate from college?
Tokyo U.
Just like you.
He's very nice.
He has another girlfriend,
but I want to take care of
him and understand him.
She's got balls.
I wonder, is this sufficient?
Oh, my boob-band is making it hard to breathe.
Oh, no!
I fainted back there, didn't I!?
Cut the bad jokes, will you?
That stupid Haruo bought me a bra
without even checking my size.
Haruo?
Haruo sent you here?
Hey, unhook me, will you?
That asshole.
Please, it hurts.
I might faint again.
Yeah, fine.
How was I?
What do you mean?
Was I as good as Monroe?
Thanks!
That feels much better.
Momoko, you'd better withdraw
your application and go home.
So... did they hire me?
The Chief liked you.
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm so happy!
This is the first time I've passed an audition!
H-Hey, Momoko! If someone
sees you here like this...
I don't mind!
I'm so happy!
Well, how do you feel?
We'll have a little celebration for you tonight.
I'm so happy that you're happy.
Oh yes, Kentaro, the boss is calling for you.
Okay!
Well, why don't you skip out on the new
girl's party and take Reiko out instead?
Department Head
Y-Yes, sir!
That makes me so happy.
Dammit.
What's the point in having a party
if Kentaro doesn't show up?
He's just a humble salaryman, but...
Aw, you silly.
That man looks like your boyfriend.
He's just a driver.
Momoko.
I'm home.
Hey, hey, hey...
Did you transform into Monroe?
Right about now, he's with that bitch.
Momoko-san?
Momoko-san...
I'm really a fool.
I'm getting in deeper and deeper.
I'm falling for him more and more.
and I'm losing control more and more.
This should do for tonight.
I'll make an excuse to Daddy.
This ain't funny.
Just do whatever you want.
Bitch.
He's late.
Kentaro...
Ah, Senpai!
Momoko-san won't come out of the bath.
For how long?
Three hours now!
Momoko!
You were late.
How could you do something so stupid?
Because... I love you too much.
It's okay.
I don't need...
Ketchup!?
Well, I didn't think you'd be that mad.
Please cheer up.
And then... I'll leave.
I'm always like this.
I thought I could live with a nice
man who would take care of me.
I guess it was too good to be true.
Well, I fail.
Can't you stay?
I'm always surprised by your boldness...
but it's refreshing, and I like it.
You kind of forced yourself on me,
but if you want to, you can
stay as long as you like.
As a token of my thanks...
I offer you my body.
Galapagos, eh?
Your shadow falls on the white
sidewalk in the daytime.
shiroi hodou ni kimi no kage ga utsuru daytime
Your pointed pistol is poised to shoot me.
hitosashi kimi no pisutoru boku ni nerai sadame
The instant before I fall in love, my heart screams.
koi ni ochiru isshun mae muna-sawagi
With my hear as your target,
you pop-pop-pop the trigger.
haato megakete dan da da hikigane o hiku
Encounters are always unexpected happenings,
deai wa itsumo totsuzen happening
and everything changes tomorrow.
soshite asu ga kawatte yuku kara
We'll take the next step together.
tsugi no suteppu futari de fumi dasu
I know the position I'm in better than anyone else.
I'm gonna make it happen.
i'm gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
See? I can feel something in the atmosphere.
hora nanika hajimaru atmosphere
You're gonna make it happen.
you're gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
Don't let this moment get away.
ima kono toki o nogasanai
Even though I ran all the way from
the subway, I'm out of time.
chikatetsu made iki o kirashita no ni time up
After watching your train leave,
I'll go back to the streets.
densha o miokuttara machi ni hiki kaesou
I wish I could stop you, even just for a second.
ichibyou demo kimi o hiki tometai yo
With a trembling rhythm, my
heart beats pop-pop-pop.
haato o furuwasu dan da da rizumu ga naru
Countless coincidences are happening.
kazoe kirenai guuzen happening
And the mystery that brought us together
futari ga meguriaeta fushigi ga
will take us into the future we create.
tsugi no suteppu mirai o tsukuru yo
I'm gonna make it happen.
i'm gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
See? I can feel something in this atmosphere.
hora nanika kanjiru atmosphere
You're gonna make it happen.
you're gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
I don't want to stay stuck in one spot anymore.
mou doko ni mo tachidomaranai