Oh, we're finally at the school dorm.
Saint Francesca is amazing.
It's huge, isn't it?
Onii-chan, you're being-too loud.
I heard your school is being shut down.
I can't believe you're being sent to an all-girls senior high.
It's not an all-girl school anymore.
Starting this spring, it's a co-ed school.
That's true...
But I don't really want to know the boy to girl ratio.
Yeah, I'd rather not know.
Onii-chan, you saw! You saw them!
Uh, sorry!
Harukoi Otome
~ Let's Meat at the Otome Garden ~
First Episode
My name is Hayasaka Akihito.
I've been attending the co-ed Saint Francesca
Academy for a while now.
Despite the overwhelming boy to girl ratio
I've finally gotten used to school life.
I've met many people and done many
things in a short period of time.
Although retraining my long forgotten kendo is really tiring,
I'm glad because it has helped me bond with certain people.
And as spring neared the halfway point,
something suddenly happened.
Wake up, Onii-chan.
Come on, get up already.
Morning already, little sis?
Sorry for the bother.
Geez, Onii-chan.
If you don't hurry, you'll be late.
I'm glad I have such a cute sister.
If we were lovers, it's possible I'd have
done some perverted things already.
I won't wake you up anymore.
Onii-chan, you idiot!
Umi, what's wrong?
Aki-chan, what's going on?
Umi-chan just ran out and didn't look too happy.
Oh, could it be...
Umi-chan found out about the late-night fun between you and I?
Ow, ow, ow!
What's wrong, Umi...
Hey! If you're going to sleep, go sleep outside.
Sleeping in class is not a good habit to pick up.
What do you want?
There's nothing wrong with me sleeping here.
Sleeping, my ass. You're fantasizing, aren't you?
As a student with other classmates in mind,
I won't let weird thoughts go through people's heads.
What?
See, I'm right, right, Yuika-san?
Riru-san, there's a limit to how rude you can...
Right, I'll stop.
Now it's the childhood friend Yuika-san's turn.
I'll just make my way over to the cafeteria, if you'll excuse me.
God, I'm so irritated! That girl is a pain in the neck!
Aki-chan, what's wrong?
You've been out of it since this morning.
Oh, it's nothing big.
I don't think so.
If Aki-chan is worrying about it, it can't be something small.
Does that mean I have to tell you too?
Ah, I'm sorry. I meant no offense.
It's nothing... just that...
It's just a morning joke, what's there to be agitated about?
My younger sister is so...
Aki-chan, you can't do that.
Although she's your sister, Umi-chan is still a girl.
Okay.
Even if you're joking, saying you want
to do perverted things is bad.
Right...
I can't believe Aki-chan is so inconsiderate.
I don't care about you anymore.
Is it that taboo?
Goodbye, Kisaya-oneesama.
Goodbye.
Akihito-dono, your mind wasn't focused today.
Is something bothering you?
You didn't put a lot of effort into practice today;
you were acting just as if you were a broken robot.
Ah... as expected of Kisaya-senpai.
You've already noticed?
Getting worked up over a small incident
won't get you any sympathy.
Especially as a man, no less.
R-Right.
Even though she's your sister, she's almost an adult now.
To think that you consider this as a small joke!
Is it wrong for a brother to worry about his sister?
It's not a horrible joke, but to say it to your sister...
Um...
I'm sorry. It's not like I've forgotten what's
going on between Senpai and I.
I didn't mean that either...
Akihito-dono...
Senpai, you're too tense.
I'm still not used to it.
Senpai's breasts are so pretty.
It's not good for us to do it here.
Does it feel that good?
You idiot.
I don't like beating around the bush.
Gotcha.
Don't make me moan.
I can't do that.
Akihito-dono, I can't wait...
Don't do it... so hard!
Yes...
Senpai, can you use your mouth?
My mouth?
I'll try.
Senpai, it feels so good.
Sorry!
It has your flavour.
Sorry about that. Now it's my turn.
Yes, please...
Onii-chan...
Why do I have to treat you two to lunch...
I don't know this weirdo,
but I made a promise last time.
I'm not a weirdo. My name is Oikawa.
Aki-chan's friends are my friends.
Let's try to get along.
Oh really? Then as a starter for our funds,
our first step is to sell you to some hentai
store in the 3-chome district.
If you need money, I can lend you some.
You guys...
Don't worry. Aki-chan's a good guy.
Oh, it's Umi-chan.
Hm? What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Now that I think about it, Umi-chan
didn't come by this morning.
Did something happen with Umi-san?
Nothing happened.
So why are things like this if nothing happened?
You probably don't think much of me.
Yeah, not much.
It's nothing, really!
Fine, eat whatever you want for lunch.
Hey! Aki-chan!
Why am I running away?
Akihito-dono.
I saw everything.
You saw everything?
Then, you know how I feel.
Your younger sister is indeed acting a bit odd.
No matter what happens, you shouldn't leave it alone.
Why don't you find out some things from your sister's friends?
Her friends?
That's right, her friends.
is she inside?
Sonya-chan, what's wrong?
Ah, Akihito-san!
What is this?
I wanted to release the newborn pigeons,
but ended up getting caught by this net.
Pigeons?
Ah, thank goodness!
Yeah.
This is a bit tough.
Sorry.
Is it hard to endure?
I'm fine.
Please don't stare at me.
Sorry!
Umm... Akihito-san, what are you doing today?
Oh yeah. Sonya-chan...
How has Umi-chan been lately?
How has Umi-san been?
Yeah.
She seems pretty lifeless lately.
Has anything happened to her in class?
Now that you mention it...
What happened?
I've heard her mumbling.
Mumbling?
Yes.
What is it?
Umi-san kept saying she wanted to forget it.
Forget it?
Looking at the calendar and mumbling...
She wants to "forget it." I wonder what.
Has she done something bad?
That's impossible.
Oh, I don't know.
Thanks for waiting.
It's been a while since I've been called out by Aki-chan.
I guess.
Since school started, I've only seen you in class.
We finally get to meet again, but there's no time to play.
That's true.
But, I was rejected that one time.
At the graduation ceremony, I actually wanted to...
Stop, stop!
Sorry, just take it as if I hadn't said anything.
I was just rambling.
Don't worry about it, Yuika.
Just pretend nothing happened.
So, anyways...
Yes?
I don't know whether anything has happened to Umi or not.
What things?
Umi's been acting weird.
You mean this matter of Umi-chan avoiding you?
Yeah...
I guess I can tell you.
Do you know anything?
No, but before that...
Please do it with me.
Is my body weird?
Not at all.
That's how it moves?
Does it feel good?
Why don't you lie down?
I want some here too.
Of course.
Such a lewd finger...
I'm doing lewd things, after all.
No!
Yuika's so warm inside.
And it's completely wet already.
It feels so good!
I'll make Aki-chan feel good too.
It's slowly getting harder.
You're not bad, Yuika
Now, do whatever you want to me.
I've liked you all along.
I'm so happy.
Yuika...
It's okay, keep going.
Move... faster!
A-Aki-chan!
Umi-chan probably likes you, Aki-chan.
Likes me?
Of course, she's my sister.
No, I meant as a girl.
That's impossible. What are you saying, Yuika?
Don't you remember the accident?
Accident? Which one?
It's probably what you wanted to forget.
When you were seven, on the corner
by the bakery in front of the park.
My little sister got into an accident before my own eyes.
I couldn't believe what had happened.
I completely shut myself in afterwards.
I didn't know for how long, but one day...
That's right. A new sister appeared.
I began loving my new sister, and completely
buried all my previous memories.
That tragic event was locked deep in my memory.
From then on, I created a whole other story myself.
I know the times I've had with Umi-chan are real.
She thinks of me very highly.
It's been that way for a long time.
To be honest, I wanted to do that too.
I wanted to forget it, forget all of it.
A little while before you confessed, I remembered something.
What was it?
I would make fun of her for stupid things.
She went through so much.
It's my fault... my fault that accident happened!
No, it's not.
I liked you, and I was so afraid of you learning the truth.
I was afraid, so I ran away.
But I didn't expect this school to suddenly
turn into a co-ed school.
But why did Umi wait?
Why did she wait until now to act like this?
I know why. Because right now...
it's the middle of spring, and since you came
here, both you and her are now together.