Senpai, your technique feels just right!
Your dick is so yummy!
Hey, gimme a break, Kaneda-kun!
This is just the third time.
You'll be fine.
My grade on the test was awful!
I have to do better!
If I fail the next test, I'll be kicked out!
Don't worry about it.
I'll cover for you.
What's going on?
It looks like the Sports Club's practices are becoming a drag.
Sportsmen are all alike.
All technique and no finesse!
It's important to incorporate a little fantasy in there!
Leona-sama,
regarding the PE budget,
we've given the girls' teams as much assistance as possible.
Well, it at least makes a nice little story.
All that remains is to take some of the
funding from the smaller clubs and circles.
Good point.
I think it's time to move on.
We'll have all of you kids perform a "hunt" next.
I can hardly wait.
I wonder what's coming?
After all, these are the literary arts.
I'm sure the lower half of their bodies will be well endowed!
Yamanaka-san?
What will you do about this Arts Club hunt?
I feel bad doing this to Leona-san, but I have my own needs.
Say, Yamagata-san, you agree with me, right?
Are you from the Tea Ceremony Club?
Yes, we are.
Oh.
Um, is there something you want?
Wh-What the hell is this?
Sorry, but I'm a bit interested in tea ceremony,
so I thought I'd stop by the Tea Ceremony Club.
Wow, you're this hard already?
Your Cowper's gland is oozing, too.
I get it. I'll lick it for you.
See? Doesn't it feel great?
Hey! That was too fast!
Sorry!
You're in the Tea Club, right.
Stir my tea for me.
Oh, no! Oh, stop it!
No!
I'm cumming!
Drink my tea!
This should help you keep it up longer.
No!
My tits! Don't squash them!
You shithead! Bastard!
That all you've got?
I don't mind.
Take off whatever you want.
You like my tits?
My nipples are sensitive.
Hey, you.
Don't you want my pussy?
See? Your dick has gotten so big.
If you want to lick it you can.
Come on, down there!
Lick my pussy!
Okay!
Yes! Yes!
The dicks of Tea Ceremony men aren't so bad.
Come on! Give it to me!
Gimme your semen!
Yes!
Semen!
Semen...
Give it to me!
Spray it all over me!
So much semen...
It smells wonderful!
So delicious!
Wanna taste?
Both cocks are so yummy!
Still too easy.
Hey, don't hold back, okay?
If you wanna cum, go ahead and cum inside of me.
Oh, yes!
Yes!
Oh yes!
If you want to, then just cum!
Amazing!
It's exploding!
So hot!
My pussy is so hot!
Inside of me!
The hot stuff is...
It's still not over yet.
You came on me a lot.
It's too much.
But fucking great.
Let's do more!
I'm so sick of it!
You left me, the great Morimoto Leona, out of the play?
I asked them to go out hunting for me!
I ordered them to bring prey back for me!
But no one has come back!
What's their problem, I wonder?
Hey! Why are you smirking?
Are you mocking the great Morimoto Leona?
Matsuno, lay him on the ground.
See? Doesn't it feel great to be ground under my heel?
Kaoru, do you understand your position in all of this?
I love you, Onee-sama!
I love you!
You're my pet.
A pet's main purpose is to pleasure his master.
I will!
I will do anything you want!
So, please don't hate me!
Kaoru?
Kaoru, take off my underwear.
Yes, Leona-sama.
Now lie on your back.
Yes, Leona-sama!
Lick me clean.
Yes.
Do I stink?
I should stink.
In order to punish you properly, I didn't wash down there yesterday.
Not at all.
It's a smell that I love.
What? You like the whip?
You're quite a pervert.
Kaoru?
Do you want to come inside of me?
Yes!
And what right do you have to enter the great Morimoto Leona?
Well, I love you, Onee-sama.
But you're just a pet.
And you want to be inside your master?
I want to pleasure you, Onee-sama.
I'd rather you not be so presumptuous.
What gives me pleasure is hearing you scream.
Come on, come on.
Pleasure me more.
What's the matter?
My juices are flowing nicely now.
Good job, Kaoru.
Thanks!
Bad boy!
Making love to a pet?
That's bestiality!
Onee-sama!
I can't...
Kaoru...
You really are an animal.
You can still go at it after cumming so much?
For your sake, Onee-sama, I'd go until I died.
Then, can you keep it up even through this?
No way.
Pretty nice, I must say.
Onee-sama! Onee-sama!
Kaoru. Not inside...
Onee-sama!
Please forgive us, Leona-sama!
Leaving the great Morimoto Leona out of the fun?
How dare you!
We humbly apologize!
This academy belongs to me now.
This means that all rooms are shrines to me.
I will not permit disobedience!
Excuse me, but...
Why are we included in this?
You were accessories to the crime! Equally guilty.
Though I'm not too interested in the limp dicks of art boys.
Oh, if you want something else...
...I think I know where you can find it.
What did you say?
Hey, where's Saori?
Don't worry.
She's sound asleep.
Okay! Time to go at it hard tonight!
Let's go have some fun!
What should we do? She s out cold.
If we don't take care of her, there's no
telling what Leona will do to her.
Oh, well. I guess we'll take her with us.
And?
This is what you were telling me about?
I apologize.
There wasn't enough bodies.
I had to make do.
Is that so?
Well, never mind.
Matsuno, use "that" on her.
Oops, was it too much?
Pump them all up quickly.
We're about to begin.
It seems to be working.
I wonder if she was on some other drugs?
Stupid bitch.
It looks like she's having fun.
Come, give it to me.
Oh, dear. What a nice noise.
You're all soaked.
I'll join you.
Feels just right, doesn't it?
Delicious, isn't it?
You've got great reactions.
What about over here?
No. It hurts.
What hurts?
Let me taste it, okay?
Girls are lots of fun, aren't they?
Truly amazing.
Your pussy is all squishy.
Oh, no...
See? Mine is nice and warm, too.
Yes right there.
It feels very nice.
Wow! This girl is a virgin!
How unusual.
A girl this hot is a virgin...
Stealing her virginity is a big honor.
Hey, you! Not there!
No! Not anal!
Stop it!
I'll take it too.
Come on. If you slack off, it'll fall out.
This toy is useful for things like this, too.
Sorry, Otokawa-kun!
Yes! She's biting and licking!
Otokawa-kun!
Huh?
Oh, no.
I wonder what happened?
Well, whatever.
Hello? Onee-sama?
Yes. Just as you said.
No problems in the Social Club.
Some good friends joined us.
Yes, of course.
I chose them, after all.
This academy is now under the total control of the Social Club.