So cruel...
I got my first sexual experience ahead of you...
I guess it's got to be the elder sister
who becomes an adult first, after all.
The vibrator feels good!
Sayuri-chan doesn't have a hymen anyone,
so you can do it all you want from now on!
It feels so good, it seems idiotic
to want to protect your virginity.
Manami-chan!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Once I cum I'll lend this to you, Sayuri-chan!?
I'm cumming!!
Sayuri-chan...
No!!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing, Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
In other words, you have a complex over the fact that,
although you are twins the younger sister is shows
more excellence, Kirishima Manami-san.
Yes...
The results from the physical examination show
that you are winning in some areas, right?
I'm can't be happy just because I'm a bit bustier.
Sayuri-chan's breasts are prettier,
and have a better balance.
Is there anything else you are worried about?
Um, about down there...
By down there you mean?
The vag...
About the genitals.
You don't have to be embarrassed, just call it the vagina.
I am a doctor after all.
Yes...
About my vagina...
I think its shape is kind of strange...
Well why don't you show me?
Huh? Right here?
If I don't have a look I can't tell.
That's true but...
There's nothing embarrassing about being, right?
I'm a doctor after all.
Okay.
I can't see very well. Can you spread it with your fingers?
I get it. Is this okay?
There doesn't seem to be anything unusual.
But, my clitoris has come out of its hood,
and the lips haven't gotten hot
and won't come together...
I think the size of the clit and the temperature
of the labia are both quite standard, though.
The color is even prettier than average.
But when I pee it doesn't come out straight...
How is it compared to your younger sister?
I haven't seem Sayuri-chan's recently, so...
We used to show each other, but I'm not sure...
I see.
By the way, both you and your sister are virgins, right?
Yeah. Sayuri-chan is also probably...
Well then, why don't you try having
sex to overcome your complex?
Huh?
If you have the experience and become an adult first,
won't that make you better than
your sister who is inexperienced?
I... I see.
In addition, if you have sex, the penis
inserted will help shape the vagina.
So my vagina lost its shape because
it's never had a penis inside?
That's right.
Then maybe I should let go of my virginity already...
If you have your first experience before your younger
sister, I'm sure your complex will also disappear.
That's true...
If I become an adult before Sayuri-chan,
I'll gain some confidence!
I'm a doctor, after all.
There are no mistakes in what a doctor says...
I'm pretty sure these are great boobs
that you can boast about.
The boys stare at them during P.E. and stuff...
And sometimes Sayuri-chan looks at
them with scary eyes sometimes...
I see.
But they're fine in sensitivity.
I... I see...
Well then let's examine the pussy next.
Okay.
Not there...
Something's coming!
It's coming!
Oh, did you cum?
Seems like this part has matured well, too.
After you lose your hymen you'll become a great adult!
Well then, let's have the experience before your sister.
Yes, Sensei...
Leave it all to me, I'm a doctor.
A specialist in popping cherries for virgins!
Yes, please help me lose my virginity!
Is such a large thing going to go inside my pussy!?
That's right. Don't worry! You'll get used to it right away.
Here it goes.
It... hurts...
That's the pain of becoming an adult.
Now I'm... a grown up woman...
It has still...  just begun!
Ouch! Ouch! It hurts! Sensei!
Sensei, it's okay now!
Please take it out! It hurts!
It'll start to feel good right away.
It hurts...
Huh? What this?
It hurts... although it hurts...
It feels good although it hurts!
It feels good to become an adult!
To think it would feel this good in my first experience...
I'm experiencing a pleasure that
Sayuri-chan doesn't know about!
It feels so good I could die!
Well, here it goes!
Now I've become an adult...  before Sayuri-chan...
If you've only done it once, you're pretty
much no different from a virgin.
Is... Is that so?
I'll take responsibility and make you a great adult,
so come to the infirmary every day from now on.
Yes...
Sayuri-chan, does it feel good?
Have you given up now?
Well then I've won the bet, right? Hehe.
You're so foul! It wasn't a proper bet to begin with!
I hope you stop making excuses.
Well then, Kurihara Chisato-kun, I'll
make you take punishment as well.
For sure!
No matter what you do to me, I won't
lose to a filthy person like you!
I love that determined attitude of yours.
Well then I'll change my plans and let you
take the punishment without hypnosis.
Chisato-chan! Take off your uniform and come here!
Well then why don't you give me your virginity?
Huh? Are you okay without getting it wet first?
I'd rather finish something like this as soon as possible!
It hurts! It's going all the way inside!
Just putting it in is not enough.
You have to make me ejaculate properly.
This is boring.
Let me rub your chest. Naked.
It's about to come!
No!
It hurts!
Here it comes!
It's coming! Hot stuff is coming inside!
There we go.
Well everyone, the party has just started!
Starting today the school is mine! Hehe.
Class Murakashi
It's the best to see everyone healthy as usual!
Yes!
Murakoshi gathered only female students he liked,
And did improper things in the name of lecture.
Everyone is forced to listen to
Murakoshi under his hypnosis,
but for some reason only Manami and I,
remain aware of everything that is
happening while being controlled.
Well then, would Manami-san and
Sayuri-san come up front?
Sa-Sayuri-chan...
We well get Sayuri-san to read something out loud.
Sensei, what about me?
Manami-san will become the character
that appears and act out the events.
Okay.
Well then, everyone take off their skirts and underwear!
What?
Why are we doing something like that!
If you don't do that, it won't be a proper lecture.
Come on, you two should take them off as well.
No...
Even though we don't want to, my body is...
No!
When Manami gripped tightly by
the teacher, she lost herself...
and started moving her hips.
Stop this!
I don't want this!
Stop! Sayuri-chan!
I'm sorry! But my mouth is...
Manami stuck out her tongue and started drooling.
She started a deep kiss with the teacher...
No!
Manami moved her large hip around...
Hey, Sayuri-san! Read with some more emotion!
Monotone is boring!
How am I supposed to put emotion
into something like this!?
Let's see... well why don't you masturbate?
What!?
If you do that you'll be able to put some
emotion in the reading, right?
You're naked down there anyways.
Something stupid like that...
If you don't rub you your clitoris rougher
you won't be put in enough emotion!
No, no...
Continue with the reading, Sayuri-san!
Manami took in the penis with her
labia, searching for pleasure...
Her drenched vagina took the penis deep inside.
Not so...
Everyone else look closely at the two of
them and write down your thoughts!
Be sure to put in lots of emotion!
Yes!
No! Don't look...
Manami became...  a slave of pleasure.
There is no longer a way for her to stop...
her growing lust... through her own will.
I can only think about things that feel good!
Manami opened...
No!
the entrance of her womb, and begged...
"Please cum lots inside..."
You can't do that!
Please cum lots inside!
No! I'll cum! Cumming!
Well done. Here is your reward.
Amazing. Since you're twins you
even climax at the same time.
Sayuri-chan...
Manami-chan...
The fun, honey pot lecture from Murakoshi-Sensei
has just started!
The next class is P.E.!
Sayuri! Pass, pass!
The team that gets scored on will have
to turn up their bullet vibrators!
If you don't work hard, you'll feel better and better!
Even if you say that...
Hey! Close your vagina properly!
Yes!
If you lose then it's your turn for punishment! Hehe.
Well, let's get you to clean up.
Okay.
Here, Sayuri-san should clean up the anal area.
Hehe. To get the beautiful Student Council
President to do this for me, I'm so sorry.
Chisato has become wonderful at taking care of the penis.
C'mon Sayuri, stick your tongue deeper inside.
Here it goes!
Graduation Ceremony
Several months later...
Awarding the Sperm of Graduation.
Student Representative: Kirishima Sayuri.
Yes!
No! Not so rough! I'll give birth!
Giving birth is fine isn't it?
It's the graduation ceremony after all.
Besides, it's almost the expected date, isn't it?
No!
I'll let the baby drink it, too!
Well, let's show everyone the sperm
in commemoration of graduation!
Sayuri-chan, congratulations on graduating!
Congrats!
Congratulations!
After being tortured day after day,
Manami's mind was broken.
If I had broken as well, it would
have been so much easier...
Looks like the celebration for graduation is going
to turn into a celebration for giving birth! Hehe.
While everyone is watching me give birth...
I'm cumming...