Hiiro no Koku
Episode 5
Are you finished?
Yes.
Wasn't that a bit fast?
Here.
Oh.
What is it?
Before we leave... um...
You weren't fully satisfied?
Very well then.
Hey, we're going to Mizuno.
I've been waiting to hear that!
Yamagawa Detective Agency
Well, I'm sorry to summon you like this.
It's okay.
How are you doing?
How's life?
Where's your daughter?
I left her with my parents.
The extended family seems to be
the only thing that calms her.
She's happy living with them.
Then...
your personal life has settled down for the time being.
Settled?
I'll never feel settled as long as Etsuko is missing.
A lot has happened, huh?
It must be very hard on you.
After all, she disappeared so suddenly, didn't she?
Your wife's disappearance...
is very puzzling.
It seems as though she was perfectly
satisfied with her life as your wife.
Still, I think that perhaps she craved greater intensity.
This past half year...
has really been tough on her.
So you've found her?
Yes.
I found someone who certainly seems to be your wife.
This is a picture we took a week ago.
This can't be...
This might come as a shock to you, but...
this is an exclusive, top-secret sex club.
When my men went there, they
found that she wasn't alone.
She always came with one man.
And also...
This is a very difficult thing for me to say, but...
What is it?
It seems that your wife...
is the special, VIP call girl at this club.
I hear she's very good at what she does.
This is... Etsuko.
He's apparently the head trainer at the club.
Apparently, women who fall under his spell become
obsessed with the pleasures of the flesh.
He's a ladykiller. He renders women incapable
of returning to their normal lives.
My men saw all this go down.
They said that your wife doesn't
want to leave that guy's side.
Oops, pardon my rudeness.
Etsuko.
Etsuko, you were never satisfied.
Secretly... Secretly you were asking me to help you.
Do you know this woman?
Ah, of course I know her.
Anal, double penetration, urination...
She's the biggest, most depraved masochistic slut ever.
She's a very refreshing maso-whore, and
she'll do anything her customer asks.
The other day she really got us good.
And then, you see,
we gave her some anal training.
I mean, when we licked her asshole,
she gasped so happily.
I was fucking impressed.
She felt bad being entirely on the receiving end,
so she licked my asshole,
and she got really deep inside.
Oh man, don't even get me started.
Then I shoved my cock into her ass.
Please, stop it!
I mean, she shoved her ass on to me.
She was fucking awesome!
Stop it!!
What the hell was that for?
Darling...
Etsuko.
I'm sorry, darling.
I...
Etsuko...
I was...
Please, don't say it.
It was my fault.
That's not true.
I didn't even try to listen to you.
In fact, I'm a bad husband.
That's not true at all.
I'm very happy.
I'm injured?
Oh, yeah...
You shouldn't move yet.
I'm sorry.
You helped me, didn't you?
Etsuko!
I never thought you'd...
come looking for me like this.
I was very glad.
Of course I'd come looking for you!
I'm your husband, aren't I?
Etsuko...
Please...
Please just leave.
How can you say that?
Haven't you heard?
A lot has happened to me.
They've done many things to me.
I don't care...
as long as you come back.
Darling...
Is the sweet reunion over?
I let you see each other this one last time.
Consider it an anniversary present.
Etsuko!
Give back my Etsuko!
But Etsuko told me...
that she didn't want to go back to you.
Just... go home.
I can't come with you.
Why not?
They've changed me.
I do many strange things.
My body needs it now.
Etsuko...
At first, I resisted.
I thought again and again about asking you for help...
but I couldn't.
I was too scared.
I was scared I'd lose you.
Etsuko!
But my changing body...
came to accept my new reality.
I can't forget what I've become.
All I long for is hard-core sex.
I...
You'd never even think such things of me.
I'm so slutty and lewd, and that gets me off.
Embarrassment makes me happy.
That's the only way I get turned on now.
Thoughts about sex... and thoughts about
erotic play never leave my mind.
No matter what I think, perverted fantasies arise.
Even while I eat, I think about sex.
It's all I can think about anymore.
So... I don't deserve your love anymore.
Etsuko, Emi needs you.
She's been waiting for you this whole time.
E... mi...
What are you doing, little girl?
Waiting for Daddy.
Where is your Daddy?
What a helpless father.
What will you do about Emi?
She needs you.
She's been waiting for you to
come home this whole time.
Emi!
And so have I.
No matter how much you've changed,
you're still you.
Darling!
In that case, let him see.
Let him see what a dirty bitch you've become.
S-Stop this now!
Please don't!
Not in front of my husband!
Then try resisting me.
However, I'm sure your true nature will emerge in time.
Yes...
Okay, I understand.
Yes, right away.
Hey, we're supposed to ready the Playroom.
I think it's for Etsuko.
Daigashi is going to be in the audience, so make it fast!
Oh, sweet. I'm joining in too.
Hey...
Oh! Kazu-san!
Long time no see.
– What's happened?
– Hi.
Have you seen Daigashi?
Oh, I think he's in the Playroom.
I see.
Sorry about that.
Hey! Where have you been this whole time?
Take a good look, sir.
What's wrong, Etsuko?
You seem extra tense today.
Perhaps that man over there...
is someone you care about?
Don't, please...
Please, I'm begging you.
Please, not today.
But you were so hot for me earlier.
That makes me jealous.
Well, never mind.
From now on, let's show him just how
deep and dirty our relationship is.
Come on.
See how wet and soft you are?
Please don't say that!
Don't say it?
But you're soaked like you want it really badly.
How can you say that, Etsuko?
The more I touch it, the more flows out.
It's begging for a dick.
Won't you beg for it like you did the other day?
Here's your meal.
No!
How many do you want in today?
Maybe I should add an extra.
Come on, come on.
It's all flowing in.
How's that? I put in six!
It's coming.
It's coming out!
How is it?
You haven't had an enema in a while.
With all that pussy juice flowing out,
you'd love to have a nice big, thick
dick in there, wouldn't you?
Am I wrong?
I want it.
You want what?
Your d...
I can't hear you very well.
Your dick!
Where?
In my pussy...
and my ass.
Oh, can't you say it like you usually do?
I won't do it otherwise.
E-Etsuko... Etsuko is...
a masochistic bitch who loves anal.
Very much...
I want it... in my ass.
Come in!
Shove your noisome cock...
into Etsuko's dirty asshole!
Here ya go.
Thanks.
I'm sure your father will come back in time.
I'd like to go back soon as well.
Oh, Shima-san!
Did you bring her here too?
What are you talking about?
You know this little girl?
Well, of course I know her.
I mean, that kid is the one we talked about.
Come on, come on.
All the way to the base.
Can you do that?
Etsuko's asshole is so happy.
So happy!
Dicks make me happy!
You want it in front too?
Yes, in front.
Then how do we ask?
Fuck me.
Fuck Etsuko's pussy at the same time.
Very nice.
That's why we love Etsuko.
Here, your reward-dick.
Dick... Please put your dick in.
It's all wet already.
Here ya go.
Oh, yes.
With your other hole plugged up like
that, you taste like a stray dog.
You love being a dog, don't you?
You're like this in front of your "beloved" husband.
Well then?
What do you think?
– My dick is yummy, isn't it?
– Your dick is so yummy!
I feel it deep inside!
Oops, sorry.
The glass was shattered.
I suppose something is unsatisfactory.
Darling... I...
Don't!
Darling!
I can't!
I can't take it!
It's too amazing!
– I'll die!
– Goodness, she's become totally helpless.
She's tasted many different dicks now.
She gets drunk from the depths of her body
from all the different flavors of dicks.
You can never reach her again.
I'm cumming!
It's coming!
I can't stop!
Come on, let's cum, Etsuko.
It's coming out!
If you understand, it's time to give up.
She is, after all, our goose that lays the golden eggs.
K-Kazu?
You asshole...
Daigashi...
It looks like you've made a lot of enemies.
You're not the actual mob boss after all.
And the second-in-command needs
to behave himself a little better.
Impossible...
Who in the world...
Was that payback for kidnapping Etsuko?
That's part of it,
but the main reason was because it's my job.
This doesn't concern you.
I have to go to the police station now.
I hate to waste this opportunity,
but I'll leave wifey in your hands.
In any case, our business is over.
I would never have imagined this outcome.
No matter who makes love to me,
I turn into an animal like that.
Truly, I'm hopeless...
so please forget about me.
I'd rather that you hate me...
forever.
Honestly, I'm not sure if I can forgive you for everything.
That much I know.
But I also know that this isn't the outcome you wanted.
If we look at it that way...
then no matter how much you've
changed, you're still you.
Oh God. If you can forgive me, then we can...
Daigashi has escaped!
Are you Etsuko's master?
Y-Yes, I am!
Mommy!
Emi!
Hey, leave through the back exit right away.
At her age, she needs a mother.
It's not too late to start afresh.
I won't pursue you guys.
Go live wherever you wish.
Shima-san...
Shima-san! Kazu ratted out Daigashi!
Yeah, I heard.
The cops will be here any minute.
What about these guys?
Leave them.
The blood of a bitch courses through Etsuko's veins.
It will never go away.
Your real problems are just starting.
We'll be okay.
I won't let Etsuko be lonely anymore.
Go live in peace.
I should say that it was also my fault.
Our hearts never communicated.
I never even noticed that Etsuko's smile had vanished.
There are many things that are important,
and I've finally realized that everyday life matters.
I want to start over,
from the beginning.
And for that... I need you.
Oh, Mommy, you're bleeding.
Lemme see.
Emi.
Come, let's go home.
The three of us, together.