Mikimoto!
Don't!
We've only been going out for 2 months.
It's... just too soon.
But...
I want to do this carefully...
with you, Shinji-kun...
please!
Shinji-kun, thank you.
Actually, I really love Shmji-kun,
but my heart isn't ready yet.
The following students pay attention: Mikimoto-san
from Class C, the Principal is calling for you.
Please go to the Principal's Office.
Me?
Virgin In The School Uniform
[Hot Tease and Desire]
EPISODE. 1
Excuse me.
I apologize for calling for you so suddenly.
And even after calling you here, the Principal
is very busy at the moment.
Please! Please give me your sperm!
Take it!
The Principal's cum is so delicious!
What a good girl you are, here's your reward.
How's the flavor?
The aroma is wonderful.
I'm glad. Now then, sorry about
this, but wait here for just a bit.
Okay.
I'm wet! It can't be! Why!?
Sorry for the wait. Now then,
let's proceed, shall we?
Please excuse me and let me go home for the day!
No! Don't look!
Amazing! You're amazing! I'm going
to cum! Yukari's coming again!
Wonderful! So good!
W-What?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yukon?
What is that? Going inside Yukari, what is it?
Principal?
She's arrived. Today's main dish!
Now then, suck on this.
No!
What's wrong? You don't know
how to? Just look at that.
It can't be... Yukari, that's where guys go pee.
Even you want to eventually make
love to your boyfriend, right?
Look how wet you are!
No! I'm making such embarassing noises...
Please don't be so rough!
Don't!
This scent... the scent of a virgin!
I've had my eye on you for a long time now.
I can't take it! Kyouto-sensei,
hurry and put it in me!
All right!
No, please! Anything but that!
You've kept your virginity up 'till
now for me to pluck it, eh?
No! That's not true!
It's in! It's in! Take it! Take it!
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts!
So good! Amazing!
Amazing! Feels so good! Too good! Fuck me silly!
No...
No... no!
Take it! Take it! It's like an amusement
park ride, right?
This amazing feeling... it's too
good! I'm losing it, Mikimoto!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Please cum inside me!
I'm cumming! Here it comes!
Pretty good for a man my age.
I filled you up good. I'll be sure to give you
a lot more training tomorrow as we.
Mikimoto!
Tomorrow, let's have lunch together.
What's wrong?
As promised, you made the bento-box
lunch the way I wanted, but...
the taste isn't the way I like it!
I'm sorry!
Mikimoto!
Mikimoto...
That's right. Just keep quiet and do what
I say and good things will happen.
You don't want anyone to
find out about us, do you?
Especially your boyfriend, right?
Now! Accept my present like a good girl!
All right... here it comes!
No...
No!
You're so cute, Mikimoto...
From now on, make sure you
remember the way I like it.
What's wrong? It's not like I'm fucking your heart.
Put yourself into it and show me what
you've got! Be more considerate!
Yes... that's the way.
All right, let's have you eat some more.
How is it? Tasty?
Yeah, just like that. I'm going to
do it all over your face again.
Here it comes!
No... Shinji-kun... Shinji-kun...
Dangit... why can't I figure it out?
How girls feel... I just don't get it.
Well, yours is so big, just do her
once and she'll be all yours.
No, Mikimoto isn't a slut like that.
How do I put it... she has a beautiful heart.
Are you serious?
That's right, she's a pure and innocent girl.
Yeah, I've heard that before.
Actually she looks like the type
who likes to mess around.
Stop screwing around! Don't say things like that.
I believe in Mikimoto! She's
surely a virgin! No doubt!
Shinji-kun... I'm already...
I'm cumming!
Hey there mister! Come in for
a massage! It feels great!
I understand all about that.
In any case, a young girl like you will
quickly get countless customers...
Now... your specialty is thigh fucking?
That's... That's like my favorite food!
My mom back in the countryside
would make that all the time!
Is that right... your mother from the countryside...
Note: "Sumata" means thigh fucking while "suama" is a type of candy.
That's not thigh fucking, that's Suama candy!
Jeez, just go home already!
Thanks for the application.
Thank you like, so much for your help!
Well pardon me!
I guess there's no-one like that eh...
a young and mesmerizing girl...
I thought it would be a shortcut...
but I'm completely drenched!
Virgin In The School Uniform
EPISODE. 2
[OVER CLOCK]
It's getting late!
Is that woman getting ready yet?
Yes, Boss.
Come on... Come on... Come
on... Come on... COME ON!
I CANT TAKE IT ANYMORE!
I WANT A TASTE, NOW!!
Wow! It suits you so well!
All right, I'll get this school uniform into
the laundry so just wait a bit, okay?
S-Sure...
Sorry for the trouble.
It's okay, don't worry about it. When people
are in trouble, you help them out.
Thank you very much.
Oh no, this feels really tight. If only
I hadn't tried to walk home...
Madam, where are you? Madam?
What's this? You're all set to go?
Boss! Boss!
There's a new girl here!
Boss!
I found her.
Idiot! You took too long!
Sorry Boss...
How about it Boss? We've got an hour.
Thirty minutes will be more than enough.
Okay... well, excuse me...
Um...
Well! You look yummy... I've waited for you.
It seems we'll first have to teach
you some manners, eh?
What the hell! It's not wet at all!
Please forgive me... I've never done this before...
What!? You're a virgin!?
Yes... so please... let me go...
Your chastity means nothing to me!
Damn! It's so tight! This tight hole
is going to make me explode!
Listen to those nasty sounds!
Ow! It hurts!
No! A stranger's dick is going into me!
Stop! Please! Leave me alone!
You hear the song of noises my cock is making
inside you? Let's bang you harder!
This is so damn good!
Stop... please, somebody help me...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm going inside you!
No! I'll get pregnant!
All right. Round one over!
Now then, let's change this outfit you have on.
Here you go little girl! Good luck!
All right, now serve me.
Does it feel good, Master?
Please, pollute this dirty maid more
and more with Master's semen.
What a perverted maid you are.
Well then, your reward is the
thing you see in front of you.
Thank you very much.
How is it? Tasty?
Yes.
You're a fast learner.
Use some different techniques, you
have to please your customer.
That's the way! So good!
Oops, a little bit came out...
No wait, just keep going like that.
Yes, good.
What's wrong? I haven't cum properly
yet, continue your work.
Okay.
Come on! It can go in deeper
than! Take that! And that!
If we keep this up, you'll get a new
breathing hole in your throat!
Yes, that's good, you're cute.
You're such a perverted slutty maid.
You want my sperm that much?
Well then, here! Take this!
Both your rear and your mouth
are my personal urinals now.
All right, I'm going to go all over
your face. Look at me.
I'm cumming!
Good, good. You really tried hard. You
would make a good secretary for me.
I know, I'll make you the poster girl for our club.
You'll soon feel a muscle-relaxing
drug making its way inside you.
I'm also giving you an enema up
your ass to get you ready.
Now, samples of patients' semen might
fill you up through this tube!
But if you make me cum in under
a minute, I'll release you.
I'll be using your asshole for this one.
These measures will ensure that you do a good job,
so that the "dead patients" can "go to Heaven".
You should be feeling the drug's effects
now. Now plant your ass on that dick!
Consider this a service to posterity.
Do it for the sake of your customer.
Let's start.
Ow! It hurts so much!
What's the matter? If you don't put your
heart into it, you'll get pregnant!
No!
No!!
It feels pretty good
It hurts!
Please hurry and cum!
Please give it into my butt hole!
All right! 30 seconds remaining!
No! Please hurry and cum
inside my slutty butt hole!
Only 10 seconds left!
5! 4! 3! 2! 1!
Damn! You're wearing me out!
Artificial insemination success!
You're too cruel...
Hold it right there! Here I come!
The Sailor of Love and Justic-
Now be a good girl, give me that clit!
No! Stop!
Secret attack!
No! I'm going to pee!
I'll be cumming soon! You don't have
any more killer techniques?
N-No!
I'm cumming!
Are you cumming?
A pathetic girl like you couldn't
possibly save the Earth!
Please... just stop... My insides are all sore...
Huh? I guess so...
but only after I've had my fill of you!
Please, no!
Whoa! Here it comes!
No more! Please no more cumming inside me!
That's the whole point! I'll be
filling you with evil genes!
No!!
Please don't cum inside me! Please!
I'll get pregnant!
Sperm is inside me...
I'll get pregnant...
Seems like we did a good job
hiring this new girl today.
A new associate?
That's strange, I expected the girl from the
countryside would be long gone by now.
Huh?
Err...
Sorry for all the trouble and such.
but I forgot my bag in there!
Oh shit!
Boss? Boss!
Boss! That girl's the wrong on-
Kamaji! This girl is great! A princess!
I can't get enough of her... She'll
become one of my associates.
I'm going to put the finishing touch
on her now, pay attention Kawaji.
Human Urinal Project complete!
Don't... I'm going to...
Check it out Kamaji! I did it!
The little bunny ran astray... when people
are in trouble, you help them out...
From now on, I'll be looking forward
to working with you...