Haruna, I'm going to ask again.
Tell me the passcode.
Dr. Yamada, snap out of it!
This isn't the kind of thing a doctor is supposed to do!
You don't know anything about me!
Oh no... This can't be happening...
Rensa Byo-toh
Your father would never approve
of you doing something like this!
This is why I'll never forgive that dirtbag...
He completely fucked up my family and my future!
That bastard!
It hurts! Don't!
Doctor, snap out of it!
Please go back to being the kind person you once were!
No! Don't!
Doctor, stop!
Please take it out!
Congratulations! You've lost your virginity Haruna!
No! It hurts!
Please stop moving! My insides are going to tear!
He'll never admit to that mistake if I don't have proof...
That's right, that's why I need your passcode.
I won't tell you!
No!
Not like this!
I'm about to cum, Haruna.
I'll hit your insides with everything I've got!
No!
Don't...
You came... You came inside of me...
I'm going to be borrowing your ID card.
Tomorrow, I'll be asking for your passcode again.
What's wrong, Wakoto-san?
You have such a grim look on your face.
No, it's nothing...
Well, okay, but...
I have to go!
Wait...
Wakoto-san?
Kiyosato Hospital
Surgical Department | Examination Room
It can't be... You really developed those pictures!?
Please, just stop this already!
Well then, can you come with me for a second?
What is it now?
If it's about my passcode again, I still won't tell you!
It's not such a big deal.
The weather's nice, so let's take a walk.
A... walk?
This... is a "walk"?
You haven't been getting enough exercise lately.
If I walk you like a dog, you'll get plenty of exercise, won't you?
A dog?
Please be honest... Once this is done,
everything will be over with, right?
This seems like a nice spot.
Doc...tor...
Doc...tor?
Wait here.
Doctor!
This is a joke... right?
Dr. Yamada, you're over there... aren't you?
Oh no! If I don't get out of here...
If someone finds me...
No... No! Why won't it open!?
Doctor!
Save me! Please save me!
Doctor!!
Dad...
I'll do it!
I'll cooperate with you, so please...
I'll... cooperate... with you...
So... Please... Please forgive me!
You understand?
Ok then!
Oh no... in a place like this?
What's this? It's soaking wet down here.
No that's-
I didn't... no, not there!
Is it good?
Why... Why does it feel so?
Doctor! Please...
Just look at you...
It feels good, doesn't it?
That's not true, it-
I'm not enjoying it! You're forcing me...
You are now my slave!
Cum for me, Haruna!
Doctor! It feels too good!
No! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Now, I'll have you tell me the passcode.
Yes...
Doctor....
It's no good. It's tougher than I thought.
I can't bypass the Director's clearance...
There wasn't anything in the digital records, was there?
It would be simple to kill someone with
a botched surgery. It's not unheard of...
It must have been him...
I'm going to expose him and obliterate his public image.
I'll search for another method, and you'll help me, Haruna.
Yes...
I'll help you... I'll do it... Ill do it...
Spread your legs. I'll reward you for giving the correct response.
Okay.
I'm so happy!
Your thick cock...
Is thrusting so deep into me...
Haruna, you've become quite slutty.
No, I...
I'm not slutty!
Doctor! Doctor!
My slutty place... Please fuck it as
hard as possible with your cock.
With the doctor's thick cock... all the way deep inside...
More! Please, more!
I'm going to cum!
Doctor! Please fill me up with your reward!
I'm cumming... Cumming!!
Haruna.
I didn't wash your body enough yesterday, did I?
You cleaned me up well!
But I never thought we'd make such
a good couple! I'm so happy!
Oh, Shu-kun!
How are you? Have you gotten used to the hospital?
Ah... yeah...
I'm so glad. Shu-kun's become such a splendid doctor.
And he's even been working in our hospital as well.
Misako-san, why did you get married to that dirtbag?
Why, with the man who murdered my dad?
Misako.
You're acquainted with Dr. Yamada?
Oh! Did I forget to mention it to you dear?
Shu-kun was a stifdent of mine back when I was a tutor.
Your student?
Well then, I'll see you around, Nurse Wakoto.
Dr. Yamada, make sure you do your job properly.
Dear? Well, I'll see you then later, Shu-kun, Wakoto-san.
Haruna. Tonight, don't bother stopping by my office.
Okay.
Today we'll let your body rest a bit.
Tomorrow... Tomorrow night, Misak-
Surgical Department | Examination Room
What's the matter?
Suddenly telling me you had something urgent to discuss...
Come on, what's the matter?
Whatever you tell me will stay right here in this room, okay?
Okay, I understand...
But actually... It's about the person I love...
Oh! Is that what you wanted to talk about?
Yes.
I... What should I do? Misako-san...
It'll be fine!
After all, Haruna-san is so cute and pretty.
I'm sure it'll work out.
But... I'm so happy!
I love you... Misako-san.
Haruna-san?
Misako-san, do you hate me?
No... that's not true, but...
I'm so happy!
Misako-san.
Let's make lots of love, okay?
Haruna-san!
What are you-
No!
Misako-san is so delicious.
No! Please don't lick me there!
Haruna-san! Don't... We're both girls...
Misako-san... you're wet...
No! You're putting it inside me!
Why... does it feel so good?
Oh no! My body is getting so hot!
Misako-san...
I'll do it here too, okay?
Don't do that there! Not there...
Don't... we can't do this!
I'm so glad you feel pleasure from this, Misako-san.
Please cum. Please show me how you cum.
No! No!!
What?
Shu-kun?
Looks like you did a great job at screwing her.
Misako-san and I were making love.
No, that's not true! It's not true, Shu-kun!
Misako-san, does the Director know you're doing such things?
No, please don't tell my husband!
If I agree not to tell anyone, will you be relieved?
I'm not sure...
I see. So then if I promise not to tell the
Director, and instead keep it a secret...
You'll share my secret with me?
Shu-kun's... Secret... Share?
If you really share my secret, I won't tell anyone about this.
Then you can be rest assured, right?
I think so...
Shu-kun, what are you-
What do you mean "what"?
We're going to make a secret that we'll never tell anyone.
You don't mean...
I didn't know... it was so big...
How does this compare with the Director's?
I shouldn't...
Stop it, Haruna-san!
Amazing Misako-san, you're already soaking wet...
It can't be... You wouldn't do "that"...
"That" is exactly what I'm doing.
You're going to become mine
Misako-san, do ou understand?
Stop saying weird things, Shu-kun!
My dear husband...
Forgive me!
It's too late for that now! Misako-san,
you'll be helping me get my revenge now!
Shu-kun... It hurts!
The man who killed my dad was your
husband... I'll have my revenge!
It can't be! He killed your...
It's too big!
Misako-san's body looks so happy that
it's receiving the doctor's cock...
We're making a secret of adultery you can
never share with anyone, aren't we?
No! Please don't say the word "adultery"!
You're getting severely agitated...
But I can hear the nasty noises your juices
are making, even from up here.
No! That's not true!
Oh no... I can't... I'm going to cum!
Does it feel wonderful?
Misako-san has made it grow even harder.
It can't be... It's tearing me up!
Please forgive me! My dear husband, I never wanted this...
It couldn't... but it's hitting me so deep inside!
It's even hitting the entryway to my womb...
I... I could never never have imagined... I never...
So deep... So deep inside...
I can't... I can't take it anymore!
It's coming! I'm cumming! My first real orgasm!
Misako-san, you never knew of the pleasures of sex, did you?
I never knew! I'm going to cum for the first time!
This huge... this monster cock...
It's completely different from my husband's!
It's coming! I'm cumming!
Misako-san, Dr. Yamada is going to pump so much into you...
No! Not inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'll be pregnant...
I'll be pregnant with Shu-kun's baby... My dear husband...
Misako-san, the doctor is now going to do something amazing.
Huh? What!? No!
It's still hard!? But I already came!
I... I can't... I'm cumming again!
Me too... I want the doctor's cock too.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!!
Do it... Cum because of the doctor's huge cock.
Please, just stop! Shu-kun, please just stop already!
Misako-san you're so unfair!
Give me a turn with the doctor's cock!
You came so much last time, and you're
going to cum so much again!
No, I don't want to cum anymore!
It's so hot...
You came! You came inside me again!
I'm cumming again because you just came inside me!
I'm cumming, doctor! I'm cumming too!
The doctor's huge cock is hitting me so deep inside.
Misako-san, I watched you with his cock
and it's still so hard and slippery.
I watched you!
It's so good! It's so good!!
Please give me pleasure!
Please unleash your load inside me!
Me too...
Misako-san, you're longing for the doctor's
huge cock again, aren't you?
You're wrong... That's not true!
I don't need anything like that!
Even though it feels this good?
Doctor... I'm going to cum...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Misako-san is watching me and... I'm cumming!!
The doctor came so much inside me...
Does it feel that great, Haruna-san?
Haruna-san! Please don't press up against me like that!
Haruna-san! Please stop sucking on my nipples like that!
I... I....
You want it, don't you? The doctor's huge...
No! No!! I don't want it! I don't want it...
Don't worry, it's okay.
The doctor's cock is going wild inside me so....
Misako-san, you'll also...
No! Don't take it out, doctor!
The doctor's huge cock filled me up with so much...
Misako-san, if you beg nicely,
the doctor might ram it into your gushy parts.
I don't know... I... I...
Doctor! I want doctor's huge cock!
I... I...
My slutty cunt wants your huge cock!
Me too...