K-Kirishima-san.
D-Don't get the wrong idea.
If you don't make me feel good,
I'll stop right away.
Hey Tsuchiya, stop breathing so close.
It tickles.
Don't stare.
Kirishima-san, it s all soggy.
J-Jerk!
Hurry up and lick it.
Jeez...
Even though you're obese, you've got a powerful tongue.
It's inside!
My insides are being licked.
Kirishima-san, suck mine.
Gosh! It's getting harder and harder every time.
Fine, I'll suck it.
This feels even better than usual.
This is so embarrassing.
Oh no... I can't stop.
His penis...
tastes so good!
K-Kirishima-san,
I'm going to...
God dammit! What was that for?
I wasn't even done yet.
S-Sorry, but I can keep going.
P-Put it in now.
Can I really?
I gave you permission, didn't I?
Hurry up.
Sony for barging in on your fun.
But could you please stop?
Look at the mess you've made.
Asaoka-sensei...
You two... need some disciplining.
M-Mikura-san?
U-Umm... Are you Kotoha-san?
Yes.
I'm sorry if I bothered you by calling you out.
Don't worry about it.
What do you want from me?
Well, actually...
I saw it.
I-I saw what you were doing...
in the nurse's office.
I didn't tell anyone about it.
So um, well...
Kotoha-san, have you had sex lately?
What did you think about our sex?
What do you mean?
What are you doing!?
Please stop.
N-No...
Hey, tell me.
Did you get excited from seeing
my pussy being penetrated?
N-No, I didn't.
Oh?
M-My heart just thumped a little faster, that's all.
Is that all?
No!
Please don't touch it!
Did you play with your breasts or masturbate
while watching us having sex?
No, I didn't.
I'd never do something as dirty as that.
To be honest, I noticed you.
You were watching Endou-kun and me having sex...
and masturbating.
Liar!
No one could've seen me!
Wow! You're ejaculating!
I'll get Endou-kun to bring his friends.
You want it, don't you?
Well...
Thanks for waiting.
Just you, Endou-kun?
Sorry, I couldn't find anyone else right now.
I see.
What's wrong?
All right.
All right? Huh?
Use this for a blindfold.
It's warm, isn't it?
Endou-kuh, I'm going to suck it.
Mikura-san, I'm going to...
H-Hold it in.
Endou-kun, could you back up to the wall?
Like this?
Yeah, just wait.
I'll take the lead today.
A-Am I really going to?
Shh. Just start by sucking it.
Ehdou-kun, does it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
Mikura-san, your tongue is wrapped around my penis.
It's amazing.
Endou-kun, it's so thick.
Your tongue is amazing.
You're not done yet, right?
Yeah.
Endou-kun, come in from behind.
I'm gushing already.
Mikura-san, your pussy is amazing.
It's inside.
Wow! It's hitting my insides!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!
Mikura-san, if you keep sucking...
I want to do it too.
Come to my house today, and let's do it there.
Sensei, I want to go home.
No. It's finally my free time.
And how many times have you done it?
Well, whatever.
Anyways, turn around and point your butt towards me.
Quickly!
Sensei, what are you going to do?
I have to discipline kids who come to the nurse's room...
just to have sex during class.
Oh, you know?
Tomishige-sensei created it.
No...
If I drink that,
I won't be able to stop.
No!
You can't say no.
Hurry up.
T-Tsuchiya!
It powered up.
You'd better drink it...
if you want to keep up with him.
How dirty.
Compared to last time, I'm...
It's been improved.
You can feel it, right?
A little stimulation like this...
will cause him to ejaculate.
No... I'm going to cum.
Don't stop yet.
Oh, I guess I shouldn't worry.
Kirishima-san, show him your dirty place.
Tsuchiya, look.
Wait!
You better let him penetrate you, or there'll be hell to pay.
It's burning!
His burning thing is coming inside me.
That was way too sudden, you jerk!
I'm in heaven.
I'm filled with warm stuff.
For being so turned on...
I'm such a pervert.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My, my, Tsuchiya-kun.
You've got guts.
Hey.
Yes!?
Where's Asaoka-sensei?
She left because it was boring.
So when did you...
Forgive me!
Well then...
Let's do it again.
With my breasts?
Fine.
Have you always wanted a boob job?
You don't need to hold it in.
Just cum whenever you're ready.
Did it feel good?