Shin Kyouhaku 2
~ Flower That Blooms in the Wound Kainloow of Blood ~
SCENE.1 [Fake]
Are you girls the Akehime twins?
Who are you guys?
You sure look too different to be twins.
That doesn't matter!
Saki-chan, let's call a teacher.
Don't do that! Running pitifully for help
is what they want to see us do.
B-But...
Kidnappers!!
Someone help!
Shit, we're in trouble.
Saki-san, are you okay?
Saki-chan, you sure can scream loud!
Akehime!
Are you okay?
Sensei! I'm just fine.
It was awesome! Saki-chan kicked those guys asses!
I didn't do anything that barbaric. Right, Mayu?
Y-Yeah...
As long as you're okay... But I wish you wouldn't be so reckless.
Aww, Sensei, you're such a worrywart.
We're late. Let's go!
Sensei...
Akehime...
Eew. I told you to call me "Saki" when we're like this.
But we can't do this.
I decided to hold off until you graduate next year.
Yeah, but you still came out to see me. Just like my note asked.
I'll be waiting by the yard.
This sort of thing is too risky.
But my phone was out of service.
Really?
I'm sorry.
We can't.
Jeez.
This and that are separate matters.
Run along now. Class starts soon.
Okay. Bye!
Oh, Mom, you're home?
I just got back.
You've been out late a lot lately.
Must be tough teaching at a cram school.
Don't say it like you misunderstand me.
o—o
It would be embarrassing if my own daughter flunked out of school.
Why don't you study a little harder like Mayu?
Yeah, fine.
I'm gonna go study.
Man, that sucked.
I'm gonna go kill some time with Mayu.
Saki-chan...
Are you dating Tsuguya-sensei?
Are you... and Sensei...
I wonder if she's already had sex with him...
Like this, his thing is inside of her...
No way.
I... am so...
...soaking wet.
Saki-chan... Sensei... I want it in me too.
Saki-chan... Sensei... No!
I can't stop it!
Don't... move so much there.
Oh no... I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
What she was doing...
...is supposed to be done with someone you love.
But doing it to yourself just to feel good?
It seems... nasty.
No. I don't want to remember. But...
Does it really feel that good?
What's this?
I'm throbbing.
Maybe just a little.
No way!
Oh no...
I shouldn't do this. I can't do this.
No... I can't stop it.
I can't stop it!
No... I...
No... I don't wanna... but I can't stop.
What's this? Something's coming.
It's coming...
Yes?
Hello?
Who's there?
Who the hell was that!?
What do you want?
Saki?
Sensei?
What's wrong?
Your voice sounds a little weird.
Huh? Oh, it's nothing.
What are you doing right now?
N-Nothing!
I see. Then, can you come out and meet me?
I thought maybe we could continue what
we couldn't finish earlier today at school.
Is it too late?
Umm... It's okay!
I'm coming!
Oh, baby!
You've got some big boobs there!
Wanna come play with me?
Your ass is looking fine, too!
Jackass!
Oops. Weak. Weak, weak, weak...
I have no business with a weak woman.
Come back to me when you've got some spunk.
Monster mash!
What the hell is his problem?
Why did he want me to meet him here of all places?
Sorry! Did you wait long?
Sensei!
Sensei?
You look... different.
D-Do I look weird?
Maybe. You do look weird.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just kidding!
Where are we going now?
Here.
Here?
Do you mind?
W-Wait...
S-Sensei...
What's wrong with you?
Sensei...
That hurts, Sensei!
A-At least...
...turn off the lights.
You're already so wet.
D-Don't look!
It's embarrassing.
N-Not there...
It's a pretty pink color. And also...
...very delicious.
D-Don't do that...
Saki?
Oww... That hurts!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
S-Sensei?
What's that noise?
Changing the memory disk.
What? What's that?
I think it's taking a good picture.
Of your loss-of-virginity scene.
Who are you!?
Pierced ears...
No, you're not my Sensei!
No!
Get off!
Just stay obedient!
You think you can get away with this?
I'd listen to me if I were you.
I'll never listen to what you say!
If this video leaks out, my brother is finished!
Your beloved man is going to see this!
A student being fucked by her own teacher!
You're his brother?
If this leaks out, he'll be in big trouble!
If you want to save him, raise your ass!
I'm gonna cum inside of you.
No!
I'll get pregnant!
Shut up! You're gonna get a good taste of me!
No!
I can't believe this.
So dirty.
I won't... lose!
That's my phone.
Your phone's ringing.
W-Who are you?
Do you remember who I am now, Princess?
You took too long to answer, so I shut it off.
You guys... What are you doing?
We're doing things that feel good.
Shit, she sure put up a fight.
But the look suits her. Especially since she's such a strong-willed cunt.
I'm not gonna give in to you assholes!
Fuck her.
Where do you think you're looking?
Get that smelly thing out of my face!
Then I guess we'll have to make your mouth smelly, too.
I've got it in!
Don't put your teeth into it. He's got a really sensitive dick.
Come on, use your tongue.
Let me taste this part.
Hey, she's already really wet down here.
Poor thing. I'll make you feel better.
No! Don't!
It's not coming out.
It's all inside her uterus.
Maybe she's all out of juice. How's this for ya?
We've struck a cum well!
You guys better hurry up and let out your juice, too.
Hey, how much longer are ya gonna take?
Come on, get your ass in the air.
It's my turn to cum now.
No!
Don't be so happy about it.
Oh, she's really good!
Isn't she? And it was her first time, too.
She's a natural for this!
It feels great on my end too!
Oh man, I'm getting close.
I'm cumming!
Oh, nice timing.
Hello, Saki-chan?
Saki-chan, are you okay?
S-Sensei?
Guess i'll give her another first.
A first anal fuck!
I can't hear you very well.
S-Sensei...
Hello? Where are you right now?
My friend's house...
So...
Saki-chan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
My friend is... calling me.
I'm sorry.
This feels fucking amazing!
Stop it! Stop it, please!
Her ass is so tight!
No... Please don't...
No!