Just you wait.
In time, you will be mine.
Ooedo 48
Translation: Voldemort | Timing: Nicolai | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWawe | QC: Brush
The First Chapter
The Beginninas of Pleasure in the First Time
New recruit.
Coming through!
Looks like another one for the Master.
In that case, allow me to be the first.
This is my safe place.
The hall where I wait for girls.
Please have mercy.
Kira-sama, please have mercy!
What good is a prostitute who
can't fulfill her duties?
I will... I will escape from you eventually!
As long as I am in charge of this room,
there will be no mercy for anyone!
And your body will feel the
brunt of your punishment.
Make sure Midai-sama knows that!
Accept the law and embrace it.
You are late, Midai-sama.
Silence!
Unlike the others, I will not be swayed.
You left the side of the one befitting of
you, Master, to see that woman again?
That ugly mannish woman? What a joke!
Just what about me dissatisfies you?
My face? My flesh?
Or are you implying that I lack skill?
Oh, Kira! Please take this body!
Bind it to yours!
Very well.
I would be pleased to.
Oh, Kira! Quickly!
Midai-sama, you have reduced the supply
of girls yet again, haven't you?
They are plentiful!
For an old man like you,
that should be sufficient.
I suppose so.
By the way, Midai-sama, isn't the
next one just about ready?
Good question.
I must hunt again.
I wish you enjoyment in your secret,
outdoor, night-time activities.
My mouth is tighter than a clam's.
On the other side of this open-air hall
are the rooms where we work.
Kazura-sama, where do
we find our customers?
Oshizu-dono, no need to trouble yourself.
You need not worry about
the finer points just yet.
First, you must acquaint yourself
with the lifestyle here.
We're lower-level workers,
scullery maids if you will.
That's all you need to know for now.
Kazura-sama! When I came here, I knew
full well what my fate would be.
You don't have to deceive me.
Oh dear, forgive me.
I suppose being overly delicate,
as I am, isn't a virtue at times.
Goodness.
But, Oshizu-dono, I'm pleased
with how pretty you are.
Even the Master might choose
you personally someday.
Well, let's get going.
But that can't be.
I buried that part of myself
when I came here.
Will you not give me even a single coin?
Despite that, you seem obsessed with
getting your hands on my body.
I know the truth.
You have no money to buy
my freedom, do you?
I don't care.
Leave this place.
I've made my decision.
I'm fully aware of the conspiracy and
corruption that brought me here.
Nonetheless...
I want to observe female
happiness at its zenith.
Here is the last room.
Um, what is this room for?
New recruits are always examined.
Come. Face front.
And open your legs for me.
Stay still.
Kazura-sama?
You mustn't move.
Good.
Kazura-sama, what was...
I apologize.
We always check to make sure our
new recruits are truly virgins.
I am... still...
What about you, Kazura-sama?
As for me...
Don't worry.
That last punishment atoned for your sin.
Work hard.
I will never release the needle.
The remaining treasure trove of
the last big military general...
I am the only one who knows of it.
How very convenient.
Seshima-sama, this way.
No one should pass through
here for a while.
Please use this until you feel satisfied.
Go ahead.
You make me sick!
You rose through the ranks merely because
of seniority. Yet you act so smug!
Just what... what are you
suggesting I have done wrong?
Accepting punishment from
another woman is pathetic.
But if it will earn pity from the Master...
Harder! Please whip me harder.
You are the new recruit,
Oshizu-sama, correct?
Yes. And you are?
I am called Kira. I deal with
kitchen duties and the like.
Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Same here.
Bring the stepping box here.
Let me use it.
Yes, sir.
Oshizu-dono, you are very pretty.
So pretty that you stand out even
amidst the other flowers.
Surely you were engaged back at home?
No! Engaged? I have no fiancé.
Is that so?
What a waste.
When you're the daughter
of a poor, nameless family,
no man wants to marry you.
That's why I came here.
I see.
Well, if you are as skilled
as you are beautiful,
I am certain that even the Master might
take a liking to you someday.
Kira-sama!
You mustn't say that.
Ah, yes, I just remembered.
What?
Have you known a man yet?
No!
What a preposterous suggestion.
I have still not...
I would have expected as much.
However, this is just between the two of us.
The Master dislikes virgins.
He apparently thinks they are disgusting.
In the past, he did lay hands
on a virgin once,
but the moment he discovered what
she was, she was kicked out.
Goodness, what a troubling story.
Well, you are the Master's type.
I suppose it cannot be helped.
Tell me, Kira. How did you find
such a wonderful place as this.
Long ago, I was playing hide-and seek here.
How unsurprising. Because you
were born and raised here,
you know more about this
place than anyone else.
I do not know where I was bom,
only that I was abandoned here.
Though I do remember that
I was raised in a warehouse.
An abandoned child received
the famous name of "Kira".
Now he enters the warehouse in secret.
Very well done.
That and everything was done
for you, Midai-sama.
Just refrain from laying hands on the girls.
Tsubune-dono gives me hell for that.
I understand, but...
Well, for now, turn a blind eye.
The Master dislikes virgins.
The Master is passing through!
Kazura-sama?
Are you tired from performing duties
to which you are not accustomed?
Allow me to console you.
Um, Kazura-sama?
K-Kazura-sama?
You mustn't!
Please take me and play with me.
With that?
Kazura-sama, you mustn't!
Relax and be honest with
yourself, Oshizu-dono.
Becoming a woman at the hands of
another woman is a good thing.
No!
Become... a woman?
Kazura! You again?
What a disgusting act!
I, Midai, have tried to rid this
place of such brutality!
But Midai-sama, I was only
trying to console her.
No excuses!
Kazura!
Oshizu-dono.
What is the matter?
It seems you have something on your mind.
Yes.
Kira-sama... I despise my female body.
You despise your body?
I heard that when men grow up, the only
thing that changes is their hearts.
But with women...
Are you saying...
That a woman must end something
before she can change?
Then let me ask you this:
Do you wish to change? Or do you
wish to remain unchanged?
Which is it?
Well, I...
You left your home,
hoping that you could become a woman
befitting of the Master's pity.
That is what you used to think.
But now you question whether or not the
Master would favor someone like you.
Then you leave me with no choice.
Allow me to help.
Rest easy.
Few people know about this room.
No other men will come by.
Once we begin, we cannot stop.
Are you okay with this?
In that case, I will not hold back.
Well, then.
No...
Come. Spread your legs.
In that case, let me begin here.
N-Not there...
Oh! Oh you mustn't!
Kira-sama!
Try using your mouth.
It's hard to believe this is your first time.
I know.
You had a fiancé, didn't you?
Why did you leave him?
Were you tired of being poor?
I just... I didn't...
Well, I am not surprised.
An ambitious and determined
individual like yourself.
Just as with all the other girls here.
The highest honor is to accept
the Master's seed.
How many have dreamed of it, I wonder?
Very good, very good.
If you have a perverted heart, then your
body should be perverted as well.
This way, no one will be troubled by you.
Do you not agree?
Become the body that the Master loves.
If you do...
Yes.
Then I shall be with the Master!
And so, I became a woman
while still a servant.
Kira-sama's lessons are strict,
but in order to attain my wish,
I must endure suffering.
I hear the Master's personal
servant is gone again.
I know.
I hear she is punished constantly.
What is he thinking?
Goodness. The Master's lust
for virgins has no end.
Virgins? He likes virgins?
The Punishment Continues...
Bamboo Flute
Tripod
Standing Tower
Drizzling Tea-Grinding Mill
Bamboo Craking
Curved Pine Needles
Scattered Pine Needles
Well Bucket