Kira-sama, will you allow
me to be your partner?
Who would imagine that a pure novice
in training would want sex that badly?
I am very surprised.
I was supposed to be an abandoned
and forgotten woman.
But I have opened my eyes to desire.
I admit, abandoning you would be a waste.
I suppose this should be more
than enough for you.
Kira-sama!
Ooedo 48
Translation: Voldemort | Timing: Nicolai | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWawe | QC: Brush
The Third Capter
The Beginnings of Puppet Defilement
I've heard rumors from the girls
that Master treated you horribly.
Yes.
Recently, Master has been in a foul mood.
Even his highest-ranking harem girls
and servants are being abused.
Abused?
His official business has
been taxing him lately.
He is totally exhausted.
So why do you leave them with me?
I had fully intended to pay my debt
and serve the man who bought me.
But I have seen the dark side of the night.
Make way for Master!
What is happening in the
Room of Hisashiku?
What is the meaning of
that entangled position?
Kiriyo.
I was foolish to see her every
morning and not notice.
I am such a careless fellow.
My goodness!
Hirojiki's technique is so awful
that I cannot tolerate it!
Is there no way to improve it?
It cannot be helped.
Until all the new recruits are corrected,
we cannot use our toys.
I cannot prepare Midai-sama's
supper outside either.
I envy your "hardship".
You receive such gentle punishment.
Say, Oshizu, can you bring it to me later?
The long rod toy is still unbroken, right?
I mustn't do that.
We have Onakai-sama and
Odokumi-sama to consider.
Azami, I will not forget this.
I will bring you a new one.
Odokumi?
Could it be?
An aphrodisiac?
Um, how may I be of help?
One of our older girls had
a painful spell at mealtime
and made a big fuss with her yowling.
You know of this, do you not?
Yes...
Even so, I have yet to receive a
report from you food tasters.
Why is that?
I wish to see all three of you tonight.
Food-tasting whores like you cannot be
forgiven for even the smallest of mistakes.
Thankfully, the old whore's
condition was not serious,
but that does not excuse
your dereliction of duty.
Not wet.
So there was no aphrodisiac in the food.
Sujima-sama, what has happened?
Master has lost his temper.
Junkei-dono has been thrown all
the way out into the garden!
Junkei-sama?
But why did this happen?
She was helping Master get dressed.
He suddenly threw her
out, from what I hear.
Thankfully, Midai-sama is available today.
I'm going to get her right now.
Things have turned sour.
Kira, stop this.
Now, now, just a bit longer.
Midai-sama is waiting. Azami, move it.
Not there!
What's wrong, Oshizu?
Does it please you that much?
Kazura-sama gave me a drug earlier.
A drug?
And the effects of it... haven't worn off yet.
But Kazura-sama says that she has used
it too often, and it no longer affects her.
Now there, Oshizu!
Why are you keeping quiet about
such a marvelous thing?
I apologize. But Kazura-sama asked me...
Well, I am not asking you but
telling you to hand it over.
I see. If you are accustomed
to the drug, it has no effect.
Well. Please enjoy your meal.
The girls of the harem work so hard
every day. You must be tired.
Midai-sama has allowed you girls to
eat your fill of amazake and sweets.
However, once the man heals,
he will demand your services again.
So be warned, girls.
Do you feel strange too?
I do. Like my body is bound.
I do too.
What is happening?
Um, I wonder!
I suppose it is just as it looks.
Everyone has succumbed to their own lust.
Was this your doing?
Do you know?
There is a bitch in the West who knows
a good deal about medicine.
This is yours, is it not?
As you see, it is quite potent.
Why did you give them this aphrodisiac?
What was your plan?
I commend you for catching me.
The girls are running amok,
and Master is in a foul mood.
From observing the general exhaustion,
it is clear something is going on.
Slipping some to Master is
very difficult, of course,
but if you win over the food tasters,
the task becomes much easier.
As long as the food tasters show
no reaction, no one will notice.
Some Daimyo is behind it, no doubt.
And perhaps the conspiracy has
spread to the Shogunate.
What a lengthy and intricate scheme.
And what will you do about it?
Will you turn me in to Hirojiki?
Or...
Your last attempt at
punishment was insufficient.
Go ahead and do your worst.
If you want punishment, I can
give you as much as you want.
As long as you remain a boring partner
who is not affected by punishment...
I will force you to scream from your throat!
I know the truth.
You are a servant of the former Shogun.
You might foment a rebellion.
That is why you stay in this brothel,
to be safe while you scheme.
Why don't you just admit
your Shogunate heritage?
I am certain there are those
who would stand by you.
It appears you don't understand.
As far as I'm concerned...
I like being the punisher here.
If you come forth now, that particular
person would be pleased.
Soak your body through.
Did you hear the news?
Yes?
Komaya-sama disappeared from
the dungeons last night!
Is that so?
Then perhaps rumors of that certain
mysterious female ninja were true.
If that's the case, I wish I could have
brought Midai-sama a drink, at least.
Goodness! How can you say such things?
Well then...
FIN.
Arabesque Nea-Grinding Mill
Tightfitting Brocade
Drizzling Tea-Grinding Mill
Weaving Tea-Grinding Mill
Inbound Boat
Horizontal Chrysanthemum
Starling
Ying-Yang
Moon-Viewing Tea-Grinding Mill
Back of the Tower
Boardwalk