Shrouded in red veils,
the Heaven Tower extends into the sky.
As if calling out to someone, it glows eerily.
And when Seiryuu and Genbu arrived,
they were invaded by Her parasites.
Next, it was Byakko.
Ignoring Suzaku's protests, she tried to save them.
And now, the final curtain will fall.
Slashing through everything...
the Four Gods will fight evil to the death.
It is a battle between Light and Darkness.
The flame of life rises high.
Onmyouji: The Sinister Goddess
Lustful Bondage
Chapter Two: The Last Goddess
N-No...
No! Not that!
Please stop!
She's squealing like a little girl. How cute.
It makes me want to shame her even more.
No! No! No...
Don't look at my special place.
You're unusually modest.
Where's your usual spunk?
Byakko-san's still a virgin.
And besides,
she wants to give up her virginity to Miyamoto-san.
No, you're wrong. That's a lie.
Too bad. Looks like your feelings won't reach him.
Seiryuu and I will separate your little flower
petals and lift your veil of purity.
We will throughly violate both of your holes.
You should prepare yourself.
Seiryuu, Genbu.
You have both fallen from grace.
I will not let you take Byakko as well!
What took you so long?
You mustn't interfere. Byakko-san is our girl.
I did not expect that you would obey my wishes willingly.
In that case...
Since she is still a virgin, I will take her place.
Is that so?
Very well.
I suppose if you offer yourself as a
replacement, we might release Byakko.
But do you have any idea what you're in for?
I am prepared for anything. Do your worst.
S-Suzaku-neechan...
Mi-Miyamoto!
You're amazing! It's so hot!
I had no idea you would feel this way!
Being soiled by you to this degree...
I can't... I can't...
I can't... I can't live without you anymore!
Miyamoto! Harder! Harder! Push deeper inside me!
H-How much longer will this go on?
Try harder, Miyamoto!
Stir up my insides even more!
Are you there yet, Seimei? Or still not yet?
Not yet... Don't stop yet!
More! More! Violate me more!
I want more!
It's inside! It's inside of me!
The sweetness... The spirit is...
The spirit of everything is in me!
But... But I'm not finished yet!
You must still violate me more!
Oh my, Suzaku-san, are you finished already?
I wonder if she fainted.
I suppose we won't get results with these methods.
But we should still have some fun.
Don't you agree, Genbu-dono?
Yes, I also wish to enjoy myself.
Su-Suzaku-neechan!
Please...
Please, stop.
Just stop it!
Let me... Let me take her place!
If I do, you have to stop hurting her!
There will be...
no need for that.
I will protect you.
She still acts high and mighty.
Then shall we violate her pussy next?
It's coming inside me.
My insides are filing up.
My goodness. She can certainly hold a lot.
And her butthole is getting all stretched out.
I'm sure she must be very embarrassed
that we're watching her like this.
Su-Suzaku-neechan...
No, stop!
I'm going to break!
The selfish queen finally got what she had coming.
That's right.
It's so pathetic I'm going to cry.
Your filthiness makes me want to cry.
You bitch! What did you do!?
I voluntarily gave myself to this demon.
I gave him my life.
Do you not understand what that entails, Seiryuu, Genbu?
Byakko, I am leaving the rest to you.
Nee-chan!
Suzaku-neechan!
I'm... I'm coming.
By Suzaku-neechan's sacrifice...
I'm going to the Douma.
That stupid Suzaku thought she was saving you.
She really messed us up badly.
But thanks to her, we've ended up like this.
We must pay her back for what she did.
You needn't be frightened.
We want to show you what pleasure is.
What's wrong? It's okay to enjoy it if it feels good.
You're so soft.
Even though you're still young, you're quite large.
No!
My breasts... Stop touching them!
They've gotten quite firm.
Feels nice.
No... My breasts feel...
It's hot!
My breasts...
What's going on?
How smoothly they move. It's like they're dancing.
How right you are!
And they appear ready to meld, like we did.
No...
Don't... Don't lick them.
Stop, stop!
It's going in!
Please...
Don't push it in.
Just stop it.
That's right. With this, you'll become a woman.
No! No, not like this!
It's coming, coming, coming, coming!
Why? Why?
Why milk?
Why won't it stop?
This is the power Douma-sama has to offer.
The milk...
won't stop.
The pleasure is burning me up.
I feel like I'm going to melt.
I'm so hot. I'm melting.
I feel like I'm one with you, Byakko-san!
I may have foreseen that the three of us would become one.
Byakko. You, too, will become one with us!
Come...
Our bodies melt, and our spirits fuse together!
We will become one.
We have stolen your little flower.
Well? Isn't that what you wanted?
My flower...
I wanted it stolen. I did.
I'm sorry, Suzaku-neechan.
I can't...
She still had some power left?
In that case...
Let us use her remaining power for a good cause.
Let's open up Byakko's flower petals with this sword.
You're sticking her sword in my special place?
Correct. It's coming in.
Slowly, until it reaches your insides.
Stop... No...
You can't do that!
No!
We're in almost as far as we can go!
I'm almost there... I'm almost there!
What the hell is this?
Shit!
What was that?
Did she merge with Suzaku-san?
Suzaku is no more.
Seiryuu and Genbu will also be empty shells soon.
There is nothing left to ask. You must do it.
Focus your feelings into your weapon.
How much longer do you intend to stay like that?
I came all this way to see you.
Wake up already.
Do you mean to say you were only
pretending to be under my spell?
You could say that.
But to accomplish this, I had to sacrifice a great deal.
So what's your point, anyway?
My point is, I want you to stop these petty fights.
Petty fights?
You're the petty one, always getting in my way.
You're really annoying.
However, I cannot overlook what you have done.
That is why I am proposing we both
stop causing each other such pain.
This isn't a kid's fairytale.
What you speak of does not exist.
But it does exist. Fairytales do exist.
That is, you and I becoming one.
You and I becoming one?
That's right.
The two of us will become one and
restore the harmony in our hearts.
No...
Don't...
If you lick me like that...
What's the matter? Can't you give me your tongue?
This is your first time being touched, isn't it?
How is it? It feels good, doesn't it?
You could at least have had sex with your shikigami.
Instead, you protected your virginity for so long.
It's almost as if you were saving yourself for this moment.
I don't like it... I don't want to become one with you.
I don't want it!
Don't play hard to get when you're so wet and slippery.
Just trust me and do as I say.
I don't want to hurt you.
That's why I'm making sure you are sufficiently wet.
My energy is ready. I'm coming in now.
Are you going to keep doing that?
I am.
I'm going to keep doing this as long as you like.
Don't think about anything.
It feels good. Just accept that feeling.
I know how you feel.
I know how it feels to have something inside of you.
I understand!
Now I understand...
how it feels to have someone else inside me.
It's amazing!
No!
I can't take any more.
Do you understand?
What it means to become one.
I understand.
Two opposites come together to be complete.
Darkness and Light. One cannot exist without the other.
However...
If we become one, there will be no more conflict!
There will be peace!
Light and Darkness. Which will remain?
Miyamoto-han!
Oh...
Oh, no. It can't be.
I wanted to save you...
Why?
Why am I the only one?
Why am I the only one that survived?
How can I go on alone?
How can I...
Year 1914
Munich
I knew you were a special man.
I'm sure you can take this world in your hands.
Because you can see how I really look on the inside.
The End