Outrageous!
Such outrageous tits!
They're too big!
That one over there's a bit'small, but it's got a great shape!
Success...
After failing over and over again at peeking...
I've finally succeeded!
You're excellent, Kazuya!
But...
Why do I feel nauseous when I see these outrageous tits?
No, I mustn't just watch.
I'll make them all mine.
That's right. My cousin did something amazing.
He impregnated the entire class that he transferred into.
And became a symbol of world domination.
I see. We share the same blood
That's why I feel this urge.
All right, I'll do it!
If he can do it, there's no way I can't!
I'll conquer all twenty girls in my class!
Kacchan.
Oh, Asuka.
What are you'doing here?
Well, I was just going...
She's Touno Asuka.
Don't tell me you were going to do that?
She's my classmate and a childhood friend
She takes care of me a lot.
Jeez! If someone saw you, you'd be so screwed!
Dammit, she knows.
Oh well, I'll keep it a secret this time–
You're so kind, Asuka.
Hey, Kacchan...
Your tits are always so soft.
No, not here.
Why not?
I've done this since I was a little kid.
But if you'do it here...
Jeez.
My name's Kagami Kazuya.
I'm a smart, honest, and perverted
student at Shirasagi Academy.
This place used to be a girls school,
so there aren't many guys.
I'm the only guy in my class.
The other twenty are all girls.
I guess you can call it a harem.
It's only natural that ambitions will sprout.
And because my parents are usually overseas on business,
I live in my school's dorm.
Everyone in my dorm is female.
It makes me so happy that it troubles me.
I'm back.
Oh, welcome back.
This is Ebihara Mai.
A classmate as well as the dorm leader.
Kagami-kun, hurry and take your
bath while the bathroom's empty.
All right, just give me a few minutes.
Whenever you say that, you always fall asleep.
Hurry up and go.
Although she's like a bossy sister,
she's really good at taking care of
others, and she has great tits.
Look at that!
Remember to put your shoes in the wardrobe!
Kagami-san,
welcome back.
Chihiro-chan, I'm home.
This is Kitamori Chihiro.
She's a kind girl who always wears a smile.
The imbalance between her doll-like face
and her huge tits is really something.
You must be tired.
Want some ice-cream?
Ice-cream? Sure.
Wait, is this..
Super-spicy ice-cream. It's really good.
She has a weird fetish for spicy stuff... And that's a bit...
Kagami!
Welcome back!
I'm back, Misha.
This is Misha Ivashkova.
She's an exchange student from Russia,
and she's also a figure skater.
She's good enough to he in the Olympics.
With her silver hair and gorgeous tits,
there's no man in the world who wouldn't fall for her.
Kagami!
Eat some pierogies with me, okay?
I don't know if it's because of where she's from,
but her actions are extremely ''bold.''
And Chihiro-chan looks really cute when she's jealous.
Anyway, I love living in this dorm.
And then...
There's one more girl in this dorm.
She's from the Planet of Tits!
Just kidding. She's Nanamiya Akane.
You bastard...
Umm... well, I can explain myself.
Explain?
Yeah, explain–
I never get tired of doing things like this.
You bastard...
By the way, she's the ace of the softball team.
You pervert!
Why do you have a metal bat?
Cut the crap!
I'll send you flying to Uranus!
This is my wonderful school life.
Episode 1 The Beginning of My Ambition
Kacchan...
How do you feel, Asuka?
You're touching me differently from the way you usually do.
And if you lick them...
We're not kids anymore, so we should do this like adults.
Oh my God... I feel so good!
No, not so rough!
What are you talking about?
I know you want it.
No, don't say that.
Look, Asuka.
Look at how stiff it got from your moaning.
Amazing, Kacchan.
It's not fair that I have to do all the work.
So you must...
use your tits to make me feel good.
Okay.
Your thing is really hard.
Your tits just made it even harder.
My breasts are so warm.
Your penis is on fire
Asuka...
Suck it
Okay.
Good job. Now take it deeper.
You're doing great, so I guess it's about time.
I'll reward you.
I'll do it gently, because it's your first time.
You're my first, so I'll be fine.
I see
You're such a good girl.
Does it hurt, Asuka?
Don't worry. Start moving.
All right, i'll start slowly.
Amazing, Kacchan!
Wow, it's hitting my insides!
You're pretty loud.
Aren't you scared your friends in
the tennis team will hear you?
They're all the way on the other side.
It'll be fine.
Who knows? You're way too loud.
B-But it feels so good.
Everyone's training really hard...
but you're the only one doing such lewd things.
You're a bad girl.
You're such a bully! You said you'd be gentle!
Should I stop?
No, don't!
Wow, Kacchan, you're really deep inside.
You feel so good inside, Asuka.
It's my first time doing this.
Kacchan, I love you!
Oh my God, I'm going to come!
I'm cumming too, Asuka.
Come! Let's come together!
All right, take in my hot cum!
Cum! Fill me with your hot cum!
Wow! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Take it all in!
First one down.
Well, I've known Asuka for a long time, so she's easy.
What should I do about the others?
Sorry for the wait
Welc–
Oh, again?
Hey, don't take that attitude with me.
I'm busy right now.
I'll get to you later.
Bye.
Izunae Meiri.
She's my classmate, and she also works
here, a cafe called Happy FulLTime.
But turning the school cafeteria into a maid cafe...
I love this school.
Here, eat this.
Huh?
This looks really grand.
Well, I just threw in everything I could find.
Really?
I love the tsun-tsun side of her.
Tsundere are great.
Master!
Oh, Mia.
This is Miyamae Mia.
She's another classmate of mine, and also works here.
She calls me ''Master.''
Because of her cat ears, she says she's a cat in human form.
A weird girl.
Kagami-dono, are you okay?
Yeah...
But you could've used a more normal method.
This is Mitobe Natsuki.
She's rather old-fashioned, and
she loves me with all her heart.
However, she gets jealous easily, and she
takes everything way too seriously.
And her opponent is...
Darling, having lunch?
I'll eat with you!
Yo, Kasumi.
Hey, stay away from him.
Can't you see he doesn't want you near him?
You're making that up!
And mind your own business!
What?
Wanna fight?
That's right. This is the girl Natsuki's
most jealous of, Oshino Kasumi.
She's a descendant of ninjas and
also Natsuki's childhood friend.
They both want to marry me, so things
usually turn out like this...
A fight.
Everyone, please evacuate right away!
Oh, Ai! Thank you!
I'm glad you're all right, Daddy.
Anyways, you should remove those first.
All right.
She's Tsukishiba Ai
An android made by our school's Robotics Team.
I was the one who activated her,
Biological Saline Solution
so she calls me ''Daddy.''
By the way, remember to keep the fact
that you're an android a secret.
So try not to catch others' attention.
All right.
Also, don't call me ''Daddy,'' call me ''Onii-san.''
Okay, Da— I mean, Onii-san.
Good girl.
Next...
Tea's ready.
Oh, okay.
The fight's over, and it's time for tea.
You girls really do get along.
Well, I guess it's because we know each other well.
The class is split into different groups.
I guess attacking by groups would be the easiest.
Okay, I've got an idea.
Yo.
Not again.
Want something to eat? We have a little left.
Well...
I want to eat you.
Wh-What?
You're the best dish here.
What are you talking about?
Quit fooling around.
Fine, i'll let you have me.
Very well.
I'll start with the marshmallows.
Don't say weird things.
But these are as soft as marshmallows.
Getting turned on?
No way!
Really?
Your nipples are erect.
Who the hell would get turned on by you?
Then serve me with your turned-off breasts.
Oh? You can't do a simple thing like
serving, even though you're a maid?
F-Fine, I'll do it.
This is amazing.
Oh no...
It's getting wet. Don't tell me you're going to cum?
What, you don't want it?
No, that's not what–
Then i'll make it even wetter.
It's cold!
No! It sounds so dirty!
It's really slippery.
If you do that...
Master, it's really hot.
I can't stop.
Oh crap, I'm cumming!
You came a lot, Master.
This is just the beginning.
No, don't lick that place!
Wow, look at how wet you are.
What a perverted pancake.
Stop saying weird things.
You're gushing. Does it feel good?
No, it doesn't!
Your tongue doesn't feel good at all!
Your clitoris is really hard.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
It's about time for the main dish.
No!!
You're so tight.
Wow! Master's thing is churning my insides.
I'll shift gears.
I'm in heaven, Master!
All right, Meiri, take it all in!
Give me your milk!
Shoot it all inside of me!
Another down.
All right, I'll follow this flow!
Robotics Team
Ai, you're an android created especially for nursing.
But you don't seem to have any
nursing data stored inside you.
I'll teach you it.
Okay, thank you.
This is a penis
Have you seen one before?
No.
It's in my data, but this is the first time I've seen a real one.
Stroke it gently with both hands.
Move slowly.
Like this?
Good job, Ai.
Now lick it.
Okay.
Your tongue feels like the real thing.
It feels great, Ai.
Onii-san, I'm so happy.
Now, i'll teach you some advanced techniques.
How to use your lower hole to nurse.
Okay, please proceed.
This is...
This hole is well-crafted too.
Onii-san, I feel really weird.
This is the pleasant feeling of sex.
Add that to your database!
Okay.
It's coming in.
A lot of good things are coming in.
Very well, take in more.
I'm full already! There's no more space!
Then this is the final piece!
Recording complete.
Today's competition will sort things
out between the two of you.
But why?
Darling, you're naked!
The one who turns me on most wins.
Let the battle commence!
N-No way...
If you're not going to do anything...
Take this!
Tornado Sucking Technique!
Th-This is...
How lewd.
Natsuki!
What's wrong? Come over here.
O-Okay.
Your weakness is that you're too pure.
You must get used to these kinds of attacks.
Darling, concentrate on me.
Kasumi! No matter what, you shouldn't
stop attacking with your mouth!
You both pass this round.
All right, next is the pinning technique competition.
Darling, your penis is way too stiff.
Kasumi, move your hips faster!
Your enemy won't let you stop!
Kagami-dono, if you do that...
Don't whine.
Massage your own tits to increase your chances of winning!
You must look at your enemy before the winner's decided!
Look at each other!
This is embarrassing.
People are seeing this side of me.
Natsuki, I'm going to...
Kasumi, me too!
I'm cumming!!
You sure are passionate when you
practice by yourself, Chihiro-chan.
The concert is coming up, and I feel really uneasy about it.
But it's no good. I can't play well.
Very well, i'll help you practice.
Play my flute.
Th-That's embarrassing.
If you can play this well, you'll regain your confidence.
And it will relieve your nervousness.
Okay.
All right, use your fingers too.
A soft touch feels great.
Your flute is so stiff.
Use your tongue next.
Okay.
Fantastic.
You've got great skills.
Next is percussion practice.
Okay.
Kagami-san...
The concert has just begun.
It's inside me!
The rhythm starts off slow and gradual.
Wow! The sounds are resounding inside of me!
A great instrumental trio with your
tits! This is a wonderful melody!
No... Such loud noises will...
All right, let's slow down.
It's my first time performing.
And then...
No! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Very well! Let's cum!
And this is the beautiful end to the concert.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm...
Healing.
Healing?
Yeah, Misha twisted her ankle.
Really? Even her hip joint?
Well, umm...
I'm making her feel good so she forgets the pain.
See?
It doesn't hurt! I'm fine now!
Quit fooling around!
You're lying!
I'm not lying.
The pain hasn't disappeared yet.
Mai, come help me.
Good idea.
Mai, come help out too.
Do it for Misha.
So Mai-san, are you licking her well?
Ask yourself first.
Misha doesn't look like she's had enough.
Mai-san, you look pretty relaxed.
Make my penis feel good too.
I guess there's no choice.
You're amazing.
Don't say things that you're not sure about.
Hey, I want to suck your dick too
Okay, switch.
Mai-san, your pussy is beautiful.
Quit staring! Make me feel good.
All right.
Your love juices are overflowing.
No...
Misha, you're skilled.
What's wrong, Misha?
I want this.
All right, put it in yourself.
Wow. It's inside me, Kagami!
No! Not so rough! I'll cum!
Kagami! I'm cumming!
All right, cum!
I'm cumming!!
Well now.
You're next, Mai-san.
Be gentle. It's my first time.
Jeez! I told you to be gentle, but you're so...
Don't worry, you're a strong girl.
Something's coming!
She looks like she's cumming.
All right, it's about time.
Kagami, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
What a beautiful sight.
The girls I conquered are doing what I tell them to.
Hey,
how long am I supposed to do this on my own?
If you don't hurry, i'll cum by myself.
All right, I'll be right there.
Yeah, I'm going to catch 'em all!
Hot!
The fire's been put out.
Will Kazuya fulfill his ambitions?