Meiji Period, Year 44 (1911)
April 9th
Yoshiwara Fire
A huge fire.
Slithering like a monster through the city,
it burned everything in its path.
And then, a beam of light fell from the Heavens.
It was as if a goddess had descended upon them.
So... So pretty!
And when her eyes opened...
From the extinguished flames, a figure emerged.
A light-haired, dark-skinned female:
Douma.
Note: A Douma is an eye demon.
And to the lost and suffering people
of the city, what she delivered was...
a new divine tower!
All of the people fell down before her and worshiped her.
Life Goddess
She was a Life Goddess.
Several Years Later
Now, after this miracle occurred and
the Heaven Tower was erected,
Neo-Yoshiwara still flourishes under her blessing.
The Douma's powerful life-force puts the politicians,
the military, and the nation's elite at her mercy,
allowing her to control all of Japan from the shadows.
Everything is going as planned.
However, one person threatens my
reign, and she must be stopped.
You must find this person.
Her name is...
Seimei!
Abe Seimei
You can't deny your connection to this!
If you let her do whatever she wants,
your reclusive lifestyle won't save you.
I suppose I will have to oppose her.
What a bother. I will have to extinguish
the sparks before they catch fire.
Seimei chose to face her destiny head on, and fight.
What will be the outcome of this epic
battle between Light and Darkness?
Onmyouji: The Sinister Goddess
Lustful Bondage
Chapter One   Indecent Curse
Just a minute, sir.
Say...
wouldn't you like to play with me for a while?
Amazing!
How about this?
I've never had it like this before!
I'm almost... there!
That's fine.
I'm about to cum, too...
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
A parasite deity, I see.
I wish you'd be a little more creative.
Genbu-dono!
Yes?
Good grief.
Such divine energy in a hideous beast like that.
I suppose you think that it was my fault.
But I can't control myself sometimes.
Are you okay, Seimei?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Killing monsters here and there is all well and good,
but this doesn't resolve anything.
I know that.
By the way, what happened to that man?
Oh, he's still unconscious.
I guess we could just leave him.
Seimei!
Hey, she's bleeding!
It seems as though some force has pierced her.
Why is she masturbating in pain?
It's too fast.
Douma...
Seimei-sama, what a lewd display.
True, but no matter what mystic powers
she has, she is still human.
She can still fall victim to that curse.
She will suffer from endless lust until
her very life force is drained.
What a frightening curse.
Penis... I want a penis!
I want a powerful penis to pierce me!
So hot... I'm so hot!
I can't keep this up much longer!
We need a sacrifice to save her.
You idiot!
Don't you realize what "being a sacrifice" means?
Yes, I do.
I will give Seimei my sexual energy.
I might lose my life.
Seimei is nothing but an electric pile of lust right now!
She won't even know it's you!
It doesn't have to be you.
But Seimei saved me so many times before.
It's my turn to save her.
That's not all, is it!?
You're in love with Seimei.
That's why... That's why...
What's this for?
For protection.
You won't be able to wear any clothes inside the barrier...
But, this should be okay.
Byakko...
I'm sorry.
Miyamoto-han...
please come out of this alive!
It's... It's a penis!
A strong, thick penis.
This is what I've wanted!
It's very...
hard.
It's so hot...
and hard.
Seimei...
I can't hold back anymore.
Starting now, I will commence the Sexual Contest.
SEXUAL CONTEST
You will participate. Understood?
Here I go.
That's it!
This is it!
This is what I've wanted!
Good! Very good!
This feels great!
I've never been... this wet... in my life!
It's so hot!
My breasts are so hot!
Here! Take a look.
My rope around you, and your penis inside me!
It's so big and hot!
You wanted to put it inside of me!
That's fine with me!
Do your worst!
Come! Stir up my pitiful insides!
Come on!
What's wrong?
If you stir up my body enough, the curse will be broken.
Yes! Yes, that's right! Very good, Miyamoto!
More! More! Do it harder!
Yes, that's good, Miyamoto!
Give me more! Harder!
What's that?
The Moon energy is weakening. Is there no hope?
What's going on down there?
Miyamoto!
Miyamoto! More! Give me more! More!
So you have returned to us.
In that case, pull yourself together and join our circle of energy!
Okay!
It feels like I'm flying in the sky!
Give me more! Make me fly higher!
G-Good...
It's tickling me...
S-Seimei!
It's so hot! Miyamoto, your semen is hot!
More! Shoot more!
Good! That's perfect!
Why did you stop? My body is not yet satisfied.
I...
I know.
Miyamoto-san looks exhausted.
I wonder if he's at his limit?
Thanks to him the barrier is stable, at least.
But it doesn't look like the curse will be broken any time soon.
As I feared, we may need to cast a spell.
What exactly are you suggesting?
We go to the Heaven Tower and defeat the Douma!
We must not do that.
But Suzaku-san!
She cannot be defeated by us alone.
But what else can we do?
We are not sure that we can even get inside the tower.
But...
Let's continue to watch over them for now.
No, I can't do that.
Seiryuu!
I'm going with her!
Genbu!
Byakko...
Genbu and Seiryuu will most likely fail.
That is why you and I must stay here and
continue to pray for Seimei-sama's life.
I'm with you, Suzaku-neechan!
Are you ready for more? Thrust yourself into me.
So she does keep the place well guarded.
In that case...
let's burst through the front door. 'Kay?
Good idea.
Genbu-dono...
What is it? We're almost at the roof.
The farther we go inside this tower,
the hotter my body gets.
There are slits in the Seiryuu and Genbu tapestries!
Suzaku-neechan! What's happened?
They were probably intercepted.
Miyamoto!
That's good! Squeeze my breasts!
Seiryuu... Genbu... Seimei... Miyamoto...
Seiryuu... Genbu... Miyamoto... Seimei!
Suzaku-neechan, I'm sorry.
I've gotta go there too!
Do not go!
You are walking into a death trap!
Byakko!
Hot!
No...
Stop it.
It's too hot!
Stop it!
I can't move.
That's not fair!
Please, stop it!
Why, you... How dare you do such nasty things to me!
Stop, you bastards!
Stop it! Not there!
I don't wanna...
I don't want you inside of me!
Your voice says "no," but your body says "yes".
Your nipples have sprung up in joy.
And the area between your legs is slippery.
Douma?
What a lovely view.
You two were severely weakened from giving
all your powers to those humans.
But here, you need not hold anything back.
You can let yourself lose control.
There is no need now to follow the rules.
Let the fun begin.
CONTROL
Genbu-dono, are you all right?
Yes, but my body won't obey me.
It's the same for me.
What the hell is about to happen?
Oh, no!
What the hell?
No! It's moving!
It's so very hot!
Shit!
I will not be controlled by this thing!
Leave me alone!
What is this?
It's all sticky.
It feels good...
I didn't want it inside of me.
This isn't what my body really wants.
But if this keeps up...
Those pests again!
Wh-What's that?
Eyes?
No... It's looking at me.
No... No, you can't fit in there!
How disgusting. Stop it!
My insides... It's looking at my insides!
No!
What... What's happening?
Shit!
Seiryuu-san, I can't...
Genbu-dono, I'm losing...
Just stop it!
It's going to tear!
It's no use. My link with Seimei-sama is fading.
It's fading!
We can't help it. We tried our best.
This was our last resort!
Seiryuu!
Genbu!
It's too much for them alone.
Must I go, too?
But...
Ecstasy
What's goin' on here?
Byakko-dono.
S-Seiryuu-han! Genbu-han!
Thank goodness you're safe!
What's the matter, Byakko-san?
You smell wrong.
Don't tell me you...
What's wrong, Byakko-dono?
Just back off.
Even if you're possessed, I don't want to fight you.
Fight?
We wouldn't do that. We wouldn't want to hurt you.
We just want to have fun with you, Byakko-san.
With this...
To be continued