The last word of J.W. Goethe
More light...
More,Light
In the literary world,
Duke Maerk Heimlich helped Goethe
rise to fame as a poet and writer.
It is well known that Goethe modeled
the devil in Faust after Duke Maerk.
But no one knew of the "Onjin" demon behind him.
Note: Onjin means patron or benefactor.
Rebia
And that story remains a mystery even today.
Duke Maerk, you appear to have
drunk too much alcohol.
I seem to have gotten badly drunk
off the wine you made, Goethe.
Ironic as ever, I see.
It's just wine. Don't take it so seriously.
Do you wish to poison yourself intentionally?
Now, don't be so stiff.
Come here. Come.
Oh, a nice unfinished statue.
M Onjin, eh?
"Onjin"?
He's a man much like Professor Faust.
He infuses himself in here and
forces the lines out of me.
So he's a being with magical powers, I suppose.
He was a real person who lived in Frankfurt.
People said that he could fly freely through
the air and unleash all sorts of magic.
And I feel that spiritual energy from him!
So you're still obsessed with
magic and spiritual energy.
I want to close the gap between Man and God.
H-He has infused me.
Ah, the grotesque you is far different from me.
You have been lured to me by my passions!
To think that your sharp fangs
and talons were mocked...
That others called you trash.
What a laugh!
So how much alcohol have you drunk this time?
You've worked up quite a sweat.
This sweat is merely a byproduct of the statue's might.
I'll show the results only to you, Goethe.
An infusion into the mind?
What nonsense.
You're speaking of matters from
the supernatural realm.
Couldn't this be something godly and not witchcraft?
Are you suggesting that Napoleon had to
answer to God during the revolution?
Wh-What is this?
Ouch!
Someone, help me!
Someone, please...
Why? He and his tutor?
Poor dear Sister.
Goethe, my boy, I will give you proof
that Onjin has infused into my mind.
That is not something I would have expected
to hear from an Arcaroid scholar.
It's exactly what Arcaroid would have thought.
My brain is sparkling with stimuli.
Look! What has just arrived will prove me right!
What is that?
To him who has summoned me...
I say this...
I will grant thy every wish.
I am here!
I am here before your eyes!
What's happening?
Napoleon, you shitty old dog!
This is my idea of revolution!
"You shall be set free from your confinement
and welcomed into my heart".
You bloody fool!
So you're the one who summoned me
and wishes to set up a contract.
Or would you prefer a gift from me instead?
No, I want to owe everything to you!
Where have you come from?
From the Far East.
The Far East... The land of the rising sun.
You seem even farther East than
I would have imagined.
Come join me. Then you'll be able to fly for 44 days.
44 days?
Well then, welcome to Leipzig!
D-D-Duke!
I didn't think you were the type of man
to be possessed by the Eastern occult!
Wh-What should I do?
It's so late.
I guess I'll take the shortcut.
What the hell?
I know it's just superstition, but this
place is just too creepy tonight.
Rebiya-sama, do you feel it?
I do. She's disrupting everything.
Do you know whether or not she's a virgin?
I would assume so.
At least by appearance, she is. Correct?
Thank goodness.
No one's here.
What the hell?
Rebiya-sama, your face is...
A virgin's vaginal fluids are pure
energy to a sex demon.
She's so beautiful.
He doesn't deserve her.
And we mustn't let her lose her virginity.
Are you certain?
I'm checking right now.
Sniff, sniff.
There's no smell of a man.
Can she return to her primordial state afterwards?
Isn't it time to isolate her from the darkness?
The primordial state is always ravished.
Darkness brings about the death of peace...
and the sparking of immorality.
Is that so?
Ah, may I help...
Hey! Where are you going?
What?
He's totally gone!
You jackass!
You're fired!
Huh?
This mansion is kind of like a temple.
U-Umm...
Welcome!
R-Right...
Milady can be found in the left wing.
Okay...
Should I leave my shoes on?
Just come in already.
I'm calling the police right now.
Um, what are you...
Idiot Are you a murderer? Or maybe a rapist?
Hey, you invited me here.
Oh, I don't think they'll believe that.
The surveillance camera at the convenience
store will show that you followed me here.
And what's more...
Why are you wearing shoes?
I could let you off if you wanted,
Mr. Slave.
Slave?
Wh-What are you talking about?
You annoy me.
Slaves have no need need to talk.
If you speak, I'm throwing away the key.
Oh my, how cruel.
He'd never get it off.
Clean him off.
I will.
How much longer do you intend to continue?
So you made a pact with this demon.
A thousand years ago.
I am the last of my kind.
A pact a thousand years old...
He must have had very strong spiritual energy.
He's your offspring, after all.
Will you burn the fire in my heart?
All of your desires and wishes will be granted.
Then my heart is at your disposal.
How can you speak such insanity?
This woman is trying to lure you into Hell!
Goethe, my boy.
Don't misunderstand.
She was summoned here by my
wish, in order to serve me.
But she's a demon...
You call her a demon?
In the Orient, her kind are worshiped as gods!
This is so frightening.
He who has summoned me here and awakened
the divine spiritual magic within my body...
My wish is to release you and your powers, Onjin,..
- ...and shower destruction on the world!
- D-Duke! Step away from the witch!
This woman is a witch, you say?
Have you sold your soul to Satan, Duke?
Satan? In the East, he's known as the god "Shiren".
I have merely become an angel of Shiren.
And you, Goethe, are a mere mortal.
O-Oh my God.
Maerk has sold his soul to the devil!
How horrifying!
Faust...
No! Mephistopheles!
Yes. Your words.
Everything which comes from your lips is the truth.
Yes. You have brought everything
to the surface, Rebiya.
You will redefine humanity!
Rebiya?
Rebiya is the strongest aide to Onjin.
We have been summoned by Onjin's mighty
powers to be sent to His guardian star!
What's the matter?
Faust has... awakened.
Faust has?
Did he drink it?
Completely.
Enter.
Smooth skin.
What a nice smell.
Wh-Who's there?
N-No!
Rebiya-sama?
Hatred and jealousy have sprung into motion, I see.
It is the persistent law of Rebiya.
Is it because of Faust's presence?
I know you're there,
bursting with impatience to emerge.
You must be the tutor.
That's strange.
You're acting like this is the first time we've met.
Does it feel good to sleep with my sister's boyfriend?
What are you talking about, my dear pupil?
Wh-What was that? What did you do?
Why not worry about yourself instead?
You're not her little sister, are you?
Who are you!?
Jealousy. Hatred.
All of man's negative emotions.
And you, openly jealous of my sister's
wealth and beauty, are quite honest.
That's why you stole her boyfriend.
Help me!
Someone help!
You like that thing, don't you?
That seems ineffective.
I hope you've made other arrangements.
I have.
Like this one.
You're impossible.
I've improved our storage facility.
I'll lead you there now.
Think of it as a large cellar.
You've certainly improved it quite a bit.
So you like it?
When did you find this place?
About sixty years ago.
Sixty years...
You're there, aren't you?
Show yourself!
Rebiya-sama, you must be
separated from the side gate.
You even made this thing?
I used one of Gaudi's designs as a model.
Did he intend to live there?
I'm not sure. He was a very eccentric man.
Well? How are you feeling?
Do you like it?
You beasts, what are you trying to do?
We won't do anything.
The one that will do something is this man.
You're so lucky.
You get to make two pretty women happy.
What the hell is that thing?
You will be granted pain, not pleasure.
No, don't do this!
Walk straight forward.
Stop it!
Yes. Scream louder.
Louder.
That hurts!
What a beautiful sound.
Scream louder, please.
No! No!
I smell pleasure.
Is she fusing with her primordial state?
Why do you hesitate?
Lord Faust!
The pleasure you smell is a human instinct.
Hatred. Love. Jealousy.
All these feelings, when combined, grant pleasure.
Rebiya...
It seems that the time has come to
tie off this 200-year arrangement.
How much longer do you plan to stay in the darkness?
I'm cumming!
Rebiya-sama, it seems you have finally
fused with your primordial self.
The two hundred years are over.
Really?
It's been two hundred years?
But I've been in this form for five hundred years.
Five hundred years?
Like I said,
five hundred years.
What is that?
Who are you?
The time of wandering was perhaps too long.
When spirits meet and interact in the darkness,
it bears spiritual food for their hearts.
Those words...
They infused into you from Onjin-sama. Am I not right?
The strength of your jealousy
was preserving you, Rebiya.
The last word of J.W. Goethe
More,Light
More light...
Faust
Who was it that rejected that light?