Kagami-san!
Chihiro-chan, you're so wet down there.
Because it feels so good...
Wow, it's gushing.
Kagami-kun, look at yourself before you talk about others.
Your thing is so stiff.
But if Akane catches us...
Don't worry, Kagami-san.
Akane-san will come back late
because she has club activities.
I see.
Let's continue.
The voice has been altered.
Today's club activities ended early.
My, I'm tired.
The voice has been altered.
He's messing around and being perverted again.
Your penis is way too hard.
My juices will flow out if you touch me like that.
My butthole feels so good!
I want your penis next.
What the...
Episode 2 Ambitions Will Expand
I'm Kagami Kazuya.
Currently I'm a student at Shirasagi Academy,
a harem school filled with girls.
Right now, I'm trying to conquer all my female classmates.
I've already done nine.
There are eleven left.
I will fulfill my ambition, no matter what!
Yo, good morning.
Wh-What!?
Can't you see I'm doing morning
practice!? Don't get in my way!
Well, I'm just saying hello.
Sorry. Go ahead.
Akane's the biggest obstacle to my goal
Pantians!
My, I thought I heard a frog croak.
I guess it was my imagination.
She's Kurusugawa Ranko.
Daughter of the world-renowned
Kurusugawa Company's CEO...
and the chairman of Shirasagi Academy.
She solves all her problems with money.
And she laughs like a monarch.
A perfect high-class lady.
Hello everyone.
And the two next to her are Yuki and Saki.
Oh, so it's you, Sagami-san.
Miss, it's Kagami-sarna.
Ranko, you did that on purpose, didn't you!
Oh, didn't you want that to happen, Mogami-san?
It's Kagami-sama.
Yeah, right!
Moreover, why the hell did you come in a helicopter?
How could someone from the Kurusugawa
family walk to school?
Well, if you'll excuse me, Kanami Deathmatch-sama.
Almost but not quite, Miss.
Then what about Kagami Zeami?
That's a bit off.
Then, Lalami.
Good idea.
I'm good.
Now, my next target group...
Lunch-time showtime!
Now, let me, Mizuno Maya, show you a charming time!
Magical Hour
Mizuno Maya. Her specialty is magic.
But because she screws up every time,
she's dubbed the Bombsmoke Wizard.
Isami'san, hand me the smokescreen.
O-Okay.
Her assistant is...
the military geek, Narashino Isami.
Because of her timidity and defensiveness, she
takes out her gun and shoots randomly.
First, with this smokescreen...
Not again!
Be quiet.
You ruined my lunch-time nap.
Ajikata Yoko, a hot blooded chef
who heads the Cooking Club.
But her cooking is terrible.
Answer this question...
What will I do with this grenade?
Oh! You'll blow Yoko-chan up with it!
Correct.
You'll die for sure.
Kusunoki Kozue, the president of the Quiz Club.
She's usually shy, but her personality takes
a 180 when quizzes are involved.
This is Homura Nanoha, a professional at making desserts.
She's always seen with her doll, Baaru.
Always having fun.
Now, what should I do to make the
craziest group in the school...
W-Wait!
...become mine?
Maya, let's practice your magic escape.
Elegantly free yourself from these bonds!
This seems rather tight.
Is this torture?
No, it's just that I used too much strength.
Let me help you.
Hey, Kagami-kun!
No, stop!
Don't do that.
You're still tied up.
Now, let's change the position.
This is so embarrassing.
What are you talking about?
Only by escaping from this position will
you earn the title of a true magician.
This is torture.
Wow, it's sweating a lot.
Onii-chan, no...
Let me lick it clean for you.
Don't lick it.
Man, it's still flowing out. Is this magic?
This isn't magic!
It seems like this will turn into an explosive escape trick.
Maya, will you be able to escape before my bomb explodes?
Th-That's...
That looks rather destructive!
Dynamite Set!
No, don't do that!
What's wrong?
You'd better escape before you're blown to pieces!
But my body is...
I don't care anymore!
Time's up! Here it comes!
No, no! I'm cumming!
Happy!
Isami, did you watch closely?
Y-Yes! That was amazing.
It's your turn next.
Start by cleaning my gun.
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey, what are you doing!?
You'll only screw up my Magnum!
Clean the magazine properly.
Take good care of the gun barrel.
The muzzle too.
That's right. Take good care of your own too.
My body's heating up.
All right. It seems like we're ready.
Let's start shooting practice.
Yes, sir!
Private Isami, how's my shooting?
It... feels... very... accurate.
That must be because of your maintenance.
Next, it's time for the machine gun!
We're going to be suppressed!
N-No! I'm cumming again!
Cooking Club
Is this next?
Yo.
Another cooking showdown?
I'll be the taste checker.
Kagami-han, please do.
Why did it turn out like this?
First, let's check out the taste of the ingredients.
I've never heard of this.
Hormone balance can affect the food.
Therefore we must check out your bodies.
Your nipples are standing up.
Both sets of tits are okay.
Let's check your pussies next.
There?
No, that'll hurt...
Onii-chan, this is embarrassing!
This is for the sake of cooking!
There's no time to complain!
Flavoring is coming from both your pussies.
Hey Kozue, have a taste of Nanoha first.
Her juices are as thick as gum syrup.
Kozue-dono, your juices are as smooth as olive oil.
You sure have a lot of yummy juice.
Your sauces...
will make a good combination with my sausage!
Toulouse sausage!
Use your mouth to clean it first
I smell something nice.
Wow! That sausage looks really good!
I want it!
Your sausage is amazing.
It's clean.
Let me eat it right!
Yeah, I guess it's about time.
Kagami-han, please hurry.
Here, have a taste of top tier sausage.
It's my first time tasting such a sausage!
I've never tasted something like this before.
Let the other two try.
How's the double penetration cucumber?
The delicious juices are coming out.
It's just the right hardness, Onii-chan.
All right, let's make a triple-themed sauce.
Yoko, you're first.
I'm gonna die!
Nanoha, you're next.
You're amazing!
I'm cumming!
Kozue, you're last.
This is a new taste!
It's extremely delicious!
How's the combination of your sauces and my Stamina-X?
It's amazing.
Now your senses of taste are fixed.
Yes, chef!
Nurse Office
Evening of the
Same Day
Ikuyo-chan.
Hey.
What's wrong, Kagami-kun, Lily-chan?
Apparently she sprained her ankle.
Help her check it out.
Just leave it to me.
I'm sorry.
Stretching it a little will make it feel better.
Will it get swollen?
You didn't pull it.
You'll be swollen elsewhere.
Where?
Here.
Hey, help me take care of it.
It feels different than usual.
That's because I'm using medical gloves.
Lily-chan, if you're so eager, come and help out.
It's even more swollen than before.
That shows it has completely recovered.
It's about time for an injection.
How's my injection?
Are you scared? Does it hurt?
I want more! I want more!
Kagami-kun, hurry up and do me too.
Patient first. Nurse later.
I'm already at my limit.
Here I go!
I'm gonna cum... from the injection!
I'm cumming!
How is it, nurse?
It's good! Give me an injection too!
Hey, give me more injections.
I want more too.
I'm done for today. Just leave me alone.
Very well.
Non-chan, do you want to make your gymnastics better?
Yes.
Do you want to become a star in the world of gymnastics?
Yes!
That's why you need this.
Really? But it feels weird.
It's not weird at all.
Non-chan, you're no good at clubs, right?
This is just a drill.
This is a drill?
Yeah, it is. It will help your body feel the club.
But...
using a thicker one is better.
Listen.
Don't change your pose, no matter what.
Yes.
It's your turn to move now.
Yes... Coach, I feel amazing.
Good movement.
Thank you, coach.
This is the finishing move!
Coach, I know... I'm going to...
...to become a star.
Saionji, still studying?
Is there a problem?
There's no problem,
but don't restrict yourself to the desk.
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean this.
Learning through bodily interaction is required sometimes.
What are you saying?
I'll teach you gently.
Don't worry.
B-But...
Relax.
Your body seems to be ready.
All right, let's start our lesson.
As expected, you're even great down there.
Wh-What do you mean?
Try touching it.
Correct, it's hot.
This hot thing is going inside you.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
All right then,
let's begin the honors material.
Okay.
How is it, Saionji? Feeling good?
Yes.
I don't get it, but I'm feeling good.
You've got an A+ pussy. It's amazing.
I'm so happy that you're praising me.
So happy... So happy that I'm...
All right, I'm cumming!
Kagami-kun, I love you.
What? That's a different reaction.
I don't get it.
There's something else I don't understand.
Wagami-san, it seems like the girls in our class
have all become your boogie-woogies.
Miss, it's Kagami.
Miss, it's called being forced.
My, my...
My group tactic has worked out well.
But Akane's still a huge problem.
You seem to think I'll he an easy target too.
I don't.
I won't let you think that.
What are you trying to say?
I want to challenge you.
A sex match.
Very well, then I'll...
Let's begin!
Let me finish.
That feels good, Kurusugawa Ranko.
Where did you learn such dirty tricks?
This is nothing to people of the Kurusugawa family.
Oh, you're going to cum already?
You're as useless as you look.
Cum. Let it all out.
Dammit, I'm cumming!
Miss!
How's my ejaculation?
That was quite a shock.
But I'm not satisfied yet.
Yeah, the real thing begins now.
Miss, that's such a lewd position!
This is nothing.
Mow long do you plan on keeping
me waiting, Kagami Kazuya?
Hurry up.
Fine.
I don't know what will happen to you.
It's so big and thick... It's amazing.
Miss is about to lose her mind!
We must do something.
Resistance is futile!
You two won't stop my attack!
No... I'm going to...
She's really going to cum!
I'm cumming I'm cumming!
Poor thing.
Kurusugawa Ranko's First Loss
Akane.
Sorry, I'm practicing.
I'll be done soon.
Wait for me in the classroom.
Okay.
I love you.
You jerk. It took all my courage to say that.
S-Sorry! I thought I heard wrong.
Did you just say...
Yeah, I love you!
I can't believe I fell in love with an asshole like you!
What's so funny?
Sorry.
I feel the same too.
Really?
What's wrong, Akane?
I know what you want to do.
So I want to do that too.
Don't do that...
My breasts are going to...
You're really... going to lick it.
Oh my God, you're amazing.
Hey, say something.
Kazuya, I'm going to...
Not yet.
Now it's your turn.
I never thought I'd be doing this with you.
Liar. You're dripping down here.
Hey, may I?
Okay.
I'm coming in.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
All right, i'll move.
You're so tight.
That's because your thing is so big.
Really, are you serious?
You know that yourself.
Hey, does my penis feel good?
Yes, very good!
I'm going to use this to conquer the world.
So come and help me.
I'll do anything for you.
All right, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming inside you.
Okay. Cum inside me!
I m... cumming.
Akane, I'm so glad.
I felt really good.
Kazuya, I love you.
Me too.
Akane. Akane.
It all went in.
Yeah, it did.
Thank you, Akane.
I'm so happy.
I prepared for this just for you.
Akane.
Everyone saw it.
Conquest of All Twenty: Complete
We'll all give our bodies to fulfill his ambitions!
But...
He might not be able to do it alone.
He'll be at his limit.
To those who have been watching...
Please come and help us.
Please, help us!
No need!
I'm still good to go!
My battle continues.
Tomorrow, the day after tomorrow...
until my goal is reached.