Bonus Vignette 2:
An Encounter with Captain Fenrir of the Dark.
I can't believe I'm being treated
like this by mere soldiers.
No! I didn't want to be watched like this!
So embarrassing...
But then again, I feel strange...
Vulgar battle maiden! I'll punish you!
Something big and hard is thrusting
into me from behind!
How dare you treat your Captain
like this, lowly grunt!
Your body doesn't seem to mind.
This thick, hot cock...
Is this what I've lost my virginity to?
Even Skuld is getting a chance to fuck me.
My pussy is being pounded by Valkyrie cock!
I'm... cumming...
I'm cumming!
I love your cock.
Please fill my insides up with your milk!
Translation: Equinileon
Timing: Ginfu
Edit: Ryutso
QC: Chaosrains
Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
softsub: торрент иваниваныч