Scarlet
Das Spiel gent weiter
Hiiro no Koku
Episode 4
Damn, what a nice view we've got.
Just look at that.
She's wiggling her hips like she wants it.
What's wrong?
Can't you get up faster?
If you slack off, your toy will fall out.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You're a lazy mess.
If you want us to help you cum, then hurry.
Yes.
But...
I can't take it.
Please.
Right here, let me...
I told you, right?
I'll let you cum over here.
Come.
No!
Don't struggle so much.
The weather outside is nice today.
Stop it.
Please, have mercy.
What if someone...
What if someone sees?
Then let them see.
That gets you off more anyway.
It doesn't.
Come on.
No!!
Don't!
You shouldn't yell so loudly.
Don't you want people to see you?
That's why you leave your
curtains open in the first place.
Doesn't just the thought of it embarrass you?
Come on, flick the switch.
Roger.
No!
Not here.
Please.
If people see you, we'll let you cum.
Tell them all you're begging us to make you cum.
I like that idea.
I...
No!
I-I'm cumming.
– I'm cumming.
– Look.
There are kids down there.
Wow, their eyes are wide open.
It's burned into their memories.
From this distance, they can see
all of your perverted body.
You're just a slut with a hot body,
and you want other people to see it.
You're a masochistic bitch, drowning
in ecstasy from being watched.
Wow, that was awesome.
Wifey's great.
She even pissed herself.
I wish I'd videotaped that.
She really gave those kids a great show.
If she can go that far, she's the perfect pervert.
Just like Shima-san says, she might become
a sex slave sooner than we expect.
What is it? Don't fumble around.
Let's go.
I...
I'm dressed like this.
I can't do it, after all.
How can you say that now?
That won't help at all.
He's right.
I recall you saying that you'd do anything we asked.
Yes, that's right.
After all, you're our slave.
But...
Come on!
Look how soaking wet you are.
You're a hypocrite.
Don't you understand?
You're the kind of woman who likes these things.
You're lying!
You'll understand in time.
Contact the office for me.
Tell Daigashi that we can use her in the club very soon.
Yes, sir.
Well, we'll be gone for about thirty minutes.
Have a nice trip.
I hope you return soon.
The two vibrators are making my
pelvis so hot I can't stand it.
Just walking is difficult.
Walking the streets looking like this...
I'm... throbbing.
What if someone notices?
Maybe someone has already noticed.
I...
They'll think I'm a pervert.
They'll think I'm a slut,
because I'm wearing so little.
I... can't believe how hot I am.
I like this. I do.
What's wrong?
Hurry, follow me.
I can't.
I can't walk anymore.
Please, let me go home.
If this keeps up, I'll...
You really want to go home?
– Aren't you throbbing?
– I'm not!
There's a big park close by, right?
I'll treat you well over there.
No! Not the park.
I can't.
In that case, how about here?
There's no one nearby.
If someone passes by... But I can't...
I can't stop.
Even though I'm in public,
I'm... gonna cum.
I don't care what happens anymore.
Aketa-san's wife...
Well, as you can see,
she can't restrain her passion.
Her husband doesn't know,
but she's a total slut, and she needs it really bad.
When I met her, she was the one who seduced me.
He's lying!
She loves this sort of play.
That's the kind of woman she is.
What do you think?
Etsuko wants you too.
It really gets her off.
Mrs. Aketa...
I can't believe we're doing this in public.
That you're dressed like this.
That you're so hot like this.
That you're such a dirty woman.
Please, don't tell my husband.
– I understand.
– Don't tell...
I understand, Mrs. Aketa.
I understand.
– Please!
– Right here.
Right here, too?
Where are we going?
To a warehouse.
What is this place?
Don't worry. You don't need to be scared.
This is a place for people who want to play around.
The patrons are mostly here to watch, not participate.
Yes.
Right there!
Wow, she's amazing!
Super tight!
Watch me.
Yes.
Right there.
I... can't stand it.
Wow, what a slut.
This is the perfect show.
Awesome.
Excuse me.
I'm here to wash your back.
Why?
Did they ask you to?
Dammit, those guys have nothing
better to do than meddle.
How was the stage?
Very embarrassing.
I was surprised.
Is that all?
I got very hot...
and very excited.
That's an honest answer.
We'll take you there for a while.
Okay?
But...
Oh, this.
Twenty years ago I was in an accident.
That's why I can't use it anymore.
But life is mysterious.
This is the reason I entered this world.
I wanted to make up for my
deficiency by exploiting women.
That's why you chose me?
Yes, that's right.
Etsuko, you still don't know yourself,
the real you.
And I want to awaken that in you.
That's why I brought you here.
You're my apprentice.
I'll make you the perfect woman.
That's awesome!
Well, sit down.
Sit down, I said.
How is it?
How is the face of the customer?
It's very stiff... and very...
You like it?
What's your answer?
You like having a man lick your pussy?
I'm sorry, sir!
What's wrong?
Don't you really wanna piss on his face?
What's your answer?
Please forgive me!
You fucking whore.
Ladies and gentlemen...
I...
I am Aketa Etsuko.
If you ask me,
I'll do anything for you.
I'm a masochistic bitch.
Please...
any of you...
take me.
Take me for the night.
Etsuko's dirty body...
Please...
Please, unleash your lust on me,
and let me relieve it.
So she's a big hit, eh?
These look like very lively pictures.
Shima-san's very intuitive.
A lonely wife who begs for punishment on her own.
I like it.
We've shown her face at the club a lot too.
Either she's used to it, or she actually
likes it. It doesn't matter.
I suppose it's time to move on.
Contact the others.
I want to come along this time.
I want to see it with my own eyes.
Yes, sir.
I can hardly wait.
Hello?
Um, hello?
Is that you, neighbor? It's Aketa.
A-Aketa-san?
I hope you're well.
Huh? Yes.
I'm still at home.
I'll be here all month.
Yes. That's right.
Actually, it's about Etsuko.
Have you heard anything?
I've been calling home, but...
I can't reach her.
Yes, that's right.
So, have you heard anything?
No, nothing.
I don't think you need to worry.
I-I saw her this morning.
But...
I'm sure she'll call you right away.
So don't worry.
Um, hey...
Etsuko.
It's about time for us to leave.
You're coming too.
Understand?
Yes.
I'll come with you.
I'm everyone's slave.
I can't think of a life without sex anymore.
Good.
Boys, give Etsuko plenty of fun tonight.
Yes, sir.
Let's have some fun!
Etsuko...
How is it?
She looks so happy!
You like them both at once?
What a greedy woman?
Very nice!
I love that tight sucking.
Her ass is so tight.
This is awesome, she's so tight.
Please, let me suck more.
I can't think of anything except dicks.
Make me your bitch!
Did you hear that?
She wants to be our bitch.
You've sure changed, wifey.
Then let's give her what she wants.
You bitch!
Cum for me!
Come on, come on, come on.
What's wrong?
You want it, don't you?
Then raise your ass higher.
Front or back? Which do you want?
The back?
How is it?
You like it in the ass?
Yes!
She loves it in the ass, eh?
You fucking bitch.
Oh, it's hitting,
it's hitting hard.
Harder.
Harder, deeper.
– So you get off on this?
– Harder, deeper.
– I want more!
– You masochistic bitch.
You really are a masochistic bitch.
You masochist!
I'm home, Etsuko.
Etsuko...