I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumining
Ever since then...
Ever since then, I've changed.
How's it looking for tonight?
No good. I have to work overtime.
You're lucky, having the night off.
Kobayakawa-kun.
Yes?
What the hell'e with these spreadsheets?
Your calculation on the first line is wrong!
How old are you!?
No grown woman makes such
a simple computation error.
Or so many typos!
Why don't you go back to
kindergarten and learn how to write!?
Yikes.
Hey, Murakami, that chick's getting yelled at again.
Y-Yeah.
I got yelled at again.
Senpai, cheer up already!
Thanks, but I really screw up everything I try.
That's not true at all!
I think the Chief is the one with problems.
He doesn't have to be so hard on you.
Oh, yeah, right...
Here you go, Senpai.
I found an interesting site you might like.
I think it might comfort you a little.
Wh-What the hell?
Amazing!
Stupid Sayaka!
So this is what she meant by "comfort"!
Aw, stupid bitch!
But I'm kind of interested.
What variety!
This one's kinda cute, actually.
I bought it.
I'm home, Mr. Security Guard.
Well, hello there, Kobayakawa-san.
You just received a package.
Here you go.
Th-Thank you.
What? What the hell is this?
It's already here.
It's moving.
It's a bit scary but I did buy it, after all.
It feels great.
Wh-What's this sensation?
I-Is this...
It's still moving!
It's vibrating inside of me.
I'm camming...
I'm cumming!
That was great.
It's such a small thing, but it made me feel good.
It really did comfort me.
If a small thing like this gets me off,
a bigger thing would probably be even more...
I'm so excited.
Oh, crap!
It's already so late!
I guess I fell asleep right after.
If I took this with me, I wonder how I'd feel?
I wonder if they'd notice?
I'm using it right now.
What if they found out?
What would I do?
Hey, you.
What's wrong? You look like you have a fever.
Th-The switch!
Shinjuku, Shinjuku station.
E-Excuse me! I'm getting off!
Hurry, bathroom, bathroom!
I'm soaking wet.
It's still vibrating.
What the hell am I doing?
You again?
You're late day after day.
That just proves you're not fit to be employed.
When will you finally grow up?
I'm sorry.
Chief, I'm sorry.
I guess it's for the best.
So big... I'm gonna cum.
Maybe they've noticed...
...that I'm using it.
If they did...
What would I do?
Kobayakawa-san...
You have another package.
Let's see...
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's heavier than yesterday's package.
What's in it?
A-A very important item.
Good night.
It's so big.
I had the little one inside me all day today, though,
so I should be okay.
I'm already so wet.
It's vibrating.
It's going in.
It's inside!
It's spinning around inside of me!
Huh?
No! Oh, no!
No!
I'm cumming!
Something broke inside of me.
Geez, I can't stop.
I've become...
I've become a slave to it.
What a great sensation!
More. I want more. I want so many different things.
More. I want to feel more.
And... I want to be led to a world of ecstasy.
It feels so great.
Amazing! It's amazing!
Arhive Room
I'm cumming.
I wonder if it arrived today?
Kobayakawa-san.
Mr. Security Guard.
You look very tired.
Yes, sort of...
Well, you shouldn't work so hard.
You got another package today.
My, but they just keep getting bigger and bigger..
Thank you! Good night.
This is... me?
Beautiful.
So this is me.
My whole body is throbbing.
My whole body is pulsating.
My... My insides are being torn up.
It hurts!
More... Mess me up more!
Stir me up more!
Stir me up more, until I break!
I'm cumming!
Something broke inside of me.
She's at it again.
This was the best toy so far.
Adult Toys
This will sell very well.
But I'm surprised a girl like that lives so dose to me.
It's very rare to find a girl...
...who will do things like this.
You really helped me out, Sayaka.