Hey! Wait up!
Good afternoon, president!
You too, Kurihara-senpai!
Serizawa-san, you're early.
Good afternoon!
You're cute today as well, Yumeko-chan.
Please don't tease me like that, Senpai.
How are you feeling today?
I'm good today.
Don't force it, okay?
Sorry about all the trouble I cause from being sickly.
No worries, the vice president is probably absent more.
Manami's such a nice person,
she's just easily influenced by others.
And she can't put herself ahead of others.
But her body is the complete opposite...
Let's wrap it up around here today.
Thanks for the great work, Senpai!
Then let's go home.
Excuse me, I should drop by the nurse's office...
The nurse's office?
Yes, I'm getting some advice about
my body from Murakoshi-sensei.
Isn't there... something strange about Murakoshi-Sensei?
Huh? Not really.
I hope so...
Murakoshi-sensei is a good person!
I've been feeling better recently.
R-Really...
Well, please excuse me. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Yumeko-chan.
Goodbye.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: Anon | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Excuse me.
Hi there, Serizawa-san. How have you been feeling?
Thanks to sensei, I think I've had
fewer cases of anemia recently.
So my special treatment has worked.
That's great.
So, umm...
I've been told that I should receive treatment regularly...
Ah, that's right.
Frail and lewd...
Let's start then.
Yes, thank you.
A man's saliva will stimulate a woman's body.
Has your body begun to feel hot?
Yes, my heart is pounding.
Has your vagina started to get wet?
It's wet...
But why?
That's the proof that your body is being activated.
Is that so...
I want more of sense i's saliva.
Let's give you something even
thicker than saliva this time.
What is that?
It's semen.
Semen? From a guy's penis?
That's right. It's the thickest of all male body fluids.
It has remarkable effect.
I didn't know that semen had such an affect...
There's a place that absorbs
semen better than the mouth.
Let's use it instead.
Where is that?
The vagina, of course.
What?
I'll insert my penis inside your vagina,
so you can absorb the semen directly.
Um, isn't that sex?
No, no.
Sex is for making children, right?
But this is treatment, so it's not sex.
Oh. That worried me.
I've never had any experience with sex,
so I wouldn't know what to do.
Don't worry about it.
This isn't sex, so even if I insert my penis
inside you, you still remain a virgin.
I'm at ease now.
Please pour a lot of sensei's semen inside my vagina.
Okay, hehe.
I've never been like this in front of
a man, it's quite embarrassing.
Don't worry about it.
Please spread your legs so I can
insert the penis more easily.
Okay.
Oh? Are you feeling stimulated already?
My heart is pounding, and it feels hot between my legs.
Is it like when you masturbate?
Huh? Now that you mention it,
it is similar to the feeling when I want to masturbate.
Masturbating also helps stimulate the body as well,
so please do it every day from now on.
Okay, I will masturbate every day.
Good girl.
Well, here we go.
Sensei, it really hurts!
It's the first time you have a penis inserted
inside you, so it can't be helped.
It's a treatment, so please endure it.
If it hurts so much just from inserting a penis inside...
It must hurt even more when my hymen breaks...
Don't worry about it.
When you first have sex with a man
you love, it won't hurt as much.
You know everything don't you, Sensei?
It's great that you came to our school.
Thank me later.
I'll move so I can pour semen inside you.
How are you feeling?
It hurts so much, I think I'll pass out...
It hurts!
It's for your body, so please endure the pain.
Yes. I can do it.
It's coming, so be sure to take all of it.
Can you feel the semen pouring in?
Yes, I can feel it!
Inside me, deep inside... Hot stuff flowing inside me!
Have I absorbed the semen now?
Your vagina was stiff, so you've only
absorbed a little bit of semen.
What?
We'll go on for a little longer.
If your vagina loosens up, your
womb will absorb the semen.
I understand.
Next please.
That's a very healthy reaction.
No problem at all.
Thank you very much.
One moment please.
Sorry for not showing up recently.
Don't worry about it. We're used to it.
By the way, Yumeko is really late today.
She been going to the nurse's office
quite frequently, isn't she?
It feels like it's a bad thing to
be around that man too often.
Yumeko-chan.
Perfect, everyone's here.
Would you guys please go to the gym right now?
Huh?
Welcome!
Did Sensei as for us?
What exactly do you want?
I thought we'd play a game.
Game?
Yes, and I'll call it the Game of Murakoshi!
Sorry, but we don't have time for games at the moment.
This is ridiculous.
Too bad, but you can't run away anymore.
Somebody! He...
I've make it so you can't call for help as well.
What? How did you do that?
Hypnosis, of course.
I've given all of you cues from the beginning,
so the game doesn't get interrupted.
Hypnosis? When did you...
We had a chance to face each other one on one, after all.
Back then!?
I also had the chance to evaluate all the girls here, hehe.
So what do you want with us?
Like I sad, I want to play a game.
The game of Murakoshi!
What kind of game is it?
It's very simple! All you do is answer a quiz.
If your answer is correct, you can go home.
However, if you are incorrect...
If we are incorrect...
You'll receive a punishment!
Just like this!
Yumeko-chan!
My pussy is hot!
Stop this!
Murakoshi-sama, please give Yumeko's virgin
pussy lots of your semen just like always!
If you do a good job as my assistant, okay?
Yes! I'll do my best!
Yumeko-chan... Is this also the power of hypnosis?
That's right. Do you understand my power now?
I've understood that you are the worst.
It must be humiliating to do
whatever a lowlife wants, right?
Well, let's begin.
First off, you there.
M-me?
Yes, Murakoshi-sama. Question one:
There are over 200 thousand camels in Australia.
True or false?
A true or false question!?
You're not allowed to discuss or tell her the answer.
The answer is true, please answer true!
Well?
F-False?
The answer is true.
Well, here comes the punishment!
Please forgive me, Sensei!
It's so hot...
What's happening?
Apparently, there is a childhood friend
she hates, that lives near her house.
I'll keep the rest a secret for the sake of her reputation.
It can't be... No! Don...
The punishment is different for everyone.
Please look forward to it!
Please stop this already!
Well then, who shall be next?
There isn't much chance that
Manami can get the answer right.
I have to protect her...
I'll stay here and do anything you want,
so please let everyone else leave!
Hmm, what shall I do...
Well, why don't we let Sayuri-chan represent everybody?
If you get the next question right, everyone can go.
How's that?
Okay. Everyone's fine with that, right?
Well, here's the special question, ta-da!
Question:
What is two plus three?
Huh?
What's with that question?
We're lucky it's an easy question, Sayuri-chan!
What? A trick question?
If you don't hurry up you'll get marked wrong!
The answer is eight!
Huh?
Incorrect... The answer is five.
Why? Isn't two plus three eight?
Stop joking around!
That's cruel! That's cruel, prez!
Did he make me answer the
question wrong with hypnosis?
What a shame. Well, let's go on with the punishments.
Well, why don't we start with Manami?
Wait! I'll take Manami's punishment
as well, so please let her go!
Sayuri-chan...
Hmm...
I'll do anything, so please!
Well I guess there's nothing to do about it.
Why don't you excite me so I can get hard?
Excite you... What am I supposed to do?
What about a strip show from you, prez?
What's wrong? Won't you do it?
I'll do it.
It's a strip show, so make it more erotic.
As expected from the President-sama.
An excellent performance.
Note: It holds the blood in the penis which causes an erection.
Blood is filling my corpora cavernosa.
Next up, why don't you suck my penis?
That's...
Wouldn't you do anything for your sister?
It's okay, Sayuri-chan. Don't force yourself.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Well, go ahead.
Huh? It's salty. Is this the taste of urine?
That's a half-hearted job there.
Huh?
Don't just lick the tip like that, suck on it lewdly.
Lewdly...
Sayuri-chan was eagerly sucking on me like
a bitch in heat, so i can't help but cum.
Sayuri-chan!
But it's still hard from the anticipation of getting fellatio
from the most popular person in the school,
the beautiful student council president!
And thinking about what's coming up next, hehe.
We're going to have... sex?
Of course!
Turn your ass this way, and get on your knees, okay?
Well, say this:
"It's not much, but please use Murakoshi-sama's dick
to break my hymen, and make me a grown up."
Why would I say something so embarrassing?
Because it's a punishment.
Did you forget about Manami's part?
It... It's not much, but...
Please use Murakoshi-sama's... dick to break my hymen.
And make me a grown up.
Well done. As expected from an honor student.
No!
Oh, you're wet.
Did you get turned on from sucking a dick?
There's... There's no way that's true!
Well then, I'm taking the president's virginity.
It's coming inside me!
It hurts! It hurts!
A penis is penetrating me down there!
My hymen was broken!
It hurts! A penis is moving inside me!
A penis is moving back and forth...
It's rubbing my insides!
It hurts! Sensei! Please stop!
Please take it out!
Well then, I'll just take Manami-chan's virginity instead.
That's...  That's terrible!
The cries of a girl are the best spice for sex!
Sensei! No!
If this goes on... It'll... It'll get torn apart!
Sensei! It's... It's going to break!
No more! I'm going to break!
Help! Help me Manami-chan!
Well, let's pour lots into Sayuri-chan, hehe.
No!
I'll get pregnant! Stop!
It's coming in... Semen is flowing inside me...
That was great.
But now... Manami-chan is safe...
Cock! Cock!
I want a real cock, Sensei!
Manami-chan...
It's too bad, but I've already taught Manami well.
That's...
It's great that Sayuri-chan gave
her virginity to Sensei as well!
The virginity that you worked so hard
to protect has long been gone, hehe.
So cruel...
This is only the beginning of all the fun!
Hehehehe...