You hit too hard.
Geez...
Sorry!
Hey.
I have a weird request...
What is it?
I want to strip naked here, can I?
Strip naked? What do you want to do?
I didn't mean it like that...
I just think the seaside at night is beautiful...
So if I stripped naked, it'd be comfortable...
Mayu-chan...
Sure, do whatever you want.
Really? I can?
Yeah.
But in exchange, you've gotta
let Sakamoto feel good.
I'll take pictures.
Me? Really?
D-Do it here... with Sakamoto-kun?
~ Do You Hate Horny Girls? ~
Episode 2
Mayu-chan, are you sure?
Yeah.
I-I'll start.
Wow... Your penis is twitching...
How does this ieel? Good?
Amazing...
You're so sensitive.
Let me make you feel better.
That's amazing too...
Oh my Cod!
It's so still...
I guess doing it outdoors is more arousing, huh?
What's wrong? Continue.
I'll take a lot of pictures of your blowjob.
That's right. Look this way.
J-Jeez... This is turning me on.
It's so embarrassing...
Mayu-chan, slow down or I'm going to-
Sakamoto-kun, my mouth feels good, right?
Juices are flowing out.
Now then, I'll make you feel good too.
Wow... I'm taking it in my mouth and pus
at the same time in a place like this.
If someone sees us...
My body's on lire... I can't hold back.
Oh crap.
I'm seriously gonna cum.
L-Let it all out, Sakamoto-kun!
Cover my face in your cum!
I'll make you cum as well, then.
Kunio, wow! Oh no, I'm gonna cum...
Please! Do me harder! Harder!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
It's coming!
I'm covered in cum... It's so warm...
J-Jeez! He enlarged them so much!
I won't be able to go to that beach ever again...
Dammit, with her here I won't
be able to stand and read.
That's right, a girl shouldn't be here.
P-Perhaps she's...
Found it.
Oh, so you're another partner of Kase-kun's.
Yeah...
But why did you want to talk to me?
W-Well, I accidentally saw it...
Your pictures.
No...
Not this!
But you like it, don't you?
No way...
At least turn off the lights.
Please be gentle.
Liar.
You want it nice and hard.
No!
No...
I'm weak down there... Please don't be violent.
So you mean you're sensitive.
Yes..
If possible, please turn your head away.
Are you ordering me?
Stop...
You're so loud. It turns me on.
Spare me... Please!
I told you I'm weak down tnere...
No... Stop... Please stop...
Don't take pictures!
Why are you doing this?
Are you really going to take pictures?
Does it not feel good enough?
No... Please...
Wow.
Stop... If you do that...
No... It's coming out...
D-Don't look, I'm begging you.
Please don't look.
It's embarrassing.
No...
Christ, how could you pee yourself at this age?
I'm sorry.
But this is way too awful.
You orgasmed, though.
Because you kept on playing around
with it so I couldn't hold back...
All right. Turn your butt toward me.
No! It won't fit!
You'll rip it in half!
Relax or it'll hurt.
I'm at my limit...
See, it's all in.
It's so tight...
It's so tight inside...
Your pee is still warm, isn't it?
Lick it.
I can't do that...
I wont let go until you do.
What's wrong with me?
I was penetrated and forced to
do something so embarrassing.
And my body is tingling...
Sounds good.
It hurts... Stop... Please stop!
When your butt hurts, your
entire body reacts, right?
If you know, then...
You're so naive. That's what I'm into.
D-Do you really feel joy from bullying me?
Yeah, I do.
The real thing's about to begin.
You're too rough... Slowly, please!
What's the point in doing it slowly?
No... Spare me... It's too tight.
Doesn't it feel good?
No, it doesn't...
Stop... Stop... I'm feeling weird!
What for?
I pity myself, but my body feels so excited...
The two mixed together are...
I'm going to... I'm going to...
Does it feel good?
Tell me how good you feel.
I'm in heaven...
Even though I'm being treated like
this, I feel like I'm in heaven...
It's my first time doing this...
My body is going to melt...
Wow.
More pictures?
You're not going to resist?
You've already done it so who cares.
If I'm all right, take as many as you want.
Yes... Yes!
Yes... Yes... Yes!
What do they call this?
"Home video."
I'm being filmed...
Good answer.
You're way too rough...
Oh my Cod... It's amazing.
I'm going to come inside you.
No...
It's gotten bigger.
Your sperm came out...
I've been filled.
Back then, I was really lonely.
I was cheating on someone but then I left him...
Then Kase-san invited me to do that, and...
Are you still doing it?
Nope. Aside from that time, I've
only done it about twice.
He probably got bored.
R-Really?
I'm still looking for a person.
If I stand there and read porn magazines,
another person like Kase-san might come to me.
Yuuko-san...
Ever since then, my desire for sex
has been growing out of control...
And then...
Reverse flirting play?
Yeah.
You go flirt with random guys on the
street and bring them to the park.
What do you think?
But doing it with a stranger...
Don't worry, we'll be hiding and taking pictures.
We'll come to your rescue if you're in danger.
Really?
Really!
Didn't you say you wanted
to have more daring sex?
Well, I did...
In the end, I couldn't refuse Sakamoto-kun.
Some old man who isn't too strong
but looks really perverted...
U-Umm...
Do you have time to spare?
Umm, what is this?
They're my friends.
After hearing your request, they said
they had to come no matter what.
B-But...
I don't know if I can do this with all of you.
Oh? Didn't you say you wanted to
have sex with different people?
W-Well...
Man, she looks so ripe.
S-Stop...
Sakamoto-kun save me!
So that guy's name is Sakamoto?
He was peeking on us in the
bush so we kicked his ass.
I took his camera too.
Now let's check out your body.
No!
No...
Stop...
No... Don't touch...
Please... Spare me...
Stupid bitch, this is just the beginning.
Ow!
I'll start then.
No... Stop... Stop...
It hurts... How could you put it
in when it's not lubricated...
Take it out...
Take your penis out!
No way.
Y-You're terrible...
Wow, she's noisy.
Stuff her mouth up.
Look, look.
Things are about to get good.
Why doesn't it feel good even though
there are so many penises?
This is completely different than doing
it with Kunio and Sakamoto-kun.
I'm just, feeling pain...
I-I'm about to cum.
You came inside me...
How could you...
That was great.
L-Let me go...
That was enough, right?
What are you talking about?
That was only the first time.
Yeah.
Kunio, please...
Please, no more...
It hurts down there...
What are you talking about?
It's so wet, how could it hurt?
Man, her pussy is beautiful.
No way... They're not done yet?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No... Not inside anymore...
Why not?
It's not like it's your first time today.
No!
Crap!
Wait up!
K-Kunio?
Mayu, are you okay?
I'm sorry that Sakamoto made decisions by himself.
It's all my fault that things turned out like this.
It's all my fault.
Mayu, I'm really...
Kunio!
I just kept on crying.
To be honest, I was at fault too.
That's why I decided to not betray Kunio anymore.
One Month Later
Kunio!
Sorry I'm late.
Oh, that outfit...
Does it suit me?
It's been a long time since I wore it.
I feel kind of weird in it.
Why are you wearing your old uniform?
Well, it was both our fault that things
turned out like that last time.
That's why I plan to start anew.
Mayu...
Y-You know, I'm not wearing any...
...underwear.
I'll do whatever you want to do.
Pull up your skirt and show me your pussy.
Like this?
That's right.
Start touching it.
Okay.
Is this good, Kunio?
Yup, like that.
No... I'm getting turned on...
What's wrong?
We've just begun.
B-But the thought that you're taking
pictures of it turns me on.
O-Oh my God!
Your fingers are sliding in.
No... It's embarrassing.
Don't take pictures of it.
I'm taking pictures of your butt too.
It's coming out...
No... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Spread open your pussy.
How's this?
No... It's like you're looking at everything inside.
It's thick... It's in...
It looks like a dog's tail.
No... It's embarrassing.
The vibrator is going to fall.
Wow... It's inside me...
I'm going to cum again...
Hey, the vibrator is coming out again.
If it drops out, I'll jam it in.
No way...
No, don't do that...
Your penis has gotten so stiff.
I want it now... Right now...
Wow... It's in...
It's huge...
You're really tight.
Oh my Cod...
My insides are moving...
I've gotta take pictures of that face.
No... It's embarrassing.
Are you going to keep these pictures?
These are going to be bestsellers.
I'm sure.
You're sure...?
They're going to be used for masturbating.
Looking at your pictures, the entire
country will cream themselves.
Wow...
Your pictures will be covered in sperm. I'm sure.
They will?
Oh no...
My insides are all filled up...
It's all sticky...
I'm feeling really weird!
Hey, you're way too tight.
That's because your penis is so big.
More... More...
Make me cum!
All right then.
Oh wow ! Wow!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum too...
Cum...
I'm going to cum...
A whole lot...
I'm cumming... Cumming...
Lets cum together...
I'm cumming!
My pussy is trembling...
My body is covered in cum...
Kunio...
I think Kunio and I have always
longed for each other.
Kunw, we're going to be together forever.