Reina, how were the exams?
Don't worry about them, Reona.
Just leave everything to me.
I'll take care of it.
But it's only natural that I'd be interested in my new schoolmates.
Put in more effort.
You guys aren't doing it hard enough.
The most important bit is the encounter.
Show the utmost confidence.
That will draw them in.
Yes just like that.
Onee-sama,
if possible, I'd like a subordinate, not a friend.
Everything has its own priority,
friendship included.
If you start by making friends, it helps a lot.
Really?
All right then.
I'm looking forward to it.
Bigger really is better.
Come on! Do it harder!
Reona, I'll leave the Social Club to you.
Don't worry about that Onee-sama.
DISCIPLINE
ZERO
Part 1
Our school is the way it is...
...because the Morimoto group occupies and rules it.
What a fabulous entrance ceremony.
There aren't many guys at all, though.
Yeah, this was an all-female school a few years back.
Since you like guys so much, you gonna be okay, Yuuki?
Don't worry about me, Nonomi.
If necessary, I'll just treat Otokawa as a guy.
Stop being weird. We just met recently.
I swing both ways.
What!?
God! Where are your eyes?
What's with that attitude? She's rude.
After succeeding as the proprietors of Batlon,
these plutocratic devils are here to intrude on our new school lives.
Seriously!?
Cheers!
Congratulations on Being Accepted
Aoyama, did you see the notice from school?
The one that says, "Dorm dwellers with bad grades will be expelled"?
The new dean is telling us to become members of the upper class.
That means we're in the lower class right now, huh?
This is a once in a lifetime paradise.
Let's go loot whatever we can.
Don't you think Otokawa-san is a bit of an airhead?
Yeah, I guess.
What are you talking about, Kaneda-chan?
By the way, I've got a pretty cool toy.
What's that?
We got it from the nurses office after the entrance ceremony.
They say it's a machine to detect illness.
You've gotta put it in down there.
It'll walk you through verbally.
Just follow the instructions.
We've already used it
It can't be passed on if you don't use it.
Really?
Go inside and try it.
You'll be done right away.
All right then.
Uh... what do I do?
Please put the front of the machine near your vagina.
O-Okay.
Checking will begin now.
Jeez...
What is this?
Please insert it 2cm inside.
This is a weird machine.
We're checking out Otokawa-kun!
You've sure got guts, Akasaka.
Wait, what's she doing?
Why must it go inside?
I can't believe we didn't get here first.
Excuse me, are you guys peeking into the girls' shower?
No! Well...
We won't say a word.
However, in exchange...
Next stage:
Continue to insert the machine deeper.
Check of your inner walls will begin now.
Beginning to collect bodily fluids. Please wait.
The ropes aren't tight enough.
But it feels amazing.
Why are you doing this?
I got turned on after hearing Nonomi talk about it this morning.
I'm just interested.
Well, you see it isn't convenient if girls just do it with each other.
Could you let us...
What do you want to do?
I'm getting wet.
Harder. Don't hold back.
O-Okay.
Oh, God!
Not that rough!
Are you getting turned on?
Look at how big it's become.
N-Nonomiya-kun!
Isn't my pussy all wet and gooey?
More!
I want you to do that harder!
How long have you guys been here?
Kaneda-chan!
Cheapskate!
Kid, show some reaction.
I'm even using my mouth. Make it harder!
Okay.
Dang, it's sticky.
How's this?
You came a lot.
Hey, lick my breasts along with your own semen.
I'm soaking wet.
Nonomi...
Yuuki...
Good!
Suck harder!
I'm cumming!
Yuuki, this is amazing!
I want more.
Now it's our turn.
Does it feel good?
Lick it more!
You've gotta move too.
Jeez!
Move harder!
Yes, like that!
My insides are getting churned up!
It's so deep inside me!
Dammit!
I'm cumming!
Give me all of your semen!
My pussy's on fire!
I'm cumming too!
Onee-sama said to wait for my
schoolmates here, in spite of everything.
It's still a pain in the ass.
That's right.
You just touched my breasts, didn't you?
What?
Don't "What" me!
Quit playing dumb.
You just touched my beautiful breasts!
Wh-What's wrong with you?
You're taking things too far.
You're a disgusting molester.
Are you still going to deny it?
I want to see how long you can last.
Tell the truth.
Come on, speak up!
Look, I found them, Onee-sama.
Good day, members of the Athletic Club.
Welcome to the Social Club.
The gentleman's study group that was originally planned
has been converted into a stamina test.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm the newly elected president of the Social Club.
My name is Reona Morimoto.
You were asking what happened to Ms. Matsuno.
Our club activities have become way too meager.
Henceforth, I'm going to reward you, Ms. Advisor.
Don't you like this reward?
Seems like you guys are having a hard time holding back.
I'll help you relax.
Karen-san, Yuri-san, Momone-san, we can begin now.
Everyone, it's showtime.
The medication is about to kick in.
How am I doing?
Hey you want to put it in don't you?
This is amazing!
Hey! Start moving!
Don't put it in.
Rub it more.
I won't let you into my garden so easily.
Come on, more!
Yes, like that.
Yes, there!
Hey, want to put it in my ass?
Fine then. I'll forgive you.
Amazing! It's all the way inside!
Hey, you came too much!
Your penis is delicious.
Wow!
How's my pussy?
Reona-sama...
I'm really thirsty.
You're only allowed to drink a little.
Leave some for Ms. Matsuno.
But I want to drink it all.
No.
It's to relieve the thirst in her lower mouth.
Amazing, isnt it? It's like you're pregnant.
Oh, lots of things are going to be put inside you.
Look, there are people waiting over there.
It seems like you're having fun.
Since your bottom hole is full,
we'll use your top one.
Hey, it's your turn now.
Just shove it down her throat.
She seems to be enjoying it a lot.
There are even more rewards in store for her.
What are you doing standing there?
Put it in that hole.
That's all for today, I guess.
It'll be your turn tomorrow.
Look forward to it.
Oh, you're a student here as well?
N-No.
I was here on a tour, but I got abducted for some reason.
That's terrible.
You're pretty cute.
I'll let you become my pet.
Pet?
Yes, my own animal.
She's beautiful, but what should I do?
I want to take a pee.
Please excuse me.
It smells great!
Oh, your shoe...
Perhaps school life is going to be more fun than I expected.