When the first spring winds blow and the days
get wanner, its that... time of the year again.
Koume Trading Company
H-Hanazono-kun, excuse me.
but can you grab that tissue?
Y-Yes.
Boss, you have seasonal allergies too? It must be difficult.
It's true, it's annoying.
No, you can't do much about it
They're seasonal allergies after all.
I've only had them since last year, so I'm not used to it.
This season, no amount of tissues is enough.
I... I agree.
Boss, you have it easy.
I'm allergic to both cedar and cypress,
so I suffer from it for a long time.
My little sister has seasonal allergies too, and I heard that...
medicine doesn't help much this year.
That's true.
Oh no, it's cumming again!
It's cumming!
It's harsh on my body.
Boss, we might need to get an air purifier.
It seems that the number of people suffering from
seasonal allergies is increasing every year.
Hanazono-san.
Yes?
C-Can I accompany you to the
meeting with Shoji-san later?
If you want but I can go by myself.
Thanks, but you don't have to.
If someone is gonna see all of it,
I'd rather have it be someone I know.
I... I understand. Ohmiya-san, you have it rough.
It's true. It's so bad that I can't wear panties these days.
Allergy season sure is troublesome.
Pollinic Girls Attack!
Let's Be Erotic Everyone Let's Do It
It happens every time.
I heard it's somewhat bad this season, but it's realty bad.
Omiya-san is holding it in with it so much
that her nipples are getting hard.
Two at the same time...
It doesn't go away, even on a train.
You shouldn't hold it in too much.
A maid?
Amazing, even her ass.
It's not something that goes away by being self-conscious.
You should make the best of it and enjoy it.
H... how?
You'll be ok.
Everyone gets sticky and gooey.
For some reason, it feels good... when others are watching.
I can't hold it in any longer!
No... if you do that any longer...
A Amazing. I didn't know it gets so big. Is it because he's young?
I... I can't...
I'm sorry, are you all right?
Yes... I'm fine.
It's thick... and it smells so strong.
I'm hopeless, I just embarrassed myself there.
So your name is Otani-sama?
If you can, can I have some of your time tomorrow?
Um, who are you?
I've had my eye on you for a while.
Pollinic Girls Attack.
How is it, Rui-sama?
G-Good...
You're doing good, Sally.
Thank you.
This seems big today, so you need to get wet early.
I know.
How are you doing over there?
Yes, I'm ready over here.
Then let's get started, Rui-sama.
I'm ready. Do it
Yes, I'm putting it in.
It's big!
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, keep moving.
Y-Yes.
It feels good. Keep going.
Yes.
Amazing, it goes in so far
Rui-sama, don't be so rough.
Sally, can you come here?
But Rui-sama...
I'm feeling good. I might be able to orgasm today.
Understood.
I think I made a mistake by introducing this to you.
Rui-sama, I'm ready.
Come here quick.
Don't let me settle down. Hurry!
I'm putting it in. Relax your muscles.
How does it feel, Rui-sama?
I feel the friction inside... and... it feels good.
It feels good for me too!
Mayu-sama, I'm about to...
Wait hold on! I'm not ready.
Again, I failed to orgasm.
Why can't anybody get me off?
No, her motions were first-class.
It's your fault.
Sally?
I've been watching you have sex for a while, and I
know what's wrong now... why you can't orgasm.
W-What is it?
Your heart's a virgin.
You haven't opened up your heart to a man.
My heart's a virgin?
I have an idea.
Impressive. I've heard about this place before.
I've noticed that there's no pollen in the air.
Yes, our air filtering system is perfect.
Hey, I'm not sure why I was called
over to Emadclla's house.
I'll be explained to you later.
Otani... I mean, Otani-sama.
Please take my heart's virginity.
Emadella, what's this about?
Sally, why did you have to pick a virgin who I know?
I see him all the time, so its awkward.
It's because virgins show more sexual interest
How do you know I'm a virgin?
Just by looking at you and your reaction.
Just b seein me naked?
Why are you looking at me like that? I can't help it.
Otani-sama, I know this is sudden,
but I want you to save her.
Save her?
She never had an orgasm.
So Otani-sama, please help her.
Why me?
You think of her when you masturbate,
so this role is perfect for you.
How do you know that?
Otani, really?
Whoa, she smells so good.
Were you imagining me when you masturbate?
Yes, Emadella.
The fire is lit. Oh to be young.
Otani, do you feel my breasts?
It works better when you squeeze it tighter.
How's this?
Oh no!
I'll cum!
You're lively.
It's so thick and hot.
Here, you have to open up wider, or else he can't see.
Sally, don't open so wide.
Otani-sama, you'll be putting it in
here, so take a good look at it
So this is yours, Emadella.
Don't...
By the way, I secretly recreated her
hymen, so I'm sure you'll enjoy.
I didn't know!
Hymen? So I'm the first?
S... Stop!
Hey, isn't that enough? I'm embarrassed.
Emadella, it's really pretty.
Otani...
I don't remember a dick being so delicious.
Emadella, don't stop.
I know!
What's going on with me? Something's wrong.
My body's getting hot.
I'm gonna cum!
It's a lot!
I'm... gonna be... violated for real.
Don't worry Emadella, I'm all right I can still go longer.
What?
How? He came twice already!
I'm gonna put it in now.
I'm gonna be violated.
I'm really gonna be violated by a man!
Ow! It hurts!
Emadella, Emadella...
Please! Be gentle! It hurts. It really hurts.
He forced his way through my hymen...
and he's going in deeper.
I'm cumming!
It's in deep!
You two are still doing good.
Rui, I'm cumming!
Please, just forget it!
Not yet.
Rui, you still haven't orgasmed yet.
Rui, I'll make every part of your body orgasm.
My brain isn't operating anymore.
It seems like there's nothing except his dick and my pussy.
I feel it now.
I feel his presence beyond his dick.
Beyond that... Beyond that, my heart is there.
I'm cumming. My body's cumming. Something's cumming!
Rui, I can't hold it.
Don't worry. Let it out.
Let your gooey cum flow into my pussy.
I came! I came! I've cum!
So this is what it means to orgasm!
It's so glorious!
I'm happy for you, Rui-sama.
Otani...
If I come visit I won't have to worry
about seasonal allergies.
Yes, you can be my orgy-pet and my friend.
O-Orgy pet?
Rui-sama, you didn't know?
For now, lets leave them as they are.
Pollinic Girls Attack.
Are you ok, Omiya-san?
I'm sorry, Hanazono-san.
Get it together. We're almost at the station.
What's this? What's going on?
Hey, big sister.
Aki-chan?
What's up?
Are you on your way home?
You have gooey stuff all over.
I can't help it this season.
Men who have seasonal allergies
are letting stuff out of their dicks.
Then there are girls who give in to seasonal allergies
and have orgasms and want to be seen.
This place is always like this at night these days.
I'm getting it again!
Hey wait Aki-chan...
S-Stop It.
Don't worry.
I'm used to it.
It seems like your friend has it worse.
Now that you say it...
No! I'm losing feeling in my body.
Don't do it so strongly.
Everyone's watching.
It's so embarrassing to have everyone watching.
Please stop it Stop taking pictures.
Huh?
Oh no, my body's getting hot
Am I feeling it?
This season's cedar and cypress
pollen is going away this week.
However, it seems that ragweed pollen is spreading.
Watch Out For Ragweed Pollen
Please be careful when you go out.
Koume Trading Company
Hanazono-kun has ragweed allergies?
She's the first in our department.
That seems harsh too. It's hard not to cum.
Hanazono-san...
Why is it just me?
Hanazono-san.
Omiya-san.
I can't just watch.
This is all I can do. I won't let you be embarrassed alone.
Omiya-san.
Oh no, ragweed pollen is spreading!
They're putting it in...
Hanazono-san, I won't let you be exposed alone.
Stop it.
Why is the pollen dick so big and hot?
I'm starting to feel better too.
Seasonal allergies...
This shows that I'm human.
I feel... a little bit better.
To Be Continued...