Onii-san.
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sofia Alexeyevich
Personal Data
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Lost Virginity
Karte   no.2
Withering Purity
Chiharu!
O-Onee-chan!
Do you want to become a masochistic bitch as well?
Come, I'll train you gently.
I've only started touching you
and you're already this wet?
Naughty, aren't you?
Don't worry, I love naughty girls.
I'll tease you much more.
I can't take it anymore...
Don't look. I'm going to cum.
No, don't stop.
You shouldn't cum so quickly.
I need to tease you even more.
No, I'm going to cum...
I-I'm going to cum!
Don't tease me like that.
Please let me cum.
My, you're such a naughty girl. I like you.
I'll tease you even more.
So I can't let you cum just yet.
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum!
Please, let me cum.
How cute.
But no, you can't cum just yet.
I need to tease you even more.
You need to last the whole night.
Why... Forgive me.
I... I-I'm going to cum.
No, don't pull out.
I'm... going to cum. I'm going to cum.
Don't... Don't pull it out.
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
Don't stop. Please let me cum.
Not yet. I can't let you cum yet.
I need to tease you even more.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
No... Please don't tease me.
Please let me cum.
I'm begging you, let me cum! Please let me cum!
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Bad girl. Didn't I tell you?
It is okay to masturbate, but you cannot cum.
But I couldn't take it anymore.
Such a naughty girl.
Even though you haven't cum since last night...
However, you are not allowed to
cum without my permission.
Yes.
Good girl. I'll suck you as your reward.
Stick your tongue out.
Stick it out more!
Pop idol Sophia-san was admitted into the hospital today.
Her management has disclosed that, although the
sickness is unknown, she is in a very serious condition.
It will be difficult for her to return
to the entertainment industry.
Hey, why are you doing this, manager?
I'm sorry, Mariel.
Recently, the company's been in a slump.
We have sold you.
You sold me? What do you mean?
Someone signed a contract for large sums of money.
That's impossible.
If I go missing, my fans would notice.
Don't worry, Mariel.
In a few weeks, you'll be pronounced
dead due to severe illness.
Farewell, Mariel. Take care.
Wait, manager! Manager!
No, don't!
No!
Chisato-kun, please massage her mouth.
Yes.
Mariel Regan
Training Initiated
Breast & Nipple Sensitiviti UP
Clitoris Circumcised & Size UP
Ass and Mouth Sensitiviti UP
Mariel Regan
Training Initiated
Breast & Nipple Sensitiviti UP
Clitoris Circumcised & Size UP
Ass and Mouth Sensitiviti UP
Mariel Regan
Training Initiated
Breast & Nipple Sensitiviti UP
Clitoris Circumcised & Size UP
Ass and Mouth Sensitiviti UP
Mariel Regan
Training Initiated
Breast & Nipple Sensitiviti UP
Clitoris Circumcised & Size UP
Ass and Mouth Sensitiviti UP
Mariel Regan
Training Initiated
Breast & Nipple Sensitiviti UP
Clitoris Circumcised & Size UP
Ass and Mouth Sensitiviti UP
Request for Traning
Shinozaki Saeko
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Saeko!?
You caught me off guard last time with
the scoop about political corruption.
This time, your mouth will pleasure me.
Hey now, your sister is much better at this.
Suck on it more, I'm about to cum.
Don't leave a single drop. Make sure you swallow it all.
I want to cum.
Please... Let me cum.
No, you can't cum yet. Bear with it.
I need to tease you even more.
Chisato-san.
Yes.
The politician in room 301 is looking for you.
Your sister just went.
Don't forget to prepare the double dildo.
How could you...
No, what are you...
Don't put it in there.
It's just so intense.
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum.
What, you're cumming already?
My, you're just as useless as your sister.
Don't say that.
I can't take it anymore!
No! I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!
C-Chiharu!
Aren't you late?
Hurry over here, I want to see you lesbian sisters.
Yes, Master.
You must be feeling good, Yuri-san.
Your owner has come for you.
I'm begging you, my breasts are getting so full they hurt.
Please squeeze my breasts.
Very well, I'll milk your breasts dry.
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Magnificent. Such wonderful breasts you have.
From now on, I'll milk you every day.
Congratulations, Yuri-san.
You're discharged.
You'll receive much love from your owner from now on.
For sure, come meet me for sure!
Come marry me for sure!
Yes.
Once the war is over, and there is peace.
For sure.
Sheesh...
Sisters doing such naughty things.
Have you no shame?
Onee-chan... No...
I'm... I'm going to cum again.
Chiharu, I'm also... also going to cum.
I'm going to cum.
Together... Let's cum together!
But, I can't take it anymore.
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
Onee-chan!
Chiharu!
Onee-chan...
Chiharu...
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Cow
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Request for Traning
Shinozaki Saeko
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Request Denied
I'm waiting for a person.
He is a person who protects lives, a soldier.
She has become more sensitive.
Her nipple sensitivity has risen as well.
The clitoris has also increased in size.
Now then, I'll check the sensitivity.
Chisato-kun, insert the dildo into her mouth.
Yes.
Chisato-kun, pressure will be applied
to the dildo when you reach orgasm,
causing the semen inside to be ejected.
Now, Chisato-kun, let her have your semen.
Yes.
I'm going to cum. I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Mouth sensitivity has upped as well.
I've made a promise with that person.
When the war is over, and there is
peace, he will come and marry me.
Hey now, that just won't do.
Change positions.
Now, enjoy yourselves until you cum.
So? Rare, isn't it?
The two masochist bitches are sisters.
They're both so naughty,
that they'll become wet with the slightest touch.
They're very harmonious.
Even when they orgasm, they do it together.
Onee-chan, I can't take it anymore.
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum.
Chiharu, no! Don't cum yet.
Together, together with me...
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum too!
Together with me Chiharu. Together...
Chiharu!!
Onee-chan!!
Interesting, isn't it?
The little sister pees as she orgasms.
Alright, I've decided.
I'll take them both.
Thank you very much.
Alright Sofia, sing for me please.
When we meet again
What's wrong, Sofia?
In the town we both left,
Expose your breasts and dance.
I waited at the usual street.
Wonderful. Her nipples are pierced as well.
Even though you finally visited me,
It's so sexy.
the two of us...
Sofia, sing properly! Dance!
What's wrong? Don't mind it, just sing.
The gentle times...
I can't.
Sofia, sing!
While I was saying good bye, I realized
something important...
No, I'm going to cum. I...
I'm cumming!
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Love Bitches
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
2nd Request for Traning
Shinozaki Saeko
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Second request for training?
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Searching DATA File
Sing, Sofia!
When I'm by myself, in the city everyone left.
It feels different than before...
Her breast sensitivity is pretty good.
No!
The nipple sensitivity is great as well.
Her vaginal contractions are excellent.
If you keep on moving like this,
I'll... I'll...
Now then, how is the clitoris?
Don't!
The sensitivity is good.
The size is just right.
No! I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
What is this place? Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
You were requested by one of our clients.
We're only the ones entrusted to your training.
My training?
Don't you get it? We're training you to be sold.
We'll make good money training you.
That's a lie!
It's fine if you don't believe me.
I'm going to examine the product now.
Your breasts are quite flexible.
No, please stop it!
So, how is it down here?
No, don't touch me there!
Look, you're wet already.
You're very sensitive.
Your clitoris is hardening too.
No!
I'm... I'm...
Oh my, you're cumming already? That's fast.
Oh my, you really came, didn't you?
How cute.
You're very beautiful.
I didn't think the ropes would suit you.
Please, don't rape me.
I know that you want to save your
virginity for a special someone.
Don't worry, I'll use the other hole.
It hurts!
You've over-exaggerating. It's not even all the way in yet.
Shall I make you feel even better?
You should be about ready.
Well then, I'm going in.
Please, don't play with my butt.
It's sad that you only feel pain.
Let me make you feel better.
Don't, if you tease me down there, I'll...
Oh my, you're cumming again?
You sure are useless.
Don't say that...
Well then, then be my guest...
I can't take it anymore.
I'm...
Slave Canary
Sofia
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Canary
Sofia
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Canary
Sofia
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Slave Canary
Sofia
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
2nd Request for Traning
Shinozaki Saeko
Training in Progress
Aini-kun!
No!
Aini, you bitch!
Minako...
Don't worry, this will only paralyze
your limbs so that you can't move.
What are you planning to do, Aini?
Strange hearing that from you.
I'm just taking care of a request which
you denied, isn't that right?
Aini...
You like her don't you?
That's why you refused the request.
Don't worry, I knew you liked her, so I left her a virgin.
You bitch!
That's right, it's that expression!
That's the angry expression I wanted to see on your face.
Mina, what are you doing?
Who would've thought your penis would be so energetic.
You sure look excited.
Well then, shall we get her to lick it for you?
Lick it?
Use your mouth to make love to his penis.
No! I can't do that.
If you don't, I'm not going to stop doing your ass.
No! Stop torturing my butt.
So you'll lick it?
I understand. I'll lick it.
Saeko...
Alright, use your tongue to lick it.
Stop it Saeko... Stop it!
This is great! This troubled expression!
It's exciting to watch.
Now, take it with your mouth.
Stop... Stop it Saeko.
I'm going to be your bride when I grow up.
I'm waiting for someone.
He is a person who protects lives, a soldier.
Saeko!
Saeko...
Saeko!!
Please, don't rape me.
I've decided that my first time will be with the soldier.
Anywhere but there! Let me go...
Let me tell you something good:
Your precious soldier is this man here.
That's a lie. That's...
It's no lie. Isn't that right, Jack?
No!
Isn't it great, Jack? You wish came true.
Let's go, I'll love you again, all night long.
Saeko, for 13 years, I haven't forgotten about you.
But I've killed dozens people in the war.
I couldn't bring myself to marry you
with my bloodstained hands.
I've decided that I would protect you from the shadows.
But now... now that we're finally together again...
I'll never let you go!
We'll be together forever from now on.
Saeko, listen, I'm going to cum.
Inside you...
Saeko!!
Come Saeko, let's spend every day together from now on.
Let's make up for the 13 years of lost time.
Saeko, why...
I don't know why I am here,
or if you're really the soldier from back then.
All I know is that I've been violated.
I'm no longer the person I was before.
There is no going back to that place anymore.
Sleep, and let go of everything.