Chisato-kun, bring the anal pearls.
Yes.
Chisato-kun, prepare the piercings.
Congratulations. This will make you
a splendid masochistic bitch.
It will be lovely. You will be treated
nicely by your new master.
Lost Virginity
Karte   no.1
The Monster in White
Mary Marceau
Personal Data
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Bitch for Raising
Mary
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Bitch for Raising
Mary
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Bitch for Raising
Mary
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Bitch for Raising
Mary
19 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
No wonder you're the most well known slave master.
You pierce them when they're horny,
then make them orgasm through pain,
turning them into masochistic bitches.
What a surprise.
Right, Chisato-san?
Speaking of which, Chisato-san...
You were trained the same way, right?
You always keep a vibrator inside
so your panties are all wet.
You enjoy it when I pull on your nipple rings.
Chisato-san, you've become a
masochistic bitch too, haven't you?
Dr. Aini, I won't be able to take it anymore
if you keep teasing my nipples like that.
Don't worry, I'll treat you well.
What a shame, they're calling for you now.
It's the politician in Room 301.
All right, Chisato-san. Let him take care of you then.
Yes, please excuse me.
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Customer File No.157
Slave Conditions
Breast: ≥90cm
Married, Age 20~30
Special Conditions
Lactation Capable
Searching DATA File
Houjou Yuri
Personal Data
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
(Married)
This is the new patient?
A soldier... Wasn't she your former officer?
What a shame... He'd be such an
amazing man if he weren't impotent...
Finally, this is the place where
all the politicians are hiding.
I never thought that this would be
the place where my sister works.
What a scoop! The politicians are having
oral-sex with the nurses in the hospital.
I'm about to cum. I demand that
you orgasm together with me.
I'm cumming. Swallow it.
Swallow it. Every single drop.
What's wrong. Did you have an orgasm?
Y-Yes.
Onee-chan!
I drank all Master's delicious milk and had an orgasm.
Now, stand up and show me your slutty body.
Yes.
With a dildo in your vagina and rings on your nipples,
do you really want to be teased that badly?
No, Master.
If you keep doing this, I'll... I'll have another orgasm.
Really? An orgasm right after another?
You really are a bitch who knows nothing about restraint.
B-But... I can't take it anymore...
It can't be helped.
In exchange then, be sure to tell me when you orgasm.
Yes! I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to cum!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Why? How could my sister be doing these things?
But... she seems to be enjoying it so much.
Take off your wet panties, spread
your legs and show me your ass.
Yes.
Now, take Master's big dick.
Well, how is it? Master's dick is inside you.
It's big and hard. It's delicious.
Is that so? Now, here's your reward.
Don't, Master! I-If you keep banging me this hard...
...I'll have another orgasm!
Onee-chan... I-I feel so strange...
It feels good somehow...
Master!
I'm...
I... I can't...
Onee-chan... I'm... I'm...
I'm cumming!
Onee-chan...
You bastard! What kind of pleasure do you
get from doing this to your former officer!?
None really.
It's just that the request from our client
was a married woman with large breasts,
and it you happen fit the bill.
Don't screw with me! What the hell do you want!?
Stop it! If you do this, I'll never forgive you!
What are trying to do?
Hey... What the hell is that?
An aphrodisiac which will make your
breasts and nipples more sensitive.
No, stop it!
No!
Don't!
It seems like this is ready too.
Stop it! No!
I'm going to have you put this on.
No, don't make me put that thing on! Please!
Don't... do this... No... Stop it...
Stop...
The vibration level is at the lowest setting.
Please bear with it for the night.
Wait! You weren't this kind of man before!
What happened to you after you left the army?!
I want to be your bride when I grow up!
Why'd ya take me here?!
Untie me right now!
Kunisaki Chiharu
Personal Data
I just found this place by accident.
What do 'ya want with me?
Kunisaki Chiharu
Personal Data
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Related Kunisaki Chisato
Training (Done)
Also, what the hell did 'ya do to my sister?
Say something!
Tell me why the hell did 'ya change
my sister into that kind of person!?
No!
What're 'ya doing!?
What're 'ya doing? Stop it!
No!
No, no! Please stop this!
It feels good when your tits are all tied up, right?
Not at all!
Is that so?
But your nipples are hardening,
as if they're trying to say otherwise.
That's not true!
Your sister has been trained into a masochistic bitch.
A masochistic bitch?
Like this... with your breasts tied
up as they're fondled and teased.
It hurts!
This kind of nipple torture turns pleasurable.
Your sister's nipples are already pierced, you know?
Would you like to give it a try as well?
No! I don't want to!
Oh? Who was the one watching
her sister perform lewd acts...
...while masturbating and wetting herself, I wonder?
T-That was...
Just like your sister, I'll make you
into a masochistic bitch as well.
No, that is...
Ah, you're wet already?
No...
So then, was that your piss?
No, don't rub it or I'll... or I'll...
Have another orgasm already? You're tied up now.
How is this? It feels good to be teased, right?
What a cute girl.
Oh my, you wet yourself again.
That's no way for a bitch to behave.
I'll have to train you well.
Flowers...
Would you like some flowers?
Would you like...
Mr. Soldier!
It seems you're enjoying the piercings I gave you.
Since you're been behaving yourself so well,
I suppose I should give you some sort of reward.
Well? Delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it tastes wonderful.
Then be my guest, keep licking it.
Okay, enough of this.
Turn around and face your ass towards me.
No, not like that!
If you want the reward, raise your ass more.
Y-Yes.
Good girl, here's your reward.
Oh my! You're still a virgin but
you're getting horny already?
I'll have to make it even better for you.
If 'ya keep on moving like that, I'll... I'll...
Oh? You're cumming already?
I guess it can't be helped...
Well then, make sure you scream loudly when you cum.
Yes!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!
Oh my... You pissed again?
What a useless bitch.
Do you want be trained again?
Yes, please train me into a masochistic bitch.
"Sleep and let go of everything."
Those were the kind words my mother
would say to me when I couldn't sleep.
Your mother must be a kind person.
How was it?
It's been a whole night, so you must
feel pretty good right now.
Please, I can't take it anymore. Please untie me...
And what do you plan on doing if I until you?
Well...
Chisato-kun, massage the patient's breasts.
Y-Yes.
No, don't put that on me again...
Please stop, if you touch my breasts now, I'll...
You seem to be enjoying it...
It seems your sensitivity there as gone up as well.
Please don't pull that out of me.
Chisato-kun, prepare the double dildo.
Yes.
What is that?
A drug that will allow you to produce
exceedingly large quantities of milk.
Once injected into you, the effects will be amazing.
No! Don't do it!
Houjou Yuri
Training Progress
Breast Sensitiviti Up 60%
Lactation Injection (Done)
Houjou Yuri
Training Progress
Breast Sensitiviti Up 60%
Lactation Injection (Done)
Houjou Yuri
Training Progress
Breast Sensitiviti Up 60%
Lactation Injection (Done)
Houjou Yuri
Training Progress
Breast Sensitiviti Up 60%
Lactation Injection (Done)
Kunisaki Chiharu
Training Progress
Nipple & Clitoris
Piercing (Done)
Masochistic Bitch 89%
Kunisaki Chiharu
Training Progress
Nipple & Clitoris
Piercing (Done)
Masochistic Bitch 89%
Don't...
Kunisaki Chiharu
Training Progress
Nipple & Clitoris
Piercing (Done)
Masochistic Bitch 89%
Kunisaki Chiharu
Training Progress
Nipple & Clitoris
Piercing (Done)
Masochistic Bitch 89%
Kunisaki Chiharu
Training Progress
Nipple & Clitoris
Piercing (Done)
Masochistic Bitch 89%
Related Kunisaki Chisato
Training (Done)
Well? Don't you think the new patients
I've selected go pretty well together?
What? You're still keeping that inside you?
That was for the patient a while ago.
Then, why didn't you take it out after the treatment?
This shows that you are not satisfied, right, Chisato-san?
Yes, you're right.
Hey, can I go to the next patient with Chisato-san?
Fine.
Please...
Did you wait long, my cute little bitch?
I've brought your senpai here.
Now it's her turn to serve you some.
You can ask her to teach you some techniques.
Onee-chan...
I'm the masochistic bitch, Chisato-san.
I will do my best to serve you. Please accept me.
Come on, Chisato-san.
Show this bitch how to make your
master happy in the future.
Yes.
Master, I'm here to serve you.
This is the urine from your master.
What will you do with it?
Interesting, isn't it? This bitch pees
a lot when she gets excited.
She still needs more training, you see?
Now Chisato-san, use it on her.
Yes.
Now, we don't need this anymore.
Onee-chan...
This... This voice can't be...
Chiharu!
What a touching moment, seeing you
two slutty sisters reuniting, isn't it?
Please, let my sister go!
I'm sorry, but your sister is beginning to enjoy it...
It can't be...
That is...
Be my guest, this is a reunion of two sister bitches.
Here's a present from me.
Onee-chan...
Chiharu, I'm sorry!
It's alright, Onee-chan.
Onee-chan... no...
If you keep on doing me this hard then, I'll... I'll...
S-Sorry, Chiharu... I can't take it anymore either.
Onee... Onee-chan, at least let us... cum together...
I'm about to cum. I'm going...
Onee-chan...!
Your breasts are extremely sensitive now.
Now that you're producing more milk,
the treatment is almost complete.
Please, stop this... If you keep teasing me,
I-I'm going to have another orgasm.
Fuck me with your penis, please...
No, you can only have an orgasm with your breasts
being fondled for the training to be complete.
Why...
How could this happen...
No... No, I'm...
I'm cumming!
Congratulations, it is done. All you need
to do now is wait for your master.
I want to be your bride when I grow up!
"Sleep and let go of everything."
Cow for Milking
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Cow for Milking
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Cow for Milking
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Cow for Milking
Yury
28 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Bitches for Fonding
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Bitches for Fonding
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Bitches for Fonding
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sister Bitches for Fonding
Chisato: 20 Year Old Bitch
Chiharu: 18 Year Old Bitch
Training (Done)
Sofia Alexeyevich
Personal Data
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
Height
Weight
Bust
Waist
Hip
Age
Real Name: Mariel Regan
What a pair of masochistic sister bitches!
I bet they could be sold at a very high price.
Do you want to become a masochistic bitch as well?
Come here, I'll train you very gently...