My father passed away when I was five.
It was in a car accident.
I didn't know what was going on.
So I tried to wake up my “sleeping” father.
My mother gently, but strongly, hugged me.
And she told me that my father had gone to another world.
Because I was only five, I didn't understand
the real meaning behind her words.
But seeing my mother cry, the same mother who
always used to smile next to my father...
That made me cry.
Then my mother gently patted my head.
In place of the big strong hand of the father I loved...
Were her soft and gentle fingers.
From that day on, the warmth of her hands was everything to me.
My mother lost both of her parents at an
early age and had no one to rely on.
My father's family was actually rich,
but since they had eloped without permission,
no one reached out to her after he died.
My mother raised me all by herself.
Dear hurana, there's dinner for you in the fridge. Love, Mom.
We didn't get to spend much time together.
But my mother made time in her busy schedule
to be with me as much as she could.
In all honesty, I was very lonely a lot.
But I was very happy knowing how much my mother loved me.
And then one day my mother became
the principal of a private school.
When the company my mother was working for went under,
the school bought it out and discovered her.
She 5 currently the principal while in
training to be a corporate executive.
It was then that I found my own dream.
I wanted to become a teacher so I could help with my mom’s job.
So I entered the school where she worked as a first step.
My mother was very pleased.
That was the happiest I'd seen her since before my father died.
Just seeing her smile like that made me so happy.
I was happy to know I could do something to help her.
As usual, my mother was very busy.
We only saw each other at breakfast.
But our bond as mother and daughter
was stronger than anyone else's.
And to me, my mother was everything.
And I knew that I was everything to her.
Yes...
Until yesterday.
I guess waking up early does pay off once in a while.
I came here first thing in the morning to check the cameras.
But it's an added plus that I got to meet my slave.
I've left a clean uniform for you here.
You won’t be able to attend class looking like that.
But don’t put undies on.
After school, come to the unused club room as usual.
I'll check to see if you're actually not wearing panties and a bra.
You’d better do as I say or else you’ll have a really
bad punishment like you got yesterday.
I can't... do this.
Having him see me like that.
Having him do this to me.
And also...
Talking to your friend? About a girls' manga you read?
Goodness.
I wondered why you were so late coming home, and this is why?
I'm sorry. So, what do you think the heroine should do, Mom?
You’re asking me how I’d feel if something
fanciful like that happened to you?
Ridiculous.
Something like that would never happen to you.
After all, you don’t know anyone bad like that.
Yeah, but this is just theoretically speaking.
So, what do you think?
Ah, yes. Well, if you got yourself in that situation...
I'd probably disown you.
If you let such a horrible man use you like
that, as a fellow woman, I'd reject you.
Oh, no... But the heroine only did that to protect her mom.
It s because she's so soft that a gay like that took advantage of her.
I would definitely disown her.
But, well, that would never happen to you, Haruna.
So forget about that and have dinner, take a bath, and go to bed.
It’s already past midnight.
And you have practice tomorrow morning, right?
I have an early morning tomorrow as
well, so I'm going to bed now, okay?
Even my own mother abandoned me.
I have no reason to live now.
I have to die..
But even if I die... he'll still...
So then...
I have no other choice.
Translation Voldemort | Timing: Plastic Yakuza | Editing: The Fullpot cat | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
Presented by erobeat | http://www erabeat.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Gakune 2
- The Day Before -
That’s cold.
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
It's unfair to have you provide all the milk.
This time I’ll let you drink some too.
Cow's milk, that is.
Stop it! Please!
Don't do it!
It’s coming in!
Cold stuff is coming into my butt!
Stop it!
Don't hold back. Milk does a body good.
It’s great against constipation.
No! Stop it!
I can't do this! I can't do this anymore!
Stop!
Oh dear. I guess even slaves have their bad days.
You’re supposed to say, "More, please".
Why would I... Just stop it!
I won't stop unless you tell me to put in more.
You're kidding!
See? If you don’t ask quickly, you’ll really explode.
I'll say it! I'll say it!, okay? So please stop!
Please... put in... more milk.
What a greedy slave.
Here ya go.
No way!
You promised you’d stop!
I can't do this! I can't do this anymore!
No! Don't put it in! Stop it!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Please have mercy!
I'll die! I'll die!!
Good. It's all inside.
I just put it in.
Taste it longer.
That hurts! Don’t put that in!
No! It'll come out!
It'll come out!
Stop it!
"Don’t put it in”?
"It'll come out"?
Too loud.
Here's your punishment.
This feels great, Madam President!
I can't stand it!
Oh dear.
You got soaked in semen and came from that?
What a slut you are.
Hey now, who said you could sleep?
How much longer are ya gonna sleep?
See? Your Master has put his penis into his slutty slave.
Talk to me about it!
It hurts!
It's hurts! Stop it!
"Thank you Master”, right?
That’s not an answer!
Thank you, Master!
That’s right!
That’s how you speak to your master.
Don’t you forget it!
Please... Please have mercy.
Let me go to the bathroom.
You wanna get all the cum out in the toilet?
Gimme a fucking break.
But it hurts.
Have mercy.
Please stop it!
That’s not the right thing to say.
You’re supposed to say, “That feels wonderful ".
Come on.
Don't go in so deep!
"That feels wonderful".
Yes... Yes...
It feels wonderful...
It feels wonderful.
Yes.
It feels wonderful on my end, too.
Time to go.
I'll fill you up and make you explode.
Please! No more!
No more inside!
I'll get pregnant!
Stop complaining.
I'll keep cumming inside of you until you really do get pregnant!
A slave has no say in the matter!
Don't do it!
I don't want to get pregnant!
Don't cum inside of me!
Okay! The third internal cumming of the day!
Don't do it!
I'll get... I'll get pregnant!
It’s coming in!
It's coming inside of me!
I really will get pregnant now!
Oh no!
No! Stop!
Looks like it felt so good you pissed yourself.
I thought you were gonna shit yourself too at that rate.
What a bad slave you are!
Well, time to put more inside of you.
I’m sorry... Kawamura-san.
I guess at this rate she’s bound to be pregnant by now.
Especially after this morning.
I guess it's about time for her to fall for good.
Well then, what kind of play shall I do today?
You’re late.
I got bored waiting for you.
I’m sorry. Um... I...
Well, never mind. Come on in.
You went to class without your underwear, right?
You... you bitch...
What did...
Die. Please, just die.
Die with me.
Oh dear, oh dear.
I’m not ready for a lover's suicide.
Why? But how?
Aw man, you put a hole in my uniform.
Oh no!
"Die with me”?
You wanna die that badly?
It’s no use.
I can’t...
There's no place left for me in this world.
My mom was all I had.
She was the only person I lived for.
But she abandoned me.
I have no place to live anymore.
She abandoned you? What do you mean?
Don't tell me... you told her!?
How could I tell her!?
Then what did you say?
I told her about this manga I was reading.
Where the heroine let a guy use her sexually to protect her mom.
I asked her what she would do if that happened to me.
And she said she’d disown me!
She'd sever ties.
And that makes you wanna die?
Fucking ridiculous!
What do you know!?
We've lived together all this time.
I was gonna become a teacher.
I wanted to help her.
I wanted her to be proud of me.
That’s what’s kept me going all these years.
But she abandoned me!
I don’t have anything to live for anymore!
Then go ahead and die.
You're asking me to die!?
But it’s your fault she abandoned me!
You’re horrible!
Which of us is the horrible one?
You wanted to become a teacher just to please your mom?
That's not a very just motive!
What kind of teacher would you be if that's
the only reason you became one?
You’re not considering at all how your students would feel!
You talk all self-righteous and shit,
but you’re only thinking about yourself!
But I was just...
And on top of that, you want to kill someone and then kill yourself?
If you wanna die, then die by yourself!
You wanna die, don’t you?
Come on then, die!
What’s wrong with you?
You tried to kill me.
Don’t think your death will be so painless.
Good idea.
Slit your stomach with that knife and die.
I hear it's really painful.
Your stomach feels like it's on fire, but it takes a while to die.
You piss and shit yourself from the pain,
and cry as you slowly die while watching your innards spill out of you.
It’s hell itself apparently.
But I...
Hey, what’s wrong?
Just slash and get it over with!
Come on! You’re dying, aren't you?!
I can't!
I can't do it!
I don't want to die!
Shit. You don’t even have the balls to kill yourself.
And you try to kill someone else?
You're the worst kind imaginable!
Eh, Madam President?
You’re not a human anymore.
You’re even worse than a fucking dog.
You’re a pig!
You don’t even deserve to die.
What should I do...
What should I...
You have no place to live?
That’s no problem.
I’ll make a place for you to live.
You’re worse off than a dog.
You can just be my slave forever.
You don’t need to think.
All you need to think about is how to please me.
A... slave?
That’s right.
From today on, I will be your Master.
You can live for that from now on.
This will be your home now.
My... home...
That’s right.
A home just for you.
Isn't it great? Being my slave...
Or would you rather live on as a suicidal
girl abandoned by her mother?
No! I don’t want that!
I'll do it! I'll be your slave!
Then swear to me right now.
Otherwise, I'll abandon you right now.
No! Don’t abandon me!
Please! I'll swear!
I, Haruna, will become your slave, Kawamura-kun.
S-So please, don't abandon me.
That’s wrong.
Call me "Master".
I... I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, Master!
Haruna will be your slave from now on, Master!
All I have is you, Master.
So please don’t abandon me!
Very well said, Madam President.
I promise I’ll take very good care of you.
Master!
That looks good on you.
Almost like you were born to be a sex slave.
Yes.
Haruna was born to be your sex slave, Master.
Master, does it feel good?
Yes.
Master, your cock is so hard and hot.
My boobs are going to melt.
I love to feel your cock in my boobs.
It makes me so flattered!
I hope this feels good for you, Master.
Please enjoy yourself even more.
Haruna will try her best for you.
She will devote her life to you.
So please... so please don’t abandon me.
If you try hard, I won’t.
Yes!
Haruna will do anything to help her Master.
Master... Master...
Do my boobs feel nice?
Yes.
You praised me, Master!
Master, it's coming.
It’s coming out of my boobs.
You want me to drink that milk? Drink mine first.
Yes! Master!
Like this, Master?
Do it harder.
It’s coming.
It’s coming, Madam President.
Drink it up!
I told you to drink it up.
I’m sorry! I'm sorry, Master!
Oh shit, what can ya do...
Sf she chokes so quickly, she’s kinda useless.
Maybe I should get rid of her.
No! Forgive me, Master!
Anything but that!
I'll drink it next time!
I promise I'll drink it all next time!
Just please, don't abandon me!
Well then, I’ll give you another chance.
If you please me well this time, I’ll forgive you.
Yes! Thank you, Master!
Okay... Um...
Please take me, Master.
Please put your big, mighty cock into
Haruna's filthy and unworthy pussy.
Please cleanse Haruna's disgusting pussy with your semen.
Swirl around inside of Haruna.
And please fill her with your semen.
But didn't you hate it when I came inside of you?
You’ll get pregnant.
I don't mind.
I don’t mind if I get pregnant.
So please fill me full.
I want you to enjoy yourself.
If my slave begs me so earnestly, I guess I've got no choice.
Okay, put it in yourself and take care of it.
Thank you so much!
Master, your cock...
So thick! Master! It’s inside!
Inside of Haruna's pussy is your cock, Master!
I'm so happy!
This feels great!
Your thick cock is thrashing around inside of me.
I love it.
This feels so good I'm losing my mind.
Not my nipples, Master!
It feels great!
Oh no, it feels so good but I don't know why.
Oh, I’m cumming, Master!
Haruna is cumming!
My nipples are tingling... Here they come!
Hey, is a slave supposed to cum before her Master?
I’m sorry, I’m sorry, Master.
But it feels so good.
Oh no!
Not there!
Oh no, Master, please forgive me!
I'll cum again!
Oh no!
Madam President, you’re a fucking insane sex slave.
Yes, Haruna is a pervert!
I’m gross.
Time to reward your sluttiness.
Master! You're too rough!
Master, your cock is inside... inside my uterus!
Your thick, hot cock is poking my uterus!
It’s hurting me!
Haruna’s uterus will break!
Here, your beloved semen.
Get a good taste.
Oh yes, please! Please give Haruna your semen!
Inside of me!
Inside of Haruna's uterus!
Fill me with your hot cock-milk!
I want it!
I want to be filled with your hot cock-milk!
It's coming inside!
My Master's hot semen is coming inside!
His cock is throbbing.
My uterus is filled with semen.
It feels so good I'm going insane!
It feels wonderful!
-Several Days Later -
Looks like... you finally accepted your
role as a slave, Madam President.
Master...
Oops, sorry about that, Haruna.
What? You didn't want me to call you by name?
Or is it just your nipples?
Oh no!
Master!
What is it?
You came before me again, Haruna?
I'm sorry, Master.
But just by you calling my name,
my mind went blank.
Just that made me so happy.
Then I guess you don’t need this anymore.
Master, how horrible!
Please, let me have it.
Let Haruna suck it more for you!
You’re such a greedy slave.
Um, Master?
I've made you a lunch!
And...
Haruna-chan? No fair!
You can't lick my Master's penis!
Damn... didn't you already lick it this morning?
That’s not enough!
Unless you fill me deeper with more semen, I won't get pregnant,
and then I'll never be able to squirt milk like Haruna-chan!
What an annoying slave you are.
Well fine. Come join Haruna and lick.
Yes!
Ayano the airhead and Haruna the straight A student.
I've collected another slave. But that’s still not enough.
Nooo! I'll get pregnant!
Who shall I add next?
Yes, Master!