If this desire became reality...
how awesome would that be?
But it wont happen just by fantasizing about it.
My dream girl, Kudo Jun-san.
If I could rub up against her skin,
how awesome would that be?
If I could put it inside her, how awesome would that be?
And if I could always hear her sweet voice...
But it's no longer just a fantasy..
Now she belongs only to me...
Virgin In The School Uniform
EPISODE. 3
[ Sweet ENGAGE]
Well, classes dismissed for today, but we need
your help with contacting someone.
The girl, Kudo, has not returned
home the last few days.
It seems yesterday she tried
to call one of her friends,
but they did not answer answer.
If anyone here knows anything, notify
a teacher immediately, got it?
Okay!
Come on! Spit it out! Some guy
saw you and Kudo together.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who do you think you are? Watch your
fucking tone of voice, fucking loser.
Kudo, she's been our idol for the longest time now.
Hey, Matsumoto, you know something don't you?
Stop screwing around and tell us!
These bums... these violent dirtbags,
I wont let them have Kudo-san.
I'll protect her from them.
After all, she and I now have a special relationship.
Resistance is futile.
I live alone so nobody is going to come investigate.
We can be together forever.
It's been my dream for so long now...
to do this to you, Kudo-san.
You're so sensitive, Kudo-san.
Look, your nipples are getting hard already.
And look at how mine's also getting like that.
Hey, how is mine? Is it big?
Let me see Kudo's private place too.
Such cute panties...
and it's just jutting out like that...
I want to look at it directly, your cherry.
So pretty...
and it hasn't yet been popped by any guy, right?
Where is it? Where's the hole?
Is it here? Wait, that's not it.
Dammit! Where is it!?
Oh, sorry! Did that hurt?
To make it up to you, I'll lick it, okay?
Oh man... I can't take it anymore.
I'm sticking it in, Kudo-san
Hey, that's weird. It's hard, but
I can't stick it all the way in?
Wow, it's so tight, it really is your first time isn't it?
It's starting to feel so good. How about
you, Kudo-san, are you feeling it?
I can't take it anymore! Is it okay
if I cum inside you? It's fine, right?
No! Don't cum inside me!
No! Stop! Don't!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming, Kudo-san!
No, don't cum!
Take it out! Take it out!
Wow, it's still coming out. It's being
squeezed out by your insides.
That was the best, Kudo-san.
Now, you belong only to me.
I have to hurry and get home...
Kudo-san is waiting for me.
Sorry about this.
It's not like I want to do this to you,
but you just won't stop misbehaving!
Trying to do something that could ruin
our beautiful new life together...
If you didn't do that, you wouldn't
be getting this punishment.
Well? How do you like your fellatio training?
What are you talking about?
Please, let me go home!
Still saying things like that...
Stop... I won't tell anyone about this.
So please... Don't!
What's wrong?
Please, Matsumoto-kun...
Untie me from this thing. Let me use the toilet.
Oh, you need to pee? Is that what it was...
well, it's all good, just let it out right here.
I'll make sure to watch closely.
No! No way!
If only you wouldn't say things like that...
No! Stop! Don't do it so strongly!
You're stubborn, aren't you?
In that case, let's try this too, okay?
No... stop...
Stop it! It's coming! It's coming out!
It's not good for your body to
hold it so much. Just let it go...
Don't!
You're too cruel...
Well? Didn't it feel good?
You're horrible...
You're the worst kind of person!
Why do you do nothing but terrible things to me?
Hurry and let me go home!
Why... When I love you this much...
When I think only of you...
When I went and took a beating
from those jerks for you. Why!?
I don't know anything about that.
Anyway, just let me go home!
Hey, say "I love you" for me.
I fucking hate people like you!
Is that right?
Well, it looks like your punishment was insufficient.
No... No...
NO!!
As I thought Kudo-san can wear anything and it'll
look great. Uniforms, swimsuits, anything at all...
What? What is that?
No, don't! It hurts!
It hurts so much!
It can't go in any farther! Please don't force
it in further! It can't go in any more!
What? What are you doing?
This toy is like a balloon.
It swells up inside your rectum and unlike a dick,
it won't shrink before I want it to.
And when I use it with a laundry pump...
What are you doing?
Kudo-san, your ass loves to drink, right?
Come on then, don't be shy, drink up!
It's going in! Something cold is going inside! No!
Wow! It's already guzzled a
whole container's worth!
Well then, let's get you another one.
No!
It hurts...
Please let me use the toilet.
Yup, yogurt made in your insides
would be so much better...
I'll give you a drink through your mouth as well.
No! Stop!
Why do you reject me? Even
though I love you so much.
What are you talking about?
Forcing me to do such things...
then trying to speak like a lover...
Why won't you love me? Even
though I love you this much...
Please! Please say "I love only you."
I won't say it.
Why would I ever say that to someone
who does such cruel things?
Come on, say it. Pretty please?
Don't!
My insides... My insides are...
When I do this... it's almost like
I'm drinking Kudo-san's milk.
No...
That's right... if Kudo-san gets pregnant
then her breasts will make milk, right?
Hey, let's make a baby.
No! No way in hell!
It'll be okay, Kudo-san and I's
baby will surely be adorable.
Please! Stop! My insides are stretching!
Please!
Let me use the toilet!
Then accept my love. Say "I love you."
I'll say it! I'll say whatever you want so...
I love you! I love you
So please stop! Don't put any more in!
From now on we love each other,
right? I'm so happy, Kudo-san...
Wait! Let me use the toilet first!
Nah.
It hurts!
It's so good! The tightness inside
Kudo-san is mushy now too!
Please! Don't move! My insides hurt!
Looking at it, it's like you're really pregnant.
No! Don't say that!
It's so good! I'm going to cum again!
No! Please don't cum! I'll really become pregnant!
So cruel... he really came inside me.
I came so much inside you. Didn't
it feel wonderful, Kudo-san?
You're so cruel... even after
I begged you not to cum...
Hey, that's no good at all, letting my
sperm leak out of you like that.
Oh, I know!
Kudo-san, take a look.
It's like our child is being born.
No!!
Okay, let's free up some room inside you.
No! If you take that out now...
It'll all come out!
It'll be fine. Just let it all out.
I'll lend you a hand.
Don't! Let me use the toilet!
Come on, it's not good to hold it in so long.
Don't! Don't squeeze me so hard!
My insides... It hurts!
It's coming out!
Wow! So much came out!
So... You've endured a lot, right?
But if you try to run away again,
I'll put in even more next time.
Looking at Kudo-san's slutty butt
hole is making me hard again.
No!
It hurts! Stop!
Oh yeah! From now on, call me Master, okay?
Okay! I'll call you that! So please take it out!
Come on, that's not what you're supposed to say.
Please take it out, Master!
It hurts! It hurts. Please don't move back and forth.
Come on. How could I stop doing
something that feels so good?
Please, just let me go!
Here I come again!
NO!!
Even my butt hole has been violated.
I cant... anymore...
Your fellatio is becoming quite skillful.
Well then, I'm off!
Be a good girl and wait for me, okay?
I won't ever cry again.
Because, I have my wonderful bride
Kudo-san, who belongs only to me.
Come on! Stop squirming around!
No! Don't look!
Move your damn hand out of the way!
What a marvelous ass! And
it's getting soaking wet too!
Holy shit... I can't wait to ram it inside...
Come on... get into position
properly! We're starting!
Don't!
Well then. I give thanks, for this
bounty I'm about to feast on.
Hey! It's slowly going in!
All right! Take it!
Damn! It's so tight!
Yeah! Now I'm really slamming you hard!
Oh! Damn! Now you understand
I'm not fucking around, huh?
Huh, what? You were a virgin?
Looks like I got you good.
Well then, it looks like round one is
almost over, let's fill you up good.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Okay, now let's give you some good news.
That didn't feel so good, did it? Your
body is fucked up and trembling.
You can really look forward to
giving birth for the first time.
To continue producing my beloved erotic film,
I'll have to continue my surprise encounters.
It might seem crude, but I will punish the girls of
this elite girls' academy in this gym storehouse.
Virgin In The School Uniform
EPISODE. 4
[ Fragments of the Full Moon ]
See you tomorrow!
Bye!
Huh? What?
My underwear's not here.
Onee-chan, I borrowed your underwear. I'll return
it soon, just come to the gym storehouse. - Miki
There shouldn't be an one here to see me...
Miki-chan!
It's me, Motoko!
My underwear...
I'm coming in!
Miki-chan!
Is this what the young lady is searching for?
My underwear...
No!
No! Please don't come any closer!
If you refuse me here, your sister will
become a laughing-stock in society!
Miki-chan....
I have no problem with spreading
this video all over.
If you want to spare your little sister such pain...
isn't it obvious what a good big sister should do?
Come on! Suck this thing!
I'll give it to you, the question is
can you take it all in one go?
Fuck yeah!
I'm going to have to ask forgiveness
for what I'm about to do!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
All right, it looks like everything
is going according to plan.
Let's have a look. I came a lot, eh?
Let's have a look in your mouth too.
Good girl. Savor that taste.
Isn't it delicious?
Put a happier look on your damn face and smile!
Good, now swallow my semen.
Come on, open your mouth and say "ahn"!
You swallowed all of it, right?
I told you to smile.
All right, now the real thing.
I'll make sure to fuck and cum inside you properly.
I'm going to rape the goodness out of you.
Stop squirming around! It's going in!
Stealing a girl's virginity all in one thrust is the best!
How dare you have such a slutty
body and stay a virgin!
I should thank your parents, right?
Here I come!
I'm cumming! Inside you!
No... You came inside me...
You finished up?
Yeah.
Wow... gaudy, isn't she?
Just like in porn, right?
Onee-chan, I'll return your underwear now.
Mi-Miki-chan?
You look pathetic.
You still haven't realized? She fucked you over.
But what a freak you are, betraying
your own siblings...
It's okay.
It's not like we're true siblings.
It can't be... Miki-chan, for your sake I...
Shut up!
Your dad seduced my mom, and then
threw her out of the house!
We're not blood-related, so
stop acting like we're family!
Miki-chan...
Hey, old man.
I can go now, right?
I introduced you to this girl,
so you can let me go, right?
Okay then, let's do this...
I'll release the first girl to make me cum.
Seriously?
Okay, start.
Move out of the way!
Wait, Onee-chan!
Come on, you have to take turns.
Onee-chan, we're taking turns!
This time for sure.
Hell yes. That is too good.
I feel it coming.
Switch! Switch! We're taking turns!
Come on, Miki-chan!
Please cum inside my mouth!
Shit, I'm going to blow it any second!
Stop!
Okay, it looks like this girl here takes the win.
Now drink that stuff that's in the other girl's mouth.
No... Onee-chan...
That's it, savor that taste while
I do something down here.
Good, let me hear you two enjoying it.
All right, that was some good footage.
Well then, maybe I should go
publish this tape right now...
From the beginning...
From the beginning, you weren't going
to release either of us and you still...
You lowly bitch, you've been
getting too friendly recently.
What the hell! Why do I have
to be tied up like this!?
Jeez, you're annoying.
Don't you feel pity for such a sweet sister
who went out of her way to help you?
Mi-Miki-chan...
This giant dildo has been soaking up
my semen in a tank for a while now,
so take it and punish your little
sister like she deserves.
This is the fruit of your sisterhood.
W-Wait... Onee-chan...?
O-Onee-chan?
No! Get away!
From now on, Onee-chan will be taking the lead.
Don't! Stop!
After all I did for you...
It's going inside.
It's slippery enough so that it's actually going in.
It hurts!
Miki-chan, you feel it? Do you feel your sister now?
Oh so good! Miki-chan's insides feel so good!
It makes me want to cum!
Onee-chan, it hurts!
Miki-chan is getting spread open so hard!
When I put a finger in I can't pull it out!
Miki-chan, I love you!
I love you so much!
Miki-chan, you feel so good!
What a beautiful sibling relationship you two have.
I feel so moved I just might shed a tear.
Come and fuck me! My butt hole is ready for you!
Miki-chan! Now we're finally together!
Yes! Yes!
Amazing! It's like a party in my insides!
Oh so good!
Come on! Shake those asses you slutty sisters!
O-Onee-chan...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Miki-chan, it's amazing!
Make me cum too!
These slutty twisted sisters!
Go to hell!
So good... I'm cumming! Fuck me harder!
Please cum inside me!
Miki-chan...
Onee-chan...
Yamada-san, sorry but...
What is it?
Please take care of the cigarette ashes.
And also, throw out the garbage.
No problem.
What, are you serious?
I can't believe it! And then, she said...
Yamada-san.
Yamada-san!
This girl is new here, her name is Ura Kasumi-san.
Please show her around.
Come on! Give the proper greeting!
Yes, sir! My name is Ura Kasumi,
pleased to meet you.
Well then, I'll leave her in your care, Yamada-san.
Yes, you can count on me.
First off, there's this room I'd like to show you...