Do I really have to?
Yeah.
He's waiting for you at the library.
I-I can't...
What? Should you really be saying that?
I'm sure you wouldn't mind if I tell the whole
world what we've been up to, right?
Don't...
Then do it.
N-No...
It's rubbing against me...
I-I'm cumming!
F-Fine.
I'll do it.
STRINGENDO
~ Private Lesson Of Angels ~
MY BLOW JOBER ACT.3
This please.
M-Miyasawa-san.
I'm sorry for being late.
Umm.
I have a request for you.
What is it?
Well...
I want to suck you off.
Hey...
Please, don't ask anymore.
Just let me do it.
I want your semen.
Are you really going to?
I want this for checkout, please.
Okay...
You have a week to return it.
Huh? Oh, okay.
Right there...
Nothing...
Bye.
Are you embarassed?
Wanna see my breasts?
M-Miyasawa-san...
Take a good look.
Jeez, it's even more stiff now.
Does it feel good?
M-Miyasawa-san...
Keep it down, this is the library after all.
Sorry.
I'll toy my best.
How does it feel?
I'm sorry my breasts are small...
I'll use my saliva to make you feel better.
My nipples are being rubbed...
It feels like I'm in heaven.
M-Miyasawa-san...
I want to see your pussy.
P-Plcase.
If I see it, I'll definitely...
Don't put it in though.
Please don't stare at it.
Wow, it's beautiful.
You're already so wet.
S-Stop...
Don't say such embarassing things...
Miyasawa-san...
I'm cumming!
C-Cut it out!
I said no putting it in!
You can't do this...
N-No!
Please, stop!
I can't control myself.
B-But...
Don't worry, I'll just put the head in.
You said just the head...
It's deep inside now...
W-Wow...
I can't believe I'm inside you fight now.
C-Can you see it?
Y-You can't!
Stop!
Just a little bit.. I'm cumming...
Not inside me!
But...
But my body is telling me to do so...
D-Don't...
No!
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
That's all you've got, right?
The test is about to begin.
Shibuya isn't here.
But wasn't she here earlier?
Hey, give me a sec, Maruki-kun.
Lets finish it off later in the nurse's room when afternoon class starts.
We can't enjoy ourselves to the fullest out here.
I heard the nurse is out today.
What's wrong with doing it here?
Hold your horses.
Today's a safe day for me.
I'll allow you to dump it all in me.
Okay?
Answer me with your mouth, not your penis!
All right, I'll see you later.
W-What?
That's foreplay.
T-Tanabc-kun...?
S-Shibuya-san?
I guess I should leave.
No, wait!
There's only one way to keep your mouth shut.
Class is not even over yet why are
you going to the nurse's room?
My dear Asaoka-sensei is absent today.
I broke a bone.
I'll help you out with it.
Wait I'm just kidding! Wait!
I love helping kids who are bully victims!
Enjoy.
We don't really know each other that well...
You're even more excited now, right?
It's really wet.
Because I'm really horny right now...
A-Are you skilled, Tanabe-kun?
Hey, I want to touch yours too.
Let's do it together.
Wow...
It's so stiff.
I-I'm sorry.
Come on, don't apologize.
Shibuya-san...
This feels extra good, doesn't it?
Wow...
It's getting stiffer.
I never knew...
...you had such a big cock.
Stop... Stop.
You're cumming?
Wait.
Not yet
Let it out inside me.
Please, inside me.
I'm about to explode...
Hang in a little longer.
Wow...
This is amazing...
Shibuya...
Let go of me...
You're filling me up with your cock.
It's so big and stiff...
I'm cumming...
I'm at my limit...
Then give me all you've got.
Every single drop.
Your semen is deep inside me.
Tanabe-kun, that was great.
Are you done yet?
Yeah, I guess.
But it's still stiff.
Let out as much as you want inside me.
Start moving.
Don't touch my Asaoka-sensei.
If you dare do it again,
as her guardian angel, I'll...
Shibuya...
Wait for me...
If you want me to forgive you, pick one!
Come on, come on!
No!
You'll make me cum if you do it so rough!
Tanabe-kun, that's a huge load.
Your thing never calms down.
Hey, come to my house from now on.
Can I really?
Shoot every single drop you've got left inside me, okay?
Hey, Ami.
Your PE clothes...
Don't you think they're rather tight?
Yeah...
I left my PE clothes at home,
so I borrowed them from a friend...
That's why...
I would've lent you mine if you asked.
Oh, oops.
I forgot about that.
Its our turn.
This is so embarassing...
Everyone's looking at me...
Gosh...
These clothes are squeezing my nipples and pussy...
I guess everyone can see it.
This is soembarassing...
Huh? Where's Ami?
No...
Oh, aren't you wet.
It must've felt great, right?
T-That's not true.
Then let me make you feel good.
See, it went in just like that
You must be really horny.
Please...
Don't be so rough...
I'll break...
I can't stand it anymore...
Why do I have to get fucked by a
disgusting faggot every single day?
Dammit, I'm cumming.
No!
It's a dangerous day today.
I'll really get pregnant!
Oh really?
But didn't that librarian cum inside you?
I'm going to do the same thing.
Please, not inside!
T-That's...
You won't get pregnant from this hole.
No...
Your thing is too big...
It won't fit.
You'll never know if you don't try, right?
See, it's in.
It hurts...
Its so frickin' tight.
My insides are getting churned...
Wow, man.
It's seriously really damn tight.
I'm cumming.
Please... Hurry...
I'm gonna break...
I...
How long...
How long will this continue on for?
I'm not fit to be a bride anymore.