I'd better hurry, or someone will see!
What am I doing? I shouldn't be doing this.
And I don't want to be caught like this.
But my pussy is squirming so much that I can't stop!
If I don't do something about it,
everyone will think I'm weird.
I know I'm being a bad girl... but... but!
I can't stop!
I can't think about anything else!
I-I'm cumming!
Someone saw me.
What should I do?
I got caught yesterday, and yet I'm still
walking around dressed like this.
Good morning, Senpai!
Good morning, Sayaka-chan.
Are you okay?
Your cheeks are all red.
Really? I-I'm fine.
Oh, crap. Maybe she can read my face?
I should probably take these
things off when I get to work.
Senpai, what's wrong?
You look like preoccupied.
I'm sorry. It's nothing.
Oh, yeah! Wanna have lunch together today?
Sure, that sounds good.
Okay! How about a sweet lunch then?
Sayaka-chan really is a nice girl.
I wonder what she'd think of me if she found
out I was wearing a vibrator to work?
Senpai, are you listening to me?
Of course I am!
I'll let you choose where we eat.
By the way, we'd better hurry
or we'll be late getting to work.
I'd better go to the bathroom quickly and take it out!
Saeko-kun.
Yes?
Why does he have to call me up at a time like this?
Your calculations in yesterday's
spreadsheet were wrong.
Oh, crap.
What if he finds out I'm wearing it?
What should I do?
I hope he shuts up soon.
I need to go to the bathroom and take it out!
Saeko-kun, are you listening to me?
Y-Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
Why did the switch turn on?
I thought I had the remote in my bag.
It's no good!
Well, fine, go back to your desk!
You coming tonight?
No, I'll pass.
I'm going out with my boyfriend.
That girl!
She's got balls.
I'm all wet and sticky.
Why did it start up on its own?
Oh, no! I can't start here... but...
But... coming to work without panties isn't good either.
I guess I'll be fine as long as I don't turn it on.
Saeko-chan, is it true you were masturbating at work?
It is true!
She looks so sweet and innocent,
but she's actually really daring!
Nipple piercings? She's really addicted.
No, please stop it.
Now, don't be so sad.
We're just trying to make you feel good.
Let's have a little fun together.
No!
Whoa, a real-life slut.
Stop it.
Don't look!
Your mouth may say that,
but your pussy says differently.
Don't! Stop it.
My fingers must not be enough.
I'll bury myself in you.
No, stop it!
But you want me down here.
Hey! Who's in there!?
Oh, shit!
Saeko-chan, well continue this some other time.
Are you okay?
Murakami-kun...
You don't need to worry anymore.
I'll take you home.
But first, let's get out of here.
Can you stand?
I.. can't...
But...
Murakami-kun...
Kobayakawa?
I... can't hold back.
Please tear me apart.
I can't stop the throbbing of my body.
I can't hold out anymore.
I've become a freak.
Yes. Right there. More...
Kobayakawa...
Yes. More!
Inside, please! Cum inside of me!
Kobayakawa!
Murakami-kun!
See you later.
I don't need these anymore.
Aren't there any stronger toys?
Now, now, don't fret.
I'm inventing a new one as we speak.
Did I put these away in here?
Really, I'm not dissatisfied with sex with my husband,
but I can't forget the pleasure I felt from the toys.
What should I do?
Since I've almost finished putting them away,
I might as well try them, just for a bit.
That's right.
It's not like I'm cheating on him or anything.
No problem with it!
Seeing it after so long makes me nervous.
I can feel it.
Sex isn't bad, but this toy fits me so
much better and feels wonderful!
He's going to come home any minute.
Yes! I'm cumming...
I guess using it after so long was a bit too harsh.
I'm so sore that I can't walk straight.
Looks like no one's noticed.
But if someone sits next to me, they
might hear the noise of the vibrator.
I wonder if the people below can see me.
Scnpai?
Senpai, is something wrong?
Sayaka-chan...
Long time no see!
Fancy bumping into you here.
I-I'm surprised too. Y-You look well.
Thanks! By the way, Senpai, are
you waiting for someone?
No.
Then can I hang out with you?
Y-Yeah, sure.
Well then, here we go!
Ever since you left, work has been really boring.
Are you okay, Sayaka-chan?
Your face is red.
Your face is red, too.
Sayaka-chan...
Senpai, wanna go to the bathroom with me?
Senpai.
Sayaka-chan, you're so pretty.
Really? I'm so flattered.
Let me see yours too, Senpai.
Let's continue this at my house.
Okay.
Excuse me!
Oh, so you put up the doll!
Of course I did.
You gave it to me for my wedding, after all.
That makes me happy.
Sayaka-chan.
Senpai!
You're so cute.
Hey, let's use this.
What's that?
You put it in here.
In there?
Is it your first time?
Don't worry. It'll feel good. I promise.
Oh, no, I must've fallen asleep.
Senpai, be sure to put my present on your bed, too.
Sayaka-chan!
We need something we can use together.
An "exterior vibrator"?
That might work.
It makes my heart race!
Now I'll get to do it with Sayaka-chan!
I hope that toy arrives soon.
Now things are getting interesting.
I'd better think up some new toys.
That's an impressive getup.
What would you have done if it wasn't me at the door?
O-Oh, no...
So you were that anxious to see me, huh?
You're already wet down here.
N-No, not here.
I wanna see it here.
I wanna watch you masturbate.
Because I was playing with it earlier,
my pussy is extra sensitive.
I'm gonna cum.
The fun begins now.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Oh, Sayaka-kun, you came to visit?
If that's okay with you!
Murakami-san, your arms are nice and muscular.
Don't you agree, Senpai?
You're right.
He lifts weights obsessively every day.
Oh, I see.
That makes sense.
That's why he's so ripped.
I wonder how his arm would feel inside, Senpai?
What's wrong?
Nothing!
Right?
Y-Yeah!
She's right I wonder how
something that thick would feel.
Don't!
Saeko?
I-I'm sorry.
I can't do it today.
I'll give you a blowjob instead. Sorry.
Okay?
Saeko...
Senpai, there's something I want to try.
What?
Murakami-san.
I want to try a vibrator with a man.
No! You can't do that.
Please, Senpai?
Even you want to try sticking his arm in here.
You normally can't do it, right?
Let's try it, Senpai!
N-No.
But I'm sure Murakami-san would be into it!
I mean, he'll get to do it with
two horny and beautiful girls.
I just know he'll help out.
I've got a plan, so don't worry.
He passed out quicker than I thought.
Sayaka-chan, I don't think I want
to go through with this.
But you can't back out now.
Come on, help me carry him.
Senpai, watch me, okay?
Sayaka-chan, I don't think we should.
Just sit back and watch.
What's happened to you, Sayaka-chan?
You're not yourself.
What about you, Senpai?
You're so wet. You know you want it.
How does if feel, Senpai?
To see something that belongs to
you being used by someone else?
What the hell am I doing?
I'm getting turned on by watching someone
else have sex with my husband.
I can't look away!
Senpai, it seems like you're getting turned on by it.
Come on, Senpai, go ahead and use it.
Don't worry.
These will make sure he doesn't wake
up for the rest of the night.
Darling...
What's wrong?
The thing you want is right here.
What's happening to me?
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
I see. You've been spacing out a lot recently.
I was wondering if you were sick.
I'm fine.
That's good.
See you later.
Have a nice day.
That was inside of me.
Saeko.
No! Don't look.
I thought you were acting strange lately.
I'm sorry.
I just... I just... I just couldn't hold back.
Don't apologize.
It's also my fault for not noticing.
Don't say that.
Saeko, I love you.
Darling.
But you really want something this big in you?
I guess I don't satisfy you enough anymore.
No, don't say that.
What do you want?
Um...
Like this?
Does it feel good?
Please... from behind.
D-Darling...
Saeko.
Yes, yes! Harder!
Please!
Yes!
l'm cumming.
This is... Sayaka-chan's...
Sayaka-kun?
What's going on?
The truth is...
Well then, I'll be off.
Have a nice day.
Senpai.
Sayaka-chan? What's wrong?
I brought you a new vibrator today.
Sayaka-chan! Snap out of it!
Let's stop.
I thought a normal vibrator wasn't
enough for you anymore.
Do you like if?
Doesn't it feel good?
But it's not over yet.
Please, help me! Darling!
Good morning.
Huh? Where's Sayaka-kun?
Ah, she's out sick with a cold.
A cold?
Saeko!
How does it feel?
Much better than a man, right?
Y-Yes.
I won't let anyone else have you!
No. If you go any further, I'll...
Saeko!
It's no use. I can't feel anything anymore!
Senpai! You're so pretty!
Let's cum together!
Hey, Senpai!
Let's cum... Let's cum together!
Saeko! Snap out of it.
Saeko!
I suppose I'll have to find new prey.