Itoshi no Kotodama
In my dreams, I will embrace,
anata e no omoi dake o
just my feelings for you.
yume ni dakishimete
Very slowly, now...
yukkuri to watashi wa ima
Ah, I am starting to take an adult form.
ah otona no kakera ni kawaru
– Ah, you're here.
Ah, I am starting to take an adult form.
The love I hold in my dreams,
yume ni aru aiji dake ni wa
– Yes. I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
The love I hold in my dreams,
shines brighter than anything.
nani yori mo kagayaite
– Oh, don't worry. That's no problem.
shines brighter than anything.
– The dream you wanted to accomplish before you died:
Oh, I have no regrets.
oh kui ga nai
– a field of cosmos flowers overlooking the sea.
Oh, I have no regrets.
Because I was able to see you again.
mata anata ni deaete watashi wa
– If there's anything I can do to make
your dream come true, I'll try.
Because I was able to see you again.
And I was happy.
shiawase datta yo
– I'm sorry.
And I was happy.
– Uh, well...
– I guess I need more training.
And I was happy.
Chapter 2:
Return
It's colder than I thought.
I never thought I'd see the day...
when you'd work so hard at something.
Ah, Yoshihira. What the hell are you doing here?
Jeez, don't be rude!
I got the cosmos flowers from
the gardening club at school
and brought them here for you!
Your grandpa said you'd be here, of all places.
Oh, I get it. Sorry, sorry.
I'll plant them soon.
So have you quit school and run away from home?
Or have you decided to become a florist?
In that case, I'll introduce you to my grandmother,
and she can teach you flower arrang
Thank you.
Hey, whoa, are you listening to me?
Oops. I don't have time to waste here.
Gotta go back to school. See ya.
I doubt he'd believe me if I told him the truth.
Rin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen.
I thought I felt something strange.
I must've imagined it.
Kin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen.
Rin pyo to sha kai jin...
The flower garden will be finished soon, I see.
Yup.
By next fall, this field will be
covered in cosmos flowers.
I can't wait to see it.
All I have to do now is plant the
seeds Yoshihira brought me.
Yes.
But when that happens, Shigemaro-san...
What's wrong?
You don't look happy.
I-I'm sorry! Did I get your hand dirty?
No, that isn't it.
I could feel the warmth of your hand very clearly.
You're right.
See?
I guess my training paid off.
Training?
Yeah. My grandpa told me...
to do a bunch of spiritual exercises
before coming here to help you.
You did that for me?
I have to.
Grandpa says my gift alone
isn't enough to help ghosts.
I have to train hard every day and work
hard to make your wish come true.
Otherwise, I won't even be able to see you anymore.
I'm so happy!
But when you finish this flower garden,
I won't see you anymore.
Yeah. What's been holding you back
from passing on will be a reality.
My real dream...
was to plant a cosmos flower
garden with the man I love.
The man you love?
Please be gentle.
You're very beautiful Kiyomi-chan.
No...
Don't.
I'm embarrassed.
What... What is this feeling? I've never felt it.
It feels...
You're already so wet.
No!
How embarrassing.
Don't.
No.
Can I look at it?
Yes.
Spread your legs.
I can't go through with it.
It's really cute.
Don't look.
I'm losing my mind.
Don't... hurt me. No.
It's very...
What am I saying?
Ready? I'm coming in.
Okay.
It's my first time. Don't hurt me.
Be gentle.
I feel it.
Wow.
So she's gone.
Could it be... a miracle!?
Kiyomi-chan.
The cosmos flowers are in full bloom.
Kiyomi-chan...
What are you moping around for?
Why aren't you training, my boy!?
Oh, it's just Grandpa.
Whaddaya mean, "Oh, it's just Grandpa"!?
As I explained to you earlier, a beginner like you
must train hard every day to be able
to communicate with ghosts!
You must protect them and yourself
from evil spirits and monsters,
if you expect to help them reincarnate.
Huh?
What is he...
Looks like he's lovesick.
I'm telling you. I saw it!
Are you sure? I don't really believe it.
Well, he might be telling the truth.
After all, that place has been
known as a haunt for ghosts.
It really scared me too.
Just after I came out of a tunnel,
this spirit-orb thingie came like...
From the tunnel?
Oh, it's just Shigemaro.
Don't scare me like that. I almost had a heart attack...
Yoshihira! You just mentioned a tunnel, didn't you!?
Uh, yeah.
It's that tunnel just above the waterfall
where you were chanting earlier.
When did this happen?
E-Early this morning.
I was going to morning practice with my club.
That's right Shigcmaro.
This morning...
Haven't you been around there a lot?
Didn't you see it?
A ghost. It's kinda bluish-white.
I'm taking your bike for a bit!
H-Hey! What's his problem?
Beats me...
Kiyomi-chan, you must've returned!
What was that just now?
Kiyomi-chan?
You're not Kiyomi-chan.
Sorry about that.
And here I was, all excited that I finally
found someone who could see me.
Who are you?
Sakaki Kaoru. And you are?
Koga Shigemaro.
You're creeping me out. Stop staring at me like that.
Sorry. I just had a hard time looking at you...
Are you saying I'm hard on your eyes!?
No! No! I mean that you're difficult to see.
I sense an evil presence.
Then, when I tried to grab my cell phone...
You lost control of your car.
Yup.
As I was dying, I kept wondering who was calling me.
Well, not like it matters now.
Is there something I can do to help?
Your ring?
Yes, my ring.
I wonder what happened to it.
Did you lose it during the accident?
Yeah.
If was difficult for me to drive with it on,
so I always kept it on the dashboard.
That ring was important to you.
My boyfriend gave it to me.
I'll find it for you.
Really?
Yeah.
Then let's pinky swear.
It's probably because you're so optimistic.
I don't even feel dead.
That's strange. I guess I need more training.
Oh, well, that's okay. I just hope you find my ring.
I will. You can count on me.
What the hell is that?
Kaoru-chan!
It's because of that thing that I'm...
Damn monster! Let me show you something I learned!
Come forth, chains that bind!
My chain binding charm didn't work?
Wh-What kind of monster is this?
Guide of the Dead, Karasutengu.
Karasutengu...
Ah, it's you!
"Ah, it's you"? Show some respect why don't'cha?
He just used his wind barrier to block that.
It can usually be countered with basic magic,
but if you want to actually defeat him,
you'll need some Chobuku magic.
A wind barrier? Chobuku... magic?
Behind you!
Oh, crap! That's the bike I borrowed from Yoshihira!
I think that's the least of your troubles!
Rin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen!
Did I get him?
What the hell? It didn't work?
That's strange. Grandpa said it would work?
Watch out!
Head for the tunnel!
Hey! You ve got spells on your back!
That's right!
It's bad enough your grandpa summoned me.
Then he put these stupid papers on my back!
Oh, that's right.
Your grandpa said I should talk to you about...
Is that how you were able to appear?
Ow! Why are you humans so forceful?
That's gonna leave a scar!
You should've told me about this at the start.
The battle will be decided by one blow.
That's what your grandpa said. I got it!
Is that...
Yes.
Chobuku magic... a trapping spell!
That's why I lured him into the tunnel.
The battle will be decided by
one blow, so make if count.
I'll make my training count.
Rin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen!
Rin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen.
Monster begone!
This is...
I found it.
Yeah.
Thanks.
But throw it away, please.
That day, I got dumped.
So I was a little out of my head.
I didn't care what happened.
I'm happy you found it for me, but I don't want it.
Please.
Are you sure?
If it's what she wants, it's what she wants.
Jeez, I never did get the hang of
understanding a woman's heart.
Come to think of it, that girl looks familiar.
Well, it doesn't concern me.
I was holding on this whole time, but I finally gave up.
Because I met you.
Back then, I thought it was okay if I died.
But now, I wish I were still alive.
Now I remember.
Go ahead. Throw it.
Throw it as far into the ocean as you can.
Okay.
Thank you.
Kaoru-chan!
That little devil...
I wonder where he went.
What's this?
"Cosmos Hospital"?
Oh, that's the hospital Aki-chan was going to.
Sakaki Kaoru
Kaoru-chan?
Kaoru-chan... She was in a coma here.
She wasn't really dead!
From this point on, it all depends on
your training and your feelings.
Good luck.
Well I guess I'm off.
Her spirit still hasn't completely returned to her body.
Kaoru-chan.
Shigemaro-kun.
Watch out!
You're still not...
I thought I was dreaming the whole time.
And I kept wishing I were dead.
But when I met you, I wanted to live again.
I wanted it from the bottom of my heart.
Be gentle.
Can I take off your pants?
Yes.
No...
No!
Don't!
It's hot...
Ready?
It's my first time.
Please don't hurt me.
Yes!
Amazing!
I'm cumming!
The instant I open my eyes,
me o aketa shunkan ni
My happiness flees from me.
shiawase wa nigeteku kara
So I want to stay this way forever,
eien ni kono mama de
With my eyes closed.
me o tojite itai
Now I am in your arms,
ima anata no ude no naka ni
Embraced gently,
yasashiku dakarete
Although I am changing into an illusion.
sou watashi wa maboroshi ni kawaru keredo
Please, don't let it fade away,
douka kesanai de
The love that remains in my heart.
mune ni tomaru ai o
Surely, someday in the future,
kitto mirai demo
I, and only I, will be yours forever.
watashi dake ga your forever