No!
Yamagishi-kun, you pervert!
Wait up, Jubei!
St. Harenchi Academy
Professor Nagai
Well, ladies and gentlemen, long time no see!
Today, we're here to discuss...
The infamous school that brought naughtiness
to all of Japan, Harenchi Academy!
Lick, lick, lick.
Even Hentai-sensei, the creator of this story,
is embarrassed by its naughtiness!
Hige Godzilla-sensei and Marugoshi-sensei
pepper the story with their lewd antics.
It's a tale of love and deep, perverted.
Yes, it's very perverse.
And what's more...
Now that we’re in the Heisei era,
it can be seen once again on video!
Do all of you remember this beautiful girl?
Jubei, aka Yagyu Mitsuko.
She's the Madonna of Harenchi
Academy, isn't she?
The pride and joy of her family line.
Oops, and here comes the unlikely hero
of Harenchi Academy, Yamagishi-kun.
And on the other side,
Ikidomari, aka Fukurokoji-kun!
He's the most simple-minded
pervert in the whole school.
Well then, well then!
Let's turn our attention back to Harenchi Academy.
What will unfold before us today?
Don't tear your eyes away, okay?
My, my...
Well, then! Let us start "Heisei Harenchi Gakuen"!
Translation: Voldemort | Timing: v1touch | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Heisei Harenchi Gakuen
Late on the first day!
That's really pathetic!
We made it!
Harenochi Academy
I've dreamed of standing before this
archway ever since I was a kid.
And now I'm finally here!
No words can describe the feeling.
Hige Godzilla-sensei, my homeroom
teacher in elementary school,
inspired me to become a teacher someday.
And now ten years have passed.
Looking back, it sure was a hard struggle.
Hey, hey, Ikidomari, if you're gonna
get a nosebleed from that,
you'll be completely drained
by the end of first period.
Be strong. Starting today, the two of us
will be teaching at an all-girls school!
Butts in full bloom.
Shaking everywhere!
Damn straight.
It's a cherry blossom orchard of horniness!
– Let's go!
– Wait up, Boss!
Wait for me, Boss!
You're holding me back, Ikidomari!
Not so fast, please!
Hey, Boss!
Check that out.
Th-That's Jubei, isn't it?
Yes.
She's really sexy.
Sure is.
And now Yagyu-san is a star athlete!
And when it comes to star athletes...
They're best when they jiggle.
But anyway, why do you think there's
a statue of Jubei at this school?
No idea.
Well, whatever.
Okay.
I'd better try extra hard to
live up to Jubei's standards.
In what way?
Isn't it obvious?
Since I've become a teacher...
I need to fuck as many cute students as possible!
I thought so!
That pair is as moronic as usual.
A pair of very enthusiastic
men has joined our ranks.
This means our school should
become more famous in no time.
Stupid assholes!
Wearing such freakin' cute uniforms to
a school where there aren't any guys.
I fucking hate all-girls schools.
Big news, girls!
I hear a young male teacher is
going to join our class today!
– What!?
– A man!?
I can't fucking stand it!
I'd better change into my cute undies.
I should fix my make-up!
A man is coming!
Nice to meet you!
I am Harenochi Academy's principal.
I feel like we've met before.
Yes...
Just your imagination.
Today is the first day we've had
male teachers at this school.
But since both of you are such fine
young men, I'm very honored.
We're very glad to...
...be here!
Aw, you're so innocent.
Here's your schedule.
Well then, I'll have someone show
you to your classrooms right away.
Just for a bit, okay?
Oh my, you're quite virile.
She's a bit sexy to be a teacher, don't 'cha think?
I can't fucking stand it.
Fukurokoji-sensei, your classroom is here.
Have fun in there.
Now Yamagishi-sensei, this way.
Sensei...
S-Sorry!
Was this the wrong room?
Sensei, come on, let's start class.
Boss!
This place is strange...
Sensei.
Amazing!
Just too amazing!
Just too amazing...
This is your classroom, Yamagishi-sensei.
They are freshmen, class 1-B.
If you have any questions, come to me.
I will.
Th-Thanks.
Well then, do your best.
Okay.
Damn, damn.
First impressions are important.
What about this is "just too amazing"?
They're really well behaved.
I am...
He's so young and hot!
Oh, please touch me!
Well, but I'm...
Sensei, harder, please!
Yumiko, stop hogging him!
He belongs to all of us!
Yes, you can't hog him!
Hey, stop it! S-Stop it!
Put me down!
Put me down, I said!
I mean it!
Put me down!
Ow.
I'm going to be your teacher starting today.
My name is Yamagishi Yasohachi.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Yamagishi-sensei!
Shake, shake.
Is it just me, or are teenage girls these days
more overtly sexual than I imagined?
Let's see.
The new semester starts today. First period is...
Physical Examinations
Physical Examinations!
How lucky can I get on my first day?
Um, so girls, first you must...
Hey, hey, easy there.
Aren't you girls embarrassed to be completely
naked in front of a grown man?
Not really.
Not at all!
Seriously...
If they're just handing themselves to me on
a silver platter, where's the sport in it?
After all!
Physical examinations at this school
are conducted by our teachers.
And barehanded too.
Barehanded?
She's right.
See? Like this.
Squishy, squishy.
Feels like an 85-B to me.
Okay, next try kneading this in there.
Child's play!
Squeeze, squeeze.
See? Look!
Amazing!
Tamami-chan, you're really squeezing it good!
Well, I should.
This makes everything more pleasurable.
Yes, but...
Here, Sensei, measure me first.
Oh, really?
Then I guess I'll start.
Lucky.
Hurry, hurry! I'm up next.
Um, I think you're an 85-C.
Aw, you're done already?
Then, next up is...
Measure this too.
Now, now, get in line. Get in line.
So I guess... This is how it's done?
Very good, Sensei.
But go deeper, please.
Deeper?
Deeper.
Yes! Right there!
No fair!
Me too!
I guess I'll just have to measure
all of you at the same time!
Aw, Yamagishi-sensei!
Very nice.
Everything is proceeding according to plan.
Oh, shit.
The new teachers will undergo
physical examinations right now.
Please make your way to the
infirmary as quickly as possible.
Us too?
We're also going to be examined?
Let me repeat, please.
The new teachers must...
come to the infirmary immediately.
So this is the infirmary?
Yamagishi-sensei, Fukurokoji-sensei.
Welcome to the infirmary.
Now we will begin the examinations,
so please remove your clothes.
Once you're ready, step this way.
Oh? Underpants too, if you please.
You mean, buck naked?
Hurry, come here.
Please help us!
Hey, Sensei, will this examination
also be conducted barehanded?
No. It's an oral exam.
This feels great!
Will you please examine me too?
I-Is this okay?
Yes, hurry up.
Then I'm digging in!
Yes!
H-Huh?
My, my.
I should have known.
What gives you the right to hog the only
two men in this school all to yourself?
Let us make use of them as well.
There's only two of them to touch, ya know.
It's a free-for-all!
Very nice. Very nice.
Jeez!
Yamagishi-sensei hasn't come
back from the infirmary yet!
Yeah.
I think that sleazy nurse has
some scheme in mind.
She wants to take the men away from
us and hog them all to herself.
No way!
Okay!
Then the Sailor Bunny Girls need
to venture forth to save the day!
Stealing such wonderful men...
From sweet, innocent girls!
This will absolutely...
This will absolutely not be forgiven!
Hey, hey, hey!
We won't let our beloved teachers
fall victim to ugly old hags!
Silence, fools!
Come back in ten years when
you actually have breasts!
Exactly. This is adult play.
No fair!
Looks like we have no choice but
to show that our skills are better!
W-Wait just a minute.
I think we can work this out verbally.
Sensei, I've come to rescue you!
He's mine, bitch!
Very nice, very nice.
This would make a great plot for a porno.
Oops. My beard always grows
out when I'm excited.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Don't worry, Yamagishi-sensei. We've got you!
Boss!
What will become of me in here by myself?
Well, just hang in there!
And take care of my workload, okay?
Ah, ahem.
Anyway, the physical examinations are done.
So second period is... P.E.?
Sensei!
Is this a new move?
Didn't you know?
There's the squeeze, the lick...
all of these are important judo moves!
Ah, yeah right!
Sensei, why are you getting
so excited all by yourself?
Ah, um, well, it's nothing.
Just a minute. Maybe sumo
wrestling would be better.
Sensei, you perv!
Bleh.
Sensei!
We're all ready...
...for P.E.!
Right?
Yay!
Wh-What's this? What's this?
What the hell is this?
We have dance for P.E.!
Hey, knock it off!
This is supposed to be a class, not a disco!
Hey!
Come on!
Sensei, you're really good!
Really?
Yeah. You look just like a rapper.
Does this also look like a rapper?
Sensei! You're so hot!
Yay.
But is this really acceptable?
It is not acceptable. Not acceptable.
Having such a fun class in secret!
Oops.
Did you all find out I'm Hige Godzilla?
Hey! Are ya all tired up?
Then let me introduce your Disco Queen!
Disco Queen?
Yes.
The girl who's wearing the best
costume gets to be the Queen.
Okay, today's special Disco Queen is...
My attention... Let's see...
Yay!
H-Hige Godzilla? What the hell is he doing here?
Long time no see, Yamagishi-kun!
Do you know that weird old man?
Nope, I don't.
Aw, you meanie!
All along, I've been the principal
of Harenochi Academy!
You're kidding, right?
I was the one who called you and Ikidomari here.
What?
Well! That strange interlude is over,
so let's go, music!
Ow! Ow!
Pervert!
Jeez!
Get off, old man!
But I'm the principal of Harenochi Academy!
You meanies!
How dare you leave me out of the fun!
I won't let you get away with this!
All of you will be punished!
It's the Morality Enforcement Squad.
Not here!
The Morality Enforcement Squad?
Oh, no! Its the Morality Enforcement Squad!
This is an emergency situation.
This is an emergency situation!
Students have disobeyed the rules.
Members of the Morality Enforcement Squad...
Make your way to class 1-B at once!
Time for punishment!
This way! This way!
Why me?
Punishment time! Punishment time!
All of you will be pummeled to pieces.
Save me, save me!
Wh-Who are these guys?
They're the Morality Enforcement Squad!
If we cross them, we're in big trouble.
What?
It's you!
Yamagishi?
Y-Yeah.
I knew it was you, Yamagishi-kun!
That voice! Could you be...
Long time no see.
Jeez, it's Marugoshi-sensei!
Cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle...
But where did you get those tits?
Aw, now, don't stare at them like that, you perv.
I had a sex-change operation, dear.
You see, there were no male teachers
allowed at this school until this year,
so I got rid of my dick.
I did it so I could be here.
M-My condolences...
But my dick is still doing okay.
Doing okay?
Here is an announcement for all you guilty people.
You're going to be punished.
You're all under arrest!
Get them!
S-Stop it!
Outta my way!
I'll give you an enma!
No, not an enma!
Help me!
Stop it!
Take your filthy hands off my students!
Easy there, boy.
Arresting wayward students is my job.
You're not immune to my punishment either!
Wh-What the hell is that thing?
Go! Lock all the students up!
Yes'm!
We must punish our bad students.
D-Dammit. They're my students.
Give 'em back!
Oh, shit, Boss!
Snap out of it!
What's this thing?
That was a close one.
But who did this?
Hey, Ikidomari, we need to save everyone.
O-Okay...
W-Wait up, B-Boss.
I don't see the principal around.
Shit.
There must be some dark school
secret hidden in here.
If only you could talk...
Shit!
What's this?
"Please Plow Me Deeper. Hitomi?"
These are all adult videos!
What are these things doing at a school?
Look, Ikidomari. These are the
students that were locked up.
What is that place anyway?
Shit.
It must be somewhere on this campus.
Bad little girls must be punished.
That hurts!
Mommy! Mommy, help me!
That hurts! Ouch!
Very nice, very nice.
I can make another great porno out of this.
Oh, stop it!
Stop it!
Good job, Marugoshi-sensei.
You've outdone yourself with this plan.
Cry for me! Scream for me!
Yamagishi-sensei! Help me!
Scream and cry all you want,
but this is a secret room!
No one will hear you or rescue you!
That's right!
The only entrance to this secret
room is in the faculty restroom.
Yamagishi is so stupid he'll never figure that out.
A-Awesome...
Y-Yeah.
Wait, Boss, did you hear that?
H-Hear what?
I guess you wouldn't hear it.
You were obsessed with the monitors.
Sorry, sorry.
Anyway, let's go to the faculty restroom!
Yeah.
Boss!
This might be a trap!
Trap or not, we still need to rescue everyone!
But where do you think the secret entrance is?
I guess we'd better just look everywhere.
Looks like a normal toilet to me.
Yeah.
Oh, Yamagishi-sensei, you pervert.
Don't you at least know how to knock?
S-Sorry!
Good timing.
Let's continue what we started earlier.
We won't be disturbed now that we're in here.
That's very nice,
but we don't exactly have time for this right now.
We're so sorry!
Oh, they're just so naive.
Come on!
Hurry, open up!
This is the worst crisis of my life.
Yeah.
Hey, Ikidomari, why are there two flush levers?
Could it be...
Let's tug them both on the count of three.
Okay.
One, two, three!
Yamagishi-sensei?
My, no one's here?
Oh, rats.
It's the exit!
Boss!
We've been expecting you.
Oh, nice to see you all.
Yamagishi-sensei!
Please!
Help me!
You're a bit late,
even though I gave you a hint
about the secret entrance.
So it was a trap.
I had you two come to this school in the
first place to star in my porn videos.
What?
Well then, as you were hoping,
let's resume the games with the students, okay?
Boss!
I'll admit that the reason we came
to this school in the first place
was to have sex with the students.
But forcing someone to have sex when
she doesn't want to isn't my thing.
I refuse your offer!
T-That's my Boss!
Oh, what a lovely, self-righteous speech.
But I won't let you leave,
now that you've discovered the
secret of Harenochi Academy.
I'll make the two of you give up
your manhood, like we did.
Wh-What?
Wh-What is this?
Leggo, you bastard!
Boss!
With my balls getting squeezed like this,
it makes me forget why I wanted to
become a teacher in the first place!
Well? If you want to change
your mind, you still can.
I-I refuse.
Then go!
Squish those balls to smithereens!
Oh dear, that can't be!
– Who could that have been?
– Who did that!?
You disguised your establishment as a proper
school that educates innocent young girls.
But in reality, you are masters of punishment.
Inflicting harsh punishments on innocent
girls who have committed no indecency.
And what's more, even further demeaning
the girls by putting it on tape!
It's coming from the roof!
For committing such heinous acts,
I doubt you will be forgiven.
Ah! It's up there!
Get her!
In the name of God, I will pass judgment.
What?
It's Takegoshi!
Long time no see, Yamagishi-kun.
We're so s-sorry!
Th-Those guys!
They all used to teach at Harenchi Academy!
The friendship between teachers
at Harenchi Academy is eternal!
That's a fancy way of putting it!
In fact, you're all nasty perverts
who are into the same fetishes!
Oops.
He's right.
Now! Release everyone!
She's really cool, Boss.
She seems familiar too.
In what way?
It must be!
Wait, Boss.
Jubei.
Oh, stop it, Yamagishi-kun.
I knew it was you, Jubei.
What is Yagyu Jubei doing here?
I thought we were in the Heisei era now.
I'm the P.E. teacher here.
So that's why your statue is here.
Look here!
You can swap stories later!
But now it's enema time!
If you really like enemas that much,
I'll give you one right now!
Damn you!
This is my final weapon!
Yagyu-sensei!
Jubei!
This is my favorite punishment machine.
I like to call it "I'll make a habit of it".
"I'll make a habit of if?"
Once you get caught up in this machine,
a normal man won't satisfy you anymore.
Wh-What?
Very nice, very nice.
Jubei, I'm coming to save you now.
Jubei's crotch.
Oops, what's that?
Not that!
Not that?
That makes me want it even more.
But that was my favorite uniform!
Oh, what a nice view.
Boss!
Time to take off the remaining clothes!
W-Wow... This is really getting me off.
No, stop it!
Very nice, very nice.
No... No, no... This feels great!
It looks like she's never felt that
good before, doesn't it, Boss!?
How can you be happy about that!?
If this keeps up,
I'll be so desensitized I'll never feel
pleasure from a normal man again!
That would be horrible!
So they still oppose me?
Time for my dick!
Time for my best weapon to come forth!
Launch the final weapon!
Wh-What the fuck is that?
I gave my severed dick a huge
power-up as a cyborg!
Very nice, very nice.
Shove that thick rod into Jubei.
No! Stop it!
Not my precious place!
It will break!
Very nice, Marugoshi!
Fine.
This only seats one!
Then you get off!
Get off, get off!
Shit! You fucking asshole!
Stop it.
It won't stop.
My school...
What's the ruckus about?
Wh-What's going on?
Dunno.
Stop it! Let go of it!
Let go of it! Let go!
You let go!
Yamagishi-kun!
Stupid, stupid, not here!
Boss!
Yamagishi-kun.
He tried to save me.
There's no stopping me.
The control room didn't even so much as shake!
Now, time to thrust my dick into Jubei.
J-Jubei!
No!
What's happening?
I was almost there!
How dare you!
You stupid fucking piece of junk!
Oh, I wasn't saying that to you.
No!
Mercy.
Sensei, I was so scared!
You're all safe now.
Oh, please have mercy!
Not yet, not yet.
Give me a nice apology.
I promise I won't do it again, so forgive me.
I really am so sorry.
We're so sorry, so please stop punishing us!
They gave us some pretty nice apologies, eh, Boss?
Huh, Boss?
Yagyu-sensei is gone too.
Boss!
No!
Oh, cut it out!
Please, just once!
Let me give you an enema!
Pervert!
But that's what I love about you.
Jubei!
No! You pervert!
It was ten years ago, when
they were students together.
Professor Nagai
But then, at Harenochi Academy...
They met once again,
and their childhood friendship
blossomed into an adult romance.
And this concludes the
"Heisei Harenchi Gakuen" series!
Well then, until we meet again!
kibou no oka ni
Atop the hills of hope,
kagayaku gakuen
The Academy sparkles.
miageru shisen no saki de
And at the end of my upward gaze,
pantsu chirari to sasou
Flashes of panties entice me.
kamatsuka houmurikomi okay
I've buried my rod, okay.
kore ga otoko no honnou
That's a man's instinct.
come on koreba nandemo ari da yo
Come on, everything you want is here.
tottemo kimochi no ii koto
It's a very nice place.
kyou mo kikoeru kiyoi sakebi ga
And the youthful screams I hear today.
arashi o yobu yo
Will call forth a storm.
heisei harenchi gakuen
Heisei Harenchi Academy.
tooku asahi ni
In the distant morning sun,
haeru manabiya
I clearly see the place of learning.
hosometa shisen no saki de
At the end of my squinting gaze,
mune no kage ga maneku
I see the light casting shadows on the boobs.
come on mokkori okay
Come on, my pants-tent is okay.
kore ga otoko no honnou
That's a man's instinct.
monbushou de buka wa dekinai
The officials at the Ministry of Education can't do this.
utatteru kimochi no ii koto
They can't sing with good feeling.
omowase buri no amaeta taido
And the fake-innocent actions of the girls.
arashi o yobu yo
Will call forth a storm.
heisei harenchi gakuen
Heisei Harenchi Academy.
omoeba fukai
I just realized how deep.
watashi no kouun
My good luck runs.
kansha no shisen no saki de
At the end of my thankful gaze,
josei o oikake semaru
Lots of girls are racing towards me.
jouken naiyou okay
The terms and conditions are okay.
kore ga otoko no honnou
That's a man's instinct.
kyoushi mo seito mo kankei nashi da yo
The labels "teacher" and "student" have no meaning.
ichiban kimochi no ii koto
And that's the best feeling of all.
dare mo ga yoromeku etchi na shigusa ga
And the sexy signals everyone moans out.
arashi o yobu yo
Will call forth a storm.
come on koreba nandemo ari da yo
Come on, everything you want is here.
tottemo kimochi no ii koto
It's a very nice place.
kyou mo kikoeru kiyoi sakebi ga
And the youthful screams I hear today.
arashi o yobu yo
Will call forth a storm.
heisei harenchi gakuen
Heisei Harenchi Academy.