Training to overcome stage fright?
Yes...
I get nervous whenever we compete and
I can't even put in half of my practice strength into it.
I understand your feelings but... what should we do?
No matter what kind of training it
is I'll be fine if it's with sensei.
Even if it's really erotic things...
Seriously?
Seriously!?
Well... t-that's going to be a p-problem...
Special training?
With onee-chan and sensei only?
Translation: Shintojmk | Translation Check: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
High School Girls' Waists
Part One: The Beach Volleyball Club
Hey don't hide it,
show me properly.
Yes...
I understand.
It's not going to be just a couple
people looking during the match.
It won't do if you can't stand this
level of embarrassment with ease.
But this is still embarrassing...
Doing this in a bikini.
You let your boyfriend do this all the time don't you?
I don't have a boyfriend!
Then how about with a bunch of old men
that you don't even know the name of?
That, that kind of thing...
Sucking a bunch of cocks in a hotel room...
What should I do? There's dicks everywhere.
I'm going to be completely messed up...
Not just your mouth,
but they use here as well.
No, sensei! Don't churn me up like that!
Having them cum all over your cute face,
and taking pictures of your cum covered body.
Sensei!
I'm cumming!
Did I tease you a little too much?
But this is part of your training as well.
Sensei...
Hey...
Let me suck you.
To think that you offered to suck me off, I'm glad.
I can't take it...
When Sensei says all these naughty things,
I get more and more excited! I can't stop!
This is bad, I can't hold it in for much longer.
But it can't be helped. Since it's one
of my own students sucking me off,
of course I'll get excited.
Saori!
Ah, his dick is twitching, he's going to ejaculate soon.
I feel like my mouth's just a masturbation tool.
If you put on such a happy and lewd face...
You'll make me want to tease you morel
Wait Sensei! This is the hallway. The hallway!
What if someone comes and sees us?
Onee-chan...
What are you doing?
It hurts... it hurts!
Saori... could it be that, this is your first time?
Yes... it hurts but I'm happy.
So... so cute!
No... if I keep watching, I'll get turned on too.
Sensei, as expected this is still embarrassing!
What if someone sees?
Isn't it perfect for your special training?
That's...!
No!
Don't!
No! Don't look!
Saori's pussy is soaked from having a penis inside!
You can't look!
You got tighter, did you imagine
something that turned you on?
I... I... I di-didn't!
One-onee-chan...
Her face says that she's really enjoying it...
I can't hide anything looking like
this... If someone comes along...
They'll see everything!
Saori... your pussy's the best!
I'm really getting turned on by this...
I want everyone to see me when I'm having sex!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Saori, can I cum inside you?
Yes!
Cum, cum in me sensei.
Someone, someone come! When
I get creampied by Sensei...
Look! Watch it! Watch it!!
How do you feel? Do you still
need special training, Saori?
Yes, please train me again next time, sensei.
Huh?
Special training? Again?
That's right. I want to have sensei train
me like you did for onee-chan.
But... that's...
It's okay sensei!
Actually, I saw you two.
if you're willing to train me as well.
I'll keep quiet about it.
You're quiet rough aren't you.
You're the one who invited me right.
That's because! I want to be done like onee-chan, too.
To be honest, I thought you were going to get mad.
I was surprised at first but onee-chan
looked like she was really into it.
Before I realized it,
I started masturbating while spying on you two.
So you were jealous, is that it?
But, it's not like I'm interested in you.
Don't get the wrong idea!
Ok, just stay like that.
Okay.
You're getting wetter and wetter. It's drenched now.
Sensei, how's my pussy compared to onee-chan's?
You're both pretty, enough to make me want to suck it.
What? You came already?
Can I suck yours as well?
Sure, get on top of me.
So it gets this big when it's hard.
This was going in and out of onee-chan's pussy...
Sawa, you're pussy's twitching, are you that excited?
This is so embarrassing, when I think
about his dick, my pussy starts...
It feels good!
Sensei, I'm going... I'm going to cum again.
Talking about onee-chan all the time, you're
quite close to having a sister complex, Sawa.
Before you go down some strange path, it's
best you remember what a man feels like.
He's putting it in, he's going to put it in!
Wow, it's so tight.
As expected from a virgin pussy.
Hey sensei, is all of it in?
What, is my dick that small?
That's not it, it's just, it doesn't
hurt like I thought it would.
In fact...
In fact what?
It feels really good!
Hey, hey say it properly.
It's good, it's really good.
My pussy feels really good!
It's making really sexy noises.
You're moving your hips by yourself.
What are you talking about?
Sensei!
I think I might want to keep sensei all to myself.
Sorry, onee-chan!
What!?
My ass, something's in my ass!
I didn't know you were being trained
by sensei as well, Sawa.
O-onee...
You know... there's a looong explanation to this.
I don't really care, it's not like I'm dating sensei.
It's just a one-sided love.
Onee-chan, what are you doing?
It seems like Sawa can feel it from her butt as well,
so I'll fuck you from behind.
Wait, wait a second!
No!!
No!
I don't want anything other than Sensei's dick!
Take it out, out, out!
Sensei, if it was me I'd let you fuck my
ass and anywhere else you want.
You can have a lot more fun with me than with Sawa.
Wow, she's churning up inside.
Onee-chan, please, stop!
Don't stir around inside so roughly.
Sawa's ass is really tight too.
My pussy's really happy too.
No way, I'm getting even more turned on by it.
I'm getting so turned on, getting fucked in both holes.
I'm slowly turning in to a slut like this!
I can't take it anymore!
Me tool My pussy is cumming soon! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Sensei, why don't we have a competition
on who can make you cum more?
Hey! Don't decided that on your own!
It's fine, it'll be easy.
It's not size that satisfies sensei anyways.
In the end, I'm being pushed around by my students.
So, with that being said, sensei, let's have sex!