Master! I beg of you.
I have done nothing wrong!
Breaking the Code is not wrong?
Shujima.
My hem... Someone stepped
on the hem of my robe!
Who did?
Well, that...
That figure was...
Oshizu.
That fiend!
Ooedo 48
Translation: Voldemort | Timing: Nicolai | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWawe | QC: Brush
The Second Chapter
The Beginnings of Binding Women
Azami-dono, enough naughtiness.
You've been doing nothing
but fooling around.
Have you no tasks to keep yourself busy?
I don't!
There are many servant girls here.
There's nothing left for me to do.
Searching for something
to do is part of your job.
Fine. But you still...
You still aren't fit to tend to anyone other
than commoners, right, Midai-sama?'
Or is it about time for one?
Damn you! How dare you
speak to me that way!
How rude!
Azami-sama!
Would you mind carrying the
belongings from Nagatsubo?
I refuse!
My nails will chip!
Well then, I would at least like you
to bring Midai-sama her supper.
I refuse!
That would soil my hands.
In that case, Azami-sama, would you
wash the dishes after the next meal?
I refuse!
How dare you ask that of a higher-class girl!
Oshizu-sama, I'm begging you,
I need some help from you.
But we mustn't!
We're both on duty right now.
Oops, wrong room!
Sorry about that. By all means, continue.
Oshizu-sama... That's your name, right?
The girl from a farm in Edo. What a
rare find in this place. An exotic girl.
Would you like to converse
with me in my room,
instead of this dark creepy place?
Um, I'd like to...
...but we have work to do.
Silence!
I did not ask the bitch what she thought!
Everyone here is so obsessed
with work and rules!
And they say it's fun here?
I should never have come!
This rotten place...
What an impudent attitude.
Azami-sama!
– Well then, I will be waiting at our place.
– Just what do you find irritating about me?
I find everything irritating!
How many times must I tell
you before you understand?
The new recruit is very nice.
That rotten girl? What do you
expect me to do with her?
I think you should just punish her
and reform her with the rest.
I thought that was the duty of the
person who brought her here.
Though if she causes a specific problem,
I wouldn't mind punishing her.
But why? Why don't we just
put her in her place?
To start with, she's a fool.
She doesn't have any skills.
I have no idea why Master wanted her here.
Well, I do admit she's very amusing.
Is that all? Are you targeting her?
Lazy girls are not my type.
Some restraint, please.
An acupuncturist once gave me a needle
and taught me a special way to use it.
I'm sure you are familiar with acupuncture?
Amazing. Very impressive.
How about you, Midai-sama?
Perhaps so...
Maybe I should try it out.
Well then, come here.
Yonemiya-sama?
Are you all right?
Shall we go?
I thought she wouldn't appear last night,
but starting this way so early?
Pretty one, wait for me.
I will rescue you from this place.
You were good last night, Kira.
Thank you very much.
That woman won't pursue the Master when
she can make love to you instead.
I'm certain we have her fooled.
Every morning and every night!
I have to meet a horny military general?
What hogwash!
Azami-sama,
you mustn't speak that way.
And what's more, that woman!
Note: Kiri means "fog". Kasu means "garbage".
Kiri or Kasu or whatever her name is!
She's from a lower-class family either way!
Please stop this!
That old lady Yonemiya is a real bitch too!
Probably because her trainee is more
popular with men than she is.
That bitch!
Azami-sama, I think it would be
best for you to seal your lips.
Oshizu-sama, you have no sense
of refinement anyway.
You're just peasant scum.
Oh, scary!
Listen, because Oshizu-sama
won't help me out,
my lower parts are getting all rotten.
What should I do?
I understand.
Very well. I will partner with her.
But her punishment... will not be ordinary!
Azami... sama.
Next, we will use this.
It is a bit on the thin side, but it will do.
No!
Not that! It's too sharp.
So she dislikes sharp things...
Yes. She says it's because
she loses her mood.
The sight of it makes her sweat.
I have heard of this before.
A person's dislikes are varied
and unaccountable.
Kira-sama... about my reward...
The warehouse key. You
may use it as you wish.
You're giving these to me?
Yes. These are training
tools for new recruits.
I also have them.
Again with the strange tools...
Are these the only shapes available?
Apparently these are
currently the most popular.
I would like something a little different.
Are there others?
Um, I think there are.
I hear that there is a secret collection
of them deep in the warehouse.
Secret collection?
Yes, including unusually long ones.
I hear that women with small
holes can't even use them.
Which means that none of them are sharp?
Sharp? Well, I suppose not.
She fell for it, as expected.
You're good, Oshizu.
This must be it.
Oh, I see.
Very nice.
Feels nice...
Damn you, intruder!
What are you doing with
our manhood dolls?
A doll...
It is a special doll that has been handed
down through the military families.
Brace yourself, bitch!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Now, I will begin this foolish
girl's punishment.
You must make sure to notice
her despicable appearance.
First, from Midai-sama.
This is something Master gave me once.
He told me I could use it any way I wanted.
See? I also have the pointed things you like.
N-Not that!
No! Stop it!
Azami-dono, you never had
such fun before today.
Let us all punish her together.
I can keep this up forever, Azami-dono.
Next, I shall...
Oh my, how embarrassing for her.
How disgusting.
Has she no shame?
I can't take this anymore!
Have you gotten a sufficient
taste of our Code?
This is the place where I was raised.
Do not come to suffer here again.
Burn this memory into your brain.
The Punishment Continues...
Dazzling Brocade
Starling
Nutty Peony
Treasure Boat
Clams Joines
Assault on the Flower Petals
Disorderly Order
High Mountains
Anvil