As a token of my thanks...
I offer you my body.
At any time...
you can throw me out.
Until you get married, you can make use of me.
Momoko...
Kentaro...
vol.2
Audition, I am the True Heroine!
Come now, cheer up.
That was nothing to mope about.
Okay.
Have a nice day.
Bye then.
Well, my first day!
Time to go at it full bore!
Ah, let me on too!
Oh, dear.
Oh, shit.
She's really late. I wonder
what's keeping Momoko?
She's reached her time limit.
Oh, well then.
And here I thought she was a good worker.
But Chief, I think she might be here already.
Let's wait just a little bit longer.
Oh? You seem to know something we don't.
What is it?
Uh, u-um, nothing.
Department Head
Now, you'll give people the wrong
impression if you dress like that.
Sorry to cause trouble.
Um, so what are you going to do about your skirt?
Right! W-Well, um, if I could
just borrow your curtains...
Curtains, eh?
Huh? You want a skirt?
You're too loud!
I-I just need it, okay?
Um, I mean that I need a skirt as a model.
But why are you in charge of this?
Because it's a necessity!
Daddy, what happened to your jacket?
Never mind that, get me a skirt!
Beautiful!
What a beautiful skirt.
Fits me perfectly.
It's a perfect fit.
She has that soft, marshmallowy skin of youth.
All the qualities of Eve...
Gentlemen prefer blonds.
There's no business like show business.
Those are Marilyn Monroe
references, aren't they?
Yes!
You are unmistakably Monroe!
Monroe is someone I deeply respect.
Are you free tonight?
I'd like you to accompany me on my dream.
Do you all understand?
I don't think yelling at us during
the presentation will help.
What makes this product useful?
And conversely, when would this
product not provide benefits?
I leave the TPO to Morita.
Understand?
I'm sorry for being late.
Momoko?
Oh, my?
What?
I got lost trying to find this room.
I'm very sorry about it.
What? That's my skirt!
Our company is a little different from waitressing.
You need to be punctual.
Yes, ma'am.
This means...
- You must not be late.
- That skirt looks good on you.
Very good.
Oh, r-really?
K-Kentaro!
Wh-What is it?
I finally got evidence that Daddy's cheating!
W-With whom?
With that girl.
Morita Momoko.
Momoko?
Spectacular!
So deeply moving!
Truthfully!
Your size is exactly the same.
166 cm.
53.2 kg
Just like Monroe!
Really?
Then let's go, Miss Monroe.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
Well, I had no idea you wanted to be an actress.
It's possible that I could bring about
a huge change to your life.
Making me dress like this...
I wonder if he's thing to seduce me?
Yes. In time.
How lewd of Daddy!
I'll never forgive him.
B-But you still don't know it's true.
He's taken a room in a hotel.
Everyone can see what he's doing.
You're just too gullible.
Momoko would do that?
Kawakami-san has ordered a few drinks,
and he just left for his room.
Spending the night with her already?
Daddy, you're so immora!
If he does that, it's all over!
B-But it's not what you think.
Goodness.
He really can't hold his liquor.
Monroe, dear...
What do you mean, "Monroe, dear"?
What happened to helping me with my career?
He had all the fun by himself.
I'm wiped out.
I found you, you whore!
What are you trying to do
by deceiving my daddy?
"Daddy"?
Daddy! Oh, Daddy, wake up!
He's her daddy, I guess.
Daddy! Oh, Daddy!
Monroe, dear...
Daddy?
You're fired!
You're fired, you slut!
Fired?
You were only after his money
anyway, weren't you?
Wh-What is it?
If your daddy is so gullible that women
can easily deceive him for his money,
why don't you lock him up in the bank?
And don't forget to bring a
match if you wanna fire me.
Oh, how infuriating!
Did you hear the things she said about you?
Daddy!
Monroe, dear...
Daddy! Oh, Daddy, come on!
You really are too reckless!
You had no reason to be alone with
the department head like that!
Yeah, but I had no idea.
That's why I say you're too reckless!
If I'd known he was that loaded,
I probably would've slept with him.
Idiot!
I was seriously worried about you!
I got fired, and I'm sorry.
You're right. I'm too reckless.
Starting tomorrow, I'll look for another job.
Never mind. Don't bother.
Just stay home.
I don't want to.
Come on.
I don't mind.
Hey, that hurts.
They've started it again.
Good morning.
Here's your paper.
Good work last night.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, what do you want on your toast?
Margarine?
Or jam?
Is there something on my face?
Um, no, you just seem different than usual.
Probably because I changed my hairstyle.
N-Now that you mention it...
I guess I got a little carried away
with looking like Monroe.
I see.
I wonder how...
the department head felt when
Monroe ran out on him?
Monroe was his boyhood dream.
I guess everyone has their innocent side.
He only looks like a harsh boss to me.
Good morning.
Hi.
Y-You don't look so hot, Haruo.
After spending the whole night awake
listening to the devil's dirty dance,
anyone would look sick!
Well then...
It's time to go to work.
Night time is completely insane.
Oh, Kentaro, you forgot something.
Have a nice day.
Cheerful pose!
Listen, listen, the Boss is raving mad!
What's the cause?
Morita Momoko.
She's disappeared!
That silly girl.
I hope the boss didn't really snap too badly.
Now listen, you!
We need to search for her more thoroughly.
How is it possible that no
one knows where she is?
I know I may be getting on
in years, I'll admit that...
but regardless!
Without that girl around, nothing will begin!
Do you know where she lives?
Sh-She looks like the type of girl
who could live anywhere.
What are you kids babbling about?
Make every effort to find
someone of that appearance!
I don't fall for just anyone, you hear?
I already have an investigator
searching for her in Ginza.
She's truly one of a kind!
She's a diamond.
A Monroe for our era.
She will truly be reborn.
M-Monroe...
But then that stupid daughter
of mine misunderstood her.
And I have the CEO's permission to proceed.
The CEO?
We're going to use her as our
company's campaign model.
She will be our company's video queen!
Momoko... Momoko will be
Soby's... video queen?
Anyway, find Morita Momoko at any cost!
What's wrong, Minami-kun?
Nothing, sir. Got it.
Comb through the grass if you have to!
Find Morita Momoko!
Oh, Juliet.
At the hour of nine.
Yes, the hour of nine.
Let me stand here ten or twenty
years till thou remember it.
Tis almost morning; I would have thee gone:
And yet no further than a wanton's bird;
Who lets it hop a little from her hand,
- And with a silk thread plucks it back again,
- Oteru, I should probably quit this acting school.
- So loving-jealous of his liberty...
- Me too.
We're doing old things like Shakespeare
or plays written twenty years ago,
as though this is Romper Room or something.
That's probably why neither
of us is getting a break.
Oh, Haruo.
Put Momoko on.
Haruo! What's wrong?
Haruo!
I-I'm busy studying.
What's wrong with him?
Oh, and also, Reiko-san is here.
Hello? It's me, Reiko.
I've left home, so let me stay for a while, okay?
H-Here you go.
Wow, you keep this place pretty clean.
R-Right!
I've found her.
She's enrolled in an acting
school called "Kazesan".
If we wait for her there, we're
sure to see her, Minami-kun.
That won't help. She's probably
at my house right now...
meeting up with her!
What's wrong, Minami-kun?
We're going.
O-Okay.
I'm a man!
If a woman is defenseless near
me, even I have my limits.
Listening to the devil's dance
every night is killing me.
Even a Tokyo U guy needs some action.
If she's asleep on my couch with her legs open,
what's wrong with showing her
a little hospitality down there?
Okay...
It's time to go for it!
I'm gonna fuck her brains out.
I-I did it!
Now I'm a man.
But I wonder how she can sleep through this.
That tickles.
T-Tickles?
D-Dammit!
Then I'll fuck you!
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang...
You're so small.
I see.
She'd prefer someone from the
other side of the Pacific Ocean?
I'm home!
Wilder, I bought you a new cactus.
Haruo? What are you doing over here?
Oh, my! How awesome. You brought a girl over!
You surprise me.
I guess even stuffy Tokyo U students
can get it on when they want to.
Oh, shut up.
She looks familiar.
She's Senpai's fiancée.
She likes a differently favored man.
Say, don't you think it'd be
bad if she saw me here?
Bad? What would be?
She's awake!
A foreign man...
- I had the weirdest dream.
- Dream?
This little sausage kept brushing up against me.
Kentaro...
- I guess I'd better explain myself.
- That's me.
Y-You are...
I'm Morita Momoko.
You're Daddy's whore, aren't you!?
I am not!
She's Senpai's sex friend.
It's true.
No way.
A Tokyo U nerd with a roommate
would never score a girl like you.
Daddy asked you to take care of him, didn't he?
You really are a horrible bitch!
You're only after Daddy's fortune, aren't you?
She's a horrible woman!
Wiener...
I guess we missed the ball.
Chief, I don't think she'll show up.
Should we try again tomorrow?
Hey, Kentaro.
What is it?
Let's forget about work for now,
and instead explore the relationship
between men and women.
Chief?
Just get out of here!
If you think you can have your way
here, you're sadly mistaken!
What a dork.
I'm only taking a bath.
I'm tired.
You little bitch!
How dare you use Kentaro's
bath like it's no big deal!
Stop being so pushy.
Ready to launch!
You lustful bird!
You sinister lawbreaker!
You're nothing more than a slutty mistress!
How does she know?
And how exactly do you intend to keep hiding it?
All right!
A sharp-tongued bitch needs
something sharp for her face!
What's... this?
It's Wilder's dinner.
Wilder!
This isn't fun.
Maybe I ought to shove a beer bottle up her ass.
We're leaving very soon.
It's started raining, after all.
Kentaro, what do you think of me?
What do I think?
Who did this!?
Who twisted my panties backwards?
Oh dear, she noticed.
Who did this!?
Don't tell me...
Sorry, but I'm the one who twisted them.
Why did you do that?
A man's pilgrimage is a big undertaking.
In other words, if this can go
in, then... Monster Hole!
Do you understand what that means?
Monster Hole!
She's right!
A dick would feel like a skinny
worm in comparison.
There's no friction.
Why are you saying something like that?
That moron.
I was trying to cover for him.
Oh, no!
I'll call the cops on you!
I was raped!
I'm calling the cops on you!
Be my guest.
And I'll also be sure to tell them the truth,
Monster Hole!
Ch-Chief?
P-Please stop this!
Oh, now, no need to be shy.
How cute!
But I like someone else.
You do?
Who?
Morita Momoko.
Welcome home.
Monster HoleMomoko.
You didn't know when I was coming home,
but you waited here the whole time?
Yup.
I guessed.
Momoko.
You're totally soaked. Let's go back.
Wanna take a detour?
Chief Kawakami speaking.
Sorry to call you so late.
We've located Morita Momoko.
Yes. Minami-kun is supposed
to bring her back to work.
Thank you very much.
What a stupid guy.
Falling for Momoko like that.
Oh dear, I fell asleep.
You're beautiful, Momoko.
I love you.
What's wrong with you, Kentaro?
You're acting strange.
You said you wanted to be an actress
like Marilyn Monroe, didn't you?
What about it?
I know you can do it.
You're going to be on TV in Japan every day.
Come back to work with me tomorrow.
Back to work?
If you tell me to go back, then...
It shouldn't matter what I tell you to do.
It's your big chance to be famous.
Kentaro...
Powers outside of my control have
already set the gears in motion.
Well, Minami-kun! You did well for me, son!
In time, those Monroe pictures will
turn into posters of Momoko.
So I'll be the video queen of Soby.
Yes. Exactly.
And I want you to meet the CEO right away.
I guess I'll give it a try.
B-Boss...
I guess it's been decided.
Idiot.
I wonder if it's okay.
You worrying won't help anything.
I can only hope that the CEO refuses.
That would suit you better, wouldn't it?
Oh my. You were here all along?
Kentaro, did you see the company news?
That girl, you know?
She's going to be our campaign model.
I really was foolish.
Oh my, my.
Looks like I'm in the way.
Hey, Kentaro,
I have a favor to ask.
Someone might come!
I want you to apologize to Daddy.
Okay, I will.
Really?
Stupid Daddy, he got mad and me
and froze all my credit cards!
Money?
Looks like she's going somewhere
where I can't reach her.
Hi. Sorry for the wait.
Oh?
Ah, this is it.
I wonder what's so great
about that bitch anyway?
She's just a pig.
That's it!
Did you talk to Daddy for me?
I was too busy, so not yet.
Then that means I can't use my credit cards!
I guess you're treating today.
Senpai! Why were you wandering around?
It's your turn to cook today!
Sorry about that.
You could have called at least... or something.
Now I can't jump out. It's too dark.
And here I wanted to surprise you,
but you look so glum.
Momoko...
This isn't like you, Kentaro.
If you have a problem, I'll listen to all of it.
Momoko...
Huh?
Momoko!
I guess it's time.
This is our PR rep, and this is our director.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
And I know this is short notice,
but we need to put send you to the Seychelles
immediately to shoot a commercial.
I thought it'd only be as far as Okinawa.
By the way, I can bring an assistant, can't I?
An assistant?
Oh, good idea.
Monroe must have her assistant.
How about Minami-kun?
Right, Chief?
Minami-kun?
Thank you.
Daddy.
I'm very sorry.
As long as you really feel that way...
No reason to look so glum.
You need to cheer up and go to the Seychelles.
I can really go to the Seychelles?
Daddy, I love you!
Easy, easy.
That girl is already...
no longer just Momoko.
She's becoming... a different person.
And she's gone to a place where
you can no longer reach her.
Momoko-chan!
We want to show a little more of
your boobs, so give us a shake!
What?
You want me to shake my boobs?
If you want more boobs, why
don't I just take off my top?
Um, we don't need that much more.
Then how much farther should I slip it down?
Tell me more clearly!
You're the director, aren't you?
Sorry.
Just be natural about it. Yes.
What do you mean, "Be natural"?
I discovered long ago that there's
nothing natural about me.
I guess she's excited about the change in lifestyle.
It's like a Cinderella story.
I agree.
Yes.
Momo-chan, you're the wind!
You're the birds!
You're the clouds!
You're the butterflies!
You're the beetles!
I appreciate his enthusiasm, but
I wish he'd just leave me alone.
What's wrong?
Hey, look at that!
Hey.
Momoko!
Someone! Do something quick!
Poke, poke.
Moron!
Just joking, just joking.
Thank God it was a joke!
Cut it out. I've got a bad heart.
So, you did come to rescue me.
Kentaro.
Kentaro...
Reiko?
Reiko-san...
What the hell!
You were making out with her!
But that was because Momoko, um,
Morita-san almost drowned.
I had to save her!
And then, I, um, had to administer CPR,
and, um...
mouth-to-mouth. Yeah...
You really do cause us a lot of trouble.
When I first met you, I thought you were cute.
But you're a firecracker.
Hey, Chief...
What is it?
I wonder if those two are having sex.
They must be.
How can you ask that with a straight face?
Should we go look?
Momo-chan!
It's only because I don't let you do me.
Isn't that right?
But I'm your boss's daughter and your fiancée
yet you're with that slut.
Fiancée, my ass.
Boss's daughter, my ass.
If we're talking bust size, I'm
better than her anyway!
Yet you fell under that slut's spell
and dared to humiliate me!
You don't even deserve to be in
the same sentence as Momoko.
I wonder if they even sell condoms on this island?
Just leave those two alone.
I wonder if Kentaro is on top.
Just go to bed!
Or maybe he's on the bottom...
Bottom or top, I'm so jealous.
Ah, what a mess.
Or maybe 69...
Oh, aren't you with the agency?
Oh, bon soir, Chief.
What do you mean, "Bon soir"?
What are you doing out here?
I was just bored and ended up here.
Yes, it's very boring.
This night should be promising,
but I guess I'll hold back.
Bon soir, Chief!
Bon soir.
I guess I do hate it.
The idea of Kentaro with another woman.
Though I already knew that.
K-Kentaro.
Kentaro...
Chief!
Oh, yes.
Harder. Harder.
I guess there are nights like this.
Momoko...
Kentaro.
Hey!
I'll shake... all you want.
So somebody, please take me!
Your shadow lies on the white
sidewalk in the daytime.
shiroi hodou ni kimi no kage ga utsuru daytime
Your pointed pistol is poised to shoot me.
hitosashi kimi no pisutoru boku ni nerai sadame
The instant before I fall in love, my heart screams.
koi ni ochiru isshun mae muna-sawagi
With my heart as your target,
you pop-pop-pop the trigger.
haato megakete dan da da hikigane o hiku
Encounters are always unexpected happenings,
deai wa itsumo totsuzen happening
and everything changes with tomorrow.
soshite asu ga kawatte yuku kara
We'll take the next step together.
tsugi no suteppu futari de fumi dasu
I'm gonna make it happen.
i'm gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
See? I can feel something in the atmosphere.
hora nanika hajimaru atmosphere
You're gonna make it happen.
you're gonna make it happen
It's gonna be a sensation.
it's gonna be a sensation
Don't let this moment get away.
ima kono toki o nogasanai
Even though I ran all the way from
the subway, I'm out of time.
chikatetsu made iki o kirashita no ni time up