Getting it all wet and slippery and then stroking it...
is how you like it right?
Does it feel good?
While I'm lost in her sweet, innocent looking face,
her lower body melts into mine.
Wow!
It's so thick!
You see!?
It's slippery... and it feels so good!
It really is great.
I guess the final parts are assembled at last.
The final... parts?
Accelerando
~ Whisper of the Fallen Angels ~
CONTENTS.4
Now, our new transfer student
will introduce herself to the class.
I'm Hirohashi. It's nice to meet all of you.
I'm still new here and don't know the town very well,
so I'd appreciate any help you can give me.
She's cute.
Yoshioka-kun?
Y-Yes?
She lives near your house, so
could you walk her home today?
Y-Yes ma'am.
Do you two know each other?
N-No.
Your brother?
Yes. He looks ailot like you, so
it surprised me for a moment.
I see. So you have a brother.
I had one.
Would you like to visit my house?
O-Okay.
I'm sorry it's still a bit messy.
I just moved in, you know.
Is this all right?
Th-This seems to be your bedroom...
I'll make some coffee. Please wait a moment.
I'll help you put away your things.
Wh-What!?
It's heavy...
Ah, don't worry about that.
That box is already "put away".
R-Really?
That picture...
It looks pretty intense.
That's a painting of me that my brother did.
So that's your...
My brother died two years ago.
He was always in poor health.
He was really sick.
I loved him very much.
What?
So, I decided.
That I would get my brother back at any cost.
H-Hirohashi-san?
And now the final parts have been assembled.
The final... parts?
I must be dreaming...
I just met this girl today.
While I'm lost in her sweet, innocent looking face,
her lower body melts into mine.
Hirohashi-san...
What's... happening?
You don't need to worry about anything.
Although you probably wont be able to move for a while.
So please, lets feel good together... Nii-san?
Your dick is so hard! Nii-san, are you enjoying it?
Nii-san! Nii-san!
I'm gonna pee!
Is that okay? It'll get all over you, Nii-san!
How was it, Nii-san?
Did it feel good?
Wh-Why... are you...
I've searched for you for a long time.
Hirohashi-san... Not there...
It's dirty.
I don't mind.
It feels so nostalgic!
Yes, like that!
You always used to... rub my breasts like that.
Hirohashi-san?
Don't you feel it?
My nipples are so hard and sensitive!
I-I'm cumming!
That boy... his feet were exactly like my brother's.
Stick your fingers... inside of me... right here.
My fingers?
Hirohashi, you're really perverted.
Please!
Amazing!
You're already soaking wet and squishy.
It's because our fingers... look like my brother's.
What you're saying doesn't make any sense.
Nii-san!
It looks like my fingers can go in deeper.
Good! Put them in deeper!
Move them around!
It's wonderful!
Hey, can I put my dick inside?
I'm sorry. Will you please let me cum
with you just using your fingers, first?
Afterwards, I'll let you do whatever you want!
What the hell? Oh well.
Then, beg me for it more.
Please!
My squishy, soaking wet place...
My filthy perverted pussy!
Stick your fingers in deeper, please!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
That boy's fingers looked almost exactly like my brother's.
Hirohashi-san!?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
I just can't hold out any longer.
It's hot.
Amazing.
It's getting harder by the second.
Please let me see it.
I knew it.
Your dick... it's really wonderful.
R-Really? I'm not really that big or thick.
That doesn't matter to me.
Your dick looks just like my brother's.
Not just the size, but the smell, and the texture...
It's air the same.
D-Don't do that!
If you do that, I'll cum right away!
Hirohashi-san! That's too rough! I'm gonna...
Wow. A lot came but.
Did it feel good?
That boy's dick and his sperm...
tasted the same as my brother's.
And then, at last I found you...
Nii-san.
But...
Just like we always did before,
let's make ourselves feel good.
I'll put it in for you.
It's getting harder and harder!
So big!
It's so tight, but it's all inside.
Nii-san!
N-No!
It's getting even bigger!
She's squeezing me so tightly, I can feel it.
I can't move...
It's been so long since I've done this!
I-I'm so turned on!
It's still... coming-out.
Nii-san, your sperm is amazing.
Lots... Shoot lots of it inside me, okay?
But.. I'm not...
I'm not... your... brother.
I understand that.
All that's the same is your face.
All the other parts are different.
I decided after it happened,
that I'd collect just the parts that looked like my brother.
All I had to do was collect them.
See, look at them!
They all look exactly like my brother's.
All that remained was the head.
And now, at last I finally found it.
Please, give me that final part.
Accelerando.
Wow, what a sudden downpour!
Geez, I'm completely soaked.
Let's get inside quickly.
What's wrong?
What?
T-Toru?
S-Sorry!
It's okay if you see my underwear.
But...
Toru?
L-Look at me.
T-Tomoe?
Let's do it.
Tomoe.
I really wanna... do it.
Toru... you're so hot.
Does that feel good?
You can touch any part of
me however you want, Toru.
T-Tomoe.
I'm going to cum...
Wait!
Now you can!
I'm sorry.
I came.
You can cum even more if you want to.
Tomoe...
My boobs... lick them please.
Toru... Amazing... You're still so hard!
Hey... This time, can you put it inside of me?
Tomoe, it's going in... there.
Tomoe... This isn't your first time?
I'm a slutty girl.
I'm really sorry!
So deep!
Yes!
So tight!
Me too. It's so tight I'm full of you.
You're being rough, again...
I'm cumming.
Did lots come out.
Tomoe!
T-Toru! You can still keep going!?
Tom, do whatever you want.. I wont mind.
Tomoe!
Tom, is it good?
Does your dick feel good?
Tomoe... it feels so good.
Toru, your cock... It's amazing! It's so amazing!
Again...
Please, let's cum together!
That was... mine and Toru's...
happiest... memory.