There is a secret event in our school's tennis club.
In a mini-game over the weekend that takes place
whenever the boys' tennis club ranks up,
the guys that make it to the top three,
can nominate a girl they like and
receive a perverted award.
Although, because of that, all the guys
are working with all their might.
The girls, too, each have their thoughts.
Seems like those guys are the top three this week, huh?
Well then, who will they be nominating?
Ogura-senpai...
So that's it for Ogura and Asahina...
And, who did you nominate, Kawakita?
I... um...
Shoot, I was so focused on winning I
haven't decided on who to choose!
What do I do?
If you're not thinking of anyone in particular
why don't you go by reverse nomination?
There is someone who reverse-nominated you.
High School Girl's Waists
Part Two: The The Tennis Club
Sen-senpai... amazing...
It's taking it in...
What's taking it in? If you don't
say it clearly I won't know.
That's... It's too embarrassing.
Nope, you gotta say it properly.
Ayumi's... p-pussy is... taking in... the net...
Your pussy is already drenched. Ayumi
is a naughty girl, aren't you?
Yes, I'm sorry, Senpai...
Please punish... the naughty Ayumi... lots and lots!
Well, how about here?
That's... My butt...
It's been twitching and getting hot.
You want it here as well, right?
That's...
My pussy and my butt... are being
attacked at the same time...
Even though it's my first time in the butt...
Anal... anal... anal feels good!
Be sure to tell us when you cum, Ayumi.
Senpai! Ayumi is going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Cumming!!
Despite everyone watching you're completely erect.
Asahina must be a real pervert.
I, I love you, Haruka-sama!
Why are you trying to mix in a confession to the disarray?
How shameless.
Don't let out such a strange voice!
Does a titty-fuck from me feel that good?
Yes! Haruka-sama!
You get turned on when I rub it with
my nipples, right? You pervert.
I get turned on! I'm... I'm a pervert!
Your penis is twitching... you're about to cum!
Haruka-sama!
Geez! How much semen were you saving up?
Not now, wait! I just came and...
Even though you say that, you're this hard.
That's... that's because...
Things are just getting started.
I won't let you go until you satisfy me.
Um, Kawakita-kun, thank you for
accepting the reverse-nomination.
But it was really surprising to be nominated by Nakayama.
Surprising?
Well 'cause you unlike the other girls
you were serious and hardworking...
I thought you wouldn't have interest
in these kinds of things.
Even someone like me is interested in stuff like this...
If it's with the person I like, I'd want to do lots.
Na-Nakayama!
Yeah, it's fine.
It's my first time so... do what you want, Kawakita-kun.
Nakayama!
That place is...
It's pretty...
That's the first time I've heard Nakayama moan!
She's so erotic and cute.
C'mon, c'mon! Make you penis larger!
I'm servicing you like this you know!
Ha-Haruka-sama!
Woah! You're penis is getting hotter and hotter!
Are you about to cum? You're about to cum, aren't you?
Yes, I'm...
Amazing... it's hitting... deep inside!
So rough!
I'm sorry! I can't hold back anymore!
It's fine! Do me lots more! If you can make me
feel good, I'll make you feel good as well!
Senpai... If you do it so roughly...
Ayumi's butt will be... all messed up!
But, that's what makes Ayumi feel good, right?
Just look at your nipples.
But, when I think that I'm doing naughty
things with the racket I use every day...
I get really... really excited...
You're getting really excited here as well, aren't you?
Yes... Ayumi's pussy... wants a penis
so much it's soaking wet...
Ayumi is feeling it... from her butt being violated!
Well done, well done.
Senpai... I'm going crazy!
Kawakita-kun... how is it? Does
something like this feel good?
Yeah... it's great...
You're actually quite daring, aren't you, Nakayama?
I want people in the club to see me
and Kawakita-kun having sex...
There're quite a few girls out there that also like you...
Wait, that's... If you do it that much
I won't be able to hold back.
Me too... I want to have sex with Kawakita-kun...
It's going... in...
Are you okay?
It hurts a little, but I'll be okay.
It's like... it's going numb down there... it feels strange...
Can I move?
It's fine, go ahead.
Let's feel good together.
Nakayama...
Amazing... It's stirring up my insides!
It's going all the way in... it feels good!
I'm... so full down there... from Kawakita-kun's penis!
Pussy is amazing! This pussy could be trouble...
Nakayama's pussy is the best!
Please don't say pussy so many times
in a row, it's embarrassing!
You're saying it yourself as well! Geez, so cute.
Wow, unexpectedly Momoka has rough sex.
Oh, no! I... just now...
What's wrong? Did you get embarrassed?
But that's because...
But your nipples are like this.
It's true... my nipples are hard and erect...
I'm getting excited from being watched by everyone.
It's a great chance that everyone has their attention
on you! You wanted to show them, right?
But, it's really...
No, no... if you tease my boobs so much...
Show me more of you when you're
looking embarrassed, Momoka.
Kawakita-kun... just called me "Momoka"...
No way... this is a first... it feels really good!
I'm going to go crazy...
Look at me, Kawakita-kun!
Look at the naughty me! Look at me lots!
Yeah, I'm looking all I can.
My boobs are shaking back a forth...
Kawakita-kun, my boobs are happy!
Everyone else is definitely getting turned on
from looking at Momoka's pussy as well.
I'm getting turned on, too...
When I think that I'm being watched,
I get excited... my pussy feels it!
Dick is... the dick is hitting deep inside...
Kawakita-kun's dick feels good!
Momoka!
Kawakita-kun, I love you! Love you! Love you!
I love your dick, too!
I can't take it anymore...
I'll cum!
Hey wait! How is it still so full of energy!?
Even though you already came so many times!
I can still keep going on and on, Haruka-sama!
You'll make me cum again!
Haruka-sama, me too!
It's fine! I'll let you cum inside, so hurry!
Hurry and cum!
Inside Ayumi... the penis and vibrator
are... rubbing really hard... Senpai...
Ayumi's pussy is squeezing really tight.
Yes, I'll squeeze... I'll squeeze harder so...
Please give Ayumi's pussy Senpai's semen!
Okay. I'll cum inside for you.
Cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm...
Kawakita-kun, please... inside... let your sperm out inside...
But, that's...
It's fine, I'll be okay.
I want to take in all of Kawakita-kun... you
can do whatever you want with me, so...
Mo-Momoka!
Please, cum! I'll cum, too. I'll cum
together with Kawakita-kun!
Cum, cum, cum!
Ha-Haruka-sama... If you're that rough... I...
So I'm doing a clean-up fellatio and
yet you're gonna cum again?
But, but...
You're can't cum until I ejaculate okay, Ayumi?
Please, Senpai, hurry, hurry up and cum...
Ayumi is about to cum!
Everyone lining up and sucking on a penis
like this... it's getting really lewd!
Mo-Momoka...
It's my first time doing something
like this, but I can't lose!
I'll definitely make Kawakita-kun cum!
Amazing!
It's, it's hot...
Kawakita-kun... this time, it's Kawakita-kun's turn...