Akihito-san...
My younger sister, Umi, isn't actually my blood related sister.
If I think about it, it's actually no very surprising.
She doesn't see me as a brother
but as someone of the opposite sex.
I don't know when this ail started,
but I have started to change as well.
Harukoi Otome
~ Let's Meat at the Otome Garden ~
Second Episode
Akihito-dono, have you not made
up with your younger sister yet?
The practice match is coming up, and
your condition is extremely troubling.
Well... I haven't yet.
While it doesn't matter that much to me,
it's important that you demonstrate yourself as a leader.
And if you're always this un-energetic,
I'm going to get very lonely.
Hurry to the cafe before the food is all sold out.
Huh?
After all, you're not going to the Cultural Hall.
Right...
Have you made up your mind yet?
Umi-san, have you done the tables inside?
No, not yet! Cover for me, Sonya-chan!
Okay.
Umm... can I order now?
Yes, go ahead.
I thought the odenpan would be sold quickly...
Man, nothing's worse than having something unfamiliar.
Hey, Ayasaka-kun.
Matsubara-senpai! What's wrong?
What do you mean? I'm only here to buy lunch.
Odenpan?
Nope, I bought something even better.
See ya.
If you're looking for Matsubara-senpai, she just left.
Can you come here for a second?
Can you do me a favour?
A favour? From me?
Yes. I want you to find something out.
What is it?
Well, it's just Reika-sama's...
Matsubara-senpai's?
Umm... that...
Eh? What?
investigate!?
Matsubara-senpai's?
Don't be so loud!
Why? Aren't you two dating?
Weren't you really happy she agreed to it?
Well, it's just that I feel like senpai is distancing herself from me.
Distancing? You think she's cheating on you?
Relationships between girls are a little too complicated for me.
It's not complicated at all!
Reika-sama is a good person, and she loves me a lot!
But still, I get this feeling that something's not right.
Not right?
That's it! Riru-Riru, maybe you're just being
too clingy and worked up about this.
That's a good thing! And there's nothing I can do about that.
Anyways, just find out if there's any suspicious
people hanging around Reika-sama.
I'll leave it in your hands.
Eh!?
Is there a point to this?
Ayaka-senpai!
Ah, Akihito-san! Good morning!
Sorry I bumped... into you.
What are you doing here?
Binoculars, huh?
These?
Ah... Reika already left.
Senpai is spying on Matsubara-san too?
That's strange. Were you referring to Matsubara-senpai?
Yes. The normally cheerful Reika has become very glum lately.
I see. I actually heard the same thing from Orito Riru already.
Orito-san? That's Reika's...
Yeah. She's a very straightforward person
so this is really bugging her.
It shouldn't be like this, really.
What?
No, it's nothing.
Now then...
What should we do?
From what I can see, things look fine.
Yeah...
Physical contact is already a bit much.
I knew it was just Riru thinking too much.
But apart from those two, there's something else going on.
Wow! That girl's boobs are so amazing!
Eh? W-Which one?
Look! The third one from the left.
Ah... children these days fill out so nicely, don't they?
No... Ayaka-senpai isn't too bad either.
Really?
Yeah.
Yuki, I'll leave the rest to you.
Everyone go change now.
Reika-sama, I'll be leaving first.
Okay, I'll lock up.
Yes, please do!
Roger.
Reika-san is staying behind?
I'll go talk to her directly.
What? Right now?
Why do you accept Riru?
Because she likes me so much; I just can't let her down.
But Onee-sama belongs to me.
Even if Riru is a friend,
I'll never let Onee-sama go.
I know. I'll never give Yuki up either.
Onee-sama... please.
I'm sorry. I don't think I should hide this anymore.
I see...
It's difficult, isn't it?
Although it's not really any consolation
Reika-san really cares for Riru.
I understand... this kind of thing...
Reika-sama is so noble-minded and so kind,
I'm the one that forced her.
But... you know...
Reika-san would want to respect your feelings above all else.
This is... so unfair...
Do it harder.
Let's lie down.
Just do it like this.
Alright.
No...
Should I stop?
No, keep going.
You're wet.
Don't say that.
Riru.
Thank you, Akihito-kun.
Oh, A-kun! You're going to be late if you don't hurry it up.
What, we're not even close to being late.
We're close enough.
It's your fault if we're late.
Why?
It's been a few days since Umi-chan has shown up.
I wonder who it was that pissed her off.
"Mr. Naughty Wakeup Call," Aki-chan.
That's just a bunch of crap you made up!
Well, I'm off first.
Aki-chan.
Yuika?
So, are you being a good brother?
Well, about that...
There's gotta be a reason you can't do it, right?
A reason?
I think it's something like this.
Is there a feeling that has started in Aki-chan's heart?
A feeling?
You can't hide it from me.
A feeling of wanting to please the other person...
So I just wanted to try it.
No thanks! It's only been a few days.
Riru-Riru recovers rather quickly.
Because of you two, Orito Riru's life
has taken another step forward!
This is not something one can easily describe with words.
It's not that big a deal.
If you want to thank us, then thank us at a different place.
There's no restaurant better than this one here.
That's true.
If it's anything more high-class than the Cultural
Hall, students aren't allowed in.
See, you should just give up now.
Why?
Why are you being so noisy?
I don't mean that.
We just ordered the legendary meal from the
top-secret cookbook, so you should be happy.
Eh? That's amazing!
What would you like to order?
Ah, Umi-chan!
Onii-chan...
Hey...
Hey, what's wrong?
What is?
I know it was like this before,
but there's something wrong with Onii-san.
Really? I think we're a normal pair of siblings.
Would normal'siblings avoid looking at each other?
W-What'are you talking about?
It's just like me and Reika-sama.
Although we don't hate each other, we still keep our distance.
So what's going on?
I'll keep you locked up here until you come clean.
It'll be bad if someone finds you here.
You idiot, what are you doing?
Today's the day the swimming pool opens.
You should just enjoy it!
See ya!
Damn it, how did this even happen?
Oh, crap!
It looks like you're ready to answer.
I'm so tired.
You couldn't resist seeing the swimming
club girls changing, could you?
It's about time you told me about
what happened with Umi-chan.
I think... I might be in love with Umi.
Eh? Love... EH!?
No. The truth is...
After this, I told Riru about everything in my room.
Kisaya-senpai came along too, and said lots of things about Umi.
So you're not really brother and sister...
After thinking about Umi, I don't know what got into me.
So, Akihito-dono, what do you plan on doing?
Well, even if you ask me that...
I can somewhat guess how Umi feels.
The first thing you should do is show
some respect to the other person.
Don't worry about her thoughts on how you're related.
It'll mean a lot to her if you tell her how you feel.
Although making this decision will still take some time...
My feelings have actually gotten stronger.
Then finally, l felt it was time.
I'm so jealous. There are so many people
who want siblings, but don't have any.
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
Good work today. You must be tired
after work at the Cultural Hall.
No. I'm used to it now.
I remember now... about what happened before.
With a little bit of help from Yuika
I now remember everything.
I'm sorry for making you have to do this.
I'm really sorry for making you a replacement
for a dead person due to my weakness.
To apologize for this sort of thing...
I've come to terms with these feelings on my own.
Umi is my precious sister, and this will never change.
But...
But?
I've found something even more important to me than a sister.
Umi... I love you.
At first, I was really happy to have a brother.
But now, I'm even happier!
I love how Onii-chan smells.
Umi likes washing clothes.
I can keep smelling your scent.
Don't say such weird things.
But it's true!
Well then, let me be honest with you.
I love how your hair smells.
But this is just the smell of shampoo.
No. It's Umi's scent.
Onii-chan, what's this?
Goodness, I wonder why it's like this.
I'll do it with my mouth for you.
It's really hard...
If you do it like that...
Onii-chan's scent...
Umi, you don't have to force yourself.
I'll do it for Umi too.
Onii-chan's fingers feel so good!
No, not there!
Onii-chan, this is too perverted!
No, it's not.
It's already so wet.
Umi's very perverted herself.
Because it feels so good!
Umi, let's feel good together.
My body feels so hot!
It's completely soaked, Umi.
No...
Don't push.
Onii-chan's... inside me!
It's already this wet.
Do you feel me?
Onii-chan, please!
More, more!
Umi...!
Onii-chan, I love you!
I do too.
Onii-chan!
Come on! If you don't hurry up...
Just like that, the relationship between me and Umi got better.
I'm even luckier than before.
For the sake of Umi, I will do my best.
If you don't work hard, I won't help you anymore.
Come to think of it, people generally want good things to last.
Hey, Umi-san.
Yes, Onii-chan?
We're lovers now.
For a good morning, doing a few perverted
things shouldn't matter, right?
Onii-chan, you pervert!