Please Shu-kun, stop this... Don't!
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry!
I never wanted something like this...
Rensa Byo-toh
Staff Changing Room
Shu-kun... Please... Just...
Shu-kun, if you grope my breasts too hard I'll...
Dr. Katsuyama! Are you working the night shift?
Wakoto-san, you too?
Oh... no...
There are some yummy treats at the Nurses'
Station, why don't you drop by?
Is something wrong?
It looks like you've cheered up.
All right, let's stop by the Nurses' Station.
Shu-kun...
Aren't you satisfied yet?
It feels... weird...
You were so rough up until now...
Why are you so gentle today?
Oh, not there! No!
Please don't! Please stop!
Shu-kun!
Don't move your hand like that!
I can't... I can't take it anymore!
Please don't! I'm going to...
No! Don't! Stop!
I'm cumming!
Stop! Don't put it in now!
Please, Shu-kun!
Please, no more! I don't want to cum anymore!
No!!
Wh-What the hell do you think you're doing, Dr. Yamada!?
Get away from Misako-san at once!
I'll untie her now.
Well, Misako-san, we've been discovered.
Shu-kun?
Hurry it up!
I... I...
There, I've released Misako-san.
What do you plan to do now?
Whether we report this to the police or take other actions,
I will discuss this incident with the
Director and the Assistant Director.
The three of us will then make a decision.
Prepare for the consequences!
A police report?
Will I really end up discussing this... with my father?
Be calm, Misako-san.
It's okay, you're safe now, okay?
I'm sorry.
You can relax now.
You're wrong...
I'm sorry Aki-san!
Aki-san?
Haruna-san... Why?
If Misako-san and Aki-san got away, the
two of you would ruin all of our plans.
You're so cruel, Shu-kun! You never intended
to let me go, even though you uncuffed me!
No. I never told her to do that. I can have it either way.
What... then?
Misako-san is so terrible.
Thinking about orders, whatever
Dr. Yamada wants is what I want.
It... It can't be...
But I've been reassured that you're one of us now, right?
After all, you were released from the handcuffs.
And I don't think Dr. Katsuyama would have liked what you did.
But I...
If that's true, then to keep this woman
quiet we'll need to persuade her...
And we both know well Dr. Yamada's ways of persuasion.
If you don't like that, Misako-san,
then you can try persuading her yourself first.
Doctor... I don't know how she'll do it...
Misako-san is handcuffed to Dr. Katsuyama after all.
I don't know if she'll be able to...
You're not going to let me go, are you?
Maternity and Gynecology Department | Delivery Room
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Doing something like this, are you crazy or something?
Please shut her up, Misako-san.
Okay...
It feels so good, Doctor!
Wait... Stop!
Don't come any closer!
It's hopeless now.
We've gone too far and we can't go back...
That's got nothing to do with me!
I demand to be released from this immediately!
I can't do that.
We're going to plunge together...
No! Don't touch me!
Here it comes.
Please cum, Doctor. Please give lots of rewards inside me.
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
You did good, Haruna.
Yes... I'm glad...
You will regret this! You won't ever be forgiven!
Yes, I'm sure I'll be reliving this moment once again later.
Stop! Let me go!
Stop this! It's my first time...
What?
So please, don't-
No! Stop it!
Please, take it out!
Aki-san, your first time is with Shu-kun? I'm so jealous...
It's tearing... My insides are tearing!
No!
Don't! You can't do this! Please, please take it out!
No... No!
Shu-kun, you look so satisfied.
You're going to cum soon, aren't you?
No!
No! Don't! Don't!!
Please, anything but that!
Do what you want to me, but don't cum inside of me!
Please! Forgive me! Anything but that!
Stop it!
It can't be!
This can't be... This can't be happening to me...
Surgical Department | Examination Room
Aki, you're also going to help me with my revenge.
No!
I can't... It's so deep inside... Please stop!
It's burning hot inside me... No!
I can't take it anymore!
More... I mean... Don't!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
No, don't put your finger in there!
Don't!
Oh no...
Take it out...
Stop it! Why my ass?
My ass is being spread open so wide!
Please stop! It's going up my butt!
You're spreading my ass... It hurts!
It's so hot... It burns!
Please stop... Stop putting it so deep within me!
I really can't take this... Please, at least let me use the toilet-
No!
You pee'd... inside me?
Please... My ass... Stop putting it in my ass!
Please stop... Stop it!
My ass... My asshole is tearing...
Take it out...
My ass... Not my ass!
What... Why am I cumming from anal!?
Please stop! I'll help you! So please... stop this!
I see. In that case I'll have to reward you.
My ass... My ass is!
Aki, from now on we'll work together.
Surgical Department | Examination Room
At long last... Tomorrow I'll settle this ordeal.
Yes... I believe in you.
But... We don't have any evidence.
That's a huge disadvantage for us...
That's right, we'll have to improvise.
Shu-kun... Even if my husband is the one who
botched the surgery upon your father...
He saved this hospital and I from the
brink of bankruptcy... So please...
Misako-san, you don't have to say a thing.
You can judge for yourself after listening
to my conversation with him.
Haruna, Aki, thank you.
I may not earn your forgiveness, but thanks to
you, this man may finally pay for his crimes.
No... I'll make sure he does...
Now it will end.
I don't want anything to end! I want
to bear your children, Doctor!
I want to be with you forever!
That's right. It's over for the both of us, but you
and Misako-san are still going to... It's too unfair!
I mean... I also want to be by your side.
I also want to have children...
Are you two... serious? You hated it so much at first.
Is it so strange? You just came on too hard...
and who are you to judge what's crazy?
I'm serious as well. By my own free will,
I've decided to stay with Doctor.
Misako!
What is all of this?
Yamada-kun, don't just stand there. Hurry up and untie me!
Hey, are we sure it was a medical mistake?
Yes. Doctor says so, so there's no doubt.
I guess you're right. I believe in him too.
Today you will be confessing your sins.
What the hell are you talking about?
Don't think that just because it was so long ago,
since you became a partner at Kiyosato Hospital...
That your deed was ever forgotten.
How about you confess yourself already!?
I haven't... I haven't done anything!
If your wife was raped in front of your eyes,
do you think your tongue would loosen up?
Stop! Seriously, stop this!
Yamada!
Stop! I'll talk, so stop, okay?
Is that right? Well, let's hear it.
Back then, I worked with an accountant...
...who was embezzling vast amounts
of money from Kiyosato Hospital.
How shocking. He went so far, just to...
Once he had stolen the money,
he simply transferred it over to me...
...so it was easy to make generous donations to the hospital.
It can't be... Didn't you save Kiyosato Hospital?
You did something like that? But there's more isn't there?
For example, a case where your shitty heart surgery...
...had resulted in a horrible incident that had to be covered up!
What!?
Have you already forgotten?
Outside the operating room, you told me how
my father's arteries had been damaged.
And how there was bleeding far worse than
expected, or some bullshit like that.
Wait, it can't be...
The last name Yamada is extremely common.
But you remember now, don't you?
There was nothing I could do.
You remember then, about your
surgical mistakes with my father.
Yes.
Wow...
Yup...
Dad, watch as I do this for you.
Misako-san, you've heard everything, haven't you?
Misako! You were awake!?
I'm so sorry, Shu-kun. Even if I apologized
forever it wouldn't be enough.
No, Misako-san. I feel very fulfilled at the moment.
Shu-kun...
My goals since that day were to destroy my father's enemy.
And you, Misako-san.
Shu-kun, please let me return to you.
And please, make me pregnant with your semen.
Misako!?
There's no need to fret Director...
It's not just Misako-san.
Dr. Katsuyama and I as well, we're all getting pregnant.
What are you...
The term is "concurrent conception".
And it's possible because of my efforts to pinpoint
and manipulate our days of ovulation.
Do all of you even realize what the hell you're saying!?
My dear husband... All three of us, we've
all decided to have Shu-kun's babies.
Misako!
Doctor, please make me pregnant first, okay?
Doctor...
It feels so good, I love Doctor's big cock so much!
Director, are you watching us have sex?
Yes...
It's so good. Doctor, it feels so good!
Please ram your cock further inside me!
I feel it! I feel Doctor's big cock pounding my insides!
It's gotten so big... Doctor's cock is getting even bigger!
You're going to cum, right? You're going
to cum inside of me now, aren't you?
Please! Please give me your seed!
It's coming in! Your sperm is going straight up into me!
Your sperm... I'm cumming!!
Wakoto-san, if we don't plug this hole
up, the sperm will begin leaking out.
Even though I just came, it feels so...
If you want to get pregnant, you can't waste a single drop.
As soon as Aki-san cums, please do me too Shu-kun!
We can't have that! He hasn't cum inside me yet!
Oh no... Shu-kun!
It's so deep! It's rubbing my insides raw!
It feels so good! It feels so good!!
Hey, do it as hard as you possibly can.
Please make me pregnant! Please cum a flood inside me!
It feels so good! It feels so good! It feels so good!!
Amazing! You're hitting my insides so hard!
You're cumming inside me! I feel you cumming in me!
Oh you... I'm cumming!!
Oh no!
No... Don't leak out! Please don't leak out!
We need to plug that hole!
Wakoto-san, don't! I can't take it!
Dr. Yamada, we want more of your cock.
After impregnating us, please do us more and more!
That's right, all of you are mine now.
Until you're all pregnant, I'll keep fucking you!
Doctor...
Shu-kun! I haven't gotten any of your dazzling sperm yet!
Your wonderful sperm, I'm the only one who hasn't gotten any!
Misako! Open your eyes! Don't be deceived by that man!
The one who deceived me was not Shu-kun, but you.
Misako...
Shuskun, I can't wait any longer, hurry and put it in me!
Stop it!! Take it out! Take it out!
No! Don't take it out!
You can't even imagine how happy I am right now.
I never knew I could feel so happy
with another man watching it all.
It's so big! Please Shu-kun, do me harder!
Make me feel even more of this happiness!
Doctor's sperm is squishy and slippery inside me.
If you move around that much, it'll leak out!
But... I'm already pregnant!
And Dr. Akiyama, you're the one moving around so much!
My hips are doing it on their own!
It feels so good! It's going so deep inside me!
My dear husband, you're nothing compared to Shu-kun!
You've never hit me as deep as Shu-kun has!
Shu-kun! Do it harder! Go deeper! Fuck me!
Doctor! I'm your slave, so please, please
cum more and more inside of me.
That's not fair! Please use my ass however you please.
Please give me your warm sticky sperm too!
Doctor! I'm so sorry! I'm going to cum again!
Wakoto-san, don't move like that or I'll-
I'm cumming!!
Cumming!
Shu-kun, please cum a lot inside me!
Please! I want Shu-kun's baby too!
I'm going to... I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I feel it inside me. I feel Shu-kun's warm goo inside me.
I'm going to get pregnant...
Afterwards, Shu-kun saved my dream for a wonderful hospital.
Through sheer willpower, he assumed the Directorship of the hospital.
And as far as the hospital and I go...
We wouldn't be here without him.
Shu-kun please, go deeper!
The baby can't wait to come out and play with you!
Director, please come here quickly.
Shu... Shu... I've also been waiting for you so...
It's so good, it's going so deep within me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
You're done with Misako, right Shu? Hurry and put it in me!
It's my turn next!
Shu-kun...