We've finally found you.
No... Stay away... Somebody, save me...
Are you sure this young lady qualifies?
Yes, absolutely.
She is a blood relative.
She has inherited Princess Kukuri's blood.
Father... Mother...
We don't have to let the others live, do we?
Finish them off right in front of her.
In order to awaken distant relatives like her,
there needs to be intense amounts of despair.
Don't... Father... Mother... No... Stop...
Don't worry, we won't kill you.
However, in order to prepare you as a sacrifice,
we'll put you through more suffering than
anything you'll ever experience in your life.
Now, let's proceed.
Let's conclude this 120 year long saga.
Kagirohi: Shaku Kei
Vol 1: Tentacles From Hell
I see.
So, you are the goddess Izanami.
Just because I was born with these eyes, my family was...
S-Stop!
No!
No! No!
Not there!
No! Don't!
I was born just to suffer as a sacrifice like this?
If I'd known, I would never have held out any hope for life.
This is horrible. I can't stand it.
Save me, Aoi!
Sempai...
I heard people in the village talking about a human sacrifice.
That's just crazy talk, right?
Sempai, please don't worry about her any more.
It's what she wants, as well.
That can't be true. Kaede, where is Ajisai?
I have to go save her!
I won't tell you. And I won't allow you to go any further.
Kaede!
Everyone! Restrain him!
Damn, I'm surrounded.
What?
After him! Don't let him get away!
You have to capture him!
Did I lose them?
Young man! Young man, you came to save her, right?
Kusanoou! Where have you been!?
I used the power of invisibility from my glasses!
Isn't it great?
Ah! So you're the one who caused all that ruckus earlier.
You saved me, Kusanoou.
I'm glad you're okay.
Yes, but...
Ajisai was taken away, young man.
I couldn't stop them.
I know that, Kusanoou. Where is Ajisai right now?
What would you do if you found out?
Ajisai is important to me. I'd go save her, obviously.
They say the spirit inhabits the depths of a nearby cave.
Ajisai went there in order to satisfy the fallen
goddess Izanami's insatiable appetite.
No!
Stop it!
Not that.
Don't put it in! Don't!
It's my first time! I wanted my first time to be with him...
I'm begging you!
It's going in! Don't do it!
It went inside. It's hot. It's thick and hot. It's twitching.
No!
I wanted to give him my virginity, and yet...
No... It's going all the way in!
It's hot! Take it out! No!
It's going into my deepest parts.
My womb is being raped by these nasty tentacles.
It's really inside me.
What's going on? What do you want to tell me?
You're always watching me, aren't you?
Huh?
Let's play a game.
It's easy, just walk over to me from where you are.
Simple, right?
O-Okay.
Come, let's begin.
No! This is disgusting!
Please, stop it already!
I'm getting hotter.
It's going to burn me.
Please, just stop!
No...
I'm really sensitive there, but you still...
Not my clitoris.
That's unfair! It'll make me cum.
I-I can't take anymore.
I'll cum... I'll cum! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
It ejaculated. There's hot semen clinging to my body.
When that thing ejaculated inside of me...
My virginity was stolen from me.
I wanted to give it to Aoi.
I'm so sorry.
This game will determine whether or not you can change
the destiny bestowed upon me by my bloodline.
What the hell is this!?
I thought so. He can't get close to my heart.
Fate can't be changed.
How? Why aren't you stopping?
Maybe he can change my destiny.
Ajisai!
If I'm with him, even if my destiny can't be changed...
Now that I think about it, I remember having
some sort of feeling the first time I saw him.
I fell for him. He was my first love.
Please stop already.
That's the wrong hole!
Please stop!
I-It penetrated my asshole.
The tentacle is moving back and forth inside my belly.
I'm taking in three shafts - one in my mouth, one in my
ass, and one in my pussy. I'm going to be torn apart.
It hurts and I can barely breathe.
I'm being raped all the way to the back of my throat.
I’m about to vomit from the horrible stench all around me,
b-but...
It's good. I-It feels good.
My head is going blank.
I can forget about everything unpleasant.
My asshole feels so good. My pussy feels like it will melt.
Why does it feel so good? Rape me more!
I want more. Give it to me. Do me more!
So good...
Who was I thinking about up until now?
I'm sure it was someone important to me, but...
My mind has gone completely blank. I can't remember.
I'm cumming!
It's ejaculating inside of me
It's entering my womb.
There's still more coming out.
It almost looks like I'm the one ejaculating.
It's still completely full of energy.
How much longer am I going to be raped?
That's good. Do more. Do me harder!
All right, now you go ahead according to our plan.
I'll leave Ajisai to you.
Okee-dokee! Roger.
You'd better prepare the escape route
for Ajisai and me, young man.
I'll handle everything on my end.
Let's see, is Ajisai beyond this door?
I knew it. You concealed yourself and came to save her.
Did you think I wouldn't notice? How naive.
H-How?
It might have been your mission to keep an eye on Ajisai-san,
but you weren't supposed to get close to her and interfere.
I was so close, young man. Ajisai.
Ajisai.
That's right, I started to like Ajisai.
That's why I don't care about my "mission" any more.
Did you want to save Princess Kukuri so badly you
were willing to go against Yoshino's orders?
What an impulsive girl you are.
You could never understand how I feel.
No, I don't.
I'm a human, after all.
Why would I want to understand how a demon feels?
You say such funny things.
You rotten woman. If it wasn't for you...
I could see you plain as day.
That's right. How can you see me?
My, my, you don't even know that?
How could you think that you had even a
remote possibility of saving Ajisai-san?
How foolish.
Those eyes! Are those like the ones Ajisai inherited?
You'll make a nice opening act for the ceremony.
You, have sex with this girl so that she can begin eating
Hell's Feast and therefore never be able to come back.
No! Stop! Damn you!
Don't touch me with your filthy hands! You idiots!
I almost forgot to tell you about this altar.
Did you know that, in ancient times, men and women would
have sex here to appease the spirit of Izanami-sama?
If you do your best, Ajisai-san might be saved.
That's an obvious lie.
However, if what that earthworm-woman is saying is true...
Don't you want to save Ajisai-san?
Not there!
No, if you stick your finger in...
No! Stop it, damn you! No way!
No, not that!
Don't you dare resist.
Serves you right.
Now hurry up and force your meatstick into that girl's womb.
Don't rub it like that!
It's pretty damn tight.
It's piercing my insides.
Even though it's my first time, all of it is being forced inside of me.
Stop moving!
Don't! If you do it that hard...
It feels strange... I overflow every time you thrust.
No! Nasty noises are coming out!
Don't! That's too rough!
It's coming inside me.
It's flowing out! So much of it is flowing out from inside of me.
There's no time for you to rest. Your asshole's up next.
Ajisai.
Hurry up and do it!
It's going into my asshole!
It's really inside of me. It's stretching my ass apart.
Don't move so suddenly!
It’s hot! My ass is burning!
My ass is being reamed out!
You're scraping my insides up!
It's hitting me so deep! It's all the way inside!
I don't want to feel good from my ass!
No! No way! I'm cumming!?
I don't want to cum from my ass!
My ass...
Well, look at that. However, it's not over yet.
Please stop it! Don't! Someone help me!
All right! Now I'll head inside.
Sempai.
You're going this far just for Ajisai?
I see.
Kaede! You can help me! You...
Onii-chan, I was the first one to love you.
Going to that other girl makes no sense.
Stop it Kaede!
Look only at me.
I'll do anything for Onii-chan.
Onii-chan... Do it with me...
I'm cumming again! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I don't want to cum anymore, but I'm cumming anyway!
Translation:
KuriosAkantha
Translation Check:
Tamesuu
Edit:
Rika-sama
Timing:
Zetsuei
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Quality Check:
Chaosrains