Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat ® irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Cosplay Paradise
If you do it that rough, my clothes will wrinkle...
This kind of relationship with him...
had started about half a year ago.
I had lost my husband early, and had been really lonely,
and let him close as he was kind and gentle to me...
If we don't stop...
Someone will find us.
Huh? Here?
Is this alright?
But he... had a strange fetish...
He loves to do it with clothes on like this.
Like this is okay, right?
It's getting even larger than before...
Feel better and better!
No... it’s making really lewd noises...
It feels really good...
Amazing... the sounds are really erotic...
Do it more!
So hot!
You've heard about me from Mafuyu Sensei, right?
I've known what’s going on between you two for a while.
I want to become a wonderful lady like Mafuyu Sensei,
and when I consulted her about it,
she said I could come, too...
Sensei... it's my first time...
So please be gentle.
How is my swimming suit?
Although my boobs aren't large like Mafuyu Sensei...
It feels like my body is heating up...
My boobs are hot...
Sensei... this feels kind of strange...
No... not there...
No!
It feels good...
Sensei's hand... feels good!
I want Sensei to tease me more!
Sensei... this is strange...
What do I do?
No!
No, Sensei...
No... Sensei, don't look!
No!!
I've... lost my strength...
Sensei... this is embarrassing...
But I want Sensei to do me, too.
I want Sensei to put his penis inside...
Sensei... I want you!
Please put it in!
It's so big!
Sensei's penis is hot... it's hot!
I can tell, Sensei!
Sensei, it feels good!
Even though it's my first time, I'm feeling so good!
Sensei is amazing! You're getting larger and larger...
I'm feeling strange again...
No! It'll come out again!
What are we doing now, Sensei?
Sensei, a place like that...
Amazing... it's making slutty noises...
It's got this strange taste...
Thank you, Sensei!
Let's do it together with Mafuyu Sensei next time, okay?
Tada! These are the uniforms Sensei really likes!
This is it, right?
It's kind of embarrassing...
That's right, Karin-chan. Lick the tip of the penis, too.
Like this?
Huh? Me, too?
Sensei's really does taste weird!
Karin-chan will also start to like it in a while.
Um, is something like this alright?
Geez! Don't look this way so much!
How is it? Does it feel good?
Sensei, you guys are amazing...
This is so erotic...
Amazing... Sensei's getting larger and larger...
The wet stuff is sticking onto my feet...
I'm starting to feel lewd again!
Even I'm getting this wet...
Me too, I'm feeling weird...
Sensei's is amazing!
No!
Sensei's is... going so deep inside.
Amazing!
Karin-chan! Don't...
Mafuyu Sensei... please feel better and better.
Sensei... is this alright?
No...
Sensei, hurry...
It's going deep inside...
Karin-chan is very lewd.
You're nipples are this hard, you're exciting me, too...
Mafuyu Sensei... amazing...
It's so good!
Hot...
Sensei, you're so hard...
If you stick your penis there...
Alright... move your penis more!
Mafuyu Sensei, I want to feel good together with you!
You're so cute, Karin-chan.
Let's cum together, all three of us.
Yes, along with Sensei... I want
the three of us to cum together!
Cumming, cumming!
Me, too...
Cumming togerther, together!
Sensei!
Cumming, cumming!
So good!
Sensei's hot stuff...
Sensei's smell... I could get into a habit of this!
Sensei's is... still so large...
One more time, all three of us...