Shinobu...
Shin Kyouhaku 2
~ Flower That Blooms in the Wound Kainloow of Blood ~
SCENE.2 [Refrain]
With that much cum in her, she's bound to get pregnant.
Wh-Who the hell would want your children?
This one's twice as big.
Th-That's too big!
You're going to go to school tomorrow with this inside you.
Your vagina is filled to the brim with our semen.
I can't... have this in me... all day!
I'll break!
Wh-What's that?
We don't want my brother whom you love so dearly to find out.
What cute little panties.
They suit her.
Akehime,
are you feeling ill?
No...
I'm okay.
Maybe you should go to the infir...
l'm okay!
Really...
Oh no. I'm soaking wet.
Stop... Please!
Mayu-chan, where's Saki-chan?
She should be here any minute.
Saki-chan! Over here.
Saki-chan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
I just didn't sleep well last night.
That's bad for your health.
I guess... so.
Saki-chan?
Sorry! I've gotta...
Bathroom?
Their semen... So much is coming out of me.
It stinks!
If I smell this bad,
everyone will wind out!
What's that smell?
Smells like a guy's "thing".
No way!
This is the girls' bathroom!
What are you talking about?
The smell of semen.
Ah! You said "semen"!
What's semen? You mean sperm?
Haven't you ever smelled semen before?
No, I haven't.
You've got too much sex on the brain!
Oh no... Not now.
You're at school, right?
If you want us to take it off, then stop by on the way home.
Or else...
Transferring your call to voice mail...
Saki-chan, are you okay?
You shouldn't keep things to yourself.
Yeah. I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Actually, I have some place to do. So go on home without me.
Some place to go?
Bye.
Come in. It's open.
I came.
Just like I promised.
So hurry.
Don't be so scared. Come closer.
I'm not scared of you!
Looks like you enjoyed it.
She's soaking wet.
Well, shall we begin?
Well then, first off...
What's that?
I'll show you. You do this...
No! Stop it!
Hey, don't talk like that. You liked it so much.
N-Not my butt!
We've got plenty more.
That's too much!
I can't take it! I can't!
The real fun starts now.
Time to cum!
It... It's coming.
It's not over yet!
I'm cumming.
Drink it up.
I'm cumming... Stop it!
I don't wanna...
I don't wanna cum!
No, don't!
No... No...
I'm cumming!
You were great.
If you keep us entertained like that every day,
I'll keep this a secret from my brother.
Keep up the good work.
Sensei...
That gang of wolves... violated me.
Saki-chan.
Saki-chan!
Saki-chan, where have you been?
Come on, Saki-chan!
Toya-san,
I can't do this anymore.
You have a problem with me?
No. That's not what I meant.
In that case...
Don't say stuff you don't mean!
If only that hadn't happened...
I can't replace my sister.
Hey, hey, where's Saki-chan?
Maybe the bathroom.
That's weird.
Saki-chan's sure been spending a lot of time in the bathroom.
Listen, Miku-chan, I need your advice.
I get it. I'll come see you today, okay?
Today we're meeting at a different place.
I'll text you the location in a bit.
Mayu-chan, sorry I'm late.
Is she here yet?
Not yet. But are you sure we should be doing this?
We have to. She won't tell us what she's been up to.
There she is.
Transferring your call to voice mail.
Sensei, please use my cell phone.
Morisaki?
Use my phone to call Toya.
Don't I...
remind you of someone?
You're Shinobu-san's...
What do you want, Ayame?
Toya.
It's you!?
Toya, what are you doing?
If you wanna know, come over tonight.
That is, if you have the balls to accept whatever it is you see.
Where are you?
In a place that's just like me. A broken church.
Sensei...
Can you accept Saki-chan, no matter what's happened to her?
What's that supposed to mean?
Morisaki, where is Saki?
Follow me.
You're early.
Why did you want to meet here of all places?
Just thought I'd change the mood.
That hurts! Let go of me!
Mayu! Miku!
Did you guys follow me here?
I'm sorry, Saki-chan...
What should we do with them?
Whatever it is, make it quick.
I've got plans right after this.
Stop it!
Wh-What're you doing?
No...
What're you doing?
No, no, no!
No, no!
No...
N-No!
No way...
No...
It's too big!
It'll break!
It hurts!
She's a newbie.
That one, too?
Mayu... Miku...
Why? How did this...
You led them here.
So it's my fault!? You didn't have to drag them into it!
My main goal is to make you suffer.
Because that will make him suffer.
Not as good as the other one... But her pussy is better than I thought!
What about this one?
Whoa! I can't stand it.
You're grossing me out!
No...
I have something more special arranged for you.
You can do what you want with me, just let them go!
Whoa, I can't stop.
I'm almost there!
Me too.
No...
This can't be happening!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
No!
Wh-What's going on!?
Yo, you're finally here.
Toya-san!
You go home. I have no use for you anymore.
But...
Get lost!
Shinobu!
Toya-san!
Shinobu was... killed by my brother.
Do you remember now? That day, everything in me died.
The only thing left was my lust for revenge!
Just stay there and watch.
Saki!
Stop it! Don't hurt her!
Hurt her?
I'm not hurting her. I'm gonna show you her pleasured face.
No. Don't do that. You can't do that!
It's... in...
Stop it, Toya!
How does it feel, bro?
To have your precious woman fucked by
another man before your very eyes?
Toya...
You bastard!
Don't watch!
Sensei!
Sensei...
You sound like you're in pain. I'll make it easier for you.
S-Saki...
Don't do it...
Stop it!
Saki...
Sensei!
Don't... Don't go there!
Sensei... Sensei...
Yes!
This feels so great!
Look... Sensei...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Huh? So they're really gonna build it here?
Seems like it.
But I guess that's a good thing.
Up until last month it was all abandoned and really creepy.
You're right.