Itoshi no Kotodama
In my dreams, I will embrace,
anata e no omoi dake o
just my feelings for you.
yume ni dakishimete
Very slowly, now...
yukkuri to watashi wa ima
Ah, I am starting to take an adult form.
ah otona no kakera ni kawaru
The love I hold in my dreams,
yume ni aru aiji dake ni wa
shines brighter than anything.
nani yori mo kagayaite
Oh, I have no regrets.
oh kui ga nai
Because I was able to see you again.
mata anata ni deaete watashi wa
And I was happy.
shiawase datta yo
Chapter 1:
Sublimation
Akio Hospital
Ah, I'm so tired.
"We don't know what caused your illness"?
"Are you sure you're not tired
just because it's summer?"
Jeez. It's not like I'm proud that I've been
sick ever since the start of summer.
I'm not gonna make it!
I wish the doctors would just do their job.
Ow. Hey, where do you think you're looking?
Sorry.
A-Are you hurt?
I don't know why you're in such a hurry.
But lately I've been...
Wh-What? I get the feeling I saw something weird.
Maybe it's just my imagination.
Ah! My charm.
When did I drop that?
Oh, well.
I wanna do it.
You like me, don't you?
Let's do it.
No! Not there.
Hurry. Do it quick. Do it!
Don't wait.
I'm losing my mind.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Urn, listen, you...
I-I feel like I should introduce myself.
Hey, you.
just because you knocked me over,
you think you can be my friend?
Wh-Why are you staring at me like that?
Don't do that. Don't.
Uh, well, no reason. Whatever.
Don't tell me everything that
just happened was a dream?
Come on, treat me!
To a marshmallow and fruit parfait at Todai Cafe!
This is so good!
Yeah, hut I wonder what I saw back there?
Why have you been doing nothing
but stare at me all day?
Uh, ha ha ha! I'm Koga Shigemaro.
What's your name?
Tachibana Aki.
Wait don't tell me you ran into me on
purpose just so you could ask me out?
That's not it at all! I really was in a hurry.
Wh-What the hell am I doing here!?
Crap. I won't make it.
What's wrong?
I was supposed to give this to my father.
He's going overseas,
and my grandfather asked me to
give him this good luck charm.
What's wrong?
I don't know. My body...
My body does things I can't control. It happens a lot.
So you missed your chance to give him the charm.
That's too bad.
But you could always just mail it to him.
That's true. I guess I could do that.
Yo!
Oh, Yoshihira, it's just you.
Don't scare me like that.
If you're that jumpy, you must be
hiding something nasty from me.
N-Not at all.
Don't hide it, don't hide it.
Looks like this summer vacation's gonna be fun!
Don't play dumb.
Introduce me to your pretty girlfriend!
The one from Todai Cafe! Todai Cafe.
You were on a date with her there, last night.
I saw you guys from the bus!
Yeah, that's right.
She saw something really weird too.
Huh? Saw something weird?
What's up with that?
Well, yesterday, I must not have really been myself.
Yup. "Weird" doesn't even begin to describe it.
You're that girl from...
N-Nice to meet you. I'm, um, Fujishima Yoshihira.
You yelled, "Ah! Watch out!" out of nowhere,
and then suddenly jumped off the cliff.
Well, that was...
The shop owners and the other
customers started yelling,
"Dine and dash!" and "He killed himself
for revenge on his girlfriend!"
and then, "You need to pay his bill."
I was so embarrassed.
Y-You abandoned this pretty girl? You ungrateful ass!
But back then, I could've sworn
I saw a girl fall off the cliff.
Huh?
I thought I saw the cliff start to erode back there...
but I don't see any debris.
I wonder where she went?
I wonder if he was trying to kill himself?
That's gotta he it.
He was killing himself to make the
girl who dumped him feel guilty!
I bet he was just dining 'n' dashing.
Sh-Shigemaro, I totally saw that too!
Saw what?
A ghost. A ghost.
That place has always been a
really famous spot for ghosts.
My sister told me about it.
Ghosts like areas with a lot of water. Also...
Never mind that. Pay me what you owe.
Bill for food and property damage.
I-It's really that expensive?
I'll pay! I'll pay already, jeez!
I'll give you your change later.
– Bye then!
– You see, ever since I was little, I've been extra sensitive...
– I've got it! I think I'll have anoter
marshmallow and fruit parfait.
– You see, ever since I was little, I've been extra sensitive...
– I've got it! I think I'll have anoter
marshmallow and fruit parfait.
– ...to ghosts and auras and that sort of thing.
to ghosts and auras and that sort of thing.
Aw, I'm gonna pig out man!
The lowest-level ghost is what we call hyo-grade.
But then if she possesses a human,
she graduates to Jiba-grade,
but she's bound to the land she's on and...
H-Huh?
Are you leaving? H-Hey!
I'll take ya home, babe! Um, I mean, miss!
Hey! Wait up!
I see. So you saw her too.
Grandpa.
Ow! My back!
It's your fault for trying to show
off like that at your age.
Ah, yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't end up giving this to Dad.
Don't worry.
In the end, it's probably best that you keep it now.
I must give you more things that you'll need.
Why are we in such a creepy place?
Because I don't want someone to see us.
Someone? Who?
I get it. You mean your rival reporter.
You don't want her to beat you to it.
Ah.
If this becomes a big scoop,
give me the reward you promised.
You have my word. Just be a good guide for me.
Well, this path sure goes on forever.
It seems like the perfect atmosphere for ghosts.
For real?
There it is.
Idiot. I wasn't talking about a ghost.
Turn out your light.
Okay.
Sure is quiet.
This is a charm we've kept in our family
for years to protect against wild spirits.
You've come into contact with one.
That must mean she sees something in you.
I see.
So that girl is dead. She was really pretty.
In that case, you must communicate with
her and help her pass on to the next life.
She has chosen you for that purpose.
Okay.
That Shigemaro...
What's he trying to do?
Feels like it'll come any minute.
Cut that out, Sis.
There it is!
I-It's her.
Hi!
Can you see me?
Y-Yeah.
You're very pretty.
Thank you.
That's the first time anyone has told me I'm pretty.
People who see me are always frightened.
They think I'm here to hurt them.
Sh-Shes in human form!
I wonder if she'll show up on film?
Shit. Yoshihira, get me another camera.
This makes me ashamed to be your sister.
Let's follow it.
Okay!
She's gone.
I wonder where she went?
Wait a minute. Something's shining.
What could it be?
Should we check it out?
I see.
It was this ocean.
Yes. It happened a very long time ago.
He tried to save you.
Yes.
And I'm still bitter about it.
I wanted to be able to thank him, at least.
To tell him how I feel...
Oh, yeah.
Do you know his name or any way of finding him?
He carved a wooden statue in memory of me.
But then, an evil spider-spirit that
steals people's feelings took it.
A spider-spirit?
Ah! Stop it!
Aki-chan?
Go help her.
Hige-san!
I'll be okay.
But she's in trouble.
Aki-chan!
Wait right there! I'll come save you!
Stay away... from me.
How did this happen to you?
What the hell is this stuff?
Run for it! You're up against a monster!
But I can't just leave you!
Wh-What kind of monster is this?
Maybe... the spider-spirit?
Shigemaro-kun!
Lay off!
Now's my chance!
These exorcism papers Grandpa gave me!
Rin pyo to sha kai jin retsu zai zen!
What? What just happened?
Huh?
There's something written on it.
"Rest in peace. –Shinohara Tatsuya"?
Was the fight fun for you?
You look like a monster... a demon?
Where's that charm?
Whoa there, go easy on me, pal.
I ain't done nothing bad.
I was just possessing that chick over there.
But it's probably more correct to say
she forced me to possess her.
Forced you to possess her?
That's the kind of body she has.
A ghost-attracting body?
It's not exactly a talent, but I guess it kinda is.
You'd better release me soon.
Why?
Unlike you, most normal humans don't
remember anything about ghosts.
That chick over there won't even
remember our spider friend.
When you defeated him, you broke his magical field.
So then, what am I still doing here? Why?
You want an explanation from me?
But she and I are just–
Don't act stupid!
She was attracted to you
because she knew, subconsciously, that
you could liberate me from her.
Anyone with your gift would have worked.
"Anyone"?
Aw, he's such a softie.
Oh no, I'd better get myself exorcised
before that chick wakes up.
Oh? What were you daydreaming about?
Did you catch a cold or something?
Well...
Sis has been out cold, sleeping.
Why?
Never mind that.
Looks like this summer vacation's gonna be fun!
Don't play dumb.
Introduce me to your pretty girlfriend!
The one from Todai Cafe! Todai Cafe.
You were on a date with her there, last night.
I saw you guys from the bus!
You said the exact same thing yesterday.
Huh? "Yesterday"? How's that possible?
Well, yesterday I must not have really been myself.
Yup. "Weird" doesn't even begin to describe it.
You're that girl from...
N-Nice to meet you. I'm, um, Fujishima Yoshihira.
You yelled, "Ah! Watch out!" out of nowhere,
and then suddenly jumped off the cliff.
Well, that was...
The shop owners and the other
customers started yelling,
"Dine and dash!" and "He killed himself
for revenge on his girlfriend!"
and then, "You need to pay his bill".
I was so embarrassed.
You abandoned this pretty girl? You ungrateful ass!
This is like deja vu.
Unlike you, most normal humans don't
remember anything about ghosts.
Never mind that Pay me what you owe.
Fine, I'll pay!
Huh?
This is?
What's that?
"Rest in peace. –Shinohara Tatsuya"?
Shinohara Tatsuya"?
That's the name of the Chief of Medicine
at the hospital I go to.
That's some random knowledge.
It's not random. He's my personal physician!
You're sick? You don't look it.
I've always had a weak constitution.
But yesterday, by Todai Cafe I–
Hey! My money!
Shigemaro!
Chief of Medicine: Shinohara Tatsua| Akio Hospital
Is that so? He became the Chief of Medicine.
I'm glad you saw him.
But that wooden carving was made in my memory.
And the feelings he poured into the carving
were stolen by the spider-spirit.
I returned it to him.
You haven't changed a bit.
Why don't you go stand by him?
This place is ideal.
Thank you very much.
With this, I can at least rest.
But I regret leaving you.
Me too.
Do you feel that?
Yes!
You're so warm.
Please be gentle.
Not down there. No, I'm shy!
Please give me yourself.
You're very pretty.
Hurry.
No!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No!
I'm cumming!
Thank you.
Next Episode
Chapter 2:
Return
Please don't miss it.
The instant I open my eyes,
me o aketa shunkan ni
My happiness flees from me.
shiawase wa nigeteku kara
So I want to stay this way forever,
eien ni kono mama de
With my eyes closed.
me o tojite itai
Now I am in your arms,
ima anata no ude no naka ni
Embraced gently,
yasashiku dakarete
Although I am changing into an illusion.
sou watashi wa maboroshi ni kawaru keredo
Please, don't let it fade away,
douka kesanai de
The love that remains in my heart.
mune ni tomaru ai o
Surely, someday in the future,
kitto mirai demo
I, and only I, will be yours forever.
watashi dake ga your forever