Thank you very much.
I hope to serve you again soon.
LOVE MACHINE
Animaid Whore Model #23
The Love Machine will make your
wildest dreams come true.
A beautiful and fascinating world always awaits you.
Tonight, the Love Machine wishes to
share a special moment with you.
Thank you very much for your reservation for tonight.
So...
Do you have your ID card?
Will this do?
I will accept it.
Thank you very much for your patronage.
And so, let's begin the Foundation Course.
I feel very lucky that a beautiful
machine like you chose me.
Did her frequency fluctuate just now?
Probably just a bug.
We'll send her to the cleaners afterwards.
A machine would never show emotion.
Don't be ridiculous. Of course it wouldn't.
You're very pretty.
And you smell nice too.
Thank you very much.
This feels great!
No...
You're already this wet.
You feel very good...
...and you're pretty.
No!
That's good.
It feels... very good!
Oh, no!
No...
Don't say that.
You feel great.
A-Amazing.
My insides have grown so hot.
What's happening?
This is a first.
Something's wrong.
What? Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
I apologize.
Apparently, we have a little
problem in the programming.
About the matter we were discussing earlier...
I trust that you can see it through.
Very well.
We'll watch her for now.
Yes... Yes...
So deep. It's as deep... as it will go.
Yes...
She's been used really hard.
It'll take at least three days to repair her.
That's no good.
I feel like a prick for suggesting this, but she has
another client in three hours. Just let her sleep.
She's a very popular machine, after all.
Is he on the blacklist?
No. If he was, he wouldn't have gotten this far.
Should I help out?
Don't sweat it.
I'll handle this myself.
It's your break, right? Why don't you take a rest?
Thanks.
This feels great!
Oh, sir, tease me more!
Harder!
Yes, there!
What do you think, Kuroki?
Shouldn't we make her get wetter?
Some guys aren't into that.
Well then, we'll make her gasps a little quieter,
but since she's supposed to be inexperienced,
we'll make her get wetter the better he makes her feel.
Maybe this will do the trick.
No...
This has nothing to do with our job.
Kuroki speaking.
Model #23 has returned.
Report to the research lab immediately.
The research lab?
I don't see anything wrong with the machinery.
Carry her to the servicing room.
Kuroki-san?
Yes?
Did you make any progress today...
...about what's been happening?
No, not really.
Is that so?
Then we're really in a pickle.
We still don't know the origin of the problem.
We have no choice but to wait
until there's more evidence.
I see.
Well, we mustn't use methods that
will inconvenience our customers.
Be careful about that.
Yes.
And also, remember the cleaner
that I mentioned to you earlier?
We'll discuss that another time.
We must make good use of our time.
Right?
Harder! Deeper, please!
How does this feel?
Very nice!
Amazingly nice!
Come in!
I'm coming in.
Amazing! My insides are seizing up!
Very nice! I love it!
You're perfect, Ms. President.
I won't let you cum yet.
Thank you.
I'd love to feel this thrill until I die.
I've concealed the materials,
but are you sure it's okay?
I don't want to apologize to the
main branch for a mistake.
I'll stay clear of the most dangerous paths.
But I've been seeing a lot of girls around
here that aren't company members.
And besides, they're all young and pretty.
Oh, don't think that.
Don't worry about trivial things.
I wouldn't want your perfect skin
to become blotchy from stress.
I can't hold back!
How was it today?
The same as always.
I see.
But the final client was a little bit better than the rest.
He made me feel good.
Feel good?
Yes. I was happy to be with him.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I'm cleaning out your insides.
So cold.
Don't lie.
You can't sense that.
I wonder if that man will come back?
He probably won't.
Men like to try many different types.
He'll probably choose a different machine.
Would you do that too?
Yeah.
I see. What a pity.
He was such a nice man.
Thanks for always making me clean.
It's my job.
Why did you become a Love Machine cleaner?
I'm not really sure.
That's pretty.
You always wear it.
Is it a present from someone?
I don't have anyone like that in my life.
An android is dreaming?
It can't be.
Their intelligence circuits contain
only what we implement.
They shouldn't have feelings or desires.
I'm with the 72nd district.
I apologize for intruding so late at night.
I have some questions that are
difficult to ask at your company.
What is it?
I've heard rumors that android sites are
collecting DNA for the black market.
Do you know anything about this?
The black market?
No, I'm just a technician, so I don't
know anything about that.
Really?
It's cold.
This feels great!
No!
It's moving inside!
You're a very well made machine.
I've never seen reactions this realistic before.
You feel great, too!
Harder! Please use me harder!
I'd do that even if you didn't ask.
How's this hole?
Even this hole smells nice! I can't stand it!
It's flinching. Amazing.
Let me have plenty to drink.
Give me lots of wetness.
Amazing!
You're the perfect machine!
I suppose that previously observed
phenomenon was just a random occurrence.
She has three more reservations tonight.
Her next client is a man who's been with her before.
It's so hard and thick.
Beautiful.
I can’t put it into words.
This feels too good!
You're... You're perfect!
Can I cum right now?
Be my guest.
There it is!
I've seen this man before.
At least I think I have.
What's wrong?
That song...
She's reacting to the music.
This is completely outside of my calculations.
I can't believe it!
What song is this?
I think I've heard it before.
Or maybe I haven't...
Anyway, it's an old tune from the last century.
Where have I heard this before?
What about this song?
H-How is this possible?
What's wrong?
I don't understand it at all.
You're a Love Machine, aren't you?
Isn't it strange for you to cry?
I don't understand it either.
You might have some remaining feelings.
Sadness? Happiness? Sweetness?
Sweetness?
I'm talking about love.
"Love", you say?
Do you know what could've happened to her?
No.
But you've watched over her the whole time.
You're not an ordinary Love Machine. You're special.
Special?
And I like you.
Yes! This feels great!
You're amazingly wet!
I feel so hot! It's so intense. I'm going to cum!
Not yet, not yet.
I like your fingers, but I want...
I want your nice, hard, thick...
What do you want exactly?
Your c**k.
I couldn't hear that. You'll have to speak louder.
I want your c**k!
Please put it inside of me now!
Okay.
Beautiful!
I'm going to cum!
Just look.
Your pussy is greedily swallowing up my dick.
How lewd.
No!
Amazing.
Yes! Harder!
Harder! Deeper, please!
You're perfect.
Thank you.
I don't want to leave you now.
So reserve me again.
Very well. I'll reserve you again.
I'm so happy.
The computer is going haywire!
The brainwave levels are at 37... 30... 60!
Libido levels rising from 30 to 40!
So she's returned.
This needs further investigation.
I understand.
It's gone from level 99 to 100!
It's reached the limit!
Her memories are returning?
Did you bring your ID card?