This is important, understand? It will be on the test.
My name is Fujishima Takano, and
I am the student council president.
And this is the secretary Konoe Chiyomaru.
As members of the council, we
don't want to work all day.
I want something wonderful that makes my heart race.
Sensei! Fujishima-san seems ill.
Is that true, Fujishima?
Oh, yes!
I have a headache.
Konoe, would you escort her to the infirmary?
Yes, I understand.
Wh-What were you thinking?
Pretending to be sick and leaving class early doesn't
sound like something a council member should be doing!
Are you listening, Chiyomaru?
Take it off.
What?
Your clothes... Take them off.
Here?
Yeah.
Well I do have a habit of exposing my body...
But at school... Especially during class time seems a little...
I don't care. Just take off your clothes.
O-Okay.
Do you want to try breaking me?
A School Where Love Is Unnecessary
I-Is this okay?
No, it's not Don't hide it.
How are you feeling right now?
T-This is... harder than I imagined...
It's as if I'm crawling under a hurdle
that is too high to jump.
Sorry, I don't understand.
I... I can't think properly.
Everyone else is in the middle of a lesson right now.
D-Don't say that...
Some of them are probably worried about you.
Thats...
It's already this wet.
No...
How horrible. You're supposed to be model
student as the council president
I'm sorry...
Apologizing to me wont help.
Spread your pussy open and
apologize to everyone in class.
I'm sorry...
Class is still in session, but I'm naked in the hallway...
My pussy is... completely drenched.
I'm sorry for being a perverted president
Looks like you need to be punished.
No, not at a place like this...
W-Wait... I'm serious.
If someone sees me like this, I...
I was at a loss, wondering if it was okay for
me to change you the way I wanted to.
C-Chiyomaru...
But, I won't hesitate anymore.
If it is your wish, then I will break you.
A-Aren't you misunderstanding something?
I was always like this.
Y-You're being too presumptuous
if you think you can change me.
Jeez...
That instructor sure prepared a lot of teaching materials.
No...
S-Stop Chiyomaru...
My voice will come out.
You don't need to hold back, Takano.
Let the whole school hear you.
That's...
What should I do?
Even though I shouldn't be getting
off, it's feeling so good.
You want everyone to see your pathetic self
moan as your pussy grips my cock, right?
N-No...
No... Don't!
If keep doing it so rough, I wont be able to take it...
Someone is coming this way.
N-No... No!
We have to hide somewhere...
Why? You don't need to hold back.
Let them see how unsightly are you when you cum!
No... I'm gonna cum...
She's going to see me as I cum.
My breasts, my pussy, my naughtly places...
They'll see everything!
Wh-What are you doing!?
N-No...
I'm gonna cum... I'm gonna cuml
I'm... I'm cummingl
U-Umm...
Would you be Fujishima-san,
the student council president?
I apologize, for showing you this embarrassing scenery.
Do me a favor and come to the
council room later, will you?
The School Where Love is Unnecessary
Student Council Room
Musashino Futaba-san, I see you're a freshman.
Umm... I won't tell anyone so...
Actually, no one will believe me even if I do say it so...
To think that the student council president
was doing something like that...
I'm sorry for startling you like that.
It's okay...
May I ask something?
What is it?
That kind of play... Is that something normal for lovers?
I doubt there are many couples
that would do what we do.
You can relax, it's normal.
Besides, we aren't lovers.
What!? Then you're...
Well if you put it that way,
I guess you could call it a pig.
P-Pig...
What?
Is it something that surprising?
B-But, doing something like that with
someone you don't love isn't normal.
Even if you don't like each other at
first, I'm sure you will after sex!
That's enough, sweety.
You mustn't let your youthful warped
delusions about sex get to your head.
W-Warped? I'm the warped one here?
If that's the case, would you like to borrow Chiyomaru?
I think you should be able to earn the
nickname "Public Toilet" in three days.
One day is more than enough.
I I've had enough!
It's clear that we both live in separate worlds!
I will forget about today, so please
don't involve me again!
Oh, you're no fun.
We've both confided in each other so let's be friends!
I don't want to!
Don't touch me like that, you're filthy!
Certainly, I'm sure you find our relationship
strange from your perspective,
but an outsider without any experience
in sex has no right to call Takano filthy.
I-I'm sorry... I...
Sorry for making it sound harsh.
With it being so sudden, you must be confused, right?
Yes...
In that case, why don't you see for
yourself if what we do is really filthy?
What?
That's right...
I guess there is no other way, so it can't be helped.
Huh? Wait...
W-Why are you stripping!?
It's so that you can see of course.
As someone of the same gender,
what do you think of Takano's body?
What do I think?
She's taking it off!
Her breasts are huge...
Her skin is shiny and a little flushed.
She's very...
Beautiful...
You heard her.
Since she complimented you, why don't you show
her your everything without holding back?
O-Okay...
Futaba, take a good look. This is my pussy.
Look. Can you tell its wet?
Takano is a pervert that loves to be watched.
Pervert?
Disappointing right? The student
council president is a pervert.
I'm sorry... I can't endure it anymore!
Looks like she started to masturbate.
She's really doing it. It's making wet noisesl
Can you see? My Clitoris, my nipples, my everything!
Futaba-chan, do you masturbate?
I don't do such things!
You don't need to hide it, something
that feels so good... Everyone does it!
Don't lump me together with a pervert like you!
I can't believe it.
You're doing such a thing in front of people...
A girl calling me a pervert is
making me quiver with excitement!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
Okay, stop right there.
That's not good. You can't just cum in front of a guest.
C-Chiyomaru, why are you?
If you are going to cum, you need her permission first.
Futaba... Please, I was almost there...
May I cum? It's okay, isn't it?
Please, let me cum !
D-Do what you want, you pervert!
I'm sorry... I'm a pervert.
Being seen masturbating really gets to me!
Look! Look, look!
Look at me messing my pussy up and as I cum!
I'm... I'm cumming!
W-Wow, that was my first time
seeing someone else cum!
So that's what it looks like...
What's wrong Futaba-chan?
Yes?
The main event starts now, you know?
No... Chiyomaru, wait...
Let me rest, please...
N-No way something that huge
can't possibly fit. She'll break!
It's inside!
Amazing! Cock, cock, cock!
The president's...
It looks like it hurts from being
spread open like that, yet.
It looks like it feels good.
Chiyomaru, go ahead and mess up my pussy!
Look, Futaba-chan is watching.
We gotta teach her more about sex.
Futaba...
Watch me! Watch me!
Watch me more...
Sex, it feels so good I
She's... so close...
It's rubbing me inside, and hollowing me out...
He's hitting me deep inside...
I feel it, I feel it!
This... This is how amazing sex is.
Being watched, feels so good...
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Futaba-chan?
H-Huh?
Please excuse me!
That girl said a lot of things, but she had
her eyes glued to you until the end.
Looks like she came too.
She's quite something, isn't she?
To think she could reach orgasm just by watching.
Musashino Takaba...
She's an interesting girl.
A School Where Love is Unnecessary
After seeing something like that...
Of course I won't be able to hold It in!
I can't believe it!
Having sex in the student council room of all
places with someone you don't even like...
Doing such lewd things...
If it were me...
If I were to be doing it...
That's right If it were me...
It would be much more romantic.
I've decided...
My first time would be in a hotel
room with an ocean view...
With the person I love gently making love to me.
No...
Don't lick there...
It's filthy...
It's not filthy. Futaba's pussy is beautiful and cute.
Huhl?
Y-You're...
Hey, everyone in class is watching too.
Wh-What is this?
This is classroom?
Wait! No, don't!
Everyone... Everyone is watching!
No, stop. Please stop!
Don't put it in here!
Why not let everyone see you losing your virginity?
You're pussy is so drenched, that it went in smoothly.
Please, take it out, take it out!
How incredible, Futaba's pussy is going crazy!
As expected of a virgin pussy!
I'm being seen by everyonel
The sight of the dick going in me...
I'm being seen in such an
embarrassing position by everyone!
Please, don't grope my breasts!
Why? It's my first time and yet.
People are watching and he's forcing himself on me...
And yet... Why is it so...
See, it feels good right?
No, you're wrong...
Look, I got all excited just by looking.
My nipples are really hard!
President...
Tell me Futaba, what is making your face look like that?
Love? Affection? It's not because of
something as vague as that right?
It seems like you're feeling too good to answer me.
Do you understand now?
You don't need love to have sex.
No... My head is going blank.
I can't think of anything anymore!
It's pounding against my womb. I might go crazy I
What's this? You look like you're about to cum!
You're being seen by everyone
and violated like an animal...
You're cumming even though it's
your first time, aren't you?
Futaba, you re so cute.
No, stop moving.
I don't want to cum!
That's impossible Futaba, your body
is already about to reach its climax.
That's right... Your pussy is hot and twitching!
No way...
No...
It's coming...
Something amazing is coming deep
from inside from my body!
No matter how much you try to resist,
Futaba, with your reasoning or emotions...
You cannot go against your primal instincts.
No matter what you do, you cannot help but cum.
Please... Stop. Stop It...
I cant... Please forgive me!
Now, cum Futaba. Go ahead and cum!
I I'm cumming... I m...
I'm cummingl I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Oh, no... I came while masturbating to a fantasy.
Futaba... Seems like it felt really good.
Why...
I was searching for outstanding students like you,
to be new members for our student council!
Well, we cant leave people who know our secret alone...
I thought we could just take some urination scenes,
but who knew that we could film a masturbation scene.
Y-You can't be serious... That was all recorded!?
Good job Futaba, you were just as I expected.
No, you exceeded my expectations.
Welcome to the student council!
It can't be... But... That's...
No!!