Fujinomiya Private School.
My beautiful place of learning.
This may sound like a cheesy line, but I can't live without it.
It used to be famous as an all-girls school for spoiled rich girls.
But it merged with some other schools and became co-ed years later.
What a merciful place the world can be!
And thanks to that, there are four
different kinds of uniforms to admire.
At first it was because it was unfair to force
established students to buy new uniforms,
but now they have a choice of which uniform to wear.
Well, the students certainly enjoy that aspect of it.
And there are plenty of people who transfer
to this school simply for the uniforms.
But then again, there are plenty of guys who transfer
to this school because the uniforms turn them on.
There is also, of course, plenty of candid photography.
To those interested, I have a photo collection
on the Internet for them to admire.
Naturally, it is hosted on the school’s server.
What a convenient place the world can be.
I can get these pictures and blackmail
the girls in them to do as I please.
And from these sessions, I can get even more
pictures to make the website even more popular.
This takes care of my money worries for life.
At first, I came to this school because my
parents kicked me out and I was living alone,
but in the end, I'd say it worked out ideally for me.
Principal's Office
Until, one day...
I was summoned to the Principal's Office
Kawamura-kun.
What is the meaning of this?
It was a photograph from last week where
I called her to an empty club room.
My slave, Tsutsumi Ayano, being punished by me.
Here's the story.
A female athlete on scholarship was raped a month ago.
Heartbroken, she killed herself.
The one who had actually raped her was
apparently me, the toughest kid in the school.
And the photograph of that was apparently sent to the principal.
So in order for the school save face,
I was quietly expelled with no explanation.
I'm sure it was just to satisfy the teachers' stupid egos anyway.
Sick, really.
What a fucking joke.
Ayano is another matter, but I wasn't about to let them
expel me for raping someone I never even touched.
If I'm out of this school, it’ll be really difficult
to take photos and keep up my adult site.
I won't be able to eat.
Expulsion Notice
But they had no mercy.
After a month's probationary period, my expulsion date was set.
Very nicely done
Translation Voldemort | Timing: Plastic Yakuza | Editing: The Fullpot cat | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
Presented by erobeat | http://www erabeat.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Gakune 2
But something didn't sit right.
Somehow, the pieces of the puzzle didn't fit.
After all, I really didn't know the girl who had been pared at all.
It seemed like it was just an excuse to get me expelled.
I cornered Ayano and asked her about it,
but she said she hadn't told anyone about me.
There must be something deeper...
Thinking this, I gathered all the data from my cameras all over
the school and discovered the Academy’s conspiracy
They had been trying to create a prostitute agency for the
old men on the board using the hottest girls in the school.
Whoever said art imitates life really was on to something.
If the girls had told anyone about it,
no one would have believed them.
The girl who had committed suicide was their first victim.
Unable to handle it, she killed herself.
And the second one chosen was Ayano.
But I also had my hands on Ayano.
Since I was in the way they wanted my expulsion
in order to keep me away from Ayano.
Gimme a fucking break.
So then I tried to appeal my expulsion by gathering
evidence to negotiate with the principal.
This time, using the principal's daughter,
who also happens to be the student body president.
Oh no, expelled?
Quiet! They’ll hear you.
Sorry.
But it’s all a misunderstanding!
The principal will understand if I explain it to her.
She’s just being lied to by the other teachers.
You’re the only one I can trust.
I get it, Kawamura-kun.
I’ll try to convince my mom to have a proper
meeting with you so you can explain it to her.
So cheer up, Kawamura-kun.
You'll be fine. I'll take care of it.
But the very next day, her attitude made a complete 180.
You're horrible, Kawamura-kun!
You've been lying to me.
How dare you treat girls like that!
Come on, I said that wasn't me!
You’re lying!
My mom showed me the pictures you’re in.
I think... you should be expelled!
Well, I wanted to be nice to her.
But I guess this way is more me.
What should I do from here on?
Ayano!
I'm sorry, Master!
How many times have I told you to be careful with your teeth?
Can't ya even perform a simple blowjob?
I'm sorry.
It’s just that I’m throbbing too much down there...
Talking back to me? You've got some nerve, Ayano.
If you think that's bad... how about this!
P-Please stop it, Master!
T-This is too strong!
Shut up!
You deserve this punishment.
This is for being a bad slave and for nearly turning me in.
Have you forgotten already?
Continue with the blowjob at once!
I'm sorry... But not like this...
Shit, you re more trouble than you’re worth.
When will you be able to give a decent blowjob?
This is how ya do it.
Don’t let your teeth touch it.
You know what'll happen if you let that happen, right?
Very good.
Get it in deeper.
Master... I...
Shut up!
Don’t talk back to me!
I’m almost there, so keep with it!
Master...
I’m almost there.
Drink it all up!
You spilled some again.
I'm sorry! But this is too much to swallow at once...
Does a slave talk back to her master, Ayano?
I'm so sorry! I’m so sorry!
Come on. Clean up the spilled semen.
With your mouth, that is.
Yes, Master.
M-Master?
You’re sticking your butt up so high.
Are you asking for it?
N-No, I'm not.
It's just a habit from volleyball practice...
I want it! I want you!
Master, please punish the lowly Ayano with your mighty penis.
You’re a really needy slave, aren't you, Ayano?
Fine.
I’ll give ya plenty of punishment.
N-No, that’s not right. That’s not right, Master!
Not there.
Not where?
Where are you talking about, Ayano?
Tell me.
T-That is my butthole.
Please don’t put it in there.
It’s dirty.
Dirty?
Even though we cleaned it up so well before, it’s still dirty?
Damn your asshole, Ayano.
P-Please don't say that.
Please don’t make me watch.
It’s embarrassing.
Well, if it's dirty, we'd better clean it out again.
Ayano.
Oh, please don’t clean it.
I’m tired of getting it cleaned.
Then which would you prefer?
Cleaning? Or my rod?
Y-Your rod, Master.
Ayano!
I’m sorry, I'm sorry.
Your penis, Master!
Please put in your penis!
My butthole is all clean.
So please put it in.
Please punish me.
Punish me through my butthole.
Very well said. That's why you’re my slave, Ayano.
It hurts...
Master...
If it doesn't hurt, it's a pretty pathetic “punishment”, Ayano.
Please don’t move so much...
If I don't move, it's not gonna feel that great for me.
What’s wrong, Ayano?
It just hurts...
And feels strange... it’s supposed to hurt...
But I feel strange.
What’re ya saying?
You like it in the ass?
What a pervert you are, Ayano!
I... I’m not a pervert...
I don’t... like it...
Oh? Really?
But, please don’t move so roughly.
If you do, then I...
But you don’t really like it anyway, do you?
No, I don't like it.
But if you move so roughly... My butt will...
It’ll what?
Oh no!
Not my nipples... Don't pinch them!
I like it! I like it!
I like it in the butt!
Because my Master’s penis is in my butt, I like it!
You like your first round of anal sex!? That’s unusual.
I like it.
Because I'm a pervert.
Master's penis ripping open my butt hurts, but it also feels great.
I know it’s deviant, but it feels great!
Then why don’t you act like it feels great?
It’s so great...
Your penis is so great..
My Master’s thick penis is playing inside of my butthole.
Oh dear.
My butthole... will rip open.
It feels like... I'm going to throw up.
If this feels any more intense, I’m going to throw up.
Please forgive me, Master.
Let me finish in your ass, Ayano!
No! Anything but that!
If you cum inside my butt, I really will be a pervert.
I'm begging you, Master.
Please put it in my vagina.
Please finish in my vagina.
Don’t move.
If you’re so rough, I really will cum.
Oh, please stop it!
I don’t want to cum.
I don’t want to cum, Master.
Forgive me.
Please forgive me, Master.
Master, your penis feels too wonderful!
Oh no, don’t rip me up!
Don’t spread open my hole!
Oh no! I really am going to cum!
No! I can't!
Not my butt! My butt... cumming... cumming!
So much is coming out.
Master's semen.
So much is coming out... from inside my butt.
So you came from butt sex, eh?
You really are a fun slave, Ayano.
Oops, you’d better cover your butthole or else all
that wonderful semen I just put in will fall out.
Shit, I don't think she heard me.
Well then, how shall I devour the student body president?
I’m looking forward to tomorrow.
What's this?
It’s from my Master... I mean, it’s a message from Kawamura-kun.
He wants you to bring that with you to the chapel after school.
If you don’t show up, he’ll show that picture to everyone.
W-Well! I told you.
I told you like he asked me to.
So please don't let him down.
I'm begging you.
Bye then!
Dear Madam Class President,
Please put on the costume in the bag and come to the chapel after school.
Don't wear panties. Put the other thing that’s in the bag inside of your pussy.
hat I say, I'll expose that picture of you.
Like I said, I really think you should be expelled!
What're you doing?
No! Let go of me!
I’m not a fan of going out to get my prey.
I guess it’s best they come to me.
No! Kawamura-kun!
Why are you doing this?
Take this off of me!
It’s your fault.
You didn't keep your promise to me.
So now it’s time for you to do as I say.
Horrible... you're horrible. Horrible!
That was my first kiss.
You’re going to pay.
I’m going to make you pay for this!
Oh? And how are you gonna make me pay?
I'm gonna tell my mom about this.
Then you’ll definitely be expelled.
How fun.
Go ahead and tell her.
No! What’re you trying to do!?
No!
Don’t look! No!
Stop it!
For such an innocent face, you've sure got some huge, slutty tits.
No!
Don’t suck them!
Stop it!
Don’t suck my breasts!
Don’t suck them!
What a great smell.
It smells like sweet milk.
Don't! Don’t smell them!
I wonder if milk will come out if I squeeze them?
Ow!
That hurts!
Milk won’t come out.
Stop... Stop it!
Hey, Kawamura-kun, please stop doing this horrible thing.
If you stop now, I’ll forgive you.
I won't tell anyone.
But I thought you were gonna “make me pay”.
That's not very president-like of you.
Taking back something you said like that.
No, don’t! Not down there! That’s dirty!
Oh? So you're dirty down here?
Now that ya mention it, it smells kinda like piss.
You’re so horrible.
How dare you talk to a girl like that.
No!
Don’t lick it!
I will... lick it clean for you.
Don’t do that!
Kawamura-kun...
Stop! Not like this!
Hey, Madam President, are you a virgin?
I'm not telling.
Well I guess I’ll find out when I put it in.
Put what in?
No! Don’t put that in there!
Don’t put it in!
I'll answer you! I'll answer you!
Stop it!
I'm a virgin! I’m a virgin, okay?
Oh, a virgin, eh?
Not anymore. You’re a proper woman now.
No... Don't move...
That hurts!
It really does hurt!
Stop it!
I hate this!
That hurts!
It hurts!
Mom! Help me!
Mom!
Hey now, the main reason this is happening
to you is because of your mom.
Just... stop it!
It hurts! I'm serious!
Have mercy!
It’ll feel good soon.
And when it does... you’ll never be able to live without my rod again!
That hurts!
Stop it! Don't!
Almost time to finish.
I’ll spray plenty of it inside of you.
Don’t do it!
If you do that, I'll get pregnant!
No!
Don’t do it!
Not inside of me!
Better start thinking of a name for the baby soon. Here I come!
I don’t want a baby!
Don’t!
Please don’t!
I'll get pregnant!
I don’t want to get pregnant!
Not inside of me!
No!
It's coming...
Lots of it... into my uterus.
So much has come inside that it s leaking out...
I'll get pregnant!
If you say anything to anyone, I'll post
these pictures all around town.
I'm sure you already know this, but if these pictures
get out, your mothers job will also be in jeopardy.
If word gets out that the Principal's daughter
was raped on campus, she’ll be fired for sure.
Well, that’s only if you tell on me.
No! Stop it!
Do Not Enter
I’m sick of you talking back to me.
But you want me to put such a disgusting toy...
...inside of me.
It won't fit.
After having my rod buried in you all week, why stop now?
No! Don’t!
Learn your place!
It seems you still don't understand.
You’re so horrible.
Not this..
It’s so humiliating.
That’s what you get for not listening to me.
Hey, Kawamura-kun, please just stop this.
If you're worried about being expelled,
I’ll talk to my mom and make her take it back.
But if you keep doing this, you’ll ruin your life.
I’ll forgive everything else you've already done.
And I won’t tell anyone about it.
So please... Okay?
You make it sound so easy.
But you're only being this nice because you’re in trouble now?
It’s that two-faced attitude that I hate!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I’m apologizing, okay?
So please go easy on me!
Please don’t hurt me!
But you already belong to me, Madam President.
You wanna know what happens when you oppose me?
Let me show you.
Don’t do it! No!
Your tits are as nasty as ever, I see.
Don't do it! Don’t suck on my nipples!
If you keep doing that, I’ll start to feel strange!
Your nipples really like it that much?
In that case...
Oh, no! Stop it!
Not on my boobs...
What? You want something below, too?
No!
If you're that wet, it should fit inside by now.
No! Don’t put that much in!
It's moving inside...
I’ll die! I’ll die like this!
This feels... weird...
What?
Don't look! It’s coming out of my boobs!
Madam President?
Don't tell me you got pregnant from that?
No.
Not from that...
No? But you're lactating!
This is...
something I've had since birth.
When I get really excited, I cum from my breasts.
I noticed it in elementary school.
So I did some research, and I apparently have an abnormal body.
Not even my mom knows about this.
But I got found out.
A boy in my class found out!
I can’t live on!
I wanna die!
An abnormal body?
What an amazing find!
You’re perfect, Madam President! You’re perfect!
Kawamura-kun...
Stop it, Kawamura-kun!
Don't!
I like you, Madam President!
I’m gonna turn you into my exclusive slave!
A girl who orgasms milk?
That’s perfect!
It’s like you were born to be my woman!
Get more turned on!
Then spurt out more milk!
No! Stop it, Kawamura-kun!
I can't take it anymore!
I don’t want to lactate!
Stop it!
Have mercy...
Not my breasts!
No!
Stop it, I’m feeling strange!
I'm losing my mind!
No!
Don’t squeeze my nipples!
Not there!
Please, not there!
If you’re that rough with me...
Very good!
Squirt out more.
Get more turned on!
Oh, no!
Milk is coming out...
More milk is coming out...
No! Don’t, it’s no good!
I’m losing my mind.
Something's strange!
Don't! Kawamura-kun!
Have mercy!
Not any more! Not any more!
I'm losing my mind!
I'm supposed to hate this...
I should be hating this...
But my breasts love it!
It feels so much better than when I touch them myself.
Even though I’m being violated...
Even though I’m being raped...
I'm getting turned on by it!
I'm becoming a bad girl.
It's coming out again!
Milk is coming out!
Now I’m even peeing.
This is no good.
I think I've gone insane.
I love it!
Even though I’m being raped...
You didn't pee.
That’s your cum.
It’s proof that a woman actually enjoyed it.
And now it’s time for me to cum too.
Deep inside of you!
No! Not inside!
I'll get pregnant!
Please!
Not inside of me!
Cum outside of me!
Here I come... here I come!
No! Not inside of me!
I'm too young to get pregnant!
Please! Outside of me!
I don't want a baby!
But you've got such great milk already.
Give me a nice big baby!
No!
Oh no.
So much hot stuff inside of me.
I feel the semen coming deep inside of me.
I told him I didn't want it.
I told him I didn't want a baby.
Now I'm filled with semen from a guy I hate again.
He's releasing more.
My insides are already completely full with it, but more is coming in.
No...
No!
No!!
So she fainted, eh?
And I was ready for more.
Well, I guess I'll change her costume for round two.
Oh no! Milk is coming out!
To be continued!