Farewell, Tita...
Luvence's...
Crown Princess.
Hime Dorei: The Twin Princesses Fallen From Grace
Part 1: Demonic Training of the Twin Princesses
N-Nee-san...
15 Years Later...
So you're my client, huh?
You know who I am, don't you?
Liese Luvence,
Second Princess of the Great Kingdom of Luvence, right?
That's right.
Waldo Crowley, free practitioner of black magic across the continent,
who does not belong to any country. A lone genius.
And for the right price you'll take on any request,
no matter how unpleasant it may be, isn't that right?
You really are a princess.
You've done your research on the dark arts well.
Yes. It's not a profession for half-hearted people.
So, what is your request?
I want to usurp the throne of Luvence.
As you know, I am the second born princess.
I want to ascend to the throne, but there is an obstacle in the way.
The Crown Princess, Tita Luvence, huh?
Yes. That's how it is. Will you accept my request?
I'm all ears.
There are three qualifications that the female
heir to the throne of Luvence must fulfill.
She must have the ability to reassure her people
as a statesperson, and be intelligent.
She must behave in a perfect lady-like manner,
setting an example as a proper lady, visibly cultivated.
In the case that she does not marry,
she must retain her chastity until the day she ascends to the throne.
I will do it under one condition...
What is that?
Let me decide the method.
Is that all right?
Here is your room.
Ah, thank you.
I see.
Such a lovely room, wasted on me.
Is there anything else?
Um... Magician-sama,
You are a real magician, right?
Um... I'm really interested in magic, you see.
Would you like to see some of my magic?
Yes! I'd love to!
You are as wise as I expected, Magician-sama!
But, my magic isn't something I can
simply show to just anyone, you know.
Eh? I see...
Well, since you're so eager, it should be
all right to show you something simple.
Really? You will?
Hurray!
How's that?
Amazing!
It's simply amazing! Just like I had expected from a great magician!
This is the first time I've seen such wonderful magic.
I'm gonna brag about this to Tita-sama later.
Are you Princess Tita's handmaid?
Yes. We all take our turns attending to Tita-sama.
That's just perfect!
Huh?
Waldo-sama... It hurts!
This is the magic you so wanted to see.
Aren't you satisfied?
No...
My body... I...
No!
It hurts! What... What are you doing?
No... It's embarrassing...
No! No! Not that!
I don't want to...
No! No! No!!
This... This...
I beg you, Waldo-sama.
Please! Please stop it!
I'll... I'll do anything!
No!
It hurts!
I... I...
No!
Don't move!
It hurts! Don't rape me!
Don't rape me! No!
It hurts!
It's dirty...
No, it hurts!
I... I... I'll get... dirty...
No!!
Stop it!
Even though it's your first time, you're such a nasty girl.
I'll cum a lot, so enjoy yourself!
No! Stop it! I'll become pregnant!
Don't do it! No! Please!
I don't wanna get pregnant!
Not inside me! Please don't!
Semen... Semen... No!
No! Don't make me pregnant!
It's coming out... The semen is coming out...
A lot... a lot of it... coming out...
Did you think this was the end!?
Tita... sama...
Save me...
It hurts...
I... I...
What is the meaning of this!?
My pussy... My pussy feels good!
My pussy is soaking wet!
Please, give me semen, Waldo-sama!
Huh?
Yeah...
Hey! Are you listening!?
To use magic spells, you need magical power. Lots of it.
Ah, my dirty pussy feels so good!
The best way to replenish magic power
is to use a woman as a catalyst.
So that's why...
Aren't you... overdoing it a little?
That woman is Tita's maid, right?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
Yes. That's right...
Therefore, ravaging her would be the
quickest way to get Tita's attention.
After all, she hasn't been under my control for long.
You... certainly work fast, don't you?
I will violate your sister.
Just relax.
I wonder if it will go well...
Wanna die that badly, you bastard?
You can't tell the difference between
what you can and can't say, can you?
You're kidding me.
If I were to take your head right now, not one soul would complain.
Don't think that I'll warn you again.
You think you could kill me like that?
You'd throw your life away?
As you wish... I'll kill you right away!
Die!
Wh-What's this!?
The great swordswoman is in shock, huh!?
Ah! Stop!
You're good at this, Captain!
No, you're wrong!
I... You're wrong!
What's wrong? This is your real nature, isn't it?
No! Don't say that!
What's the matter? You sound like you enjoy it!
No, you're wrong.
It hurts... I... I...
This is great!
No, don't say that! Stop!
You could make a living like this!
No... No...
My body... What's happening to my body?
That's the ultimate fencer for you, taking it like a whore!
It hurts!
Surrender to me!
If you do, I'll treat you 10 times, no, 100 times better!
Yes, Master.
Feels good... It feels so good!
Do my pussy harder!
It feels so good! Please give me more!
I feel good! I love it!
Waldo-sama's cock... shove it into me!
Shove it deeper into my pussy!
I... I'm cumming! Cumming!
S-Semen... Give me semen. Make me pregnant!
Please, give me your cum!
Let me bear your children!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
A... baby...
I'll... have...
What is your intention?
Looks like the letter I wrote posing as your sister got you here.
What is the meaning of this?
I won't let up until you answer me!
I lived in the nation of Izuur.
You... What in the...
Accused of heresy, everyone, even women
and children, were murdered.
I am the last survivor.
Impossible... Then, you...
You must be worried.
You don't know what may happen to your sister.
My sister... Sister...
For my sister, for her only...
I don't care what happens to me.
Waldo-sama, I beg of you...
You can't go back on your word now.
I'll give you one last chance.
If you taint your purity, you can no longer inherit the throne, right?
Wh-What are you saying? Liese matters more to me than that...
Have you no heart?
Because of you, I threw it all away 15 years ago!
No...
Father, I'm sorry! Forgive me!
It hurts! It hurts!
Liese...
Just as I thought, the Princess's body is the best!
No! Stop it!
Don't say that!
I can't... can't...
I'm sorry, Liese. I... I...
It feels good!
No, something like this... It's wrong!
Waldo-sama's cock is violating my pussy...
It's fucking me! Please, more!
Yes! Your cock feels good!
Cum, give me a lot of cum!
It feels good! Give me more. Give me more cum!
Drench my pussy in cum!
Are you listening? My pussy is...
Give it to me in my pussy. Make me pregnant!
Waldo-sama! Waldo-sama! Waldo-sama!
It's coming out... My pussy is gushing while I'm getting fucked.
I'm... I'm cumming!
It feel good!
So deep inside...
I'm cumming again!
I can't stop cumming! I can't stop!