Hiiro no Koku
Episode 1
Yamagawa Detective Agency
Could you...
please find my wife for me?
Did she run away from home?
A month ago, she left this note.
I'm sorry. Please don't look for me. -Etsuko
Do you have a photo of your wife?
Just this.
It's my wife... and my daughter.
She's very pretty.
Can you find her?
Do you have any idea where she might be?
None at all.
She lived a very untroubled life.
I thought she was happy.
For the last month, I've been calling all our friends.
But she hasn't contacted any of them.
I'll take your case.
Um, what is this place?
It's a warehouse.
We need to test the results of your training.
You don't need to be scared.
It'll be mostly decent things.
Well, Shima-san! Long time no see.
We're here to play.
I'm delighted. Come in.
Oh, so this is your lady friend today?
She's a pretty one.
No! Oh, don't!
Don't pretend that you don't like it.
I can feel how wet you are down there.
Come on, stand up.
Let's show everyone what you're like down here.
No! Don't look.
Now, you're up next.
I can't. I-I don't want to!
Never mind, just come.
Don't pretend you weren't looking forward to this.
Now, let him have some fun with you.
Are you sure, Shima-san?
Do as you please with her.
Then I won't hold back.
Looks like you've already had fun with her.
She's so wet.
Oh... Oh, no!
Come, let's show the audience how wet you are.
Well, let's start the show now.
No!
Now, let's reveal your lovely wet area.
Hey! I can't see it! Hey!
Now let's use these.
N-No!
I think your body has a better idea
of what it wants than your mind.
See? Even your butthole is taking it well.
They're watching.
All of them...
with perverted eyes...
Eyes filled with excited lust.
Watching me.
Here's a present.
Now. Everyone in the audience, have your fun with her.
Hey! Spread your legs wider!
Let us see inside.
What a dirty slut.
I'm... I'm up next. For real.
Come on, look.
She's wiggling her hips.
She's really happy about it.
She's got such a whorish body.
Awesome, man!
They're watching me.
Watching my pussy.
They're watching.
Fuck me! Fuck me!
Okay, I'll put it in here.
Oh, yes!
Oh yes, yes!
Wow, she's so tight!
Yes! Right there!
I love it! I love it, love it!
Come on, lick it off.
It's your pussy juice.
Welcome back, sir.
Wow, she's really tired.
Looks like she had her brains fucked out.
Let her rest.
How was the stage?
A roaring success.
So she did it?
Yeah. She knew just how to entice the audience.
How to suck their dicks
and how to take anything they gave her.
I look forward to seeing it!
She's quick to swallow, too.
Her body learns fast.
She's really depraved, isn't she?
We always have tomorrow.
Let her rest for tonight.
Okay.
Why am I doing this?
I used to live such a peaceful, fulfilled life.
So why?
It all began that morning.
Have a nice day.
Yes, thank you.
Mommy, have a nice day!
Yes, take care, you two.
Bye, Etsuko.
Hello, delivery.
Coming.
Hello, madam.
Let's get started.
Mmm, she's got nice boobs.
Who are you guys!?
We're just fans of yours.
We've always been watching you.
You're the hottest MILF around.
But with just one man in your life,
you can t possibly be satisfied.
I-I'll scream for help!
Be our guest, wifey.
St-Stop it!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Don't! Stop it!
– Why? Why are you...
– We want to have a deep relationship with you, wifey.
Oh! Her boobs are even bigger than I thought.
Whoa! I can't stand it.
No!
I've always wanted to do this to you, wifey.
This body of yours is wasted on that old man.
We'd better apply this on well.
It's a great drug.
We bought it especially for you.
You've been so depraved this whole time.
We see through everything.
With such a hot wife like this?
What a neglectful husband.
We'll untie the bonds of your morality.
Well have fun with you until your heart explodes.
You were lonely, weren't you?
Your boobs were especially lonely, right?
Looks like the drug's working well.
Her hole is soaking wet.
Are you sure about this, wifey?
Your hole is throbbing like it wants it bad.
No! Please, anything but that!
We'll make you forget about everything else right away.
I'll take the front end then.
You're so cute, wifey.
Move your hips more!
Yes, that's right.
Wow, she's crying out cutely just from us plunging in.
She really is a masochist.
For someone who's being raped, she sure looks happy.
I'll bet she's been fantasizing about this all along.
Probably.
Time to untie some other bonds.
You're so wet. Aren't you embarrassed?
No. Stop it. Please!
Time for me to change it up and have some fun.
No! Wh-What are you doing?
Can't hold back anymore, wifey?
I guess I'll entertain you with just a finger.
But... unless you tell me what you
really want, I won't give it to you.
I can't... say something so lewd.
I'll make you want it so bad that you'll beg for it.
You look like you're enjoying this.
No!
I can't...
She's really turned on.
Maybe she'll cum from just a finger?
She can't hold back anymore.
I'm... I'm losing my mind.
Please... Please...
Please what, wifey?
No, I can't say it. I can't. I can't...
I don't understand you.
You'd better tell me clearly what it is that you want.
In...
What?
Put it in... please.
I can't hear you very well.
Say it louder.
Please put it in.
Put what in?
My finger?
N-No, not that!
What is it that you want put in?
I want...
You want my dick inside you, right?
Y-Yes, I do.
Then try shouting out, "Please fuck my pussy!"
Please fuck my pussy! Hurry!
Guess I will.
I promised, after all.
Okay...
Listen to her moan.
She wanted it really bad.
She really is a bitch in heat.
Now, let's give wifey some lunch.
Come, lick it off.
You like sucking it, don't you?
She's even wiggling her hips.
She's soaking wet.
Look at her.
She's so happy.
Take a look, wifey.
Here's a lovely shot of you and your husband.
Stop it!
What, you don't even want to see his picture?
Well, I guess you wouldn't, looking like this.
Please, stop it!
Wow! She's so wide open I can fit my fingers in too!
I guess seeing his picture got her excited.
Go for it. Right in front of your husband.
Etsuko.
Where are you?
What happened to you?
I don't know.
You looked so happy every day.
I'm home!
Mommy, Mommy!
Welcome back.
I met up with Emi on the way home.
At this time of the day?
How unusual.
Yeah.
I'm going to be extra busy at work starting tomorrow,
so I took the rest of the day off.
But I still have to prepare for
my supervisor's business trip.
Oh...
Mommy! Look, look!
I drew a picture of you, me and Daddy!
And the teacher said it was really good!
Look!
Wow, she's right.
That's a beautiful picture.
Yeah! I'm gonna put it up in my room.
Etsuko, is something wrong?
Why do you ask?
Well, you look a bit pale.
I'm fine.
Okay. Well, I'll take a bath now.
Etsuko, is something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
I'm sorry. What's come over me?
I'm like a zombie.
Maybe I'm just tired.
Must be.
I'm sure you're tired.
Go take a nap upstairs. I don't mind.
My husband didn't notice anything that day.
But if I'd only told him the truth, I'm sure
none of this would have happened.
The next day, Emi went off to school
and my husband went to work.
It was a morning just like any other.
It was as if nothing had happened.
Wifey, we'll come by tomorrow too.
I think you need us, wifey.
Even if you lock the door, we can
still get in through the window.
While I'm still safe, I must do something.
Something's wrong with me.
How do you want it, wifey?
Good morning, wifey.
Here we are.
Just like we promised.
You wanted us to come, right?
No, I didn't!
But you left the door and window unlocked.
You wanted us in, right?
I was letting in a nice breeze.
I was just about to close it!
Gee, I wonder.
Didn't you want me to do this?
We'll have lots of fun with you again today.
So much fun that you won't be able to stop.
No!
Stop it!
Not "No", but "Hurry up with it", right?
Tell us you want to be fucked
even harder than yesterday.
No!
You were waiting for this, weren't you?
Just look, her panties are already soaked.
Suck it. Come on.
More and more is flowing out.
Well? Is it tasty?
I think you've come to appreciate the taste of a man.
Even if you say you don't want
it, you won't run away, right?
You've come to like giving us head, haven't you?
Wifey, just be honest with us.
Be honest with yourself.
Even if she refuses to speak, her body is still honest.
She's already like this.
I guess you really want it bad, wifey.
What's wrong?
Are you ashamed of being turned on?
Isn't it better than being with your husband?
I'll make it even better.
Wow, she's good at sucking cock!
It's deep in her throat.
Awesome!
If she's this excited when getting gang-banged,
her husband can't be any good.
Didn't I say so? Even if your mind
resists us, your body is rebelling.
How cute.
Okay, time to switch places.
No! Stop it!
I'll make you want it so bad you can't stop.
Here we go.
It's in so deep... all the way.
Awesome!
I feel it.
She loves it.
What a slut.
She's a bottomless pit of lust.
We'll keep at it until you die,
you freaking whore.
There's plenty to go around.
Well? Isn't he bigger than your husband?
I've never felt one so thick.
Wow, awesome.
Her pussy juice keeps flowing.
Take a look at her face.
She looks so happy. She wants more.
You should thank us, wifey.
Well, I don't think she'll be able to forget our flavor...
from now on...
That was the beginning of everything.
For the next month, Etsuko
continued relations with those men.
A time colored scarlet that her
husband knew nothing about.
Against the wishes of her heart, Etsuko
let the passions of her body take over.
Countless times, she tasted ecstasy,
her body entirely enslaved.
But she didn't truly fall until later...
into the bottomless pit of masochistic hell.
Etsuko couldn't believe what
was happening to her body.