Hiiro no Koku
Episode 2
Keep up the good work, Hira-kun.
He really does work hard.
You stayed late last night, too, right?
Uh, yeah.
Because that little daughter of his is so cute.
I hear his wife is a real beauty too.
With two pretty ladies under your wing,
you must want to work extra hard to provide for them.
Work is important, but your wife is also important.
It is a man's job to make his wife feel beautiful.
Uh, yeah.
Did you two forget anything?
Nope. We're fine.
Nope, we're fine.
Did you remember to take some change?
Yes, it's in my wallet.
Emi?
Is your handkerchief in your bag?
We're fine.
Good grief, Etsuko, you're such a worrywart.
Mommy! We're going to draw in class today!
I'm gonna draw a picture of you and Daddy!
And I'll bring it back home!
Oh, Mommy's looking forward to it.
Emi, we'd better get going.
Okay.
Well, we'll be back.
Mommy, bye!
Have a nice day.
Take care.
Looks like the drugs have started working.
Both holes are soaking wet.
You really want it that bad, wifey?
You really like it, huh.
You were lonely, weren't you?
Especially this part of your body.
It's about time to put it in.
You want it so bad you're throbbing, wifey.
That's right.
No, I... I...
"I want it in my asshole", right?
In time, we'll make you forget about everything else.
I guess I'll enter through the front door.
Whoa, she sure sounds like she enjoys it,
when we both thrust into her at the same time.
You're so cute, wifey.
Shake your hips harder.
We'll send you to heaven.
Oops, still too early to cum.
You were about to cum, right?
We've only just started the real show.
It's too soon.
See? See?
Your hole is wide open...
and soaking wet.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Stop it!
What's the big deal?
We're just taking pictures of how wet you are.
Seeing a lens staring at you makes
you even more excited, doesn't it?
Stop it, please!
A month passed...
and my relationship with those men continued.
A time colored scarlet that my
husband knew nothing about.
Despite my heart's intentions, I let my
body take over my consciousness.
Countless times I was given ecstasy,
violated at their hands.
And every time it happened...
inside of me...
the part of me that longed for it grew larger.
I was...
Etsuko. Etsuko!
What's wrong with you?
Sorry.
I was just thinking about something.
You've been acting strange lately.
Is something wrong?
Strange?
Me, strange?
Well, not strange.
It seems like there's something you're not telling me.
Is something troubling you?
No.
That's not it at all.
Well, okay then.
It's just that you don't talk much.
You seem less happy.
And since I've been so busy at work,
I haven't been able to talk to
you much lately, you know?
So I was thinking that we should take
Emi to the zoo this weekend.
How should I put it?
You see, I want to spend more
time together as a family.
Would you like another cup of tea?
Thanks, Etsuko.
Are we going to the zoo?
Emi, it's bedtime.
I want to see the sheep!
But Daddy is too tired.
I don't mind at all.
But, Darling...
Yay!
Both Emi and Etsuko are my precious family.
Let's have fun together, just the three of us.
All right!
Huh?
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you very well.
Today...
Today will be our last day together.
I was afraid you'd say that.
What's wrong, eh?
Hey, hey...
I don't want to betray my husband and daughter.
Please!
Okay.
Hey, are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
But in exchange,
let us have lots of fun today.
Well, I...
You want it to end, right?
Yes, yes, just be a good girl, and it'll all be over soon.
She's pretty right here as always.
It's throbbing,
as though it's saying, "Give it to me quick".
No, I mustn't get caught up in this.
No.
Withstand it!
I...
Why...
Why am I so...
How is it?
Don't you want it now?
Come on, wifey, take a look.
Look over here.
You want it, right?
Put it in deep, okay?
Whoa, awesome.
It went in all at once.
With her hips moving like this...
She want more?
It's sucking me really hard.
You're enjoying this a lot,
yet you say you want this to be the last time?
"But my body won't listen to what my heart says", right?
Just be honest with yourself, wifey.
You like this, don't you?
Once you've tasted it,
you'll never forget it.
Wifey,
don't you want mine too?
She's acting like a horny bitch in heat.
Even if she says she wants to stop,
we won't let that happen so easily.
But she's super crazy, huh.
It was a good idea to bring this along.
Hey, wifey, since this is your last time,
how about we indulge one of your fantasies?
Fantasies?
What kind of play do you like?
I think we already know.
She likes ropes the most.
You wanna be tied up, right?
You're really cute, wifey.
Those ropes suit you well.
Don't you think so?
Yeah. She looks pretty.
Being tied up makes you want it even more,
because you're a masochist.
A masochist...
She said it!
It's something you can't hide even if you want to.
That's for sure.
You're saying you're a masochist down here, wifey.
It's really tight.
You want something in there, right?
But you really do want it in there, right?
Yes, I do.
Wifey, where exactly?
You have to tell us, or we won't know.
My pussy.
You're our bitch.
Our slave.
Yeah, you're just a slave bitch
who spreads her legs for us.
That's right!
I'm your slave.
So please...
More...
Hey, hey, did she cum the moment I put it in?
It's because we increased the tension.
See?
So cute.
She can't stand being tied up.
Once you've discovered you're a masochist,
there's no turning back.
Awesome, wifey. You're great.
Not so... rough, please.
Oh, no. I'm gonna cum.
Before you cum, remember that face.
And think hard about what you're doing right now.
Hey, wifey! You've got a guest.
Oh, your daughter's come home, I see.
Emi...
Mommy...
She looks like you... pretty cute, if you ask me.
Emi-chan, eh?
How old are you right now?
Don't you dare! Keep your hands off my little girl!
I know that, silly.
Emi-chan's still a little too young for this, wifey.
You seem to get a kick out of being watched.
Won't you find this sort of thing addicting?
No! Please forgive me!
No! Let me go!
We're not being mean to your mommy, Emi-chan.
She really likes it.
Hey, untie the ropes so she knows we're not raping her.
Okay.
We'll untie you, wifey.
You need to dear up this
misunderstanding with your daughter.
Right? You want that, right?
Just stop it, please!
How can you say that when you're so wet?
Holding back is bad for your health.
How does it feel to have your daughter watch you?
You can't stand it, can you?
You're super tight.
Just say it, "I'm a masochistic
bitch who loves being raped".
"I'm so happy, I can't stand it".
See, Emi-chan? Your mommy likes it.
I feel it hitting your womb, wifey.
No, all the way inside... all the way inside, please!
What great moaning.
Oh wow, in front of your daughter?
What a whore your mommy is.
Well? You okay with it?
Is it okay if your daughter watches?
Yes!
You're fine with it, after all that?
Then ask for more dick!
More... I want more dick!
Your mommy is very cute.
Harder! Harder!
M-Mess me up!
Careful, wifey. Emi-chan is watching you.
Mess me up!
I can't stop it.
Yes!
Yes...
That was fun, wifey.
It was really awesome and smoking hot.
Oops, almost forgot.
Keep this as a memento.
This is...
You like it?
I think it turned out pretty good.
I wanted to keep it myself, but I'll let you have it.
Yes, just one copy.
All of them...
Give me all of them.
How can you say that?
They're not your property, right?
B-But...
Okay, fine.
If you want them that badly, I can take you
to the person who has the negatives.
The person who has them?
That's right.
This guy said he absolutely needed to have
them, so we sold the pictures to him.
Well? Will you come with us?
Are you sure...
that he'll give me the negatives back?
That's between you and him.
Mommy...
Emi, I'm sorry.
Mommy's going out for a bit.
I'll be back right away, so don't worry.
Come home soon, okay?
Oh, I see now.
You're even more beautiful in person.
Well, I don't want to be rude. Have a seat, Miss.
Thanks.
I enjoyed your photos.
I was surprised...
that someone as beautiful as you would do such things.
The pictures... Could you return the negatives to me?
Yes, I have them here with me.
I find them quite exciting.
They're truly exquisite.
Well then, I'll...
Not so fast.
I paid good money for these.
I can't return them for free.
B-But you can't!
You young ones really had some fun,
and it looked like you enjoyed
having your picture taken.
You shouldn't be ashamed of it.
It's only natural for a woman to lust after men.
Especially a woman like you.
You probably have a special lust.
Now, now, I'm not suggesting you pay me with money.
How about you let me have some fun
with that beautiful body of yours?
I'm sure you wouldn't mind doing that, right?
Then we'll talk.
Or would you rather your
husband bought these pictures back?
Why don't you let me peek under your skirt?
Well, well, very nice indeed.
What a nice view.
Well, why don't you remove your underwear
and slip them into my desk drawer?
You understand, don't you?
I didn't call you up here just for a chat.
I'm sure you envisioned more yourself.
Yes, that's right.
You're a smart lady.
Lately, I've been having lots of fun
buying time with hot wives like you.
Well, well, I'm flattered.
Now spread yourself on top of the photos.
Wow, for someone who's played
around a lot, you sure look clean.
Inside that happy little home, how many
dicks have you buried in there?
If other people found out, you'd be in big trouble, huh.
Or maybe it's an aphrodisiac for you.
Oh? You're still tight.
It seems like you haven't even realized
yet what kind of woman you really are.
Let me show you.
Wow, you're so delicious.
Well, then.
This is nice.
You're really enjoying it for me.
It's quite different when the woman is pretty.
I suppose a young man wouldn't appreciate it,
a fine specimen of womanhood like you.
There are still pleasures unknown
to you, hidden deep in your body.
Pleasure is something that gets better
and better the more you taste of it.
The more you taste, the more you need to be satisfied.
Oh, I can't stand it.
Now I need more.
Well, how do you like it?
It's been a while since my mighty
rod has gotten this big.
It's thanks to you.
Well, then...
Wow, you're in really great shape.
It's like you're hugging my dick.
How is it for you?
Do you like my little friend?
This is the first time you've tasted a real pearl, isn't it?
But it's a waste to use my instrument on an amateur.
Your pussy...
I look forward to the honor of awakening...
the beast within your body.
W-Wow, you're so tight.
It's quite a special treat to see a pretty
woman like you fall from grace.
You really like it that much?
What's wrong?
Are you about to cum?
Then say it.
If you don't say it, I'll stop.
I'm cumming... I'm...
– I'm cumming!
– I can't stand it anymore.
Come on, open wider.
This is all of them, including the
pictures that were just taken.
Are you suspicious because I
handed them over so easily?
Don't worry.
I keep my promises.
Then, I'll be leaving.
Yes, have a safe trip home.
Should I have someone escort you?
No, thanks. I'll be fine.
What are your impressions?
Very nice.
I think an audience would really enjoy her.
Oh? That makes me happy.
Well? What's your expert opinion?
Another month.
Another month?
She'll be ready that quickly?
Yes.
In a month, I'll train her into a woman
who only thinks about sex.
If you say so, then I trust you.
But won't you tell her husband?
I won't tell him.
In time, he'll pay her ransom.
That bitch will earn us some good money.
Hey.
Get Kazu.
You called, sir?
Kazu, leave that woman in our hands.
What are you talking about?
Why do you sound surprised?
She's a real gem, that one,
so we're going to take special care of her.
Weren't you just going to taste her?
Yeah, I was.
But I've changed my mind.
If you understand, then how about you wash my car?
What, are you dissatisfied?
No. Excuse me, sir.
Are you sure that's okay?
Yeah, I don't give a shit.
He's a stupid goon with all his brains in his dick.
Never mind him.
Look forward to our brilliant future.
I wonder what kind of whore she'll
become, under your care.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Daddy!