I fell in love
with you twice.
Memory of Love
We shouldn't be doing this, Yasuda.
A teacher... and his student... shouldn't...
Didn't I tell you before, Tengo?
I may be Yasuda Eriko...
But at the same time, I'm also Kawana Kyoko.
I had no idea that I'd go as far as having
sex with Tengo in a hospital bed.
So the nurses wouldn't find out...
My first...
first...
blowjob.
I was so... excited.
Innocent ~Memories of a Girl~
I'm Kyoko!
Kawana Kyoko.
The ex-girlfriend you lost to illness!
How do you know about this, Yasuda?
What? Urn, well...
I have a past-life memory!
At first, I wasn't that into it.
It happened when I found the diary of the teacher's ex-girlfriend.
September 18th, friday.
Clear skies.
Our first date.
September 19th.
Cloudy.
Our first kiss.
September 20th.
Our first time... having sex.
Sensei's fingers are...
...inside of me.
T-They're twirling around...
Next, his penis will be inside of me.
It's so thick and hard, coming in.
Coming inside!
We were both so stiff that I can't exactly say it went well.
You came right away, didn't you?
But I was so happy.
Hey, Tengo.
Comparing the former me and the current me,
which one feels better?
Lately, for some reason, maybe because of my illness...
I can't write well anymore.
I don't think I can write anymore.
S-Sensei...
I love you.
My diary ends here.
I'm so sorry!
I love you so much!
Her temperature, her pulse, her blood pressure...
Everything is stable.
But, for some reason, she won't wake up.
As long as...
...she's asleep anyway...
Sleeping Beauty
Why don't you just wake up?
Onee-chan, how much longer are you going to keep this up?
Until Dad comes to visit me, of course.
I know the truth!
I know what you do with Shinya-kun!
That's not real love!
Huh? Maybe this is backwards.
Huh?
Shit.
Why won't it fit?
Shit!
I guess I'll just...
If she's this wet...
I had no idea her insides were this tight.
I'm cumming.
Shinya-kun...
My pussy... My insides...
Just by putting it inside...
I also love Shinya-kun.
If Onee-chan doesn't wake up, what will I do?
Truthfully, I hope she never wakes up.