Stop this, Duke. Please, no more. I've had enough.
So, you don't care what happens to the holy lance Gungnir?
Is that right, Aliya?
Odin would be most dismayed to hear that the
weapon he entrusted to you was destroyed.
All right,
just leave Gungnir alone!
I don't like your tone. Open your legs and beg.
Scum!
Come on, beg for it.
Put your cock... I can't! I won't say it!
I think you will.
Now, what is it you want?
Please... put your cock inside me.
That's what I wanted to hear.
What a thrill to hear such filth coming from such a proud warrior.
Good! Cry out with sexual pleasure!
Don't flatter yourself. There's no pleasure in fucking a dog like you.
No? I think you might change your tune...
when I introduce tonight's special guest.
G-Guest?
It's someone you know...
but she's changed a bit.
No fair, Aliya! I want Master's cock, too!
Introducing Black Valkyrie Leia!
Black Valkyrie? Leia, is that really-
Yes, it's me. You're going to love being fucked by Master Duke.
Leia, what are you saying?
Look how hard your nipples are! Don't tell me you don't want it.
Stop it, Leia!
Unbelievable She used to be so refined. And now..
It's no use. The new Leia knows only prurience and lust.
No, this can't be happening!
Leia!
Forgive me, Aliya.
Only Masters cock means anything to me anymore. I'm his slutty slave now!
[Master, Please Forgive This Indecent Servant...]
Ikusa Otome Valkyrie 2: Part 1 [The Fallen Goddesses]
It all started when we were captured by Master Dukes Knights of Darkness.
Demon Clan Battlefront Fortress
Please, kill me.
End my suffering, Duke!
Behold, people!
Witness the end of this battle maiden.
Soon my demonic minions will dominate all of Midgard.
It's time.
Well, if it isn't Aliya... Champion of Heaven
and custodian of Odin's lance, Gungnir.
Aliya, I can't believe it's you!
And I can't believe you were clumsy enough to get into this mess, Leia.
I'm sorry...
Duke!
You've embarrassed this maiden long enough. For that, I'll have your head!
Odin's Valkyries... Always falling from the sky at the most inopportune time.
Most of your minions are dead.
Surrender yourself.
I don't know about that. How about you, Leia?
What?
Aliya, forgive me.
Leia, what are you doing? Let go!
Leia... you...
Champion of Heaven..." Without that ring, you're a common
woman! It's not easy when friends turn on you, is it?
You've betrayed me?
I'm sorry, Aliya. I had to do ft... for the good of the people.
Aliya!
Now is the hour of the Demon Clan!
Kill me! You'll be sorry if you don't.
So defiant. Leia was like you at first, too.
Isn't that right, Leia?
I'm not a traitor like her!
In a moment, your body will understand.
Do it, Leia.
As you wish.
What is the meaning of this?
Master,
permit me to serve you.
Stop, Leia! Do you realize what you're doing?
What? What's happening to me?
It's a magic chastity belt.
It vibrates when Master is sexually excited.
This jokes gone far enough!
No joke. I really am aroused... by the sight of you two wretches.
Filthy cur!
Leia, what is that between your breasts?
What?
Tell me. Show me what a dirty mouth you have.
I can't say... that.
Say it, and I'll make you feel even better.
It's a...
No, Leia! Don't listen to him!
I'm sorry, Aliya. It's a... a phallus!
Aliya...
Aliya... hold on.
If I can make Master climax, the belts should deactivate.
"Phallus?" Certainly you know a dirtier way to say it.
It's...
Oh my God!
It's a cock!
Cock!
COCK!!
I'm cumming!
Aliya, forgive me.
Enough.
Leia...
Now then, let's see what you look like down there.
Duke, you bastard!
No! Don't look!
The goddess had an accident!
Who knew the Champion of Heaven was such a whore?
Don't look, please...
You must be wet enough by now.
No, stop... stop it! It's too big!
What an adorable cunt.
Your pussy is gripping my cock like a hungry mouth!
No, it isn't!
All the way in!
Lord Odin!
Aliya...
Like it? You're finally a woman!
Huh? What are you jabbering about?
Odin, please grant me strength...
How noble. Pious to the very end.
Right, Leia?
Don't look!
I'm sorry, Aliya.
Cry! Scream! I love it! Ill drown you in cum!
Stop! Stop it, please!
Aliya...
Aliya's making Master's cock so big...
No!!
No more!
I'm saving myself for Odin...
Aliya's body... dripping with Master's semen...
M-Master...
You want me to design disciplinary equipment?
You have experience in this department.
Remember the Re-Virginizer?
The LactoBlast Elixir?
The Easy Pee diuretic supplement?
I'd rather forget that last one.
On the contrary, you are to use that experience to develop new equipment.
I suppose I can't say "no," can I?
It's an order.
All right, but-
What?
Are you going to use the new tools on... me?
Didn't I tell you?
The items are for breaking Aliya.
What? For Aliya?
What, you want me to use them on you?
No! I just...
All right, I'll make the items for Aliya.
Master's cock is delicious!
So good... so good!
Let me!
Let me suck it more!
Why put Leia in charge of the disciplinary tool development?
You know how good I am at making nasty things.
Just shut up and watch.
I have a plan.
Please, you mustn't see me like this.
I've been bad. Please punish me.
Stop...
Aliya...
Enough already... get your repulsive dick away from me.
Come on. Don't you like it?
Not in a million years!
You'll have to rub harder.
It won't be over until you make me cum.
What's the point of embarrassing me like this?
Here's the point.
You said you weren't going to put it in!
My chastity belt is vibrating.
Master must be fucking Aliya again.
Yes, keep moving your hips like that.
Shut up! I'm not moving my hips!
Your body betrays your words, Aliya.
Dammit... dammit!
I shouldn't... but I can't help myself... I'm so wet.
Good. Do it harder. My cock and your cunt at the same time.
I'm doing it as hard as I can.
Aliya...
She's making Master feel so good.
My fingers... they won't stop.
I want it... I need his cock in me!
Look. Watch how your pussy swallows my cock.
Shut up!
I won't look!
Get ready to receive my demonic seed!
No, don't! Wait! No... no!!
What's going to happen to me?
I don't want to be corrupted any further.
Why is Duke keeping you alive?
Waste of a room.
What? You don't want to help with Aliya's obedience training anymore?
Please, it might not be too late.
She can still go back to normal.
Take my body instead, and do as you will.
You're prepared to be a slave to my desires?
Y-Yes.
Ouch!
Be honest, Leia. Do you want my cock?
No! As one of Odin's fellow battle maidens, I...
Your body is saying yes.
Take your fingers out of me, please!
If you wish,
I'll give my affection only to you.
That's not what I meant...
So it's all right for me to have other women?
No. I won't let you.
So what you're saying is, you want me all to yourself.
Yes.
I couldn't bear for another woman to have you.
I see. You'd bke me to violate you.
Yes... I want to be violated.
I... I...
Please, play with my pussy.
Duke, I'll give you everything! Be mine, and mine only.
Now I've got you.
What is that?
You've summoned it, Leia. Now you'll be reborn.
What? No... no! Stay away!
Don't come. Stay away!
...But I can't let Aliya have my Master
Filthy battle maiden.
Your miserable human emotions will darken your armor
and transform you into the Black Valkyrie...
just as was foretold.
This body... This armor... This is my true self!
Come, Leia.
As you command, Master.
Thus I was reborn as Black Valkyrie, and became
the sole winner of my Masters favor.
What is this? What's going on?
Look, everyone! Witness our true nature!
Odin's battle maiden Aliya is here for your viewing pleasure.
Have you ever seen Lady Aliya like this?
Leia! What are you trying to do?
It's alright, Aliya. Don't worry.
I just want everyone...
...to see us enjoy ourselves.
Now, Aliya... the fun can begin!
Look at this device I made just for you! Do you like it?
What is this?
It's programmed to teach you obedience.
Stop it.
No! Stop! You can't...
Please... don't look at me!
Lady Aliya!
I never wanted the humans to see me like this...
It's all right, Aliya.
Remember, we're women before battle maidens!
Leia...
Now, let the fun begin!
N-No!
Not that!
No!
No! I can't hold it in!
Lady Aliya!
Lord Odin...
Please forgive me.
It looks like you really like my invention!
No... please... please make it stop!
Stop? But I haven't had my turn yet.
Your "turn"?
What are you talking about?
This seed will grow inside me and enhance my body.
Don't tell me...
Yes! I can feel it growing!
It's hot! My pussy is getting hot!
Oh my God, what just came out of you?
Amazing.
Look how big and thick it is. It's almost scary!
No... I can't...
Get it nice and wet, or I can't put it in you.
Sorry Aliya, I'm going to pop your ass cherry!
Your ass is so tight and warm. It shouldn't be long before I cum!
Oh, my ass... it's so full!
God, it's big! It's ravaging my insides!
Well? Do you like my new dick?
Leia, stop it.
What should I do? I can't...
This doesn't feel... Your cock isn't... No!
It feels good for me, too.
Your ass is like heaven!
That cock... that cock!
Lady Aliya! Lady Aliya!
Aliya!
Oh, Lady Ahya!
I can't... take it...
Your ass is amazing! I'm going to cum, Aliya!
My pussy... my ass... you're tearing them apart! I'm going to cum!
Let us perverted maidens climax together!
Alisya!
Leia, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Cumming!!
Well, it's not every day you see two of Odin's
maidens up to their eyeballs in fuck sauce.
At this rate, the Valkyries are done for.
Is this the "plan" you were talking about?
The eclipse is coming.
Its darkness will mark the beginning of the end for the Valkyries.
Aliya...
Lady Leia! Lady Aliya! Beloved holy Valkyries!
Together, Aliya! Into oblivion!
To Be Continued...