You've sure gotten good at this, Kagido-san.
That's right. Gently lick the back of it.
Yes. That's right.
The foul smell.
The nauseating taste.
I used to hate it so much.
To think that you'd do that sort
of thing in the nurse's office.
If people found out, they'd be shocked.
I can understand seeking a thrill,
but that's going too far.
A good little nerd should never be seen
in such a compromising position.
See? You're holding back, but
your bloomers are all soggy.
Kagido-san, I'm ready to cum.
Taste good?
How could it taste good?
Aw, Kagido-san, you never had good manners.
Please, not that. My butt feels
like it's going to fall off.
No, stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
I want you to be my lover forever.
Says who!?
I hate you!
b37˚C
Binetsukko b37˚C
My Lower, The Asshole
Nice to meet you!
Who's this boy?
He's a distant cousin of Sagimura
Hinako, that girl in our class.
Hinako's cousin?
Yes. I'm Kenji.
I came here today to become
Inuhiko-san's apprentice.
Apprentice? What exactly does that mean?
I want to get a girl to be my
slave, just like Inuhiko-san!
S-S-Slave? Like me?
Not you. I want Hinako-Oneesan.
Hinako?
Yay!
But you're just...
Help me out with this too, okay?
Kenji-kun needs our help.
H-Help?
Thanks for helping!
What the hell? Help him seduce Hinako?
I've got enough problems of my own!
I'm trapped in that asshole's game.
This is just too cruel.
Oh, no. My hand is moving on its own.
He's so mean. He makes me
stop before I'm finished.
I want to be able to finish too!
Oh, no! I can't stop now!
In the end, I'm playing right into his hands.
Here, Kagido-san. It's a beautiful present.
I feel...
just like an animal.
But it feels good. I can't stop myself.
This is... so good...
Oh, no. Why does it have to feel this good?
It's coming. It's coming. It's really coming!
My bed's gonna get wet.
It feels great! Feels great!
It's coming. It's coming. It's coming!
It's coming!
Sometimes it's good to have a spare.
She's fairly deprived.
Wonderful!
The bumps on this thing feel strangely good.
Wow!
I could try it inside my vagina.
Hard! It's so hard!
Completely different from a man!
Who's there?
I wonder what I should tell Hinako?
Hey, Mutsumi!
Hinako!
Wanna come visit today?
My parents aren't gonna be there.
Your parents?
Yup. With them gone, we
can do anything we want!
Uh-oh. This is an extremely dangerous situation, the kind they want.
Sorry, but I can't today.
What did you say?
You mustn't turn this down. It's a great chance!
If you turn it down, there'll be trouble.
That secret-thing might be revealed to everyone.
I think you catch my drift, right?
Welcome home, Hinako-Oneechan!
Oh, Ken-chan, you're visiting today?
Mutsumi, this is Kenji.
Nice to meet you.
This is my super-best friend,
Kagido Mutsumi-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Make yourselves comfortable.
I'm gonna get something to drink.
Okay.
Hey, kid. Are you really planning
on having sex with Hinako?
Y-Yeah.
I decided I'd give up my virginity
to Hinako-Oneechan.
Why does it have to be Hinako?
Choose someone else!
But Inuhiko-san told me...
that I should make my favorite girl my slave.
That stupid asshole. What's he trying to do?
Mutsumi-Oneesan, you'll help me, won't you?
If you don't help me, I'll tell Inuhiko-san on you.
Here, as promised. I want you to
slip this to Hinako-Oneechan.
Wh-What's this?
The same tactic... that he used.
This kid is going to do exactly the
same thing Inuhiko did to me.
For some reason...
I've gotten really sleepy.
H-Hinako, don't push it. Go ahead and take a nap.
Yeah. Good idea.
Hinako, I'm so sorry.
I really am sorry.
I really can't do this.
I have to stop him.
It smells just like her!
Okay, all ready!
Now I finally get to see it.
Hinako-Oneechan's special place.
What a cute pink color!
It tastes like pee.
Hinako-Oneechan. This is my penis.
Just like Inuhiko-san said.
Feels great.
Hinako-Oneechan, I'll give it to you.
My hottest thing.
Hinako-Oneechan...
Onee-chan... Onee-chan...
O-Onee-chan...
Wh-What?
Wh-What's going on?
Hinako-Oneechan.
I've decided to make you my woman.
Wh-What are you saying?
Untie me right now!
But I can't.
The ceremony to make you my slave begins now.
C-Ceremony?
Here I go, Onee-chan.
Stop it, Ken-chan!
I don't want to lose my virginity to you!
Don't worry! I'm a virgin too,
so it should be all right.
That's not the issue.
No!
Stop it!
That hurts!
Just a little further, Onee-chan. Hang in there.
Ouch! Ken-chan, that hurts!
Calm down, Onee-chan.
Wow.
There's no way I can go in there now.
I can't stop him now.
There's no way around it. She's being raped.
She can't move at all
And the kiss prevents her from talking.
Disgusting.
What a disgusting scene.
Stop it! We can't do this, Ken-chan!
You can't do this to me!
Stop it!
You're hurting me!
Are you about to cum?
I'm about to cum, I think.
I'm really big, aren't I? Does it feel good?
What are you saying? It does not feel good!
No! It hurts!
P-Please!
I get it. You're big. So take it out. It hurts!
No! Stop it!
It's hitting my womb. I can feel it. Stop it.
My back is breaking.
I'm cumming. I-I'm cumming!
Not done yet.
Ta-da!
I'm going to make you feel even better!
Super
Pleasure
Strong
What the hell is that?
This stuff I got from Inuhiko-san
will make you wetter.
I'll make you scream for more.
No! Stop doing weird stuff to me!
Don't worry. It will feel really good.
And there's a special clasp on it, so I don't
have to take it off when I pull out.
I'm not letting you do this! No!
That boy...
He looks so innocent. How can he do that?
He's even worse than Inuhiko.
Hinako is so wet.
She's getting it really hard.
Looks like it's proceeding well.
Wow, she's all messed up.
Where did you come from?
Be quiet.
Kagido-san, you'd better check this out.
Kagido-san, your face says, "I want dick".
Come on. If you're not quick, I'm putting it away.
N-No. I want it!
Wow, Kagido-san! You're sucking really strongly!
I had no idea you wanted it that bad.
I did want it. I really did want it.
Even though I used to hate it.
It's smelly, gross, and ugly. So why?
Why does it taste this good?
Oh well, I guess I'll help you cum a little.
No! No! Please, don't swirl it around!
My insides are getting torn up!
It's inside... It's inside my womb!
When it goes in that far, you really
can't hold back anymore.
I'll swirl your insides around
even more, Onee-chan.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming again!
With this thing on, I think you
can cum multiple times.
Oh, no!
Oh, please...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, too!
Don't! Don't, Ken-chan! Please
don't spill into my womb!
No!! I don't want... I don't want to have a baby!!
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum!
Hinako-Oneechan, your womb got
a good shot of my semen, didn't it?
It's in there.
There's so much hot stuff swimming around
in the deepest part of my body!
It feels great, doesn't it, Onee-chan?
Ken-chan...
Apparently that went well.
I'd better get going.
Don't go.
I want...
I want to have the same experience as Hinako.
What?
Do it to me too.
Just like Hinako.
Didn't you feel differently before?
I want it for real!
What are you saying, Kagido-san?
You should only have sex with
someone you really love.
So until you love me, we'll have to stop here.
We're not going all the way.
Aw, Ken-chan.
Onee-chan, will you lick my fingers clean?
Sure I will.
Ditching class to come up here was a good idea.
It's great not to have anyone around.
Listen...
How much longer are you going to play with me?
Didn't I tell you?
Until you fall in love with me.
But I hate you!
I hate everything about you!
But... But you see...
For some reason, the me that's down there...
doesn't agree with that!
You're right. You're already wet.
It sucks, but that's reality.
I understand.
No, you don't!
Ta-da!
This is what you wanted, right?
Th-That's amazing.
If you do it like that, I'm gonna
cum too soon, Kagido-san.
No, please don't. Don't cum yet.
Why not?
Just because...
Hey...
Why can't I cum yet?
B-Because... I want you to put it in down there.
And where exactly is "down there"?
Stop teasing me.
I'm not teasing you.
I just want to make sure I
understand you correctly.
I'd hate to make a mistake.
I want it where you haven't put it in before.
Is that so? A place I haven't put it in before?
In that case, can you give me a good pose?
Hurry...
Hurry, put it in quick.
Here, take this.
What's that for?
We wouldn't want someone to hear you.
You're really ready for this, aren't you?
You're already throbbing down there.
I'm kind of scared it won't feel right.
Then I'll just come in fast.
Wait. Don't. This isn't right.
Isn't right? But you said you wanted
it where it hasn't been before.
I did say that, but I didn't mean that.
How is it, Kagido-san?
How does it feel "where it hasn't been before"?
Seems like it's doing something.
No, that's not what I wanted.
Well, then I'll make it feel even stronger.
My butt... My butt is...
How's this, Kagido-san?
No! I didn't want...
Kagido-san...
why don't you try moving it how you like it?
Come on, Kagido-san, try harder.
The bumps... The bumps are rubbing
against the inside of my butt.
Oh, well. I guess I'll have to move it for you.
Ow. That hurts! I'm finished!
This is great. Your butt feels so wonderful!
I'm about to cum.
Not yet! There's one more place you haven't put it!
Please, just at the end, can you put it in my pussy?
K-Kagido-san?
I'm tired of holding back for you!
Really?
I want you. I want you real bad.
Wait, slower. And be gentle.
Here I come, Kagido-san.
Oh no, not so fast!
I'm gonna put it deep inside of you!
I...
Kagido-san, what is it?
It's okay. Whirl it around inside
as much as you want.
I'm cumming inside of you.
That's fine. Cum!
Hey...
That picture...
You don't have to give it back.
I think being your slave isn't so bad after all.
Kagido-san!
I am...
a slave.