I'm Kagido Mutsumi.
Everyone thinks I'm a sophisticated,
smart, top student.
I'm about to cum, Kagido-san.
But I'm constantly with a stupid
pervert who thinks only of sex.
That's a good girl. Don't drink it all at once.
Take time to taste it.
Okay.
And now, I've become his love slave.
b37˚C
Binetsukko b37˚C
Would You Like Something Hot?
Hang in there, Mutsumi. You can do it!
Fight it, Mutsumi!
Only three more laps!
Don't make me run. It'll dribble
down my legs too fast.
I'm trying to prevent anyone from noticing.
It's no use.
I want to touch it. I want to rub it.
Huh? Hinako?
It's no good! I can't hold out anymore!
This feels great!
No! Hinako!
Not out here!
This feels great! I finally got it!
Great! This is great!
I wanted to do this with my fingers!
Wow, Hinako-Oneechan, that's amazing!
There's so much fluid coming out!
Things are amazing on my end, too!
Those two sure had a hard time hanging on.
Hey, Kenji-kun? Shall we make
them feel even better?
Okay, Master Inuhiko!
Target, power-up!
This... This can't be happening!
It's strong! It's too strong!
I'm gonna pee!
It's coming!
Did we go too far?
They won't be able to go to
their next class like this.
Oh, well.
Then for sixth period, I guess we'll
give them a special lesson.
Okay, Master!
First, step one.
No! Don't do it!
Oops.
Hey, don't move.
These are really sharp.
If you move, I might cut your special place.
Okay.
The coldness of the scissors is chilling.
I'm scared! Please, don't cut my special place!
Got it.
It's shaped like a heart!
What about you, Kenji-kun?
I thought this might look good.
That's very artistic.
What do we do about the undies
under their PE shorts?
You do this...
and then...
this!
She's all wet.
Okay, me too!
Y-You cut them.
Good. Now you slowly pull it out.
It's out.
Mine came out too.
And then, you gently twirl the
clitoris with your fingers.
Okay!
Yes! Ken-chan...
After it firms up, stroke it and press it.
Okay!
Wow!
No!
Do you feel it, Onee-chan?
Yes! It feels great!
And next is the butthole.
No, wait.
I can't wait.
Look, it's in, it's in.
I'll provide you an even better time.
You've got her clitoris and her anus.
I wanna try it too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
No! I'm cumming too!
We made them cum with just our fingers.
Yeah. They're very good girls.
We'd better reward them.
Here's your snack, Kagido-san.
Smelly!
Is it too smelly?
I thought a little smell would be good.
I hate this smell.
But it's no use. I want it!
Should I lick it?
Don't you like it? Shall we stop?
No! Let me touch it!
Me too!
Wow! She's come to suck me on her own!
They want it so bad that they can't hold back.
It's no good. My mouth is sucking on its own.
Ken-chan... Ken-chan, you're delicious!
I can't get this hard, thick thing out of my mind.
I can't help but suck on it.
Ken-chan, I want you. I want
to drink your white milk!
No, Onee-chan, don't suck too hard.
I'm gonna cum!
You want it now too, don't you?
See? You're so wet.
Well? What do you want?
Dick...
I want your dick.
No, not like that. I can't reach it from here.
Well, we have a decision to make first.
Which hole do you want my dick in?
Well, I...
Come on, you have to tell me.
Oh, no.
My mouth is about to speak for me.
It's no use!
My... hole.
Well said.
It's in! It's in at last!
Yes! Swirl it around more!
Onee-chan, you like it?
It feels wonderful!
What about it feels wonderful?
You have to speak more loudly.
Deep inside...
Deep inside feels great.
You really like it that deep?
You're really crazy, you know,
you perverted Onee-chan!
Perverted?
I'm a pervert?
I'm having sex with a distant cousin.
I really am a pervert!
No! Why did you have to say that!?
I'm cumming! Here I cum!
All right, say ah.
Yummy. Kenji's milk is so yummy.
I don't care if I'm a pervert.
That was good, perverted Onee-chan.
Kenji-kun.
Let me show you something good.
This asshole has run around the
school more than anyone else's.
No, stop it!
Well, Kenji-kun? Do you see something?
It's kinda dark. I can't really see.
Then stick your lingers in there and spread it out.
Okay.
Do you see something?
Um...
Stop it!
There's some brown stuff in there, right?
Now that you mention it,
something's stuck up there.
What the hell? I don't believe this!
Let me clean it out for you!
Please stop it! I'll do anything you say, just stop it!
Kenji-kun, how does that taste?
Um, it's sweet and salty and a little bit bitter.
Kagido-san, I wonder what that tastes like?
Come on, answer me.
I won't tell anyone. Come on.
You know what I'm getting at, right? Just say it.
Don't you want to feel even more ecstasy?
It's good.
It tastes very good.
Well said. Time for your reward.
It's hitting... It's hitting me all the way inside!
Ken-chan.
Onee-chan?
See? Your insides are throbbing.
Do you know why? Kagido-san...
I know! I know why!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, Ken-chan, I'm cumming!
It's coming. It's coming deep inside to tickle me.
I'm cumming!
Ken-chan!
I remember it.
I remember this taste!
Kagido-san.
Kagido-san, you're a top student, after all.
And you did very well.
Onee-chan, you also did very
well in your special class.
Ken-chan, I love you.
I love your milk.
Master sure is amazing!
That's why we invited you guys to the hot springs,
to celebrate us becoming a couple.
Right, Onee-chan?
Ken-chan, where do you think you're touching?
It also feels great in the hot springs.
We shouldn't...
Ken-chan...
Oh, no!
Mutsumi-Oneesan?
Where did he go?
He said he was going to see an old friend.
An old friend?
He says she's a housewife who
lives in his neighborhood.
I know it's you. I know you're the
one who's always peeping on me.
But if you give me a good time,
I won't tell anyone about it.
Wh-What should I...
So, you're wondering what you should do?
What's that?
It's a must for the solo traveler.
I'll show you something even better.
Hurry! Hold it down with your hands!
Okay!
That's good. Hold it firm!
W-Wow.
Well? Wouldn't you like to get inside me?
Yes!
Well, you can't!
So? How does it feel to be teased?
You know, it's become a recent
trend with housewives.
Making a young boy like you
into your own personal pet.
You're so cute. You're twitching,
trying to hold yourself back.
Well? Wouldn't you like to have a woman like me?
Yes!
Very well. Then show me yours.
Show me how you do it.
Okay.
That's good. Stroke it harder!
You always did that while you were peeping on me.
Right.
I love this!
Can I cum now?
Yes, you can.
Shoot it out as hard as you can!
A young man's semen is delicious.
Don't cry, Mutsumi.
But I've put up with so much
from him all this time!
Mutsumi...
Onee-chan!
Let me comfort Mutsumi-Oneesan.
You're already revived again.
There's a young man for you.
Hey! Don't take the lead!
But it's trembling with loneliness.
Hey, stop it! Don't do anything
without my permission!
Stop it!
What was that? I couldn't hear.
Stop it.
That's no good.
Aren't you having fun? Do you want me to stop?
No!
No, what? Clarify yourself.
No. Don't stop.
Liars must be punished.
Ken-chan?
It's okay, right? You guys are best friends, after all.
H-Hina...
See? She said fine!
Just pretend I'm Inuhiko-san and have fun!
Come on!
Ken-chan!
Onee-san.
Okay, Onee-san, I'm putting it in.
Make way.
I can't do it.
What's wrong? Don't you want it?
It's not right.
B-But...
I can't betray him.
Alter all, I'm his slave.
Onee-san...
Good for you, Kagido-san.
It's not what you think!
We haven't done anything yet. It's true!
I know.
You really resisted well.
I'd expect nothing less of my lover.
Hey, Inuhiko-san, who's that woman?
Oh, this? She's my new slave.
I'm just punishing her right now.
Come on. In.
Come on.
Where did he run off to?
My penis.
A deprived housewife caught him.
Oh, poor thing.
Okay, well, I'll console it.
I want to lick it too.
I want to suck it.
You mean this?
You can lick it if you want.
Please! Let me get closer.
Ask me nicely.
I beg of you. Please let me suck you!
Hey, that's not fair! Don't hog it!
Hey, Kenji-kun, wanna try teaming up?
Let's enslave this housewife together.
I'm so happy!
You'll finally put it inside me! Make it quick!
Hurry up!
Kenji-kun.
Okay!
Hurry up!
Hurry what?
Put it in fast! I'm sick of all this teasing!
Oh well, she really doesn't have good
manners, this wrinkly old woman.
Wrinkly old woman, you say?
That's right.
You should be thankful that young men
like us are willing to be your partners.
Ken-chan...
Shall we have some fun too?
Let me join in.
This condom feels really good.
No! That's the wrong hole! Stop it!
Well? How does double penetration feel?
Irresistible, isn't it?
Inside me... the two dicks... are filling me up.
I'm jealous! How dare he put
it in someone besides me!
How dare he!
Mutsumi... I'm cumming!
Come on!
Cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Here. It's young semen.
Wrinkled old lady.
That tickles, Onee-chan!
Don't complain, Ken-chan!
You promised me you'd clean it well.
What's our problem? You
had fun back there, right?
This time... it's my turn.
No, you don't. I'm going to use him again.
Well, well, girls, calm down.
I could get used to this.
Really? Then I'll wash it every day from now on.
I'm so happy! I guess I only need one slave after all.
Ken-chan! I'm so happy!
You stupid wrinkled old lady!
At least my technique is better than yours!
Now, now, you're both my slaves, alter all.
You'd better get along.