"Personality" and "memory" are what makes humans
human. If there was a means to link flesh with
machine, it would be that sort of "programming".
LOVE MACHINE
Animaid Whore Model #23
Did you bring your ID card?
This... This is perfect!
It feels wonderful.
I can't hold back.
You... You look so sad right now.
I...
It's here.
I don't think that reaction is a problem.
I'm sure I've seen... this man somewhere before.
You're getting wetter and wetter.
What a naughty body.
No!
Because you're acting so shamefully,
you must be nearly there.
My fingers fit into you perfectly.
Deep inside, I... I feel as though I'm tingling.
Harder! Harder! Come deeper into me!
Wow! My body is melting!
I'm about to cum.
Please cum.
Don't laugh at me for saying something stupid.
What do you want to say?
I think I might have actually fallen in love with you.
Love, you say?
I'll always love you, Mary.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Who... am I?
It feels good to be cleaned.
Then this hole next.
It might sting a little.
Hey, do you think a Love Machine
like me could love another?
I want to respond to his feelings.
Mary's feelings must've awakened.
Even though she's an android.
Even though she's a machine.
Oh, very nice. I feel you getting deeper and deeper.
You're so pretty, Ms. President.
You're the ideal woman.
Further. Come in further.
Very well.
I see. That's very interesting.
If you put it eveiything into the machine
and make it do the work for us,
very little of the responsibility would fall onto us.
But I'm still worried about Model 23's reactions.
It seems as though she's really confused
about something a customer said.
Well, as the founder of an android
company, I can't have that.
She's just a machine.
Even the words she speaks were programmed by you.
Yes, you're right.
Rather than that, there's something
else you need to be careful about.
What is it?
A policeman came by today.
He asked a lot of questions about you.
In the worst case scenario, I don't want
you giving the company a bad name.
You understand what I mean, right?
Occupation: freelance writer.
Annual salary: 5,200 pons.
He doesn't earn enough to afford a Love Machine.
Is he trying to capture a hidden part of Mary?
Yes? Johansen speaking.
Ah, is that you, Kuroki-san?
What's wrong?
Is there an emergency or something?
Anyway, I'll send you the data as soon as I can.
In the meantime, get a security team on it at once.
Model 23 is headed for his apartment as we speak.
I see. I admit, they do look alike.
But their names and ages are different.
He's an evil man who's destroyed
fifteen machines in tne past!
It will be too late if we wait for him to strike!
At least do what you can. Search through his
paperwork with us, and try to find out for sure!
I can't do something that intrusive.
Why not?
Without any proof that they might be the same person,
I have no authority to violate his privacy.
But, sir!
Just follow orders.
She may have been your wife in the past,
but now she's a machine who belongs to the company.
Do you understand?
Kuroki-san?
Hello?
Hello? Hel...
Johansen speaking. We have a
small, unanticipated problem.
Keep up like that.
Just like that. Just like that.
What's the matter?
You're usually more gentle.
Does a machine have a right to complain to a human?
You were such a unique machine.
I thought I'd be able to treat you differently.
But I suppose it's futile.
Futile, you say?
You know, I get tired of it.
Normal sex, that is.
Wh-What is that?
You just wait and see.
Shit.
You taste good.
Hey, annoying pig-bitch.
I'll make it so you can't open that noisy mouth again.
So this customer is into S&M.
We'll have to give her special maintenance later.
Sir.
You really are a well made machine.
I appreciate that.
You don't like it?
That's fine with me.
If you're enjoying it, I'll enjoy it less.
I don't think this should hurt.
Since you're a machine, after all.
Even if you break, I can always get you fixed.
Though I don't have money for that.
Shit!
Howard speaking!
The machine that's with him is the
one you're concerned about?
Yes.
Putting something so thick into
your front hole for so long...
...will really make this sting, I guess.
It won't take much to make me cum at this rate.
You sound like you're in agony.
How interesting.
Even though your face looks pained,
it seems like your lower half is enjoying it.
Come on, get more slippery and wet down there!
Maybe I went too far.
I guess I did.
Even though you're a machine,
I still can't be too rough.
Or you'll break...
She won't be able to take it!
Sir!
Don't worry. I've already made arrangements.
Yes? This is the observation deck.
Sir, the police are here, apparently.
What? The police?
There doesn't seem to be
a link between him and Ford.
We still need to find out whether
Johansen knows where he is.
Who is this?
It's me! Johansen!
Don't use your name.
I can recognize your voice.
We have a problem.
One of our employees is trying to steal
one of our malfunctioning machines!
It's a long shot, but if her memory returns,
she could bring down our company!
Hello? Are you listening to me?
That one, eh? She was a good woman.
Don't you understand the gravity of the situation?
Nothing to worry about.
Nothing to woriy about?
Just leave this to me.
Why don't you go fuck that
female president some more?
What's wrong? Broken already?
What a cheap toy.
You know what? If you're bored with
a toy, it's kind of fun to break it.
It's the last fun I can squeeze out of you.
Let go of Mary!
Don't do it!
Stop it, you two!
Mary! Don't you realize what a scumbag this man is?
He doesn't love you.
It was all a lie!
Who the fuck are you?
One of your stalkers?
No, he isn't!
That man is... my...
Say... What happens if I kill a human?
I've always wanted to try that.
I had no idea such an opportunity
would fall into my lap.
You're an unknown violent intruder in my house.
Anyone would agree I killed you in self-defense.
Mary!
Mary...
Hitting a human? That wasn't in your programming.
Wh-What's... What-s happening to me?
M-Mary?
She must still be near.
Search for her.
This is a complete analysis of all the data in Model 23.
The man who invaded the customer's
apartment was a cleaner who'd been fired.
The man called Ford was also taken care of.
All we need to do is to give the police
a good story, and we're clean.
Our company has done nothing immoral or illegal.
Understood?
Doctor Johansen?
Yes.
With this, you'll be my slave for life.
You understand, right, Johansen?
Howard speaking.
We've received a report that a client of one of our
androids has been attacked in his own apartment.
The culprit is still near the scene.
Please report at once to investigate.
Yes? Kurozawa speaking.
We have more details on the apartment break-in.
The intruder is a former cleaner for
the company: Kuroki Shuu. Age 30.
He has escaped with the android
he was assigned to clean.
We found many bodies throughout the
apartment building. They'd all been shot.
The intruder is likely armed.
Be careful.
Everything will be all right.
Don't worry.
The company will handle everything.
None of the blame will fall on us.
There they are!
Can you run?
Anyway, we need to get past them,
then get back to the company
and explain everything to the police.
Understand?
Yes.
So this is where the intruder ran off to?
Yes, we had a tip-off.
He sure chose a horrible place to hide.
Don't worry.
We'll stay hidden here for a while.
Okay.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry, Mary.
It's my fault this happened to you.
I didn't have the courage to face your death.
Mary?
Does it look good?
Yes, it does.
Yes? Kuroki speaking.
Oh, the pleasure is all mine.
What? Now?
Yes. I'll be there right away.
Huh?
That's strange.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Huh? Really?
Mary?
You're Shuu?
Are you Shuu?
Mary, did your memories...
This ring was... a present from me.
Mary!
I'm glad.
This is for the best.
You belong to me.
You belong only to me.
Mary...
Shuu...
I've waited for this day for years.
For this day to come.
Yes! Very nice!
My body... is filled!
Me too.
So hot!
So hot and tingly!
Deeper! Deeper, please!
Okay.
Shuu... you're deep... hitting deep!
Mary.
Amazing! My body is melting!
Mary... We'll be together forever. Okay?
This... This is perfect! I can't hold back.
I'm cumming.
Yes. Cum, please.
I love you, Mary.
I'll love only you forever.
And you?
Me?
Say it, Mary.
Say you love me.
Please.
D-Do you have a reservation?
In that case, do you have your ID card?
Do you have your ID card?
Your card... Do you have your ID card?
Your card... Your card... Do you have your card?
Do you have your card?
Don't you hear something?
I do.
Do you have your ID card?
Mary, thank you.
Shuu... From now on, we'll be together forever.