Hey, Shuji, how about that one?
I don't know... Would it fit you?
You don't think so?
Well, just take it easy and look around everywhere.
You're right... I'll do that.
Today is my first date with Shuji in a long while.
I don't know if it's because he's studying so hard,
but he's been a bit sullen lately.
Still, he came to hang out with me nevertheless! And so...
Is something wrong?
Just a friend asked me suddenly to buy something for her.
I'm sorry, but could you wait for me here?
Sure, okay. I'll wait for you here. Go get it done.
Yeah, thank you!
I'll be back as soon as possible.
No way, that again?
The girl who gets turned on by shady otaku 3: Slave to Semen
FAKKU! Presents
He got jealous of Shuji, so he wants to hear my dirty voice...
He's eavesdropping on me somehow.
I must do what he says... I can't make the stalker angry.
The inside of my pussy is tingling...
I want to be seen!
I've been found out!
He sees that I'm playing with my pussy in this shop in broad daylight!
He sees that I'm masturbating!
So embarrassing! It's embarrassing how wet my pussy is!
But I... can't stop... my fingers...
I can't... I'm embarrassed I can't keep my voice in...
Public masturbation is so embarrassing...
Why does something so dirty feel so good?
I'm really a pervert... A filthy, hopeless pervert.
I'm such a pervert...
Look...
Look at the dripping hole of this bitch!
I'm so embarrassed... Public masturbation is so embarrassing!
My dripping pussy is embarrassing too...
But the more embarrassing it is, the better it feels.
Look! Look at me!
Look! Look at my dirty self!
I'm so embarrassed... My head feels weird...
Sorry... But I can't stop!
I can't stop playing with my dirty pussy!
If you take pictures, it'll feel even better!
Masturbating... like this... feels so great!
My pussy is dripping...
I'm terrible... I'm a terrible pervert...
Look at my perverted pussy!
My pussy... I can't stop playing with it!
Look at me!
They're looking at how my pussy is turned on all the way to my womb!
Look at my pussy, look into it!
I'm the only one who can protect Saki...
I'm the only one, Mizuhara Shuji!
The stalker contacted me a number of times since then.
We had a number of such "dates".
I started to like it, and I was led to a world of pleasures.
I'm sorry, Shuji. My friend called me again...
But as an apology, I'll make a dinner as good as your cooking!
I knew.
What?
That you're stalked and raped by some pervert.
I knew and I couldn't help you.
Why... Why do you...
He told me himself.
He showed me the video too.
I didn't know how he may abuse you if I threw a fuss.
I couldn't do anything!
I want to do something, Saki.
We're lovers, aren't we? Let's return to how we were before!
Are you... sure I'm good enough for you?
You're you, Saki.
My dear Saki hasn't changed at all.
I was bound to Shuji already,
but though my heart was happy,
my body wasn't satisfied.
Thanks for your hard work, Saki.
You were really pervy yesterday too. I was totally turned on.
Let's have a date again.
I want to face you and love each other.
He wants to face me...?
Let's just decide where to meet.
I'll be waiting for you. I'd be so happy if you came.
But if you don't want to, I might have to split up with you.
I'll throw away all my memories of you as well.
I'd be so happy if you...
I might have to split up...
throw away all my memories...
What does this mean?! What does he mean by "split up"?
He would do nothing to me?
I must go... I don't want to be thrown away...
After all those wonderful lessons...
Ah, here she is!
We've been waiting for you, Saki!
Why do you know my name?
Everyone knows here. We're all your fans.
Fan? What do you mean?
You're so hot! Let's undress you!
Amazing boobs! I want to grope them!
Her nipples are so beautiful too!
Don't look at me!
But you like to be looked at, don't you?
You came so wild masturbating on that video...
That was really something.
But I... I only came here because I didn't want to be abandoned...
Welcome, Saki! I'm so happy you came.
What's going on here?
I really enjoyed this whole thing.
I was happy that you turned into such a perverted slut.
But it's over today.
It's over? But I'm here...
I won't contact you anymore, so just let those people treat you.
Do your best, okay? See you!
What? What does he mean by "see you"?
I betrayed Shuji and chose him...
He threw me away because I betrayed Shuji?
I was thrown away?
You don't have to feel so down. We'll treat you well.
Yeah, yeah!
Really? You'll really treat me well?
Of course, leave it to us! It will be the best feeling of your life.
Then... Then... Please!
I'll do my best, I'll serve you all!
So please mess me up totally!
Rape me please! Please!
Please rape me to pieces!
I can't go on! I'm so turned on!
Then...
First drink this, Saki.
What?
It tastes weird...
We got this funny drug, you know.
Funny drug?
What's this? I'll burst!
Amazing!
She got a double dose after all.
Won't she just pass out right away?
My nipples and my clit are going crazy!
Look how it swelled up!
Just look!
What's happening to my nipples and my clit?
It's the effect of the drug.
And this... isn't just getting bigger.
It hurts! I must play with myself!
You're dozen times more sensitive now.
I must play with my ass... my pussy... Let go of my hand!
The drug is all over her body now.
Too bad, I can't let go of your hand.
Then you do it! I'll go crazy if I can't touch my pussy!
Would just playing with it be enough? Don't you want this instead?
A cock! Put your cock in me!
My pussy wants a cock in it so badly!
I'm a filthy, perverted pig!
I'll go crazy if you don't put your cock in me!
My pig pussy wants to suck on your cock!
Can she go any lower than this?
I'll stick it into you then as hard as I can.
Cum as much as you want.
Yessir! I'll cum with your cock in me!
My filthy pussy is in heat!
The cock's in me!
She came from just putting yours in.
You count how many times you cum!
Or I'll have to pull out.
I'm cumming... Please turn me inside out with your cock!
You don't need to say it.
It's in me!
Your thick cock is moving in me!
It feels too good, by pussy's going crazy!
I'm cumming again...
Your cock is so deep in me!
You can cum as much as you want, just count how many times!
Third... This is my pussy's third now!
I'm cumming!
Don't hope I'll hold back just becuase you're cumming!
I'm still cumming... If you're doing it so wild I'll cum again!
Fourth turn now!
You don't want to leave these out...
My nipples!
You're doing it to harsh, it hurts! But great!
I can't take anymore!
You're doing it so wild!
My nipples... Tease my nipples more!
My womb... I can feel the cock at my womb!
If you keep on I'll cum again... Again...
My pussy came again!
This is tough, it's so tough!
Don't! It feels too good, don't touch it!
I'm cumming... again... and again...
I forgot to count... I'm cumming again!
Oh no... I'm turned inside out by perverts!
My clit is teased too!
My ass... A cock is attacking my ass!
These cocks are going wild... too wild in me, it's too much!
They're so thick!
It feels so amazing!
The cocks are attacking my pussy and my ass in turns!
I'm coming again! I'm coming so much that I'll die!
It tastes so good!
My ass! My pussy!
I'm filled with semen!
I'm coming!
Come on, don't you get exhausted just yet!
You really did great, Saki! Well done, well done!
What's going on?!
You'll have to satisfy all those people from now!
You really have to do your best!
I'll break if you fill me so much!
You wanted to be broken, didn't you?
Be honest with yourself, Saki.
You should treat them all well.
Tell them to mess you up totally!
Hey guys!
From now, please, rape me as much as you want!
It doesn't matter which hole you use, so hammer me with your cocks!