Are you scared?
You're so cute.
Megumi...
Do something for me too, Megumi.
Yes, lick it.
When you do that, I...
Lots is coming out.
Is this... are you...
a man?
I'm not a man.
Well, I'm not a woman either.
We're a lifeform that fails to fall into those two categories.
To use your words, we are...
God.
Your jewel will be mine.
What's the color of your flower that I'm drawing out with pleasure?
Fabulous.
What clear brilliance.
What vivid color.
You have a taintless heart.
Did they find me?
That's as far as you go, evil goddess.
Break!
I can't let them catch me.
There it is.
Open!
Give her the jewel back.
Who the hell are you?
Guess I have no choice.
I wonder if your jewel can take the pleasure I'll give you.
Fabulous.
What's going on?
Show me what you really look like.
What's your name?
I don't have to tell my enemies my name.
Adorable.
I'm not giving it to you.
Guess I have no choice.
I'm Natsumi.
Natsumi Jinno.
This is my duty.
I wonder what your jewel's color is.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Thank you.
This is how it should be.
Your pure heart is yours alone.
Who are you?
Where is Lapis?
Lapis?
Is that her name?
Lapis...
won't be coming anymore.
Why?
Because she did something horrible to you.
I don't believe that!
She'd never do something bad.
She tried to steal something important from you.
No!
I gave it to her!
I gave her all I had!
You did.
That was all an illusion, though.
Forget all of it.
I gave it to her!
I gave her all I had!
Good work, Natsumi.
Reiko!
You were in battle, I think.
Did you get the human's jewel back?
Yes. I gave it back to the owner.
The evil goddess ran away.
I see.
We have to stay low for a while now.
You got the jewel from her.
Her name was Lapis, you say?
Lapis...
Lately they've started to act more often, haven't they?
I just know they're scheming something!
Mei...
Did you notice something, Mei?
Not really.
But we have to prepare.
I don't want to be ambushed.
You're right.
You always have to be on your guard.
Natsumi, if you find them,
take their jewels without mercy.
I'm a bit depressed.
It feels like we are going against our own people.
We goddesses have our home on a different planet.
We are guardians sent here from God's planet.
The evil goddesses try to flee from their exile on this tainted, vice-ridden planet,
and it is our duty to keep them from returning.
The evil goddesses gather the jewels that they steal from mankind when their personality crystallizes.
They are trying to use them to reactivate a spaceship hidden in hyperspace.
With it they can make their way back to their home and ours, God's planet.
That's the only way.
They have to activate the Sun Ship.
So, Luudi, what's Lapis' condition?
She lost her jewel and is comatose.
It will take 2000 years to regrow it.
What about the Goddess who did it to her?
She has disappeared.
She is masquerading as a human, I expect.
I see.
Have your fangs gone dull too, Lyktaito?
Mistress Jirokon, your orders.
What kind of orders would you like, Luudi?
"Avenge Lapis."
It's not our goal to wage war on the goddesses.
Rather, we are trying to gather jewels.
I object!
I do not wish to lose more friends than we already have.
Do you hate me so badly?
Do you have a chance to win?
Mistress Jirokon!
Make sure you succeed.
That's my condition for letting you go.
I will.
I won't forgive her.
I won't forgive the Goddess that put you in this state!
Lapis... Lapis...
Lapis...
Share your heart and your strength with me!
What's wrong, Reiko?
I felt the force wave when a consciousness crystallized.
A jewel is developing nearby.
Oh, no.
I only drove them back hours ago.
Are there others?
Start trailing it immediately.
Can you help me with this, Reiko?
Sorry.
Huh? Was there someone here?
I'm going there!
Natsumi hasn't recovered yet, has she?
Will I lose her too?
If it is a sin to love someone...
then this cosmos is born of sin.
If that's how it is,
then I would rather not be burdened with the knowledge.
I will avenge Lapis!
This is for Lapis!
You are stirring up the beast in me.
Your jewel is mine!
Don't fight it.
This is fabulous.
My power seems so very vast.
I can feel your jewel through your flesh.
My power...
Show me yourself in the depth of lust.
What a huge flower.
It is just right for the awakening of the Sun Ship.
The Sun Ship?
Don't.
Anything but that.
I won't lose to you.
No!
Don't look at me!
Fabulous.
Can you feel it?
I'm about to come too.
Fabulous.
You are simply fabulous.
I'll give this back.
Natsumi.
I'm fine.
I recovered the jewel.
That's great!
I'm coming there to end it.
Don't let her escape.
I will.
It worked!
That wasn't a human's jewel.
That was one of our jewels. One of an evil goddess.
It is the crystal... of my little sister Sapphire.
Our jewels are pure poison for the soul of a goddess.
You will either keep your pure soul and suffer for all eternity,
or you will turn into what we are and fall to evil.
What?
What happened to her wings?
Natsumi!
I won't let you get away.
Mei!
Look after Natsumi for me!
I'm going to chase her too!
Sorry, let me borrow this.
Jeez!
Natsumi!
Natsumi, what happened to your wing?
Don't get closer!
No!
You did something unnecessary.
What?
You've disrupted our plans.
You won't get my jewel.
I don't have to rob it.
It's always been mine.
What?
What are you doing?
What is this?
S-Stop it!
You bastard!
Who are you?
What are you doing, Natsumi?
I'm sorry, Mei.
I forgot.
What happened?
I... I...
Don't, Natsumi!
Stop it.
Goddesses are forbidden from uniting.
I can't stop... I can't stop...
I'm sorry.
Don't!
Any more than this and we as Goddesses will...
Natsumi!
I'm not a Goddess anymore.
M... Meiko...
I'll lend you a hand.
Come.
Natsumi.
Soon.
What is this...
Meiko, what is this?
Keep this from the mothership.
But...
Finally...
The day of the awakening has come.
Has the time come?
I won't give up here!