What?
Should we go home for today?
Chinatsu
Summer is close.
What?
Well, um, Can I?
I don't care!
She's wet...
She wants it too, right?
I'll get dry...
Can I really?
Ouch!
Are you all right?
Of course I am!
I want to kiss...
What?
Nothing...
The sunset's so beautiful.
Her name is Aoba Chinatsu.
We're pretty much in a relationship now.
Hey, I'm Sahara Satoshi. I'll be sitting next to you.
Nice to meet you.
Did I do something wrong?
The first impression was the worst impression.
Hey, Aoba!
But still, I talked to her every now and then hoping we'd get along better.
Um, could I see your textbook too?
Thanks.
And when I got used to spending my days like that...
What did you just say?
I said...
I said I want you to go out with me.
What? You don't want to?
No, that's not it!
One day she suddenly confessed to me!
Her kissing gotten amazing!
What?
No, I just...
She's dripping wet.
Um, you don't have to...
You want it?
No, I'm really happy!
Then why not?
I'm almost there!
You're fine with it?
I'm putting it in.
Aoba...
Aoba, I love you so much.
We've been going out only for a short while now,
but I've never seen her smile so far.
On the contrary...
She's getting moodier every day.
Oh It's nothing. Nothing at all.
I mean it's one thing to be cold,
but when she looks at me like that, my confidence evaporates.
Does she really love me?
Like, she tried going out with me,
but I was below her expectations,
but she asked me out so she can't back out...
Or something like that.
Damn, that might be it!
Hey! Hey, listening?
What?
We're already at my house.
Oh right! Then see you tomorrow!
Um, wanna come in for a little?
Um... Chiaki, right?
What is it?
Chinatsu's been in a great mood lately!
So this is why!
She's smiling at home?
No.
But she furrows her eyebrows and looks angry a lot, right?
She's actually holding back a smile because she's happy.
The more she makes that face the happer she is!
She's a really shy girl!
I see...
So she was happy!
Yeah!
Your sister went out somewhere?
Yeah, it's her calligraphy class today.
I see.
So she was actually having fun?
But the happier she is the more she makes that face?
That's beyond shy...
What are you staring at?
So she was just shy about being happy?
Really?
What? So suddenly...
I thought we should continue where we left off.
You don't want to?
That's not it.
She's not angry, right? I hope.
Your boobs are so beautiful.
They're just big... nothing more.
She's just happy again?
No, it's not just the size, the shape and the touch is great as well.
Can I just continue like this?
And they're heavy and soft, and warm...
Stop...
And the way they fit in my hands, it feels amazing!
I really love them.
It feels like she's relaxed...
No.
But she furrows her eyebrows and looks angry a lot, right?
She's actually holding back a smile because she's happy.
The more she makes that face the happer she is!
She's a really shy girl!
I didn't realize that until now, but now that she told me...
Your face is really cute when you're enjoying it.
Don't say weird stuff, stupid!
Hey, don't try to hide!
What's weird? That she's cute?
No!
But still...
Stupid!
I want to see this face more.
Hey, why...
It's okay, it'll be fine!
She's back to the usual.
I did it!
She's so cute!
Your boobs really feel amazing!
Don't just play with them like that!
You're really so cute!
Her expression melted.
Look how hard your nipples are!
Your voice is cute too when you're enjoying it!
Aoba...
Your mouth feels really... really good!
I'm cumming!
Aoba, you're so cute...
Stupid!
You caught me off guard with taking it in your mouth so suddenly.
I thought you'd be happy if I did.
There are strings of juice...
Don't say that!
Wow, it's dripping wet already!
Don't stare!
You're like this just from your boobs...
Shut up, stupid!
You're so cute!
Aoba, I'm putting it in.
Are you okay?
I think I just came.
You just made an amazingly cute face!
Stupid!
It's true! You're really cute!
But I'm...
No...
I don't want you to see my ugly face!
That's not true!
Your face is amazingly cute when you're enjoying it.
It's not weird? Really?
Yeah. I love it.
I love you and your flushed face.
Show me your cute face more!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Satoshi... I love you!
You were so cute before!
Why are you making that face again?
Shut up! This is normal for me!
You could show me more of your honest face.
Shut up! Shut up!
What?
But this face is really cute as well.
Huh, what's wrong?
Let me see your face.
Shut up!
Aoba!
This is normal for me!