Yamato...
No, Yamato...
If you put it all in, my pussy will break.
Yamato!
It... It feels so good.
I-It's going inside!
Yamato's cock is so big.
It's so deep inside of me.
Harder, fuck me harder!
N-No...
My pussy's going to break.
I'm so happy...
Please don't stop.
Yamato, you're amazing.
You're so amazing!
Your cock is so deep inside me.
I-It feels so good.
Please, fuck me more.
More!
Y-You're cumming, right?
Please, give me your big load.
Yamato!
Tachibana-kun, please fuck me too.
I want it... I want it so bad.
So big!
More... Please give me more.
I want it too.
Please give me more.
Please fuck me as much as you like with your huge cock, Yamato.
Very well, but you're never to disobey me again.
I'll make you a slave to pleasure.
You and your children.
I want it so bad.
Amazing!
I-It's so good.
Tachibana-kun, please fuck us too.
Amazing. It's so good!
W-Wonderful!
So good!
Please... Please, fuck me harder.
Yamato, don't stop!