Word came so very suddenly.
The prince I was arranged to marry suddenly passed away.
Thus, I was to remain here at the castle.
I held on to memories of that night, and the days passed as though it never happened.
Alois also began to count on me like he used to.
I tried to convince myself to think nothing of it, but...
Alois!
Brother! Oh, Brother!
Alois...
My body... cannot forget that night we shared.
Night after night, I remember when we made love and my body burns and aches.
Who is it? Who goes there?
'Tis I, princess.
Mother!
It appears as though you cannot forget about Alois, hmm?
Do you recognize this, Eifa?
It's the potion I gave you before.
Drink once more, and return to him and relive your night of pleasure.
However, this potion is slightly different than the previous one.
You must first drink all the contents, then place your lips on his.
And then, just like before...
My body... feels like it's on fire!
WANDERING LUSTFUL LUNATICS
FAKKU! Presents
Finally, the time has come.
I can banish those siblings from this castle.
I've been waiting for this ever since I married the King.
This land will be mine at last!
Oh Eifa, you've become so very wet...
Every night you pleasure yourself to thoughts of your brother.
Such a naughty girl you are, Eifa. I've got just the thing...
This is a device for punishing naughty girls.
You simply insert it into your filthy hole...
whenever you body throbs from thoughts of him, this squirms inside you.
No! Please... don't
Sorry Eifa, but this is your punishment.
When you think of Alois it squirms about, becoming unbearable.
Now stand up, and hold onto it tightly.
I'll help you put this on.
With this, you can no longer indulge in your carnal desires.
You'll stay that way as long as you don't have this key Eifa.
But Mother, I don't want this!
No dear Eifa, I can't remove it now.
Don't! If you grope them like that, my body will begin throbbing again!
Once you're feeling it again that thing inside you will start moving, and you'll feel good Eifa.
And the only one who can remove it is your brother Alois.
You must beg him to yourself.
Eifa, you will kiss Alois before long.
Now, let us end this.
First, I'll have some fun with you two.
They will relive that night of forbidden love...
Who's there?
My body! I can't move!
You're awake, Alois?
Before you see Eifa,
I'm going to have some fun with you.
Feels good?
I guess it's about time. Would you like to see Eifa?
Come in Eifa.
Eifa...
Brother, forgive me.
I'll teach you kids all kinds things...
Just stand there and watch, okay Eifa?
Eifa's been constantly teasing herself, unable to forget that night, Alois.
Has she really?
You haven't been able to forget about it either, have you Alois?
What are you doing over there, Eifa?
I can't bear it, Mother.
Oh Eifa, you just can't help playing with yourself, can you?
No Eifa. Endure it.
Please, I beg you!
Oh very well then.
You want this, right?
Your little sister was being punished for not being able to stop doing naughty things.
Allow me to relieve you now, Eifa.
Look at this; this is what's been moving inside you.
Now Prince, be thorough with your tongue.
You've been wanting this for so long, haven't you?
Eifa, now let's lick his penis.
Just like that, give it a try.
Like this?
Make sure to lick around it too, he'll love it.
It's twitching...
It's twitching as it goes inside...
That's right! You'll be able to do this real soon.
Well Prince? Doesn't it feel great?
Your sister will have her turn real soon.
Alois, me as well... do me now...
Men love it when you're even more rough.
Alois, does it really feel that good?
You're so mean. I'm... I'm so much more...
Oh my. Jealous, are we? Just a little longer.
Shall we switch, Eifa?
Alois
Alois, I've wanted this so badly
Brother, you're so big!
Oh my, you're dirty assholes in plain view.
If you do that now, I'll-
It feels so good!
Now I'll play with these.
So good!
Eifa! Eifa!
I knew I had to forget, but I couldn't, Eifa.
I don't want to let go of you again!
Brother! I don't want to let go either!
I understand how you two feel. I'll grant you your wish.
Do it inside! Come inside me, Alois!
Brother! It so hot!
There's another hole women can use to please a man, Eifa.
Another hole?
That's right; using this right here.
Eifa, lick it and get it nice and slippery.
Brother's thing can go in here too...
See? Look how wide it opens!
If you tease your pussy like this, your ass tightens up. It's even better if you move more intensely!
Go on, touch it. It's completely soaked, isn't it?
Even your asshole can get wet like this.
My ass is starting to feel good!
Now let's pleasure him together.
Does it feel good, Alois?
Oh my, how lewd. You're twitching, Eifa.
Tired already Eifa? Let's try something different then.
This will let you experience the same pleasure Alois does.
Alois...
It's just like a man's penis. Doesn't rubbing it feel nice?
What is this? I've never felt this before.
I suppose you could compare it to teasing your clitoris.
See for yourself.
This is just like Brother's...
It feels strange.
Yes, just like that.
It can even ejaculate like a real penis too.
So good!
How does it feel to be pleasured inside and out at the same time?
I-it's amazing!
What is this feeling? It's so strange...
It's growing!
Oh no, this feeling!
I'm cumming!
Now it's finally time to use that asshole of yours.
Alois! Don't tease it!
So this... is how your ass feels?
I feel so good! My ass! My penis too!
I'm cumming again!
Well then, time for the finishing touch.
No! Stop it!
Get away!
Help me!
Brother's penis is touching mine... Oh god!
Brother, I'm going to-
Me too, Eifa!
Cumming!
Enjoy it to your hearts' content.
Your last night...
Alois...
Eifa...
Do you regret this?
Not a bit. Memories of tonight, of being held in your arms, will surely give me strength to keep living.
INEXCUSABLE!
Once, there was a beautiful princess named Eifa.
She loved her brother ever so much.
But one day she drank a potion from an evil witch.
This potion's effects drove them mad with passion, and they were found by the King.
In his rage, the King placed a curse upon them.
The two were never to see each other again.
Alois by the Sun
and Eifa by the Moon
thus their wandering began.
Waar - Does anyone even read these?
ACF - ...and that's why I love Lilith. I'm honored to sub their work, and I plan to do more soon.
__ar - ^_____^ KAWAII DESU NEE UGUU~
Sindalf - The abuse of greatness is when it disjoins remorse from power
TehMikuruSlave - TMS was here, Jacob is a fag