Hospital?
Yeah. I'll have an operation, so I won't be able to come to school for a while.
What sickness is it? Will you be all right?
Sorry, I can't really talk about the details.
But I'll be back for sure.
I see.
I'll be lonely.
You helped me a lot since I became a girl.
I think there'll be a lot of stuff I won't know...
What's with all this biology stuff?
It hurts!
I'll be back soon.
The story of how Takumi Swapped gender and Fucks a lot
Since then guys were fucking me in every free moment.
More and more of them every day.
I was totally messed up.
Melon bread...
Eat it.
They are all perverts, so it started going into weirder and weirder directions.
I tried hard to keep up with them.
But I was crazy about sex.
I lived like that for a month.
It feels like the smell of cum soaked into me, and I couldn't get rid of it.
Every day I get on the same train... Meet the same groper.
And enjoy my way to school every day.
I can't hold back... Put it in like you always do!
Should we go to a hotel?
Sogahara isn't here... I have no reason to be careful...
I should just do what I want.
Okay, I get it.
There I was fucking an old man I didn't even know.
I knew there was nothing ahead...
You're cute! You're really cute!
Come on... Don't say stuff like that...
Amazing... I feel like I'm melting!
I'm cumming! I'll pour my semen into you!
Semen! Semen!
I'll fill you with semen!
It's good, right? It feels great, right?
Semen! Semen! It feels great!
You're really cute.
Should we go on a trip together?
A trip?
I'll call some of my friends and rent an inn for ourselves.
We'll eat, drink, have baths and fuck all the time.
Sounds good, doesn't it?
I'm already past the point of no return.
Let me introduce our special guest!
Such a beauty!
So many old men!
I'm his new girl, Takumi.
You're all here because she wanted to meet you.
I'll show you my special dance.
Here.
Here!
Clap the rhythm!
You should use this too!
This here!
This feels so lame! Just imaging myself looking as I do now...
And I'm already about to cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Great!
Yeah, just what I like!
Show us more interesting arts!
This is wonderful!
Where should we start eating?
Beautiful!
That's not it!
Let's use your sauces.
Don't...
This feels great!
Have you ever heard about the "Lady Booze"?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
She's cumming!
Does it feel good?
It... feels... amazing!
It's different from the guys of your age, right?
It is totally different... your tongue-tech is amazing!
It's about time to stick in your pride!
Just the thought... is making me wet!
So tight! Young pussies forever!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Takumi, I like it from the behind!
Your cock is so curved...
I'm cumming again...
I'm about to cum...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Strike a pose now that you got cummed into!
That's it!
You're overdoing it.
You shouldn't engage in wild sexual acts before it stabilizes.
What stabilizes?
What? You didn't realize?
You're pregnant.
Pregnant? There's a baby in me?
It's been five months since I got pregnant.
I got used to it.
They just called out to me, I'd get in the car of men I didn't know.
I know very well what it means.
Hey, I'm Takumi! Nice to meet you!
It's quite big, isn't it?
It must be hard to walk too.
Well, kind of.
But when I think of meeting you, this much is nothing!
You're so cute.
Takumi, you're really good at anal too!
Your boyfriend likes to make his cock dirty too, doesn't he?
I don't have... a boyfriend...
You don't have a boyfriend yet you're really good at anal...
You must be a lewd girl.
Does your ass feel so good?
It does... My ass feels good...
I love to get it in the ass!
You're such a nasty girl.
But it feels good!
Oh my, oh my, you shitty bitch.
I'm not a bitch.
What?
Sorry... I love cock like a bitch!
You look really cute.
You're really into fucking, aren't you.
I'll dump lots of cum into your ass as a sign of my thanks.
Don't cum inside...
What are you saying?
I know you like it. Should I stop?
Don't stop!
I lied! Cum inside! Cum in my ass!
What should I do?
I don't feel like it anymore.
No! Don't stop!
Put it in! Please!
I'm about to cum! Mess me up!
Let's stop here for today.
You'll get a double load next time.
Quick... Please!
I'll pay you, just put it in!
Cum in me!
You'd pay me?
Well then.
It feels so warm inside...
Manga cafe
That felt amazing.
But now I'm just a whore.
I should think this through.
I got an invitation.
Amazing! Is it a hotel suite?
It's amazing!
It's this hotel's most expensive room!
Come in, it's open.
Excuse me, it's Takumi!
You're...
It's been a while. You're really Takumi!
Sogahara! Are you out of the hospital?
What's going on?
Your belly looks big. How many months?
I... didn't want you to see this.
Why did you call me?
I saw your site, and I think I get what's going on.
I called you as a customer.
Customer?
We're both girls! Kind of.
It's okay. Does that really matter?
Well, it kind of does...
Or did you get addicted to the taste of men, and you can only enjoy that?
Your panties are so bold! You're lewd.
You're already wet, Takumi.
Are you... leaking cum from your ass?
You reek of cum.
You had anal with someone before coming here, didn't you?
Well... can't we just skip that part?
No! Open your mouth, stick out your tongue... Let's kiss.
She's different from the guys...
Her tongue is smaller, her lips feel so soft...
So girlish!
It's embarrassing...
Do you mind it?
That's not it... Just you were the girl I always fancied...
So I don't know what should I do...
I wanted to do this all along, Takumi.
I want to have sex with you!
You had sex a bunch of times, didn't you?
Well, I'm still a virgin.
Sogahara... What happened to you?
Do you like it? I got gene terapy from that doctor.
I can produce semen as well.
It was hard ever since I came here to wait for you! It was difficult to endure!
I can't hold back!
Wait, that's...
It's too big!
It's in! My virgin cock is in you now, Takumi!
I'll let the semen I held back inside you!
Your pussy is so warm, it feels great!
Takumi, I'll start moving...
It feels like she's turning me inside out!
It feels great to have you squeeze me!
Takumi! When I put it in, semen sprays from your ass!
Amazing! Nothing felt this good before!
You're so lewd! Your whole body smells of semen!
Do you like cocks that much?
Sorry...
I love... I love cocks!
I'm a pervert, right?
I think I'm the only one who can truly love a pervert like you!
I'll... I'll become your woman, Sogahara!
So stay with me! Never leave me alone!
Make me go crazy with your giant cock every day!
You only follow your urges!
Takumi, you're squeezing so hard!
My cock is all the way in!
Amazing... Your pussy feels... amazing, Takumi!
I love... I love you! I love you!
I'm cumming! I'll spill my semen into your pussy!
Do it! Fill me with... stinky cum!
Give me lots of semen in my pussy!
This is the first time... I love... I love you!
Sogahara, I love you!
Let's do it again.
It was the second spring after I turned into a girl.
Such a quiet baby. He doesn't resemble either of his parents.
That's what's cute about him!
Have you decided his name?
Ryosuke. Takumi decided it.
In retrospect, I could've done stuff differently.
If I did this then... If he was there then...
But there is only one life fit for me.
I'm happy I became a girl in the end!