This bastard!
A molester!
So stupid.
He doesn't know I'm on the karate team.
Okay! If he comes any closer, I'll teach him a good lesson!
Now!
How did you like that, molester?
That was quite a nice elbow punch.
Too bad I blocked it.
Such a tomboy. I'll need to punish you.
I can't believe this!
Help! A molester! A molester!
How dare he!
Horrible!
Get off at the next station! I'll hand you over to the station staff!
I wonder.
I have this, you see.
What's that?
A molester licence!
Hey, stop! Stop!
Help! He's molesting me!
He's molesting me! Help!
Why? Why are they ignoring me?
Deal with it.
No one can interrupt me as long as I have my molester licence.
Molester licence? What's that even?!
As you can see, no one's coming to help you.
Also, you've gotten a lot more sensitive, haven't you?
N-Not at... at all...
Shall we test it?
Don't reveal my boobs in the train!
Don't push me so hard!
How's it? You're enjoying even this, aren't you?
Not at all!
Why... Why are my hard nipples so sensitive?
It's not normal!
Look at yourself in the glass!
What kind of a face are you making?
I'm making such a lewd face...
How can I get turned on from this?
No! Don't touch me there!
Please, don't!
I don't want a molester to touch me at my important spot!
No! Don't touch me!
Don't do it so hard!
Stop!
No! Stop!
No way!
Don't rub me so hard!
I'm so wet!
I don't wanna enjoy being molested?
Stop!
Don't touch me so deep!
Don't... Don't touch me!
Very well. It's time.
No way!
I told you: it's your punishment.
No! Don't! Stop!
Stop? Should I really stop?
Don't you remember what I told you?
You can't control your body anymore.
No... That's not true...
Please stop!
I'm not enjoying...
Aren't you?
No! Stop!
But it's so wet and inviting here.
No! Don't!
No way!
Stop! Pull it out!
It hurts! Please! It hurts!
This's your first time?
It hurts more if you try to resist.
Stop! You're so cruel!
I can't believe a molester took my virginity here!
It's so thick...
Your cock's so hard it's breaking me!
Stop!
Why... Why am I enjoying this?
It feels good! I'm enjoying it!
I'm feeling weird...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Very well, good girl.
Let's do it wilder then.
No! Please don't!
Please, just stop it!
I'm feeling so weird!
No!
Please!
Stop!
No!
I can't believe I got raped here...
So cruel... So cruel...
Stop... Please stop...
Let me go, please!
No, stop!
Someone! Someone, help!
Please, help!
Why? No way...
Deal with it. No one's coming to help you.
Why? Why's this--
No!
It hurts... It stinks...
My throat hurts...
I'm about to throw up...
He's using me as some masturbation tool...
I don't want this!
My head's going dizzy...
Okay, let's fill your mouth with my juice!
No! Please, don't!
Don't cum in my mouth!
Very well, good girl.
Let me give you some pleasure next.
What? What are you going to do?
Please, just stop!
Please, let me be!
I'll make you cum until you go crazy.
What's that?
It's... shaking so hard...
Stop! Stop!
Don't do that to my nipple!
I can't bear it!
Don't give up just yet. I haven't even started.
Oh look, aren't you wet?
No way...
Not there! No!
Don't lift my leg--
You already cummed? It feels that good?
Not at all...
It's not good...
Stop, please!
Stop, don't do it so hard!
I'm feeling weird!
Please stop! I cummed! I cummed!
Stop!
It's weird...
I can't stop cumming...
It comes again and again in waves...
Stop, please!
Then I'll make you cum wild last.
No!
Stop, please!
I'm cumming!
Stop! Leave my butt alone!
I'm cumming again! So many times!
Then how about this?
No! I'm cumming again!
I'm peeing... I can't stop it...
I'm an adult and yet...
You enjoyed it so much you wet yourself?
Did it feel that good?
You... You can't get away with this...
Oh yes I can.
I have a licence to molest.
A licence... to molest?
Thank you for taking the Second Central Liner.
Next is--
Mr Passenger, please stop that!
What's going on?
Whoa!
What's wrong? You're enjoying it?
No! I'm not!
Stop!
Passengers are watching!
Stop this!
And yet, your nipples are already rock hard.
No! Stop!
Whoa!
The train driver's really enjoying it!
Stop already!
Why are you doing--
No!
No! Take your hand off me!
Please!
Don't put your finger in me!
If you do it so wild, I'm... I'm gonna...
Stop!
Let them see it too.
No! Don't look, please!
Don't spread me!
They can see in me!
Aren't you about to cum?
No! I don't wanna cum!
I don't wanna cum!
Don't look at me!
Aoi!
Homura!
Oh no! Don't look at me!
I'm cumming...
Aoi...
She's... amazing...
What are you doing?
Don't do anything weird to me!
I must punish train drivers who do nasty stuff on duty.
What's that?
Stop!
Don't open my butt!
Don't do that! Stop!
What are you injecting into me?!
Stop! Don't put something weird in my butt!
No! It's weird! Stop it!
Aoi...
Are they gonna do the same to her as me?
But by the looks of it, she might get something even wilder...
My tummy... My tummy feels weird!
It's agonizing!
I can't hold it back!
Then how about a little help?
No, don't!
It's so hard!
It's moving!
It's stimulating...
I can't...
Okay, then I'll pull it out.
Don't! Don't pull it out!
It'll get even worse!
Aoi, your voice...
It's so erotic... and cute...
No, please stop!
Anything but that!
I'm still a virgin! Please!
What are you talking about? Just look at your little sister.
Homura?!
They're in me!
They're in my pussy and butt!
It's amazing!
Two cocks are in me at once!
It's great! Do it more!
Mess me up!
Suck my... Suck my tits!
Lick them! Wilder!
It's great! It's great!
Homura...
The molester licence has quite an effect.
She's like that after I took her just once.
You raped her?!
And you too!
It hurts! It hurts!
Wait! Don't move!
You're breaking me!
No!
She says that, yet his cock's in her to the shaft.
Look at your sister's pussy!
It's just like yours!
Whoa!
First time I see your pussy close!
It's so cute!
Homura, don't!
Homura!
Aoi... Do it to me...
Homura... Your pussy...
It's so pretty pink...
It's great! Aoi, it's great!
I love you!
Sis! Sis!
Lick my pussy!
Lick my pussy more!
And impale me from the back too!
I'm going crazy!
It's so great!
I love anal!
Aoi, would you rather forget about what happened today?
I can erase all of this using my molester licence.
Can you really do that?
Of course. If you'll become my sex slaves.
Sex slaves?!
You don't have to if you don't want to.
The less people know about it the better.
Wait!
Okay.
Homura...
What, Sis?
Did we do the right thing?
Yeah... We didn't have much of a choice anyway.
True, but will Takako be alright?
She's a quite slow person, so I'm a bit worried.
That's true... I'm a bit worried about sis Takako too.
But I think Takako's really tasty too...
Well then Mihashi, we'll be leaving ahead.
Please take care of the rest.
Sure, see you!
This is weird.
He's molesting women in the public, yet no one stops him!
His name was Sawanagare, right?
There should be something on the net...
Since he did that to me in the train...
I shouldn't be doing this in the office...
No... I'm cumming already!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!