Science Room
Um...
Hey, Jun...
This Sunday's your birthday, right?
Do you want to come to my place?
Unsweet.
Women who came to like being stolen away.
Female teacher: Kurose Katsuko.
Sign: Kurose
Sunday
Okay, Jun. Do it.
Um, Teach... You know, this is my... first...
So... I don't know how good I...
Don't worry, Jun.
It's my first time too.
So, Jun...
Let's both see it through.
Teach...
Come on, Jun.
Jun...
Jun!
Your body...
Jun...
is so soft...
This is so embarrassing.
I want to put it in you, Teach.
Okay.
Do it, Jun.
But...
Jun, put this on, please.
Sorry, but if we don't use this, I might get pregnant.
Do it.
Teach...
Sorry, Teach!
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Jun...
But...
I'm okay.
Just go on.
Teach...
This is my first itme too, so be gentle, okay?
Okay!
Jun!
Teach!
This feels good!
It does, Teach!
I'm so happy...
Does this feel good, Teach?
Yeah, even though it hurts a bit because it's my first time.
If you feel good, then it's all good.
Teach...
Teach!
Jun...
It's okay, Jun.
Do it harder if you want to.
I love you, Teach!
I love you too, Jun!
Jun! Jun!
Teach!
I'm gonna come!
Okay, Jun!
Teach!
Jun!
I became one with you, Jun.
I'm so happy.
It really was your first time, Teach.
I must be a failure as a teacher if I sleep with my students.
Absolutely not!
I was the one who confessed to you.
I was happy, too.
I've thought of you as different from the other students too.
It made me happy I could give my first time to you.
Teach...
All right. Let's celebrate your birthday properly.
Happy birthday, Jun.
This still feels like a dream to me.
Oh please, Jun.
You're always so strict at school.
Now look at us.
You're famous for being strict.
I only hit students when there's a reason.
Seems like only Kazuya gets hit.
It's shallow people like him I can't stand.
Hey... want to do it again?
No...
It hurts a little...
Then I'll just take a look.
But that's embarrassing.
Please.
But not for long.
You said you only wanted to look!
Stop, Jun!
You're pretty wet, Teach.
Stop!
Your pussy says otherwise.
You're tightening up around my fingers.
I can't pull them out.
Stop, Jun!
No!
Stop!
Jun!
That's enough!
What about tomorrow?
How about it?
Okay, okay.
I love you, Teach.
I love you too.
Monday
Science Room
That's a strange sound.
Stop...
I can't stop.
You idiot... it's lunch break...
Ain't that Katsuko and Jun?
We can't do it here.
What if somebody sees us?
You're so wet, Teach.
Stop, Jun!
No... Stop...
I'm gonna put it in, okay?
Get a grip!
Fine!
I'm sorry, Jun.
But this is my first love.
I don't know what to do either.
Hey Katsuko.
Shinohara!
What went down here?
Be quiet.
Call me by my last name.
You're being impolite.
I wanna touch your butt too, y'know?
I'll call you parents tomorrow.
Look forward to it.
Found summin' nice.
How will about the fate of this woman this time?
The translation of this title is "How will about the fate of this woman this time?".
You look like you've had an argument with your girlfriend, Jun.
Not really.
Jun looks upset.
Look at her ass and tits, Jun.
That's some A-tier shit right there.
We're in class, Kazuya.
I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna confess to her after classes.
Dream on.
We'll see, man.
Wanna find out?
Whatever.
Ms. Kurose!
Sorry about this morning!
I've heard your apology.
Now get out.
I hate shallow students like you.
Oh, come on. Don't be so hard on me.
I've got something serious to say.
Don't be ridiculous.
Listen.
It looks like one of the students is in love with you.
Please.
I found a cell phone in the science room.
That's Jun's.
I looked at whats on it and found out.
By the way, the name of the student is...
Me! Shinohara Kazuya!
How's it? Properly excited?
Enough of the bullshit. Want me to expose it all?
You two look like you haven't gone too far.
Seemed like you had an argument in the science room too.
He saw us!
He didn't respond when I told him I'd come here and confess to you.
Jun, but...
You bastard!
I'm serious! I love you!
What?
Stop this madness!
You're committing a crime, Shinohara!
Come on, think about what it means to be a teacher.
Isn't it a real bad idea to do it with your students?
Don't sweat it.
This'll let it work between you and Jun.
For Jun...
You just have to let this pass.
Jun would want this too.
Just think of me as a sex friend.
Right, Ms. Kurose?
All right! Open your mouth!
It's so different from when I was with Jun.
I'm afraid.
No!
Don't put it in!
Wow, Teach.
Fucking your mouth is awesome.
Fucking my... mouth?
I'll give you a good taste of my cock.
What's this taste?
It's salty and its making my throat wet.
I don't like this.
Your mouth is like some toy made to pleasure me right now.
A toy?
Don't fuck with me.
I can't... breathe...
Hey, gotta do something in return.
You're wetter than an otter's pocket, Teach.
You got damn excited from sucking my cock.
Your pussy is really swollen.
You're kind of a slut, Teach.
Come on, don't stop!
I'm coming!
This is the taste of semen.
It's sticky and tastes of fish and hot like fire.
No!
Take it out!
Take it out now!
No!
You're really resisting.
You'll come to like it.
You asshole!
Huh? You're not a virgin!
Still pretty tense.
You really are a slut.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're a slut, Teach.
It hurts. It hurts.
Am I the second?
Let's reshape that pussy to suit me!
This is what hurts.
Stop, Shinohara.
Stop!
Please stop...
You came!
Enjoyed that?
It just hurt!
Get off me!
You're a cold one.
I love you, you know.
I only love Jun!
I just have to make you fall in love with my cock, then!
No!
Please!
Stop!
I won't stop until you say you love my cock!
Like I would!
I cum quickly, but I've got a lot of charges.
Your pussy feels great, Katsuko!
Don't call me that!
How pitiful that I could enjoy someone like him.
Now I can reach all the way inside!
What's this tingling?
Found your weakness!
This is... different...
No!
You're fucking soggy down here.
The sound is amazing, Teach.
No...
I'm not enjoying this...
I'd never enjoy it with someone like him.
No, no.
I can't think straight...
I'm scared.
I don't want this.
Looks like I'm outta condoms.
I... can't...
You really enjoyed that last one, huh?
Who knows what'd happen if I fucked you a twelfth time.
I didn't enjoy... this...
You're pissing on your bed, Teach.
I wouldn't tell anybody what happened here.
I'm sorry, Jun.
I'll come again tomorrow in return.
I love Jun.
See you, Katsuko.
Jun...
Self-study
Katsuko said she's out with a cold today.
Tuesday
Seems like it.
By the way, this is yours, right?
Yeah! It's mine!
I found it in the locker room.
Thanks, man.
Be more careful.
I'm sorry, Jun.
Why did this...
He's going to do it again.
Guess that's another condom gone.
You really like it now, but you've got to work on your attitude to please Jun.
Men like it when the girls say they like it too, even if it's a lie.
A lie?
Yeah, acting like it.
Pretending is enough.
Let's try it out.
I've got no condom anymore, though.
Don't be—
Not like that.
Say it yourself.
Show my newbie pussy the raw sex.
Look at my wet pussy.
I can't wait to have your unprotected cock teach me.
Is this your first time without a condom?
Yes. It is.
I want it.
What?
That. Inside me.
Tell me plain you want me, Teach.
No, no.
I want that.
Do you want this cock?
I want it! I want your cock!
No, no!
What am I saying?
Do you like my unprotected cock?
I like it.
No...
I can't get in as far without a condom.
Do you like it?
I like it.
No.
I like your cock.
Your cock...
I can feel it.
It's so hot.
Am I just accepting this?
My cock is kissing your womb!
Do you like it?
I like... kiss... cock...
Kiss... cock...
Kiss...
See, you can do it.
No, stop.
No...
You're one slutty teacher...
I'm a slutty teacher...
You're moving on your own, see?
Don't you feel any shame?
Sorry...
But I can't stop...
I can't stop...
Yep, you've got to say it like I told you to.
My hips are moving on their own.
It feels so good.
All right. Say it, Teach.
No.
Come now...
I...
You?
My...
Your pussy and my cock?
My pussy loves your cock!
So?
So fuck me more with your cock!
Very good.
You did it!
I'm gonna get you pregnant now. Ain't that nice, Teach?
Just pretend!
No, I don't want to be pregnant.
I'm going to get married.
Then let's marry.
Don't joke about that.
Here's my kiss!
Put your legs around me so the chance to get you pregnant is higher!
I'll marry Ju—
I know he can get me pregnant.
That's fine. Just act!
Come on!
Act...
Put all your semen inside my womb!
Am I going to be pregnant with his children?
Tell me you're a slutty teacher.
Tell me you enjoy it.
I'm a slutty—
In enj—
No, I don't!
I'm not enjoying this.
Jun...
You want to bear my children, right?
I'm not enjoying this.
I'll come inside, then.
Don't!
My body won't obey me.
You want to be pregnant, right?
Jun...
I'm sorry.
Here are my children!
I'm gonna be pregnant.
I love you, Katsuko.
I'm not lying.
I've been in love with you since I enrolled.
I won't tell Jun about this.
I hope it works out between you too, so I'll keep teaching you.
What if I'm pregnant...
Just marry me.
Look, Katsuko.
I want to fuck you again.
Come on.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
Incoming Call: Jun
Wednesday
Calls While Absent: 5
Unread Messages: 3
I've ended up taking another day off.
Jun has tried contacting me a lot.
But I just can't answer him.
I don't know what say to him.
How did it come to this...
He's going to fuck me until morning again.
I only love Jun, but...
I'm sorry, Jun. Help me.
Thursday
Katsuko has been absent for three days now.
She says it's a cold, but...
Calls: 0
Messages: 0
She won't answer my calls or respond to my texts.
I wonder if she's angry about what happened.
Maybe I should go to see her.
I have to apologize.
I'm also worried about her health.
It feels good.
More.
I want more.
I can't think straight.
I don't want to think about anything.
Yes!
I can just live on if my head is blank!
No! I'm gonna come again!
I'm sorry, Jun.
I love you.
No reason to brood over it if we do this every day.
Are you stupid, thinking that showering five times would cool your head?
Shut up.
This is your fault.
Hey, put some pajamas on. You'll catch a cold.
That's it for today.
Get out, idiot.
This is my hole now, huh?
Katsuko?
Stop it, idiot.
So long.
Jun...