Long ago, when wishes could be granted, there lived a beautiful princess named Eifa.
Her skin was white as snow, and her lips red as roses.
Her ebony hair and eyes were as deep as black pearls.
She was called the "Moon Princess", for her beauty shone like the moon against the night sky.
Her elder brother was called Alois.
His blonde hair shone like polished gold.
His eyes, the color of serene pools of sapphire.
For his gallant, gentle form, he was dubbed: "The Sun Prince".
Alois the Sun Prince, and Eifa the Moon Princess were the pride of the kingdom.
WANDERING LUSTFUL LUNATICS
FAKKU! Presents
Brother Alois...
Alois, it's me, Eifa.
Are you awake?
Thank goodness...
Alois is asleep.
Umm... Alois?
Pardon me, I'm coming in.
Brother, forgive me.
How marvelous.
E-Eifa?
Eifa, what are you doing!?
Stop it!
Alois, it's gotten so big...amazing!
Eifa, wait! This is wrong.
Somewhat bitter.
Eifa, why?
Well, you've hardly even...
Are you two enjoying yourselves this evening?
Yes!
I see. I'm glad to hear that.
By the way, did you enjoy riding horses?
Yeah, we saw lots of neat things, like a huge deer!
Oh really?
Wasn't it great?
Yeah
Hmm. I suppose. Well at any rate, go on and mingle!
Yes!
Okay!
Lord Alois, please dance with Marguerette next, okay?
Alois.
What's the matter? Hiding out here...
It's nothing.
You musn't spoil the ball with such a bored expression.
No, I'm not bored... just a bit tired; that's all.
There's no need to hide it. You're worried about Alois; no?
One cannot suppress their feelings for another.
Not as your mother, but as another woman, I offer you this.
This is a love potion.
First, you drink some.
Then have Alois drink some as well.
You must give it to him by mouth.
If Alois feels the same; your wish shall be granted.
Before you're married off to another prince you've never met, you long for the embrace of your loved one.
Here.
That's why I drank the potion.
Look, Alois. Look at Eifa's vagina...
It's really wet, see?
E-eifa, wait!
I can't!
I can't wait any longer!
Stop, I really mean it! Eifa!
Alois, it's okay.
It hurts, but I'm so happy.
Amazing...
It feels so... good... Alois!
How did this happen?
Eifa's my sister, and yet...
Brother, Brother!
Eifa, you love me that much?
Alois!
Eifa, I'm so sorry.
Alois?
Eifa, I love you.
Brother!
Eifa.
All this time, I've just been afraid.
I knew that the day you ceased to exist as my sister, there'd be no turning back...
Then you feel the same as I do?
Brother...
Here I go.
Okay.
Right there? Does it feel good, Eifa?
Brother, you're wonderful! You're so wonderful!
Eifa's pussy is making such dirty sounds!
Eifa... Eifa!
Brother! Brother!
Brother Alois!
I'm cumming!
Brother, I'm cumming!
Brother?
Eifa.
Brother!
Cumming! I'm cumming again!
Bro... ther... Brother!
I'm gonna cum, Eifa!
Brother... Alois.
Alois.
Eifa, do you regret what we've done?
Not a bit.
Memories of tonight, of being held in your arms, will surely give me strength to keep living.
Timing/Typesetting: Sindalf - Mattarat stinx
Editor: Waar - A wise man once told me "Semen is made up of two things, the sperm and the goo" I remember it to this day
Translator: Acf - The other group finished faster, but we have more staying power
Didn't do anything: SHiN_aKuMa - I hate kittens and sunshine
Mascot: TehMikuruSlave - I spoon feed bitches trix from a golden chalice