*ed credits*
Boundlessly bloom, O spirits of the Water.
Sages of the earth, come hither.
Breathe life into me!
In this mansion lives a lone witch.
Her name is Yuko Morino.
And by day, she is my homeroom teacher.
Upon the sorceresses' hand, betwixt thine fingers, I
summon you, Qreet the Undine!
Bask in the sunglight, and grant warmth unto me!
Episode 1: I Have Become a Tentacle
FAKKU! Presents
My name is Ichiro Tachibana.
And gazing upon the gorgeous Ms. Yuko is the single
greatest joy I have ever known.
Oh man, those tits are practically spilling out of her top!
And those plump, juicy thighs!
I'm in heaven!
What do you think you're doing, commoner?
H-hey, I know you...
Oh no!
Splendid, Ms. Yuko!
What glorious, bountiful boobies!
Squish, squish!
Soft, pale thighs!
Milk!
Ichiro!
Are you okay?
Just leave this freak alone and continue the game, Ms. Yuko!
Her name is Lily Ramses Futaba.
She's 1/4 Egyptian.
She's quite attractive, as you can see.
Get your foot offa me!
You're still breathing, commoner?
You're more stubborn than a cockroach!
But she's a total bitch.
For some reason, she's particularly cold to me.
What kind of parenting led her to harass me like this?
I'd love to see what her parents are like.
Then again, not really.
Ms. Yuko!
This commoner lacks motivation.
Oh, Ichiro...
What am I going to do with you?
Thanks for the assist, Lily!
Where the hell're you looking, scumbag!?
I thought I said no stomping!
You'll never find a husband with that attitude!
Don't you worry.
At my estate, from dawn to dusk, without a moments rest,
24 hours a day, 365 days a year, I uphold the highest moral standards!
What's her problem!? Acting like a stuck-up princess!
Hey Tachibana! How dare you speak to Ms. Lily that way!
She's way out of your league, man!
What if she gets sick of us and switches schools?
Lily Ramses Futaba
Lily transferred to our school a few months ago.
And she immediately became the school's idol.
Her ditzy attitude's makes her as popular as Ms. Yuko.
Eat this!
Watch your aim, you little-
Damn you, Lily!
I'll punish you in my fantasies tonight, once I'm done with Ms. Yuko!
But...
Stay out of my way, commoner!
Why'd you hafta show up before I had my dream-revenge!?
Your what? Don't play dumb with me.
We're both here for the same reason.
To peep?
Not that!
Upon closer inspection, Lily's outfit is kind of odd.
Kind of similar to Ms. Yuko's.
You're dressed like a naughty witch.
Who're you calling a "naughty witch"!?
This is the traditional formal dress passed down by my ancestors!
So you've got a witch fetish too?
No, you moron!
Ouch...
It makes no difference how much you deny it.
The fact that you're here is proof enough.
Proof?
But only I shall become the Solar Witch Yuko Inoue's apprentice!
The Solar Witch's apprentice?
Still trying to deny it?
Quite shrewd of you, nonetheless.
You're more clever than you look.
But the fact that you've broken the barrier and come here proves it!
Prepare yourself!
With this ominous-looking charm I bought from the shady street vendor, I will banish you to oblivion!
I have no idea what's going on, but I've got a real bad feeling in my gut.
Upon the sorceresses' hand, betwixt thine fingers,  I summon you, Qreet the Undine!
An incantation?
A-are you a magical girl?
I'm a witch!
Repent, Ichiro Tachibana!
Ichiro... Ichiro!
Can you hear me?
I'm fine. I can hear you.
Ah! A monster!
Wait, what happened to my hands?
What the hell!?
Remain calm, Ichiro.
You've been transformed into a monster!
I'm a monster?
Just stay calm and listen to me, okay?
The nerve of that peasant, flirting with Ms. Yuko like that!
Pardon me, Miss.
Is there something troubling you?
I have just the thing.
This will transform anyone you wish into your familiar.
But I never expected something like this to happen.
You tried to make me your familiar!?
S-sorry.
Ha! Who'd wanna be the familar of some uptight cunt like you?
What did you say!?
Stop it, both of you!
Futaba truly regrets her actions.
Please forgive her, Ichiro.
Doesn't look that way to me!
This charm is a fake.
It may look like magic used to turn someone into a familiar at first glance,
But it's conterfeit.
I sense great evil from it.
Please, Ms. Yuko!
Please return me to normal!
Dealing with monsters can be tricky.
I'm afraid it'll take a while.
Oh, come on!
This is it...
Futaba!
No!
What have I done?
Ichiro, fuck me.
Whaaaat!?
Ms. Yuko!?
Fully manifested monsters require energy from their summoner.
The need mana to survive!
But you weren't summoned by anyone, Ichiro.
So your only choice is to absorb mana from a witch directly!
Directly?
In other words, you must fornicate with a witch!
She's right. I understand completely.
The hunger welling up within me has transformed into intense lust,
And wishes to slake this thirst with Ms. Yuko's mana.
To feed directly from Ms. Yuko.
Absorbing nutrients via her fluids.
Feasting until it can feast no more!
Pleasuring witches in exchange for sustenance!
Impregnating them with my seed!
And then fuck them all over again!
And again!
Ms. Yuko, I...
Run away.
Fuck me... and absorb my mana!
Don't try to fight it.
If you resist, the monsters instincts will take over,
and you'll go berserk!
And not just Futaba and I...
You'll violate countless women before you're through!
Ms. Yuko...
I'm still a virgin, so please be gentle with me.
Ms. Yuko!
Ichiro...
Don't come any closer, Futaba!
Don't breathe his musk!
It contains an powerful aphrodesiac!
An aphrodesiac?
Monsters cover witches with their magic sperm, and make
them their slaves!
Ms. Yuko's absolutely right.
My monster instincts are telling my body to do it!
Merely dousing her once with this magic musk will make
her my slave for eternity!
Constantly in heat, unable to live without fornicating with me!
A life of sin and demonic seed!
Now, Ms. Yuko! Become my eternal bitch, and satisfy my desire!
Don't worry. I'll swallow your seed.
So please, try to limit yourself to just me!
Don't attack Futaba!
Ms. Yuko!
It's rather embarrassing, but because I've devoted myself to studying magic,
I'm still a virgin.
I'm sorry an old lady like me has to be your first.
No, wait!
Don't tease my nipples too!
I feel like I'm melting!
My breasts feel like they're going to melt!
The tips... they're...
Please, not my nipples!
Ichiro, stop!
You're going to use that to finish me off, aren't you?
I won't forget this!
You won't get off easily!
Oh god! No way!
How can it feel this good!?
Not my butt!
My asshole!
My asshole and pussy feel incredible!
You're turning my asshole out!
Oh yes! You're going to break me!
You're ruining me!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming, CUMMING!
Let me help you with that.
There!
Good morning, Ms. Yuko.
Good morning.
Ms. Yuko! Ms. Yuko!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Despite what happened yesterday, Ms. Yuko smiles at me like it never happened.
Good morning, Ms. Yuko.
Good morning, Futaba.
Didn't Ms. Yuko exorcise you yesterday?
You've got a lot of nerve for a mere familiar!
I'm not a familiar!
And besides, this is all your fault to begin with!
H-hey! What the heck is that!?
Ms. Yuko, look!
It looks like a horn.
It must be an aftereffect from your transformation.
I've got a horn?
By the way, you guys're getting a little to close for comfort...
Who do you think you are, growing a horn?
That's against school regulations!
Either let me have it, or chip it off!
Don't bite my head off, blondie.
How come I gotta give it to you anyway?
Let me see it, dweeb!
That's a valuable magical item!
Hey, be gentle with it!
Gimme! Gimme! Gimme!
So there you have it.
It's certainly a rare condition, but please be kind to Tachibana, okay?
'kay!
Go ahead, Tachibana.
How should I put this?
I know it's a bit off-putting, but please carry on like normal!
A sickness? Well, I can't really blame you.
If Ms. Yuko says it's okay, then we won't shun you,
Tachibana.
Looks good on ya!
You've finally starting to open up, Tachibana!
They didn't even bat an eye.
Alright! Chow time!
Hey, what gives- Oww!
Would Lily like me if I grew a horn?
You're so lucky, Tachibana...
Occult Research Club
What the hell, man!?
If you're after my horn, forget it!
Umm, M-miss Lily, is something the matter?
Let's begin, commoner.
Come again?
Go ahead and... jeez!
Just hurry up and fuck me!
Fuck you!?
Are you serious?
It's my fault you became a freaky tentacle monster.
Lily, are you...
Hurry...
I don't mind.
I can't do it, Lily.
If you inhaled my musk as well, you'll...
Don't worry about it.
Take a good, hard look, Ichiro!
Look how stiff they are.
Wait, don't tell me...
I can handle a little rough treatment.
You're horny?
That's right. I breathed some of your scent the yesterday.
I-I'm so sorry!
That was my own fault, stupid!
I breathed it knowing full well what would happen!
What're you saying, Lily?
I'm telling you to absorb my mana too, before you transform and attack other girls!
You know, you don't deserve a beautiful girl like me!
Yeah, I know.
This is my first time!
Y-you don't say.
A-am I not good enough?
Do I lack the charm Ms. Yuko has?
That's not true at all!
Just the opposite, in fact!
I wanna fuck you really bad right now!
O-ok, fine. If you say so.
I'll let you fuck me just this once.
Even though I really don't want to, I'll make an exception.
I'm sorry, Lily.
I can't suppress my lust any longer.
I wanna to fuck you senseless.
D-do it then, Ichiro!
Hurry up and... fuck me.
W-wait... Hey!
Ichiro!
Lily...
I'm about to transform.
Okay, I'm ready.
Tease me!
I'm being rubbed all over!
You're treating me like a toy!
Ichiro, what are you doing?
I-ichiro, you're already cumming?
You're already ejaculating!?
Oh god, your musk...
Oh my god! I'm in heat!
My body's going numb!
Your musk has taken over my body.
Amazing!
N-no way!
Why!?
Why does it feel so good!?
You've made my womb your plaything!
I won't let you get away with that!
I'm cumming!
You're gonna make me cum!
Here it comes!
It's gushing into me!
So much cum...
You shot so much cum!
I know, I know!
You pervert.
You're such a naughty little tentacle monster!
You're not finished yet, are you?
Alright. I'll keep you company.
Next episode...
Yes! Right during homeroom!
That's a first!
H-hey! You're getting a nosebleed from ogling Ms. Yuko's breasts, aren't you!?
You pervert!
What the hell is this?
Don't think you're hot shit 'cause you've got two horns now!
M-Ms. Yuko, why's your stomach...
What else would it be?
This is your responsibility.