Futaba bought a charm from a shady street vendor,
and unintentionally turned Ichiro into a perverted tentacle monster.
Me and Futaba were caught up in monster Ichiro's curse,
our bodies reacted as if in heat, and that was just the beginning!
First of all, we must return Ichiro to his original form!
But is this just a coincidence? Or is there something more to it?
Episode two: I'm wet from the water!
Good morning, Ichiro.
Good morning!
How are you feeling?
Great!
You were so wild last night too!
Please, Miss Yuko, your boobs...
Oh?
It's...
Let me see, Ichiro...
Amazing! After so much exercise, you still have a hard on!
I'm sorry.
Miss Yuko...
This thick smell of semen...
Miss Yuko is licking my...
If you take all the mana, you'll be able to return to human form.
But be careful, Ichiro. Your sperm is still a magic potion that can turn women into slaves!
So you must learn how to control it.
Can I do that?
It's okay, I'll teach you how to do it.
Just give me more semen now!
Wait, Miss Yuko, have you already become slave to my semen?!
I'm sorry you have to put up with me.
Miss Yuko, you're so intense...
I promise I'll return you to your original form.
Until then, take it all out on me!
Miss Yuko, swallow it deeper.
Like that, Ichiro?
Yes, it's amazing! Miss Yuko, I can't hold back...
Just let it flow. Fill my throat with your semen!
Drink it! Drink all of my semen!
Sorry, my body just gave in, I can't satisfy you anymore for now!
Just bear it somehow, okay?
I'm very satisfied!
I see. I'm glad.
Miss Yuko, are you all right?
I'm fine, don't worry about me.
Why do you go so far for me?
Your grandmother was a witch of the sun.
I don't want it! Please don't say such sad things, Master!
The time is near. Forgive me for putting such a great burden on you.
Master...
That child is cursed.
He is innocent, but the Far Eastern Witch Association wants him dead.
I don't consider it a burden at all.
But...
I wish I could protect him together with you, Master!
Master!
My life is nearing its end.
Listen, Yuko, if you face a situation you can't handle, don't push yourself too hard!
No, I will protect him, no matter what!
He is a precious link between me and you, Master!
Thank you.
Master!
Ichiro...
It's thanks to my Gran that I am alive now.
I will protect you, Ichiro, in your grandmother's stead too!
Now that Gran is gone, Miss Yuko is my guardian.
And...
Who the fuck do you think you are that you can step on my treasure?!
You're up, Commoner?
Lily, what are you doing here?
We've got to talk. Get up, trash.
Huh? You got another horn now!
What?! Why have I got another one too?!
The curse is changing.
That's not a laughing matter!
Are you so bored you come here just to laugh at me?!
What did you want to talk about?
Umm... Let's talk on the way.
The hell?
You're still just a lowlife, so don't talk back!
Hurry up. I'm going to school.
Why has she come here? And she hasn't even taken off her shoes!
Morning!
So, Lily, what did you want to talk about?
Uh, well...
Commoner, what's that cute thing on your bag?
It's a memento of my dead gran. It was her last wish that I always keep it with me.
She was a witch of the sun!
A witch of the sun.
So, what did you want to talk about? Just get to it already.
Umm, well, it's that, you know...
Good morning!
I'm glad you two get along so well! You're almost holding hands.
That's not it!
We don't get along! He's just stupid trash!
Who's stupid?!
Now, now.
But professor, this idiot's got another horn now!
Really.
Miss Yuko, you're a bit too close.
Ichiro, when did it appear?
It was there when I woke up...
There is certainly some kind of change.
I should ask the Far Eastern Witch Association, maybe they know something.
Those are the ones who want to kill Ichiro, right?
I've done nothing wrong!
Yeah, you're not an evil magician. Don't worry.
Did you just "tsch" that? And what did you want to talk about?!
Shut up, you idiot!
Come on, kids, let's get going.
Wait for us!
Do you like my little present?
The charm's true powers are only just awakening.
Just a little more. I'm looking forward to it.
Play last-one-standing water dodgeball!
Miss Yuko in bikini!
Those great bouncy tits!
Who hit me with the ball?!
You were thinking of perverted stuff again!
Lily, today I'm not gonna...
The pervert has been judged!
It's the punishment for opposing Lily!
Miss Yuko, Tachibana passed out!
Oh my, what should we do?
I'm worn out!
Do you want to kill me?!
Play along for now.
Huh? Why?
I'm sorry! I wanted to apologize for what I've done.
I just couldn't say it... I'm sorry!
You're so cute when you apologize like that!
What are you saying, you pervert!
I should be the one apologizing for turning you into a tool of lust.
I'm sorry you got mixed up in this.
You don't need to apologize. It was my fault.
But for you, I'm...
That's not true!
Sure you're a commoner, but a good one at that...
Sure you're an idiot, but among the blind the one-eyed man is king...
Are you praising me or scolding me?
I'm telling you, I don't hate you!
I see... Thank you.
You love Miss Yuko, right?
Well, I have other interests...
What was that?
What do you mean?
What do you mean what?
Since when are you such a playboy, Commoner?!
No, I'm earnest! I'm not a playboy...
You're getting big.
You're getting big down there.
This is just...
So you love Miss Yuko and me too?
Well... Sorry.
Don't apologize!
Sorry.
Idiot!
Are you turned on?
Only as a human. I don't think I'd turn into a monster.
I'll sort it all out for you. I'll train you so you can only look at me.
Yeah...
Then as a part of that training, spread your legs.
Huh?
Spread them.
Like this?
Yeah! Otherwise there'd be no point to the training.
Lily, you're wet already.
It's just water! From the pool! I'm not wet!
Or so you say.
You're still not wet?
I'm not gonna cum for you!
Then let's have sex.
Stupid, what are you sayi-
You idiot, what do you think you're doing?!
I want to fuck you without turning into a monster!
Ichiro, you're so big... and thick! How can it be this thick?
Your pussy is welcoming me so warmly.
No! Don't look!
No! Not there!
I'll carve the shape of my dick into your pussy!
I'm totally fucking you!
No! Just now...
I'll carve it all the way into your womb!
I'll fuck you countless times from now on!
Idiot!
No!
You're gonna cum? You can't cum in my womb! You mustn't!
I'll fill your womb with semen!
I said don't cum in me!
Wow, a lot's flowing out!
It turned into our juicy pool.
Idiot! I wanted to keep it all in...
I feel so sluggish...
You're pathetic!
It's natural to be tired after a class at the pools!
You're the only one still fresh!
Miss Yuko's class is next!
We could fantasize new ways after her bikini!
Who was that?!
Shut up, pervert.
What are you doing there?
Miss Yuko left early because she wasn't feeling well.
What? Miss Yuko?
She said we shouldn't worry as it's just a bit of low blood pressure.
Let's talk about what we should do for the school fair!
Yes!
Is she really all right?
Can't you keep quiet? You idiot are just a slave, so sit there with your mouth shut!
Sit!
Now let's start the discussion.
Damn you, Lily! As if I could keep quiet after this!
I'll show you the powers of my magical body!
First let's decide what we should for the fair.
As I was learning to control magic, I discovered I could turn invisible!
From the questionnaire earlier, we know everyone's ideas, such as maid cafe.
Take this, Lily!
Now let's pick from-
Ichiro, what are you doing?!
I'll teach you not to be rude to me again!
It's your punishment!
Don't you get cocky!
Behave!
What's wrong, Lily?
Lily, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine, no problem!
Now, let's see, there was a play, a haunted h-
I just have a slight cold.
This might turn into great fun!
Also, maid cafe...
This is fun!
Sorry, my cough just won't stop...
You commoner! I'll remember this!
How long can you withstand it?
No... I'm gonna...
I vote for the maid cafe! I said it!
Maid cafe, one vote!
I can't cum in front of everyone! But that stupid Ichiro will make me...
Sorry, Lily, I'm about to cum too.
Don't! If you cum in me now...
No way! You can't!
We can't do maid cafe?
But if you say so, Lily, I'll live with it!
Sorry, but if I go any further I won't be able to hold back the semen's power!
Stupid! You're cumming!
Huh? What was that, Lily?
Cum- I'll come along shopping too!
It'll be so awesome if you're the one picking stuff out.
Her father is some Arab oil tycoon, I think?
Stupid, that's not it! He's a pharaoh or something!
Damn, you're still cumming...
If it leaks, you'll be found out, so hold it in!
That's impossible!
Then just use your panties if it spills.
But now...
Sorry, I have one more load ready to shoot.
Drink it, Lily!
They'll find out if you let it spill! Drink it all!
I'll kill you...
Don't say that! It tasted good, didn't it?
I'm cumming...
Is something wrong with her?
Lily, are you all right?!
Huh?! Miss Yuko is?!
What's going on?!
Miss Yuko called us and said it's urgent!
Hurry, let's get going!
What's that?!
I made a room for myself in this space. If you peek, I'll kill you.
I decided to watch over you, so that you won't abuse your magic.
Like yesterday.
What?!
You don't like it? Yet you took my virginity.
That's different...
Men shouldn't look for excuses!
Let's hurry to Miss Yuko!
I get it, I'm going!
Miss Yuko!
Looks like she's not here.
It's weird. I'm sure that's her familiar over there...
I'm here.
Miss Yuko, what happened...
It seems I got pregnant.
Is that... my child?!
Yes... probably.
But it was her first time... and mine too... or what?! I don't get it!
It's not the time to be upset, Tachibana Ichiro.
Who are you?
Dem titties...
Sweet.
This is an emergency. You must get ready.
The time is ripe.
Next Episode
You filth! You can't do this to me...
No! Don't suck my boobs...
Your cum feels so good!
You'll get hurt if you get in my way, you untrained witch.
I won't let you lay a finger on Ichiro!
Cum in my womb!