This is a tiny island in the Southern Pacific.
And a resort beach all alongside the sea.
We, the bikini model idol group Live Un Veil came to this island for a shooting.
Hoshisaki Nanami
With us came fans chosen by lottery for a six days-five nights photo-tour.
Sena Nagisa
It was bound to be a fun event!
But both us and the event got messed up by that filthy pervert.
Kuroha Kaede
Shameful boob filming on a tropical island
"Please take a picture of me naked..."
FAKKU! Presents
Chirping Beach
When he took pictures of us, our bodies felt hot and a dirty feeling overwhelmed us.
No... Pervy juices are leaking down there...
What happened? This is too arousing...
That shyness is just like a little girl!
I've to... hold back... or they'll realize.
We'll have a shooting tomorrow too. Please don't do anything strange!
You're still shaking, aren't you.
I've to fix you before you can return to work.
Don't...
Kaede, just relax.
But... I... can't...
Why?
Because...
See, it's nothing.
Stop... If you excite me anymore it'll come out...
Come out? What will?
Pervert... You know...
I don't, that's why I'm asking.
Pee...
What? I couldn't hear you.
Pee... I feel like I'm gonna pee!
Let me go to the toilet... Please!
It's okay. No one's around. Just do it here.
That's...
Stop...
Come on, just give up and leak.
Leak...
No, no... no...
It's coming! I can't stop!
Don't look! Don't look!
Amazing!
A bikini model's undiluted piss!
I can't hold back anymore!
What?
No... wait...
At least let me wipe the piss...
Le... Let me down...
Your shaking won't stop just from having a good leak.
Th... at's... That's...
This is mean... so suddenly...
Such a dripping hot pussy cries for getting fucked.
My breast... don't...
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
If you touch my nipple...
It's hitting... so deep in me...
What's hitting where?
Want... me... to say... such stuff again?
Of course.
My inside... your cock is hitting...
Your cock... is hitting... the inside of my pussy.
Kaede, you're turning me on so much.
Don't... make me say... so embarrassing things...
It'll break... if you're doing it so wild my pussy will break...
I'm coming soon... I'll be going inside.
Don't... Don't...
Don't come inside me... please stop... don't!
That's... it's coming inside me... inside me... it's hot.
Did you calm down from this?
Pervert... you filthy pervert.
Nagisa, smile please!
Sure.
You're hot, Nagisa, you're too hot!
Don't say that...
This swimsuit... he made me...
Nagisa, are you turned on?
I'm taking all the pics I can!
They're taking pictures of me... like this.
They're taking pictures!
Hey, what are you doing?!
You bastard, get away from Nagisa!
Nagisa, you get it, right?
Yes...
Guys... it's different.
This is... this kind of a shooting.
A special event where you can take pictures of a me you won't see anywhere else.
This man is an actor.
Are you serious?
Please don't hold back, take your pictures.
Hey, what now?
Well, if Nagisa says so...
This is going well, isn't it.
They're looking at me... Looking at me... This is too embarrassing!
Not yet... The main act comes now.
Are you really putting it in?
Are you really doing it?
You're kidding, right? That can't be! I'm taking pictures!
Be gentle...
You're tighter than usual.
Are you turned on, Nagisa?
No... that's not it...
It's because I feel dirty...
You really are, Nagisa!
You're... amazing!
They're taking pictures... of me having sex...
They're taking pictures of it all!
It's too embarrassing, looking like this!
You still have something to say to the others.
Everyone, please... take pictures... of me naked...
of my dirty boobs... of my pussy...
I'll show you all there's to see...
You said it right, Nagisa. As thanks, I'll make you come in front of them.
That's...
Okay, it's time to finish, Nagisa!
Everyone... I'm almost... coming!
Please take pictures of that too!
Please take nice pictures of me covered in cum!
I'm coming... coming...
More pictures... of my orgasm... of my boobs... of my pussy...
Pictures of all of it!
Come on, do it already.
I know.
Like this?
Move them or it won't be tittyfuck.
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
I'll do it. I should just do it, right?
Stop...
Don't turn me on any more than this!
Continue. If you don't satisfy me, it won't be over.
Why... it's so embarrassing... but my boobs are hot... and my nipples are hard... and tinkling.
Boobs are your weakness, it seems.
That's not... it's because... you're taking pictures.
You shouldn't lie.
Don't... my nipple!
Don't fondle my nipple!
Oh my... Looks like tittyfuck won't do it.
Guess i'll have to put it in.
That's... but...
If you don't hurry, the shooting will begin.
I get it. I just have to do what you want, right?
I should just let you rape me, right?
Please... be gentle.
My bikini will get stained...
Are you this wet already? Such a pervert.
Nanami!
Could it be that you came already?
That's...
Don't lie. You came, right?
Because you stuck it in so suddenly...
You're such a pervert, coming from just putting it in.
Don't say that. I'm not pervert... at all...
Whose fault is this?
Let's finish this quick so that you'll make it back to the shooting.
This... animal-like pose... how you're clinging on to me...
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's embarrassing! Finish it quick!
I'm coming soon, Nanami! Let's go together!
Together? Together... then you'll be satisfied?
What?
I'll come together with you... I'll do what you say... so please... leave me already.
I'm coming!
You're such a fool. How could I leave you alone just because we came together?
You're so mean... The shooting is about to start... And you covered me this much....
Don't worry. I've prepared a new bikini for you.
They're all looking at me...
This bikini is worse than being naked!
Hey, Nanami... that bikini... it's amazing.
It may be a bit too daring, but i thought i'd reward you for supporting us all the time.
Is it weird?
No, it's great!
Now if you'd only throw some equally daring poses...
That's... with this bikini, wouldn't that be a bit too much?
You're doing it all the time! Can't you now?
Well it's not that i can't...
Nanami?
It's okay. I'm fine.
Then let's give you some special service today.
Nanami!
It's embarrassing! Too embarrassing!
Don't look at me like that! Oh please finish fast!
Or I'll get turned on again!
That filthy pervert turned us on with his camera,
and they took a lot of embarrassing pictures that afternoon too.
Our boobs... down there too... everything.
It's strange that though in the beginning it was very embarrassing,
with everyone looking and taking pictures, it started to feel good!
We can't return anymore.
I'd like to continue this secret shooting for all eternity!
If you'd like, please join...
I'm coming... I'm coming again...
Take pictures of my orgasm... take embarrassing pictures of me!
Please... let's come together!
Cum... wherever you want...
You can cum anywhere...