Teach.
It's fine.
Go ahead and enjoy it.
It's gotten so big.
Your dick is really hard.
Teach...
FAKKU! Presents
High-School Girl and a Lewd Teacher 4
Fashion Model Shizuka - A Cheeky Model's Self-Account of her Sexual Escapades
Pleased to meet you sir.
Umm, so you're transferring in this late into the semester?
That's rather unexpected.
Well, there are reasons for that. I'll leave her to you.
Sure.
All-girls' schools are so pretty. I'm glad I managed to transfer here.
You think so?
By the way, why did you transfer in now? The vice principal was hazy about it.
The school I was in was covered in graffiti. And this place is so great. And then there's you...
Please show me around the school soon.
Please teach us our way around.
It's nice to meet you all.
You're a fashion model for magazines? That's amazing.
No wonder the class wouldn't calm down.
Thank you.
So have you heard who our attendant will be?
What's an attendant?
Huh? So the vice principal didn't tell you?
What should I do? We have to go to work now.
I'll go ask real quick.
Well, we have to go to a photo shoot now, so I'll see you later.
Let's go Satsuki.
What do they mean by attendant?
That's good.
Smile!
That's the way.
You're glowing!
You're flawless!
You're absolutely beautiful.
Wow, I'm so tired. They've got no skill. I'm fed up with it.
Are you OK Satsuki?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Huh? Why are you here?
The vice principal told me to look after you so I stopped by.
I see.
But, the vice principal told me he'd send us our attendant right away.
That's right, the vice principal told me to look after you as an attendant.
What? I haven't heard anything about that.
Did you know about this Satsuki?
No, I haven't heard a thing.
This has to be some kind of a joke.
Is this the vice principal? Are you aware of the stipulations of our contract?
Right, this doesn't fulfill them at all.
He's supposed to be young and hot...
Finding someone young and hot is your problem. This is ridiculous.
Are you trying to take advantage of me? Did you think you could fool me that easily?
Hey, Takai...
Shut the hell up, I'm discussing something important you disgusting pig.
Wakao, what's wrong with Takai?
I can't revoke the contract now that we're so far along.
Fine, but I'll take latitudes with other aspects of the contract.
I can't believe this. And there he was telling me to abide by the agreement.
That baldy should stop screwing around.
H-Hey...
He's taking me too lightly.
Having an fat pig like this around me would be so stifling I couldn't bear it.
Hey now, Takai...
Be quiet. Can't you keep your mouth shut for a bit?
Even at your best you're stifling.
This sucks. I'm so tired. I'm gonna head home and sleep. Let's go Satsuki.
Weren't you going to head back to the school?
I'm not in the mood for that. Go back on your own.
I can't do that...
You're pretty damn persistent. What is it, do you want to be around me that badly?
What do you mean?
I get it. Did you get excited seeing me in a swimsuit?
That's gross. So you've been throwing dirty glances at me.
I thought all along I wouldn't have much of a future with a guy who looked like you.
You little...
I'll feel creeped out if you keep looking at me like that.
Get him off Satsuki.
Wait what? Get me off?
What kind of reaction is that?
Are you seriously a virgin?
Wait a second, what are you talking about? And I'm not a virgin!
What are you getting so worked up about? It's not a big deal.
That's exactly what's creepy about you.
Why you...
You look like you've been holding it all in for some time.
She's not quite as cute as me, but be grateful for having a girl like her get you off.
This is a good opportunity for Satsuki too.
I'm heading out. I'll leave the rest to you.
Wakao, is she taking advantage of you somehow?
No, that's not it at all.
Teacher.
W-wait a second Wakao.
Shizuka will get even more angry if I don't do this.
Fine. But let's head back to the school instead of doing it here.
Ok.
So you didn't change your mind on the way here. Do you always end up doing this? Geez.
It's not like that. This is my first time.
Sir.
But if you do this sort of thing, won't a guy want to go all the way?
No. Shizuka told me she'd protect me if that happened.
She said if anything happened to me she wouldn't work anymore.
And you're fine with her making you do this?
She told me I have to gain experience with this sort of thing.
Takai will protect you? So does that mean that anyone who makes an enemy out of her is out of a job?
That's right.
Oh, it's so hot.
That means you're about to come right?
Your thing is amazing.
Really? But you know, the really amazing part is just beginning.
No! What are you doing? Please stop!
If you go any further I'll tell Shizuka.
Go ahead and tell her.
She can only influence my job. That doesn't matter to me at all.
I'm not that attached to my teaching license anyway.
No, no!
Please stop this!
It's too late to start saying that now.
No way.
This is experience for you too.
No. Stop.
No. It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts!
My insides are squeezing tight, it hurts!
You'll get used to it after fucking for a while.
No.
No more.
No. Don't go any further.
I can't take any more.
I won't tell Shizuka, so please.
That's a relief.
I'll fill you right up as a sign of gratitude.
Wait, don't do it. Don't come inside of me.
I'll get pregnant.
No, no! I'm begging you!
No!
It's twitching inside of me.
That was so cruel.
Takai would suffer from the publicity if this got out.
I'd be fine with it though.
Yes. That's true.
It's obvious that this sort of thing would happen with a guy.
Yeah.
So from now on you'll get me off whenever Takai turns me on right?
Yes.
Sorry, I have to take care of some procedural stuff with the teacher now.
Geez, you should be blissful that I'm even talking to you.
Who do you think you are addressing me so casually?
So you're that kind of person.
Don't call me 'you,' address me as Miss Shizuka.
You're impertinent for an attendant.
I'm a teacher first and foremost.
Where's Satsuki?
Satsuki was with her friends earlier.
What's with that girl...
And another thing, do you think it's OK to call her by her first name like your lover just because she got you off once?
I've got to hand it to you. That's why I know you're an amateur and a virgin.
Wow, yap-yap-yap, complain is all you do.
You're starting that again? How many times do I have to explain it to you?
I'm building up a ton of stress from you, you fat pig without an ounce of wit or grace.
Why you... I'm the victim here. It's your fault that I...
It's Miss Shizuka.
Kneeling down suits trash like you.
You little... you just kicked a teacher...
Did getting on your knees help you understand?
If you address me as 'you' again...
This little...
Having someone like you bend their head to me doesn't even do anything for me.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Why did I get paired up with that little princess.
And the bathroom of all places... Wait, she's not even here.
Where did she run off to.
Doing it here...
Oh no, I can't stop.
What are you doing?
What kind of question is that? I'm here by the vice principal's orders.
Oh, right, fine. Come along.
What is it? Let me go.
Instead of coming along, how about we come right here?
What are you talking about? I'm leaving so let go of me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't play stupid. What's this here?
Stop it. If you keep going I'll make sure you get fired on the spot.
I don't mind. I knew I'd quit teaching eventually anyway.
But only after I'd deflowered a little butterfly like you.
Wait...
It must have felt good rubbing up against the corner of the desk.
How could you ditch someone and go off to feel good on your own like that?
So you don't care about where you do it?
If you want to get off that badly I'll make you come right here.
No!
Wait, this is a joke right?
Hey, I'm telling you to stop.
I'm not kidding, stop this.
Stop it, stop it, why should I do it with someone like you?
I'm not kidding either.
No, no! It's really going inside!
I'm telling you 'no,' hey!
This is my first time! Why should I have my first time with a fat pig like you?
It's way too depressing.
Christ, you mouth off, you're violent, you're a terrible person overall.
Calling people trash and pig...
Yeah about that, I was wrong.
Sorry for calling you a fat pig and all that.
You're not that fat, you're just chubby.
And I take back calling you trash as well.
You're just a little slow to catch on to things.
I'm really sorry. I have to be cute right?
I'll tone it down from now on. You'll still stand out though... So that's why...
So that's what? How the heck were you brought up anyway?
You need to be punished.
It's going in, it's going in!
I apologized didn't I? I took back what I said!
When I of all people apologize you should forgive me right? You should understand that much at least.
You get on my nerves even when you're apologizing.
Why?
It's going inside of me.
It hurts, stop it! It hurts! Hey!
Hey, really, please...
I'm sorry.
Really.
No more... Forgive me.
Eww. It's really going inside.
For all that, you're letting out a dirty voice.
What are you talking about, that's not..
I couldn't...
I'm telling you to stop.
I'm being serious.
Get a hold of yourself you pervert.
You're making even dirtier sounds now than before.
I think your taking it the wrong way. There's no way I'd anything from a fat pig like you
Why would I feel anything when you suck so much at thrusting?
That's an interesting thing to say when I'm the only man you've been with.
Wouldn't it be great to get filled up by that sucky guy's semen?
Hey, wait. Are you kidding?
That's not even funny. Hey!
Wait! You really can't do that! Hey!
No! No way! You can't come! You can't!
You can't do this! No!
This can't be real. It's going inside me. No...
How could you do something like this.
You're not being honest with yourself about how much you enjoyed that.
Let's go another round.
What are you doing?
Do you mean I have to put up with more of this?
Hey. Stop. Wait...
You can't even control your voice anymore.
Shut up.
That's your fault.
You're still full of energy. I'll shoot another one inside of you.
No, I'm already full. I don't need any more.
There's no need to hold back.
No... Not again...
No!
So much of it came out inside of me again.
That pose would make a great picture, Miss Model.
Stop fucking around! Filth is as filth does, you trash.
But you'll end up eating rotten food anyway.
So why were you rubbing yourself on that desk?
Shut up about that. What does it matter? Just enjoy what you got to do today.
Fine, I get it. It was stress relief. When I get angry or fed up with something, doing it gives me relief.
Everyone my age does it. It's not weird.
So that's how it is. But from now on I'll relieve your stress for you so there's no need to worry.
What are you talking about? Is something wrong inside your head?
You're going to get locked up and eat rotting food for the rest of your life.
If you report me I'll take this to some publishers.
I'll spell out everything from your personality to your masturbation habits. The Slutty Nympho Model. It'll have a great plot.
Do what you want.
Whoa there...
If you do that all that'll happen is that portrayal of me will become popular.
It won't affect my cuteness in any way.
Did you think you could blackmail me with that?
You're naive. You're trash after all. Spend some time reflecting over it in your cell.
Is that how it will be? Then I won't be able to make you feel good either.
What are you talking about? Make me feel good?
As if you could make me feel good, idiot.
The body doesn't lie. You came even though it was your first time. That alone means we're compatible.
W-what?
Didn't it feel better than doing it alone?
You can relieve your stress and feel even better from now on.
How could I have felt good when you forced yourself on me?
And besides, I can relieve all the stress I want if I get a boyfriend.
Can you have sex with a boyfriend for nothing but stress relief? You'll end up hating each other.
I'm fine with being nothing more than a tool for stress relief.
Then masturbating on my own would be a thousand times better.
You'd better get your luggage ready.
Damn that pig. It still stings.
What should I do? Even if I make him eat filth this pain won't go away. Damn it.
And what was that about being nothing more than a tool for stress relief? He'll cause more stress instead.
No way. No way. No way. What's he doing here? Is that really him?
Why is he here?
He couldn't have followed me all the way here.
He's strange. He's really weird.
No. Stop it.
Please stop.
You're so cute Shizuka.
You're so happy about doing it with me you're trembling.
I'm begging you, stop.
We're lovers, there's no need to get so nervous.
No! Please, stop.
What's this squid-like stench?
You... is this... could this be...
Are you really Shizuka?
This is a bitch-pig's stench.
You pig, you're not Shizuka.
You pervert!
Hey, wait a second. Who's a pervert?
Are you alright Takai?
Teacher. You trash. You fat pig.
What were you doing? I was in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Aren't you my attendant? Why aren't you attending on me?
Wait.. what?
Are you fine with me getting assaulted? You idiot. You fat pig. You pervert.
I have to act a certain way on top of being beautiful.
Not there!
That's why I want to relieve my stress.
It's going inside! The fat pig's dick is inside!
What is this?
It hurts but... No!
We're really a good match.
You're feeling it already.
That's not.. No!
It feels so...
No, no!
We can't do this.
Doing this only makes me throb harder.
I'm only using your dick to cheer myself up... that's all this is.
So I'll let you do this much. You should be grateful.
Yes, that's it. I'll let you thrust deep inside of me.
More...
Am.. this is amazing. I'm going to lose it.
That's it. All the way inside. Deeper.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
It's amazing. It's so good!
Thrust it inside of me!
Oh no! I'm going to come from this!
I'm coming!
I can't believe how good this feels.