By "strange," do you mean Reiko appearance?
I guess she does seem tired, but...
I wonder if that's all.
I definitely get the feeling she's grown more womanly lately!
Yeah, I want that! If you cry out, you'll draw attention here...
If someone comes...
Why don't we try asking her to come hang out?
We'll all go to an amusement park!
Reiko is just so cute when she gets worked up!
No more...
Please don't cum in there!
This is too humiliating...
No more, please.
Why does it feel so good?
I thought I heard Reiko's voice...
Looks like you wet your panties like a brat!
My dick's standing up straight because we're doing it however I want!
It's warm...
There's so much!
A few days later
Misaki's pretty late.
Even though she's the one who suggested this...
I'll go buy us some drinks.
What would you like, Reiko?
I'll leave it up to you.
Man... this is the best!
Misaki's pussy is so dirty!
I always wanted to do this. I got hard just passing by you!
Cumming while I was still inside you was a great choice.
Come on! Grab your old boyfriend and come here!
Let's all enjoy a fun day off together.
Oh yeah, I already had some fun with Misaki earlier!
Hey, thanks for coming, ex-boyfriend!
Let's all have some fun together. You enjoy it too, Yasu.
Now, come here.
Check this out, ex-boyfriend.
Your girl's been tainted by another guy all the way to her panties.
See? This woman's mine now.
Got it? Look!
Enough... Please stop.
No, please. Don't...
He got me to cry... I'm so awful.
Reiko...
Please, no more kissing...
Ah, but you seem to like kissing, Reiko.
You keep tightening up on me!
N-no, that's not...
No... it's not true!
Then maybe it's my dick you're enjoying...
Because it's bigger than your ex-boyfriend's!
Damn! Is this how you pay off your debts?
My dick feels good inside a girl like this.
Noo!
You don't mean that.
You should enjoy a big man!
A "big man"... is this...?
At this rate...
It's not like that... no!
Amazing!
The cock that made a woman of me... how far in is it gonna go?!
It's so long... and warm... my head is spinning!
It feels really great getting big inside you, right?
C'mon, how is it? C'mon, c'mon!
Your dick feels... good...
It's not true! He just forced me to say that! Please...
All right, time to cum! Your pussy's nice and tight!
Yes...
Come on, don't spill out like that, Miss Class President.
Getting to cum inside a girl who just lost her virginity. I'm a lucky guy!
No... please don't!
This is really the best... so, let's make a little me together!
Deep inside of Misaki, my seed is planting itself!
What are you doing?! N... no!
Letting it all out feels so good!
My kid will be sleeping in here.
No...
Hey, it's okay if this one gets pregnant with my kid, right?
Yeah.
How could this... how, how...?!'
My shameless pussy is getting wet...
I'll make you wear that same look!
N...no...
I would never make such a sleazy face!
No... Shintarou, don't look at my face like that...
I'll show you... Just how exactly she's tightening around my dick!
No... don't look... no!
Heh... I called you here.
Well, I'll leave lookout duty to you, vice president.
Man... he's a good guy, Reiko's ex-boyfriend.
It'd be all too easy just to expose this picture.
So you'll listen to whatever I tell you, right?
The only one who can make love to your body is me.
No, not that...
It's too big, it'll reach my womb like this...
But... but, it's good...
I'm cumming!