It's just the third day of vacation,
and I already had to come back to school for some notes I forgot.
This year's swimming classes were awesome.
The lewd meanie girl Sukumi
No one should be able to find me...
I'm just here to pick up what I forgot in class...
What's this sound?
Is that the girls' changing room?
That's Natsumizu Sukumi from my grade.
It feels... good.
If I do it so much, it'll leave a stain.
It feels... feels...
good!
Good? What are you doing?!
Ah, sorry!
I think your name was... Yui something!
Something?
How long are you going to peek from the window?
Get in here already!
Why is it so big?
And why is it out in plain sight in the first place?
I couldn't help it! After all, you were...
You saw me, didn't you! You saw me masturbating!
You pervert!
Sorry!
Who said you can put it away?
It's unfair that only you get to see me!
Then what should I...
Let's see.
Play with it. Masturbate.
But...
You can't?
Well...
Okay, I get it. Then...
Natsumizu, what are you doing?
I'll scream "Help me! He attacked me!"
Wait!
Then will you do what I say?
I didn't look that closely before, but this is really big.
Even though you have such a girlish face.
Come on, do it already.
You're really doing it.
You told me to!
Guys do it like this?
It's so stupid.
It's so big. What turned on you so much?
It's because I saw you masturbating,
and you're the cutest girl in class...
I... It's not like saying that would make me happy or anything!
Then how about this? So?
So what?
Don't you get turned on?
Well...
And if I do this?
How is it? You getting turned on?
Yeah.
And how about this?
It feels great to do it directly with my fingers.
What about you?
It turns me on a lot.
What? You really get turned on? You freak.
But it's making such a sound...
And it's pink and beautiful...
Come on, don't say that!
I'm cumming...
Me too...
I'm cumming!
Seriously, you fapped in front of a girl!
You really are a pervert!
But...
Oh right. You come here every day from tomorrow!
Every day?
Should I scream instead?
Okay, I get it!
I'll come every day!
You will?
Why is this here?
What? You're telling me to put that on?
I think it'd fit you.
Come on. I'm already wearing a swimsuit.
Why should I change into that?
How should I put it, the white school swimsuits are special.
You have a swimsuit fetish?
Well... Yeah.
Too bad. I hate swimsuits.
I see, I see!
So that's why your cock was so big when you saw me in my swimsuit!
No, that was....
Look!
Really? Look how big it is. Your body is honest.
It's twitching.
You were pulling it like this, right?
Why are you making that face? Does it feel good by chance?
So it feels good if I do this?
Are you fine with just this?
I said, are you fine with just a girl doing this to you?
I want to...
You want to?
Touch your pussy!
No.
But!
How can you even think that?
But...
You're hopeless.
Who told you to touch it directly?!
Stop! This is too much!
Sukumi, I'm there...
I won't let you cum.
I... I...
What is it?
What are you doing?
I want to put my cock in... in your pussy!
Hey, stop!
Don't just push me down like that! Stupid!
You pervert!
Sorry...
It's lower.
There.
It's coming in!
It hurts! That big thing is coming in!
Sorry, Sukumi! I can't stop now!
It's full! My pussy's full with your thick cock!
I'm gonna move, Sukumi.
Don't!
It's... It's stretching... my insides...
I can feel it moving in me!
Your dirty cock is moving inside me!
What's going on? It hurts, but still...
I'm speeding up.
I can't take anymore!
It's so hot inside me!
Your cock is rubbing me and it feels hot!
This is sex... I'm having sex with Sukumi!
Shut up! I'm doing...
Nothing like that with you!
You can hear it too right?
I don't want to!
Does it feel good now?
How could this feel good?
That thing is just going in and out! No way that would feel good...
That big thing is coming all the way in!
Your cock is... going wild inside me!
A thick cock is inside me!
I can't... I'm...
I'm at my limit too!
I'm sure next time will feel better.
Let's do it again tomorrow, Sukumi.
I found this on the way...
Don't spew nonsense! Get your cock out already!
You are a swimsuit fetishist, aren't you.
Then why should I even put on that sailor blouse?
Sorry...
Look, I can handle a stupid freak like you with just my foot!
Look, look!
It's not fair that only you get to feel good!
But it was you...
Right there...
Yeah, there! Lick all over it.
Up and down. Like that!
It's good...
It's amazing...
You came, Sukumi?
Stupid!
Don't ask stuff like that!
Turn around and stay at the bench.
What are you doing?
Shut up! Don't look!
Sorry!
I-It's not like I put it on because you said so or anything!
I put it on because I wanted to!
Thanks.
No.
I won't let you do as you please today.
I won't let you always have your way with me!
I'll rape you today.
Be prepared.
See? You're entering me.
Are you even looking?
Yeah....
So deep... Your hard, thick cock is in me so deep!
How is it?
It feels great.
But the fun... starts now!
What do you think you're doing?
Sorry!
Stupid! Don't stop!
Does it feel good?
It... It's not like... it feels good... or anything!
It's squeezing! Are you cumming?
I'm not! You cum first!
We came together.
Who cares about that...
I didn't... cum or anything.
Why are stuff like this here?
No! Not there!
Don't touch my ass!
I had a dream like that.
Now tell me, why did an octopus fuck me in the ass?
Sukumi, you're into anal?
Of course not!
What is this even?
Come on, don't just drop it.
Huh, where is it?
Found the tail!
And the ears...
Gotcha!
Stupid! Don't just touch me!
Hey, stop teasing me!
Sukumi, put on the cat ears.
Why would I?
Because you'll turn into a cat girl now.
Stupid, if you keep that up...
Let's move.
Whatever, just don't be so harsh...
Here we go...
You idiot!
Now that you're a cat girl in a swimsuit,
you should turn into a real cat.
How could I... meow!
Your cock feels good, meow!
Don't tease meow ass!
Does it feel good?
It's not like it feels meow or anything!
Really?
It feels meow! Master's cock is ameowzing
and it feels meow when you play with meow tail!
You said it. This is my thanks.
Master's thick cock is in me so deep!
It feels ameowzing!
And meow tail moves with every thrust, it's great!
It's fantastic! You're meowing inside me!
Meow head is spinning, it feels so meow!
It's too meowch!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Meow!
It looked like you enjoyed it a lot.
That's not true meow!
Ouch!