I told you not to worry about it.
Not much you can do about it anyway.
Kagu...
You want to see me naked?
You can ask for whatever you want.
It got harder. You got turned on?
You can cum whenever you want, Shun... Shun...
It's really a lot...
You can always depend on me, Shun.
Don't hold back.
I shouldn't... do this... really...
Just after I touched my little brother like that...
I shouldn't be comforting myself like this...
If he knew that I got turned on as well...
Just accepting these feelings isn't enough...
Even though I'd be binding Shun with them...
Comfort your perverted sister, Shun...
I want him to hold me... To take me...
It doesn't matter that we're both Sagimiya, that we're siblings...
I love Shun...
Shun... Shun... My...
Shun...
Naturally cool, bewitchingly sulking, but lovely long black haired Kagu
Shun? You're back?
Kagu, why are you in your underwear?
Because it's so hot today. This is the most airy.
But still, that outfit...
You've seen me naked so many times.
You're really weird.
That's not it...
Shun, where are you?
I was looking for Misaki.
Now that you mention it, you two get along really well lately.
Yeah. Just like in the old days now that we cleared the misunderstanding.
I'll be going now then.
Shun... you...
Brother, I can't bear this!
Not yet, Misaki. Won't you do what I ask for?
But... But...
This is so embarrassing, brother...
You pervert! Meanie!
You tease me dressing me up like this...
You dressed up yourself.
Because your expression said you wanted me to!
It's not my fault!
You stir up my ass as well... I can feel it...
Make me enjoy it there too...
You're really so mean...
You're amazing! Your cock feels so good!
I can't take anymore!
I can't... I really can't take anymore!
God... I even wet myself...
You're so hopeless, Misaki.
I'll have to punish you again.
Do it please! I want you to punish me!
Shun... what are you doing with Misaki?!
I see.. Shun... You chose her?
I'll go clothes shopping today. I'll take Shun too to carry the stuff.
Oh Misaki, since when do you two get along so well?
What are you talking about? We don't get along that well!
Something's wrong, Kagu?
Nothing... I see, you're going out.
Enjoy yourselves.
It was Shun... But his eyes were so different.
I almost came just from him looking at me.
Were those the true eyes of Shun, the head of the family who accepted the fate of blood?
Shun...
This is bad...
Kagu!
What? You're back?
You're really rude, coming in without asking.
Why, where were you then?
This and that... But you--
Kagu, today too...
No. Today I...
Can do it, right?
Kagu.
I'm sorry.
Won't you let me go?
Just do it as usual!
No... I can't.
Why? You always do it.
Stop it.
What's wrong, Kagu?
You have Misaki. Not me but Misaki.
You should just... be with her. That's...
You were peeking yesterday after all.
And you played with yourself.
Well... I think you're mistaken.
Sorry for making you feel so bad.
I'm a coward.
But Misaki...
I looked at you as a girl.
As a girl I love...
That's a lie... You did all that with Misaki...
Don't say such stuff now!
I love you!
I didn't want to destroy our relationship as it is now...
But I... I really feel this way.
It's not because the Sagimiya blood.
I... for me it was always only you.
But I held back, because I thought you didn't want it...
I love you too, Shun. I've loved you for so long.
Shun... I've been waiting for you.
I'm fine. If you come all in, the pain will be gone quickly.
You are inside me... Shun...
Shun...
Move as you want. That would make me the happiest.
You could reach me all the way in...
Shun...
My pain's gone too...
How can it feel so good...
You are reaching all the way in me...
I'm feeling weird...
How can this feel so good...
So deep... This pose you're going much deeper!
It's so good to feel you so close to me, Shun...
I can't live without you... without your thing.
My body's numb... I can't think...
Shun... I... can't...
I can't take anymore!
You're filling me...
Shun... Shun... I love you... Shun...
Shun... I never thought you'd return my feelings...
Kagu...
But you took Misaki, took me... Is Mother your next?
Or am I the last? The two of us...
What are you saying?!
Doesn't matter. It's just me from now on.
You're only mine.
Huh?
Here, Shun. Eat this too.
Sure.
What's this atmosphere? It's more cheerful than usual...
Could have they...
You're harder than usual.
Does your ass feel that good?
I'm doing it just as in your magazines. It really does feel good then?
I bet you're on the verge already.
It's okay. My tongue and hands lure your semen out!
Shun...
It's a lot more than usual.
I'm happy you're so happy.
Shun... Next I want you to make me feel good!
Your tongue is in my pussy..
There...
Your tongue is moving all around... I can feel it!
You're so hard again...
Hard as a rock.
There, that feels great!
You're too good, Shun... You're making me crazy.
Shun, with your thing...
Make me feel even better!
You're interested in that one too, I guess.
This feels weird... To put it in there...
My ass is full with you...
My stomach's full with you.
You are in me now...
It feels weird.
Are you all right?
I'm yours. I'm happy with whatever.
It's wet...
Does it feel good? Does my ass feel good?
It really does.
I see. I'm glad then. If you feel good, I...
Shun...
What's this? My ass...
I'm enjoying it with my ass...
This is amazing... Even though it's just my ass...
I'll cum... cum from... my ass...
You too, together!
You are filling my ass...
How can it feel so good?
Your cock is going out of me...
Kagu... Kagu, what are you doing?
He promised it's gonna be just me...
Just because he accepted the blood and became the head of the family...
Misaki?
So now, what are you going to do?
Yeah! You said you chose me!
Tell Kagu that!
But I...
You said you'd dedicate yourself to me.
Isn't that enough?
What are you saying, Kagu? You're imagining things!
Shun, which one of us will you choose?
I can't really do that...
Why can't you just choose?
It's all right, Shun.
I'll wait forever. Take your time deciding.
If it's waiting, I can do that!
Which means...
I guess so.
This is great, Shun!
Your tongue is...
This feels so good, Shun!
So good...
Don't... Kagu... That...
You're so sensitive, Misaki.
This... I can't...
What's this? This feels so good!
I can't take anymore... I'm...
Shun hasn't come yet... Just me...
I'm next.
This is so perverted...
Shun is inside Kagu...
I feel it more with you looking as well...
Shun, you feel bigger than usual!
It's so thick!
Misaki... that...!
It's in so deep!
With Shun's thing and Misaki's tongue I'm about to go crazy!
It's amazing! Feels like I'm about to melt...
Shun, I can't take anymore!
Please, fill me...
Shun's semen is flowing in me...
Shun, the seeds of your babies are in me...
Shun, it was wonderful.
Shun's semen! It's not fair that it's all Kagu's!