I've always... been just her lookout.
D-Damn it!
It's as if sperm is coming out of her mouth.
Contents. 2 [ ~ Ruma ~ ]
Stretta: The Animation
Hmm... so you're into these kinds of things...
Recently, since you haven't been asking me for help with your studies..
"What could you be doing?" I wondered...
A-Amatsu!
D-Don't make so much noise.
You'll get reprimanded, right?
W-What are you doing here...
I've... been looking for you, you know...
Just kidding~!
A-Amatsu!
Shh... don't make so much noise!
B-But...
So you prefer erotic pictures on the Internet to a real girl?
Of course n-
A-Amatsu-san...
It's becoming bigger...
You've been saving up?
Let me lick it for you...
You're not done yet, right?
Do me from the back...
Doing it in a place like this also is quite thrilling, isn't it?
Go ahead, come.
I won't be able to stop myself from moaning...
Hey, don't be so violent...
Amatsu-san, I'm gonna, again...
Eh, already?
You too, Amatsu-san, you're squeezing me so hard inside...
Go ahead... and come... just like this!
What fruitful harvest!
With this, no worries about not having enough stuff to masturbate to for a while.
I guess it's about time I went and called Okada-kun out.
Fruit juice is delicious!
"Ah?" isn't what you should be saying!
Hime-chan, what's wrong?
No idea, my belly is blocking the view of my feet.
W-What?
Hime-chan. don't look at her in,the eye, let's go.
Yeah. I'm starving.
Unbelievable...
The usual place
Today, how many days has it been?
Who knows?
You haven't been masturbating at all since?
You've been stroking yourself-every night. Am I right?
I... haven't.
Is it really that much of a waste to do it by yourself?
If you're gonna come, do it inside me.
D-Don't be stupid-
You know, whenever I drink the semen from a guy...
I can go oh for three days without eating anything.
Strange, isn't it?
Maybe I'm not even... human.
Your partner isn't here yet, though?
Nobody is coming today.
My mouth, and my pussy...
...they're all made to be erotic.
My body is designed for sex.
Look.
Long, isn't it?
S-Stop it.
To hear that from someone who's gotten so big down there...
Not very convincing at all.
My tongue feels good, you know.
My saliva... amazing, isn't it?
It forms bubbles so easily...
Not enough, huh?
Well then.
Use here too.
Look.
You do know that it's moving, right?
It's like a living thing, isn't it?
Okada-kun, you stare too much.
Just kidding!
Ero-lotion...
Go ahead.
Well, how's my pussy?
I know... the exact size, and shape... of your cock, from my pussy...
Amazing...
So rough...
Do your best!
Your cock is twitching...
Are you gonna come?
Come inside my mouth, spray it onto my tongue!
A-Amazing...
Maybe... Okada-kun, this sperm... from your blood!
Look...
Girls have three holes to use for fucking.
The mouth...
The pussy...
...and here.
"Here", you mean...
Complete conquest of all my holes. Well?
I'll rub your dick using my anal muscles, okay?
You can see it all, right?
It's going inside my ass...
Well? It's your first time having anal sex, isn't it?
Go ahead, come just like this inside my ass!
Okada-kun, you're spraying so much sperm...
...inside a girl's ass!
You... pervert!
No need to rest?
M-My ass... amazing!
Okada-kun, have you gone crazy?!
Coming!
No, no! Coming? That's a girl's... hole, you know?!
Are you gonna... come inside?
Y... You came inside...
Ah, no!
W-Wait no way!
You're using me however much you want now...
You'll be done soon, right? Okada-kun.
You're not human.
Maybe... you're a beast?