Kouichi, I'm...
Makoto
In the summer break my childhood friend cousin's coming to the capital.
She's rude, wild and boyish.
She put me through quite a lot of trouble when we were hanging out.
But I think I still loved her.
That day...
Stupid Kouichi!
We fought, and then we moved before we could make up.
I haven't met her ever since.
Coming!
Hey! It's been a while, Kouichi.
Yeah, it has... Makoto.
You grew your hair.
Thanks for the meal!
It was really good!
Really?
I'm so happy!
I practiced a lot to get better!
I'll wash the dishes then.
Sorry for the trouble.
Don't worry about it.
Just take it easy.
Okies...
Has she always been that cute?
She's totally different from back then.
And has she forgotten about that?
Makoto, want some tea?
Makoto?
Oh, she's asleep.
She's... became really pretty.
I must apologize about that fight.
And then...
Makoto?!
Makoto...
No-no, I can't! What am I thinking?
Yeah, I wanted to apologize...
If I did this, I'd be beyond all hope...
But does she remember that fight at all?
Could it be it's just me making a fuss about it?
But still...
What takes you so long?!
Whoopsie.
Your hair!
That doesn't matter! Why didn't you do anything?!
You like gentle, long-haired girls, don't you?
What kind of girls do you like, Kouichi?
Why would you care?
Just tell me!
Well, cute and girlish, with long hair.
What?! That's my exact opposite!
You know I can't grow my hair long!
Do you hate me so much?!
That's not it! Don't be stupid, I just--
I don't care! Stupid Kouichi!
I thought you hated me for that.
Then you moved away too.
You remembered that...
How could I forget it?
I remembered it all the time.
Am I wrong for still loving you?
Don't you get it, stupid...
Makoto, I'm sorry!
I love you too!
I've loved you all along!
But...
But my hair's still short...
Who cares about that?
But I'm rude...
And I'm childish...
That's not true! You're really cute.
Really? But...
But... Wait!
Why did you put that back on?
I told you I don't care how long your hair is.
Because it's embarrassing.
I feel like I can be more honest this way.
Is it bad?
It's fine.
No... Not my nipples...
It feels weird...
Don't....
Makoto, it's like it's on fire.
Kouichi...
Makoto, can I?
Huh? Wait...
Let me do it first.
H-hold on.
Put your cock there...
Makoto...
It's fine.
It's tough...
Are you okay?
Don't overdo it.
It's okay. It doesn't hurt at all.
Instead it feels great!
I guess it's because I practiced thinking of you...
You practiced?
You can move, Kouichi...
Make me feel great, okay?
Say, does it feel good?
Does it feel good in me?
Yeah, it... feels great...
I'm... I'm really happy!
Kouichi, do it... do it harder!
It feels... so great!
Kouichi!
Makoto, I can't hold back...
Give it to me like this!
Something bursted inside me...
Kouichi...
I can still go on.
No! I don't...
Don't look! It's embarrassing!
Stupid!
Why did you take it off?
I want to have sex with you, not the wig!
But... But if I don't have it on, I'll say uncute stuff again!
That's not true!
You're cute! You're cute as you are!
I told you!
I love you as you are!
But, Kouichi...
Kouichi... Kouichi!
Kouichi... Kouichi, I lo-love you!
Why did you lie?
I was so embarrassed!
And we were kids too.
Oh geez! I was embarrassed too!
Crap, I've been so roundabout just because you had to hide your embarrassment.
I learnt to cook and grew my boobs...
Well, I couldn't fix my hair though.
I'm sorry, okay?
And what do you mean you grew your boobs?
How was I supposed to figure that one out?
It was so different from how you usually acted.
Throwing questions like that at me suddenly...
Huh? So now it's my fault?
Kouichi, wait a little more!
You put that on again?
I can cook better with it on.
And aren't you happy to see a girl you love in the kitchen?
Come on, I even apologized...
Stop, that's not a good idea...
Stop...
No...
Quit it.
Could it be you get turned on from putting it on?
No! Stupid!
Then why don't you have a bra on?
But...
How about this?
Don't...
You've got undies on...
Stop...
Actually... I was practicing dressed like this...
Practicing dirty things...
So....
That turned my switch on...
Whoa, so this is Kouichi's thing...
I didn't look carefully before.
This huge thing went in me...
I don't know if I can do it well, but I'll try.
Good luck...
Is this okay?
Kouichi?
It feels good to him...
I'm happy.
Even I enjoy it...
Kouichi... Kouichi...
It's getting bigger...
A bit more...
It's so hot!
Sorry, Makoto!
This is how Kouichi tastes?
Is there some more left in?
Did it feel good?
Yeah...
Take me... please...
It's so wet...
Don't say weird stuff, stupid!
I'm putting it in!
It's in... I put it in again by myself...
That you did...
It's so big, Kouichi!
I think it might be even better than yesterday!
It's great!
Stupid!
This position's so embarrassing!
But you're on the verge of cumming alone!
You're moving so hard!
Stupid!
Something feels tingling down there...
Could you put it here? Around here?
Yeah, deep like that!
Oh, I'm about to cum!
Let's continue... there... on the bed...
Let me reach the top like this, Kouichi...
I'm doing this, Makoto!
It's so deep in me!
It feels great! It's hitting so deep!
It's tickling me!
You are filling me up completely!
Do it... harder!
Do it deeper!
Oh...
It feels great when you do that to my nipple...
It's great...
Oh, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, Kouichi! Kouichi!
Makoto, I'm cumming!
Give me... Give me lots of it!
Kouichi, I'm cumming!
Makoto, you were so cute...
Stupid!
Ouch!
This is what you get for stopping me while I'm cooking.
I'll get it ready soon. Let's eat together, Kouichi!
Then let's have another round.
Kouichi, I'm done!
Kouichi?
He's asleep...
Hey, Kouichi!
Kouichi!
Wake up! It's time to eat!
Kouichi, don't you dare just snore there
after making me cook something great for you!
Wake! Up! Already!
Makoto...
Monkey!
Who did you call a monkey?!
Not me, right?!
Hey, Makoto!
Don't "hey" me! Who did you call a monkey?!
I might or might not kill you based on your answer!
Ah, monkey?
Yeah, you were amazing back then...
You were jumping around on branches like a monkey...
So it was really me?!
You'll pay for this!
You woke up?
Wait, that look...
Yep, naked with an apron!
You're late noticing. It's your fault for pretending to be asleep.
But that's quite amazing. You're like some pervert.
Do you have to say stuff like that?!
Do you have any idea how much I had to practice?
You said that before too. You practiced dirty stuff.
You're so proud of masturbating?
You've got really lewd.
Yep, I'm lewd.
You opened up!
Every day I was thinking of you,
and did lots and lots things.
I'll show you all of it!
Saying it in a cute way won't save you.
You were running around healthily in the mountains,
then you decided to catch that huge frog at the pond!
I like frogs!
You can never know what they're thinking!
And crabs?
I hate crabs.
They hurt.
That's not the point!
I get lewd because of you!
It's the same as back then. I'm the happiest when we're together.
Makoto...
And you know... you know...
There's this thing I wanted to try...
Can you take me from this way too?
Can't you?
You're really lewd.
Come on...
By the way, you've been naked all along, Kouichi.
Whoopsie!