Eisen Faust's behind it all.
It's his fault that Ichiro became a tentacle monster!
To prevent the return of the evil sorcerer Faust,
it would've been enough to infiltrate the evil's ranks,
but he caught us because he could easily control Ichiro!
If this goes on, we can't save Ms Yuko either.
Come to your senses already, Ichiro you moron!
Episode 4: I get the harem end!
Ichiro!
Ichiro, wake up already!
When did I fall asleep?
Don't just sleep after pumping me fuill of semen, you freak!
Uh...
Looks like I conceived just like Ms Yuko...
You're like some breeding horse.
He even made me pregnant!
Shut up! It's all because Eisen caught you!
You fail as an Inquisitioner!
Lame! Loser!
Silence, you immature witchling.
What?! We came all this way to save you!
Ichiro, shut her mouth with your tentacles!
Can I really?
You woke up at the best of times, boy.
You!
Let us resurrect my master now.
Lily!
Something's coming out!
Something's trying to come out of me!
I'm not gonna lose!
I'll help you!
Don't touch Lily with your filthy tentacles!
Only I can touch her!
I never gave you permission either!
Pathetic kid.
My body won't move!
Watch the solemn ceremony of birth!
What?
What're you gonna do with that?!
Don't open it so wide!
It'll come out! That thing inside me will come out!
Don't spread it so wide!
It'll come out! I'll give birth to it!
I can feel it coming! From the core of my body!
I won't lose to your drugs!
Not there!
That's not for putting in anything!
It's moving!
It's raping me where I pee!
How can my pee hole feel this good?!
It took my... It took my pee hole virginity!
I didn't let even Ichiro do that!
Lily...
No, don't look at me, Ichiro!
I don't want to see me enjoying getting raped in my pee hole!
It's coming! I can't hold it back!
Ichiro saw me... cum and pee at the same time...
You'll tear... You'll tear them off if you pull so hard!
Not such a big one! It's impossible!
It hurts! My asshole's splitting!
It's so thick!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming with my ass this time!
I cummed! Don't do it so harsh now! I cummed!
My ass will break! I won't be able to close my asshole anymore!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming again!
I can feel it... It's so thick!
Spread it wider! Open my asshole so wide I can't close it again!
It's coming! Something's coming out of me!
Give birth to them!
The keys to my master's rebirth!
It's coming! I'm giving birth!
I'm cumming from giving birth to that thing!
It's coming! My baby larva...
My baby larva's making me cum!
Don't suck on it! I'll cum again!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from my baby larva sucking my milk!
The preparations are complete now.
You shall become the vessel for my master!
What?!
My... My body!
I did it! Finally!
Now only one step's left!
Look! This is the heart of my master.
If I transplant this into you, he will be reborn.
Transplant his heart?
Then what about mine?
It's in the way.
Doesn't that mean I'm gonna die?!
I only need a body with magic in its veins.
Give your life to my great master, Faust!
Farewell!
I can't move!
I'm done for!
Lily!
You might be weak, but show me you can grow!
I should've just killed you after you gave birth.
I'm not the kind to give up!
Heart of the mother, show me your wrath!
Wash away the evil!
Ichiro!
I can move! I can move!
Eisen's magic is lifted!
Lily!
For me...
I'm sorry. I can't leave you behind.
I'll fight!
Give it up, boy.
I'm full of power.
I can do it with this body.
That body isn't something for the likes of you.
It's my body! It's mine!
You forgot, boy?
You wasted the chance your lover gave you.
Damn! Move, body!
I'll kill your bitch first, so that she won't get in the way anymore.
Stop!
Who do you think you are comm--
I'll fight!
To protect the ones I love!
No way! My magic!
I'll protect Ms Yuko! Kaya! And Lily!
What's going on?!
What just happened?
How was my spell lifted?! Answer me!
My dear, mischievous witch gran, left me this to protect Ms Yuko.
And her love is what saved me from the claws of evil.
Don't even dream of it!
Your body's already my master's!
Eisen Faust!
You already died in the middle ages!
Your vengeance is what lived on to throw the world off balance!
Silence!
My master's secrets were passed down in long history!
Don't you dare talk lightly of them again!
You must fall!
You failure of a wizard!
I lifted your spell.
The broach my gran left me awakened my power.
No way! This power!
It's apparently called Animation.
It's what your master seeked so much.
No way! A brat like you couldn't possibly...
I'm Tachibana Ichiro, the grandson of the Witch of the Sun.
I'm a wizard of life!
Then you're all the more fit to be my master's vessel!
Rest along with your medieval vengeance,
Eisen Faust!
You won't do what I ask for?
Even though I healed your wounds with my great life magic.
But you can't use magic anymore!
I just pitied your begging and came here!
But you liked it, didn't you?
Don't get it wrong, you freak!
What's this?
I don't know!
You're so sensitive.
Shut up!
How dare you do this to me? I won't forget this!
So that's how you're gonna act, Lily?
Are you sure?
Ms Yuko!
And Kaya Blanche!
If you're always so mean to him, Ichiro will leave you!
Ichiro, let's ignore that flat-chested girl,
and enjoy my huge breasts while having sex!
It's not like I got addicted to the smell of your semen or anything!
I'll... I'll give myself to you out of my own volition.
So I'll get two fuckmates instead of Lily?
You mustn't! I'll have sex with you!
Really?
You made me wear these erotic underwear, and my pussy's already sopping wet!
Please take me and mess me up with your cock!
You're my favorite bitch, Lily.
Why make the three of us lie down?
I'll grope-compare you!
You start with my boobs!
I'm happy, Ichiro.
Your big and soft boobs are so nice!
So sudden! So strong!
Your boobs are a lot more stringy.
It's a whole different feel than Ms Yuuko's.
But my boobs...
What?! I don't have boobs!
Lily's nipples on her tiny boobs are the best!
Is that even a praise?!
This is my thanks for you.
Hurray! I'm first to get Ichiro's cock!
Your cock feels bigger than usual!
It's spreading my pussy so much!
Ichiro, give my pussy some love too!
It's crying itself wet with loneliness!
We're not done yet!
Excuse me!
It's been so long since I could last enjoy your cock!
You shouldn't stop in the middle...
You shouldn't keep him all to yourself! No matter the reason!
You want it too, right, Kaya?
Let's dig in!
Are you really fine with taking someone like me?
I wouldn't mind being the last!
I promised you we'd have sex properly this time!
Thanks for remembering that!
Looks like Kaya'll get the first load.
He's gonna cum if you move so wild!
Kaya'll take Ichiro's semen!
Sorry for the wait, Lily!
I won't let anyone take you from me!
I'm impaling myself on Ichiro's rock hard cock!
Come! Come inside!
Enter my lewd womb!
It's not going in!
Your cock isn't entering my womb!
It'll go in this way.
It's in!
Your cock's in my womb!
Amazing! I can feel your cock hitting my womb!
Whoa! It's like my womb's stuck to your cock!
I won't let you go!
I won't let you go until you cum in my pussy!
I'm cumming!
Give me your seed!
I'll fill your lewd womb with my semen!
Okay, Ichiro!
Pour it in me!
I'll be your breeding girl!
Fill my womb with it!
Here comes the semen!
It's filling up my womb!
It's overflowing my pussy!
My womb's so happy you cummed in me!
It's in spasms of happiness!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming with my happy womb!
Hey!
You must have some more left, right?
Whoa, Ms Yuko's boobs in my face!
Don't bite on it!
I can't hold back my nipple-cocks!
Don't pull it!
You'll end up tearing it off!
I'm cumming!
My nipple-cocks are cumming!
My pussy's tired! Don't scrape my womb!
Give it some juice!
Give me semen!
Fill me with your semen!
Ichiro's semen is overflowing in my pussy!
You're next, Kaya.
Show me your butt.
Like this?
I'll give you lots of semen, Kaya.
You're so vulgar! Though I don't mind it!
Fill my pussy with your smelly cum!
Soft.
Gotcha! I'm not letting go of you now!
It's so dirty!
Thank me for cleaning it nicely!
Aren't you hard again?!
Your peerless perverted cock still hasn't got enough?!
What can I do about that?
Your blowjob feels so good.
So it's my fault now?
You're cheeky, Ichiro!
I'll do this then!
It feels too good, Lily!
I'm cumming!
Drink it all!
I'll drink it!
I'll drink all your filthy smelly seme--
I'll give it a good cleaning too!
You should try too, Kaya.
Two girls on my cock! I'm the happiest man!
You should taste the semen well, Kaya.
Like this?
Hey, don't take my semen!
But I only got a little!
If you want so much, I can give you more!
More! More!
Fill my mouth and pussy with your semen!
I'm cumming!
I'll take even more so that you won't cheat on me!
Should we go watch the sunrise?
It's really pretty as it rises from the horizon.
I don't think I can stand up now...
I see...
You'll have invite me again!
Lily, let's do it more!
Okay!
Let me introduce a transfer student!
Come in!
So cute!
Kaya!
I'm Kaya Blanche. Nice to meet you!
Don't be so happy about it, stupid Ichiro!
Come on!