Don't run so fast, you'll fall!
It's okay!
You worry too much, Brother!
Really?
I'll be fine!
I told you! You've been a klutz all your life!
Thank you... Brother...
Brother, you perv!
You've grown too, Kasumi...
That's not what I mean!
Kasumi
A dream, huh?
It's not like I'm the only one home.
Always this stuff...
Brother, that's mine.
I know.
Brother!
Thanks, Brother!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You'll catch a cold if you sleep there.
I'm not sleeping.
You take a sick leave and never return.
Many become neets that way.
Not me.
I've read up on this because of Kasumi.
I get it.
I wonder. As if Kasumi didn't give me enough trouble.
I said I get it...
But Mom...
What?
I wonder why did she become a shut-in.
That's a good question.
Didn't you say you'd read up on this?
It's different for everyone, how could I know?
What could be the reason? I wonder.
Hey, have you got a boyfriend?
You're interested?
Not really. I was just wondering.
And what about you, Brother?
You're interested?
Not really.
Whatevs.
It's since then that Kasumi started acting weird.
What? You can't come?
Why? Something came up suddenly?
See, I have this drama I want to watch tomorrow...
But yesterday you didn't say anything about that!
Because I forgot about it!
But...
You know, I don't like it if a guy is clingy like that.
No, I'm not...
Oh well, if you have something to watch, that's okay.
I'm looking forward to next time, okay?
Yeah, too bad it's not tomorrow.
I managed to get her to agree on a date,
and now it's all for nothing.
And for a TV show? Are you serious?
I'll have to cancel the restaurant reservation I guess.
That'll cost me too...
Kasumi?
See, I was to go with a friend from my company,
but something came up so it won't work.
I reserved it already, so I don't want it to go to waste.
So, you know.
Like a date?
She's always in her room.
Her hair is a mess, and she always wears the same oversized sweater.
Is she taking baths every day at all?
So, how about eating out together?
Lately we haven't really hung out, have we?
I know it's embarrassing to go with your brother,
but I think it's good if you get out of the house every now and then.
Really?
Then tomorrow when I finish at work,
let's meet at the restaurant, okay?
Umm...
Well...
I was surprised when I saw you.
Lately I've hardly seen her face at all.
She's been hiding behind her hair.
And her oversized clothes were hiding it,
but she's grown quite nice.
Oh wait, I shouldn't look at my sister like that.
Sorry, Kasumi. I need to take a rest.
What am I even thinking?
I'm seriously drunk. Why else would it be like this?
She's my sister!
Kasumi!
What are you doing?
You're kidding right?
Hey, stop!
Don't be stupid, this shouldn't...
It's hard...
I'm just...
I want to do this to you.
Huh?
Hey!
Hey, Kasumi!
Stop... I'm cumming!
There's a lot. I'm happy.
What are you doing...
Didn't it feel good?
No, it felt amazing...
But that's not the point!
We're siblings!
Do you understand what that means?
I love you.
I've loved you all along, Brother.
You cared about me,
you were nice to me,
you said I'm cute.
But someone like me is still no good?
Kasumi, you're hanging your head again.
You could say it clean and clear.
I'm a failure as a brother.
I'm happy that my sister confessed to me.
Brother...
Brother!
Brother, I think...
I'm putting it in.
It's tight.
Kasumi, are you all right?
I'm so happy I can feel you in me!
Brother...
Brother!
I'm sorry...
It's just today...
From tomorrow I'll be your sister again.
Kasumi, don't say a thing.
Say...
Are you really fine with this, Brother?
And you? Are are you truly ok with this?
Don't run so fast, you'll fall!
It's okay!
You worry too much, Brother!
Really?
I'll be fine!
I told you! You've been a klutz all your life!
Thank you... Brother...
Brother, you perv!
I wanted him to touch me...
Just him.
It's evening already.
Welcome home, Brother.
Hey, I'm back.
You should just act like back then!
Or something.
Kasumi?
That me is only yours. I can't act like that all the time.
Just when I'm with you.
Look Kasumi, this inn looks amazing!
They have an open-air bath in every room!
I was lucky and could get a reservation.
So, you know.
Look at this, Kasumi!
We have our open-air bath! You're fine with this, right?
Do you want to go in?
Or rather after dinner...
Let's go in together now.
I can't believe we're having a bath together like this.
I couldn't pay more attention to you lately.
I'll make you feel good next.
It's good...
Kasumi, it's really good.
Kasumi!
Brother...
I'm going in.
I'm almost there...
Me too!
Together...
I'm cumming!
You filled me...
Hot springs are really nice...
We should have a bath after dinner too.
Before we go home, ten times at least!
Not only in the bath...
We should make out in the bed too.
Yeah, I just thought that now we're at a hot spring we should use the opportunity...
Ten times at least!