20...
19...
Here's my second command.
Always pick me from now on.
Kei!
Takatou...
Hey! We're done with this now, aren't we?
Don't be ridiculous.
It has been judged that the
conditions were satisfactorily fulfilled.
With this, the first turn is over.
The recess begins now.
As soon as recess ends, the next turn will start.
You guys must be tired.
You should try to get some rest during recess.
Finding out more about the situation we're in is more important.
What good will that do?
The voice on the intercom explained the rules just fine.
We should be fine if we obey it.
I don't disagree.
I still don't think it would be impossible to improve our situation ourselves.
I don't like this.
Can't we somehow escape this place?
Just wanting to escape will get you killed, you know?
Manaka, please don't joke about that.
Oh boy, did I make the kindergarten my enemy?
Don't fight, everyone.
Don't get even more worked up when you're already tired.
Let's try to get some rest.
Sorry.
I want to look into this place.
I wish we had somewhere to at least sit down.
I'm hungry.
Are you going out with Manaka?
I saw you two kissing.
That was...
I don't want her to know.
You see...
Choose me if you want.
We can't let Manaka bear it all.
You see, I...
wouldn't mind if it's you...
Kanae...
Drinking
Water
Toilet
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
Let's go.
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
0...
Confirming.
All players have lined up before the door in good order.
Would the Solver please step forward?
Please decide on a Lock for this turn.
30...
29...
28...
27...
26...
25...
24...
23...
22...
21...
I just have to pick someone.
Always pick me from now on.
I don't want anyone else to find out what Nemu knows.
So what do I do?
I could go the safe path and pick Nemu like in turn one,
and I could disobey her.
Whatever I do...
No, calm down.
The most important thing is giving off the impression that I'm playing by the rules.
So, what now?
Whom do I go for?
Whom do I pick?
Hokari Kanae.
The Lock and Solver are asked to move to the indicated room.
Beginning countdown.
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
It has been confirmed that both have entered the room.
I picked Kanae from all those girls lined up before me.
It was my own decision.
I was happy that you choose me.
You don't have to be gentle.
Let's try to escape this place.
Lock: Genital Organs
Ejaculation Count: 1
These are the release parameters.
Comments: Hard
Finally.
Will I take her virginity here?
Wait, get a grip man!
That was the whole reason you picked her in the first place.
Is she afraid?
No... I don't think so.
I've seen this before. I remember it.
No... Kei, wait.
Kanae...
I-I-It hurts!
It hurts!
My virginity...
It hurts, it hurts!
Kei!
Yes, Kanae!
That expression!
Do you hate this? Do you?
Yes! More!
Your cock is stabbing into my vagina!
Yo-You're raping me!
It hurts! It hurts!
I wanted to see your face twisted by pain.
Kanae...
Release confirmed.
The Solver and the Lock may exit the room at their leisure.
Three turns are left, right?
Yeah.
I'll go take a shower and get dressed.
My relationship with her is warping little by little.
Is it it okay...?
Is it okay if it warps any more than this?
No way, right?
Tell me, Kanae.
Why am I imagining these things?
My consciousness is detaching from reality.
This white room that seems like a nightmare,
has turned into our everyday life.
I feel brutal and sadistic feelings well up inside me.
I don't want to be around Kanae.
Two turns done now.
Three are left.
Will you pick her for the rest?
Mind your own business.
Go away.
Nope.
What now?
Don't complain if you force my hand.
I love fallen beings.
You're suffering.
No shit, Sherlock.
Do you really think this affects you?
Sure.
I mean, you have a woman you really want, right?
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
You made her scream in pain,
and you want to wrench open the lock of her flesh.
The flesh called a girl.
Shut the fuck up!
You can torture and punish the girl you're attached to.
You can punish and torture her,
and in the midst of your sadism,
you ejaculate.
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
Your neck would be improved by strangling,
your beautiful hair by staining,
and your eyes by gouging!
And here you stand!
No!
Don't, Kei!
Don't!
That went perfectly until she came.
You didn't catch what I said, huh?
Dying is the greatest pleasure!
Stop this now!
Don't cause Kei so much pain.
Are you his wife or something ever since he picked you as Lock?
I'm his childhood friend!
I've understood him for much longer than you!
You're just a sex toy he raped.
I don't mind.
I love him.
Well that's a surprise.
Are you hoping to be his personal slave with your cute antics?
I don't give a shit whether you're his childhood friend or not,
but I know a side of his you don't.
You lie!
Stop, Nemu!
I'm the one who understands him.
Stop it!
Stop it now!
Don't worry, Kei.
I don't care what they say.
Kanae...
Okay?
She's stroking my cheek.
She's gentle.
Gentle.
She's doing it to hold my madness at bay.
Please decide on a Lock.
Hokari Kanae.
Lock decided.
She smiles when I designate her.
To smile there is just...
Human Toilet
I'm sure she would accept whatever cruelty I throw at her.
That's why I shouldn't.
More, more...
I don't think I could put an end to it.
Hokari Kanae.
This is getting out of hand.
My feelings, my impulses, my greed...
It's all getting completely out of hand.
Hokari Kanae.
It has been confirmed that both have entered the room.
Don't say that anymore.
Tell what?
What you told Nemu.
"I don't care what he does."
Oh, that.
I just can't bear it.
Lock: Nipples, Genital Organs, Rectum
I can't bear to hand you over to Manaka.
Ejaculation Count: Arbitrary
Comments: Hard
I don't want to lose you to Manaka.
I've always loved you.
I'm the one who knows you best!
Right?
Kanae...
I can do everything.
So, Kei...
Look at me.
Your cunt is pretty fat and colorless.
There's not much blood in your boobs either.
Have you been masturbating in secret?
No... I've never masturbated.
You know what comes now.
I want to see you in pain.
I know.
My body is yours.
My Master's.
You're my property, my slave.
Yes, Master.
My nipples!
They're going numb...
I feel the current...
What are you going to do if this causes you pain already?
You'll get us all killed.
No! I won't!
I'll never...
let you...
die.
Do you understand, Kanae?
There are two powered vibrators in your cunt and ass right now.
Do you know which is on right now?
I have no idea... which of the two... is on...
Press them together a little and you'll know.
The one in my butt.
Exactly.
Here's your reward.
Does it hurt?
I feel the current going through me.
It tickles in my pussy.
I'm a little afraid.
I feel it tingling inside my pussy and my butt.
The current is going through...
It's tingling all the way through my stomach.
Do you like it?
You're sure getting wet.
I'm getting wet from the current.
Doesn't seem like you're in pain.
Your body is consumed by greed and lewdness.
No.
It hurts.
I'm in pain.
No, Kanae, you're in heaven.
You will like whatever comes now.
Got it?
Okay.
I will.
Whatever comes.
Tell me.
Okay.
It feels good...
to have the current inside me.
Next one.
Do you like it, Kanae?
You like this, right?
Tell me you do!
Yes!
I like it!
The electricity feels great.
Looks like we're still good.
If the electricity torture feels good, you must be screaming for more.
I'm fine!
I can do it!
I like the electricity torture.
Crank it up!
It hurts! It hurts!
You like this, don't you?
You like this tingling pain, right?
I-d-o.
I-like-the-vibrators-raping-my-pussy-and-butt.
It's off the charts.
A normal woman should a gone insane from such voltage.
Although I'm already using an almost lethal doses...
Now...
This is the end.
This will keep up until you say you like it.
Yes, even if it tears apart your insides, your ass, your cunt, all of you.
Y-e-s...
Kanae...
Do you like it?
Y-e-s... I-l-i—
I-t-s-o-o-z-i—
Tell me you like it.
Tell me you do, Kanae.
I do! It's great.
It feels great to be broken.
Amazing.
Is this the Kanae I know?
Right.
I'm the one who drove the gentle Kanade I know to scream out her agony, almost fainting.
Do you like it, Kanae?
You do, right?
Yes!
I like it!
Cute Kanae...
My sweet Kanae...
Now she is more messed up... and more beautiful... than I ever thought possible.
Ouc—
Kei!
Fill me up, Kei!
Give me a minute!
Wait! Please!
It feels weird!
My head goes funny when you thrust it in!
No! I'll come!
It's going all the way in.
You're going to come inside.
If you come inside you'll get me pregnant!
I'm gonna have your baby!
I'm gonna come!
I've had sex so often but when you're in me, I come!
I'm coming!
Cum is leaking out...
I'm really going to be pregnant from so much cum.
What are you doing, Kei?
That one is wrong!
It hurts, Kei!
Are you serious?
Yes!
I can't get enough of your pain!
My butt!
It hurts!
Kei...
I always wanted this.
The one I want to protect the most in this world
is the one I want to break the most.
That's Kanae!
I'm coming! Coming!
Kanae!
Kei!
It's coming out of my butt.
So much is in me.
Kei...
Release confirmed.
Stage cleared.
I did well, didn't I?
You did.
I'm proud of you.
Am I ugly?
No!
I couldn't look away from you.
There's nothing ugly about you.
I see. That makes me glad.
This is the end.
With this we can leave.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
At last the final door opens.
A new world opens to Kanae and me.
Good morning.
How are we feeling today?
Yes, yes, good boy.
All right... let's take your temperature.
Hey, hey...
Something white just flew from your cock.
Came already?
This man can't remember his name.
Left to him are only the impulses of an animal,
and nothing resembling human reason.
Cute.
Poor Kei.
But don't worry.
I'm here.
I won't abandon you.
Relax.
Your beloved lives.
Water... water...
Please...
Toilet water
Forever... together.
Hokari Kanae   End of Paradise Chapter