What would you want in a bar like this, girlie?
Get out! She's here for you, isn't she?!
Do something about her!
Don't need to tell me! I'm on it!
Calm down!
You're Otonashi Miki, right?
My brother went missing. I want you to find him.
I came looking for him dressed like this,
but I can't do it alone after all.
But the famous detective Annerose could surely help me!
That's what the brown-skinned lady said!
Brown-skinned?
Ah, you mean Ms. Aishwarya?
I'm impressed you came here alone.
This town is dreadful.
The scene is the largest ghost city in Japan, Amidahara.
There is a slum there called the Freedom of Darkness,
where humans and demons mingle and coexists.
Assassins and criminals are in a strife for power day and night.
It's a lawless land.
Rikurou? Tachibana Rikurou?
Are you listening at all?
Of course I am, Miki.
Is something weird with my breasts?
No, it's just been a long while since I last saw a human girl.
I was so happy I spaced out.
Please leave it to me.
We'll find your brother for sure!
Thank you very-
Don't get all syrupy, you fucking human!
The hell are you doing, Michiko?!
I'm done shopping. We're going home!
I'll ask Annerose for you.
See you tomorrow here!
What's taking so long, you fucking human?!
Full Metal Witch: Annerose
Don't get so full of yourself!
Who do you think you are?
Your mistress Michiko. Problem?
You're just lady Annerose's maid!
Don't go ordering me around!
A mere human has no word in front of a full-blown demon.
For fucks sake...
You look cute but you're the moodiest bitch ever.
Let me make this clear.
What?
It'd seem you've got a thing for Annerose, but she's mine alone!
You're in the way, so you should just die here!
Wait, Michiko...
I'll tell her some starved, ferocious wild dogs ate you.
Wait, this isn't funny...
I'm not joking!
Die, fucking human!
Here, doggies, your dinner!
Thank you for saving me! I will--
I like you.
You are mine. My servant.
I see you are awake.
This beauty has been awake for a while though.
Ms. Aish? When did I...?
When did you get hard?
That's not--
It's so lively!
It was rock hard the entire time your body was regenerating.
Anne still knows which cocks are good.
You told that Miki girl about me, right?
Ah, the machine-gun girl?
I'm glad you met her.
Ms. Aish, why are you doing this?
I've been interested in you for a while now.
You're cute, but you have no real good points.
Why would Annerose raise a student like you then?
I want you to tell me that secret.
There's no secr--
This is a secret to your master!
There's so much cheese on your cock.
I'm sorry...
I just realized I like licking the cheese off your cock.
Ms. Aish...
It's stinky and gooey...
I love your cheese!
I like that look in your eyes.
I'll let you see your future.
My future?
Is it your first time taking a mouth?
It... is.
Move harder. You can use my mouth and throat.
Come in deep!
Deep?
Stick it in deep?
Violate my throat!
It's deep! Deep in my throat!
Ms. Aish...
Deeper!
Ms. Aish!
Harder... Stick it harder in my throat!
It's going straight into my throat pussy!
Ms. Aish!
You'll do it to Anne as well once.
You'll use her lips to clean your cock!
Lady Annerose?
Amazing!
It's so thick and delicious!
What's this?
This is your inner world.
I scratched the surface of your power,
and it's amazing.
Your semen almost drove me mad.
What power in me?
You are bound, because a witch stole your soul.
But not just anyone can end up like that.
It's thanks to the immense power that was born with you.
With me?
Even if you're Annerose's pet, Michiko overdid it this time.
Let me help you teach that demon a lesson.
Use this.
What's this?
Try playing it beside her when she's sleeping.
I'm back.
Rick... You're just a slave, where have you been slacking?
Lady Annerose...
You were late so I had to make dinner myself.
Michiko chopped me up...
Again?
Then you're back quite quickly.
Ms. Aish picked me up.
Aish did?
I couldn't get rid of her ever since we were kids.
She's a sadist pervert who enjoys it from her heart
to watch people get into some really big mess.
You're better off without her.
I understand.
I'm going to sleep.
I drank too much because of you.
I should sleep too.
But a certain fucking human should make sure to clean up.
Shut up!
Lady Annerose said what she said,
but I can't let Michiko get away with this!
What was that?
What's this?!
I can't move!
Is that Ms. Aish's magic?
Is it you? You did this to me?
You look lovely, Michiko.
Shut up! Cut me free!
No. Try to remember all the crap you put me through.
All of it?
I cut off your head when we meet...
I put sleeping pills in your food and threw you out...
What else?
Today you chopped me up and left me there.
Right, that!
I even left there some dog food so the hounds would find and eat you.
You're really hard to kill, you fucking human!
So you don't feel like apologizing?
What are you doing?!
It's dangerous to struggle too hard!
It's cold!
Hey!
How dare you cut them all!
Stop!
Done!
Shut up! Don't look, you fucking human!
You can stop acting strong now, Michiko.
Stop...
Don't touch me!
You're so sensitive.
Are you masturbating, you lewd demon?
I... stop!
You should admit it honestly, or this is what you get!
I don't... masturbate!
You should be honest.
This is next!
Stop!
You're really wet. Look! Look!
I'm going to cum!
A fucking human is going to make me cum!
Then cum!
Let your twitching clitoris take over your mind!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Michiko, something's coming out of your pussy.
Don't look!
I'm... wetting... myself... No...
Your pussy is a wet mess.
You're kinda cute, messy Michiko.
Don't say that... Don't...
Look at this.
Are you gonna violate me?
Yeah. I'm gonna violate you now.
It's punishment time.
I'm putting it in.
Your pussy will be full with my cock!
Wait, you're a virgin?
You're gonna pay for this!
I get it.
I'll take this responsibility and form your virgin pussy to fit my cock!
Lick my finger!
Your moans are so lewd!
You must enjoy my cock a lot!
It sucks to admit, but it feels good!
Let's get along well this one time!
Let your womb be mine now!
Don't stick it in so hard!
I'm not used to this yet!
If you do this, people'll say I'm yours, you fucking human!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming into your pussy!
No! I don't want you in me...
No!
I don't want to, but my pussy is cumming!
You were amazing, Michiko.
You ok?
I'll kill you.
Looks like you're still not my woman.
Then let's call this a truce for now.
Can I punish you again?
I can't stop you...
I'll punish you a bit more and turn you into my whore.
It's morning!
I must wake up Lady Annerose!
It always surprises me how defenseless she is in her sleep.
This is Lady Annerose, the Fullmetal Witch who all Amidahara fears?
I've held back for so long,
but I can't stop myself today!
But if she woke up...
Lady Annerose has amazingly low blood pressure.
It'll be okay!
Be brave, Tachibana Rikurou!
You're a man!
Amazing!
So soft!
It's her fault for exciting me every day!
She's enjoying it!
It was worth living!
These are Lady Annerose's boobs from my dreams!
I can't stop! I'm doing it!
Could it be she's awake?
She's awake and she's accepting me?
Her nipples are so hard!
She's enjoying my cock!
Her boobs are so soft... and warm...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Amazing! I've covered her face with my sperm!
Here, Lady Annerose! Drink all my semen!
It's still not enough? I get it.
This? Or this way, Lady Annerose?
Then I'm doing this.
I'll make you cum with my finger, Lady Annerose!
Cum, Lady Annerose! Cum with your pussy!
My fingers really won't cut it.
I can't satisfy Lady Annerose with my fingers.
I'm putting it in, Lady Annerose.
My cock... is in Lady Annerose's pussy!
I'm in! All the way until I reach her womb!
What? Rick?
Lady Annerose!
This is a dream. Please sleep!
A dream?
No way! She was a virgin too?
Amazing! I'm her first man!
I'll make you feel even better!
Rick!
What?
Lady Annerose! Lady Annerose!
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm cumming! I'll fill you with my hot juice!
I can cum inside, right? Right?
Annerose!
Amazing...
I cummed so much in her! What should I do?
A tissue!
Rick! You're heavy!
I'm just... I...
What exactly did you just do?
How dare the slave give his master a night visit?!
I hope you're ready for the consequences!
I just...
This is your obvious reward.
Lady Annerose...
I've found you, Annerose.
Rick, do you understand what you did to me, you filthy slave?
You were just too enchanting!
Did it feel good to take me?
That was done in the previous episode!
You fucking human, you cummed a lot in me too!
Rick, what's the meaning of this?
I can explain this...
Do you really want to die?
You're going to hell, you fucking human!
Next time, Annerose episode two!
It's gonna be evil!
Hey, who are you?