This phone possessing hypnotic abilities was designed and sent to me
by my father, it has the ability to carve pleasure onto one's heart and body.
Which was put to test on the cute slaves I hypnotized.
Yuna, Nagisa, Lady Himeno, and lastly, Sayuri.
I'm playing a certain gamble with these girls.
Gakuen Saimin Reido
Even though I hated you just a moment ago
No, I'm not pregnant yet
Once their pregnancy is confirmed,
the intense pleasured carved into their bodies from my training
Analysis
Result
will leave them unable to be satisfied with anyone but me.
Someone like you doesn't deserve to live
Then, I'll restore their minds to the point when they were just about to be hypnotized,
You stink too bad to be physically sound
Satou is just a friend
and force them to choose.
They can either choose to protect their self-esteem, battle against the carnal desires,
How filthy, even lower than a bitch
and go back to their previous boring lives.
Or, they can throw everything away, become enslaved by me once again,
I can't live without your cock
Cum inside, and make me cum
There's no way for me to live without you anymore
Rape me hard, and make me pregnant
and bear my children.
It sucks to admit this, but this is driving me crazy.
Being hit like this, my body seems to be going crazy.
I can't go on without your cock anymore.
I'll do anything, so make me your love doll!
My lewd pussy can no longer be satisfied if it's not your cock, Futoshi!
I'll be sure to carry, and raise your children.
So please, rape me more!
Doing something like this to me in front of my fiancée...
No!
If you fuck me that hard, I'm going to lose myself!
Fucking me against my will, and attacking my holes like this...
And even though I'm being forced into sex with this disgusting guy...
Not only my body, but even my heart itself can no longer oppose his disgusting cock!
I'll swear
to bear your children!
So please knock me up!
Sakurazawa Yunna
Serizawa Sayuri
Mizushiro Nagisa
Tatsumiya Himeno
So at the end, none of them managed to leave me, huh?
Regrettably, Himeno experienced a miscarriage, but...
Nagisa really did manage to fool me.
Acting like a lowly bitch, she said she'd give birth to it, but ended up aborting instead.
Even then, the limitless lust preventing her from leaving me is quite cute.
She's quite a bitch.
Well then, why don't I do it with Kaoruko next?
Because of her overly sensitive breasts being teased regularly.
She seems to have taken a liking to titty fucking.
Ah, I'm cumming!
My milk is coming out!
Well then, shall I present her with the final choice too?
Kaoruko, let's kiss!
I love kissing.
E-eh? What was that?
W-what am I doing...?
Here we go, that kiss reverted her mental state to right before the hypnotism,
This can't be! Why?! Hey...
making her remember every part of the training.
What sort of reaction will you show me now, Kaoruko?
S-satou, how could you ...?
To think you'd apply hypnotism to girls,
r-rape them, and making them do so many lewd things...
These are unforgivable by our standards!
Saying those in that pose bears no persuasive prowess at all, Kaoruko.
No..
No!
What happened?
You aren't gonna escape?
Well if that's the case, let's continue!
No! I have a fiancée named Shinya already.
Please stop this!
Oh, hey. Look at Kaoruko saying all this stuff while enjoying sex, Minazuki.
Shinya!
T-this isn't what it...
The only one that I love... is Shinya.
Shut the fuck up, you bitch!
Shinya?!
That was terrible!
The hell is terrible?
I'm the rightful fiancée, and you didn't even let me kiss you
because you wanted to "maintain your purity" till we got married.
And here, you're letting someone like Satou cum inside on his discretion!
That's not it! I'm not letting him do this because I like it!
But during our "practice" sessions, didn't you even let me do anal?
Wearing a wedding dress, you gave me your virginity.
We even exchanged our vows, didn't we?
Stop it!
As a teacher, your job is to educate, but you're even willing to cosplay like that?!
You're the worst.
That's not it!
Satou ordered me to wear this!
Oh my, you were even hiding hobbies like cosplaying from your fiancée?
That's just terrible, teach.
That's not it! This isn't the real me!
If you're willing to bear my child, I'm fine with hypnotizing even Minazuki,
so you two can spend a happily married life.
Stop fucking around!
Who the hell wants to bear your child?!
But, isn't that a bit too late for that?
Did you have your period this month?
No, don't tell me...
There's no way...
That's because we've been doing this everyday,
and I've cum inside countless times.
That must be a lie! I can't be pregnant...
Sense, I'm about to cum!
No! Put it outside!
There's no way I can already be pregnant!
All the more reason to do this, then.
I'm gonna make sure you get pregnant!
No way! I'm begging you, please release it outside!
Don't cum inside!
No!
Climaxing infront of your fiancée while riding another man,
you even let him cum inside...
Just how slutty are you?!
I'm calling off the engagement.
Be happy with your "master".
Please wait! This isn't what it...
Please, don't leave me!
Oh my, so Minazuki completely abandoned you, huh?
I suppose that could not be helped,
since you climaxed infront of your fiancée while being cummed inside by another man
That's not it!
That's... not it.
Well, how about it?
If you agree to my proposal,
even your slutty self will still be loved by Minazuki.
By Shinya?
If you bear my child, you can still get married to Minazuki.
This slutty body of yours is too much for one to handle alone,
so just like before, as fuck buddies, I'll make you feel good!
Doing something like that...
Not there!
You want to marry him, right?
If you keep yourself silent, nobody will ever figure out who the real father is.
If you want, I can even hypnotize everyone into thinking that it's Minazuki's kid.
Now, swear it!
Not there!
If you swear it, you'll be able to obtain happiness with Minazuki.
I can live happily with Shinya...
I swear!
I swear to bear your child!
No! I'm gonna cum!
That completes the deal.
With this, Kaoruko is one of my sex slaves as well.
I'm gonna train you so you can't even think of anyone but me.
Please stop this already!
Doing such things to me day after day...
I'm going to just say this straight.
If you do any more horrible things to me,
I'm going to report to the teachers!
You're abiding everything I told you to today as well, eh?
No! If you do something like that, it's gonna erect itself!
My thing is gonna erect itself!
You still don't seem to understand your own position, it seems.
If you keep up that farce, the one to be suffer is going to be you, no?
It'll be quite a surprise if I were to spread your secret on the official site of the school for everyone, don't you think?
The supposedly beautiful transfer student is nothing but a hermaphrodite,
who can't even control herself enough to go back home, and masturbates at school.
Stop it!
What's even worse that she's indulging herself in sex with the most hated pervert in the school almost every day.
That's not it!
You were the one who did...
Regardless of that, the end result will be the same.
If that secret of yours comes out, you'll be pushed around by the delinquents and the boys will turn on you, don't you think?
On top of that, countless guys will come inside you everyday.
You're sure to get pregnant.
No!
Oh my, did the thought of that turn you on?
Oh, so the thought of pregnancy aroused you?
Well, let's keep on having unprotected sex then!
No, stop it!
I won't defy you anymore,
so please use contraceptives!
If you do things like this to me everyday, and I get pregnant,
there's no way for me to live anymore.
"You'll get pregnant if I cum inside your ass,
that idea I planted inside her through hypnotism seems to be working better than expected."
I can't bear this anymore!
If I were a normal girl, there would be no need for me to suffer like this.
There's no need to lower yourself like that.
It's what I've been saying ever since we started to "love each other," no?
You have a very beautiful body and you know you love this.
No! Don't look! Please, forgive me!
Well, please make sure to come to the usual place then.
If you're late, I'll have to turn on the vibrator.
And, and another thing,
please hold onto these till school ends.
There's also a lewd photo of you inside, so make sure not to lose it.
Aihara!
Yes?
I've got something to talk to you about, have a moment?
You've just transferred in, and you're already putting your grubby little paws on other people's property, aren't you?
Swimming Club, Women's Room
What is this about?
Don't try to fool me.
I'm obviously talking about that fatty.
Fatty?
I'm talking about that disgusting pig Satou!
There must be a misunderstanding,
because I'm not particularly...
That hurts!
You're gonna tear off my breasts!
These must be the reason, huh?
You've probably enticed him with these lewd breasts of yours!
And here I was wondering for the past month why he hasn't contacted me,
and to think he found himself a new woman...
Are you Satou's girlfriend, Mizushira?
Girlfriend?! You must be kidding.
Who the hell wants that guy?!
He's my s-slave, that's right, slave!
If that's so, then please make him stop!
I don't want to be his fuck buddy, or sex slave anymore!
Fuck buddy...
Does that mean you even want to be his lover?!
N-no!
The fact that the fatso pushed me aside and chose you really pisses me off!
Very well then, I'll make it so I don't have to hear that voice of yours ever again!
No!
W-what's this thing I'm feeling?!
N-no, please stop!
I'm sensitive there!
Noo...
You're...
a transvestite?!
N-no, I'm a girl.
Oh? I've just thought of something nice.
No, stop this!
Please don't take photos of my embarrassing posture.
You've even got a vibrator in your ass.
If these photos were to be released thoughout the school,
the boys will almost unanimously rape you.
Afterwards, just like you wished, the fatty will dump you.
Oh, but you've still got that disgusting penis attached to you,
so nobody will probably even go close to touching you.
It's different! That's my clitoris!
I'm a girl, I don't have a penis attached!
Well, what was that you splashed onto my face a while ago?!
T-that is... it's how my sensitive clit behaves when touched
Are you retarded?
No matter how you look at it, that was an ejaculation.
Well, whatever.
I'm gonna use this little toy you had,
and photograph your posture when you release in detail.
W-what are you gonna do?
Stop, please forgive me!
Noo...
Stop, don't move it like that!
It fits so well inside this onahole, what were you calling a clit again?
I can't anymore.
It's gonna come out again.
I'm cumming!
Oh my, you came already?
That won't do, will it?
Since you're a girl, you need to hold back when you're about to come.
Well then, let's try again.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
I apologize, so... No!
I'll make you feel even better, so say it properly!
No, I can't anymore...
I don't want to release it again...
It's already time for our meeting, Satou's gonna get mad.
I don't want to...
Saying that you want to conceal your clit-penis, but still masturbating at school...
It seems you were careless, huh?
If you don't want people to learn your secret...
I'm gonna cum inside your virgin ass!
No, I'm gonna get pregnant if you release it inside!
No, don't!
No...
I'll cum, I'm gonna cum again!
You sure are a pervert, since you're supposed to be a girl,
but you've cummed in this onahole countless times.
Yes, I admit to being a pervert.
So, please forgive me already.
Oh my, but if you're a pervert, there's no way this much can satisfy you, can it?
I wonder what I should do to please this perverted tranny.
No, please stop already!
That was correct, she won't be satisfied with just that.
Fatty?!
That was amusing.
What were you doing, Nagisa?
W-well you see, since you weren't around,
I was training this tranny in your place.
Oh? How impressive, Nagisa.
But Shouko's no tranny, she's a full-fledged woman, right?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
My womb's becoming numb.
Stop!
Stop...
Stop, it's no good.
I'm gonna cum inside of you too if you cum before I cum inside Nagisa.
No, please!
If you cum inside me anymore, I'm gonna get pregnant!
No, I'm cumming!
I'm gonna release it again!
You came before me, huh?
Well then, I'm cumming inside Nagisa too.
No! Today is really not a safe day for me!
I don't want to be pregnant.
Don't cum inside me anymore!
You're saying that, but your womb can't wait any more!
If you cum inside me, I'm gonna kill you.
I really will, fatty!
He's releasing it directly on my womb!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
I don't want to be pregnant!
Well then, it's your turn, Shouko.
No! Please, just don't cum inside!
I'll do anything, so please!
No!
Your ass feels so great.
Your body is the best, Shouko!
No!
Since this is a rare occasion, let's have Nagisa help too!
It hurts!
It really hurts!
Stop!
No, my clit-penis and butt are both gonna break!
Now, how should I bring down Shouko?
The fun is just getting started!
Next Episode
Season 2 has finally started!
We get to meet Futoshi who's now lusting after pleasure even more!
Now, the time to shine for the married woman character beside him - me, Serizono Sayuri has finally come!
I wonder if I'll end up doings things like this and that with him
Geez, if you just say it, I'd let you do anything...
Futoshi, you dummy.
Next time on Hypnotized School Slaves: Eh? There's not gonna be a next time?!
There you go off joking again...
Eh, this is really the last ep?
H-hey, that's not what we agreed to!
Stop! Stop!
Hey Shouko, did you hear, the staff drew these after the Anime went into sale?
Yet another memory: Bears called Kumagawa!
Eh? Should we really be saying that now?
You're worried about that?!
How naive!
With the power of my exceptionally high I.G.U , my character can easily make ratings in fighting games!
Mizushiro, you shouldn't be saying things like that.
What's with you teach?!
Impossible to measure?!
Don't tell me, she's the legendary war goddess?
She doesn't even have any skills!
I've heard of it before - supporting the Eroge world, there's a bridge in the Japanese cosmos.
Among the 12 guardians charged with protecting it, if we were to go by I.G.U levels,
the one to come out on top would be this goddess.
It's said that in the last war within one night, while saying "For the nation, this is for the nation",
she lead a group of veteran Eroge players who bidded as high as 5,000 or 10,000 to Valhalla.
Moreover, it's even said that even when she's tired from all the sex, she can still do some simulation RPG!
Don't tell me, Kaoruko can too?!
W-what happened guys?
We were in the wrong, goddess!
Eh, huh?
Leaving that aside, do we have everyone here?
It somehow feels like I'm forgetting someone...
Eh? Did we have anyone else?
Looks like we've got everyone, no?
We did count after all.
Since I just transferred in, I don't really get it.
Teacher! That purple haired woman isn't here.
Purple haired woman?
Ah!
Everyone's teasing me!
Bullying isn't good!
Capture everyone, won't you?