Our tennis club has already gone to a training camp,
but we have to keep practicing over summer break.
Get ready Ai, I'm serving.
Next!
Pick up the pace!
Mio!
Come on Mio, get it together.
I'm done for! It's too hot to run around.
I already told you that we could use the pool after practice today.
Hang in there a little longer.
Dang, it's hot.
To be honest I'd really like to get in the pool right now.
Me too!
I'm actually already wearing a swimsuit.
You're really something Mio.
What? Changing is such a pain.
Excuse me, to tell the truth...
I am too.
I'm sorry.
I came wearing a swimsuit.
Geez. Fine, whatever.
Let's call it a day then.
Hurray!
Oh?
Looks like someone else was looking forward to this too.
Hey!
Everyone!
Let's get in the pool together!
T-Teacher?
You've already changed?
I bought this new swimsuit.
What do you think of it?
What do I think?
Well...
You know...
What was that for Mio?
Shuu? Are you OK?
Try not to drool so much.
Stupid brother.
Calm down.
That's not good for the racket.
That event turned out to have led to a certain something...
FAKKU! Presents
I really love you♥
Oh, have you finally woken up Shuu?
Huh?
How do you feel? Are you still dizzy?
Does your head hurt?
I feel fine now.
You shouldn't get up yet.
Stay still for a while longer.
No, really...
Shuu! You've gotten hard.
Sorry about that.
Want me to take a look?
I mean, your shorts are stretched so tight around it.
It would probably hurt to leave it like that.
Do you think Sugiyama is alright?
We should just forget about my stupid brother.
The teacher is with him, so I think he'll be fine.
Mio, could you do me a favor and go check up on him?
Huh?
This is all your fault anyway.
It's not right to make the teacher take care of him.
Geez, that stupid brother.
I guess I should go.
I'm coming too.
Those two were just looking for an excuse to go anyway.
Am I doing it right Shuu? Does it hurt?
That's fine.
Wow. It's not just big.
It's so hot. And it's even twitching.
Teach... That feels good.
Really?
Does having your dick rubbed really feel that good?
Shuu?
I'd feel guilty if I was the only one who felt good.
You can't do that!
You can't touch my breasts like that!
Your tits are really amazing.
Don't do that to my tits!
I'm sensitive there.
Are you feeling it Teach?
It feels good.
But... but... if you keep this up, I'll lose control.
Play with mine too.
Something clear is slowly coming out from the tip.
My hand is getting soaked.
How does this feel?
It feels like my nipples will melt.
My nipples feel so good.
Please do more to me Shuu.
You're about to come aren't you?
Coming. Is that what this is?
I'm getting hot on the inside.
My head's going blank.
I'll come together with you.
You're rubbing them so hard.
That's it, I can't take any more.  I'm going to come.
So this is semen?
It's really hot.
Sorry for getting all over you.
You're probably not satisfied yet are you?
Just look, your dick is still so big.
Oh wow. Both the teacher and Sugiyama are really horny.
Hey, is my stupid brother forcing himself on her?
No. It doesn't look that way.
Th... This time I'll make you feel good with this.
T-Teach...
Hurry up. This pose is embarrassing.
Sure.
Go slowly.
Teach, is this your first time?
Don't worry about that. Go all the way.
But...
It's fine.
I'm an adult.
I can handle your thing.
Got it.
It hurts... It hurts!
It's all inside you Teach.
You can start moving a little Shuu.
But you're...
It's OK.
Move however you like.
You don't have to worry about me.
Make sure to tell me if you can't take it anymore.
Shuu, Shuu!
Teach, I'm hitting your womb.
You shouldn't knock on my insides like that.
That's a very special place.
It's where a baby lives.
You can't, you can't do that.
If you keep that up I'll go crazy.
But down here you're hot and slopping wet.
You meanie.
That's it.
It's my first time... it's my first time, but I'm...
You're about to come aren't you?
Are you going to come too?
Will you come together with me?
Yes. Together...
Do it together with me Shuu.
I'm going to come, I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Wow, he came. He really came.
And so did the teacher. She had her first time with Sugiyama.
This could be bad.
I didn't expect to have her as a rival.
She's our rival?
That's right.
Come by my house on the way home. I want to talk to you about something.
OK.
After that, we pretended not to have seen anything and went back to the pool.
Sugiyama and the teacher came back a little later.
But they didn't seem in the mood to talk, so I ended up not asking them anything.
Sugiyama
Mio?
What are you doing?
You take your clothes off too.
We're going to figure out how we can become more erotic.
Look at this.
Is that a porno magazine?
Yeah. It was hidden in Shuu's room.
It looks like he's turned on by this kind of stuff.
Are we going to do the stuff that's in this magazine?
Exactly.
If we don't we'll lose to Teacher.
Are you fine with that?
I wouldn't want that.
But if Sugiyama came home...
Don't worry about that.
I asked him to go shopping with Kei.
Come on, hurry up.
OK, fine.
I'll take my clothes off too.
Wow, this is really something.
You can see everything.
She's just wearing a string.
That's way more embarrassing than just being naked.
What the? She's getting screwed by such a big crowd.
Gross. She's covered in semen.
This girl's taking such a huge penis.
But it looks like it feels so good.
This one's doing it outside.
Sugiyama is such a pervert. He has so many dirty photos.
He's so lewd.
This must be what they call adult toys.
I wonder if Shuu wants to try it out.
That would be embarrassing.
Mio, I'm starting to feel weird for some reason.
Yeah, me too.
So, if you're not against it, could we try some of this out?
I just think there are some things you can't get from a magazine and have to try out for real.
Yeah, you're right.
We're both girls, so there's nothing embarrassing about it.
We took a bath together at the training camp,
but being stared at like this is still embarrassing.
Hey, can I try touching you?
Sure, go ahead.
Wow, your skin is so smooth.
You're touching me so softly.
It's different from how a guy does it.
Hey!
Nipples get hard like this when you're excited right?
I'm sensitive so this is kind of embarrassing.
Me too.
When you touch me I twitch. I'm really feeling it.
Mio, let's keep going on the bed.
Maybe we're perverted too.
We're getting so wet even though we're both girls.
It's all Sugiyama's fault. He does so many dirty things to us.
I'm going to put a finger in, Ai.
Go ahead. I'm going to do it too.
Hey Ai, do you masturbate?
Yes. About three times a week.
I always imagine Shuu is touching me when I masturbate.
Me too. I remember the things I've done with Sugiyama.
I really want Shuu to do me.
I want him to stick his dick in here.
Yes. I want him to stir me up deep inside again and again.
If Sugiyama wants to, he can do the dirty things in those magazines to me.
I'll get more and more pervy too.
I'll start doing things I find embarrassing on my own.
I can't take it. I'm going to come.
Give it to me. It's coming.
I'm coming too! It's coming out!
I'm coming!
Mio and I put our plan into action three days later after tennis practice.
Huh? Where'd they go?
Why'd they call me out here?
Shuu.
So you're in here Mio?
H-how is it? Do I look good in this?
What are you doing Mio?
And you too Saeki?
I thought you'd like this sort of cosplay.
Huh?
We've decided that today we'll do dirty things like never before.
It's really embarrassing but we'll try our best.
Whoa, what the heck is going on?
Hold on a second Saeki.
I'm sorry, but I can't wait any longer.
And you're already this big too.
I'm telling you this is a bad idea.
If you go that far I'm going to get in the mood...
That's fine. Do whatever you want.
I'll become a dirty girl today.
Saeki...
Please Sugiyama.
Do mine too.
Play with my embarrassing place.
If you say so.
It feels good.
You can be more rough.
You're already soaked here.
No!
I'm sorry, I'm getting turned on.
I'm getting turned on by playing with your dick.
Can you tell? I'll use my breasts.
I'm getting so excited my breasts are hot.
Wow, even though Ai is so shy she's really dirty.
It's even getting me to feel weird.
No! Don't lick me where I'm wet.
Are you really saying I can't?
No.
Please lick that place... please lick my pussy lots.
You're saying some dirty things.
Yes, I am.
I'll say anything if it makes you happy.
Then say some more.
When I play with your pen... I mean, with you cock, my pussy, my pussy starts to feel good.
You're really dirty Saeki.
Why am I starting to feel good even though I'm so embarrassed?
I'm about to come.
Me too, I'm going to come, I'm about to come!
Please cover me in lots of semen!
Punish me for being so dirty.
Oh no!
Wow, there's so much semen.
But Shuu's dick is still this hard.
Stop that Mio. I just came.
No way.
I'm going to make you come lots today.
Look at how hard my nipples have gotten.
They're smaller than Teacher's or Ai's, but they feel good right?
You look so cute when you get turned on.
It makes me want to tease you even more.
Let's begin.
Saeki?
I'm going to do it Mio.
OK, go ahead.
I'm already so wet.
It's going inside. There's so much going so deep.
Mio. Saeki.
Look at us Shuu. Look at how dirty we are!
Are you getting turned on by how...
I'm obsessively licking...
Your dick?
Mio, I feel so good I can't stop thrusting.
Me too, I'm really feeling it.
You're thrusting me from behind, and I have a dick in my mouth...
Mio I'm about to...
Go ahead Shuu. Shoot it into my mouth.
Oh no, I'm about to come again.
No Ai, I'm going to come.
Stir up my pussy, stir it up!
I'm coming!
It's hot. Your semen is so hot and sticky.
I'm sorry Mio.
Don't say that.
This time do it here, give it to me in my pussy.
You can do both of us at the same time in this position.
Please Sugiyama, we can't take it anymore.
The way you look, I could go again...
Good. For you we'd do way, way more dirty things.
I'm putting it in.
Shuu!
That's amazing! Sugiyama's dick is rubbing right against our pussies.
You're both so hot down there.
No, don't say that. It's all your fault.
We've wanted you thing, your cock, for so long.
This feels weird. Everyone's private places are slopping wet.
This is so dirty!
Mio!
Mio, your hard nipples are rubbing up against mine!
Oh yeah? Your breasts are so hot, you're a pervert too!
I can't hold back any longer.
Shuu, you can...
Plow your semen into our pussies.
Y-Yes.
You can shoot all your cum wherever you like.
Make us really, really filthy.
I'm about to come too. I'll come again.
I'm letting out so much perverted juice.
Me too, I'm going to come too.
My pussy is twitching so much...
Together... Let's all do it together.
Shoot it! Shoot it out, shoot it!
Amazing...
I'm still tingling down there.
This might be the first time I've come so much.
That's enough already you three.
How did you know Reiko?
How could I not notice with you screaming like that?
Girls bathing
What were you thinking, going as far as wearing costumes?
I'm sorry. We saw Sugiyama doing it with the teacher, so we felt that we couldn't lose to her.
Oh no, you were watching?
I'm embarrassed.
It's all Shuu's fault anyway, he's so indecisive.
He's too nice to everyone.
You think so? I like that about him.
What? Why?
I don't think being too overbearing would suit Sugiyama either.
Being kind is his strong point.
H-hey! How'd we end up talking about that?
You're right.
In the end, I think everyone can't help but care about Sugiyama.
I also really love Sugiyama.