This is a special treat.
Special Sushi, that is!
Of course, the topic's about our mom.
Will mom be coming home tonight?
Certain circumnstances got in the way today,
but she said she'll certainly make time tomorrow to see you.
I see!
Leaving that aside,
let's dig in!
Thank you for the food.
W-well Yuki, it's been a while, I guess.
Y-yes, it indeed has.
Seiichi and Yuki - being bashful of each other,
and ever since their meeting on that station, they haven't really interacted much.
Even though both sisters lived at the same mansion, their relationship only developed
up to passing by each other on the passages, and bowing at best.
Uhh, how much of our relationship have you explained to Yuki?
Well, I've told her that you're my boyfriend,
and will someday become her brother-in-law.
Well anyway, let's get along, Yuki.
Y-yes.
L-likewise.
Misono Yuki - possessing a face even younger than Maki's,
she certainly bears enough beauty to resemblence that of her ex-model mother.
She's 3 years younger than Maki.
Compared to her vibrant and cheerful elder sister,
she possesses an introverted, hesitant personality.
Maki too had the same last name till her parents decided to divorce.
The current name, "Sanjou" is her mother's maiden name.
And so Seiichi, I'll be leaving Yuki in your care from the afternoon.
Ah, well... sure.
Sis, are you going somewhere?
After all this, I need to show my face at school, in the very least.
Wait till then.
O-okay.
Maki-chan to Nau
Innocent Angel - Misono Yuki's Chapter
Well then, I'll head out.
Yeah, take care.
I'm going then.
H-have a safe trip.
You don't need to be nervous like that, you know.
Y-yes!
I'll try my best!
Since Maki practically considers this her own home anyway.
Is that... so?
Yep, indeed.
Umm...
Can I take care of washing the plates?
Plates?
Oh, you mean those?
As a reward for taking care of my sister,
let me clean up.
Well, let me think.
Well then, I guess I'll leave that up to you.
Sure.
Eh, she seems so gentle from the outside,
but seems to have good hands.
Yuki, perhaps, are you good at housework?
Ah, well, rather than being good at it, I like it,
since sis never does any of it.
Or rather, fearing horrible destruction, it can't be entrusted to her - would be correct.
She's got a great figure, and excels at almost everything.
She's even versatile at sports, but she's really clumsy with her hands.
If you leave her to take care of housework, she'll end up causing world war three.
That's her specific quality.
Umm, is there anything else you need me to do?
Ah, nope. It's fine, Yuki.
But it looks like you've been taking care of sis, so...
But we help each other out, so...
That's specially true in the sexual favors department,
she's been taking care of me.
Doing things like this, or even that...
Leaving that aside Yuki, didn't you like Animes and Comics?
Yep, I do!
Come on in!
Ah, amazing!
This is almost like heaven itself!
Now you're exaggerating.
Dad never lets me watch any of it since he thinks they only serve to rot one's mind
and are completely useless without any value at all.
I see.
But since books can help with studies, he's okay with Light Novels.
Is that so?
Well then...
Have you read this before?
Yep, up  to the third volume.
Did you have fun?
Umm, well, I don't really remember that well.
I s-see...
Are you a fan of this book's author?
Well, that's not it - I am the author.
Me...
Amazing!
That really is amazing!
Brother, you're a real writer?
Ah well, but it didn't really sell much at all.
However, there's no way I can tell her that I write scenarios for Eroge on the side too.
Because as long as they don't have that one special characteristic, it won't take long for that revered look to turn into disdain.
I see.
So sis has someone this amazing as her boyfriend.
Feel free to read anything you like to your heart's content.
It's always been a dream of mine to read a complete series from start to the end!
Thank you, brother!
T-take your time!
Brother, huh?
Yuki?
Don't tell me, you've been reading Manga the whole time?
Ah! Welcome back, sis!
Brother's room is really amazing!
It's a mountain of treasures!
Brother?
How does it feel to be called Brother?
Well, rather great, I suppose.
Are you really fine with giving me these, Brother?
Of course.
If there's anything else you want, the window on the veranda is always open.
You can take them as you wish.
Indeed, since I can't even figure out which home you live in anymore.
Or rather, you're way too unrestrained.
Brother and you really do seem to get along, sis.
I guess so, jealous?
There's no way I could be jealous.
You don't have anyone you like?
N-no way! There's no way I'd have someone like that.
Hmm? That's suspicious.
Well, I suppose that's it.
Since in your case, we'll need to do something about your extreme shyness first.
I understand that already...
Good mor-, that's not it, it's already noon!
Please wake up, brother!
There it is!
Brother's thing is swelling up so much...
That's amazing!
I can't be serious, being fascinated with that thing only makes me a regular pervert!
W-what's this? I was thinking Maki's thought up some new perverted play in the heat of the moment, but...
No matter how we look at it, you're sleeping too much, brother!
Your eyebrows are gonna end up sticking together if you keep sleeping like that, brother!
So I'm telling you, wake up! Brother!
Brother?
Wake up...
W-wait, Yuki?!
You finally awoke, brother!
Good morning!
Ah, uhhh, good morning!
Umm, well, why are you waking me up?
Sis left for school the first thing in the morning,
so she told me to wake you up.
Ah, thanks.
Yuki fits so well in that apron outfit, so cute...
What's wrong, Yuki?
Uh, well...
I'm grateful since you came to wake me up.
I'm preparing breakf-, not that, lunch. Please wash your face and join me soon, brother.
Y-yuki, that outfit's...
Eh?
Well, Yuki...
What's with that outfit?
Umm, well, sis told me to wear this when I came to wake you up.
Maki did?
Y-yes.
I see.
I'm fine with being seen if it's you, brother.
That, and the kitchen was really hot.
It's easier to move around in these too.
So I thought, "Why not?"
I see...
That, and she said that since she was incompetent,
she realized that's it's better to be smaller to do this, and that made her relieved.
Though, I didn't really understand that...
Do you think so too, Brother?
Ah well, I suppose so.
Anyway, that posture really suits you.
The apron's really cute too.
Really? Thank god!
I really like this one too.
Wow!
You made all these by yourself, Yuki?
I'll be glad if they're to your liking, Brother.
I'm digging in!
Delicious!
Geez Brother, you're exaggerating!
W-what are you doing, Bro?
Are you okay?
I just panicked for a moment...
Say Brother, can I look at you work today?
Sure, of course.
Really? Thank you!
Huh? Wait...
Today, I'm jesting around while trying to gain Yuki's trust as a legitimate Light Novel writer.
There's no way I can tell her that I'm writing such indecent and lewd scenes of those 2D nymphs.
I'm hiding the ero-scenes discreetly too.
That should do it!
Now, about writing the next scene...
That's...
from the time when you and sis did it before?
There's no way that could be...
Brother!
Y-yes?
Want some snacks?
That should do it.
Of course, her full blown naked view is wonderful too.
However, that's subject to being overly candid.
Daring to conceal a girl's important parts,
and creating that sensation of seeing, yet not seeing at the same time
is the epitome of the appeal of the naked apron.
There resides a elegant butterfly that hails from the harmonic world,
leading to aesthetic, yet quiet simplicity.
Yep, it definitely does suit you, Yuki.
Really? Thank god.
W-wait, Brother?!
Don't tell me, you were there the whole time?
Eh, I wasn't supposed to?
You weren't!
That's why I even said that I'd call you once I was done...
Seeing her in naked aprons were alright, but the change itself was not.
Seiichi at that point failed to understand a maiden's feeble mind, and its reasonings.
I made hot cakes, but...
They look delicious!
Thank god.
Then, I'll prepare some iced coffee, Brother!
Watch out!
Seiichi fell over with Yuki on top.
As if straddling his groins, Yuki with her naked apron was leaning on him.
Moreover, one of the laces covering the shoulders moved to one side,
revealing one of her breasts.
Superb view! Wait that's not it...
I'm s-sorry.
Are you alright, Brother?
How about you, did you knock into something?
Nope, since you pulled me away.
Thank you, Brother.
I can't let our precious Yuki be hurt.
Maki'd get mad too.
Seiichi's gaze was rooted to Yuki's revealed breast,
breasts that were well shaped when compared to Maki's volume.
Her white cleavage that appeared to be so smooth just by looking at them...
Those faintly raised hills make people delusional with animalistic lust.
W-well, Yuki?
W-what is it, Brother?
Umm, well, your breast is...
Umm, you can see it, right?
Do you like them more hidden?
Um, well, if I had to say, I suppose I prefer them like that.
Or rather, Yuki, your nipples are getting hard!
Don't tell me, she's...
At this rate, I won't be able to control my delusions..
My reasoning's about to ...!
Hey, Brother...
I know that the relationship between you and sis is that of a man and woman.
Eh?!
That thing you guys were doing in the train back then, t-that was, "molester play," right?
So you did understand it...
When the doors open, sis' face looked so happy and pleased...
My heart really throbbed when I saw that.
I even felt so jealous of sis,
and thought that I want to do things like that to you too.
Umm, Yuki...?
Wait a minute...
The situation's getting even stranger by the minute.
And so, I went ahead and asked sis about what I should do a while back.
You asked her?
She suggested me to wear lewd clothes, and tempt you.
And if I succeeded, she said I could do as I please afterwards.
So Brother, do me like her too.
I want you to teach me about sex too
T-that means giving up your virginity to me, no?
Yep.
Since I'm in love with you.
I want to do it with you,
I don't want anyone else.
She sure is Maki's sister...
Wait, that's not...
Or Brother, you don't want to do it with anyone but sis?
That's not it, but...
Yuki, do you understand what it really means to have sex?
Nope, I don't really understand well, that's because I want to know more.
I want you to teach me.
I see...
Ah, the hole women have in their special place is called a vagina, right?
I know that we need to put in your thing, the penis in there.
I had sis show me a movie for that, so...
Ah, wait, Yuki!
So, this is your... penis.
All I need to do now is put this in there, right?
Well, that's the gist of it...
Then let's give it a try.
Doing it so sudden is reckless!
It hurts!
As I was saying, it's impossible to put it in without any foreplay.
Before that, we need to make it wet as well.
Eh? Foreplay, making it wet?
The excitement from the immorality, while lighting up Seiichi's whole body,
gradually pushed his nether region to the pinnacle of erections.
Well, to start with, why don't you come down from there?
Sit up here, Yuki.
Now, spread your legs
S-sure.
But it's so embarassing, Brother.
Embracing that shyness and transforming it into pleasure is what sex is, Yuki.
Is that so?
You're cute, Yuki.
Brother, is this okay?
Yep, that's fine.
I can see your embarrassing spot clearly.
If you stare at me like that, as I thought, it's so embarrassing.
Brother?!
You shouldn't lick me there.
Why not?
Because it's so sweaty, and dirty.
I can't smell anything but good smells though
And besides, if we don't get it wet like this, we won't be able to go all the way.
Wetting my pussy?
You mean by wetting it like that with your saliva?
Not by saliva, you'll making it wet by yourself.
It's like that? But I don't really understand it well...
Brother?! That's the hole my pee comes out of...
Indeed, what of it?
Since, it's really dirty.
You're fine licking a place like that?
And above that, it's really embarrassing.
Do you know what this small, uplifted-dot is called?
Umm, well, I don't.
But I've been feeling so hot and bothered, and can't seem to settle down for a while.
It's called a Clitoris, Yuki.
Or rather, a clit.
No, Brother!
It feels all weird.
I'm gonna go all crazy.
I really am!
Look Yuki, lewd juices are coming out of your pussy.
That's how the sensation of cumming feels.
I didn't know anything like that, is my first time.
I'm gonna go crazy.
My mind's still completely blank.
That felt really good, Brother.
Sis' been doing things that feel this good with you everyday?
Actual sex is more intense and pleasant, Yuki.
Even more pleasant?
It's probably going to hurt a bit at the start.
You're really sure about this?
I'll hang in there.
Well, I'm starting then.
Yep, it's fine. Put it in.
Don't be so tense on your lower body, you need to relax.
I'll try my best.
It hurts!
Yuki, hey, look!
Your dick is in my hole...
Eh? Blood's coming out.
Oh right, my period was supposed to start really soon.
I'm gonna put it in a little deeper,
think you can hold on?
Yep, I'm fine.
I believe in you, so...
Do as you please.
Does it hurt, Yuki?
It does, but I'll handle it - if it's only this much.
More importantly, I'm really happy right now.
Happy?
Since I've just managed to become one with my beloved Brother
I too am really happy to have become one with you, Yuki.
Think you'll be okay if I move like this?
Umm, moving?
It means to rub the penis back and forth to the entrance and the end of your vagina.
With that, the penis will rapidly start feeling good, and at the end, ejaculate.
That's what it means to have sex.
I see.
Yep, it's okay.
I'll hold myself back if it hurts,
so use my pussy to feel good, Brother!
Well then, here I go, Yuki!
You're raging inside my pussy, Brother!
It seems your breasts have swelled a bit, eh?
Brother, it's embarrassing if you touch my breasts.
They're really cute.
If you rub my breasts like that...
I'm really gonna go crazy.
When girls feel good, their breasts swell up, and the nipples become erect and sensitive.
Oh my, it's true. My nipples are erect.
And then, if I tease those erect nipples like these...
No! If you rub my nipples like that, my breasts are gonna get numb.
B-brother, my pussy's somehow starting to get hot.
Did the pain go away?
It does hurt, but somehow feels good too.
This is the first time I've felt like this.
Are you gonna cum?
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming?
But this somehow feels different from the time when you teased my clit...
Something warm seems to be accumulating inside my pussy.
You wanna cum?
I want to, I want to try cumming from my pussy too!
Well then, I'll make you cum.
Brother's hot and hard thing is spreading my pussy.
Give me more!
Penetrate me even deeper!
Your pussy's started to burn up.
My pussy feels really good, Brother.
It hurts, but I'm still feeling it.
It feels really good for me too, Yuki.
I'm happy.
Use me to feel even better, brother!
When you agonize like that, it's so perverted, lewd and cute, Yuki!
Brother, something's gonna come?
I'm going crazy.
Yuki, I'm at my limit too.
Let's cum together!
Yep, cum, Brother!
Cum with me, with me!
Cumming, I'm cumming!
My pussy's gonna burst!
White stuff burst forth from the tip of your penis, Brother.
That's semen, Yuki.
This is your semen?
Then, if this gets in my womb, I'll get pregnant, huh?
If you're interested, you can try licking it, Yuki.
You can lick it?
Maki seems to love it, and is drinking it all the time
Really?
Then just a bit.
How's it?
It's not delicious at all, Brother.
Two people silently watching each other,
Seiichi's lips slowly approached Yuki's.
Brother...
Seiichi's tongue stirred up Yuki's mouth.
And with his left hand, he gently caressed Yuki's breasts.
He stared into Yuki reassuringly.
Pupils glittering in passion, Yuki returned his gaze absorbedly.
Hey, Brother?
That was...
That was my first kiss.
They were glistening - grabbing Yuki's right hand, and opening the bathroom door,
they started their journey towards being devoted to pleasure.
Eh?!
They'd started their journey towards being devoted to pleasure.
Maki?
You've been going on like that for a while...
Geez, that's because you two are always so lovey-dovey.
My pussy can't wait anymore.
Geez, sis.
I wanted to do it a bit more.
Sorry, sorry.
Well then, let's all do it together from now on.
Let's head on to an extraordinary paradise!
Thank you for watching to the end, everyone
Please keep an eye out for Collaboration Works' stuff next month too!