UD Academy Cheerleading Club
Um, sister, I can run by myself!
Makoto asked for my help. Let your sister show off for once!
No surprise Makoto fell for you.
Your butt's almost as great as mine.
They're happy to see it too.
Fuckers!
You've really got a nice butt!
Epidemic Outbreak
Hanazawa...
No!
If you want us to release your little brother, obey me.
Whatever you do to my body, I'll never be broken!
Hey!
If you can say the same thing an hour from now,
I'll let both you and your brother free.
Don't forget those words!
Episode 1: Rape Harem
Rapidemic 5
Don't look away, Akari.
See what the boy's going through.
He's doing quite well compared to what a baby face he's got.
He's rock hard all the time because of the pheromones you and your friends spread out.
Mako...
Hold out just a little longer, Makoto! I'm gonna save you!
What're you doing?!
Stop!
Stop! Hey, stop!
Finally you put on a feminine face.
Damn you!
Makoto, I'll overcome this and we'll be going home toget--
Come on, suck on it!
So much lust in such a little girl!
It's the result of your family's long years of research and deceiving the public.
Dumb people's brains can't handle so much personality change.
Is that what you're interested in? You whore!
Don't say such rude--
Give him a blowjob! Like last night.
You damn kids're so lewd!
I feel something amazing in me!
Can't get enough of this cunt!
I never wanna take my cock outta you!
Get pregnant!
You can have some too.
I don't want it, you bastard!
You aren't honest.
Stop it!
Damn you! Why does this--
Damn!
Oh, you can still put on that face?
Such a cutie.
Don't screw with me, you damn bastard!
I'll show you how it's done!
You lewd bitch!
Damn you, you cowardly bastard!
How does it feel you're never gonna forget this bastard's cock?
You coward! You're only teasing the same spots!
You look ecstatic. Guess your nipples are the key.
You damn pervert!
N-No!
It doesn't feel good at all!
Damn! Don't move!
You're brea... breaking me...
Your cunt's so sensitive!
You lewd pig!
N-No!
Now show your face to your brother!
Explain to him with that shaking voice!
It's not... not true, Makoto!
No!
Oh? Your cunt's so lewdly tight around my cock!
You damn pig!
No!
What happened to your resistance? Your cunt's crazy for me!
Stop! Please, stop! Not inside!
Not a chance!
I'm giving you more, so tighten that cunt!
No! It's coming in me again!
Take it all and get pregnant!
He twisted my insides over and over again.
Damn! It's still hot!
He cummed so much, and it's still so hard!
I don't get it. Is something wrong with me?
It makes me feel like giving up...
Don't move anymore!
Should I give you the rape you want?
I'll smash my cock into you and make you show your true colors!
I'm sorry, Makoto...
I think I'm losing... This cock feels too good...
Don't disappoint the missy, boy. Give them lots of juice.
See, there it goes!
Missy, you can't hold back, can you?
Sorry for the wait, you filthy pig!