above guy "stop fighting!", speech bubble "Ha!", above girl on right "smack!" #I don't.
How's this?
That's not really the issue here.
Come on, hurry. Somebody might walk in.
Everybody has a crazy dream or two, right? But I never expected one like this could come true.
So basically, I just need to find the "Booby Champion" who's somewhere in town?
Card: Sex Coupon
Right. And to do it, you'll need those Sex Coupons.
Hand-made, one of a kind, ultra-premium.
So whoever I show these to will have sex with me?
How many people it will work on is all up to the cards.
You'll be fine if you just put in some effort and look for her.
Alright, deal!
Onward to my titty harem!
Charge!
Yes! Oh god!
My breasts! Grab my breasts!
They're soft, really soft!
This is a dream come true!
Deeper! Go deeper!
Does it feel good, Ohtsuru? Well?
Good! It's so good!
More! All the way to my womb!
Yes!
So deep! You're reaching my womb!
Here it comes!
Wait! Cum on my tits!
This is for you.
So this is the champion bra...
But how did you know it was me?
Because your breasts have a special charm to them, Ohtsuru.
I'm glad it was you, Inatani.
I already told you!
Her name's Nihru, and she's basically just a referee for this game!
Then explain what the hell this game is, damnit!
That's... uhh... confidential.
Yep, confidential.
Fine then!
I was planning on graciously helping you with your report, but whatever!
Fakku! Presents: Booby King 48
Suck every tit in sight, no hesitation!
That Hurts.
Fuck you! Jerk!
Wait, what about my report?
Matsuri!
There's no time for self-pity. Get to campus!
Ha!
Smack!
Stop Fighting!
Booby King!
She's gonna chew me out for sure...
Oh, Inatani. I've been expecting you.
G-good morning!
About that report...
That doesn't matter right now. Check this out!
Bam!
I pulled 3 all-nighters to make this state of the art scouting device!
Uhh, won't we be in deep if we don't mosaic this?
Who the heck are you talking to?
There's nobody there, you know.
Just hurry up and try it on!
O-okay then.
WHAT OVER 9000!?
That's right! That's my power level!
Curse you Kakarotto!
Pretty cool , huh?
This is incredible.
By the way, what is this supposed to be?
A Breast Scouter
What the hell kinda name is that!?
At any rate, you're a boobie freak, aren't you?
Y-yeah I guess, what does that have to do with this?
Try pushing the button here.
I don't have all day!
Y-yes ma'am!
T-t-the hell!?
A perfectly healthy response for a boy your age.
Yours may be a little extreme though.
W-wai- what's going on?
Well, how do mine compare?
C-c-compare to...?
You like 'em?
Very much.
Having you eyes glued to my chest's got me kinda hot...
You've gotten pretty big.
N-no, that's not it-
What is it then?
Look, I'm about to swallow the tip of your dick.
T-this is amazing!
It's okay, you can be rough.
Ohh! You're hitting my insides!
My mind's giving way to my instinctual lust!
Doctor! Doctor Miyu!
Oh yes! Harder! Do it harder!
Oh god! This is it!
I've wanted this so bad!
Doctor, I can't... hold out anymore.
It's fine! I'm gonna cum too!
Blow your huge load on my tits!
Cumming!
Dr. Miyu, to tell you the truth, I got mixed up in this weird game...
I'm on the hunt for the five Boobie champions living in town.
And so I explained the game I'm playing to her.
That proves it was fate, I was meant to create the Booby Scouter!
Did you know about this beforehand?
Booby King!
This school a girl's sanctuary attended only by the true upper crust of Japan.
And right now they're holding their school festival!
Festival Committee HQ
Which is all well and good but...
But why am I being held and interrogated by this girl?
It's the real thing, alright.
See? I told you it was legit.
Had to have Nihru arrange for it though...
Even though I had an invitation, those idiots jumped me before I could take one step past the gate.
Alright, Alright! I'm sorr-
What's so funny?
Oh, come on. Take a look!
What? Just a bunch of food stalls.
Wait, those aren't students! And over there's-
That's the famous okonomiyaki shop Suigetsu! And Kano, the high-grade beef restaurant!
This here's a super-high class ladies school. You know that, right?
Don't insult my intelligence. I'm aware of that.
Do you honestly expect delicate young girls to go out there and sweat?
Simply put, the girls here are this country's elite.
They live in a completely different world than you, mister.
If someone like you just waltzed in, of course they'd find you suspicious, right?
So who exactly are you supposed to be anyway?
I'm Orie Chikuho. The student council president.
What are you doing? Cosplay or something?
Don't worry about it.
I don't have a fighting chance without this.
Hm? Ah, got it.
No point fighting a losing battle, huh?
Alright! I'll escort Mr.Unpopular around school, okay?
Isn't the president normally busy during the festival?
The executive committee's top notch, so I'm pretty much free.
So there you have it. Where to first?
We've got everything from common fare to the full course!
Come again?
First, we need to get some meal tickets, then...
Hey Orie, I've got a great meal ticket right here.
Huh?
Cooking Lab
I'm sorry for all those mean things I said.
Oh no, I'm fine. Perfectly fine.
I'm sorry for this.
Oh, you silly!
Now then, time to dig in!
Delicious!
A sweetness I've never tasted! And just enough sourness!
Both in perferct, exquisite harmony!
Completely organically grown on private land.
An ordinary person couldn't dream of eating one!
And this cream... what rich taste!
Completely-
You mind putting this between your boobs?
Okay...
It's no fair if I'm the only one eating.
Now it's my turn to feed you.
Big brother!
So good!
You're incredible, Orie.
Your hot insides are wrapping around my dick!
That's because it makes me hot when you're inside me!
Your tits feel amazing! They're the best!
I'm starting to feel funny!
I'm gonna go crazy!
I'm sorry, I-
I'm gonna cum! Here it comes!
That felt wonderful, big brother.
Uh, how'd I end up being your "big brother"?
You don't wanna be?
No, no, that's not it...
Yay! I can't wait to introduce you to grandpa!
Excuse me?
Hello? Is something wrong?
Uhh, Nirhu, I've gotten myself in a bit of a bind...
Bagged me a husband!
Booby King!
Come in!
Thank you for your order, Master!
Oh good, I've been waiting!
T-t-terribly sorry!
I'm supposed to be your maid, and yet my eyes are lusting over your big body!
My what?
I know it's an unforgivable offense, but please...
Please punish this vulgar maid!
W-why aren't you wearing panties!?
The maid's code state I must be ready anytime, anywhere, if my master desires me.
I strive towards meeting those expectations!
Oh, oh noo!
You're gonna cum, aren't you?
Go on and finish whenever you want.
Cumming! I'm cumming!
Master, you're amazing!
I'm a filthy, no-good maid!
I beg you, please punish me severely!
Not again! I'm cumming!
Cumming!!
How unsighly, cumming before your master, and right in front of him too...
It's not over till your master cums!
Noo! I just came!
Please, no! Oh god, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
M-master...
L-let me catch my breath!
Just a little more.
Don't you dare cum until then!
I'm going to cum!
Master's penis is making me cum!
You're being so rough with me!
Cumming! Gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Please, cum!
That's the champion bra!
With this, I'm now your maid and only yours.
Congratulations, Master!
Service!
Lemme go!
Booby King!
Man, it's hot.
Um, please feel free to use this.
I apologize for startling you.
Thanks. Are you one of the priestesses here?
Yes, I am. I'm the daughter of the head priest.
My name is Sachie Hayakawa.
What's that you have there?
Ah, it's nothing.
Huh? That's weird...
Guess I'll have the Doctor take a look.
Please take the handkerchief with you.
Hm? What?
Oh no, it's not that I don't want it anymore...
That isn't it...
It's a birthday present for my father!
Did you two have a fight or something?
Um, well, for a long time I haven't been able to communicate properly with him.
I'm always with him, but my words never seem to reach him.
I don't completely understand,
but I think you should give this to him instead.
Would you do me a favor?
If it's within my power, sure.
Could you give the handkerchief to my father for me?
You got it.
I'll only ask once more...
But are you really okay with me?
Don't be ridiculous! I want you, Sachie.
But you might... no, I'm sure you'll regret it.
That's not true at all.
You're beautiful, Sachie.
You're gorgeous.
Thank you... That makes me so happy.
You're beautiful here too.
That's embarassing...
Did that feel good?
Yes, very good.
Good. Now I'll make you feel even better.
Here goes.
Alright...
Hold it... are you a virgin?
Please, don't worry about me.
Make lots of memories here...
Amazing! You feel great!
Sachie! Sachie!
You're amazing, Sachie!
Inatani, I, I-
Sachie, you don't have to force yourself...
I want you to feel good! I don't want you to forget about me!
Sachie, I'm gonna cum!
Please, cum!
Cum all over me!
Cumming!
I'm glad I was born...
From the bottom of my heart.
Well I'd better get going.
Is that so?
Then I guess this is goodbye...
I'll be lonely without you.
Now, now. I'll be back to return your handkerchief.
Goodbye.
I'm Home~
Sorry to intrude~
Booby King!
Hallo everynyan!
Our circle had a drinking party today!
And you know what? My senior, right?
He just kept staring at my boobs, right?
Fascinating.
This isn't half bad...
I've been nothing but trouble for Matsuri. I really owe her a lot.
Nihru's been cooking and doing laundry. She's been a huge help too.
I wish this could last forever...
Good God! They're beyond my wildest dreams; the king of racks!
I-uhh...ahh...
You understand, don't you Inatani?
H-hold-Huh!? Hang on!
Wait a sec! What're you-
Nihru, do something!
Why the hell are you doing it too!?
Just reading the mood, going with the flow.
Wha-
Hey, over here!
Let me be your number one!
I'll prove just how good I am!
My, how steamy!
Make her stop!
Actually, I was planning to join in.
Juth leeb hewwr bee!
Gimme more!
H-hey!
Stop it!
Don't!
I'm cumming!
Cum buckets.
S-stop!
I'm cumming!
I can't hold on!
Cumming!