I mean, let's do it next time.
Next time?! Don't get full of yourself!
You pig!
You've got the face to ask that!
You bastard! Stop it already!
Just relax. I know you like it.
Who are you kidding? How could I like it!
You always just do as you please...
Says the girl who's dripping wet.
Shut up!
Why is my body enjoying this?
Your cock is teasing my insides!
How does it feel to get raped at your own desk?
I'm not being raped! I let you do it!
Why kiss me just like that?
Don't act cocky. Your entranced face tells the truth.
Don't just start so suddenly! Hey!
You'll pour your semen into me, right?
Pour it!
Your cum is filling me... I'll get pregnant...
You don't care about the place as long as you get a pussy, do you.
I told you I'm not interested in fat pigs.
Classes will be over soon. You should get going.
I'm going as well.
Teacher!
Satsuki, don't surprise me like that.
Wait, when did you come here?
It's not fair that you only do Shizuka.
It's covered in dirty juices.
Satsuki, I can't...
Since when are you so close to Shizuka?
Are you twisting her around with your cock?
It's... nothing to do with you!
That's right. Sorry, it really has nothing to do with me.
When did you...
It's okay, don't hold back.
I'll lick your cock clean.
Your cock is in me!
It's amazing!
It's because it's yours!
Stupid, shut up! What if someone finds us?
Teacher...
Your cock...
Satsuki!
Huh? I thought I've heard her voice.
Where has she gone?
Your cock is trembling.
You should cum quickly.
I know.
Your cock is pounding my pussy!
This feels way better than Shizuka's!
Please mess up my pussy!
Tease my pussy even harder! I want to be full with you!
Feel free to cum in me! My pussy is only yours!
Your cum is...
My pussy is full with you...
Your cock is still so big...
Let's continue after the shooting!
The great debut! Satsuki, the model of pure lust with huge breasts!
What's going on, Satsuki?
It's amazing... but did something happen?
I got carried away by the atmosphere.
No way! I knew something happened!
Shizuka, are you ready?
Shizuka, they're calling you.
Yeah... I'll be going then.
So big...
What if Shizuka comes back?
Then cum in my mouth quick!
You're always so hard... Are you so turned on by Shizuka?
That's not it... Why am I like this?
You should cum a lot!
Sure! Let's work together again!
Now I must get the truth out of Satsuki.
I know something happened.
Changing room
Satsuki!
What? You?
Oh, you're here?
What are you doing here? I said I don't need you today.
Oh? You couldn't live without my body?
That's not...
It's okay. Go down on all four, lick my feet and apologize.
He got even bigger since Shizuka came in.
You could lick my beautiful feet. You should be happy.
It's all right today.
What do you mean?!
It's stone hard! Amazing!
He's still talking with Shizuka.
Okay, call me a pig if you want.
By the way, would you get me something to drink?
You want me to run errands for you?!
His cock feels like it's going to explode!
Shizuka left?
Your cock was so hard when you were talking with Shizuka.
Satsuki, I still can't calm down.
What's wrong with me?
This is all for today.
Hey, don't...
You are into Shizuka, aren't you.
I just...
You shouldn't be selfish.
Give me a break!
Satsuki! Hey, are you teasing Satsuki again?!
Heh, you did run an errand for me...
You asked me to... You pig!
But more importantly, what were you doing...
It's all right, Shizuka. He didn't do anything. See you later!
Wait, Satsuki!
I found mine.
Why did it have to go all the way in?
I can almost reach it!
Something's spilled here! What's this?
No way, this is... Hey, pig!
You were jacking off here alone?
Hey, don't touch me just like that, pig!
Cut it! Don't even think about it!
You're shaking your ass so invitingly.
Who would be inviting you?!
Stop, pig!
You're wet already! Who was thinking about it then?
What are you talking about?! It's nothing like that!
Hey, stop!
Stupid! Don't! There are still others!
Don't just do it wherever you like!
It's too late. No potent man could ever resist this ass.
It's... It's all the way in!
You put your cock in me here!
I don't want it!
You're enjoying it already? You really like this too, Shizuka.
What are you talking about?
Get off your high horse, idiot!
Your precum is flowing in...
Isn't it enough yet?
How could I stop after just this much?
You want to go all the way, don't you?
You old fart, you fuck like a rabbit! Cut it!
Hey, pig, what are you doing?!
Quiet. Someone's here.
They are the other models...
I'll be fired if they see me like this!
What the hell is he thinking, at a time like this?!
You're kidding me! Are you mental?
I can't stop him... and my nipple's already hard!
And what about that Shizuka girl?
She's got a lot of hype.
She's getting carried away.
Who cares, she'll be going down soon.
She's such an innocent little girl. What is she thinking?
She's just a kid, I bet this is just like a part-time job for her.
But that other girl, who was in the back today.
Ah yeah, you mean Satsuki?
Now she's the thing!
If I'd have to bet, she's better I think!
Calm down!
Anyway, let's get going. We'll start early tomorrow.
Shizuka, are you all right?
Don't cry...
I'm not crying! Why would I? I'm not sad or anything!
Those bitches... Those bitches!
Calm down!
How could I?! Get it done already!
I'm telling you to make me feel good!
That's your job, isn't it?!
Deeper... Harder...
Make me feel better!
Mess me up with your cock!
You're this excited? You're very wet!
Shut up! Just care about pushing me beyond the edge!
I'm impaled on your cock! Stick it in deep!
Your pig cock feels good... My pussy is happy!
What? What is it?
Try asking me.
Come on. Ask me to move if you want it.
What?!
What are you talking about?! Don't get cocky!
Just move already.
Say please. Say please and I'll make you cum.
Seriously... Okay, I get.
Hey, teach, please!
Hey, I said please! I did say please!
That's all you've got, I guess.
Hey, so suddenly! What's wrong?
This is...
My pussy is going crazy!
This feels amazing!
Cum in me! Fill me with your stinky cum!
Have your way with me!
What... This feels...
So good... Amazing...
My head's blank...
The pig cock is out of me...
You have no principles. Pig!
I'm cute for sure, but this isn't the place!
You're not the one to say.
And we heard some...
Hey, what's wrong?
It's just that I trusted those girls.
It hurts that that's their opinion of me.
It's because I'm too cute, right?
Hey, Shizuka...
Tomorrow we are shooting at a different location.
Don't be late!
And now I'll forgive you for being rude.
Put on a smile!
There!
Hey, teacher!
I left mid-way yesterday. Was it all right?
Yeah, it's okay, don't worry about it.
You did it with Shizuka, didn't you.
What are you talking about, Satsuki? How would I...
I know! You'd have to deal with me if you got turned on by Shizuka.
Do it quick!
What's up, so suddenly!
Shut up, it's none of your business!
Satsuki is getting popular as well.
So you can't be honestly happy for her?
I'm starting to understand.
Shut up! That's not it!
Hurry! I know you want to do it with me!
Your thick cock always makes me feel good.
It's coming in!
Come in all the way!
Your cock is coming all the way in me!
My pussy is so happy!
This is too...
This is too good!
You're driving me crazy!
It's getting even harder!
Huh? What?
Hey, why do you stop, pig?!
Do it until the end!
Satsuki... no way...
Teacher, what are you doing?
Is this the right way?
That's... well...
Hey, what...?
You sholdn't do it like this, Shizuka.
It's not fun if you alone feel good.
What are you doing, Satsuki?
Men want to feel good too!
No way... Why is she licking there...
He'll get fed up with you if you're always mean.
So quick!
It's because you're not good enough.
Why Satsuki? When did you get like that? Me too, I...
It might be quick for you.
No way...
Satsuki!
It's so hard again...
Teacher, your cock is amazing again!
Again? Satsuki, what do you mean?
Amazing! It's even better with Shizuka watching!
Teacher!
Your cock is so hard in me!
Hey, I'm here! Stop it!
You're the next for the shooting, Shizuka.
What? Say that earlier!
I won't lose!
You shouldn't show off like that.
I won't give her your cock! It's mine!
Teacher, fill me, fill me!
I can feel it... in me...
This is bad. What should I do?
Satsuki?
It should be somewhere around...
Isn't  someone bullying you? Maybe Shizuka?
She's jealous of--
That's not it!
Shizuka wouldn't do this.
I'm more envious of her. I wanted to become like her.
She said...
If you want to be my rival, I'll take you on the challenge.
Let's do our best!
She accepted me.
I'm really happy I could work with her.
She's wonderful.
I know why you're so into her.
I'm no good no matter how hard I try.
I wish I could catch up to her.
What are you talking about? You're not bad either!
Hey, teacher!
Don't do it here!
Are you listening? What if Shizuka shows up?
You're a great chick as well.
No! I know it's not true!
No! My boobs are in the open!
It's embarrassing!
Put it in yourself, Satsuki.
Your cock is in my pussy!
It's in so deep!
Your pussy feels good.
I shouldn't... but my pussy won't stop.
Teacher, you're amazing...
I can't think!
Shizuka will find us! She'll see us again!
Why would it be there... seriously.
Satsuki! Hey!
Shizuka! Don't...
Don't look at us fucking!
Satsuki... Pig, what are you doing?!
Hey, come on... I'm here, stop it!
Don't look, Shizuka! This is too much for you!
What are you talking about? This much is...!
Don't lick me there, Shizuka!
I won't lose!
Not there! It's too much!
You're licking me, Shizuka! That's...
It seems to feel so good...
Shizuka's here, but it still feels so good!
I'm about to cum! You didn't cum in me, and still...
It's in me!
You did it to Satsuki and now it's in me!
It feels amazing!
My pussy is going crazy!
Fill me... Fill me with cum!
Do it wilder! Wilder!
Do it!
It's coming...
It feels so good...
It's filling my womb...
Let's enjoy it together, Satsuki...