Happy Birthday, Takumi!
E-Ena?
What's going on so suddenly?
It's your birthday today, right?
This was finally released from our department.
Don't tell me, is that...?
Indeed!
The Free Sexual Intercourse Permit!
All of you will have let to let me cum inside you!
Y-You idiot!
Brother!
Noo, Takumi, you pervert!
The authority of this permit is absolute!
I'm going to keep cumming inside till you're all pregnant!
You're stirring me up so much, Takumi!
I guess I don't have a choice, huh?
I'll take care of everything!
I'll let you do it to both my pussy and mouth.
Just cum inside to your heart's content!
Cumming, I'm cumming in your face!
No, don't!
Stop it!
For you to be raping my butt and pussy at the same time...
I can't anymore, it's rubbing me wildly!
I can't...
I'm going insane...
I'll break.
Me too!
No...
Take this, take this!
Amazing, you're doing me in such a weird position...
My breasts and pussy are being raped at the same time.
I'm gonna cum too!
You're gonna cum, you're gonna cum on my face!
Brother...
It hurts.
Though, it feels so good that I can't stop!
Punish your lewd sister with your cock, Brother!
Brother's semen...
Wow, so amazing!
Takumi, you're filling me up!
Cum, give all of it to me!
Give it to my face as well.
More, do it more!
Cum inside me more!
I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum while being ejaculated inside!
I can't anymore,
I'm gonna cum!
Thank you for having cooperated with us...
Perfect Compliance☆Compulsory Conception Permit
The First Story  ~Cum inside everyone~
E-Ena?
A-Anyway, the authority of this permit is formally accepted.
Whenever, wherever, regardless of who the girl is,
this permit guarantees you being able to do it with them, and releasing inside.
From today onwards,
you're the sex warrior of love and hope!
Leaving that aside,
we're expecting big things from you.
Things just turned into a disaster.
Does this mean I'm going to end up having sex with Brother,
even though we're siblings?
Let's make more children, everyone!
Eh? Why must we make more children?
That's because...
I feel sorry for Ena,
but I had no intention of getting into the "free sexual intercourse" idiocy anytime soon.
To begin with, the real problem is how the male population of our world has decreased sharply.
Actually, in this town...
Or rather, this city,
there are no other men other than me.
And as such, the mission assigned to me by such a world,
completely just for the existence of the human race,
was to go on a impregnation spree.
Ena, who seems nothing like a giant per from the outside,
is a member of the tactical branch of said department, in reality.
Someone get me a tissue.
For me, who has been treated as nothing but a rare creature,
contrary to just being a member of the opposite sex,
it felt like the permit was there to just use me as a breeding horse.
Don't you think you're overthinking it?
I mean, they explained it to you, right?
Using that permit to have sex with a lot of girls,
and to get as many of them pregnant as possible,
is your responsibility, right?
Responsibility, huh?
If you can't manage that,
there's a strict penalty too.
Don't scare me!
By the way, the girl here is Kirishima Rin.
She lives next door to us, I've known her since we were kids.
Ta-ku-mi!
Sis!
Geez, why are you guys getting all serious?
It doesn't suit you at all, Takumi.
Saki.
By the way, Saki is Rin's older sister.
A sister like existence to me as well.
It's just that...
Her breasts, they're...
Alright, once more!
This is the last one.
Alright!
I don't think I can just pick randomly for this.
Team A will be here, and Team B will be there, alright?
Understood, our best regards!
So it'll have to be someone close to me, I guess.
It's not often for you to stay behind so late here, eh?
Hm? I heard a weird voice.
The hell do you mean by "weird"? Rude much?
Oh, it's you, Sara.
Due to your small size, I didn't realize.
Don't just nonchalantly touch people's heads!
What are you gonna do if I lose my genius brain?!
You sure like exaggerating things.
You really don't understand, do you?
If that happened, that'd be a loss for humanity in whole, you know!
This little girl is Katsuragi Sara.
She's a genius with a ridiculous IQ.
And for some reason, she seems to always treat me as an enemy.
If you're that much of a genius,
why don't you work on your height first?
Hmph, I'm not worried at all about my height or figure at the moment.
I see!
A genius, eh?
That means you hold some great genes, right?
That should be obvious!
So you finally realize how amazing I am.
Of course, I believe you should leave those genes behind then, correct?
That should be nature-
What was that?
Wait, Ibuki Takumi, that's...
Let's get on with that process, then.
Well, that was the gist of it, but...
The hell is this?
When I activate the permit,
it seems that the targeted girl seems to transform into an outfit that offers easy access for copulation!
Though, this is the first time I've seen it too...
You're the worst!
How does this feel, Sara?
Good?
No, it just tickles!
It's somehow starting to get damp.
You idiot...
To feel it from someone like you...
What an wonderful orifice.
Don't call it like that!
It's embarrassing to have your groins be played around with, you know!
This place of yours smells nice, and is delicious!
And besides, your hole's considerably wet now.
Stop, don't touch me there...
Your nipples are getting so hard as well.
Sara, I'm gonna do it.
My thing is supposed to enter here?
Are you scared?
I'm not about to back off due to something like your penis.
Don't underestimate me!
Your insides are really tight.
It feels great.
Oh crap, I can't hold myself back!
Your pussy's really great, Sara.
Don't refer to it with vulgar words like that!
Don't tell me, you're feeling it too?
My insides, it's piercing my insides!
Your insides are so hot, Sara!
It's vexing.
If you shove it in that much, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum already!
Cum?
Inside?
Are you about to cum inside me?
I'm cumming!
Doing it like this?!
I can't stop.
I can't stop myself, Sara!
Does my pussy really feel that good?
You're being so rough!
It's reaching up to my womb.
So hot.
Your insides are twitching.
You're about to cum too, right Sara?
Cumming!
I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum inside again!
Inside?
You're gonna cum inside again!
I'm cumming...
I'm being sucked inside...
It's really coming out inside me.
Ugh, my groins have gone numb.
It's all you and your stupid dick's fault!
Sorry.
Your pussy felt so good that I couldn't stop myself.
Shut it!
A compliment like that isn't about to make me happy!
I'm going to get back at you now.
Eh?
Wait!
You're smashing it, it's gonna break!
Don't lie, it's already gotten so big.
If I do this here,
it feels good, right?
Oh look, it's getting so stiff too!
Well, this is...
It's because of that lewd position of yours!
You talking about this?
Woah, amazing.
You're like this just from my feet.
Besides, there's precum leaking from the tip too.
It's twitching.
You're gonna cum like this?
Take this, this!
Wait!
If I release it anywhere but inside,
I'm gonna get penalized.
And you're saying that while being this stiff?
You didn't get to ejaculate properly, so let's keep going for a while longer.
Aren't you gonna cum if I just rightly rub it like this?
You keep saying that, but aren't you getting wet again?
Shut it!
You're the one who's flooded with precum!
Geez, so perverted.
Experiencing pleasure only once turned you like this?
If you keep that up, I'm gonna...
You sure about that?
If I remember correctly, didn't you say you weren't allowed to waste it?
Let me put it in once more!
What was that again?
Well, it's true that I can't reject your command.
But I told you that I'm still numb there, no?
Well, that is...
Getting so hard like this...
Do you really want to cum so bad?
I do!
How helpless...
Just keep quiet there,
I'll make you cum secretly!
Really?
In exchange, you'll have to refer to me as Madam Sara from today!
I'm cumming!
I'll keep it a secret from everyone.
Amazing, you still came so much?
You splattered so much of your lewd stuff on my face...
With this, I'll consider us even about you forcibly taking my virginity.
How about that?
I'm really generous, right?
You're under arrest!
Takumi, you should know better,
than to waste your semen like that!
Eh?
W-What?
Ena?
Your semen is no longer just your property.
Put it all inside properly!
Well, it wasn't by choice...
It's your responsibility for not being able to hold it in, just so we're clear!
Hey, that's not fair!
Now then, I'll have to penalize you with a heavy penalty.
What do you mean by "penalty"?
It seems to have tons of "energy" left, so,
we'll be sure to squeeze every last drop out of it, Takumi!
Wait!
Wait...
No!
Brother?!
What happened?
You alright?
I was squeezed dry.
You got squeezed...?
Every last bit of it...
Every last bit...
I'm gonna sleep for the day already.
Heya! Welcome back!
Takumi, happy birthday.
I've always been waiting for this day.
The present is, of course, none other than me!
Why are you in my room, Saki?
I came through the window.
That should be obvious, no?
Leave the small stuff aside.
It's not that simple!
Leaving that aside, what's up with that getup?
Now now, don't keep asking questions like that.
Especially when you've been unable to tear your eyes from my boobs for the last few minutes!
The truth is, you want to rape my tits hard with your cock, right?
Amazing!
So this is your cock?
It's already getting so hard...
I keep telling you, we can't.
If I end up cumming like this,
I'm gonna end up with a penalty.
Eh? Didn't you get a new permit from Ena today?
Let's test it out with my breasts first!
Why?!
Woah, it's so stiff!
It's so perverted.
I'll use it,
I'll use it, okay?
You're so hard!
The tip of your thing is coming in and out of my breasts!
This is all so perverted!
Due to rubbing your cock, my nipples and insides are starting to get hot as well!
If you do it that hard, I'm gonna...
You're already releasing so much precum!
My cleavage is already so wet,
and it's producing such a lewd sound!
There's no need to hold yourself back.
If you're gonna cum,
I'll be sure to receive everything with my breasts!
I'm gonna cum already!
Just release it like this.
Your big sis will make sure to look at you cumming.
Cum!
Give your big sis all of it through the titty fuck!
I'm cumming!
You came loads!
You released so much of your lewd smelling stuff on my breasts.
It's still twitching so much.
That's fine, I'll be sure to suck it all out with my breasts.
Sorry for cumming all over you like this.
It's alright.
Your big sis will make sure to suck up all of it.
Saki, your blow job feels so good!
How's it?
The taste of my first fellatio, that is.
It feels just like putting it in, right?
It's fine to cum inside my lewd mouth as much as you want!
Saki...
You can thrust your cock inside my mouth more!
It's also fine to put it out inside my mouth.
I'll be sure to accept it all!
Cumming, I'm cumming!
Give it to me, give me all of it!
Amazing, so much...
I'll suck it all out, okay?
Saki, I released a lot of it.
It's unfair for you to be the only one who's cum.
I want to feel good too.
I'll give you my virginity, Takumi.
How about it?
Don't you want to do it?
I do!
It fits so nicely into my crack.
Don't tease me like that.
That helpless expression you're making right now,
looks so wonderful.
Stop that.
If you keep this up,
I'm gonna cum outside again.
Geez, you can't be helped
Well then, I'll eat up your cock with my pussy.
Your hard thing is entering me.
Saki, you alright?
It hurts a bit, but I'm alright.
Leaving that inside, my insides are so hot they're getting numb.
It's hitting me deep inside,
at the opening of my womb!
This is the only part where you're really skilled!
Amazing, it feels so good.
It's my first time, but to think I'm feeling it so much...
Saki, I'm about to burst already!
Don't, I won't forgive you if you leave me behind and cum first!
So good, your cock feels so great!
Cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Takumi, cum with me too!
Inside!
Give it all to me inside my womb!
I want it inside!
I want all of your cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
You're cumming so much inside me.
I'm gonna suck up all of your stuff.
Oh crap.
I can't hold all of it inside.
Amazing, so much of it coming out from inside me!
More, do me more!
More, do it loads more to me!
Deep, you're so deep inside me.
Reach me even deeper with your cock.
Amazing, Takumi, you're amazing!
I'm gonna cum again.
Inside.
Implant your seed inside me!
You're cumming loads inside my womb again...
It's inside so deep...
More...
Do me more.
Give me everything you've got, Takumi!
Oh yes, do it harder!
It's okay to be rough.
If you do me so hard,
my pussy's gonna break.
I'm gonna cum again!
Impregnate me!
Impregnate me with your dick!
I'm gonna cum again!
Takumi...
You're so amazing.
So much of it is inside me...
You did me a lot.
And to think I went through the trouble of preparing a birthday present too...
The hell are they doing?
With them going at it like rabbits, there's no way I can get inside.
Takumi, you idiot!
Takumi, it's already noon.
We're scheduled to eat lunch with everybody today, right?
Uh, yeah.
Though if you think about it, it's still weird.
Just by showing someone this card once,
and commanding them to let me do it,
I can get them to have s-
The hell is going on?
Wait a sec.
That wasn't... what I meant!
The permit has bound someone?
What can I do?
Nothing, you can't take it back.
That can't be...
That means there's no way for you but to do it with me.
Eh?!
If you don't hurry up, you're gonna get penalized again.
This sucks.
What's up? Why are you so troubled?
Eh?
Does that mean you don't want to do it with me that much?
Well, that's not it...
Why not just do it then?
What?
You got it on with sis like that last night and all...
Rin...
You sure you're okay with this?
We have no other options, do we?
If the permit has chosen me,
then it's part of my responsibility to accept that.
I'm fine with you...
I've got to give Takumi lots of stamina.
"Stamina", huh?
She intends to go at it like rabbits with him again, eh?
Oh my, what might that be?
Everyone's watching me while I do this with Takumi.
This means we can't get lunch today as well.
Hey Rin,
Why are you in your PE clothes?
Because the next period was supposed to be PE.
Geez, what's with you?
Don't ask me weird stuff.
Amazing, it's already getting so wet.
It's so sexy.
Don't say that!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
So this is Takumi's penis...
Oh no.
It's completely different from when we were kids.
You want to put it in, right?
That's fine, just do it however you want it.
Everyone's gonna watch me while I graduate from my virginity.
Here we go!
It's going in.
So he did me like that too?
I'm really doing it.
Geez Rin, you're feeling it too.
My two sisters are really perverted.
Rin, you okay?
I'm fine,
I'll hold on.
It feels so weird to think that Takumi's inside me...
No way...
This is supposed to be my first time,
and everyone's looking at me doing it,
but my body's gotten so hot.
Oh crap.
I'm going insane,
and it's gradually making me even more perverted!
Coming, something's coming!
Me too, I'm about to hit my limits too!
I'm cumming!
Inside, release it inside me.
I won't forgive you if you do it outside!
My mind's turning blank.
Rin, you're about to cum too, right?
That place is starting to itchy, it's painful!
I beg you, stir up my insides more!
It feels great.
My voice's gonna come out...
I'm cumming!
You're sucking me in.
Rin...
It looks like she fainted, huh?
So it felt that great?
Oh man, if you show me something like that,
I'm gonna get wet too.
S-So this is sex...
Doing it in the public and raw at the same time...
You're quite something, Takumi, I'll give you that.
I wondered how it was gonna turn out for a moment,
but everything seems alright if you keep going like this.
Well then, next up is,
Adult Toys, Cosplay Sex, and pregnant breast-milk sex.