I think that was when it began...
Hazuki wore that super-short skirt, and underneath it...
Lovely Day. Our Seven Days Together.
Wait here, I'm gonna buy some drinks.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Sorry.
Can you hit the ball back?
Here you go!
Just what is going on there?
Thanks!
Did you see that?
What do you think?
That was on purpose, man!
Doesn't sitting around in the park put all kinds of ideas into your head?
Please!
Give me panties back!
No can do.
Didn't you mess them up yourself?
But...
More importantly, when I saw you earlier...
got a boner.
Will help me here?
A blowjob is enough.
Just sit still.
Come on.
Don't spill it. Swallow.
Gracias.
This is too much... it's too embarrassing.
Shall we do something more embarrassing together, then?
No!
This is too much!
It's all visible.
Be more quiet or someone will come.
I'm putting it in.
Hazuki...
You're wetter than usual.
It feels good.
I don't care.
Really, though...
It's fatter than it usually is.
What are you doing?
No.
Don't resist.
It will tear.
Please...
This is so... so... embarrassing.
So let's do it before someone shows up.
Are you happy?
Yeah.
Hurry up.
Man, I'm real sadist.
I'm having a lot of fun teasing the girl I love.
Hazuki... this is good...
Hurry...
I'm sorry, Hazuki.
But this was nice.
Thanks.
It was nice.
Three days later.
Huh?
I see... after we did it yesterday...
It's warm. Nao's warm.
Is this his...
But it's so soft and squishy...
It was never like this.
It's just as embarrassing as always,
but this is the first time I see it like this.
Is this what he sticks in?
It's warm and wet.
Amazing.
Hey...
Just go on.
You startled me.
Imagine my surprise when I woke up.
Stop.
You were sucking on it.
Touching, too.
I didn't t—
Yes you did.
Look, you're soaking wet here too.
No! Don't! That's embarrassing.
Hazuki, just go on.
I still have some time.
We shouldn't do this anymore.
It's abnormal.
I told you to stop, Nao.
We have to go.
We'll be late.
You sure seem to like it if I prod you here.
No, I...
Does it feel good, Hazuki?
Tell me it does.
It feels good.
You're hot as hell.
Fucking you has woken me right up this morning.
Where do you like it?
In the cunt.
Louder.
In the cunt. That would feel great!
What do you like in there?
A cock.
Your cock.
No!
Don't do that!
You liked this yesterday.
Can I keep pulling it in and out?
Not together. Not together.
It's twisting me up inside.
Come with your cunt and ass, Hazuki.
My ass and cunt...
I'm coming with both!
I'm coming!
Guess we're marked as absent for today.
More importantly... we have only one more day.
Today is the last day.
My parents aren't home for a week,
so I want you to do it with me in the meantime!
It was a week full of some many indescribable things.
Well, it's not like there won't be ways to do it from tomorrow on anymore...
But still...
Hazuki?
Yes?
Did you wash my school uniform?
Can you get it out when you're done here?
Sure!
Show it to me.
You're wet already.
Sorry.
Me too.
Sorry!
I didn't know you disliked it.
It's fun.
I've turned into a real slut.
Please, Nao.
Don't stop.
I'd never do that.
Besides, you did it for me to begin with.
I love it when you resist.
I love it when you are embarrassed.
And I...
I love you too.
I don't mind what you do to me.
So... So...
Okay... let's do it.
Is it embarrassing for you to show it?
Yes.
And it's a bit scary if I can't see anything.
Spread it more.
Like this?
Yeah.
I want to do something for you too.
It looked kind of dry there.
No!
Getting better now.
It's so warm in there.
It's swelling up.
Hazuki.
That's Nao's smell.
It feels like syrup.
Do you like my cock?
This fit in too.
That's good.
It's still inside.
Feels good.
This is good.
After that,
we kept doing it for 24h straight.
We did it and did it and did it.
And then our unbelievable week together ended.
Sorry if I kept you behind.
My parents seemed happy.
Don't worry, it was nothing.
I'm glad.
Take care on your way home.
I'll send you a message when I'm home.
I'll be waiting.
After this, more...
and I mean more...
between and Hazuki and me would follow.