Cleaning In Progress
Are you sure it's okay to just put up a cleaning sign?
And I'm a guy, I shouldn't be in here.
It's fine. As thanks, I'll pay in advance.
I just carried your luggage, you
don't have to do this much.
Guys get horny when they're tired, right?
Girls are like that too.
The plane ride was so exhausting, so I can't help it if I feel horny.
See, you're already like this.
K-Kanae-san...
It's huge and going inside me!
I'm getting laid as soon as I get to the airport... as expected of the southern island!
Daisuke-san, how are you finding my pussy?
It's so wet and tight inside you, it's the the best!
Then, be sure to move inside me a lot!
Okay!
Your cock is thrusting into my pussy!
Daisuke-san, you saw my tits!
My tits feel so good!
Kanae-san, your breasts are so squeezable!
Move around more, thrust it in harder!
Alright!
Daisuke-san, do you best, I'm twitching deep inside!
I can't hold it anymore!
It's okay, come, give it to me inside!
I'm coming!
I'm coming~
Onii-chan?
Ichijyo Daisuke-sama
Maya?
Ehhh?!
R E S O R T   B O I N
Chapter 2
~ The Harem Side of uhe Southern Island ~
Your plane finally landed and when
I thought you weren't anywhere...
Why did you come out of the girls bathroom?
And with someone like her...
I-I'm sure there's an explanation for this.
What kind of explanation?!
Daisuke-san, you see,
Was doing something good with me in the bathroom~
Something good...?
That's right, "something good", like this...
What are you doing here?!
Sorry, Mika. I just couldn't hold back.
As soon as you arrive you're with a guy? Geezus...
C'mon, hurry up!
Mika, you're always so forceful.
Daisuke-san, see you later~!
Ah, yeah...
We came to pick you up and you're
ignoring us to pick up girls?
N-No!
S-Since it's been a long time since we saw each other...
I'd be happy if you could take it easy on me...
That depends on you, Onii-chan.
Grandma told us to make you work hard, you know!
Geez, Mika.
Riding a good wave feels better than sex, yo!
Aww~
I was looking forward to a hot vacation with Dai-chan.
It can't be helped Nao-chan...
Daisuke-sama's so busy during summer
break that he can't even go home.
He should just leave work alone and come play with us.
Geez...
I agree!
But his grandmother is the board chairman
so he has to listen to her orders...
Otherwise he'll be discharged as a party member.
Grandma's too hard on him.
Here you go, please take your ti-!!
Dai-chan, play with us!
Hey, I'm in the middle of work!
What? We finally meet and you don't feel like it's destiny?
Yeah.
I don't.
Besides, why are you guys-
Like I said, it's destiny~
That's right~
That's totally wrong!
These two said they were on a trip during summer break so I didn't think I'd see them...
Is grandma planning something again?
Are you ok, Momo-chan?
Are you hurt?
Thank you very much, Daisuke-san.
My my, being held by Daisuke-san... I'm so jealous.
Kanae-san?
We meet again.
Why are you here?
Why" you say? Mika and I come here everyday we're on the island.
Although today Mika is out surfing.
Oh, I see, so Mika-san likes to surf!
Kanae likes riding too.
Or more like, I love being ridden.
No matter what the conversation
always goes "that" way, huh?
"Kanae, you're too faithful to your desires" is what Mika tells me all the time.
Oh yeah, we're having a barbecue tonight,
so why don't you come with Mika-san?
We need to get rid of the meat and vegetables left over from when customers didn't come due to the typhoon.
In that case, why not? Kanae loves meat~
I guess this is what they call "meat greed".
Who knows... Ow!
Hey, Onii-chan, what are you deciding on your own?
It's fine, isn't it? We can't finish
it all with just the three of us.
But still, it doesn't have to be her.
It's not something to get so mad about.
You gotta treat regular customers well.
You say that but your ulterior motives are so clear.
I-I don't have anything to feel guilty about!
Dai-chan, are you having a barbecue?
If you're talking about barbecues, it's our turn!
We love meat!
Even Nao-san and you are...
Nao-chan's faithful to her desires!
This is meat greed!
Meat~!
Do we have enough for this many people?
Um... That's why I told you...
Now then, how should we do this?
Alright!
Let's all find ingredients!
Get what you like and we'll barbecue it!
Good idea.
I'll do it too!
Me too!
Umm, Mika-san, it's dark and we can't see anything...
You have flashlights, don't you?
Now then! The time limit is one hour. Start!
Why are there so many women around Onii-chan?
For a barbecue, we could use mushrooms or something...
A ghost?!
Hey, that wasn't very nice.
Oh, it's just Kanae-san.
I was thinking of finding ingredients
with you; but it's okay now.
I found a big mushroom!
Look, it got big~
You made it big.
That's because I like it better when it's big and hard~
Get bigger, okay?
Daisuke-san, you have a fine cock!
And you have amazing tits.
How is it, do you feel good?
Yes, I feel great.
Really, something hot's come out.
Daisuke-san, you really like being done like this!
It's amazing, your tits are squeezing me.
Your cock wouldn't lose to my tits either you know.
Kanae-san!
Get even bigger, okay?
Oh my god, your tongue feels so good.
Oh ho, Kanae-san!
I'm coming!
Ahh, and I only just got you hard too.
I'm...
Still good to go!
As expected of yoy,Daisuke-san! In that case...
Kanae-san, here I come.
It's hard! It's so hard!
So good!
My cock and your womb are kissing.
That's my cervix, use your cock and fuck it harder!
Gotcha, Kanae-san!
It's so big, Daisuke-san, your cock is so good!
Come!
I'm coming!
Wow, it's dripping, so much of your hot come...
Let go!
What is this thing doing?!
Stop it!
M-Mika-san!
Mika!
This sucks, I have to do something.
You ero-leaf!
Mika, that isn't a leaf, it's ivy.
Bitch, stop arguing with me and help me!
Daisuke-san will save you.
Hurry up!
Mika-san!
Shit!
Onii-chan, here.
Okay!
Hurry!
Thank you. that helped-
Man, thanks. For a second I was wondering what to-
You're the worst.
Eh?
I overslept...
And?
Um... Maya?
If you don't need it you don't have to eat.
Damn that Maya. What the hell's up with her?
Um, Mika-san, this is?
Thanks for yesterday.
Nah, I'm glad you're safe.
I came to thank you.
So I'm saying I'll pay my debt with my body.
Kanae-san thanked me in the girls' bathroom...
Mika-san thanks me in the shower room...
I guess birds of a kind flock together.
What's with you, you don't look too happy.
You like this kind of stuff, don't you?
Kanae told me.
Yes, I love it!
Then don't hold back.
Yours is pretty good.
Your breasts are quite nice as well, Mika-san.
Looks like I can ride some nice waves with this.
Maya-chan, should I help with anything?
It's ok.
Alright then.
For Onii-chan
You like this kind of thing, right?
How is it? It feels as good as Kanae's, right?
I-It's amazing, Mika-san.
Hey, what about this?
M-Mika-san.
Your tongue is touching me, I-!
Come here, Daisuke!
Mika-san, that's...
You can still go, right?
Hurry up and do it.
Okay.
How is it?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Your ass is so tight!
That's good, you're doing well aren't you.
Mika-san, your voice...
This much is fine. Keep going.
Daisuke, it feels so good.
It's just like surfing on a wave.
Mika-san, your tan lines are so sexy.
Daisuke, fuck me more!
How's this?
That's right, show me a big wave with your fat cock!
Here I go.
Mika-san...
D-Daisuke, I-
I'm coming!
Me too, I'm coming!
Again?
Daisuke-san.
Onii-chan, you idiot.
The pot's burning.
Should I help?
Do what you want.
Onii-chan, are you mad?
No.
Tomorrow there's a fireworks festival, wanna go with me?
What about Momo and the others?
They said they'd watch from the hotel.
Okay.
Maya-chan!
Dai-chan!
Whoa! Hey!
Last year I came here with Momo-chan...
But this year it's just you and me, huh?
Y-Yeah...
Since when did Maya get so cute?
Sorry for being sulky like a kid.
If I was more mature I thought maybe...
Even though to you I'm just a cousin.
It started, Onii-chan!
Maya, I don't think of you as just a cousin.
Onii-chan...
Maya, show me your breasts.
I have small boobs so it's embarrassing.
That's not true.
No, Onii-chan...
No...
You're cute, Maya.
Onii-chan, this is so indecent...
No, not there!
It's nice and wet.
Onii-chan, it's embarrassing.
No!
Maya, is it ok?
Yeah, but it's my first time.
No! Onii-chan, your tongue feels so good!
Here we go.
Okay, Onii-chan.
It-
It hurts!
Are you ok?
Yeah, it hurt a little, but I'm fine.
Okay then, I'm gonna move a bit.
Right now, the two of us are having sex!
I'm becoming one with you!
I'm so happy!
Me too.
No! You're too big! It's all coming in!
I love you, onii-chan!
Maya!
No!
Who cares, it's just one!
Nao-chan, you eat too much!
But I wanna eat it!
Maya-chan...
Sorry, Onii-chan, for coming first.
Sorry, did it hurt?
No, just a little bit.
You were gentle with me.
Maya?
Now I'll do the rest.
When I look at it up close, you're really big.
Maya...
I might not be very good at this.
Maya, if I don't pull out...
Are you okay, Maya?
Yeah, its yours, so I'm fine.
Maya...
Wow, Onii-chan, you're still so energetic.
It's because you're cute.
It looks like doing it just once isn't enough.
Onii-chan, you perv.
Maya?
I'm not as big as Kanae-san, but...
Maya!
Onii-chan?
Maya, I love you!
Me too, give me lost of love!
Maya, it's about time...
Yes, give it to me, Onii-chan.
Does it not hurt this time?
Yeah, it feels a lot better Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, you're so good!
You already feel this good, Maya, you're naughty.
No, I'm just happy when you feel good...
No, Onii-chan, I'm going to come!
Me too.
Give it to me, Onii-chan!
Maya! Maya!
Onii-chan!
It's kind of embarrassing.
If you're embarrassed by only this much,
you won't be able to handle me.
No, Onii-chan, someone's gonna come...
It'll be fine.
Maya-chan, that's unfair!
Totally!
Don't misunderstand!
The love I feel for you and my innate love
for big breasts are totally different...
Onii-chan you idiot!!