7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
Let me tell you about the rules.
You win this game by opening the five locked doors and escaping to the surface.
You have either the role of the Solver or the Lock.
The key you need to use is in the corresponding room, inside a box.
The Solver is the one who selects the Lock, uses the key and opens the door.
All those with XY chromosomes are potential Solvers.
All those with XX chromosomes are potential Locks.
The man designated the Solver will use the key in conjunction with the mouth, rectum, genital organs
or the breasts of the woman designated the Lock.
If you refuse to take part or try to break the rules, a game over will result.
Stop this sick prank!
A game over means death...
10 Minutes Earlier
Roll call.
Rokukeikan Academy, Class 2-B, Keisuke Takatou.
Same school, same class, Miyako Andou.
Same class, Kanae Hokari.
Same class, Nemu Manaka.
Class 2-A, Rinne Byakuya.
Class 1-D, Rika Makiba.
What's going on? Please, don't!
I'm scared.
You don't have to be scared, Makiba.
English teacher, Natsuki Aoi.
You seven will take part in the game.
I don't want to!
If you refuse to take part or try to break the rules, a game over will result.
This isn't funny!
The lights are out!
She's gone!
Andou!
Is this really Andou, the chairman?
Amazing smell.
I'm about to throw up.
It hurts...
Kei...
Kanae...
Who's that?
My butt... my panties are going in...
This is so embarrassing.
This is more embarrassing than being naked.
I'd rather be naked than endure this.
Please, let go.
It hurts.
Why?
Why are you hitting my butt?
It hurts.
My butt is swelling up from your slaps.
I can feel it.
Wait!
Kei!
It hurts!
I'm a virgin.
It hurts.
It's going in and out.
Why, Kei?
Why?
What? Who is this?
Kanae? No.
Makiba?
Manaka?
She's my classmate, Nemu Manaka.
They say she has some western blood in her.
Her face sets her apart from other Japanese.
Her proportions are perfect.
She doesn't hang out with others or flirts with them
Everyone just stood around her, staring from afar. She was out of their league.
That describes her best.
And now she is hugging me?
More importantly, why now of all times?
I wonder what you are doing here.
Come on, offer an answer.
You...
Does this give you a boner?
She found out!
She knows!
She knows what I'm like down there right now.
Seeing her broken, dirty body is hot for you, right?
Is this really the time to feel like this?
What do you think will the others say?
They... would...
I'll keep it from them.
Obey me in exchange.
Well...
I guess three times all in all would be enough.
What do you say?
I...
Okay.
What choice do I have?
Good boy.
All right, here comes number one.
Manaka, I...
Call me Nemu.
Nemu.
Ne-mu.
Let me confirm something.
Kiss me.
Here?
Is this your first kiss?
Yes.
Mine too.
Get ready.
Not done.
Kanae?
Hey...
That...
I...
Kanae, this is...
This is how it is.
Kanae!
Hey, look at this, Kei.
Welcome to the main room.
Let us confirm the conditions.
Player count: six.
Locks: five.
Solvers: one.
Phase: wait for orders.
Release conditions mean that the Solver uses the key to open a lock and observes all rules.
Each time the Solver is judged to have opened a lock, a door leading to the exit will open.
There are five doors in total.
Let us resume the game.
Please assemble in front of the door with the flashing light within the next ten seconds.
The line marks where you are expected to assemble.
10...
9...
8...
We have to obey.
Everyone, go to the door.
Is this the line she means?
2...
1...
0...
Confirmed.
This is sick shit.
All players have assembled where they should.
I ask the Solver to step forward ten steps and turn around.
The Lock will be designated now.
The Lock...
Those are all the girls lined up there.
The Solver will designate the Lock himself.
You will be given thirty minutes to designate the Lock.
The Solver is asked to perform this task in the allocated time.
Should the Solver refuse to do this in the given time, the game will end immediately.
The same applies should the Lock refuse to perform its role.
"The game will end"?
I guess we will all die in that case.
Quiet.
That would be all.
Turn 1. Decision phase.
All players are asked to remain silent.
Everyone will die if I don't choose.
Nemu...
Choose me.
I have to choose.
Nemu Manaka.
Lock has been designated as Nemu Manaka.
Lock and Solver are asked to move to the next room.
The door will be unlocked.
It is now open.
Beginning countdown.
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
It has been confirmed that both Solver and Lock have entered the room.
The next phase will begin.
Starting release parameter phase.
Defining key and release parameters.
Should the release parameters not be fulfilled, it will be judged a failure.
The key and the release parameters encompass the physical and metal conditions of both Solver and Lock.
Physical and mental? How do you measure that?
Maybe the collar does it?
Beginning scan of vital functions.
Scan finished.
Offering key to Solver.
Presenting release conditions.
The Solver is asked to open the box.
Whatever transpires in this room is relayed in real time to the main room.
Once the lock has been opened, both audio and video broadcast will stop.
Look.
Those are the release parameters.
Lock: Genital Organs, Ejaculation Count: 2, Comments: Hard
The conditions of both Solver and Lock will still be monitored.
Please continue to adhere to the rules.
I guess cheating won't work.
Is that the key?
Yeah.
I expect you will rape me when I wear that.
Guess so.
This outfit is amazing.
I'm something like your personal sex slave now.
Lock: Genital Organs
Ejaculation Count: 2
Comments: Hard
It says hard.
I suppose that means you're supposed to mistreat and rape me.
Can you do that?
Fuck, yeah.
This isn't the place for love.
Go in without hesitation.
Into my cunt, you know.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I know that.
This is Nemu's cunt.
Is she a virgin?
Is she seriously a virgin?
My virginity...
You got that.
It hurts, right?
Taking her virginity with my cock and weird fetishes
feels so great.
I'm raping you.
Can you feel it?
I thought she was a sadistic control freak,
but there's some serious masochistic streak in her too.
You slut.
You're right.
I'm a slut.
I enjoy being raped.
I love this.
You've broken through the hymen.
You like seeing your girls in pain, don't you?
I can see it in your face.
I can feel his cock in me.
Get on with the rape.
I'm rock hard down there.
I'm going to come.
You're too gentle.
My head is going funny.
I felt it in my hymen.
Put some more violence into this.
You're not going to order me around!
You're smashing against it.
It'll break!
Still got the breath to speak?
Guess I need to crank it up.
He's coming... He's coming!
It's going in... your sperm...
I can smell it... and it's so hot...
So much...
She's tightening up on my cock.
Do you want to quit here?
Don't be a loser.
You're supposed to come twice.
Come at me like a crazed bear.
Do you know what you're saying?
My turn now.
Not my tits!
Don't do that to my tits!
My tits!
I'll scream at this rate!
Don't do that or they will melt.
You'll tear them off.
Does it hurt yet?
Does it hurt, Nemu?
It hurts.
They feel hot.
And... your hard cock...
is going in and out...
Yup.
I'll dig up everything there is to find in there.
I'll fill you up to brim.
I'll show you the meaning of rape.
Your cock, your cock!
It's gotten bigger again!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Soon, soon!
I'll get pregnant... from your rape...
So hot!
So much of it is in there.
Your cum tastes great.
I got your semen all over my skin and face.
Jeez...
After a faint "Jeez" at the end, nothing but raw breathing could be heard from her.
As I listened to Nemu's heavy breathing,
I had fulfilled my role as the Solver and the first door opened.
~Nemu Manaka   Chapter: Hell Commences~