What do you do after turning into a girl?
Blood pressure 85/65.
Breathing 110.
Pulse 140.
I was a normal high school boy, when one day I suddenly collapsed.
It was too late for anything, so I could only wait for my death.
I see. The cancer spread all over his body.
I accepted that my life was over.
Your doctor gave up all hope already.
But don't worry. There is a chance to survive.
A lady from a medical corporation visited me.
It's still just an experimental treatment though.
There is plenty of risk, but if there are no complications...
I only looked at her boobs, I wasn't paying attention to what she said.
And as a result of that...
The secondary effect of the treatment, Musashino Takumi turned into a girl.
Hey.
The story of how Takumi Swapped gender and Fucks a lot
You're kidding me!
No way!
I can't believe this!
Is this even possible!
Are you really Takumi?
So cute!
I'd prefer if you didn't call me cute.
Can I touch your boobs, Takumi?
Boys are terrible.
Hey, I'm a guy in this body!
But if you're a guy, you know how we feel!
If you don't let me, I probably never will touch a tit in my life!
Shut up, I almost pitied you.
Do whatever.
Great!
Wow, amazing!
Takumi, have you touched it yourself?
It's really amazing!
I did, but it felt weirdly good...
It got hard!
Your nipple's hard.
Are you enjoying this?
Well...
It's not bad though.
Not exactly.
I must act cooler.
So soft! You're wearing no bra!
Takumi, you smell great!
Hey, what are you doing?
Some new game? Playing pro wrestling?
Stop it! It's my boobs, don't grope them!
Sogahara?
Sorry. But you really turned into a girl.
Your body got smaller too, so your uniform is big on you.
Yeah, all the clothes I own are like this.
Then come to my place after school! I'll give you some clothes.
Will the size be all right?
This net design's so lewd! Not bad, Sogahara!
Try on whichever you like.
Girls' panties are always this small?
If I had my cock it'd poke right out.
Don't say weird stuff.
It's just my used stuff, but feel free to take any!
If I told the guys I'm wearing your used panties and bra, they'd be so envious.
Cut that...
But if you don't wear a bra, your boobs' shape will be lost.
Now that you turned into a girl, remember how to wear a bra, okay?
Girl, huh? Wearing stuff like these, I'm starting to understand it a little.
Since you're so cute already, you should act more girly.
Then the guys will be all over you.
Not that I'm happy about that.
All over me, huh?
Wow, cool!
You really look like a girl!
Amazing!
I know, right? Not that you virgins will ever get anything like this.
You're a virgin too, Takumi!
Stupid, I'm a girl now! It gives status to be a virgin!
He's totally abusing it...
Then show us how it's done, Takumi!
We're want to try stuff as well you know!
You're seriously crying...
What do you expect of me?
Confess...
Hold hands...
Kiss... Date...
Do something, Takumi.
I get it! You're creepy.
Rehearse with me then.
Then...
I love you... I really love you!
I'm so nervous!
Really? I love you!
I love you!
It's just practice so you should say it too, Takumi.
I... love you.
That hurts! Do it more gently!
Like this?
Hey, where do you think you're touching me!
What do you mean? I need practice in fingering.
Fingering? Are you mental?!
I don't want to be bad when it matters.
But here? Someone could see us!
It's all right. We'll cover you, so no one can see.
These really are girl's panties.
Get off of me!
You're so cute, Takumi!
Was this weird voice me?
Show me your pussy!
Your pussy's so wet already from my fingers!
Really? Let me touch as well!
Your pussy's really wet!
I... hardly have the power to stand.
I can only ask you to do this.
Won't you give me a blowjob?
Don't just pull out your cock like that!
Please, Takumi! I want to get a blowjob at least once in my life!
Why do I have to lick your stinky cock?
He's so hard... because of me?
What am I doing? I'm not interested in this!
Take it in like that.
So warm... and a bit sour.
Suck on it harder!
So good!
So hot!
Takumi's mouth feels amazing!
Takumi, are you a pro?
It feels weird that he praises my blowjob, but not bad...
Takumi, you're good!
I'm cumming!
He's cumming from my blowjob?
Then cum from my blowjob!
I'm cumming!
It's coming! I can feel the cum's smell!
What's this taste? Cum doesn't taste good.
That was amazing. It felt so good!
Next how about we...
Cut it there.
If you continue, they'll find you out.
Ryo?
Thanks for walking me home.
Nah.
I guess I might've gone a bit too far with them.
Seriously, they're hopeless.
Just because they're hungry for girls, this is overdoing it.
Ouch...
What the hell are you doing?!
You perverted woman, give Takumi back!
Let me go!
He's strong... Guys are so scary... scary...
Stop, Ryo...
My skirt lifted...
Your panties are all wet.
Because of what they did earlier.
Wait... Wait!
Don't! Don't touch me just like that!
It's okay. I know you want this.
Ryo's... is huge...
A cock is touching me there... So much for my virginity...
His cock...
The hymen... It'll break... It'll hurt!
It's in me... Who said this hurts?
This feels amazing!
It feels so great to have my hymen broken!
Not so suddenly!
I might be fine with this after all.
Ryo...
What? Why does it feel better? Because we're kissing?
Is that... deep in my pussy... my womb?
My womb's so happy!
It feels so good!
Damn, this feels too good!
Ryo is... Ryo is just amazing!
Ryo...?
Ryo, stop it!
Shut up, you pig.
Stop it, it hurts!
Don't do it so hard... Do it more... kindly...
This is because you sport a pussy!
Do you like it? Have you expected it?
No way I have! But though it hurts it gets better and better...
Why? Why?!
It's good... I can feel you in me...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming from this?!
Damn you, you pig! I'll cum in your filthy pussy!
He'll cum into me! I'll get cummed into!
Okay, cum into me! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
So mean... I can't take anymore...
This is a girl's peak?
Amazing! My pussy's a mess, and this...
It's the best...
And again... How many times will I cum?
My body can't move...
What's gonna happen to me now?
Can I go on being a girl after this?
It's been a month since I turned into a girl.
After I lost my virginity, I discovered the delights of girls.
Lately I'm masturbating all the time.
Getting turned on by my own body.
I played with my pussy all night yesterday as well.
But it's different...
It's not enough compared to back then.
I'm cumming... cumming?
Something's missing.
Blood?!
You're kidding?
I think it's just biology.
I thought so...
But now you're a real girl too.
Your body can now bear a child.
I don't even want to imagine it.
Let's go buy napkins or medicine after school together.
It's troublesome to be a girl.
Ta-Takumi...
She's being molested?
Takumi?
Are you all right, Sogahara?
Yeah, thanks.
Takumi?
It's all right now.
It's nothing.
What's this? He's sticking a finger in my ass!
I should just cry out loud.
No way, I can't!
Why? It's just my asshole!
If someone saw this...
No...
No... It's scary... A stranger...
Don't look... I'm a girl...
So embarrassing...
Takumi? Are you all right?
I see. This is interesting.
What is?
As a side effect of the genetic treatment, your genitals are extremely sensitive.
My genitals? No way!
Really?
Take that off already!
It's just as I thought.
This is bad... It feels amazing.
What is the next station?
Four of five more stations for me.
Why only my ass?!
Here... I'm lonely here!
My head's going weird!
I'm cumming from my ass...
I'm... I'm... cumming...
No matter how many times I cum from my ass, my pussy is still lonely!
What should I do? This way Sogahara will realize it as well...
But I can't hold back... I want it in me...
I want it!
Do it...
Quick!
Why does it feel this good?
This is it!
Takumi, what's wrong? Your face is so red.
Nothing... Don't worry, it's nothing.
But...
It's really nothing!
It's so deep in me!
Amazing! This is it!
Takumi...?
It feels insanely good!
Masturbation just wasn't enough!
I love cocks! I don't care whose it is...
Ryo's or a stranger's, doesn't matter!
There...
It feels so hot!
Two holes at the same time, this feels amazing! This is too good!
Amazing... This stranger's cock is amazing!
And his fingers too... My head's going blank!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming in you.
I'm cumming!
This... I'm a real girl... Biology... Babies...
I don't know... I can't think....
The train will now arrive at Gakuen-Sakashita.
Gakuen-Sakashita. Gakuen-Sakashita terminal.
Please take care not to forget anything on the train.
I was afraid he would never go away...
Takumi? Are you all right?
Sogahara... Being a girl is awesome...
It felt awesome!
Oh? Sogahara, if I recall right? How may I help you?
Takumi's gender swap is the side effect of the treatment, right?
Yes.
I have a request.
Next episode preview
Hey, do you know the TSF story is all about?
The story of how Takumi Swapped gender and Fucks a lot?
Trans-Sexual Fantasy. Which includes gender swapping of course.
By the way, shouldn't you talk about the next episode?
Ah right.
TSF Story Trans 2 is coming 2012 winter!
Grope! Gang rape! Human toilet!
Scheduled for 2012 winter
This time I'll do it with Takumi as well.