Kurenai.
Come on, enter a contract with me.
The Six Sisters of House Kiriya
Is it here?
Hey, the man over there!
Are you Daisuke Tokitsu?
I am.
I'm Botan Kiriya.
I could be your sister.
Come on, let's go.
Seems this letter wasn't just a prank.
I was a journalist in Tokyo,
but decided to be guided by this weird letter, and came here.
The sender was an energetic woman wanting to be a writer,
Kiriya Fujino.
However, she is presumed to have died ten years ago.
We're there.
Sorry I'm late.
Welcome, Daisuke Tokitsu.
I'm the head of House Kiriya, Kiriya Takaomi's wife.
My name is Sumi.
Well met.
You've become a handsome man.
I guess you don't remember.
That's not a problem.
You were little, and a lot happened since then.
Well...
This is Kiriya Takaomi.
Regrettably, due a long illness, his health is somewhat lacking in many ways.
I see.
Good to meet you, Earl.
I'm Daisuke Tokitsu.
Behind him stands his personal maid, Sagane Aya.
Nice to meet you.
Let me introduce the girls.
This is the eldest daughter, Nadeshiko.
Good to meet you, Daisuke.
Next to her is... well, I don't I have to introduce her.
What?
Introduce me!
Next to Botan is the third sister, Ai.
Next to her is the fourth one, Kurenai.
The last one is number five, Sumire.
Nice to meet you, Daisuke.
There's one thing I want to know.
The invitation said something about wanting to be a writer.
We're sorry about that, Daisuke.
That was just a pretext.
Please, sleep with my daughters.
I want you to get them pregnant.
Daisuke.
You have been chosen.
Chosen as the one man to produce heirs and to inherit the estate.
Daisuke! Let your Sis Botan give you a tour of the mansion!
Wait! I'll tag along!
Daisuke!
Give me a break.
Good to meet you.
Who are you?
I'm Ludmilla Mikhailovna Krasovskaja.
Call me Luda, Daisuke.
Why do you know my name?
Let's save that for when we are alone.
Hey, you!
Ku-re-na-i is my name.
Forgot it already?
Daisuke...
I won't lose.
Wait.
What's wrong.
Kurenai, enter a contract with me.
Did you sleep well?
Kind of.
What's wrong?
What am I doing here?
I put you here to sleep and rest.
Did you get to see the estate?
Yeah, Kurenai showed me around a bit.
Tomorrow she wants to show me the garden.
I understand.
Is something wrong?
I'm just a bit lost as to what's going on.
I got a letter that had your dead sister's name on it and came here because of it.
Normally I think nobody would put any kind of faith in that sort of letter.
Why did you come?
I'm a journalist.
I thought it would make for a good article.
I don't mean to offend, but many rumors have floated around about the Kiriya household.
What kind of rumors might those be?
The worthless sort.
But a man has to make a living.
I see.
Even now I wonder if this isn't some devious plan.
You are so skeptical.
I'm a journalist.
Hey...
Then let your sister disperse your doubts.
Nadeshiko...
You've gotten so hard.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Nadeshiko.
This should start... tomorrow...
I am delighted it is my job to ascertain that you are truly a man.
But I thought all this would start tomorrow.
It's so thick, hard and long.
I'm sorry.
This is making me so happy.
But...
Will you make me feel good now?
No need to hurry, my tits won't run away.
Ever since we first met, I've loved your tits.
Did you like that, Sis?
Jeez...
Come on, Daisuke!
Are you...
a virgin?
The daughters of this house all protected their innocence until the day they would lie with you.
I expected it to be more painful, though.
I can take this.
Now, please, take me.
All right.
Your penis is moving inside me!
Amazing.
Great!
Nadeshiko, milk is coming from your breasts.
When I feel your cock with my body I can't control myself.
Harder, harder!
Daisuke!
Good!
More milk is coming out!
Your milk is delicious, Nadeshiko.
You shouldn't taste it.
It won't stop.
Don't drink it!
I'll decide that.
More will come out if you do this.
Your pussy has gotten really soft.
I can go all the way to the end.
Take my cock!
My pussy... your cock...
It's in so deep.
Your cock is scrambling my insides.
This feels so good.
My breasts will...
I'm coming, I'm coming.
It's my first time and I'm coming.
This feels too good.
It feels like it will split.
This is good.
I'm coming too.
Let's come together.
Yes, let's come together.
Come inside me!
I'm coming!
Something hot is pouring inside my pussy!
So hot!
This is the job of a daughter of House Kiriya.
It felt so good.
I'm fine.
Decide!
No!
Never!
If I do that, you won't be yourself anymore.
I don't want that.
There's not a soul out here, is there?
The Kiriyas have always had weak skin,
so we can't stand strong sunlight.
I didn't know.
Is that why you have the curtains drawn all day?
Yup.
I kind of like the sun if it's as weak as this, though.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What's wrong?
What are you using this warehouse for?
It used to be my sister's atelier.
I see...
Don't you remember this building, Daisuke?
We played here together with Sumire and Fujino.
Did I really stay here before?
Did you really forget?
Sorry.
Don't worry, we can just make up for it now.
Who the-
Gon, this man is a guest of the House.
Begone.
Who's that?
Gon. He's a servant here.
He looks scary but he's harmless.
Hey, Daisuke.
Starting tonight we lie together, don't we.
Have you decided whom you will visit?
To be honest, I have doubts about all this.
Don't!
This is important for us!
Be serious about it!
Well...
You have no backbone!
Listen up.
The first time is important.
I think you should go to the one closest in age to you.
Isn't that you?
Quiet!
The first night is an important ritual, so don't stand me up!
Got it!
Make sure!
Hello, Daisuke.
Have you come to pray to God too?
Nah, I'm just wandering around.
Sorry I interrupted your prayers.
Don't worry.
Hey, Luda.
Is the first night so important for the people here?
Also, why me?
Sex has always been a sacred ritual too.
If you wish to learn of the reason you were chosen, come here once this day turns into the morrow.
Hey!
Sorry.
Sumisa, I have something to ask.
This will last for four days.
Whom will he choose, I wonder?
Yes.
Unrelatedly, why isn't Botan back yet.
I don't think you have to worry.
The importance of this ritual is known to her.
I guess.
Come in.
Welcome.
You really came.
Kurenai.
Wait a second.
I want you to enjoy this.
Please?
Sure.
Look, Kurenai.
What is it?
How exactly will I enjoy this?
Aren't you?
See, you are.
All men like footjobs.
Who told you that?
I heard it said here and there.
I like your cock.
It's also so hard.
You really got a hard-on when I touched you.
You like this, don't you?
Look, there's some pre-cum.
It makes it so wet and hot.
You like this.
Wow, this is cute.
You're not giving in, though.
Stop.
You want me to stop?
Your cock disagrees.
If you really dislike it, turn around and run for the hills.
Wow, I can feel your nervousness.
This is cute.
Don't you like this?
Remember, Kurenai.
Goes for you too.
Remember this, how you came because I touched you.
Look at how you are coming when I touched your perverted cock.
There is so much pre-cum.
I'm all excited now too.
Come! Shoot with all you've got!
I'll touch you until you do.
You're coming.
Amazing.
So much came.
It's hot.
You got it all over me.
Is it really my turn now?
Daisuke, this...
We shouldn't force this.
Let's stop here for tonight.
I'm sorry.
Hey, will you come back tomorrow?
Sure.
Really?
Yeah, I promise.
Seriously, Kurenai.
Ai?!
Sorry, I didn't know you were already in here.
I'll get out.
Stay.
I was waiting for you.
It is our duty to bear your children.
You can still do it.
Put your offspring inside me, Daisuke.
Do you like this, Ai?
I don't know.
It feels weird.
How about this.
You're already so wet, Ai.
Let's both feel good.
I'll put it in, Ai.
Stab me with your mighty cock.
Are you okay, Ai?
I'm fine.
Go on.
It's hot.
My insides are spreading out.
They're so hot.
You're feeling good, aren't you.
I don't know.
But...
Ai.
You'll feel good if you move your hips yourself.
Okay.
I can feel it inside.
I can feel it hitting inside.
This is good, isn't it, Ai?
It feels good now.
Your hard cock is going in and out.
No, I'll break, I'll break!
Ai, I will...
Come inside, inside.
Be the first to come inside!
Ai!
It's hot.
So much hot stuff came.
Ai, shall we take a bath together?
I have something to do.
A ritual, huh?
If you wish to learn of the reason you were chosen, come here once this day turns into the morrow.
Daisuke.
What kind of light is this late at night?
What is this?