OAV
Eroge!
Indulgently developing sex and H-games!
So what it comes down to,
is that our company faces an unprecedented crisis.
Because our last work was a failure,
we can't pay our employees' salary,
and if our next work fails,
that's it for Flower.
We have to make every effort to ensure our next project succeeds.
Everyone, we're having an emergency meeting!
Convene in the meeting room!
Shut up!
Shut up.
Himeno Kisara
Love Begins
Eroge!
Indulgently developing sex and H-games!
Our last work was soft porn, but we can't have a failure like that again,
so we'll challenge ourselves by doing a hardcore rape story.
So, what's this?
Ah, this boy.
I'll be working at this company starting today.
Huh? Say that again.
I'm Mochizuki Tomoya.
Nice to meet you.
Working here means employed? Or part-time?
Either way, are you serious?
We can't afford to do that!
Hiyori, say something!
Himeno Kisara
Age 21
E cup
I'm Himeno Kisara.
-In charge of artwork
-This is her third project
-Has been publishing with
a fairly popular doujinshi circle
I'm in charge of the art.
Virgin
That should be all you need to know.
What's with you? Don't look at me so weird.
I'm Fujiwara Momoka.
Fujiwara Momoka
Age
H cup
I'm the scenario writer.
-In charge of scenario
-Somewhat popular for writing
stories for BL magazines
Virgin
That is all.
Kosaka Yuri
Age
Kosaka Yuri.
C cup
Graphic art.
-In charge of graphics
-Somewhat known for selling out works from her digital art-related doujin circle
Virgin
Was I sleeping?
Sunono Nene
I'm Sunono Nene.
AA cup
-Owner, manager
-Director, Scripter
-Due to reasons,
lives at company HQ
I think I told you in the interview,
but I'm the company president and a super lady.
Virgin
32 yrs old
And so, your duties are...
Nene!
Where's the hot new guy?
Reina!
What do you need today?
Have you come to close the company down?
Good job. You can leave now.
I thought you guys wouldn't have a proper welcoming party.
Here.
No way!
Thank you, Reina!
Well, everyone, no more work today!
Time for a party!
Yay!
Jeez, you're a man, aren't you?
Don't you have any jokes or one-liners?
Shouldn't you have one?
Kisara is strong.
I like strong people.
That's why men are useless.
Aw, when you drink, your body gets really hot.
Listen up, people!
Let's strip!
Reina! You can't get naked today!
Uh, why not?
We're all girls, and there's no one else around.
It's like I'm not here...
Tomoya looks like he's got a great package.
I wonder if your dick has already been used.
Oh, sexy!
Hey, you'd better promote yourself more.
It's the job of a new guy to ingratiate himself into the company.
Uh, yes. Well then.
I've played about a thousand eroge.
And of course, all the games produced by this company.
The reason they failed, to put it bluntly...
The art, the writing, the coloring,
it's not erotic enough when you put it all together!
I'm bad at drawing, and I can't write a scenario or color,
but I won't lose to anyone in terms of my passion for eroge!
You talk big, so you must have a lot of real-world experience, right?
Well, um... I'm a virgin.
This isn't worth our time.
Then what's your real life experience?
Well, lately... I've been busy with work, so...
I'm not really a wordly person...
Lies.
If you're so insistent, then you'll help us flesh it out, right?
Literally.
It looks like you'll put those words to action down there!
Oh, come on.
I'm used to seeing these.
Ohho. Is this how the real thing is?
What's this!? Put it away quickly, Reina!
So it gets this big?!
Well then, Kisara, you better punish this wild kid.
Oh, yeah.
Leave it to me.
Something simple like this...
Hey! Don't make weird noises!
This is nothing!
What's this?!
They look delicious as if covered with dressing.
I brought you home, so let me off the hook - Reina
So was that for real? What's with me?
What can I do for them, when I can't do anything?
All right.
I'm so sorry!
You!
Well, he was a victim.
This is why you can't trust men.
There's something I want you to see.
What's this?
It's a document containing descriptions of routes from games that I've played that are especially erotic.
I thought it could be a reference.
All the ID's and basic data?
So coloring like this is sexy?
Info on how to make eroge sell?
You gathered this much data on your own?
That's great, Mochizuki.
Since you are women, you might not be very interested in erotic material,
but people who don't know erotic material can't make it!
I want to make Flower's next work a success!
You are really obsessed with eroge.
I get it. Thanks.
I have one more piece of data.
Even though a mosaic will hide it, your players will notice if you skimp on the detail.
Also, that hasn't been used, so Kisara can use it if she wants.
As if I'd use it!
Heave ho!
I'd like Mochizuki to check everyone's work.
What? This guy is a newbie.
None of you have really played any eroge, so the most knowledgeable about them is Mochizuki.
Hello, this is Flower.
Oh, we're indebted to you.
Thanks for the other day!
Here.
Um, boss?
Yes, what is it?
Isn't this room kind of hot?
That can't be.
That's right!
It's hot, but...
But but...
This is broken, isn't it?
Momo!
Yes!
If you turn on the AC while everyone's PC is running, it overloads the breaker.
You could've told me that earlier.
But what did you do last year?
Well...
Actually, everyone took off their clo—
Don't tell him!
We took off our clothes.
Because it was so hot, everyone was in their underwear.
You did?!
Tomura, check my art now!
No fair. My scenario comes first.
Tomoya, I was thinking of coloring this art the same color as my nipple.
Tomoya, pick me up!
What are you grinning at?
Ugh.
Someone say something to him—
Yay, it's cool!
We have no choice. We can't let these two embarrass themselves.
I suppose so.
Oh, just like a dream!
You strip too. Otherwise, it's not fair!
Okay.
We each have our own skills,
but we all act as if we weren't interested at all,
and we know we shouldn't be doing this...
I see.
Good work today.
Good night.
Well, I'm going to the public bath.
Okay.
G'night!
Why can't I draw well?
Hey!
You were peeking at my art all afternoon, weren't you?
Yes.
Well, what did you think of it?
I'm telling you to give your opinion!
Okay.
It's become more erotic than before, but
for example, this tit fuck scene,
instead of holding it between her breasts,
it looks like the cock is there just by coincidence...
Jeez, I can't really get the picture of what you're talking about.
Well, if you had experience, you might know.
Then, take it out.
What?
You're the only one here I can do this with to see it,
so take it out.
That's...
We'll do tit fucking.
It's fine, right?
It's just gathering materials.
I'll put up with you being my partner.
Eroge!
Why do I have to do this with a guy like you?
You're taking pictures of it properly, right?
If you don't take the picture right, you're dead meat.
Don't get my face in there because someone else might see it.
Okay.
Well, what now?
I've never done this before, you know.
You go up and down.
What's with this? It's moving around!
Men are sensitive.
With just a little bit of stimulation, it gets like this.
It gets even bigger?
Don't move around. It makes this harder!
This is just for the purpose of gathering data.
This probably feels good for you, right?
This is pretty...
Like this, right?
This is tit fucking?
Yes. Do it more intensely.
Then, how's this?
Men are such perverts for being able to get off on this.
Also, your expression is important for the guy to get excited.
Are you saying my expression isn't good enough?
No, that's not it.
For example, in a tit fuck scene, the heroine will typically gaze up at the protagonist.
Azunyan
It feels... good
Looking up... like this?
Make your expression a bit gentler.
I'm doing something so perverted like this, I can't make a gentle face!
Hmph! Even without you teaching me, I know how to do this!
Himeno, a bit gentler!
What? It's plenty gentle, right?
I can't get enough of a red-faced, angry Kisara!
You're giving out too many orders.
Even though you're the new guy...
What?
Just now, something strange came out!
It's sticking to my breasts!
This is a man!
Shut up! Then take it like a man
and be useful for my artwork!
It's good.
I'm gonna cum... I think...
Three
until ejaculation
It's dripping properly, right?
Two
until
ejaculation
Hey, are you listening?
One
until ejaculation
What?
What's this stuff?
It's hot.
You! You came on me again!
Eroge!
Jeez, I drank most of it.
Why does this place not have a bath?
I had no choice but to show you my breasts for the sake of research, all right?
I'm sorry, I became excited suddenly.
Oh, whatever. When I shower it'll come off, anyway, so I'll forgive you.
If it doesn't come off I'll hit you.
You already hit me.
I want to check the pictures, but I want to take a shower as soon as possible, so I'm going home.
Okay, good work today.
But to let me take pictures of her like this...
Could she possibly like me?
Heave ho!
Cold!
I'm sorry, Momoka—
This is why men are...!!
Somehow, it doesn't look real.
It certainly does look like a toy.
Shut up!
If you throw them around like that...
Shut up.
I'm just in a bit of a slump.
Stay after again today.
Okay.
I see. The base is like this.
Hey, don't move. It makes it hard to draw.
Even if you say that, being dressed like this is...
Under my foot is warm.
This is what you call a foot job, right?
Does something like this feel good to you?
Of course it does!
What do you call this part?
That is the head.
It's dirty and gross, but it's getting excited from my feet.
Strange.
But it's kind of interesting, a penis.
If I keep moving my feet, you'll come, won't you?
Yeah.
You're hopeless.
It was so sudden yesterday, so I couldn't see, but today I'll properly look at it when you come.
So tell me when you're gonna come!
Jeez, how much are you gonna cum?
At this rate, my socks will be ruined.
Well, I gathered enough data, so I'll let you off the hook.
Great! You drew it really realistically!
Compared to my skill, a penis is... nothing.
That's the way! Erotic art brings about an erotic scenario and erotic coloring!
Here, please learn the words commonly used in eroge!
Whats this? Penis? Semen?
What language is that?
Puss—
I can't say something like that!
It's your job. Come on.
P-Pussy...
Louder!
Don't get full of yourself!
Is this a fellatio scene?
Ah, I get what you're going to say already.
You have to figure out how to make it look erotic.
I know!
Like this?
Use your tongue on the whole thing.
For me to lick a man's penis...
Do people really do such a perverted thing?
But I feel kind of weird.
Am I getting used to the penis?
It's not... so bad.
It feels good. It's erotic.
Who are you calling erotic? You aren't gonna shoot your slimy stuff in my mouth—
I'm sorry. It felt so good.
Who said it was okay for you to come?
Now this isn't good material!
We're redoing it!
Is this me?
Sucking a cock with a perverted face?
You can't show this to just anyone, you know!
You can't watch it either!
Well, I watched it in real life.
Forget it right away!
Here, this gaping pussy, I think it would be more erotic if we had a matte finish.
Then it would be erotic if we added some semen.
Oh, Momo! This is sexy!
All that's left is to add something like, "Why am I feeling good even with this kind of man?"
Drawing on my experience.
Experience?
As expected, Kisara.
I guess so.
As the boss, I can't afford to lose!
For various reasons that would be a bad idea...
Kisara tried hard to gain more and more erotic experiences.
And she's pulling everyone in with the future of the company at stake to make the product more erotic.
It'll sell.
I'm certain of it.
The work is going well.
Finally, the next scene is...
Well, what do you think?
Of my art so far?
Yes, I think it's getting really good.
Tit fuck, footjob, fellatio, I think it's all perfect.
I hate to admit it, but it's because I worked with you.
So, the next step would be...
S-Sex.
What? Say it properly.
It's just you and me here.
Your thoughts are written all over your face, so I know what you want to say.
Which means, next is... of course... sex.
Um, if you just need data, I could search though as many pornos as you like.
No, just do it.
"Do it"?
It's not as simple as that, is it?
What are you saying after all this time?
You've used my body to jack off all this time!
So just do it with a smile like always!
I'll do anything to make this game a success!
For that, having sex isn't a big deal!
I'm going to get... as much experience as I can from this one time.
Fine. If you really don't want to do it, I'll find some other guy.
That's...
Are you really okay with it being me?
I don't really... It's your first time too, right?
Then... it's pretty much perfect, right?
Okay.
Sit here.
Hey, this is my data gathering, so close your eyes!
If I do that, I can't move well!
It's our first time. It won't be bad or good.
You're a virgin. Don't talk as if you know anything.
You're a virgin too, yo.
Hot! It's too hot!
Something like this is going to go inside me?
Kisara, are you scared?
No way.
Adults do this all the time.
It's a matter of course.
Just... put it in already.
You want to, don't you?
Then I'll put it in.
Okay?
You don't have to ask me every little thing!
Sorry, I get it.
It's inside me!
It's really going inside me!
I've taken her virginity.
Blood is really coming out!
With your penis... I...
And its deep inside!
That penis is deep inside me.
I'm...
having sex right now, aren't I?
Kisara?
Ow!
Your penis is inside me!
Going inside me!
It's so tight.
Penis...
It's deep inside. It feels strange inside.
So this is what a penis is like.
It's totally fine.
I shouldn't have worried.
Oh, man, I'm gonna...
I'm sorry for being a virgin!
No way. Already?
It's overflowing inside—
Hey, didn't I tell you to warn me when you're going to come?
Sorry.
You surprised me!
That's why virgins are...
I'm not a virgin anymore.
Did it feel good inside me?
Well, of course.
Well, I'll forgive you then.
But it's not fair for only you to feel good.
I'll take care of that.
No, not here. Everyone can see us!
My nipples are rubbing against the cold glass!
It's like the pain is going away, and I feel strange.
Since all this sperm is inside me, my body feels like it's going crazy!
Your love-juice is really coming out.
That's a lie.
I'm not that perverted!
Burn the image of yourself into your eyes.
You have to draw it!
I know it all—the shape of your penis, the hardness of your cock head.
It's burned into my vagina!
I'm gonna come!
I'll etch it all into you.
Come? Are you going to come again?
You're going to send that sticky sperm inside me again?
It's intense. It's rubbing. It's scraping inside me!
No, no!
It's coming out! A lot of it.
Even though I'm already full inside.
Kisara, we're still going.
Let me go already!
Let me rest!
It's best to have a lot of data.
Your penis is going all the way inside me.
It feels good!
Even though it really hurt at first,
somehow, as I got my fill of your sperm,
I can't think of anything but sex.
Your penis and my pussy are rubbing together.
I can't think...
My mind is full of your penis and my pussy.
This is what you should draw!
The heroine being pleasured by a thick penis!
Kisara, can I come on you?
You've already come so much inside me.
Okay, if you want to.
I'll let you.
Here I come, Kisara.
If you move that much...
I'm gonna come! Going to come!
I'm coming, I'm coming! I can't hold back any more!
So there's a scene after the heroine is raped when they all do bukkake on her.
This is good material for that, right?
I think so.
My body is hot.
It's like your sperm is still in my stomach.
Are you okay?
What are talking about. Having sex is normal.
This much isn't... anything.
Not anything.
Oh, crap, she's too cute.
Her personality is tough, but she's forward looking and won't give in to anyone.
I like her.
I wonder what I should do now. Should I confess to her?
Um, I...
Don't misunderstand me! I don't really think anything of you.
I'd be troubled if you want to be my boyfriend!
We are just coworkers!
Get it?
I told you.
I warned them.
I said it before Nene.
Idiot!!