I'm off to school, everyone.
Walk quickly, Milady.
It you've been taking your time on your way to school lately.
We've received numerous calls regarding your tardiness.
I'm very sorry. I'm trying to hurry, but...
Thick and Creamy Milk Pot - First Load
FAKKU! Presents
I, Iori Yukidoh, was born into a local well-known, wealthy family.
My parents, wishing for an heir to the family, first gave birth to my sister, Kaori.
They desperately prayed for their next child to be male, but instead I was born.
Much unlike my intelligent and sociable sister, I was an incredibly timid, frightful little girl.
Lately, my family's made no effort to hide their disappointment in me.
Ah...Oh no!
It's still morning, but I'm already aroused!
I can't stand it!
I wanna tease it!
I wanna stroke it!
Just real quick. A little bit won't hurt...
I've got to jerk off!
P-penis!
I wanna stroke my dick so bad!
I've got so much milk saved up. It's nearly leaking out the end!
My dick's so hard!
Even this gentle breeze makes my dick feel so good!
Oh god! My dick's so stiff!
I wanna squeeze it! Tug on it!
My panties are in the way!
My dick's in pain, so I've gotta milk it!
Some came out!
Trying to resist fapping makes it hurt so bad!
I love fapping! I love it so much!
Oh god! My dick feels so good!
My cock's saying good morning to me!
My cock wants to say hello and blow its load!
Oh look, a utility pole! I bet it feels really good!
I wanna grab hold of it and let my cock juice explode all over it!
I'm gonna rub my dick all over this hard, thick pole!
It's so hot!
I'm rubbing my burning hot cock up and down this pole!
Oh, I bet it'd feel really good to just cover it in my semen!
I'll mark this pole with my filthy cum like a dog does with its pee!
Up and down, up and down with my cock!
This feels so good!
I wanna pee standing up, just like my uncle!
I'm gonna pee out of my dick!
Oh, I'm so embarrased!
It's so humiliating for a girl to pee standing up!
Watch me urinate, everyone!
Watch me while I fondle my cock and balls and wet myself!
At this rate, I'm going to shoot out cum instead of pee!
I'm gonna blow a nasty load of cum while I stroke my dick!
I'm gonna shoot cock milk while I fantasize about urinating!
Cock milk! Dirty, sticky, fap juice!
Then we plug this in here, which get us that.
Why didn't they shower after their morning practice?
They're practically oozing with sweat and pheromones!
Oh no... If they keep releasing this scent, I'll...
I have to resist!
Penis! Dick! Cock!
It hurts! My dick hurts so bad!
Oh penis god, save me! Make it stop!
My pussy's dripping wet, and my dick's twitching and pulsing!
Meat! Mash! Shaft!
It's bursting with milk!
This is bad. My cock won't calm down!
Everyone's going to see my giant stiff rod!
Umm, excuse me...
What is it, Yukidoh?
I'm sorry, but I'm not feeling well, so, umm...
You need to see the nurse? Alright then, go on.
Thank you. Please excuse me.
She always goes to the nurse around this time, huh?
What's the matter with her?
Ahh, such a pungent, powerful smell of men's penises!
This is heaven! My cock is itching with excitement!
Everybody's in class right now, so noone will come in here.
I can masturbate in peace!
Hey, I told you to calm down!
My cock's poking out from under my skirt!
It's become so engorged!
Bad penis! Naughty penis!
You fat, naughty penis... I'll stroke you nice and hard, okay?
So good! My dick feels so good!
My cum's already about to come shooting out!
N-nooo!
Cock milk! Hurry and blow your milk!
Dick juice!
I wanna keep cumming!
I wanna spray my nut milk all over the bathroom!
Nut milk...
I just thought of something wonderful!
Perfect!
An artificial pussy made from a urinal and my panties!
My idea is a complete success!
The feeling of rubbing my dick on my panties is mind-blowingly incredible!
Normally boys only pee in the urinal, but I'm gonna fill it with cum instead!
This is great! My panty-pussy feels so good!
I'm fucking my panty-pussy!
I'm a girl, but I'm masturbating to the thought of a pussy!
I wanna fuck a girl's pussy!
I wanna fuck so bad I can't stand it!
This is way too erotic!
I can't hold it anymore! My cock's gonna blow!
Cumming! I'm gonna cum!
My dick! My dick's gonna explode!
My cock's gonna explode!
Oh yes! Cumming feels so good!
Uh-oh, I did it again...
The smell is so strong...
My naughty scent... Oh no, I'll be exposed!
If I keep doing this, everyone will know my secret!
Hey, you're Yukidoh, right?
This is the men's room. What are you doing here?
I... umm...
What've you been doing all this time?
'Fess up, babe.
Impossible... My beloved Iori...
N-no, wait!
I was, umm... Cleaning the restrooms!
While covered in cum?
No... This is so wrong...
I always admired you from afar...
I'm sure we could figure out what you were doing if we peeked under that skirt.
N-no, don't! What're you doing!?
C'mon, give yourself up already.
Oww!
A dick!? She's actually a he!?
Nooo! Don't look!
So you're a tranny, Yukidoh?
Is all that jizz yours?
You're wrong! I'm not a transvestite!
I'm just a girl!
Iori, I...
Iori!
Noo! Don't finger my asshole!
Iori! Iori!
This is Iori's asshole!
Noo! Not so deep!
Don't play with my ass!
Please, not my asshole! Not my asshole!
Not there! Please, I'm sensitve there! Stop!
Iori... I can't believe you like it in the ass!
Ohh, Okazwa... Right there!
The pleasure of having a man fingering my ass is...
More!
Harder!
Finger my ass harder!
My asshole's so sensitive! I'm gonna go insane!
Ohhh! That feels so good!
Check it out! His dick's rock hard just from getting fingered!
Iori...
Oh god, my dick!
Don't look at it, Okazawa!
My asshole's twitching!
Right there! That's the most pleasurable part of my ass!
Oh god, I'm cumming!
You're not even touching my dick, but I'm gonna cum!
C'mon, let us see you cum!
No, please!
Don't make me cum!
Don't make me shoot my cock milk!
C-cumming! I'm cumming!
Please, no! Don't blow a huge load!
I'm so ashamed!
Don't watch me cum!
They saw it... Everyone saw my most humiliating moment...
Iori, I can't take it anymore...
You may be a guy, but I'll do you anyway!
Okazawa?
W-wait! By "do", do you mean my-
Oh god, my ass!
I-it doesn't hurt!
My asshole feels good!
N-not again!
Ahh, your dick is amazing!
Your cock's going in so deep!
I... I'm having sex...
I'm fucking my beloved Iori!
Yeah, but you're fucking a dude in the ass, bro!
I'm having sex! I'm being fucked in the ass!
Being skewed by your dick feels so good!
I love anal sex!
I love how your dick scrapes my asshole!
My ass feels amazing!
I'm gonna cum again!
I... I'm gonna shoot cock milk again!
When he thrusts, I can feel the pleasure in the tip of my dick!
I can feel my cock milk coming!
I'm gonna cum too, Iori!
Do it! Blow your load!
I'm cumming from anal sex!
Your thick semen's flooding my asshole!
Me too! I'm gonna spray my cock milk too!
Cumming! Cumming!
My milk! My cum!
What the fuck's wrong with this guy?
Shit, now I'm hard too...
Wow... Now everybody's horny...
Now it's our turn to tease you.
Take this!
If you treat me so roughly, I'll break!
But it's SO good!
I beg you! Somebody fondle my cock!
I was stroking myself before you all came in!
I love masturbating so much!
Please tease my cock!
Rub my dick!
It's been my dream to have my dick stroked by a man's big, rough hands!
Please! Squeeze it!
Yes! Stroke it harder!
Like hell I'll stroke some tranny's nasty dick!
Hey, that's a pussy!
So you really are a chick!?
I thought it was awfully wet down there!
So she's been leaking love juice, huh?
Oh no! They found my female parts!
Don't look at it!
That place is off limits!
I can't use that place until I'm married!
N-no, don't tease it!
So she's a hermaphrodite...
You're not a guy after all, are you, Iori?
I'm a girl!
A normal girl with a pussy!
A girl with a penis who loves doing naughty things!
So please! Please squeeze and stroke my cock!
Okay, if you wanna masturbate so bad, I'll help you schlick instead!
If you let me fuck your pussy, I'll jerk you off.
You mean it? If I let you, you'll stroke my dick?
Okay, you can fuck my pussy.
It's my first time, but fuck my sloppy, wet pussy!
Just please promise me you'll  jerk me off too!
Promise me! Promise my penis!
Yeah, sure thing.
Yes! Oh my god!
Oww! It hurts! It hurts!
Mommy!
Save me, Mommy!
Stroke it! Stroke my cock!
Stroke it and ease the pain in my pussy!
You promised me!
The head is pounding!
If you don't jerk me off, I'm gonna die!
Okazawa, please stroke me!
You want me to do it?
There you go, Yukidoh.
Don't forget these either!
My pussy and asshole are being ruined!
And my balls too!
I'm in heaven...Oh god, my dick!
My dick's being rubbed!
My ass! It's so good!
My cock's being stroked!
Milk my dick! Make me cum!
Let's see you beg for it, Yukidoh!
If you do it right, I'll jerk you off.
O-okay, I beg of you...
My name is Iori Yukidoh, and all I think of is dicks.
I'm a loose, slutty dickgirl!
I've been masturbating since this morning, and I came over and over again!
I'm your little cock slave, Masters!
I'll pleasure you whenever and wherever!
So please jerk me off!
My dick is so lonely!
Tug on my naughty dick!
It's fucking gross to use my hand, so I'll cover your cock in my jizz instead.
W-with your jizz?
You'll cover my dick in your cum?
I'm so happy! That'll feel so good!
I'm surrounded!
Everyone's staring at my package and masturbating!
I love it!
Cover me in semen!
I love teasing my cock even more than my pussy or asshole!
Here it comes! Take this!
This is it! Everybody's cum!
My dick's being covered in semen!
My cock is going to cum!
My balls! They're drowning in your jizz!
I'm gonna blow!
Oh no!
I did it again!