How is it? It's gotten way better, hasn't it?
Yeah!
I know! Praise me more then! You're allowed to praise!
Not that getting praised by you is such a big thing.
But I can't lose to Kisara!
I see. If it's all right, I'll carry on.
Tomoya, a total eroge maniac joined the company in an emergency.
As the result of Kisara's pervy sacrifices,
this last try of Flower, facing bankruptcy might be good after all! It might even sell!
It might save us from bankruptcy! We have hope!
We"re nearing the end of development too, with debugging and then we create the master disc.
Let's do our best, freaky boy Tomoya!
Then I'd rather be eroge maniac.
Eroge!
Indulgently developing sex and H-games!
Soaking wet?! Beauty Creators Chapter
It's been three months since Mochizuki joined us.
It's been so long?
It feels as if it was last week.
Really...
I still feel as if it was still just the four of us.
You're mean.
He's doing his job, doing errands, and maintaining the homepage.
We still have lots of work to do, so let's do our best together!
The cuteness was overwhelming in Kisara's pictures,
but now she draws erotic scenes that would fit in the best games.
Momoka's scenarios weren't erotic either,
all were texts like a romantic flowery garden,
now she uses rude and mean lines as well.
And Iori's stuff lacked all kind of life,
but now it's all bodily and suggestive.
The president is still the mascot of the company, getting hugged and patted,
but now she can say what she wants as the director.
I'd be troubled if you want to be my boyfriend!
Mochizuki, will you check my drawings?
Sure.
Right, I shouldn't be all about Kisara.
Momo, I'm leaving first! Don't stay for too long.
Leaving too.
I'm going to take a bath!
Okay!
This doesn't fit, it's wrong.
Something's wrong, Momoka?
Nothing! I'm just a bit stuck with this.
This much I can solve by myself, so don't worry.
Sure, but if I can help with anything, just ask.
Really? Then.
Why do you look at me so opposingly? You should be grateful!
This noble lady offers to use your filthy thing for reference!
There's no line like that!
Shut up. Just try to be useful.
I'm not a masochist!
How long can you keep saying that I wonder?
For me, controlling the desires of men is easy.
I'll prove that for you.
What's wrong? You're only staring at my boobs.
Do you want them?
You're really just an animal, grabbing them so strong.
What? By chance you want to put your filthy cock in me?
You want to get it in you, don't you?
Oh? You're still talking impudently.
You're all lively. Maybe you want to have sex with me, with your pig cock?
I do.
What? I couldn't hear you. If you don't say it, you won't get no sex.
Please let me put it in!
My cock in your pussy, miss Momoka!
You said it well. I'll let you put it in.
But in exchange, if you cause me pain, you'll have to pay for it.
This is your cock? With this size you can't satisfy me!
Just because your boobs are a bit bigger than usual?
You're still talking back?
Seems your cock needs a bit training of slavery.
My pussy will give you all the training.
You'll turn into a masochist cock that wants to be used!
You're so tight!
It's so nice to be held by her, her shape matches me perfectly.
You're so happy with my pussy?
You... You'll offer me your cock and live in my service forever!
How dare you act like that in my pussy just after putting in?
You're as wet as it gets as well!
What are you saying? No way I could get wet from your filthy pig cock!
Very well. I'll punish your cock with my pussy so you won't ever talk back again.
See? Your dirty precum is flowing!
It's unfair that only you let your juices in me.
Open your mouth.
Very well. To you pig, going wild with your hard cock in me, I'll give this.
Oh? Who told you you can touch my tongue?
Know your place.
How about it? Is it delicious?
What? What?! Your cock!
You're really a simple pig!
You got carried away and now try to twist me around with your cock!
You're digging into my pussy!
This one's so annyoying, tickling my boobs!
Don't do that!
What? It's so embarrassingly hard!
Your filthy nipple is mine to do this!
So vigorously... You're cuming into me...
You're not bad, you cock-lover sadist princess?
You too, you masochist filthy pig.
Now I'm the princess deflowered by the delights of the cock!
Now I totally get the image!
I'm glad about that.
Now like this... Now like this!
Umm...
No! Not that!
This is bad.
Could you stop for a moment please?
What's wrong? You went crazy form the heat?
Do I look crazy to you?
You do, that's why she said it, I think.
Really.
What's wrong, Mochizuki?
Your work effectiveness is decreasing.
Shouldn't we go out to have some fun somewhere?
Have fun? Where to?
Such a great view!
Be grateful for my car.
Thank you very much!
Reina, let's play beach volleyball!
Mochizuki, if you're not doing anything, you join too!
I'll pass for today. I'd get covered in sand.
Me too, I'm not fond of sports.
A summer bug fried by the heat of the sun.
I'll teach you manners and obedience in beach volleyball!
Mochizuki, you were a nice employee.
So cowardly! Is this how adults play?
Adults are supposed to use their heads!
You'll regret making me your enemy!
I could dodge such a weak ball with my eyes closed!
Looks like your head's empty!
So stupid.
Are you all right?
If it comes to this...
We have to run away!
Why me too?!
Wait!
Adults don't run away!
Why are adults chasing then?!
What are they doing?
It doesn't look like volleyball.
The eighth wonder of the world!
This is one big hole.
Sorry, which way is the toilet?
Ah, this way.
Umm, Iori, where is the toilet?
Here.
Huh?
Here. My mouth is the toilet.
We're just at a yellow shower scene. I want to know more about piss!
Come on, it's all right. Don't hold back.
What's wrong with her?
Is she serious? No way...
This is bad...
What's wrong? You won't do it?
It's just I'm this way?
So? You can't do it if you're hard?
Yes.
Then I should just relieve you and make your cock melt.
Your cock is getting harder and harder.
Iori, I'm...
It's okay, cum!
I know the taste and smell of semen.
Now I want to taste it with my pussy.
Look, in here.
You shouldn't, Iori...
Amazing!
It hurts just as I thought.
Your cock's so thick!
Feels so good!
Make our skin touch!
Let's rub together!
If you're too loud...
It's okay.
But I want a stronger smell!
Smell?
I want it! I want it!
So wild!
I can't take anymore!
This is the strongest smell I ever felt.
It's so thick, I can hardly get it off.
You can do it now?
I'll really do it.
She was such a person?
Hurry, Nene.
If you don't do it quick, the crabs will eat you.
Don't just look, help me!
What are they doing?!
It's over. We have to go home.
Let's come again together! Next year too!
Yeah, you're right.
This was a fine day!
It really was!
Yeah.
Tomorrow the fun is starting!
Debugging, huh?
Let's do our best.
You're going home too?
Yeah?
I have a bit of a request.
Come in.
I could even pay for it.
That's from back then... I want to see it again!
Skip that! We have no time for that!
So you drew a dojinshi as well?
Yeah. But we're getting more busy from now on, so I want to get it done tonight.
I see.
But where should I fill it all?
Umm, how was this one again?
What do you think?
I asked because I don't know.
Just kidding.
Let's... make it the hair. Yeah, the hair.
The rest is all right in black.
I wrote in the directions to make it simpl--
Hey, what are you doing?!
Sorry that I didn't realize you were inviting me so hard...
What are you talking about?!
Kisara!
Don't!
It's been a while since I've seen your ass.
Don't grope it!
Why are you so hard already?!
It's the spur of the moment!
You smell so sweet, inviting my cock!
I'm not inviting it! Not at all!
Then why is your pussy so wet?
It's not... It just got like that.
Also, there's no scene like this in the game!
Don't just swing your cock around like that!
Your pussy is so wet it's dripping.
If I don't do something about this, the floor will get stained.
Your cock's in me! In my own room!
If you do it so wild in my pussy I won't be able to use this as a resource!
It's alright! With your head, concentrate on the drawing!
With your hips, on sex!
As if I could do that! I'm impaled on you!
Don't come in so deep! My neighbors will hear me!
Who cares? You're an adult woman with adult desires!
I don't want my neighbors hear me having sex!
You're rubbing me so hard!
My insides are melting!
You just want to enjoy this as much as you can, right?
Not at all! Not at all!
But I can't resist! Your animal cock is taking me!
It's all right. You work better if refreshed.
You idiot... Your hard cock is the only good thing in you!
Don't grope me!
I'm about to cum.
Don't... I don't want to be cummed into after such a dirty sex!
Your semen's filling my pussy!
Your pulses are filling me with semen!
I'm cumming too... Your animal cock makes me cum...
Don't... I'd cum too much...
Don't worry about it. I won't let your perverted pussy cum tonight.
A filthy, hard cock is invading my pussy!
More... Do it harder in me!
If you move so hard...
Shut up! Just because you're an animal with a big hard cock,
I'll squeeze your cock to pulp!
Hurry, move more and turn my pussy inside out!
If you want it that much, I'll turn your violent pussy into a helplessly cumming pussy!
Your cock is amazing! You're twisting my insides all around!
It's pushing so deep in, hitting me in so deep!
No! I can't hold back anymore!
My buttocks are raped by a big cock!
You're rubbing so hard my butt and my pussy are both cumming!
My neighbors heard you teasing my pussy for sure...
I love cock...
What's wrong with you? Now we left early for nothing!
I'm sorry.
As a punishment, you'll get no payment!
I got my payment just now, and quite generously as well.
You're really a monkey!
Idiot! Stupid, stupid idiot!
We're done.
Now I only need to put it together. I can do that alone.
You really worked hard.
I'd rather have booze instead of juice.
You can't have booze, that's for sure.
You'd do something weird again.
Hey...
You love me, right?
Yeah.
You really worked hard today. Umm...
If you're fine with it, I might even agree to go out with you.
Huh?
She refused me once already, then why now...
Has she done all this today just for this?
Come on, say something already!
I-It's not like I care about you or anything!
Not at all.
I'd be the happiest.
What's with that expression? Are you making fun of me?
It would even occur to me.
I know you are!
Idiot! You stupid idiot!
She's one troublesome girl.
Say something already.
You're so cute, Kisara!
You don't have to be shy!
I'm not! Not at all!
Let me go, you idiot! Stop it!
Cancel going out then!
Don't go killing yourself.
Geez... Stupid.
Debug
Saving electricity!
Iori, the cock's already in her here, so you should add some juice!
I'll do it. But then the pussy will be all sloppy.
Who put this script here?
"If you put in the cock it sounds like a cannon"?
Like a cannon? Where is that?
That was me! I edited it, did I do wrong?
Cock this... Pussy that...
All the innocent, flowering girls matured splendidly.
But when is this gonna end?
Master disc
Give me more cocks! More semen!
Warm me with your hot semen!
No problem here either.
Are we done then with the game?
It's all right! Everything's okay!
We did it! We managed to do it! We did it!
We really got it done!
I'm really tired though.
Finally! Finally...
The new Flower game, complete!
Everyone, thanks for your hard work!
Thanks to you, we finished the game without problem!
Thank you so much!
Cheers!
I'm glad I could join this company.
I'm happy I came here too.
Me too... This is the best!
Yeah. Really!
I'm so happy!
Congratulations! You're done with the master disc!
Reina, why are you drunk already?
We should celebrate! I can't resist drinking now!
Let's do the usual!
But this is a bit too much...
You're so sexy.
I think we should say thanks to him for his hard work.
One more!
What are you doing, Reina?
Then me too!
You can't, Nene!
It's still not over!
You woke up? Good morning!
Why are you dressed up like that?
You put it on?
You said you wanted to see it.
No... Your cock is going wild in me!
We're free until next week, so until then...
Let's do it a lot!
Sure. I love you, Kisara.
I love you too, so much, Tomoya!
Come again, Tomoya.
Don't ever let go of me, okay?
Of course.
I love the feeling of your cock filling me!
Your cock exploded in me!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
Tomoya...
Kisara...
What are you doing?!
I told you!
I'm here to stop them!
Nene said we could use this for our next game.
So nice, doing it in the middle of the day!
Even Reina?!
Idiots!