Let's go!
Pass it to me!
You want special training to overcome your anxiety?
Yeah.
I get really scared when the matches start and can't remember half my training.
That must be tough.
Let's see...
I think I can do something about it with you!
Any training you suggest is okay!
Even something I might find indecent.
Seriously?
Seriously?!
Ok... ay...
Special training?
My sister is getting special training from the coach?
Schoolgirl Hips in Action
Chapter One Beach Volleyball Club
Take your hands away.
Let me get a good look.
Okay...
Here.
Many people will see you during a match.
I have to be able to conquer your shame.
But it's so embarrassing.
The bikini is so skimpy too.
I'm sure you wear it for your boyfriend all the time.
I don't have a boyfriend.
So maybe you whore yourself out to old geezers you don't even know the name of?
I...
I don't...
You probably suck all their cocks in some hotel room.
What should I do...
There are so many cocks...
This isn't going to end well...
And you don't just suck them, I think.
You also fuck them.
Coach...
Don't rub it...
And finally they shower your pretty face with semen.
I bet they take pictures of you with their phones while you're covered in it.
Coach...
I'm going to come.
I'm gonna come!
Did I tease you too much?
It was part of your training.
Coach...
Let me suck it.
I can't believe you suggested this yourself.
A tip of the hat to you, Saori.
Oh, no.
I'm getting excited when he says these things.
I can't stop.
Holy crap.
It won't end with this, will it?
But what am I supposed to do?
It was she who wanted to suck my cock.
Nothing unusual about liking it.
Saori!
I can feel it twitching.
He's going to ejaculate in my mouth.
It's like I'm a sex doll.
Damn you look happy.
Let's see if I can tease you some!
Wait, Coach!
This is the hallway!
What if someone comes?
Saori...
Why are you doing this?
Ouch!
It hurts!
Saori... is this your first time?
Yes.
It hurts, but...
I'm happy.
You're so cute!
Oh, no.
How am I not supposed to get excited when I see this?
Coach, this is really embarrassing.
What if someone sees us?
You need your training.
Don't say that.
No.
No!
Don't look!
Don't look at my pussy!
I can't think straight because of your cock.
Don't look!
You're really tightening up!
Did you just fantasize about something?
I didn't...
I didn't!
S-Sis...
You look so happy.
We're in plain sight.
If someone comes, they'll know what we're doing.
I love your cunt, Saori!
I'm really enjoying this.
I want them to see me fuck someone!
I'm gonna come!
Saori.
Can I come inside?
Sure.
Just come.
Just come inside, Coach.
I hope someone comes!
I hope they see him come inside me!
Please look!
Please!
Look!
How was that?
Do you need more training, Saori?
Yes, please, Coach.
Special training?
You too?
Yeah...
I want the same kind of... training... my sister is getting.
That might prove...
Don't worry, Coach.
I know exactly what you were doing.
I'll keep it a secret if you give me my training.
You're pretty overbearing.
You want this, don't you?
I just want to be treated like she was.
I thought you'd get angry at me.
I was surprised at first...
But my sister seemed really happy,
so before I knew I started to masturbate and peek around the corner.
Jealous, huh?
But don't think that I like you...
Don't get the wrong idea.
All right, stand still now.
Okay.
You're getting wet.
You'll be slogging wet in no time.
Coach...
How is my vagina when compared with my sister's?
You both have a beautiful pussy.
Makes me want to lick it!
Did you come already?
Um...
Can I suck your cock, Coach?
Sure thing.
I'll stretch out over there.
They get so big when they're erected.
This thing went into my sister's vagina.
Your pussy is twitching.
You must be pretty excited.
This is so embarrassing.
My vagina starts to twitch when I think about cocks.
It feels so good.
Coach!
I'll come again!
Sawa, you do nothing but talk of your sister.
Do you have a sister complex?
You better know what a man is like before you get any funny ideas about girls.
He's going to put it in.
He's going to fuck me.
You're so tight!
Virgin cunts are the best!
Hey, Coach.
Are you really in now?
What?
Is my cock that small?
That's not what I mean.
It doesn't hurt like I imagined it would.
Instead...
Instead what?
It feels good.
Say that again.
It's good.
I love being fucked.
I can feel it.
I can hear soppy sounds.
You're the one moving your hips and making them.
Coach...
Maybe I wanted to have him for myself.
I'm sorry, Sis.
What?!
My ass!
This is news to me.
I didn't know you were supposed to get special training too.
Sis!
Hold on! Let me explain.
I'm okay with it.
I'm not your girlfriend.
No strings attached.
What are you doing, Sis?
You seem to enjoy getting things put into your ass, Sawa.
Let me help you with that.
Hold on!
No!
No, stop!
I only want his cock!
Not my ass!
Coach, you can take me in the ass if you want.
I should be a lot more fun than my dull sister.
Holy shit!
I can feel your rubber dick all the way to my real one.
Stop, Sis!
Please!
Don't be so rough!
It's your fault because you're tightening up.
I'm feeling the impact in my pussy.
Oh, no.
So this is what it feels like.
Now I know what it feels like to be taken by two dicks at the same time.
It's like I'm some random slut.
I'm gonna come!
Me too!
I'll come!
Now that it's come to this, why don't we have a match who can make him come more often?
Hey, consult me about that!
All right, deal.
Making him happy isn't so hard.
Somehow I feel like I'm no longer the one wearing the pants here.
Which is why...
Coach, let's fuck.