Senpai...
Tomohisa-kun, it's the middle of class, but look how big you are.
T-That's because you, um, made me wait...
Oh, so it's my fault?
This is what you get for saying that.
That's, kinda...
How dirty of you.
I bet you're fantasizing about my body...
while I'm sucking your cock right?
Looks like you're about to come.
I'm about to, S-Senpai...
Let's continue someplace else!
Ultimatum ~ sera ~
Stringendo & Accelerando
#2 [ Daily Events ]
Sign: Infirmary
Kirishima-san, your underwear's being pulled into your pussy...
H-Hey, don't pull on it like that.
My underwear is stained...
Yeah.
You shouldn't moan so loudly.
The girl over there's gonna wake up.
I-I know that.
H-Hey, six o'clock, the gym storage room. Be there.
Gym storage room?
No one will come before club activities start...
R-Right.
W-Wait, don't!
Don't just do what you want...
H-Hey, Kirishima-san...
Make me feel good too...
Nope. Make me come first.
Then, I'll be a little rougher.
Your fingers are going in...!
Coming... I'm coming!
U-Um, Senpai?
I've changed my mind.
Wha-?
Let's continue after school.
What!!
K-Kirishima-san, now it's my turn...
It's squishy... feels kinda good.
L... guess I eat too much.
Well, nothing wrong with that.
There are good things about being fat.
Like?
Hmm, let's see...
Firstly, if some bad happened, you'll be fine for two months,
Since you have such a thick layer of fat!
...And then?
With that ravenous appetite of yours,
You'll spend so much on your food that you'll affect the economy!
And, above all you'd give everyone else courage!
When they see that bloated body of, yours, they'll
think that they're actually still okay won't they!
Uh... hey?
What's that!
You want some weight-loss formula?
Kirishima-san she said I was fat, bloated, and screwed up!
Huh?
Sensei, please do something!
Hmm.  It's not like I can't do it.
S-Seriously?!
Muahahaha~!
Come back here when you have a break.
I'll make your body as thin as a pencil!
What's wrong with him?
Could it be he's not coming?
All I did was I tease him a bit, jeez.
If I drink this, will I really...?
No need to worry!
Drink that, and before you can finish saying "Ah!", pencil body, YES!
With this, Kirishima-san might change her mind about me, probably.
S-Sensei!
Eh? What?
*Yahoo!*
Guess I got tricked after all...
I thought something was weird.
A weight-loss formula made in less than half a day...
Damnit! What on earth is that bastard doing!
YOU'RE LA-
...te.
W-Wait. W-What are you going to do?
N-No, stop it!
I don't want this!
It's as if he's using my mouth as a pussy!
Hmm. How strange.
I was sure this would be enough to...
I guess I'll use my own body to test it.
T-Tsuchiya, that's enough-
H-Hey!
Wait, no-
Stop, please stop!
No! You're too heavy, you're gonna crush me...
Please, be more gentle, you're tearing my pussy apart!
I didn't want you to make me feel good like this, but...
I can't help it!
No. stop, not inside, don't come inside!
N-No, aahh!
You actually came...
inside...
No, I don't want this because...
I'll come, I'm gonna come!
TSUCHIYA!
I, uh, it's not what you think!
Sensei gave me some sort of weird medicine to drink...
You went ahead and came so much inside me...
No, I, umm... sorry, um, that I...
It's a s-side effect I think...
Those will be your last words...
T-Tsuchiya... so you were here...
l-l found you...
Who?
That's all for today.
Come to think of it, Mikura never came back to class.
I wonder if Mikura-san's okay with that cold...
Since lunch break she was in the infirmary the whole time...
Mikura-san, still here?
Eh?
Mikura-san?
Y-You'll catch a cold...
You're awake?
Sorry!
Feeling better?
Endou-kun! Thanks so much for coming!
Is something the matter?
I wonder...
When I was alone with the cold, I became so scared!
l-l see.
Shall we lock the door?
Don't lick it so much...
I sweated, and it's dirty
No!
W-Wait a minute!
No. I can't...!
I, I'm gonna... I'm gonna come!
Mikura-san, you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
I'm sorry, my come made your face all sticky!
I'll clean it for you okay?
Hahah, Mikura-san...
It's ticklish...
Endou-kun, come to me...
Yeah.
Mikura-san, you're all wet and sticky inside.
I wonder if it's-because of my fever.
it feels much better than usual...
So deep, it's hitting me deep inside!
Well then, here too...
No, not your fingers!
If you do that, I'm... I'm gonna come again!
Mikura-san, you came didn't you?
Y-Yes... I'm sorry I came, all by myself...
Endou-kun, come too, you can come inside me today...
Your cock is making love to me, it's throbbing inside me...!
Mikura-san, I'm gonna...!
Y-Yes, come, you can shoot all of it inside me...!
It's coming out, your hot come is... flying out...
Ahh, it's so hot! I'm sweating again!
It's better if you don't force yourself.
It's fine, because I'll be resting.
The one who'll be moving is you, Endou-kun.
You know what I mean?
M-Mi, Mikura-san...
Oh my god!
You just came, but you're this hard already!
Mikura-san, your pussy feels so good...
I-It's okay, Endou-kun, you can do it however you want...
Amazing, you came again!
My insides are all full now...
What should we do about... that?
Ah, I uh... this...
There's no need to hold back, come lots more...
B-But...
If you don't hurry, it's gonna spill out you know...
Mikura-san...
Inside, my body feels so hot!
It looks like my body became really sensitive!
You, you keep rubbing against the inner walls of my pussy!
These lewd noises are getting weird...
Mikura-san, I'm,gonna... again...
Yes, I think I'm about to come again too!
Please, together!
Wait, don't pull out!
Let's stay like this just a little longer, please?
I wonder if Mikura went home.
Maybe she's still in the infirmary... heheh.
Mikura, still here?
Mikura!
Not here huh.
It's still warm...
You okay?
I'm fine I'm fine.
I definitely got well from my cold by transferring it to you.
Mikura-tan... ehe, ehehehehe...
Eh? What could that girl be doing at this hour?
Who knows. Doesn't matter right?
I wonder if those two had been going
at it the whole time until now too...
W-Wait, don't just suddenly do it so roughly, we'll get found out...!
But you've been making me wait for it all this time!
Hey, don't, the two of them are looking-
If you do it so roughly, I won't be able to stand properly...
Sheesh, I told you not to be so rough because I
wouldn't be able to stop myself from moaning...
I'm sorry, but I couldn't stop myself...
I didn't think Tomohisa-kun was the kind of person
to get carried away and do this sort of thing.
S-Sorry...
Next time, feel free to get carried away even more.