He fell in love with me.
But I...
Episode 2: Yukino, the good student
I haven't talked with Kirihara since then.
And here I thought it worked out well...
Kirihara!
Are you all right, Kirihara?!
What's wrong, Kirihara?
Someone call the teacher!
Okay!
Teacher!
Good morning...
It's six pm already. Don't overexert yourself.
Six pm? But I...
It seems to be just a light case of anemia, but you should rest a bit more.
Have you been here all the time?
I have night duty.
If you're troubled by what happened the other day...
That isn't it...
This is...
I get mails every day...
What should I do?
I'm sorry, Kirihara.
I can't stay at the school.
Don't quit!
I don't want to make you suffer anymore.
I don't suffer! I love you!
Love... the man who assaulted you?
You're the only one who listened to my problems.
That spot...
Teacher...
Kirihara, you're wet!
Not at all! It's sweat!
You sweat a lot then.
My body feels weird, it's all so dizzy...
This is your weak spot, isn't it, Kirihara.
I'm cumming!
You're such a led girl.
Don't tease me...
I'm going in, Kirihara...
We should undress first...
It's all right.
You're entering me!
Does it feel good, Mr Kannari?
You're amazing, Kirihara.
I'm happy.
Can I move more?
Do what you want.
You sound so cute.
You're so wild! It feels weird...
Is it bad?
No, I like it!
How does it feel? Honestly.
It feels great!
Your honesty is so cute.
You're so deep in me...
Don't stick it so deep, or I'll get weird...
Just forget about it and enjoy it!
I'm dizzy...
It's coming...
Is that you, Kirihara?
I'd like to say thanks.
Is it about those mails?
Thanks to you, they stopped!
I'm glad about that.
Um, Mr Kannari...
You're really into me, aren't you.
Should we try that now?
You look really cute, Yukino.
Mr Kannari, what's going on?
She sent you those mails.
Yuri did?
I'm so envious of your big boobs.
Yuri, don't...
Let's just forget about it all and enjoy ourselves.
But all that until now...
Just do have you, of course.
You're joking, right?
Hold it tight with your hands
I played the nice teacher and waited for you.
To take the bait!
This is a dream...
You came here to have some, didn't you, Kirihara?
I'll give you a lot.
Stop...
Kirihara, you're sensitive deep inside, right?
Please stop...
Stop doing that...
Don't do that!
It's in me... so deep...
His... warm juice... is flowing into me...
You have a good pussy. I can put a couple of loads into you.
I can't think anymore...
Your cock is going wild down there...
Not "down there", it's your pussy.
My pussy is pulsing...
I can't take anymore!
This is the mistress of the great Kirihara Group for you.
A few weeks have passed since then.
She stopped coming to school and wouldn't pick up her phone either.
That girl... No way...
Kirihara!
Mr Kannari? It has been a while.
Why would you quit school so suddenly?
I left the dorm and I'm now living alone.
I have my ways of making money.
Love Mail! Welcome! Lady Yukikko, You have 93 new messages
Hey, Kirihara!
Leave me alone. It has nothing to do with you.
Wait, Kirihara!
You want to have me?
I was a good student.
I couldn't get satisfied with you alone.
Hey... Kirihara...
Please get over with it quick.
The next person is waiting.