The winning school in the girls' nationwide single combat tournament is Shousen.
The winner is Kiritani Konome.
2-C Kendo Club
Tamao Tsukamu
Kiritani...
Konome... I love you.
I love you!
Point!
Pisu Hame! Episode 1
Tamao!
Is Tamao Tsukamu in here?
Captain of the Girl's
Kendo Club
Senior Kiritani Konome
Y-Yes.
That's good. I have something to ask of you.
Sure.
I can't tell you here. Come with me for a second.
S-Sure.
Kiritani Konome...
She's just too perfect.
She's the champion of the nationwide Kendo tournament for the girls in single combat.
Everyone loves her and she's the vice-chairman of the student council.
She's cheerful and sociable.
The lower grades love her personality.
Her breasts are in the top three of the school.
Her ass is amazing.
She's just too perfect.
It must be hard for her to be so perfect.
So what does she want from me?
Hey... Can you undo this for me?
Hey...
Look at me.
Please!!
Hold me!!
This is it.
The student council?
I'm sorry, Tamao!
This is all so sudden.
What happens now might shock you.
I'm really sorry.
But I want to depend on you.
I think you can do it.
I want you to help me.
Okay!
Student Council Room
I have no idea what's going on, but hell yes!
Are you Tamao?
Tamao Tsukamu, right?
Well met, Tamao.
I'm the student council president, Sasugaki Kunitake.
Student Council
President
Senior Sasugaki Kunitake
Are you the one my fiancee recommended?
Oh.
I got all worked up for nothing.
Guess she's going to marry him.
Tamao.
I want you to be a special member for the graduation album committee!
Sure, why not?
Sorry if that was a bit anticlimactic.
But this is sort of important.
Look at this album.
The first page shows the whole class.
The next shows them during club activities and other stuff.
Also school trips and such.
You're in charge of the next page.
Open your eyes!
This is... the grad sex album!
This is our school's reverse sex album, Tamao.
Do it for your own sake and the seniors. Support Kiritani.
Together you will gather the pictures necessary to complete it!
I'm sorry, Tamao!
I knew it would be a huge hassle for you.
You can refuse if you really don't want to do it.
I'm really...
It's okay.
It makes me really happy that you chose me for this.
If I can be useful for you,
then I'll do anything!
Thanks, Tamao.
And that's the story of how I wound up working on the graduation album.
Club activity for the album is after school.
Inamura Satomi
I met with the third-years that Konome talked to away
No Club
Kishinaga Keiko
Library Club
Momose Kumi
from prying eyes and collected the pictures.
Let's check the pictures.
Are you sure?
We have to make sure they are all right.
Okay. Got it.
This is... I...
Sorry!
It's... just natural, right?
Just stand straight.
Brass Band Club
Kitazawa Youko
A lot more girls participate in this than I would have thought.
Their partners are boys of similar age and lots of older ones too.
Osou Kishiya
No Club
Hamano Yukina
I wouldn't have expected this.
Bicycle Club
Kawamura Saki
I'm surprised what sides they hide.
Akiyama Nanami
Some submit a bunch of pictures at once.
Two weeks doing such committee work passed quickly.
Michisato Madoka
This is Michisato Madoka from class D.
Hey there, Kiritani.
Sorry about this.
I'm Tamao Tsukamu and helping with the album.
Hi, I'm Michisato.
Okay, so.
We have to talk about the album.
Well, you know.
I broke up with my boyfriend last week.
It seems like a funny idea, so I definitely wanted to submit some pictures of me having sex,
but I don't have a partner anymore.
That's too bad. I guess it won't work out, then.
Well, maybe...
Hey... Tamao, right?
Yeah?
Got a minute?
Michisato... Michisato!
Don't! We shouldn't!
What choice do I have?
I have no boyfriend right now.
I have to do it with you.
I'm getting the impression you don't disagree.
If you do that...
It's so big... amazing...
Kiritani... I...
What should I do?
Well...
I was prepared it might come to this when I asked you.
I don't mind! Just bear through it!
But even if you...
So now that we have her approval...
Do you like tits?
Open your mouth, now.
I'm sorry, Konome.
How could a man hold back here?
I'm happy you like it.
Are you a virgin?
Yes.
That's nice.
I've only done it once, but I can teach you lots, I bet.
You look so cute down there.
I'm so pathetic.
Someone's watching and I'm still rock-hard.
I'm gonna take it off.
Let's get your cock out.
Wow.
It's huge.
Don't look at it. I've got phimosis.
It's huge. I love it.
Take some pictures, Kiritani.
Okay.
Here I go.
This is sort of embarrassing.
Michisato...
Madoka...
Sorry... Sorry...
I can't stop now.
Stop worrying and just come.
Sorry.
I came in your mouth.
Don't worry.
That was amazing.
It got even larger when you came.
Want to do it now?
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Oh, whatever.
This is... unprotected!
It's so warm!
You hadn't put it on!
This is unprotected.
This is better.
Are you sure?
This is my first time without.
Tradeoff for your virginity.
I'll give you my first time without a condom.
I feel honored.
Make me feel good, okay?
Good. Harder.
Okay.
It's warm and wet.
Boning her feels so good.
Harder.
Yes. Yes.
Make it slap against my ass.
Does it feel good?
Yeah. Very.
Try to hold it in if possible.
If you think you're about to come, just come inside.
Unprotected is so much better.
Maybe it just feels better because of you.
I'm gonna come.
What did you do?
Your cock...
I can't stop.
No... I'll come too.
I'm coming... I'm coming...
Okay, Michisato.
Face this way. I'll take a photo.
Put your tongue out.
Like this?
Tamao...
Took one?
Make sure to use it, Kiritani.
Sure. Will do.
Okay.
Let's do it again. Please.
Lift me with that cock of yours.
Okay.
I want fuck you standing too.
Amazing.
Tamao... Tamao...
More.
I'm coming.
I'm coming too.
I came so much...
This is her mouth.
This feels so awesome.
I want to keep it in there forever.
I'm coming.
Let me go.
Please.
Wow.
You just came and now your this big again.
It's not just your tits, I have your cunt down here too.
It's so hot and I like the smell.
The body of a girl feels great no matter where.
Don't! Stop!
I'm coming again!
I'm coming.
Tamao...
Stop now.
That's enough!
Michisato went home.
She seemed really happy.
I'm sorry.
I lost control.
I shouldn't have done that with you watching.
You...
Turn around.
Konome...
Konome is cleaning my cock...
I belong to someone else, so I can't do much.
I'm doing this a member of the committee.
I don't really know what's happening,
but you're amazing.
I don't know why all that happened.
Don't worry.
I asked this of you.
I'm pretty sure this won't be the last time.
So don't worry about me.
The album is what's important.
Yeah...
Hey, listen.
I'll work hard for the album from now on.
Can I ask you something?
If the same thing happened again, would you clean me?
Sure. Just leave it to me!