Notice of New Appointment.
Kensuke Udai from department 2, section 4.
Due to the company's recent expansion,
you will be temporarily transferred to the Matsunami branch office for a period of one month starting May 1.
-Minamori Co. Human Resources
Maybe it's not such a big deal. It's only for one month.
Ken!
I'm so glad I made it in time.
Ayumu.
You look so surprised.
I told you I had a match, but I didn't say I wouldn't see you off did I?
To tell you the truth I sneaked out.
You'll get kicked out of the club.
I don't mind as long as I have you.
All passengers please prepare to board.
You'll visit on your days off right?
As much as I c...
What am I saying, I've already told you I'll be back in just a month.
A whole month?
Her name is Ayumo Momose. She was my underclassman in high school.
She confessed to me right before I graduated and we started dating.
And now she's my beloved girlfriend.
I believe
in her!
FAKKU! Presents
Volume 1: Second Virginity
Sannomiya? Sorry, who was that again?
Geez, he's a grade above me. He's the club president.
I told you about him earlier.
Oh yeah, that's right.
You said he's a spoiled doctor's kid who radiates his wealth like an aura.
I didn't say that.
But it's true that I have trouble getting along with him.
How could I put it, maybe he's just too nice. I don't want him to be so friendly with me.
I have to get back to work.
If you don't like someone just tell them off.
I'm home! Oh...
She's not back yet.
I wanted to surprise her by showing up unexpectedly.
I have to buy her a dryer.
Ayumu and I started living together after she graduated high school.
I get transferred right when my lovey-dovey life with Ayumu begins, and I can only come back to the main office for meetings.
I'm sorry. It looks like I'll have to work this weekend, so I won't be able to see you.  -Kensuke
That's OK.  I was ready to go meet you when you arrived though.  Be careful of your health.  -Ayu PS. To be frank... I want to get married...
They treat people rough at my company.
What're you doing?
Sannomiya.
It's all tidied up.
You're so scrupulous about even the smallest things.
I only agreed to let you use the bathroom.
Hurry up with it and get out of here.
Aren't you the one who wants relief?
I mean, you seem so lonely.
Nothing about being lonely ever came out of my mouth!
But what did you put into your mouth instead?
That's what loneliness is.
I was drunk...
Stop treating me like a stranger.
Once you've been intimate with someone, it's easy to tell what they're feeling just by looking at their face.
Stop talking about that. It was a mistake.
Your boyfriend seems like a nice guy.
Maybe he'd let you get away with playing around like this.
I'm fine making this something serious though.
Can I meet him and declare myself as a rival for you?
Absolutely not!
Then I guess we'll just be fuck buddies.
The way you work your tongue is so dirty I'm already this hard.
Take responsibility for this as my fuck buddy. I'll head home as soon as you do.
Ayumu.
That's more like it Ayumu.
That's right, if you've done it once the second or third time is no big deal.
This is the last time for sure.
It's big.
Take a good look at it so you don't forget it.
I don't want to remember it.
Did you remember what happened the other night?
I was drunk so I don't remember anything about what happened.
It was a mistake. I have to forget about it.
I have to forget...
I'll take a nap until Ayumu gets back.
No way.
Wow.
You were just thinking about how sturdy it is weren't you?
Yea- I mean no, I was just thinking about how indecent it is. That's all.
If you say weird stuff I'll bite.
That's a good expression you've got on your face.
If you showed that to your boyfriend he'd fall in love with you all over again.
Ken... He's not that kind of dirty person.
I wonder about that. Maybe he's doing this exact thing to some other girl right now.
You drank it all up.
I just didn't want to get the floor dirty.
Anyway, now that we're done you're going to leave right?
How about we enjoy the afterglow a little more as fuck buddies?
I won't be your fuck buddy, and I'm never doing this kind of thing again.
Wh-What the?
You don't remember what happened the other night?
You came three times just from me fingering you there Ayumu.
Didn't I only give you a blowjob?
Why? We just did it, so why's it like this? No way!
I told you what happened last time. That got me a little turned on.
No!
You're getting turned on too. Just check these out.
You can't do that!
Your boyfriend doesn't know that you're the kind of girl whose nipples get hard when she has her asshole fingered does he?
It's not like that. Stop saying dirty things.
Eww, something's touching me. Something hot...
No, don't do that!
So this spot is for my exclusive use right?
Th-that's the wrong... No!
We agreed...
I'll definitely make an agreement with you.
If you become my fuck buddy I'll do you real good.
I'm sorry Ken. I'm sorry.
Can I take that as your agreement to become my fuck buddy?
You'll become my fuck buddy right?
Right?
No... I've never had something like this...
I'll... I'll go crazy.
I've never had this done to me.
Never.
I'll really lose my mind.
You'll become my fuck buddy right?
You will right?
Don't go so deep inside.
I'm telling you not to.
No way, it's filling me up so much.
It's unfair.
It's my first time... I won't know..
So what do you say? You'll be my fuck buddy right?
Geez, you're lying down again.
You've got to move your body around.
We've finally made it out of the house, there's no point if you just lie around.
You were unexpectedly proactive this time.
Wake up Ken.
You haven't called me for a while, so I just showed up.
I didn't think you'd take the trouble to come all the way out here.
Did you say something?
No, it's nothing. Didn't you used to wear more childish ones?
Childish? Do you want children, Ken?
I do want to do it without a condom.
Well, you know...
Oh, and sorry about the other time. I fell asleep so quickly we couldn't really talk.
Then let's spend more time together.
Ok?
Let's get on this one next. Come on.
By the way, how did you get out here?
By train? It's a long ride.
Oh, yeah. It was a pretty long ride.
Ayumu.
They're my friends from the tennis club.
What a coincidence! I'm was so surprised. We just came here too.
So is this your boyfriend?
Yes this is Ken... Udai Kensuke.
I'm Chika. Can I borrow him for a bit Momose?
We have to tell you all about what Ayumu's been up to while you've been gone.
I'm Izumi Kurogi, pleased to meet you.
It's just for a bit.
It's no big deal right?
Why don't you try cheating on her too?
Ayumu?
You're so pushy Udai.
This wasn't a coincidence. Did you bring them here?
Are you jealous? I think not tying each other down should be one of the highlights of a fuck buddy relationship.
I'm not in the mood. My boyfriend is nearby.
You mean that guy from before?
He said something about condoms didn't he?
Don't worry. Nobody can see us from below until after we've reached the peak.
She's wearing one's she can show off.
Eww, you perv.
Girls hide them from all but the ones they love on special days.
For example, if it's a dangerous day but they're asking you to do it without a condom.
Please stop.
Should I give you a child?
What are you thinking? In a place like this?
I'll get angry!
I've flipped your switch right? Just enjoy it.
No. I wanted Ken to do me.
Today was supposed to be only for Ken.
Stop! Don't touch me there today! No!
No.
Are you sure?
Don't you want me to plug up your mouth-pussy instead of your asshole with that?
We can't do that...
But it's hotter than usual. And it's so much harder.
What am I saying? Today is out of the question.
But, if you put on a condom...
It's amazing. It's really amazing.
Oh, she's alone.
Hey Udai, this is even more amazing.
Looks like it's decided then.
You never said I had to choose.
At least do me in the ass as usual.
I'm.. I'm Ken's.. I'm that guy's girlfriend.
Sorry, I lost my balance.
Hey!
Ken.
It stopped for some reason.
I want to stay like this a bit longer.
Maybe the Suspension Bridge Effect is real after all.
That scared me.
But this is a thrill you can't experience normally.
Oops, that was rude of me.
So which one did you pick?
If you put on a condom...
You've never been with anyone other than your boyfriend have you?
I've always thought that having just Ken for this kind of thing was enough for me.
Then this is your second virginity.
Second virginity?
It's big...
It won't fit.
I'm sorry Ken.
You're not wearing a condom!
Now that you mention it, I guess I forgot.
You can't do this. Pull it out right now!
I can keep going right?
Doesn't it feel good?
It's fine right?
No!
That's good!
You've finally admitted it.
That's not what this is.
But...
It's amazing.
It's so amazingly good.