Mizuho-senpai,
About this particular question...
Ah. first you have to factor this equation here.
Sorry about this, senpai.
Having you stay after school just for us.
It's fine.
Teaching others is my specialty.
S-Senpai, you can't do that...
But the atmosphere of an upperclassman's classroom sure is different.
Really?
Hmm. Is that where you normally sit, Mizuho-senpai?
Yeah. Why?
Ah, nothing. Just asking.
Senpai, I'm really gonna...
Ah, oh no!
This was a written invitation from Mizuho to come to her house.
Stringendo & Accelerando
Ultimatum ~ sera ~
#1 [ Sugar Train ]
How wierd.
She's usually on this train-
Whoops, the handle broke...
N-No way!
Eh?
Ah, uh, g-good m, m-morning.
At this rate. I might even be able to have a conversation with her...
We're arriving at Bosoyokojo, Bosoyokojo.
It's finally not so crowded.
Yeah.
Ah, that guy.
He's always standing next to a woman.
He's a rather... complicated pervert huh.
She laughed!
You're always looking aren't you.
Not really-
Tihat's not what I meant.
I was talking about me.
A pair of people board at the next station.
Let's see, there's this guy who looks like a potato,
And this babbler guy, right?
You wanna guess who's gonna board first?
Ah? uh, okay.
I think I'll take the babbler guy.
Then, I'll take the guy that looks like potato.
Here goes...
No, not again!
Yes!
Looks like I won.
W-W-W-What?
What? It's your reward for winning.
It's half-erect.
My sweater feels good doesn't it?
What a thick foreskin.
It has become this hot...
Look, it's all sticky now.
It's okay to come, if you want.
The cleaners aren't going to like this aren't they.
Well, let's play another game.
If you win, you can use... this.
This time, I'll let you fuck me until you come.
Over there.
That woman will get off at the next station.
Out of the two guys from before standing in front of her, who do you think will sit?
Well?
Um... maybe the babbler guy.
I got it!
It's you day today isn't it.
Is it really that rare for you to see what a girl looks like there?
No. I uh...
Let's loosen it up a bit...
You sperm is really thick.
I just might get pregnant.
Come on. Let's not waste time.
Ah. okay.
Even though I'm not moving, your insides are pulsating...
It'll feel even better if you move.
Even though you just came a while ago, you're still so hard...
T-that's because, it feels really good...
Yes, it feels so good!
I've always been waiting, for you to violate me!
Please, harder, fuck me harder...
You can pound into my pussy all you want!
I can't, I'm gonna...
Yes. anywhere's fine, come anywhere you want!
You're gonna blow a hole through the wall!
You're just like a bull.
Next station is Shinbojo, Shinbojo.
Ah. I have to get off...
Nope, not yet.
One last game.
If I was to scream right here, which of the two carriages
would people come from do you think?
Well, which one?
If you get it right, l act as if nothing happened!
[It sounded like it came from the gate!]
Hey, did you hear about it?
This morning, they arrested a pervert from this very train!
No way!  Really?
I also heard he was quite young!
Are you sure?
I'm always carefully observing those around me, you know.
W-What a huge house...
You're late. Even though I gave you such a great map.
You mean this?
What kind of map is-
Don't worry, come in, since there's no one else at home ricjtit now.
You must be thirsty. How about some Calpis?
Note: Calpis is a cold yogurt-type drink.
Ah! How nostalgic.
Look, look! It looks like sperm.
Shall I help you drink it?
What?
S-Senpai?
Different from perfume, the sweet scent of a girl...
Recently, just the scent of senpai would be enough
for my mind to go completely blank.
Might be a conditioned response.
If my dad were to see us doing this sort of thing, it would bad.
He might even kill you.
Y-You're kidding right.
It's true.
Like the other guy who came here before. He was at the doorway for just two seconds...
The next thing I knew he was screaming in my dad's room.
And then?
Who knows.
It's empty now.
Should I fill it up?
N-Nah. I'm quite full already...
That's not what I meant.
I want to fill it up from here.
S-Senpai.
Look, the good little boy just woke up!
Or has he been awake the whole time?
Does my tongue feel good?
Yes, it's really soft.
I'll put it into this little slit right here.
Senpai, your tongue went in...
Look, it's this foil already.
I'm looking forward to how full we can make this.
I'm home, Mizuho!
It's my dad.
Looks like we'll be seeing blood.
D-D-Don't scare me like that, please save me!
Hehe, you're right. Over here!
Get inside here!
Oh? You're here?
Welcome home!
I'm hungry, cook something up for me.
Is Carbonara okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
Tomohisa-kun. you still erect?
Since it's open, if you stick your dick out through the gap...
What's wrong? This time I'll hold it in with my throat.
You want to come in my mouth, don't you?
It's getting all tangled up inside, with the pasta, and your tongue...
Senpai...
I choked...
While I bring the food to him, go to the room on the second floor.
Roger.
Sorry for the wait!
Mmm... it looks good.
It's a cat.
Well then. I'll be in my room.
Everything's fine.
Yeah.
Well then, you still have to put it in.
I-It's so good, my pussy is making all these wet sounds!
Senpai, your pussy feels so good...
Did it hurt?
It kind of hurts, but it also kind of feels good...
I see. In that case...
It's so good, it's amazing!
It's twitching inside me so violently!
S-Senpai, if you do it so hard...
No!  Do your best in holding back...
Look...
This time, let's have you on top.
Y-Yes!
Senpai...
I'm gonna...
A-All of it, in my mouth, please!
Coming!
Wow. I thought you were going to impregnate me from my mouth!
Look! The Volume's ridiculous!
Sorry, looks like we filled it up.
Mizuho, you have a moment?
You're there aren't you?
I'm so sorry, please go home today, since he's bound to misunderstand...
B-B-But how?!
You should be able to leave through the window...
Ah. oh your shoes!
Here, the map to get to the station!
I'm coming in!
Just a cat. Hehehe~
Huh?
I kfiow it.
Exactly what am I to senpai?
To Be Continued...