So you came.
Don't be so nervous.
Today, I'll make your penis feel good.
It's embarrassing if you stare at me like that.
Take your clothes off too.
Well, show me.
So big...
Since when did you start saving up I wonder.
Looks like you're about to ejaculate already.
It's become so hot...
Don't come just yet.
My mouth is warm isn't it?
Does it feel good like a pussy?
Go ahead, come whenever you like.
Your thick sperm, fill me up...
Defile me with it...
Look!  It's still so hard.
In that case...
I'll show you more perverted things!
Stringendo & Accelerando
Ultimatum ~ sera ~
#3 [ Prologue & Epilogue ]
Hmm?
Hey, what are you doing?
Help, help me!
Help me!
What are you doing, Yoshizawa?
Why did you call out like that?
I really wanted to die you know.
Weren't you screaming "help me!"?
T-That's because... well...
If you're gonna kill yourself, do it properly.
Must be great to be you.
You get good grades, and you have lots of friends.
As for me...
Wha-!
W-Wait, what are you doing-
You pervert.
You're all hard even though you just tried to kill yourself.
T-That's not...
You're so big, Yoshizawa.
What?
I'll give you something you'll like.
It's uncomfortable to be this hard isn't it?
W-What are you saying-
I'm gonna eat you up~
It's what you talk about isn't it?
A-About that...
It's what you always fantasize about isn't it?
Please feel good.
Come on.
You can put it in my mouth you know!
My tongue's soft you know.
A-Amatsu-san...
Woah, it's still getting bigger...
Amatsu-san, in your mouth, it's going all the way to your throat...
You can't do that, Amatsu-san...
If you do it like that, I'm gonna...
So? Why did you want to throw yourself off the roof?
My studies, I don't get them...
And, I don't have any friends I can ask...
That's it?
"That's it" you say? To me, it's...
It's just that you don't know how to go about your studying.
I'll help you a bit.
After school. You have time don't you?
Y-Yeah.
Erm, it's this formula right.
Well, got it?
Just a bit I guess...
Which part do you not understand?
Ah, with this, all you have to do is substitute it in.
Amatsu-san, I'm wondering why you
suddenly decided to help me study.
Oh? You wanted me to teach you something else?
W-What do you mean with "something else"...
Hey, you have a boner again don't you.
Even though you shot so much come into my mouth a while ago...
Uh, well, I...
Geez, there's no other way is there?
A-Amatsu-san...
You won't be able to concentrate like this right?
I was right!
Woah, hang on-
But, if you suddenly put something this
big inside me, won't you rip me apart?
I wonder if this is fine.
Alright, let's do this!
Uh, Amatsu-san...
Just sit still for a bit.
It went in..
The saliva made it all slippery...
Yoshizawa, you're a virgin aren't you?
Y-Yeah.
Y-You should thank me!
Since you get to lose it...
...to such a cute girl!
It feels so good!
It's rubbing against me everywhere...
Amatsu-san, if you do that I'll...
You can't come inside me got it?
Tell me when if you can't hold it in anymore!
I'm... gonna!
Wha-!
Amazing~
Well, did it help?
Now you can concentrate on studying... uh?
Looks like you still can't.
Go ahead, do it however you want.
Okay.
This time, you do the moving.
More, more!
All the way in, as if you're drilling it inside me!
Amatsu-san. you're pussy is so hot and tight.
N-No, you came twice already, butt..
...you're still so big and hard!
Amatsu-san, I'm gonna come again...
No, no, you can't come inside!
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it...
Even though I told you not to come Inside...
That's all the studying we'll do for today.
See you tomorrow.
In the end, nothing changed.
I wasn't able to study after all.
I see.
Well, why won't you listen to my request?
No shit! Don't fuck with me!
The negotiations were unsuccessful?
Hey Ryou, help me with the preparations for dinner.
You're annoying.
Don't complain.
I'll make you something tasty.
A-Alright...
Shall we start, Tomoe?
The game begins.
Nooo!!
Well, the preparations are complete.
You're fast, as expected.
Behave yourself. The game starts now.
Oh? Your sister's nipples have sunken in.
We'll have to suck it out.
Well then, I'll explain the rules.
Everything depends on you, Ryou-kun.
Soon, Tomoe and your sister will be squeezing
semen out of your meat rod.
The time limit is before my bos... your father comes back home.
If you end up coming four times before then, then we win.
If you can keep yourself from coming that much, then you win.
Look, your sister's amazing. Is this... milk?
N-No! Don't say such things!
It's just that, I have a condition where if
you touch my nipples, my breasts will...
Get your brother any more turned on, and he'll come straight away.
Don't look, Ryou!
This embarrassing state of mine... don't stare at me like that!
You understand the rules, brother?
Now, let's extract your come using your sister's lewd breasts.
M-My sister... with her breasts...?
Well then, squeeze that come out of your brother's dick.
Warm isn't it, your sister's tits.
Let's have direct contact.
Ooh, your sister's tits are so slippery.
It's like a lotion.
No! I had no idea a guy's dick is this warm, and hard...
Hey, you gotta catch all of it properly.
It's your cute brother's semen after all.
This is... Ryou's sperm...
Looks like you came.
If you don't endure this properly who knows what will happen.
Your dick got this big already.
You pervert.
There's no helping it is there?
You've always been looking at them haven't you.
Your sister's tits.
You masturbate everyday by fantasizing about
getting a titjob with these breasts don't you?
N-No way...
Ryou fantasizes about my body, my boobs, and masturbates...
It's great isn't it, to have your dreams granted.
Look, seems like he's gonna come again.
You've soiled your sister's face again.
If this keeps up, just four times will be an easy victory for us won't it.
Looks like it, since we have his sister squeezing it out directly for us.
I'll show you your sister's pussy as well.
Oh? Your sister's all wet and sloppy.
P-Please. Ryou. don't look attme there!
You got turned on too when you were stimulating his dick?
Look, your sister looks like she's about to come soon too.
Watch closely.
N-No! I shouldn't feel this good, but I... can't hold it!
Well Otouto-kun. This time we'll squeeze it out with this.
Come on, this will be your first time with your sister.
N-No. anything but this...
It'll be fine.
You know that don't you, Onee-chan.
The two of you aren't true siblings.
So, just relax and put it in.
All of it's in.
Come on, move properly.
Onee-chan, I can't...!
Oh, you came already?
S-Sorry, Onee-chan, l came inside...
No, it's okay. I also showed you my dirty side...
That aside, I wonder if you can hold out the remaining
time before your papa comes back?
What's with this fucking car, parking in front of my house!
O-Onee-chan, you're...
You're moving by yourself...
B-But it feels so good that I can't... stop...
I-If you do It so rough, I'll come...
Hey, I'm back!
Oh? It's dad!
Q-Onee-chan, nol
If you do that, I'm so deep inside...!
Onee-chan!
Ah, no!
It's been fun.
Hey, what's going on? I'm back!
Me too. See ya.
Kotoha!
Hey, can'jt be helped, here's something extra!