Hey, Yu...
I'd like to ask you something...
Afterschool Nyan Nyan 01
Are you serious about this?
Yeah!
But you said it's okay.
Sure I did...
No one would come to this classroom, and I even locked the door.
Okay then, I'll do it...
But still, asking to watch me fap is close to sexual harassment!
You know, I don't get what you do just from stories!
I can only ask you, so please!
I ended up in some weird situation again...
It's the real thing... Looks different from how it's in the books.
Its shape changed!
Would you keep quiet a bit? I can't concentrate.
Sorry.
So it really changes like this... Just how the others said.
I want to get this done quick!
Can I touch it?
Done?
This is enough, right? Then I'll be going home...
It was so quick, I didn't really get it.
Quick?
Come on, do it again! Come on, okay?
But then...
Come on, senpai.
This is so embarrassing...
You've seen mine too, so now we're even.
Yeah, but still...
You said you'd help out.
Come on, do it.
Like this?
Yeah! Just like that!
It looks just like earlier.
So guys really do stuff like this...
How does it feel?
It feels good, of course.
I see...
Wait!
Don't touch it!
But it's so wet.
Don't do that! It's dirty!
It tastes so... erotic.
Does it... Does it feel good here?
No...
She really turns me on...
You dirty boy.
But you...
Pervert. Lecher. Satyr.
I'm sorry.
But...
I kinda liked it.
Eh?
Just slowly, okay?
Sure.
If you hurt me, you'll be in trouble.
I'll do my best.
Huh?
I put it in.
I'm fine!
Then I'll move it.
It feels so weird...
Amazing... You're so amazing... And wet...
That's not true...
It feels way better than jerking off...
Just slowly... I'm... melting...
I... I'm...
Do it!
We kinda... did it.
Sorry...
You don't need to apologize. I told you I liked it.
Yeah, but...
Close your eyes.
But then I can't see...
Just do it! Please!
Okay, okay.
It all started when in a stuffed voice she said,
"Ryo, make my red even redder."
My parents are away for a week travelling.
So I thought...
I couldn't believe it.
Hazuki is always mature, takes her work a bit too seriously,
and she had no idea about sex whatsoever before going out with me.
I want to do lots of dirty things with you!
And thus our week of living together at her place began.
Loveryday. Our seven days together
Then I'll do it... Are you sure?
Come on, you're so nervous...
But it's all right... We'll do lots of stuff...
Amazing... First time I see it in the light.
Umm, Nao...
I might cum in a flash... But don't stop...
I'm fine. So you just do whatever you want.
Could you moan a bit...
Okay...
I spread the girl I love... Her legs are wide open too...
And I'm licking her...
What are you doing?! Not my ass!
Is it enough if I do it with my fingers?
Hazuki... Do you want me to put it in?
Say that you do...
Put it in... please...
Then I'll put it in...
Into your dripping wet pussy...
I'm putting it in.
I didn't dare to do it, afraid she'd hate me.
But I wanted to do it, because I love her.
And now she said it's okay, I'll do my best.
Slowly... It's so rough...
Nao!
Nao! Nao!
Nao! Nao! Nao!
Why did you say that suddenly?
You know...
We don't do it often, right?
Dunno, I guess...
Well, I'd love to do it day and night...
My friends said that's weird at our age.
Especially for guys. So you must be holding back...
And then other girls could take you from me...
That's why you asked me to?
But that's...
But I'm happy we really did it today.
It was a bit scary at first though.
So let's do it tomorrow as well!
Okay.
I woke up in the morning...
My dear girlfriend was in the kitchen making me breakfast...
Can a man be happier than this?
Wake up, Nao, breakfast's ready!
It's really delicious!
Really? I'm so glad!
It's all thanks to you.
You can have seconds too.
Hazuki is so cute. She cooks great. She's kind.
She's mature. She's beyond perfect.
And her body...
I'd like to do lots of pervy stuff.
I'd like you to do as you like.
To do as I like... Does that mean
I can do stuff like this?
Nao, we're eating...
She didn't let me touch her breasts at first because she was embarrassed how big they are.
Such a waste. This is...
What?
I can even do this.
What are you doing?
Amazing... It just won't stop... And still...
Do it with your mouth now.
What should I do?
Here...
I'll show you, so just take it in.
She was eating just earlier... and now she's sucking my cock.
Yeah, like that.
She looks so hot...
Though she probably has no idea what she's actually doing.
Her mouth is so wet and warm...
I can't get enough of this!
Sorry! I just... I'm sorry!
I gave up all hope then. But then...
Next morning...
You don't want to?
I guess we could...
I'll drop the plates.
Bear with it.
You're such a pervert, Nao.
I just wanted to try it once.
You're interested too, aren't you, Hazuki?
I don't know...
It's so sweet all the way in...
Don't lick inside!
Hazuki, you came? It felt good?
Nao, this position's so weird!
Not at all, this is normal! Everyone uses this.
Really?
It's amazing! Your pussy's sucking on me so hard!
So amazingly hot!
Nao!
Grab... Grab my breasts...
Hazuki...
Hazuki... Next in the room...
And thus in a flash three days passed.
But I still have four days with just Hazuki!