Once upon a time, there was a demon girl and her familiar.
Her name was Twiska.
She was a succubus who kept attacking human towns one after another.
She fed upon the sperm of humans living a free and willful life.
That is, until a certain fateful encounter.
Episode one: Got a nice boy!
Oh well.
Nerin, tonight we're going to that town!
It's a demon!
Run!
Help!
Found my first one.
Just accept it.
My amazing cunt is waiting for you!
Let's see how long you'll last.
Oh my, he's already cumming!
Were you a virgin maybe?
It's a bit unrefined, but I like how thick it is.
Prepare yourself demon!
Got my second load!
Your semen shower is so warm!
Who'll be my next prey now?
He's just my type!
Found myself a nice boy!
Theo!
So you're called Theo?
Stop! Give me back my Theo!
It's useless!
Don't mess with devils like her!
Give up on your son already!
No! Theo!
Theo!
So annoying.
What did you do?
Don't worry, she's just having a nice dream.
Let's have some fun too.
His tongue is so soft. And he's moving it instinctively.
How do you like your first kiss's taste?
Huh? Was I too passionate?
Perhaps, I'll take this next then.
Stop...
Nope. I'll show you heavenly pleasures.
It's dirty!
Your pee-pee's so cute.
I'll undress your shy pee-pee hiding under its skin.
Your tongue is under the skin!
Don't pull on my pee-pee's skin!
Stuff will come out...
Are you sure you are not enjoying it, virgin boy?
I got his first kiss, and now his first blowjob too!
Don't lick there! It's twitching!
It's getting big!
No!
I'll pee!
The first blow always tastes best!
I'm sorry.
It wasn't pee, it was sperm.
How does it feel to be an adult, virgin boy?
I don't get it...
My pee-pee is weird.
I can't put on my pants like this!
He cummed but it's still hard.
Come now, Theo.
I'll teach you the pleasure of penetrating a girl.
I don't want to! It's dirty!
It's not dirty! Your mom has the same!
No way...
Mine is a hundred times better than hers though.
It's quite big!
Come on, why am I moaning?
He's just a virgin but I almost came.
Oh yeah, first timers are always the best!
It can make even me move!
Don't move!
What are you saying?
It feels the better the more you move!
Doesn't it feel great as your cock rubs against the inside of my pussy?
This is it!
You're so cute!
Theo, you're so cute!
No... something is coming out of my pee-pee again!
Please stop it miss!
It feels the best if you let it out!
You can cum inside, so ejaculate as much as you want!
Cumming inside is just the best.
Huh? What?
Who do you think you are to play around with me like that?
You slutty bitch!
You transformed?
You're not cute! Who are you?!
A mere devil tries to defy me?
You're a million years too early!
Ouch!
No way... A simple human is raping me?
No...
This time I'll be dictating the pace!
It's amazing!
It reaches all the way to my womb! It's hard and thick!
What... happened to Theo?
That is indeed the great hero of legends!
A hero? Him?
He looks like just a delinquent to me.
He is the descendant of the legendary hero who defeated the devil lord centuries ago.
The hero's blood awakened in Theo when he was attacked by a devil, just as the legend says.
I'll break if you do it so hard!
Do you really think I'll just let you have it your evil way?
Stop...
You talk back? Cocky!
Cumming time!
Amazing! So much inside!
I can't get enough of this hot semen!
Why does it feel so good if he cums inside me?
Who else wants to take revenge on this devil girl?
Follow the hero!
It's bright!
As a pride descendant of the hero,
I can't let a demon run and escape!
That was close...
But it felt so good!
That boy was so cute! I hope I can meet him again.
And if I do, I'll kill him!
Don't ever forget those words!