Yuu... I'm sorry.
Today again, I have to...
Yuu...
Yuu, please...
Yuu, I can feel... you inside me.
Yuu, it's so hot... it's hitting my insides... I feel so hot.
It's so deep inside me...
Yuu...
I'm about to...
It's getting bigger inside.
Yuu... Yuu...
Your feelings are this strong?
Your feelings for each other. That's why the reaction is so strong.
The way you go along with my wants without saying a word.
Otherwise you and her would be...
I'm sorry, Brother.
FAKKU! Presents
Maho's unloving uniform
The endless requests of the cool ponytail
As always.
It's morning! You'll be late! I'm going on ahead.
Hey, Rie!
Huh, Ayaka?
What are you doing here at a time like this?
I was just too worried.
Is your beloved boyfriend still around?
Oh come on! He left just a while ago.
Do you love him that much?
Yeah!
I can't control it.
I'm sure he doesn't return your feelings!
You'll be both hurt this way!
That's not true.
I know it it! I only have to look at you.
And this town you know...
There are gossips?
Rie!
So the cruel reality...
Would never allow it to be true?
So deep... All the way in...
Come all the way in me!
I want to be with you like this forever!
I'm sorry...
I love you... so much!
I love you, and only you!
I'm sorry for calling you now. You had to skip class because of this.
I mustn't do this, right?
The swimsuit would've been better?
Though it'd have been an old hag in a swimsuit.
I love you.
Huh? Maho?
Your feelings are too strong. If you don't stop now, it'll all be gone.
Think about Yuu too!
So we've been found out!
From Maho: I'm waiting.
Why? I love him so much... Why is it so hard then?
I'm sure he doesn't return your feelings!
That can't be!
Yuuji!
Professor? Professor Kirisaki? Are you all right? Professor!
At a time like this...
Why...
Yuu...
You're inside of me...
Only you can do this...
Thank you.
So deep...
Feels so good, Yuu...
More! More!
It feels great there!
I'll stay with you forever!
Even if it's hard at times...
It's okay, don't hold back!
Brother...
You shouldn't be here. Understand where you and Rie are standing.
Go home for now.
Her emotions overflowed.
We'll understand it all tomorrow... Her problems too.
Professor, good morning!
Are you all right?
Yes, it's nothing.
It was just a sudden faint. Sorry for making you worry.
Class is already starting. Go, go!
Yes!
Good morning! You should hurry too, Touno.
Good morning!
Are you all right?
Yes, I am. No need to worry.
Her feelings were too strong for you.
And this is the place to be released from them.
I'm sorry. I should've known much earlier!
I knew you had so strong feelings in you, but I couldn't do anything!
I couldn't do anything.
Brother?
Brother...
Brother!
I'm sorry.
Brother, I love you.
I love you, Brother...
Brother, Brother...
Brother... I'm sorry that it ended up like this. I'm really...
Brother...
Sorry for the wait!
Are you all right?
Sure! You worry too much, Ayaka!
Really? Yeah, I guess...
Should we go drinking?
But you just recovered!
Still I feel so... refreshed.
I guess it's because I had to stay at the hospital.
What's wrong?
No, just this smell felt so familiar.
Let's go.