All right.
Suzumori, please read the next part.
Okay.
The world is a beautiful place
and it's worth to
fight for it.
Yup, that's fine.
You're next, Mizuno.
Yes.
You could see it.
You could see it there.
Uh, well...
I...
Damn.
I wasn't really watching out for it.
I'm glad no boys were around.
I wasn't watching out either.
Don't give me that, man.
Just don't, seriously.
Let's go already, Shizu.
We always eat our lunch of the rooftop.
Go ahead, okay?
I'll go buy some bread at the store.
Pet Life
Man, this is the worst day of my life.
Nothing good has happened all day.
You two always go so well together.
But you know, Mizuno will get tired of you if you always wear white.
Don't pay attention.
He's just poking fun at you.
Good morning, Mizuno.
Yesterday was good.
Yesterday?
We spent some time after work.
Was hard, let me tell you.
Hey, Kazuya.
You remember what we promised each other, right?
Why is he doing that childish stuff?
That's so sad.
He has no class or delicacy.
He's pretty popular, though.
Hey, watch out!
Oh, sorry.
Your ass is in the way.
Nope, your boobs are in the way.
By the way, I heard something.
They say he asked you out in a letter.
Is Ozaki that cool?
Isn't Mizuno cooler?
Tell me, Shizumori.
Do you think she has something with Mizuno?
Hey, Shizu, we'll be late for class!
I know, I know.
I'm going ahead.
Did someone forget this here?
I'll leave you here, not kidding!
I have to be beautiful in class.
Don't be angry.
I am angry!
Calling a girl stupid and a waste of space is just not funny!
I'm sorry.
Your reaction is always so cute, so I did it without thinking.
What kind of girls do you like?
Let me think...
I like it if they have long hair.
So I guess I should grow out my hair...
if I want you to marry me.
Oh damn, I really will be late.
What? Oh no.
Where did I leave them.
You have to be kidding me.
I put it into the right locker, I think, but what if it belonged to the one next to it?
Well, there's nothing I can do now.
If Kazuya finds out I forgot my panties and bra somewhere.
He will call me stupid and laugh at me again.
I have to find them!
Ozaki!
What do you have there?
They're mine!
He'll know by smell!
I thought I could know whose they are by smell, but turns out I can't.
Looks like somebody forgot them.
Give me the rest!
You have it, right?
Give me back the rest!
Why are you here to begin with?
Maybe I was looking for a good place to jack off during lunch break.
You're the worst!
That over there is left.
There's no way thats all!
Could you see it?
Clear as day.
You have to be kidding me.
Delete it!
Good going.
You like this, don't you, Shizumori.
Stop this!
This isn't funny!
What do we have here?
You like flashing it?
What are you doing?
Return the favor.
Look what mine is like.
You can touch it!
I don't want to!
It's dirty, isn't it?
Want to be the ultimate jerk-off fantasy for the whole school with that photo?
You little exhibitionist.
Or you could just go home.
You're blackmailing me.
I don't want this.
It's getting hot.
I love how you seem to like this.
I think you're enjoying this.
Hey, don't do that!
Stop!
When I look at you from up close, you're pretty cute.
Stop joking around!
Oh, no!
I can't believe this!
No!
Don't stick your tongue there.
I haven't done this before.
Don't!
Don't! Not there...
Stop.
No.
My head is going all white inside.
It all goes blank.
We shouldn't do this!
I kissed him.
Oh, no!
I knew it when you flashed me.
You little slut.
Hey Mizuno, why hasn't Shizumori been back?
Yeah, she stood me up for lunch break.
Did you see Mizuno's?
Of course not!
Come on, be honest.
I really didn't!
Then take a good look at mine.
Please no.
What's this smell?
Let me compare this.
Man, this is way better than on the photo.
I shouldn't do this!
Why am I just obeying him?
Hey, stop!
Yours is beautiful, Shizumori.
Mizuno has seen it too, right?
What did he say?
He hasn't seen it.
I don't show it to him.
So I guess I have to show him this photo as soon as possible!
Don't do that!
No.
I don't want this.
Not like this!
He can see everything.
It's so beautiful.
I have to show it to Mizuno.
He'll love me for it.
No, Kazuya and I aren't there yet.
That feels weird.
Send him a mail then.
If he shows up because he's worried about your absence, he'd see it, right?
I'm not really feeling good. It's like anemia.
"I'm skipping the classes in the afternoon and sleeping in the infirmary."
"Tell the teacher, Kazuya. Nodoka."
No.
Don't.
Why do I like this so much?
Ozaki?
They say you change girls so often.
Do they know each other?
Where do you touch yourself when you're alone?
Nowhere.
Come on, tell me.
Where does it feel good?
I don't know.
All right, I'll find it then.
I'll find out where it feels good for you.
I don't get it.
Maybe here?
Ozaki!
This is my first...
It hurts!
Seriously? This is your first time?
Of course!
No!
No, don't move it!
You've been waiting for this for so long, so I'll go all the way in.
Relax, relax.
Don't tense up.
"Rare for you to get anemia."
"Sleep it off. I'll come see once classes are over."
That's what he wrote.
We've got a lot of time to have fun until then.
You're great, Shizumori.
I hit the jackpot here.
I hate this!
I like your voice too.
I told you.
I hate this...
Dump Mizuno and go out with me.
I mean, look at what we're doing.
No, I want to marry Kazuya.
I promised him!
I'll marry him!
I promised him.
No!
That's what you say, but I think you should have different priorities.
Hey, go out with me.
I'll break... you're too forceful.
Come on, you like this.
It just hurts!
But... it tingles when he comes in.
Yes, like that.
This feels weird.
This is sex.
I'm having sex.
What should I do?
My mind is going blank.
That thing is all I can feel.
This has to stop!
My head is going empty.
I'm coming, Shizumori.
No, idiot.
You can't!
Don't do that!
Not inside!
Now you're my wife, Shizumori.
No...
So much is there...
Hey, didn't you forget someone?
Hey, just how long do you plan to stay mad?
You liked it, didn't you?
Of course not.
Huh?
What should I do?
Now we're officially a couple!
Or something.
You're unbelievable.
If you wear this, you won't stand out.
Tell them you were in the middle of changing.
Hey... this is so small...
Hey, it's the seniors.
Look, why am I hiding together with you?
Hey, someone left their uniform and stuff here.
Probably a first-year.
I don't really like the uniform either.
Maybe she's going braless.
Wow, have yours gotten bigger again?
You're not one to talk with those scanty panties.
They're for night clubs and stuff.
Won't the school confiscate them the second they see them?
Nice view.
I've gotten a boner again.
This isn't the time for that!
Haven't you gotten hard here too?
No...
But man, they are so big...
Even with all those girls around, yours are the biggest.
They... aren't really for you...
Oh, crap.
She noticed something.
Hey, stop this.
At this rate we won't make it back to the classroom.
I kinda knew.
No.
So, now...
The girls are gone now.
Don't just decide on this.
How is it?
Does it still hurt?
Still, don't!
That's my weak point.
H-Hey...
You're still so uptight.
What are you saying?
This feels weird.
Isn't that just fine for a little exhibitionist?
No, idiot.
Instead...
This is weird...
Stop this...
No!
Did I lose it somewhere?
Hey, can you get that out for me?
I think so.
This is so grown-up.
You love men, don't you?
You're grown up once you realize when guys are looking at you.
Probably your breasts, though.
Now that's just careless to leave it here.
Hey, that's mine!
I wonder whose it is.
It's kind of simple.
See, just white isn't good.
It's so big again.
Sixth period started.
But where is she?
Let's look for her again after school.
Wait, Shizumori.
Felt great. Let's do it again.
What are you talking about?
You're the lowest.
I'd never like you.