P-Please.
I'll masturbate, but please don't make me take off my panties.
I really can't masturbate while showing my pussy to men.
I'll die from embarrassment!
Why would I make you do it if I can't see?
Hurry and begin.
The way you always do, Princess.
What a nice view, Princess.
Bastard!
Making me do such dirty things...
You get punished for failing your duty.
That applies even to high noble ranks like you, Princess Lunatemis.
It's the absolute rule in our Great Lunarium Kingdom.
A man, one of my underlings watching me masturbate...
I'm going to die from embarrassment!
A princess's panties sure are full of elegance.
Wh-What are you trying to do with my panties?!
Any man who gets a woman's panties would start by sniffing them.
It stinks, too.
Noooo!
Shut up! I always keep myself clean!
It doesn't smell!
But it's stained, Princess.
That's not true!
I'm sick of this.
How long are you going to keep me doing this?
You're still soaking up your pussy even when someone is watching you masturbate, and even getting your panties sniffed.
I didn't know the princess was a pervert!
These panties smell like your sweat and piss.
You're lying...
I wash them!
I don't think the stains and smell built up over the years come off so easily.
An underling of mine is sniffing my panties...
Don't sniff them...
Not when my underling is watching...
It's about time?
Princess, open your legs up more.
Stop! Don't touch me!
No... I can't resist...
A man, an underling is watching while I...
I-I'm going to come!
No, I can't come!
I can't, yet...
I'm... I'm... I'm coming!
What's happening?
No, I'm scared!
Emblem Steal!
No more, I can't move.
What are you doing, Katsuma?
W-Wait, isn't my punishment over?
Look what happened while I was watching the Princess masturbate?
No, stay away.
I'm telling you to stop!
Don't move, Lunatemis. Stay still.
I can't move my body.
You enjoy these kind of things, don't you, Princess?
Stop, please.
I've never done it before, so...
That's a surprise. You seemed to enjoy masturbation so much.
It'll be over before you finish counting stains on the ceiling.
N-No!
It won't feel good unless you relax.
I just masturbated, so my body is sensitive...
Look, it's all the way in.
It hurts... pull it out...
My purity is...
Don't be so rough!
Hard, thick thing inside my stomach...
is moving violently!
Lunatemis is no longer a pure virgin.
No! I can't take it anymore!
Please be more gentle.
No! If you're so rough, I'll...
Forgive me already!
If you keep punishing me...
It's too thick!
Too rough!
No!
Don't grab my breasts so hard.
My body is feeling strange.
I'm going to come!
It's starting to feel good.
No! It feels good!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come again!
I just came from masturbating...
This time, I'm gonna come from my underling's cock!
I'll release inside, Princess!
No!
Not inside!
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
It's coming out... inside...
Lots of it.
I told you not to...
You're going to punish me!?
FAKKU! Presents!
Screw you!
Where do you think you're sitting?
This is the throne room.
It's where the Queen presents herself to the lower classes.
And I'm sitting on the King's throne.
A low ranking executive like you violating me is enough for death sentence.
Now you taint the holy throne?!
You bastard!
Don't get all worked up, Princess.
Shut up!
I will finish you off this minute!
Lunatemis! Don't resist and come to my side.
A-Again... my body is...
As I thought.
Wh-What's going on?
Oh, Princess!
Your pussy is all wet.
Did you enjoy fucking with me so much?
No... because it just happened...
My body isn't moving...
Or were you looking forward to something after I called you out?
Insolence!
Allow me to explain to the dirty princess.
Lunatemis! Suck my dick!
My body is...
moving on its own...
In our Great Lunarium, the Kingdom with ambition for world domination...
Strength and class are decided by the Lunar Emblem we are born with.
From top, Double Moon, the Queen class.
Next, Full Moon, the Princess class.
That's your class.
Then Half Moon, the Senior Executive class.
And my Crescent Moon, the Junior executive class.
Finally the lowest, Peace Moon, the Soldier class.
I can steal the absolute power, Moon Emblems.
What?
It's called Emblems Steal.
I can steal Lunar Emblems from people when they're in climax.
How can that be possible?
As a proof, you're obeying my order now.
That's... because...
Now that you've lost your Lunar Emblem, your rank is lower than Soldier.
And you've become me slave.
N-No!
You give a good blowjob even though you were virgin until just now.
Shut up!
I'm going to come.
Take it with your pretty face!
No! Not something like cum on my face!
Ugh! Filthy!
Lunatemis! Don't clean your face!
Why... my face... disgusting.
Stay still until you remember the smell of your master's cum.
Sticky warm things are on my face...
No!
How did this happen?
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone you lost your emblem.
I will eventually return your emblem.
Really?
Yes.
It'll be easier for me to make my move that way too.
I just want you to follow my orders for a while.
What do you want me to do?
You're a quick learner, as expected of a princess.
Senior Executive Kaguya, who has Half-Moon.
Find her weakness in secret, and send her to the Punishment Room.
That's...
You don't have the right to refuse.
I hold your fate, after all.
B-But...
I can't hear your reply, Princess.
As you wish.
Kazuma, are we doing it again tonight?
Of course.
You couldn't find Kaguya's weakness.
It's time for punishment.
It's coming in!
I can't find her weakness while fulfilling my duty.
For swift completion of missions, we have created a fictional country Moonland's embassy on Earth,
to gather intel everyday, don't we?
But other executives are always getting the combat missions.
All you do is live as a student for information gathering.
But...
Finding Kaguya's weakness is an easy task.
But I'm really busy with homework and test and stuff!
And lately, you're doing this to me until morning, every night!
That's because you can't complete the mission I gave you.
Violating my royal body night after night...
No! My body is...
Looks like you're enjoying yourself.
Do you like my dick that much?
This is not me!
You would never...
Not there!
No, stop, stop!
No more!
If you keep going, I...
No!
Don't tell me you want to come?
No, no!
I don't want to!
Not with someone like you...
But you do all night, every night!
I absolutely won't...
Not with you...
I'm gonna come!
I don't want to...
No...
At this rate, I'll...
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
S-Stop...
I have to go to school.
You fucked me all night again.
Please, end it for today.
I-I have to go to school.
N-No, I'm coming again!
It's coming out... You came inside me again!
I'm coming from your sperm shooting in my womb!
You pervert!
You're the pervert.
It's time, Princess.
Go school just like this.
This is disgusting.
I will escort you to school, Princess.
Kazuma... I found Kaguya's weakness.
Report after.
I'll confirm to see if you've completed my order this morning.
B-But... here?
Show me now.
In front of a man... someone might see me.
Please hurry!
What are you talking about?
You wore the uniform without washing off sperm from all of last night,
your pussy stuffed with cum,
set up vibrators on your nipples and pussy,
and attended class like a good student.
That's because you ordered!
I let you clean your face, but I still see sperm stuck on your beautiful hair!
I'm so sick of this.
Maybe someone noticed the perverted princess.
Please... stop already...
Looks like you're pretty turned on.
Your panties are soaked with sperm and pussy juice.
You peed a little too!
No!
I smell a faint scent of your pee.
No, I didn't...
Idiot!
In a place like this...
No, someone will see us...
I can't believe an underling is violating me from behind!
Don't be so rough!
I'm too sensitive from getting stimulated all night!
If someone sees me, a princess like this...
You're right.
The threat of Earth, Great Lunarium's princess is fucking away in the park during daylight!
No! Shut up!
Great Lunarium and the Earthlings,
and all enemy organizations will know about it!
N-No!
I can't live on if something like that were to happen!
N-No! People can hear you thumping from behind!
It's too rough!
Slower!
Your moaning is louder than my hip tapping into yours!
I wonder how long you can hold on.
See? I can hear you moaning!
Well, Princess.
Please report on Kaguya's weakness.
Now?
Give me a proper report and beg for reward!
I-I can't...
If you can, I'll let you come to your content.
Slowly... slowly... no...
I would never beg for it...
No, no! Don't move!
No, no, I...
I'm sorry.
Kaguya's weakness is...
you, Kazuma.
She said she grew up with you.
She said she can never abandon you.
I see, that's what she said?
Kazuma... are you such good friends with Kaguya?
Princess, are you jealous?
N-No way!
I would never!
Did you think Kaguya would steal my cock from you?
N-No!
You can be pretty cute too, huh?
No, idiot! I said no!
Cute pervert princess, did you forget about begging for reward?
It's so deep...
No...
Please.
Please let me cum with your cock.
I'm being violated outside in such lewd way!
I can't take it.
Someone might see me!
No, I'm gonna cum!
No, no, no!
My pussy is drinking Kazuma's sperm.
You're next, Kaguya.
You're a fool, Kaguya.
You wouldn't failed in the mission if you abandoned me.
It's not your fault.
I was just not strong enough.
I'm fine as long as you're safe.
No! What are you doing, Kazuma?
Perverted thing, of course.
Is this what they do in punishments?
You'll just feel a bit embarrassed.
Really?
I guess that's fine, if it's with you.
Hmm? Did you say something?
Nothing, just get it over with.
No, something is...
N-No!
N-No! Such a perverted punishment!
No!
I can endure any torture, but...
If you scramble me down there so much...
It's all wet already.
I didn't know you were such a lewd girl.
N-No! Don't say that!
I'm not lewd at all!
You're so mean, Kazuma.
Why are you punishing me like this?
But your pussy is twitching so happily.
No! That's not true!
I'm not happy...
I'm going to lose it, I will!
No, Kazuma!
It's coming out!
Something is coming out from there!
Isn't it enough?
You've embarrassed me so much!
Should I stick a super fat dildo in your pussy next?
No, don't!
Kazuma, that's mean, so mean!
No, I don't want to lose my precious virginity to a dildo!
N-No!
I'm scared, Kazuma!
Damn, I'm soft on my childhood friend too.
I'll spare you from that.
Kazuma.
Change of plans.
Hey, come in.
Princess... why?
Kazuma, you took too long.
Look what happened to me?
What does this mean, Kazuma?
I thought the three of us can have some fun.
Lunatemis, come here.
Make her feel good.
No, please don't!
Kaguya, you have beautiful tits and virgin pussy.
D-Don't look, please.
My pussy was beautiful too, but Kazuma stuck his cock inside everyday.
The shape is all messed up now!
P-Princess?
Kaguya, you're tasty.
Kazuma, Princess, why?
Don't think too much, and just enjoy the moment, Kaguya.
Lunatemis, I'll give you some reward later if you make her feel good.
Really?
N-No, it's not like I'm taking orders from you because I want reward or anything!
No, this is wrong!
Don't put your finger in there!
K-Kazuma, don't look.
Don't look.
You're moving your finger too hard!
No, I'm going to let out...
Let out perverted sounds.
Kazuma will hear it!
No, Princess!
Anymore, and my body is going to feel strange!
I guess I should put my dick inside soon.
You want it, don't you?
Kazuma, the princess is right here!
So what?
Your pussy will happily lose its virginity to my dick in front of the princess!
N-No... my first time will be in front of someone?
Kazuma, what about me?
I'll stick my dick in you later.
Suck Kaguya for now.
Woman's pussy tastes nice too, doesn't it?
Kaguya's pussy tastes nice.
But Kazuma's dick is the best.
The princess is making me feel all good.
I'm honored.
If you put that cock inside me and I got pregnant...
You'd better take responsibility!
Yeah, I'll take responsibility or whatever.
I-I-It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
No, pull it out, pull it out!
You make such cute sounds, Kaguya.
N-No...
I'm being watched while I'm losing my virginity!
The princess is watching a cock sliding in me!
Does your first cock feel that good?
No, no!
There's no way it feels good when it's so painful and embarrassing!
Don't look.
Don't look at me while I'm in such an embarrassing act!
The princess is watching me having sex.
I can't be in public anymore!
No, not something so perverted!
No, Kazuma's dick is starting to feel good!
No... I'm an executive.
I won't be consumed by such a dirty pleasure!
Then I'll fuck you without protection everyday so you'll get consumed!
No! I can't do something so embarrassing everyday!
I'll lose my mind!
I'll stick my dick inside everyday.
If you get pregnant, let's get the princess and all the executives to watch you give birth!
No, no, no!
I can't let others see me having sex or giving birth!
Being watched turns her on. She's such a pervert!
That's so cute, Kaguya!
But, but...
I didn't know sex feels this good!
I would be a pervert if I got turned on and felt good while being watched!
Don't look! Don't look at my boobs and pussy!
If you keep watching, I...
I'm going to release inside, Kaguya!
No, not inside.
No, not in front of someone!
Do it outside!
Let the princess watch you get pregnant!
No, I don't want to get pregnant while the princess is watching!
No!
Your cock is swelling inside, it's hitting me inside!
Emblem Steal!
Kazuma's hot thing is coming out inside.
I can't continue working as an executive if I got pregnant!
Kazuma, I'm next!
Kazuma's cock feels so good!
My pussy is all hot from watching you having sex with Kaguya!
I'm going to fuck a lot today!
Kazuma, do you feel good?
I felt really good.
But I'm not even your girlfriend, let alone wife.
But your sperm is all the way inside my womb.
In front of someone too!
Kazuma, I didn't know you had an ability like Emblem Steal.
Please stop doing dangerous things.
You don't have to do this, I'll follow your order...
Hey, Kaguya!
What are you trying to get all lovey-dopey when I'm still here?
You just have to help make Kazuma's cock big and hard!
Don't be full of yourself, you mere underling!
Kazuma feels better with me than you!
Don't be full of yourself!
That's not true!
He's my childhood friend, so I can make him feel better!
Are you turned on?
It'd be strange if I didn't, when you're doing something so erotic.
You pervert!
Don't get distracted on a lowly underling!
My pussy feels better, doesn't it?
There's no way my royal pussy would lose to an underling's weak pussy!
Lunatemis's pussy is intense.
I'm about to come inside.
Princess, don't get in my way.
His penis is about to come because of my pussy.
My fresh pussy feels better, right?
Look how comfortable he is!
Th-That's not true!
My pussy is really lewd, so it's so big inside!
Hey, you two.
Stop being jealous.
Idiot! I'm not jealous!
Yeah! We're only doing it because it's your order!
Hurry and come!
I'm working my pussy so hard!
I'm doing such erotic thing like a girlfriend!
Hurry and come!
No!
I'm making Kazuma cum with my pussy!
N-No!
Kazuma, your tongue feels so good!
I can't control myself!
My hips are moving on their own!
The thick thing is inside, all the way in!
It... it feels so good!
It's so good, oh no...
My pussy is turning all hot!
I'm gonna come.
I'm a princess, but I'm hopping on his cock, shaking my hips...
I'm gonna come!
Me too...
No... I'm gonna come with the princess!
I'm coming!
I'm coming, coming, coming!
I can do it.
I really can do it!
With my Emblem Steal...
I'll rule all the snobby female executives!
Lune Pictures
2011: "Evil Woman Executive Committee" / Cotton Doll
Yeah I felt like typesetting this. I bet this is such a boner killer.