I'm shooting!
Could you put on more of a smile?
Damn you...
You can do it, Leader!
Leader!
Next, take your panties... your panties off!
Dammit...
Is this enough for you?
Take it if you want.
It's so pink!
It's so hot...
I can't hold back, so if you'll excuse me...
Please, Kizaki!
No! Don't come close!
Damn, this bastard...
He's so turned on!
Don't spank my ass with your cock!
Ka-Kardina!
Don't touch me there!
No...
No... No way!
It can't....
It's in!
My cock only went halfway in!
It can't go deeper but it feels good!
Pisu Hame! Episode 4
Bitch Club
Kizaki Kardina.
Are you seriously challenging me?
Gamble over! Tamao Tsukamu wins 5-4!
Tamao Tsukamu won the Gamble against Kizaki Kardina,
and started the intercourse.
The Bitch Club girls will probably get turned on and join the orgy.
That Tamao Tsukamu, he ain't half bad.
This was only his second Gamble,
but now he'll get lots of bitch photos.
Nothing less from the guy Konome picked.
Indeed.
He might be fit to become the council president next year.
He could become a useful piece in my business game.
As you wish.
Kizaki! Kizaki!
No! No!
He has his brains in his cock...
First time I have seen someone like him...
Come on, deep in!
You did it weird so it wouldn't reach deep.
My pussy's only opened at the entrance, but it's still tight deep in...
It feels strange.
It's my honor, Kizaki,
that someone as pretty and cute as you wants my cock deep in them!
Not that!
It feels great inside you! It's so tight and wet!
It's because you're doing it so wild!
Stupid... Stupid!
Now I'm
on top!
This is it...
Damn... He'll make me cum!
This trash! This...
Damn... I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
First time someone came inside me!
How long... have you all been there?!
Don't take pictures!
Sorry, Leader!
But you were so intense and pretty,
I couldn't help myself and called the others!
You've never been gaudy, Leader!
You never had orgies or anything,
so I'm happy I could see you having sex!
Why is it getting bigger again inside me?
I'm sorry...
But when I think of all these girls staring at me...
You idiot!
Don't take pictures!
Go somewhere else!
Leader, cheese!
Leader, you're so pretty! So hot!
Take us as well!
So cute! Your nipples are like a girl's!
We can't hold back after watching such an awesome fuck with your giant cock!
Here, Tamao!
Um...
Next, the panties!
And mine too!
My G-string!
Geez, my panties are dripping wet.
Here, take them!
The smell of women!
Come! I want your crazy dick in my pussy!
As you command!
It's great... This feels great!
It's not just huge, its shape is great too!
I cummed... He made me cum...
Come on, Tamao! We're waiting!
Pussies are queuing in front of you!
You can use any hole you want!
Damn, it's so good! It feels so good!
I can feel it all the way in myself!
It feels great!
It's... It's... just too much!
Amazing! It's so hard!
My pussy gets drenched when it goes wild inside me!
Please, take my mail address!
Put it in your address book!
Don't worry about anything! Just call me anytime and fuck me crazy!
That's not fair!
Me too!
Give me... one more... shot of cum in my pussy!
Of course!
You can have as much as you want, Kardina!
I'm taking the picture!
Peace!
Are you sure about this?
About Kiritani Konome.
She is your fiance, yet she does so much more to assist Tamao.
She often acts without reporting to us.
Could it be she's planning something behind our backs?
Kiritani Konome...
The Kiritanis have been a powerful family for many years.
Kiritani Matagoro is a famously great swordsman.
He has huge influence in the police and the Ministry of Defense.
He's a true national hero.
Both for me, who'll eventually take the spotlight, and for the Sasugakis too,
this is an engagement of great importance.
It's of course a political marriage decided by the families.
Ever since we were introduced when she was 8,
I can see that on the surface she's obedient, but beyond that...
This is a great chance.
I'll break her pride, honor and her plan too,
and turn her into a wife fitting for me!
What is it?
Heh...
I just thought of making Tamao take pictures of my cock erasing Konome's virginity.
Amazing...
Tamao's so strong!