Welcome back,
Master.
Master" you say.. so this is your part time job at the cafe?
Yes. Am I cute, master?
You don't have to call me master-
This is a maid cafe, so you don't have to be so reserved,
Master.
Master, may I take your order?
Ah, yeah. Let's see... what is this thing called "special service"?
Ehh! Special service?!
Uh, well... if it's not available I can go with something else...
Got your order!
Please wait a moment, master.
Mikura-san, what are you doing?!
I'm... preparing.
Please wait just a little longer, okay?
Sorry for the wait, master.
M-Mikura-san, that getup is...
You don't like it?
I did try my best...
N-No, that's not what I meant...
Ah, thank goodness! It's getting bigger.
That's uh, I mean...!
Well then, I'll start the special service, master!
Stretta: The Animation
Contents. 1 [ Maybe I'm a Breast ]
Hey, Ruma! You wanna go for some shopping after this?
Sorry! I'm on lunch duty today.
Hmm? By the way, those clothes...
Eh?
No matter how you look at it...
Aren't they too... extreme?
Really.
See? There's nothing wrong with it.
See ya!
I wonder why she's in such a hurry...
Amazing, master! It's so hot and big...
Does it feel good, master?
Ah, I'm sorry! You want more don't you, masted?
Please, master, allow me to lick your penis directly.
Ahh, it's so big!
Well then, I,ll start servicing your penis with my mouth.
Mi-Mikura-san, this is really... good...
Master... this time, please make me feel good too...
M-Mikura-san...
My love juice... is also special service.
Please lick it all, master.
Master... you're so good at... licking...
I-I'm supposed to be the one servicing you, but...
I-I'm sorry, it feels so good I...
I'm... gonna...
Go ahead, I'll take every last drop of it! All of it. shoot it all!
Did you feelgood, master?
Ah, you're still so hard. That's good.
Mikura-san, if you touch it like that
I'll want to... again, uh, you know...
You know, umm... no one will be home today.
Wanna come over?
Hmm?
Please choose the photo course you want!
T-Tsuchiya, make sure you see this through to the very end!
Uh, yeah.
Once you re ready, please press the photograph button!
Please look at the camera lens!
Three, two, one!
Hahah, it captured my boobs!
One more photo!
Three, two, one!
Oh wow, it got captured this clearly...
Once you re ready, please press the photograph button!
Ki... Kirishima-san.
Oh no, I'm so much more turned on than I thought I would be...
Once you re ready, please press the photograph button!
K-Kirishima-san...
You, hold on to this!
Please look at the camera lens!
Three, two, one!
Next, lets see something cute!
Go for it...
The next two photos will be taken in quick succession!
Three, two, one!
Hahah, this is really embarrassing!
It's round!
It zoomed in on the second shot?! Hahah...
Hey, my asshole is cute, isn't it?
The next shot will be a full-body photo!
Three, two, one!
How pretty!
Next, next!
The next shot is the last one!
Three, two, one!
Ahahah! Just like a performing artist!
Next, next!
Uh, looks like that's it.
Let's do it once more, you take yours out too.
Huh?
It's been bothering me for a while already.
You wanna have sex, don't you?
Once you re ready, please press the photograph button!
Please look at the camera lens!
Three, two, one!
How lewd... your dick is so hard.
One more photo!
Three, two, one!
Ohh, erotic, how erotic!
Hurry up and put it in!
Once you re ready, please press the photograph button!
Oh, this is so thrilling!
Please look at the camera lens!
Three, two, one!
Next, let s see something cute!
Tihat's not cute at all, it's way too perverted!
The next two photos will be taken in quick succession!
Three, two, one!
As I thought, it zoomed in right there...
K-Kirishima-san, I'm... gonna...
The next shot will be a full-body photo!
Oh no, I'm gonna come!
Three, two, one!
The next shot is the last one!
Three, two. one!
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Nope, don't touch me just yet.
Wanna see?
Come on, take a good look.
Wait just a bit...
Feels good?
Ruma-san...
I wonder if this is enough.
You wanna put it in, don't you.
It's okay, come.
It's all... in.
U-Unbelievable, I'm actually doing this with you, Ruma-san...
I'll let you experience something incredible....
W-, Amaz-
Hey. My special skill is... good, isn't it.
My body isn't normal.
I can't... I can't stop myself anymore...
Go ahead, do it however you want.
Again. Her partner today is yet another guy.
I think I'm gonna come!
That's fast!
I wonder what your sperm tastes like?
A slightly salty taste... I suppose.
Y-You know, Ruma-san. I was wondering if we could do this ag-
Nope.
That's all you get.
Oh, and if you tell anyone about this
I'll report this encounter as rape.
A-Alright.
Okada-kun?
Did you... masturbate?
I'm always... just her lookout.
Amazing, amazing! You're really trying hard, aren't you?
Y-Yes.
Hey, those club members will come here pretty soon. Leave it to me.
The way my pussy wraps around your dick is
different when we do it sideways, isn't it?
Coming, I'm coming!
Hmm, sweet. Might even be diabetic.
Damn it!
Seems like sperm is dripping out of her mouth...
Hey. You've never masturbated this whole time, even
though your dick looks like it's about to burst.
You have some serious willpower, don't you?
As I thought, choosing Okada-kun was the right thing to do...