Doctor, what are you doing?
I'm observing young people in their natural habitat.
Don't let me distract you.
Distract me?
Hey, eyes over here!
What's come over you, Matsuri?
C'mon, Nihru, back me up here!
Do what now?
What, again!?
Let me have a turn, Matsuri.
With two mouths, I'll cum right away!
Fakku! Presents: Booby King 48
Suck every tit in sight, no hesitation!
You sure look exhausted, Naoya Inatani.
It's like you're swimming in lust.
Your parent's would surely weep if they saw you like this.
Goddammit, she's making fun of me!
But this actually feels really nice!
You truly are a specimen worth observing.
Well now, may as well join the fun myself.
Okay, lick to your heart's content.
Yes ma'am...
Deeper! Go deeper!
You're this wet, and you still want more?
You're such a naughty girl!
Please don't say things like that!
Oh Nihru, you're so cute.
Superb! What a marvelously erotic life you lead!
Let's make it even raunchier!
Since we've come this far, I'll fuck you all till you beg me to stop!
How's that?
It sure is summer...
Watch out!
I-I'm so sorry!
Umm, I'm really sorry. Are you okay?
I'd feel terrible if you caught cold, so would you mind stepping inside?
Sure, but before that...
Of course.
I'll keep you warm until your clothes dry.
It might slip out, so scrub it harder.
Eek! I'm so embarassed!
Oh god!
Whoa! What're you-
How indecent.
My breasts have become all wet and sticky.
Why did you take it out?
I want to warm myself up inside of you.
No way! That's my-
My dick won't be warmed up unless I do this.
No, I...
Please, it's working really well.
This is so wrong, and yet...
You're hitting so deep!
You're so warm inside, Ms. Mizuki.
My dick is starting to warm up!
Thank goodness. The rubdown's starting to show results!
I can feel it too! I can feel your hot, throbbing penis!
So hot... I feel so hot!
Me too! I'm burning up!
Your clothes won't be dry for a while, so would you like me to warm you up some more?
Elmininate All Trespassers
Good afternoon, passersby!
We're currently handing out free Juice!
Please feel free to take one!
Mind giving me a cup?
Sure! Enjoy.
A small thank you for the juice, miss.
What's that?
We'll now begin our exclusive event!
Hey is that...
Check out her top! Her nipples are totally poking out!
Whoa, really!?
Calm down, guys!
What be this bulge in her pants?
Maybe she's got a vibe or something?
Okay, now that things are heating up...
A little bit of this.
I can't believe myself! I'm masturbating with a vibrator in both holes!
I'M SUCH A DIRTY WHORE!
I'm teasing myself while wearing vibrators in my pussy and asshole!
It's making me soaking wet!
So I want all you guys...
To masturbate with me!
Look at me! Everyone, stare harder!
Jerk harder!
By the power invested in this coupon, I will be your proxy dick!
Hurry! Ram your thick rod into me!
Here goes, fellas. Are your bodies ready?
It's so thick! Incredible!
Are you watching, boys?
I'm sorry for being a dirty, filthy, whore!
Tomoe!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm done for!
Cum all over me! Bathe me in it!
I'm just a dirty slut!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
Everybody, CUM!
I'm gonna blow too!
Fuck-
That event was so much fun!
I'd love to do it again sometime if you're up for it.
I think I'm hooked!
Sumika Satomura CD Debut Memorial Autograph Session
Finally! Sweet!
Please keep up the good work. I'll be cheering you on.
Thanks so much for your support!
C-Could I trouble you to sign this for me?
Okay...
So you want a dirty-talk CD, do you?
Sure, why not?
Seriously?
But I have some conditions.
First, you will not distribute to others what we record here today.
Second, during recording, you're to masturbate in front of me.
Finally, you can't cum until we're done recording.
Recording
My clit is throbbing every time I touch it!
Oh god, its feels so good!
My naughty pussy lips are twitching at the mere thought of you!
My whole body's twitching while I masturbate!
It's so hard, and twitching!
I get so naughty whenever I see your penis, Inatani.
I'm getting so horny, my nipples are erect!
Ohh, my feet are getting hot. Something's coming!
My chest is getting so hot! My pussy too!
Give me more!
Come on, tease my clit!
No, don't! Don't finger me so hard...
Inatani...
Ah! I'm gonna cum!
My mind's going blank... I-
Nooooo!!!
Y-you're amazing! You feel so good Inatani.
God yes!
You're dick's rubbing so hard!
I'm gonna break!
So good!
I'm being skewered!
This is it! I'm gonna cum, Ms.Sumika!
Me too! Having my pussy drilled is making me cum!
Recording
Ever since you guys moved out, every day's been so lonely I can't stand it!
But the thing is, we may not be related, but we're still siblings.
You understand what that means, right?
I appreciate your feelings, but-
Damn her, stealing our chance!
Talk about bad timing...
Now what!? You're the one who said to wait and see!
Hey don't try to pin this one on me!
Knock it off, you two!
Photo op!
You sure you wanna do this?
Yeah. Just this once, make love to me, big bro.
I'll get you ready down here too.
Wait, that's my-
Now what!? He's already teasing her!
We gotta stop them!
Not yet! We have to time this carefully.
I don't believe it! How could Naoya say such dirty things?
Kaya's been tainted!
Quit pushing! We'll have our chance.
Look at this. You're such a bad girl.
I'm only this wet because of you!
Incredible! The very picture of lust!
Look! He just inserted his fingers!
Unbelieveable! He's fingering her!
Where the hell did he learn something like that!?
And he calls her a bad girl! Disgusting!
Naoya's all grown up now. I'm so proud.
It's okay, go on and cum.
I-I'm cumming! Your fingers made me cum!
EEEEK!
Kaya!
Well, here's the thing...
Do you have any idea what you just did!?
Yeah! I thought you were better than that!
Where did you learn those things, Naoya?
And how come your dick's still hard while we're yelling at you?
'Cause you're all stark naked!
Naoya dear, when did you become such a smart-ass?
H-hey, stop it!
I guess we'll have to re-educate you, hm?
Whoa! You came from a footjob?
You're a bonafide masochist Naoya.
Eww! Naoya, you perv!
What a pathetic sight! Say cheese!
I am shocked!
You're disgusting!
Aww, this sucks! Somebody!
Hey no fair Ichi! You have to wait your turn!
Hey come on! I wanna do it too!
Yeah! We can't let Ichi have all the fun!
Yeah!
Hurry up and switch!
Hang in there Naoya!
I'm cumming!
No!
I was fucking like there's no tomorrow.
After all, I was literally living the dream!
Day in, day out. Fucking and cumming all over them!
Horny houswives...
Cover me! Blow your load all over me!
Cumming!
I even starred in a porno!
Elevator girl, check!
And even my beloved teacher!
Plus a devil's threesome with a doctor!
But once I find the final bra, it's goodbye, halcyon days...
This dreamlike bliss will one day have to end.
This painful reality came before I knew it.
Look Nihru, I did it!
This is the final champion bra!
What?
Congratulations. I've confirmed receipt of the final bra.
Hey, wait. You're not gonna leave, are you?
I'll now return to my old location.
I wanna be with you Nihru!
I love you!
You've received your prize, have you not?
Thank you for your efforts.
I'll be leaving now.
No, wait up!
If I have you, I don't need any stupid prizes!
Thank you. That makes me so happy.
Inatani...
If you don't wake up, the vacuum will get you!
You can't be... Nihru?
Yes, I've come to deliver your prize!
This is my final form.
Do you like it?