Misono Yuki
Next episode
Seiichi became a qualified wizard.
You can do that by losing your virginity.
It happened about a month ago.
It was a night in the middle of June, at about midnight.
As usual, Seiichi was immersed in his work.
This sucks, I'm getting nowhere. Let's take a break.
It was in the summer, but the night wind was chilly a bit,
just enough to clear Seiichi's head.
This is a nice wind.
What should I do now? If it doesn't get popular, then next one will be my last.
What's this?
Is it coming from the neighbor?
I'm doing it here...
It's coming from the neighbor veranda!
I'm such a pervert...
I'm playing with my clit here...
There was a girl masturbating in the moonlight.
She was sitting on the ground with her legs spread wide, touching herself.
As the waves of pleasure washed over her, the girl moved as if to block the intruder.
Do it more...
Is this a dream?
Even then, this is beyond what I could do as an eroge writer...
Look how hard are my nipples! I'm such a lewd girl.
The girl was panting with pleasure as her hard nipples appeared dancing from under her bra.
Amazing! Her boobs are huge and so beautiful!
She had beautiful and huge breasts,
and her waist was slim as could be.
Her buttocks were shapely.
A girl of beautiful proportions.
The name of this girl with a bit too much lust...
But why is Sanjo fingering herself on the veranda?
All that Seiichi knew about her was that her name is Sanjo Maki, and that she is his neighbor.
Her mother is a retired model who owns a fashion brand, so they are quite rich.
And that she attends the private girl's academy nearby.
That academy is what you could call a school for princesses.
It's ranked very high in the country and her results are exceptionally good even there.
She is on the student council, and she's considered something like a Madonna of the school.
My nipples... feel so good... they're so hard...
My pussy's juices are... overflowing too...
My panties are dripping wet...
Gasps and lewd moans were leaving her beautiful lips.
Her heated body suddenly stiffened, her back arching up...
I need more stimulation!
It's not bad with underwear on, but this...
But it feels better directly!
Just a bit more and I could see her pussy...
A girl is enthusiastically masturbating here...
If someone saw me...
They would surely take embarrassing videos...
They would use that to blackmail me and use my body...
I'd become a sex slave!
She has hell of an imagination...
They'd rape my pussy, my ass and even my mouth...
They'd fill me with stinky cum...
Wonderful!
Is that wonderful?
They'd fuck me... every day... Break my hymen with a big, dirty cock...
She's still a virgin?
They'd fill me all the way in my womb!
So much?
A thick cock would pour lots of semen into me!
They'd rape me all day all night long!
Is there any limit to your imagination?
Just imagining it turns me on so much!
I'm touching my clit... I'm cuming!
I'm cumming loud on my veranda! I'm having an orgasm!
Amazing... she really just cummed.
Seiichi was watching the girl in the night...
Not realizing the chill of the wind...
Oh damn.
Moments of silence passed between them.
With Maki
Fuck until you pass out -- Sanjo Maki episode
I'm... sorry.
Maki's long hair was flying in the night breeze.
The pieces of the veranda wall she broke down dance noisily in the wind.
Why are you apologizing?
Well, I kinda peeked on you...
I was doing it on the veranda enjoying the risk that someone might see me.
You don't have to apologize.
Sorry.
I said you don't need to apologize.
So what are you going to do with me now?
What do you mean?
Well, you learnt about how I lewdly spend my days...
If you tried to blackmail me with that, I'd have no choice but to obey.
You know, I'm a writer, but my novels aren't selling all that well,
so as a side job I'm writing eroge scenarios.
Eroge?
You know, those "18+ only" kind of adult games.
You don't know?
How could I not? I love them!
See, now we both know some embarrassing secret about each other,
so this could be a good beginning.
You're a weird person.
That much I'm forced to admit.
That's not it. You told me your secret even though you didn't have to.
You're a crazy nice guy!
You told me about yourself too... Wait, didn't you change your tone?
But now I get it that you're a nice person!
I'm happy.
Now that you've found out about me, I have a bit of a request.
I'd like to exchange my virginity for yours!
Excuse me?
Maki's eyes almost burnt a hole into the point where Seiichi's pants were tellingly bilging.
Then Makis hands reached out for Seiichi's shorts.
She pulls down what she grabbed.
Seiichi's penis stands gloriously.
A girl is rubbing against my cock!
It's so hot... and soft... and wet!
I can't give my virginity to a guy who doesn't understand and accept my perversion.
And I do?
Yeah! I realized it while we were talking.
Will you accept it?
Well, I guess...
I'm happy! Thanks!
It's a bit surprising that my neighbor was just my type.
Your big cock isn't just hard, it's flexible too.
It's so hot and a bit grotesque...
The hot juices from the girl's pussy dripped on what was about to enter her.
Is the angle right?
Can I put it in now?
It's so hard and thick...
The feeling that something was broken echoes in Seiichi's member.
I think you just broke my hymen!
Are you all right, Maki? Does it hurt?
I just lost my virginity... It's wonderful.
It's a bit tough because it's so thick inside me!
Are you all right, Maki?
I am! It's amazing...
So this is how it feels to have a cock rubbing on the inside of my pussy...
Maki, I can't hold out...
This new level of joy pushes Seiichi beyond his limit quickly.
It's okay... I'm getting close too...
So... this is the real thing!
My pussy feels great...
My head is dizzy...
Me too!
I'm cumming! My pussy is cumming!
I feel something hot deep inside...
Fill me! Fill my lewd womb with lots of cum!
Cum inside me!
Inside?!
It's okay. Today should be relatively safe...
Relatively?
I wanted to try how it feels to get cummed inside...
So please don't hold back...
Fill my womb with hot cum!
I'm there... I don't mind if I get pregnant either!
My womb is yours!
Make you pregnant... are you kidding?
I'm... I'm at my limit!
My pussy is... my pussy is there!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My pussy is cumming... It's my first time, yet my pussy is enjoying it all!
Her pussy is surprisingly, unexpectedly wildly pulsing
with the power of her orgasm, not tainted by the pain of her broken hymen.
The night echoes with Maki's cries of joy.
Oh god! I forgot something important.
Something important?
Your name. I don't know your name.
Seiichi. Sakonji Seiichi.
Seiichi, huh? I'm Sanjo Maki.
You knew that already, didn't you?
I hope we'll get along well.
You're my future husband.
I too hope we'll... wait, husband?
That's why you don't mind getting pregn--
Their lips pushed against each other.
Maki's tongue enters Seiichi's mouth.
That was the first kiss between the beauty and the otaku.
Seiichi...
While Seiichi was busy working,
Maki was doing her summer homework at the table in the living room next door.
I could hear that you're working on something hard
all the way to the next room!
Yeah, my next novel isn't coming around right.
I see. Then you need to cheer up!
To... cheer up?
Exactly.
Turn your back to me.
If your cock is relieved, you might get some good ideas.
Right?
Maki...
You should just keep working, Seiichi.
I'll just squeeze out your cum.
Your cock is so big already!
I love you!
I'm happy...
It's twitching so lewdly, even though I haven't done anything yet.
I'll get to it then!
I love how your erect cock feels!
It feels amazing...
I know what your weak spots are, Seiichi.
Does it feel good?
Of course... I'm the happiest man ever.
Your cock is always so thick and hard and big...
It feels great just to lick it...
That spot...
I can feel it twitching as my tongue touches it...
Maki, I'm...
It's okay, cum!
Cum in my mouth!
I'm cumming, Maki!
It's coming out! So much is coming out!
Your sperm is really warm and stinky...
It's yummy!
While licking the cum off her face, Maki smiles lewdly.
Have you cheered up?
It's so hard again! Are you ready for another round?
Maki cheered up so much that she couldn't suppress her urges.
She pushes Seichi down on his mattress and
treats him in preparation of their union.
This is big enough already, right?
Then I'll be on the top.
We can pass the foreplay, Maki.
Don't underestimate my lewd pussy.
Look.
I don't underestimate it. And it's magnificient.
So I'm taking your cock.
My perverted pussy will take it all in!
Your phone is ringing.
Worst timing ever. Who could it be?
It's Yuki?
Yuki?
My parents are divorced. I live with my mother,
and my sister Yuki lives with our father.
We were the best sisters ever,
but now we're living separately.
Hello, what's up? I wasn't expecting a call.
You want to live with me? You don't want to go back to dad?
Where are you, Yuki?
We're going for Yuki... Why do I need to put on my suits?
There's a reason.
Maki and Seiichi changed clothes and they are taking a train to the next town to pick up Yuki.
It's just after noon, but the train is relatively full.
I wanted to try it once...
A salaryman assaulting me on the train...
Come and assault me!
My body is more sensitive than always...
I can feel you through your pants.
Maybe you're dripping precum already?
Probably. But so are you.
You're such an exhibitionist pervert.
Yeah... I enjoy that you're groping me on the train...
I'm really an exhibitionist pervert.
I can feel something warm is soaking through your pants.
Really? Damn, I didn't want to ruin my pants...
Really? Then I should just do this...
It's so hard! Your big cock is really lively.
I'm groping you and you're groping me on the train...
I'm really turned on! This feels amazing!
It feels too good if you do it like that!
That wouldn't be good. I'll put it in then.
Your finger is in my pervy hole!
Rub it harder there...
Warm juice is dripping from your cock.
Just like that, Maki...
It feels great.
Touch my breasts too!
You're daring, aren't you.
But...
Maki is most definitely aware of the curious gazes invited by her exhibitionism.
On the other hand, she tries to push her delight to an even higher grade by letting them see.
My breasts feel weird if you grope them like that!
Don't tease my nipples like that!
It's twitching!
This is so embarrassing... and it feels even better because of that!
My pussy... my nipples... I feel like I'm going to melt!
Your erect penis is so hard...
It's twitching against my hand... So lewd.
Your hand feels good...
You can cum anytime.
You can cum anytime as well.
Now two fingers?!
You're stirring up my pussy!
I can feel you spreading me...
So much!
I'm cumming!
Don't be so loud, Maki!
I can't stop, my pussy and my breasts feel too good!
I'm at my limit too. But if I cum like this, it's gonna get on your clothes...
It's okay, just cum! It can go all over my clothes too!
I'm there!
Your cock is pulsing... Spilling cum all over me...
The train is slowing down more and more.
They don't realize that in their excitement.
Maki's sister is waiting at the next station.
The door opens right behind Maki and Seiichi as they push against each other.
In the crowded train, Seiichi and Maki are standing there covered in cum.
Their eyes meet.
Silence echoes between them on the platform.
Collaboration Works! In the next episode...
The main character, Osaka Ippei dreams of raping a girl,
but he lacks the courage to actually do it.
He finds a mysterious beauty unconscious in the park,
and not even considering rape, he carries her home with him.
One day he was watching an idol's show on the tv,
and murmured "she wants to get raped".
She's the popular teen idol Kujo Sakura?!
I want to try rape too?
Original animation video: Please rape me!
Chidori Yuma, "Beep! Beep'd! Beep!" Episode.
On sale from 2012. April 27.
At least we plan so!