Endo and I went to a a hot spring resort over the weekend.
When Endo got excited, the excitement spilled over to me.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Could it be that you... want to have sex?
He was always horny.
My nipples are so hot.
Your hard cock is going inside me.
Hey, I think the open air bath at this hot spring is mixed bathing late at night.
The private lessons of the angels
FAKKU! Presents
Women
Some of it is still inside.
Don't look at me like that, Endo.
Sorry.
You had all the time in world to touch me just a minute ago.
It's so warm...
Mikura...
I can see your privates.
You pervert.
But...
I can't believe your cum is leaking out.
Sorry about that.
So warm.
I feel great!
Endo.
Endo, do you want to cum again?
It must be hard to bear your boner.
We've done it so often today, but I guess that's what perverts do.
Mikura...
Don't worry.
I'll make sure none of the others notice anything.
We shouldn't be doing this.
They'll find out if you're too loud
But...
It's hard as rock, Endo.
I want you too.
Mikura...
The others haven't noticed, right?
We're doing this, and they don't suspect a thing.
Mikura, don't be too rough or it'll be difficult for me.
Sorry there.
Sorry to interrupt.
See you later in the common room.
She didn't notice.
Hey, Endo.
There's a lot of room over there.
Mikura...
It's so wet now.
Mikura... I...
Your cock is so hot and twitching...
You're putting fire into me...
Do you like that?
Next I'll do it with breasts turgid from the hot spring.
Mikura... you're as slutty as ever.
Am I?
Maybe I am.
Since I went to a hotel with you, the different locale...
Mikura, that tickles... I can feel it scraping against my cock...
It's twitching so much...
You came a lot.
I'm sorry it went all over your face.
Make me cum now.
You're so hot, Endo.
You're amazing... it's hitting my insides...
I think they're watching us.
But I don't mind, I can't stop!
Faster, Endo!
They're watching us.
I'm sure they can see us over there now.
This is so embarrassing.
I'm think I'm gonna cum.
They're watching us...
Oh no, I'm loving it~
I'm about to cum.
Me too.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum!
I'm coming!
Didn't that feel good?
Let's go to a hot spring again someday.
This is weird.
They should've been here a while ago.
Thanks for taking me.
See you tomorrow.
Oh! Here she is!
If it isn't Tanabe.
You don't recognize me?
It's me.
Shibuya?
What's with the getup?
I'm doing this as part-time work for the winter holidays.
There's a package for you.
Oh, that... that...
It's kind of suspicious that you're waiting down here for it to arrive.
Hm... it says on here that it contains spare computer parts.
Say... isn't this...
It's just a massage stick.
Lately my shoulders, back, legs, nose and eyes have been kinda...
Still, in what world are these computer parts.
Well, you know...
I've seen something like this before, you know.
Isn't this thing for sex?
Wow.
It's trembling so violently.
Hey!
This is how you use it, I think.
You look adorable.
Seems you like it.
Shibuya, don't do this.
If you rub it like that, I'll...
Oh, look... do you already have an erection?
I can feel it.
Shibuya, you really shouldn't...
Come on, stop.
You've got to be kidding me.
You came?
I told you to stop.
Sorry! Sorry!
I didn't expect you to cum so quickly.
Shibuya?
Hey, will you do the same for me now?
You don't want to watch me while you do it?
Okay, let's go.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
This feels weird.
It tickles.
How can I describe it?
Hey... do you want to try it out?
Sorry.
Did that hurt?
I'm fine.
I was just surprised.
Do it like you did.
This isn't so bad.
It's tickling my nipples.
If you moan like that, it's going to make me hard again.
That's just the way it is.
It feels good.
Put it over there too.
Give this place a good rub too.
I don't think I can hold it any longer.
Tanabe... please.
Make me cum.
Put all you have into it.
How's this?
Do you like it?
Please... keep it leveled at one spot.
Do it down there too.
Amazing...
When you do it down there, it shakes my insides,
and even my stomach...
I think you can set this massage gadget on a higher setting.
What the... this is so...
Don't... rub it against it...
I'm going numb down there.
I told her to stop until the end, and she didn't.
I'm gonna cum...
No...
I'm soaking wet.
Well, I'll be fine.
You've got a job to do to the end now.
You're already hard as rock, aren't you.
See, it's all hard.
Shibuya, if you suck it so hard, I'll...
Just wait.
You want to fuck right here?
Yeah.
I crave your cock too badly by now.
Stick your hot prick inside me.
Shibuya...
Hurry up...
Hot... hot...
Your cock is so hard... I love it...
It's so hot inside you... and wet...
No surprise considering how long you prodded me with that.
No... don't come here.
Hey, you... wait, okay?
What are you doing?
She'll hear us.
Is somebody there?
I'm sorry I scared you.
I just fell.
Are you unhurt?
Yes.
I'm fine.
Be careful, then.
Why didn't you stop?
You were too tight inside.
I couldn't stop.
What's that supposed to mean?
Didn't you like it too?
I didn't, I didn't...
Don't say weird stuff.
Don't...
If you do that now...
You're tightening up down there again.
No!
If you put both there...
I feel so weird!
Amazing...
I can feel the tickling too.
I'm going to check out a higher setting.
Don't... don't...
It's rubbing it...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
You came a lot, didn't you.
I guess.
Look how sticky I am all the way inside my body.
I'll have to take a bath at home.
Sorry about that.
I'm going to borrow this.
I want to look into this whole electric massage thing inside my bathtub.
Maybe I'll feel even better next time.
Look forward to it.