Sorry. Let me think about it.
Are you kidding me?
Kaito!
Kaito.
K-Kaito!
Kaito!
Tropical Kiss.
Don't you think Hanabi has gotten beautiful with her big tits?
Your drinks are coming!
Momoi Ichigo
Hinata Hanabi
Pretty hot here.
Kazane
Himuro Rikka
Got it.
Miru
Aoi Matsuri
They'll come pick you up soon.
Kurata Mariya
Minaduki Izumi
Yes. Very well, then.
Nanagase Rin
Saotome Nagi
Kawashimo Rino
Fuurin
Why am I running into everyone here?
You're a cute one.
Wanna hang out?
Get lost.
And that's how that happened.
We always have customers lately and can't ever get a day off.
Why's Hanabi so normal around me? She rejected me.
Hey, Kaito.
I'd like to talk to you af—
Kaito!
Izumi!
Still want to get married to me?
Er...
I thought it was an established fact, but I see I have trouble.
Now, then! Let us proceed to fight the falling birthrates now!
Yeah, about that...
Why would a daughter from the family in control of Minaduki Industries do that with me?
It's futile to ignore it in order to stop me from loving you.
Ignore what?
There are circumstances!
You pervert!
What happened?
You two haven't changed.
Aren't you popular?
You were my first love, though.
Same for me.
But you had Hanabi.
So I figured you saw me as the big sister type.
I knew I'd meet you again here, though.
I figured I'd still love you.
Nagi felt like that?
There were circumstances.
The reason I vanished after confessing to you back then is because my parents were fighting for custody.
They made me quit my part-time work too.
So that's what happened.
I thought I'd never see you again.
I really love you.
Back then...
Matsuri...
...and now.
Perfect.
Were you trying to get away from me when you moved away all of a sudden?
Lots of stuff happened back then.
But I feel the same as back then.
I want to make up for my mistakes.
You've got it wrong.
Not the sharpest tool in the shed, huh?
Here's my answer.
You know, there's no way I'd let a guy in room I don't like.
I don't regret it.
You took a long time.
Where were you?
I went home with Rikka.
Hey, what's your relationship with Rikka?
That's none of your business.
You rejected me.
That's not it!
The reason I said that was...
I... thought you were joking...
I wanted to tell you my real feelings, but...
You ran home right after.
I did something that can't be undone.
I came here to look for you too.
You did all that to look for me?
Please believe me!
I've loved you ever since we were little.
This time I'm the one waiting.
Whom should I pick?!
Something on your mind?
Pretty much.
But man, she sure grew while we didn't see each other.
We're on break in a little while, huh?
Want to eat lunch wi—
Kaito!
Why are you slacking off here?
I'm not slacking off.
Oh, there she is.
Of course I'm here!
Sorry. Couldn't see you.
Want me to tell you of a good optometrist?
Want me to tell you of a good plastic surgeon?
Want me to tell you of a good breast augmentation?
No thanks.
You were thinking about it.
Hey, Kaito. Do you want to spend lunch break together?
Kaito!
Let's spend our lunch break together!
Kaito is spending his lunch break with me!
That's not yours to decide!
Shut up.
That's exactly why he's not picking you.
Who's not picking whom?
Do I really have to spell it out for you?
Jesus Christ!
Come on, Kaito.
Um, I...
Kaito!
Want to eat lunch?
I can't help the outfit. I had to help out Fuurin.
Why do you take it so seriously?
Rikka's a good person.
You sure seem to know her well.
Surprising how close you can be just by being neighbors.
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Don't worry, it always looks like this.
How's it?
I'll be done in a minute.
Should I clean up?
Don't bother.
I'll cook, then.
Good idea!
Your cooking's great!
Been a long time since I could make it for you.
Now, where's the kitchen?
I'll cook.
Reconsider!
No. I'll do it.
Chill out, Hanabi.
But...
I'll do it.
There's a lot of alcohol here.
What is it?
Nothing.
All right.
You're online.
Thanks.
I just finished too.
Let's go home, Hanabi.
What's your deal?
There's food.
Elaborate.
Microwaved?
Made it myself.
Get back!
What's wrong?
Rikka's cooking is... yeah...
Bad?
Worse than anything upon the face of the Earth!
You're a rude one.
Let's eat it.
So, what did you make?
Special udon and cheese miso soup.
I'm done. Eat.
It's so good!
I thought I'd never eat your cooking again!
I thought I'd never meet you again either.
I was really surprised myself.
I was more surprised.
No, I was.
I was!
All right, see you tomorrow.
Thanks for the food.
Oh, Kaito.
I've got something for you.
If something ever happens.
Okay.
I want yours too.
Okay!
I owe them an answer.
Something on my body?
No.
You're weird.
Nothing at all sticks out, in fact.
Hey.
You went in already, I see!
No sweat.
Why are you smiling?
Looks like we're all together.
What, is this group bathing?
This is a lost battle for me too.
Overkill.
Now we've all gathered.
Looks like everyone's here.
Feel better?
Not particularly.
Can't Kaito swim?
He almost drowned when he was little.
If he should be in danger of drowning, I'll perform mouth to mouth resuscitation!
I think if you're persistent enough, he'd accept you.
I don't think I can do it.
Let him touch your tits and see if it makes him fall in love.
What kind of suggestion is that?
Isn't that your plan?
So that he kisses me?
Not just that. Other things.
That's not really...
I did that.
I'm really not trying to force this or anything.
But his feelings are a bit...
Of course I want to do it.
But then again, I can't really imagine what a kiss is like.
Did you ever kiss anyone, Hanabi?
I...
You haven't, huh?
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
And what about you?!
What is it?
Good thing there are no clouds.
That's right. Today is Tanabata.
You just realized that?
We wrote little wishes earlier.
I see.
What did you wish for?
Mine was...
I don't think it will ever come true.
What are you saying? It won't?
Yeah. It never will.
How about being a bit more positive and saying it's unlikely?
Unlikely, huh?
Want to write another?
Then...
Will you kiss me here?
Kiss me.
Whats up suddenly?
You told me yourself.
This is my wish.
But...
You only kissed Rikka?
You kissed her, right?
I've wondered for a while now, but what happened between you two?
What's the matter?
This is sudden.
It's obvious to wonder when I see you two.
Right after I moved here, I started working as a bartender.
Rikka is practically an alcoholic,
so we used to drink a lot together.
One day there were fireworks nearby.
It made me remember it.
I thought I'd gotten over you, but...
I remember it all again.
I loved Hanabi
I was telling her about you.
But that is when suddenly...
Something regrettable happened.
It was a horrible mistake.
You're the one I love.
And still, it was Rikka...
I see.
So that's what happened...
I'm not really upset or...
So why are you crying?
Sorry...
I put you through so much.
It's not your fault.
That was my mistake.
Do you love Rikka?
I don't know.
I want to start from zero again.
I was waiting so long for you to confess!
I've wanted to tell you that.
Then... then we can...
I want to go back to how it used to be.
I want to go back to how it used to be: Hinata Hanabi
We hope this thing sells like hotcakes: The Staff
I guess I have to give her some time.
I know you're in there, Hanabi.
Open up.
I know you can hear me.
How long are you gonna mope?
What's that gonna change?
Is that what you want?
Hey, just ignore that wench, Kaito.
You've got me.
But hey... It's been too long since the last time.
Don't!
Just as planned.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's go, then.
Are you kidding me?
Grow some breasts first!
Shut up, bitch.
What?!
What are you doing?
Kaito, between Rikka and me...
whom will you pick?
I'll save...
both!
Have you come to?
Sorry! Sorry!
I thought you were drowning there.
We weren't.
It was all a ploy.
We wanted to figure out who you'd pick.
A ploy?
In the end, though...
I think he'll pick you.
Me?
You're really important to him.
I think...
He'll save us both!
Both of us.
You're crazy.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating. I think we went too far.
Definitely.
Now, then.
Would the loser go away now?
Hanabi knew you better than anyone.
That's the truth.
Thank you, Rikka.
What happened between you two?
Not telling.
Women's secret.
I see.
Sorry I made you worry.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
You said you wanted to go back to how it used be, right?
I don't want to go back.
That's another experience which makes me who I am.
I wouldn't even be working here.
Also...
You're saying you can't answer my feelings and just want to be just friends?
You presume.
I realized when he grabbed me a moment later than her.
Honestly.
I love you more now than I did back then.
Kaito...
I love you, Hanabi.
I hope I'm not being pushy again.
No, no.
I feel the same.
I love you too.
Don't refuse me again, okay.
I won't do that to you again.
What?
Kaito and Hanabi are together?
A couple?
Jeez.
Are you serious?
Yes.
We're serious.
And with that all my chances are gone.
Don't give up. Otherwise you can kiss your love goodbye.
Well then, congratulations.
Now the real hell begins.
Hanabi is so obstinate, so they fight over everything.
I know! They scream and hit each other!
And when he's wounded, I'll...
Come on! Don't lie!
Come to my place if you're sad, okay?
You can come to me too!
You're welcome any time!
I'll listen to you grief!
This is some obvious NTR shit, ladies.
I won't let you!
Well, this looks difficult.
Tropical...
Kiss.
Kaito!
Stroke me.
There, there.
Slacking off during work for the second time.
Now they get their pay deducted, huh?
Hey, do that during your free time!
Think about what all the people here will think.
Hey, stop right there, Hotaru!
I'm so tired.
We can't rest yet.
I'm on break too. Want to sleep on the table?
Okay.
Let's do that.
Sorry.
Let me apologize in advance.
What are you doing?
I saw your underwear and...
Don't just act.
Shh. Keep quiet.
What's the problem if we don't have sex?
You can't expect that when your boobs are right here.
But we can't do anything here...
Come on.
You tit lover.
Just my breasts, okay?
Be more gentle.
I can feel it.
Yeah, it's good.
Then let's get rid of this.
This is embarrassing.
That's a bit...
This here?
No!
That's it.
You said only your breasts, right?
That's right, but...
Break won't last forever.
We've got to eat too.
But Kaito...
What's wrong?
Do it.
Do what?
Fuck me!
Do you want to lick it?
You don't have to.
It's not that I don't want to...
I just don't know what to do...
All right...
That's right.
Now move.
Like that?
Go on.
That's great.
I'm gonna...
Oh? You're alone, Kaito?
Yeah, Hanabi is—
Fuurin?
Still eating?
Hanabi went to get the food.
Why are you here?
Something's wrong with my rabbit ears.
What could be?
I'm pretty sure there's a spare here...
The rabbit ears I use are special.
They wobble around like real rabbit ears.
Something wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, stop it.
She won't notice me.
Well isn't this suspicious.
Don't come here.
Nothing is going on here.
Oh, no. Does she know?
There they are!
So long.
Tropical Kiss episode two coming December 28th 2012
My heart was about to stop!
This is my punishment for you.
Atone!
Jesus...
This feels so good...
That's my revenge.
Really?
We can't stop here, right?
Should we really go on?
I've gotten all hard because you're such a pervert.
I'm not.
So what's this?
Really? Like this?
I've wanted to try it.
It's a bit embarrassing.
It feels like I'm being forced.
Are you okay?
It hurts.
Don't take it out.
But!
I'm okay.
Move as you want.
That's amazing.
It feels good now.
Okay.
Got it.
It's good.
It feels good.
This is amazing.
You're amazing, Hanabi.
You're so hard and big, Kaito.
This is too good.
You'll get used to it.
Yeah.
You're the only one who can do it for me.
This feels weird now, Kaito.
Weird?
It tingles.
It's weird.
All right!
I can't stop myself.
It's good.
I'm gonna come.
Don't come...
inside...
Soon...
For me too...
Not inside, Kaito.
Hanabi...
You idiot...
I told you not to come inside.
I can't get pregnant now.
Sorry. I'll take responsibility.
What the hell is wrong with these rabbit ears?!
Oh, you're back, Hanabi?
Yeah...
We're already done eating.
I see.
You ate Hanabi, I guess?
Of course no—
It's oozing down your leg.
I saw you giving him a blowjob earlier too.
And I even told you not to come inside me!
I love the mistakes of youth!
This woman is a devil.
After that, Hanabi and I...
slowly came to really like sex...
We enjoyed all the pleasure
which we could think of.
Not there.
Where?
I'm getting dizzy.
They'll see us.
Why does it feel so good?
Someone's going to come.
No, not during work.
We already did it this morning, right?
Why are we doing it alone...?
I'm going to come.
Hanabi!
Shot your hot seed inside me!
I want it!
How many times did we do it the last week?
I stopped counting after twenty.
32.
You like it too much.
You've come to want it too.
You... idiot.
I wish I could tell myself from back then that it would all work out like this.
Yeah, that reminds.
I've got somewhere I want to go during the next holidays.
It's just like back then.
Why did you want to go here?
Maybe we took the long route since then,
but we still have some important memories here.
Hey, Kaito.
Want to redo it?
What happened back then?
Wouldn't it be a lot more fun if we were together?
Hanabi, go out with me.
I've always waited for that.
This is how it should have been.
Would you have wanted to do that too?
Who knows?
Kaito.
We'll be together forever.
Of course.
Let's go back to our Aloha.