My slave, Tachibana Ichiro, turned into a tentacle monster.
To collect magical power,
I had no choice but to have sex with him.
But then Kaya Blanche from the Far Eastern Witch Association showed up.
Wait what?! You made Miss Yuko pregnant?
What do you think you're doing, you moron?!
The time has come.
Episode 03: Eisen Faust's trap
This is really an emergency!
I made Miss Yuko pregnant!
What should I do?!
You moron!
Just how much do you want to cum?!
You pervert!
That's not pregnancy.
Kaya? What do you mean?
It's resurrection magic.
What?!
It's a secret, forbidden spell,
that takes a man with magical talents as a host,
then absorbs the magical power of a witch
to revive the dead.
Forbidden magic!
The caster isn't human.
It's a mud puppet trying to revive the evil magician Faust.
One of the seven golems,
Eisen Faust!
You found me out?
What's this power?!
No way!
It's coming! It's being born!
Miss Yuko!
A magical barrier?!
We can't get close.
If you suck on them so hard...
I can feel something coming out!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from evil suckers torturing my breasts!
What!?
I can feel it... flowing in my breasts...
Stop it!
You're raping my breasts with spikes!
Don't... such huge spikes can't go in!
If... If you cum in my breasts...
My milk is spraying! I'm c-cumming!
I'm ejaculating from my breasts!
It's fondling my breasts so hard... it feels...
It's coming... It's really getting born!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
The evil magic makes my pussy so sensitive. I'm cumming from giving birth!
I'm cumming!
Miss Yuko!
I must destroy the cursed egg while I can.
It vanished?!
You did well.
You're that monster magician!
Eisen Faust!
He did it?
Well done, Tachibana Ichiro.
Futaba Lily Ramses.
I appreciate your cooperation.
I should thank you honestly.
You fooled us badly! You're not getting away with this!
Be prepared, Eisen Faust!
Such a strong-spirited girl. But I don't have time to play with you.
Wait!
He is the cause of all this!
Miss Yuko!
Master!
Master?
Don't come close to my master!
You filthy magician!
She's still not waking up?
Kaya, you and Miss Yuko know each other?
Forgive me for going against Master's will.
Kaya?
Is something wrong?
There is only one way for us to save Master and thwart Eisen Faust's plan.
And that way is...
You won't suffer. It's just a moment.
What kind of joke is this!?
I could die from that!
Murderer!
She wants to kill me!
Stop there.
If I destroy you, the vessel of the resurrection magic,
everything will be resolved.
Now I'm so reassured!
Wait, I still don't want to die!
I have no sympathy for filthy magicians.
Die, Tachibana Ichiro!
Lily!
You came to save me?
What are you doing, you moron!
Are you getting in my way?
I'm Futaba Lily Ramses, the apprentice of the Witch of the Sun, Miss Yuko!
When did you become her apprentice?
Shut up, you moron!
A little chick like you as the apprentice of the Witch of the Sun?
Don't make me laugh.
What?
If you get in my way, you won't get away with a scratch like that!
Lily, you're bleeding!
It's none of your worries. Stand back, you moron.
You stand aside, girlie.
We're the same age. Don't just look down on me, you get it?!
Fascinating.
Then show me what you little boaster can do,
if you claim to be her apprentice!
I don't boast!
I'll never forgive you for bringing shame to the name of the Witch of the Sun!
You're not bad, Kaya Blanche.
Stop there.
Master!
Kaya, Ichiro is very important for me.
Even if you're an inspector, and he's a magician, please don't take his life!
I'll take responsibility. Please, Kaya!
Who is she? Why is she calling you Master just like that?
Kaya's mother was my best friend.
At the time of her tragic death, she entrusted her young daughter to me.
Kaya has always been and will be my apprentice.
Then why did she try to kill me?
She's worried. I fell in Eisen's trap and lost much of my powers.
Please don't blame her.
I know it's much to ask, but please help her.
Please!
Miss Yuko!
We'll do something about it. Just rest.
We must chase Eisen.
Wait a second! Is that wound alright?
This much is nothing!
I must examine you!
Huh?
You're bleeding!
It's nothing important!
Thanks... going so far for me.
I must check if you're not hurt elsewhere.
Yes, that you must.
Your nipples are hard already.
If you don't touch them... If it wasn't for your examination, they wouldn't be!
You want examine me there too? You lecher.
Amazing, why am I so wet?
Your finger feels good.
My pervy juices are overflowing!
You're toying with my pussy... your filthy finger is making me cum!
I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...
I came from your finger...
So this is how my pussy juices taste...
I think I should use appropriate tools for thorough inspection.
I'll need you to prepare it though.
I don't have a choice.
Okay, it's ready. Can I inspect you... deeply?
Feel free to... as deep as you want...
It's in me! Your finger is nothing compared to your cock!
Amazing! Your cock is filling me!
Inspect... Inspect me deeper!
Amazing! You're cumming so much.
So much! It feels like my pussy is ejaculating.
Are you going to inspect me there too?
Of course. I must check everything.
Anal?! You're teasing my ass, and now you're sticking your cock in too?!
This is too much! My pussy can't take any more!
Lick it clean.
I'm wetting myself... and you moron are watching me...
Let's keep the examination going.
Are you sure that compass is right?
Huh? You don't trust Miss Yuko's magical tools?
That's not it! But such a ruin?
Could you be afraid?
Not a sin-sin-single chance!
That's Eisen's familiar!
This is it! Let's go, Ichiro!
Hey, hold on...
They must be down there.
This is it.
Welcome to my castle.
Let me welcome you.
We are your valued guests, yet you won't even give us some tea?
Forgive me. I had another guest already.
Kaya!
Oh my, you got caught by Eisen? How fitting.
Don't look!
Eisen Faust, you misunderstood something.
That woman was targeting one of my possessions.
A possession... Wait, you mean me?
Sorry to tell you, she won't do for a hostage.
Then you don't care what happens to her?
Kaya!
Don't worry.
I just injected a love potion.
A love potion?
Remember it, when you were little, I took you as a hostage and raped your mother!
Stop!
Shut up!
Under the effect of the love potion, your mother was having an orgy with my beasts.
In front of your eyes.
How horrible...
Stop... Stop....
Your mother was a proud witch, but at my hands she turned into a lustful swine!
Mama...
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Now the girl came to avenge her mother, and she'll become the subject of my research again!
You damn magician!
I see! So that's why she hates magicians so badly!
Disgusting...
You're disgusting, Eisen Faust!
So what?
I'll kill you!
It's pointless.
Hey, what are you doing, you moron?!
I don't know! My body's moving on its own!
What are you saying?!
Now you can't get in the way.
The preparations are complete, boy.
Rape her.
Kaya?!
I won't! Why would I listen to you?!
Are you sure? If you don't help her, she'll go crazy from the love potion.
Rape me! I'm at my limit! Please, rape me!
But...
I don't want to die! I'll just use you to stay alive!
Don't worry about it.
Damn!
Okay! But next time let's have proper sex!
It doesn't count in front of a guy like that!
You're a weird guy, Tachibana Ichiro.
You can rape me all you want...
But it's my first time...
Never mind.
Sorry, I can't hold back!
Stop, Ichiro!
Don't... Don't stimulate me at so many places at once!
I'll be cumming... so hard... My whole body feels like it's a huge pussy!
I'm cumming!
Stop... I can't stop!
I can't take it!
Don't... Don't look...
Don't look so hard at my wet dirty place!
I know... Even without experience, I know...
That's a peni--
I-It's huge!
The first time a cock is in me!
It's sliding inside me!
My first cock... a tentacle cock is sliding deep into me!
I lost my virginity to a tentacle cock!
If you keep this on, I'll turn into your bitch!
I can't stop! I want to take you!
I asked for it. Do what you want!
Stick your cock in me so deep, so hard,
that my pussy will lose its shape forever!
Finish it... quickly... I'll become your bitch!
It's coming! Your semen is filling my pussy!
It's amazing... I'm cumming!
Stop it! Won't you listen to me?
Kaya. Stick out your tongue.
This is going just as Eisen wanted it...
We can't save Miss Yuko like this!
So good... your saliva tastes so good...
I can't think... I can't do anything without you!
More... Give me more...
Pleasure me with your mouth...
Wait! Ichiro, you idiot, is this serious?!
The next episode will be the last!
You cheeky little commoner!
It seems to be true...
R-Really?
Oh Ichiro, it's so big again!
It's male biology!
What are you doing, you stupid pervert!
It's the last time, so we'll take a lot of your cum!
I've no choice then...
Thank you very much!
Tachibana Ichiro, tonight will be amazing!
That's true.
Be prepared!
This will be the end for you!
Don't miss the next episode!