This voice! No way...
What do we do? Will we just let her have Kouta for herself?
I want to do something, but Kou doesn't pay us any attention anyway...
Did we tease him too much before the teacher arrived?
But Kou enjoyed it more or less as well.
That "more or less" might be the reason.
Kouta, thrust up deeper!
Is this all you can do? I'm disappointed!
Yeah, just like that!
Should I fondle your balls?
What's with that cry?
Kouta, your cock is just the right thickness and hardness.
You're touching some great point there! Very nice!
You feel good as well, right, Kouta?
Y... Yeah...
Then say it clear: "professor's pussy feels great."
Professor's pussy feels great!
You can't get my favor talking like that!
Stupid boys get this.
Your cock got even harder!
Too bad, but it feels good!
My pussy is dripping.
Huh? Kouta, you're too early!
You showered me quite well now.
Because you suddenly pulled out!
Whatever. I've stuff to do anyway.
I wonder why you came back to this middle-of-nowhere place.
This is my hometown after all.
Well...
And you make us study by ourselves, and leave everything to professor Encho.
Why are you coming to school at all?
It's obvious. To do stuff like this.
But this school is only me and the three girls.
Isn't this a bit...
It's fine, isn't it? They had their turns as well, didn't they.
Well...
They are all different types, so I bet you weren't bored.
I bet the first thing that caught your attention was Rui's boobs.
If you get titty fucked by those, I bet you'd cum buckets.
Pretty much.
Hitomi is a perfect loli. The forbidden fruit, huh?
You're happy you plucked her, right?
It's not like I did anything wrong.
How is Maiko? She acts really mature usually,
but she could be really active in bed.
She was the first one to ask me.
You're good at licking.
Have you licked their feet as well?
Yes.
I didn't think you were so well trained.
You have good childhood friends.
What do you want to do now? Put it in again?
Hey, don't touch there!
It's the payback for earlier!
I'm not good at anal!
Hey, Kouta, if you do that I'll...
This is what two-hole feels like?
I can't take this!
Don't play with my butt!
Your finger is tickling me inside...
Kouta, thrust in stronger, deeper!
Like that!
Anal feels good as well!
Do it more! Mess me up!
What do we do?
Want to join?
No... It'd feel so...
How about some funny entry line?
I can imagine you saying "mix us in as well!"
Kou is sometimes so indecisive,
he might be just unable to resist her...
Thank you for helping out with the class, professor Encho.
Well done!
I have a bit of office work to catch up with, so I won't be in in the afternoon!
Not like you ever are.
I wonder what work it is.
Just study by yourselves and clean up as always.
Then if you'll excuse me.
I'll have my lunch outside.
I can't even have my lunch peacefully now.
Such a nice weather.
Hitomi?
What are you doing?!
I caught the escaped criminal!
Damn! Why do you know this place?!
And how did you find me so quick?
I just followed your footprints.
I looked for my lost little pony with the best of my abilities.
Pony?
By the way, Kouta.
You did pervy stuff with the professor, right?
I just... well...
Why? Why won't you let us too?
Professor Hikaru came here and took you from us in a flash!
I want to do it a lot, but you're always running away!
It's not that I don't like you, just the timing and stuff...
I know you hate me now! Because of my childish flesh!
Flesh...?
Whatever.
If you do it with me too, I'll forgive you.
But...
I didn't ask for your opinion!
Do it well, okay?
I can feel your tongue.
The first time I licked you. I was surprised how big and hard your cock was.
Your tongue touched my clit!
I want you to lick more.
Kouta, you're getting better. I can feel your tongue inside... in...
There...
You're licking me so good I can feel I'm getting wet!
My pervy self is taking over!
You're licking my pussy so well... Playing with my clit...
I'm cumming! Cumming from your tongue!
Next, with your cock please!
Now is my chance!
Kouta!
Sorry Hitomi, I want to have my lunch!
No one's back yet.
Dammit... I just want to have my lunch in peace.
Oh, isn't this Haruko, who debuted as a teen star,
then entered the adult world without realizing? So lucky!
There's more! I guess professor Encho dropped these.
Here! Here too! Next here! So sexy!
Welcome, Kouta.
Damn, it was a trap!
You like pictures like that, don't you.
I understand why you're running away from us.
We might have overdid it a bit being with you in turns. I apologize.
But I get pissed from the thought of professor Hikaru taking you!
Because she's a mil-- I mean, an adult woman.
You wanted to try her so badly?
You should've just let her join us then.
I still value my life.
I know you're fine.
Look how healthy you are.
Good afternoon! It's been a while, Kouta's penis.
It's so cute now, but if I stroke it a bit...
I don't think this is right...
I love the touch of penis. It's a weird thing that's missing from a girl's body.
I'm weak at that one.
I did quite a bit of research. I want you to be happy.
Look, how lively it got!
It's tingling! You're enjoying it then!
Your penis is so beautiful, Kouta. I really think it's pretty!
Really?
Let me taste it.
You're so sensitive!
I love this taste!
Please enjoy my titty fuck.
Rui? Did she die?
My head hurts! Give me some medicine!
Hey, Rui...
What happened?
Kouta, let's cum more!
Sorry. You were sleeping so sweetly.
I don't really mind.
It's been a while, just the two of us.
Really?
You're avoiding us recently, aren't you?
That isn't it...
Hey... I want to...
Do it with you, Kou.
I should go home and study!
You always say you study in the night.
I should make dinner and warm the bath...
Your dad does all that, doesn't he?
He's treating you great, to compensate for marrying into a farmer family.
Rui might pop in on us.
She's still sleeping in the nurse's office.
Hitomi may come to the library by some mistake.
It's fine. She's allergic to old books.
Then what should I do?
I want you to mess me up again.
I can't wait any longer.
You're so turned on, but you still keep the order.
This is important as well.
Do it as you like, Kou.
Bite it... I want you to bite my nipple.
You're playing with my tits... So lewd!
I'm already dripping wet down there.
It's your fault, Kou, that I'm this wet.
You're touching me in pervy places!
I'll get even wetter down there!
This is too much...
I'll do it now.
It sounds so weird... So lewd.
Because your pussy is so lewd.
Don't say that...
Have I held back so much? I'm so wet...
It's because you don't masturbate.
I do! Since you wouldn't do it for me...
Then why are you so sloppy?
I...
You're so pervy, Ai.
I am, but it's natural!
Your cock got thicker!
It feels so warm!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I was surprised when she invited me to her place to continue,
"because her family isn't at home."
We can't do it calmly in school...
Turn me... inside out!
Mess me up!
So hot... Your cock's so hot!
Your pussy as well.
My pussy is going crazy...
Play with my tits... taste them!
They aren't as big as Rui's...
Don't hold back!
Your cock feels so good! So great!
Do it wilder in my pussy! Wilder!
It feels amazing!
Don't pull it out...
It's coming in so deep!
Twist my insides around more!
Your cock's so deep in!
You're getting bigger!
Getting even bigger!
So hot! My pussy's burning! It's going crazy!
Ai, can I cum in you? Can I?
You can, if you want! If you want!
Your hot juice is flowing in me...
Study by yourselves
Hitomi, didn't you hate the library?
It... smells.
Smells like what?
Among the smells I hate, there is a smell I love.
Huh?
Really. Something raw... Something alive.