Masterrr...
What if someone saw me like this?
M-master!? Where are you going?
Don't leave me! What if somebody else comes?
Where are you, master? You're right there, aren't you? You'd never just leave me like this, would you?
Master, I need to relieve myself...please, let me go to the bathroom! Or else I can't-
I'm so sorry, master. I couldn't hold it, and now I've soiled myself.
Please punish me for being so shameful.
The Secret Face of My Wife.
FAKKU! Presents
First Exposure
Ichika, I'm home!
Welcome home, Masato.
I've already got dinner and the bath ready, so what'll it be?
Guess I'll eat first then. Then we can take our time in the bath before bed.
Oh, honey. You just got home, and you're already...
Our marriage was the envy of the neighborhood.
We don't have any kids yet, but because of that, we still live like newlyweds after all these years.
That was great.
Glad you enjoyed it.
Man, I'm stuffed. Your cooking is something else, Ichika. I just can't stop myself.
Love is the best spice, they say.
So the reason the food's so good is 'cause you love me so much?
You got it.
Dear...
Ichika! What're you wearing!?
I was just thinking we need a change of pace. You don't like it?
No, I do.
Oh, Good! But don't force yourself though. You must be tired from work.
How could I say no to you?
Honey
There's no way I'd not be turned on by this.
Would you mind doing it with your mouth this time?
My mouth? You want oral sex?
Yeah. No good?
Don't be silly. It is a little embarrassing, but I'd gladly do anything for you.
She rarely does blowjobs, so why's she this good?
Ichika, I'm about to come.
Then please feel free to come in my mouth.
I-ichika!
You don't have to drink it, you know.
I'm sorry, I just got caught up in it... was I being too lewd?
Don't apologize. Come here, Ichika. This time, I'll do you.
Okay.
You're pretty wet, huh?
Y-yes.
Ichika, take your panties off and raise your hips.
Like this?
Your ass just a big and lovely as your boobs, Ichika.
Oh stop that, dear.
You've blossomed beautifully, but this just like a cute little flower bud.
Oh, don't play with my butt like that. That's dirty...
Dear, are you saying you want to do it in there?
You don't wanna try Anal?
"Anal"? Well...
You're don't like experimenting much, right?
Well maybe if I cleaned it beforehand...
It's okay, I don't wanna force you.
Your pussy feels so good I'd never get bored anyways.
You don't mind me being on top?
There's nothing to be ashamed of. Go on and move however you want.
Okay then.
Alright, now you start moving.
Okay.
You're hitting my womb!
It feels like it could push all the way in!
It can't stop myself from playing with my breasts too!
Ichika!?
Milk's coming out. It feels so good! I wanna keep squeezing them! Honey!
Ichika!
Honey! Honeyy!!
Give me your milk too dear! Maybe I'm already pregnant, but keep giving me your seed!
Ichika!
Honey, I'm cumming!
Ichika, if you're producing milk, then you think-
I might be. I'll have the doctor check.
But if you are pregnant, then we won't be able to make love for a while.
Yes.
You're right... For our child's sake.
I'll get going then. I'm sorry to leave you all alone on your day off.
Don't worry about it. It's been a while since you've seen your friend anyway.
Yes. It's been so long, and I just made plans without a second thought.
I'll be fine. Just take it easy, okay?
Okay then.
Well, my schedule's opened up.
You forget something?
This was in the mailbox.
Something wrong?
No, nothing...
It's for me. Wonder who it's from?
Dear, I better get going.
Okay, have fun.
The True Face of Ichika Itsuki
"The True Face of Ichika Istuki". Wonder what that means? Only one way to find out I guess.
Ichika!
Hey, Ichika, you see yesterday's show?
You bet! Mokutaku's the coolest, huh?
What, that geezer? Kamiari's obviously better!
Whaddya mean geezer? Kamiari's too childish.
That's what makes him so cute!
No way, Mokutaku's way better.
Huh? How?
Ichika, what do you think?
You two are such suckers for a cute face.
Well, yeah!
Come on!
Looks like your boobs got bigger again!
They did not!
Your butt's shaping up nice too!
Oh, come on! Knock it off!
Alright, Alright!
It looks a bit small to me, though.
Nah, it's just perfect.
Stop it, I'm serious!
C'mon, lighten up!
Huh? I can see something shiny over there.
Where...am I?
What the!? What's going on!?
How'd I end up like this?
Oh no...Who's there!?
Yamazaki?
Help me, please! I can't move.
W-what're you doing?
Smells nice...
Stop it, Yamazaki! You're creeping me out!
I've only begun savoring you, Ichika.
Stop! Quit groping them!
So these are Ichika's tits. Soft as marshmallows.
Please, stop it! Or else I'll tell the teacher-
Shut up! Quit fighting, damnit! Just shut up and listen to me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, so stop punching me!
Shoulda just listened at the beginning.
If you're a good girl, I'll make you my bride!
No! S-Stop it!
Awesome! Nothing compares to bare tits!
Even better fap material than those videos of you in your swimsuit!
Oh, your nipples are getting hard! You're turned on, aren't you?
T-that's not...true...
Don't be shy. 'Cause we're gonna become husband and wife now!
Time for the main dish!
No way! You're not going to fuck me, are you!? Anything but that! Please, have mercy!
Didn't I say to shut your mouth!? Keep pissing me off, and I'll chop your clit off!
Aw man, you pissed yourself? And you call yourself the council president?
Don't cry, Ichika. I won't scorn you over such a trivial thing.
Noo! Don't look!
Ichika's virgin pussy! Here I come, Ichika!
Please, anything but that... Don't take my virginity!
I'm not taking anything; you’re giving your virginity to me, Ichika! I know how you feel about me.
Owwww!! Stop it!
You're so warm, Ichika!
It hurrrtss! Owww!! Take it out!
I know, I know. You want me to go in and out right?
It hurts! You're messing me up!
Ichika! Ichika! You feel so good! I'm gonna blow!
"Blow"!? You don't mean-
We're married, so I'll make sure to cum inside you!
No, don't! You'll make me pregnant if you do that! Please don't!
Here it comes, Ichika!
You're horrible... you actually came inside me.
What's all the commotion? Someone in here?
Somebody's coming!
Help me!
Y-you idiot!
Hm, what's this?
Sasaki!
Well if it ain't Yamazaki the nerd. What'cha up to in a place like this?
Holy shit! 'That Itsuki, the council president?
Did you do this?
I-it's not my fault. Ichika brought me here.
He's lying! I didn't do anything like that.
She just wouldn't take no for an answe-
Can it, fatass! Well, guess that's not a problem for ya now.
Thank you. Um, would you mind untying me please?
Thank you so much.
Whaddya mean 'thank you'? Oh, I get it. You wanna say thanks by having sex with me, right?
Have sex with-
Sasaki, you wouldn't!
What the hell are you doing?
You'd have to be fuckin' impotent to pass up a chance like this.
No way... Please, stop.
The hell's that stench? Piss?
Man, it's all dirty now.
Having Yamazaki's jizz in there'd just ruin it.
Stop it, Sasaki! Please don't make me suffer any more!
Just relax. I'll make you feel real good.
Your pussy's clean now. Doesn’t it feel like you're losing your virginity all over again?
Heh, pretty soft.
Alright, let's do this!
Damn, this is awesome!
It's so tight!
Here it comes! I'll rinse out Yamazaki's leftovers for ya!
There!
Wh... why...
It'd be such a waste to leave a gem like her unpolished.
Hm? You're not gonna change, Ichika?
Sorry, it looks like "that" just started.
I'll go rest in the Nurse's room. You two go on ahead, okay?
Okay, but Ichika, isn't your period off-schedule?
It's just been a bit irregular lately.
Hmm, it's probably just due to stress from Student Council work. You shouldn't overwork yourself.
Thanks.
Stayed behind, just like we agreed. If everyone knew Sasaki raped you, you'd have to leave the school.
It's no picnic having to keep our meetings a secret from him either.
U-um, my period's just started, so...
Let's see...It sure has.
See, I'm not lying, so today could we-
Ah, no choice then. Guess we'll use the back door today.
Good timing. I've always wanted to try anal sex.
You really want to do it with my butt?
You bet.
No, I don't want to!
Shut up and do as you're told! C'mon, hands against the lockers!
Let's just stop, okay? It's dirty there.
Don't sweat it. Here I go!
It... hurts...
It's in! It actually went in!
N-No!
My butt's is gonna be turned inside out!
Not "butt"! Call it your ass-pussy, damnit! When my dick's inside, it's your ass-pussy!
My ass-pussy! You're gonna tear my ass-pussy! It's gonna bleed! Don't be so rough!
No can do! It's your fault! Your ass-pussy feels too good.
Ohh, my stomach! I was just in the cold pool, so please let me go to the bathroom!
Once I'm satisfied, you can go wherever the hell you please!
No! I can't hold it!
I'm cumming!
Now can I go to the bathroom?
Not yet. Still a bit left to release.
What the!? More hot stuff is-
Don't tell me...you're peeing?
You got it, Ichika.
Stop it! Don't pee inside me!
Okay, all done.
No! If you pull it out now, I'll-
Haha! Pissing from your ass? That's a first for me!
No...
No more! I can't hold it!
Where the heck is Ichika?
We all decided to go to Karaoke after the graduation ceremony too...
That little shit Yamazaki took her anal virginity too. God damnit.
No need to hold back, since we'll all be going our separate ways after graduating.
That's right.
Well, Ichika? Feel good? You fuckin' slut.
No... I'm just being forced by you all to have sex and do dirty things so...
So you're getting turned on, ya damn slut!
You're wrong! I'm not turned on...
Okay then. If you don't cum after all of us do, then we'll admit you're not a perv.
You mean it?
It's pretty much impossible, but sure.
If I can just make everyone cum...
This chick... she just started stroking me on her own!
Damn, she's good with her tongue!
I'm gonna train you real good.
Everybody, hurry up and come!
It's scraping inside my ass pussy... and rubbing against the one in my pussy. It feels so good!
Sorry, I'm gonna-
From your handjob!
Ahh, sperm! Just the smell gets me so wet!
Sasaki, me too!
More hot stuffs pouring into my ass-pussy!
Oh no! If you shoot your hot stuff into me, I'm gonna-Cumming!
Well there you have it! You really are a slut!
A-a slut... I'm a slut?
Yep! You're a first-class slut!
I'm... a slut! A pervert! So it's okay to get turned on from my pussy fucked?
Even if I love the taste of dicks, or if I come from my ass, it's okay 'cause I'm a slut, right?
Of course! Alright Ichika, I'm gonna cum in your slutty pussy!
Oh no! I'm cumming again! Cumming in my slutty pussy's gonna make me cum too!
I'm cumming!! I'm cumming!!!
Even if I love the taste of dicks, or if I come from my ass, it's okay 'cause I'm a slut, right?
Ichika? I don't believe it...
My wife... my wife, making faces like that?