Are you focusing on your studies?
Of course!
This says otherwise.
No...!
Do you like a maid's footjob?
I'm beautiful and have the body of a goddess.
If you beg me to teach you manners, I might let you put it in.
Sex in the bath!
Thank you, god!
I don't understand you.
Don't you know my body well enough now?
How can this get you excited?
Because you're wearing it!
He sure sucks washing me.
You haven't answered me yet.
Not there!
Hey! Were you gonna ask me something or what?
I love you, Kiriha.
I want to stay with you.
This is cowardly!
No...
You're...
Stop...
Say it!
This is my order for you.
No, you jerk.
I don't want to get carried away.
I will! just stop!
Let's hear it.
I love you.
Tell it to my face.
I won't let you see me when I confess.
I love you too, Eishun.
Seriously?
Did you want me to dump you?
Please don't.
What a brute, raping me just when I confessed.
Before you do it, apologize you were born and swear to be my slave.
Sorry I was born.
Where's the second half?
I'll be with you forever now.
I'm gonna come!
He proposed to me when he fucked me...
My womb is accepting his proposal...
I love you, Kiriha.
Wait... My head...
He's touching something he hasn't touched yet!
Please, let me rest...
I can't stop yet.
I'll make you come, Kiriha.
Please...
You're my personal maid.
I'll leave my mark on your body!
No! No!
I'm gonna come!
It's close!
Together!
I'm coming!
More!
Those were several orgasms...
Want to get out?
We're not done here.
I still have more, you know?
The way you washed me was weak.
I won't let my master be weak.
I love you, Eishun.
I won't leave you alone.
Sex and spanking!
The collar is ruining my cute face.
Your ass is sex.
You're seeing my dirty cunt.
I love cock-teasing him.
You're begging for it, you dirty maid!
Don't be happy about it!
This is punishment!
I'm sorry!
Ouch!
Think about your misdeeds!
Discipline your maid for liking her punishment!
No!
Don't finger it!
I wonder if the spanking really was enough.
You bitch maid.
He's going to know everything about my ass.
Master!
Punishment for the dirty maid!
Master! You're sticking it into my ass!
Don't move!
Master!
What is this?
This is... No...
Deep...
No...
Stop...
It feels good!
Good!
I'm coming!
It's inside me!
I can feel it going inside me.
You're at your cutest now!
He sure has some nerve, being so rough.
How long are you going to look.
Until you want this.
More! In!
Do you want to be raped?
Punish my cunt! Please!
I love your cock!
You're so wet!
Don't suck.
No!
Master!
Don't hide!
No!
Don't!
More! Punish me!
Master!
I love you!
Don't tease my cunt!
I'm going to come!
I'm gonna come again!
You brute, Master...
But even so, I love you.
In! Harder!
No! Not like that!
I'll come inside, Kiriha.
Put a baby in me!
Get me pregnant!
Kiriha!
I'm coming!
I love being a maid.
Punish me more...
...Master.
Eishun!
I'm back from buying girly games!
Hi, Mom!
Mornings are nice, but get dressed.
You'll catch a cold.
You're a loud one.
Oh, Kiriha.
Good morning, Miss.
Teach that idiot some manners, Kiriha.
Leave it to me.
I'll discipline him.
What now?
Isn't it nice that we have her approval?
I love you, Eishun.
She loves me too!
Now she'll stop with the bipolar shit!
Time for punishment!
What?
We could impound all you own...
Well, I'll let you choose.
I'm compassion incarnate.
Guess she's just a bit rebellious.
All right, Master.
Thanks, Shun.
The first one who gives up during sex loses.
I hate losing.
I know that, Master.