Just a bit more...
Amazing...
It's reaching...
So deep...
What am I doing?
I shouldn't be doing this...
Just because I'm older...
But just now... just now...
I'm... coming...
I'm coming!
Just me...
Huh? Ms Kirisaki?
Sorry, I was leaving already, but I forgot something...
It won't take long, and I'll lock the doors.
Ah, sure. Thank you.
Then, I'll leave that to you.
That was unexpected!
My heart's racing.
It's amazing, right? I can't calm down.
He might come back anytime, so we should hurry.
Amazing...
You're touching me where it feels the best...
You... got better, didn't you?
I'm coming...
It's okay... come...
It's okay, I'm coming too...
This was amazing.
You're still seem to have some left...
Let's... do it again.
FAKKU! Presents
Ms Rie's private class - A cutely perverse lady
But to become a teacher... It must be tough!
Well...
They listen to what I say and stuff...
Then you're just one step ahead.
But you have a boyfriend I guess.
Hit the nail on the head, did I?
But I hope it's not someone you met online.
What are you saying, how would I...
A boyfriend...
You don't need to hide it! Or is it something too dirty?
You didn't!
Don't stay weird stuff!
But dirty, that I wouldn't say.
Oh, so you do have someone!
What kind of a guy?
What does he teach?
Umm, well.
He's not teaching.
Or is he one of your students?
You're kidding me, right? Isn't that a crime?
Crime?!
Then what, the big sis is giving the boy some lessons?
Ayaka... You just got married, but you're still saying weird stuff.
Let me have my fun.
But it sounds so fun... just don't change him for your tastes.
Don't say so stupid things! So embarrassing... That...
"That's nice," your face just said.
He must be so cute...
What are you saying?
He is, by the way.
Here we go.
But remember to keep stuff separate!
You're the older, so be responsible!
Shut up, I know that!
Sure, just don't get burnt.
Or rather, don't burn him.
You don't have to tell me, I know!
I know! I'm prepared!
That's why I promised him that we should go on together!
He's doing his best too, right?
Student counseling room
I was so surprised! I told them not to give me any work because I'm busy...
Sorry, they were about to pass me some work, so I escaped.
I mustn't! I got all soft when I looked at his face.
Now, do you know why I called you?
By the look on your face, you don't.
This is bad... He looks close to crying...
He's too cute, what should I do?
10:05am. 11:17am. 1:42pm. 2:32pm. What were you doing?
I'm at a loss... what should I do?
If I look at his face again, this could get bad!
You were sleeping, right?
We promised we'd both work hard for our sake, didn't we?
I was happy...
Other teachers told me, that recently your grades are getting worse.
You shouldn't be like this!
If it goes on like this, you really...
So, special counsel:
you should study hard.
Huh? You'll show in the next exam?
Really?
Then prove it with the results.
But I want you to show it with your attitude as well.
I wouldn't want my... boyfriend to sleep in class, you know.
Show it with your attitude right now as well.
Pass.
Expecting good results from you.
It's getting big, right?
Did you hold back?
Don't look like you'd cry any second.
It makes me want you.
It's already coming out.
Please make your teacher feel good as well.
Stop...
Don't, stop! Stop!
I... I...
This was better than anytime before.
You're getting better.
You were much... harsher.
And this one too, it's only touching places where I like it.
You're turning into an adult like this.
Well, I turned you into an adult, right?
You're too good at flattery!
I'm all ready...
My boobs too...
Go on...
If you suck that hard...
Come a bit forward.
It's all jiggly.
Wait, i'll let you go wild now.
Man, I came from just this...
Let's feel great...
It's hitting inside... so deep inside...
My... My pussy is getting full...
And you're groping my boobs so much...
Don't! If you lick my nipples...
This... pose feels different...
It's much better than usual!
If you go on... I'll come so hard...
You're hitting all the good places up to my womb...
I'd scream out if we didn't kiss.
I'm about... about to come.
I... Let's go together... together!
Stop... Stop... I'm still coming, and so is the juice...
Don't...
I can't...
I shouldn't be doing this so much...
More than this wouldn't be good for him either...
But remember to keep stuff separate!
You should make everything clear while you can!
It'll be too late if something happened!
I know... I know, but...
Huh? Here already?
We can't... walk together like other couples.
Yeah, we part ways here are student and teacher...
We can't go any further. We can't!
And here you were saying you're not interested in younger guys, see how deep you're in already!
I can't! I can't! I can't go any further!
Umm... Would you like to come to my place?
I want to be more with you...
I feel so refreshed!
Ah, you're doing your homework?
Nice, nice!
Is there anything you don't get?
Let's see, this one...
Your homework...
Don't...
Wait...
It's okay... let it out...
So much... so much is coming still.
So good...
Come a lot!
I can't stop!
Sometimes you lose sight of your surroundings.
Don't rush headlong into something weird.
I can't stop... I can't leave him... I don't want to leave him...
I love you! I love you!
Only you...
Who cares about anything else...
More, more, more!
To the deep... you're coming to the deepest parts!
It's... It's too much...
It's way too much, I can't...
More, wilder, wilder!
I... I love him so much... My whole body's loving him...
I... I...
Love... me... love me deep...
It feels amazing!
Just a bit more!
I ... came so well.
I shouldn't... fall asleep...
I fell asleep? I see... He stays over...
This is the first time we slept beside each other.
So cute... you looked so manly before...
But you're not there yet.
That boy has many more years ahead than you! Do it properly!
That... I know that.
But... I can't leave him.
I love him so much!
Also, he's so far in age from you, he'll get bored with you right away!
You're an old lady!
From Maho
Maho. His little sister?
Taku, don't be an ass!
Whose place are you crashing at?
Call me! Stupid! I'm looking for you!
I won't forgive you if it's
that woman's place!
.
"That woman?"
Is that... me?