She confessed to me before the start of
next year's exams, and I accepted.
She calls me Senpai, yet we're in the same grade.
However, I was bored of my mundane, everyday life.
U-Um.
Tomorrow, we're starting morning lessons again for our club, right?
Yeah.
Um, Senpai. I don't mind what happened.
A molester.
Sorry.
I just can't do it right.
Don't mind it.
It's okay.
Senpai.
I love you.
Misaki-sensei.
Senpai, your thing is touching me.
Secret
You always take the crowded route to school, don't you?
Misaki-sensei.
I leave this early when I have lessons in the morning.
Um.
You didn't take your car. That's unusual.
Yeah, it's in the shop for a little while. They're changing the clutch and some other parts.
Still, you're here pretty early.
I wanted to ride the train with you.
You're not with your girlfriend today?
Well, no.
We just happened to meet up yesterday.
It's not like we're always together.
I see.
You were watching me yesterday, weren't you?
So? What did you think of me?
You got turned on, didn't you?
Um, Misaki-sensei?
Stay quiet.
It's just like yesterday.
A molester?
Misaki-sensei.
Is she getting excited?
But how?
She's being felt up by some stranger.
Why...
didn't you resist?
You're holding my hand really tight. It hurts, you know.
That was just strange!
You're so kind.
It was strange.
Hey, come with me.
Um, w-what is it?
Take responsibility, my dear, gentle Takashi-kun.
Sensei. I really don't think we should do it in a place like this.
It's fine. Don't worry.
No other teachers besides me come here, and no students use the library this early.
Hey, touch me...
down here.
Can you tell...
how I'm feeling?
Sensei.
Looks like you can't hold out any longer down here.
S-Sensei!
Hold out...
for a little while, okay?
Sensei, I can't.
I'm going to cum.
It's coming out!
Senpai's pretty late.
Your dick is so wonderful.
Let's enjoy this more.
Make me cum this time.
Kiss me.
Yes.
That's the spot.
Lick me.
Yes.
You're so good.
Hey, your finger. Use your finger.
It feels so good.
Sensei.
I can't wait any longer.
You can put it in.
There's no need to rush.
Okay.
So good.
I want to feel more of you.
Sensei.
This is amazing.
Your pussy feels so incredible.
Yes!
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
No, stop.
My breasts are extremely sensitive.
Sensei.
I want to do it again.
Hey.
This time, come at me from behind.
Push yourself inside me as hard as you want.
I feel you...
so deep inside me.
I feel so good.
I'm going to cum again.
I'm going to cum!
Sensei.
Sensei!
I wonder what happened to Senpai.
Does he hate me now?
That felt great.
Sensei.
Are you sure...
we didn't need to use any condoms?
That's a bit of a mood killer.
Did your head finally cool off?
Huh?
No, that's not it.
It'll be fine.
What's the matter?
Your stuff is coming out.
Well, you did give me a lot.
I'll get a tissue.
Jeez, you're so crude.
Let me feel you for a little while longer.
But classes are going to start.
Senpai, about our lesson this morning...
Yeah. Sorry, I was busy.
Um, my friend told me about this great café.
I'd like to drop by on the way home.
Sorry, but I'm not feeling too well.
W-Will you be at...
Will you be at tomorrow's morning lesson?
I don't know.
Senpai...
The door is closing.
Please be careful.
What's the matter with Sensei?
She's making me touch her in a place like this?
What if someone thinks I'm a molester?
Do it slowly.
Yes.
Slowly lick me all over and work your way in.
Do it gently.
You touched me there while on the train.
I lose control of myself when I'm touched like that on the train.
Couldn't you see...
how turned on I was?
Hey.
You got off, just like me.
You got so turned on when you were groping me.
Senpai.
I guess he couldn't make today's morning lesson either.
Sensei, I can't hold back any longer.
Not yet.
You have to bear it.
The longer you hold it, the better it will feel.
Just like a molester would do.
Yes, touch me gently.
Women are sensitive all over their bodies.
He shouldn't do that in a place like this,
not somewhere he can get caught so easily.
Other men are going to see.
There might be some perverted men looking at you.
He sounds like an adult.
It feels sort of... different today.
I'm so sensitive.
Sensei.
You're so hot down here today.
What's his point? I can't do anything about it.
You're so perverted today, Sensei.
Hey, hurry up.
Hurry up and push it inside me. Please.
Sensei, I still haven't...
Let's go over there.
Huh?
We can't do it here!
Someone might hear us.
Stop.
It feels so good.
Senpai, it's Tomomi.
Ever since then, we've been kind of drifting apart, and it's made me feel lonely.
And I love you so much too.
Senpai, you're different from our classmates.
You're mature and composed.
I still haven't called you by your first name, not once.
And also, you're very distant from me, like you're floating above the clouds.
So...
when that didn't go well,
It felt like the distance between us shrunk.
I know it bothers you it didn't go well,
and I know I shouldn't think this way,
but that just makes you all the cuter.
I love you so much more now than when I first confessed to you.
Okay, good night.
Oh, today's Saturday.
I guess he doesn't have morning lessons today.
There are so many molesters on this train. I'm sick of them.
He's being rough,
but he's very good.
It feels great.
I can't hold on.
So you'd get off on anyone's finger.
Takashi-kun?
Please.
I can't wait any longer.
Keep going and make me cum.
Sensei, you're such a whore.
Um, Senpai.
Lately we haven't been talking much, not even during club.
Um, I left a message on your answering machine,
but I didn't get a call back.
Um.
Senpai.
You shouldn't make a girl cry.
Sensei.
Your car.
I don't have to ride that crowded train anymore.
See you.
What's the matter?
We're heading home, right?
Let's go.
I was sort of worried...
about my grades.
I felt a little bit lonely.
And considering what happened the other day...
Um, if you get that close to me...
Senpai?
Um, I...
Be quiet.
Here? On the train?
Tomomi, it'll be fine.
You don't like it?
It's embarrassing.
Someone will see.
It's okay.
You're cute, Tomomi.
Senpai, I'm starting to feel strange.
Let's get off at the next stop.
The roof?
I want to hurry and be alone with you.
Senpai, we're doing it here of all places?
No one will come here.
But, Senpai...
Here, feel it.
I can't hold back any longer.
Senpai, this place...
Ah, no! I'm dirty down there!
No, it's very pretty, Tomomi.
Senpai, I can't stay standing.
I'll go slow, okay?
Just bear it for a little while.
Tomomi, take a look.
I'm inside you.
You're inside me.
I'll go a bit deeper.
It hurts, Senpai.
I love you, Tomomi.
Senpai, it hurts!
Did you feel good?
Stop! This is embarrassing!
You're so cute, Tomomi.
Senpai.
Do you feel good?
I do.
Tomomi, your pussy feels incredible.
Senpai, I... feel strange.
I'm not home right now.
Say something after the beep.
U-Um, it's Tomomi.
Um. Good evening, Senpai.
Can we meet up again and...
Hello?
Ah, Senpai!