No!
Oh no!
What's going on?
Gosh!
Oh, gosh!
General Hospital
I was really surprised to see you admitted to the hospital I work at.
S-Sorry.
But that aside, Tomohisa-kun, you're quite the scatterbrain.
Oh, sorr-
Wait, a scatterbrain?
I never would have expected this to happen to me.
Tomohisa-kun.
You haven't taken a bath yet, right?
Do you want me to wipe down your body?
You don't look too happy about this.
Well, um, I just figured we were going to have sex again or something.
My, how rude.
If that's how you're going to be,
then maybe I should just leave.
Er... um... I'm sorry, Senpai.
I was just kidding! Please do it with me!
Gosh.
I guess it can't be helped.
Okay then, I'll do this for you.
~ The Angels' Private Lessons ~
Does this feel okay? It's not too hot, right?
Yes, the temperature's just fine.
Y-You don't have to wipe down my front.
I can take care of that myself.
It's all right. I'm already cleaning you anyway.
Plus, you hit your shoulder too, right?
S-Senpai...
You smell really nice.
Oh?
Huh?
Tomohisa-kun, you've gotten so big just from me drying off your body.
Th-This is because, um...
You haven't done it since you've been admitted in the hospital, right?
You must be so backed up.
I'll clean this place too, okay?
But you don't like girls who want to do these kinds of dirty things, right?
Th-That's not true.
Tomohisa-kun, it's getting so stiff.
It popped out of your boxers.
I'll lick it for you.
U-Um, you need to wipe it off with a towel.
And I haven't even taken a bath.
It's okay.
Your scent drives me crazy.
It's so thick that it's sticking together.
S-Sorry.
But cumming once is hardly enough for you, right?
S-Senpai.
Don't!
Wait.
Wait a second!
H-His tongue is inside me.
Wow, that feels so good.
I can feel him.
I'm going...
to cum.
No, not yet.
Hold out a bit longer.
Look. Your semen, our love juices, and my drool are all mixing together.
See how soaked we're getting?
Tomohisa-kun, do you want to stick your dick in my pussy?
Y...
Yes.
I want to stick it in.
You being so honest makes me a little happy.
See how soaked your dick is? I bet it'll slide all the way in.
S-Senpai!
It's so warm inside of you.
You're injured, so don't move.
Wow, it's so hard.
It's hitting the deepest part of my pussy.
Tomohisa-kun, don't be so rough or else I'll start moaning loudly.
Sorry, but it feels so good I can't stop myself.
Senpai.
Your pussy is squeezing down so hard on me.
I can feel your hard dick so deep inside me.
I'm...
about to come.
Go ahead. Come!
Inside... You can come inside.
Together... Come with me!
Let's come together!
Tomohisa-kun.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Did something happen?
I heard someone shouting over here.
Well, um, I dozed off and had a really strange dream.
I'm glad to see that you're fine, but this is a hospital, so don't do it too much, okay?
Ah, okay.
I'll be sure to remember that.
She noticed, didn't she?
Senpai, that's not a good idea.
Hey,
let's do it again.
~ The Angels' Private Lessons ~
What? A hot spring?
Yeah. I found this nice resort nearby.
I figured we could stop by on a weekend.
So... it'd just be the two of us?
Of course.
We'd be in such a rush if we went there and back in a single day,
so I think we should just stay overnight.
Endo-kun.
You don't want to go?
Oh, I don't mind.
Then it's settled!
I can't wait!
Good thing it's not crowded.
Yeah, I guess it's one of those undiscovered treasures.
These chips are good.
Try some, Endo-kun.
Ah, thanks.
So what do you think? Good, right?
Yeah, they are.
I know, right? I wonder why I've never bought these before.
Mikura-san really is cute.
What's wrong? Why are you staring at me?
Did you notice by any chance?
I haven't been wearing any underwear since this morning.
H-Hey!
That's a bad idea!
Someone's going to notice if you yell.
Doing this sort of thing excites me.
Look. You've gotten so big.
It's so hot and hard.
I'm sort of starting to feel...
Say, you wanna do it here?
Endo-kun, you're so big.
It's about to burst out of your pants.
Erm, well.
It must feel cramped inside your pants.
Endo-kun, you naughty boy!
C-Come on.
Should I take it out and lick it?
Endo-kun, it's so incredible.
M-Mikura-san.
Mikura-san.
Your dick is twitching.
You can come in my mouth if you want.
Thank you for riding Senouiki, your go-to railway company for commuting.
I will now be checking your tickets.
Please have them out and ready.
M-Mikura-san!
Sir, may I see your tickets?
Y-Yes, of course.
Okay, two people.
Is she all right?
Ah, yes, she's fine.
Okay. Well, if you happen to need anything, please tell me.
Th-Thank you very much.
Ah, that's...
Wh... uh, I mean, I'm so...
I-I'm fine.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I guess she didn't notice.
Of course she did. Anyone would have.
I see.
Well, who cares?
This little guy is full of life.
I think those are two different matters.
We're about to reach our station.
Let's finish this later.
Yeah, I guess.
Lu Jiang Inn
Wow, so pretty!
Amazing. This sunset looks like it came straight out of a movie.
Endo-kun, come take a look.
Endo-kun?
Well, this is because...
Is it because...
of this?
I'm so sorry. We stopped right in the middle of things earlier, didn't we?
Then...
for now,
let's go soak in the hot spring.
Y-Yeah.
I guess no one told us it wasn't a co-ed hot spring.
Endo-kun, come take a bath with me.
Come on, show me your dick. I'll clean it for you, okay?
Do you want to come here?
Or in here?
Or maybe...
in here?
E-Enough of this!
I'm so damn horny!
Ah, I'm so full.
That was some great food, huh?
Yeah, it was.
Um.
So don't you think this sort of feels like a honeymoon?
R-Really?
My heart's starting to beat a little bit faster.
M-Mikura-san, I'm guessing you're not wearing any underwear, right?
Wh-Why do you ask?
Well, um...
D-Do you want to check?
M-Mikura-san.
Endo-kun, come check over here.
Well, it's bright inside the room.
Mikura-san.
You can check now.
Be gentle.
Endo-kun,
are you done checking?
Mikura-san.
I-I can't...
Okay then. Let's do it.
Endo-kun, stick your dick inside.
You feel so hot, Endo-kun.
I can't hold back anymore either.
Put it in.
Your dick's so hard and stiff.
Mikura-san, you're getting so wet.
Endo-kun, I'm getting so turned on!
N-No!
I'm going to come! I'm about to come!
The tips of my nipples are so hot!
They're getting erect!
Ah, no!
I'm going to come now!
Endo-kun, did that help clear your head?
Y-Yeah.
But I wonder why this little fellow is still up and kicking.
Well, this is because, um...
We're all sticky. Now let's go do it in the open air bath.
Preliminary
Announcement!
Stringendo: The Angels' Private Lessons.
Act 10 of this unforgettable series will come out in the summer of 2011!
~ The Angels' Private Lessons ~
Next time, we'll continue on with our sex-filled trip as well as Shibiya-san's side story!