Training... session?
I'll probably be away for three months starting next week.
I see.
It'll be lonely around here.
Once I come back from my training session,
I'm thinking
of telling the principal about us.
And after I do,
you'll be able to proudly wear your ring.
Eiji-san.
M-Miyuki-san.
N-No.
You can't.
Y...
You can't do this.
We can't go anything further...
than this!
I'm sorry.
I'm happy...
but I want to follow the steps and do this after we're married.
E-Excuse me.
I just got lost in the moment.
Eiji-san, are you mad by any chance?
O-Of course not. This is very much like you.
I'm falling even more in love with you.
Thank you, Eiji-san.
Female
Teachers
Obscene and Shameful Classrooms
Episode 1: I've Been Sullied.
Wow.
It's in my ass.
What?
It's scraping against me.
C-Carrot.
What?
Carrot!
T...
The carrot's...
I'm going cra...
Wow. Wow.
T-The carrot's...
Carrot this, carrot that. You're so noisy.
One's not enough for you?
H...
Hey, wait!
It's scraping against me!
I'm going to cum. It's rubbing against me!
Stop.
Spare me!
That was mean of you to put in two at onc...
Their roughness is rubbing my insides.
Don't turn while rubbing it!
My ass is widening.
W...
What in the world are Misawa-kun and Hasekura-sensei doing?
Yes.
It's big.
I-I want it.
It's so big.
Mi...
Misawa-kun's dick.
That's her...
Go deeper... deeper!
Go as deep as you can!
It's digging into my anus.
Your hard dick is stuck inside me.
It's hard, incredibly hard.
It's hollowing out my ass.
It's hot, so hot.
I'm getting so hot.
Your thing is rubbing against me!
So much hot stuff is flowing out.
St... No!
No!
D-Don't!
Don't touch my breasts!
They're so unbelievably hot.
I wonder what's packed inside these things.
That'd be...
milk!
There's so much milk packed inside!
N-No.
My breasts feel good.
I can feel it.
Oh no.
If you go so deep inside of me...
You're doing my breasts too.
Yes!
It's so good!
No!
I'm cumming.
Misawa-kun.
Why did he do something like that to Hasekura-sensei?
But Hasekura-sensei...
seemed to be enjoying it.
So good!
What does this mean?
Miyuki-sensei.
Y-Yes?
Sorry, but could you lend your ruler?
Mine's missing.
Yes, that's fine.
Meet at
our usual spot after school.
Is something wrong?
N-No, nothing in particular.
Thank you very much.
I'll try discussing Misawa-kun's matter with Eiji-san.
Did you relay the message like I ordered you to, Sensei?
Yes.
I see.
As a reward, I'll cum a lot inside your throat.
Later. I'm off to have my fun.
Did you wait long?
Huh?
M-Misawa-kun.
Why are you here?
Well, that's because I'm the one who called you here.
Huh?
Or were you waiting for Sanada-sensei to come here?
W-Why do you know that?
Now then,
all I want to do is have a nice and private chat with you.
W-Wait a minute.
Why here of all places?
What in the world do you want to talk about?
What, you ask?
Well,
you don't have to be so afraid.
N...
No!
N-No!
Stop!
Stop! Please!
You've got some sexy underwear on.
No!
D...
Don't touch me there!
No!
Don't!
Let me go! You really can't do this!
No!
You pretend to hate it so much,
but you're getting off, aren't you?
No!
That's a lie, a total lie.
That can't be what's happening.
P-Please.
Take your hand away.
Just stop already!
No!
Stop.
You're soaking wet.
No!
Don't!
Stop!
I'll put it in soon.
You want it, don't you?
No, stop. No!
Save me!
Somebody save me!
Don't! No!
No!
Don't!
Come on, open it up wider.
All right, I'm going to move.
No! It hurts. It hurts!
Don't move!
Ouch!
It hu... it hurts! Take it out!
You're squeezing down so hard. It's tight.
P-Please.
S... S... Stop!
No!
Save me, Eiji-san.
It hurts. It hurts!
Please!
Save me!
Your pussy's started to get foaming wet.
You're getting off from being raped by your own student, aren't you?!
No, I'm not!
I'm not!
I'll keep going and fill you to the brim with semen.
Don't! You definitely, definitely can't do that!
No!
No, no, no, no! Please stop!
Anything but that!
Spare me from that! I'm begging you!
No, no! Not inside! Take it out!
Not inside! It hurts!
It hurts! Don't cum!
It's coming into me.
It's so deep inside.
Sanada-sensei.
Makiyama-sensei?
How about we go get something to eat?
Sorry, I'm a little busy today.
I heard that you were leaving for training.
That made me feel lonely, so I wanted to be with you.
S-Sorry.
Makiyama-sensei.
Y-Yes?
Do you know where Toudou-sensei went?
Who knows?
Maybe she already went home.
I suppose... that's the case.
Bye.
Sanada-sensei.
Eiji-san.
His picture's...
been ruined.
Hey, doesn't Miyuki-sensei seem weird today?
She's so gloomy.
Yeah.
I wonder if something happened.
No!
Miyuki!
Miyuki, why have you been spacing out?
M-Makoto.
The students are worried about you,
saying that you didn't seem very cheerful.
S-Sorry, but I... uh... don't feel very well.
If you're feeling that bad,
maybe you should take the rest of the day off?
It's all right.
H-Hey, Makoto.
I want to talk about Misawa-kun, a student in my class.
Did Misawa do something?
Sorry. On second thought, it's nothing.
Miyuki...
But to think Makoto-sensei herself would call me out to here of all places...
Misawa.
Don't tell me you went so far as to lay a hand on Miyuki.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Don't do anything else to Miyuki.
You already have enough, don't you?
Don't get the wrong idea.
Do you think you're in a position to order me around?
P-Please.
Let Miyuki off as a favor to me.
And in exchange,
I'll do anything you want.
Oh? Anything?
Y-You can have your way with me.
W-What?
Are you telling me to change into this?
That was a pretty good guess considering you're a sports-crazed physical education teacher.
Come on. Get to it.
Fine.
It looks great on you.
A-Are you going to make do some
perverted stuff with these kinds of clothes on?
You like it, no?
You really got off on it last time.
I-I didn't...
get off on... anything.
Stop complaining and come lick it.
I just need to lick it, right?
You know that's not how to do it.
You have to go at least this far.
This is wet enough.
Next, use your huge breasts to stroke it.
Ah, okay.
I...
Is this okay?
Put the tip in your mouth.
Like this?
I bet you're getting off while you're sucking it.
That's not... true.
So? Do you feel refreshed?
Turn your ass this way.
Quite a masochist sow.
A fitting sight.
I-I'm not a masochist sow!
You're soaking wet.
You sow, you want my cock, don't you?
You won't get anything unless you say you want it.
Yes, I want it.
Excuse me? I can't hear you.
I want it!
I want your cock!
Please put it inside this sow's dirty pussy.
Let's have our guest watch as well.
Mi...
Miyuki!
Don't do that so suddenly!
Miyuki will see!
It's hot, so hot!
Ah, no!
No, it's going so deep. It's not what it looks like, Miyuki!
This is... not what it looks like!
Miyuki-sensei's found out that you're one hell of a masochist sow.
This is embarrassing!
Hey, you sow, make sure she can get a good look!
So hot!
If you stir me up that much, my breasts... they'll...
Your dick is filling me up!
Ah, it's coming out! It's coming out!
You're really tightening up.
What a dirty sow.
Don't say that.
I feel... all tingly.
Be glad. I'm going to cum a lot inside you today as well, you sow.
Ah, it feels good!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Why?
It means you're pregnant, of course.
Th-That can't be.
Well then,
I should get going.
Y-Yes. Take care.
Is something the matter?
Your face seems rather pale.
No, I'm fine.
G-Good luck on your training and come back soon.
I'll...
be waiting.
Okay.
I'll be back.
Sorry, Eiji-san.
I've already...
been sullied.