How filthy.
This doesn't look anything like the real thing.
But I'm glad I decided to do some practice runs before the real deal.
Humans are so worthless.
They shrivel and decompose quickly.
And if I plaster and let them dry, they lose more and more of their feminine essence.
I have to get some more materials for my work.
I'll get a girl my age that looks like the real one.
Girl in the Shell
They say this man has a large black egg, with a doll inside.
Yeah.
The doll has no limbs since they'll get in the way when putting it inside.
But since it look similar to a human, you can mistake it for a corpse.
When you look closely,
you'll find that it's neither a doll nor a corpse.
Within the shell of this black egg lives a girl with no limbs.
If you meet this man, you have to tell him you're not a "Girl in the Shell."
Otherwise, you'll take her place inside the black shell.
Tokisaka
The academy isn't aware of it yet,
but apparently, there was a student who didn't return home.
So, she's the fourth victim, huh?
We were able to easily discover the victim's identity today, thanks to your help.
But to think it'd turn out to be four students in a row from the same academy...
I don't think we can consider this a coincidence any longer.
Yeah.
Ah!
I'm sorry. Was it too hot?
Heh, don't worry about it.
Something like this is lukewarm, compared to the boiling water we'll make the culprit drink.
I guess so.
Yes, this is the Tokisaka residence.
It looks like school's been canceled.
They don't have much of a choice with the current situation.
The fussy higher-ups still haven't been informed...
that victims who caught the public's eye all went to the same school.
However, if the culprit is doing a thorough check on the students,
then the girls aren't necessarily safe even if they're not going to school.
Besides,
the academy seems to require students to wear their uniforms off-campus,
so the culprit might take notice of them instead if they're wandering around alone.
Ah, damn.
I don't have any idea what the culprit is thinking.
This person doesn't care where the limbs are dumped, yet we can't find the bodies.
It's connected to his objective...
and definitely linked to his motive.
Could it be necrophilia?
This would be easy to understand if that were the case.
Nii-san.
Kuchiki-san called.
Oh? Touko did?
She said she didn't have to speak to you directly,
so she left a message.
What was it?
Did I keep you waiting?
Not at all.
I also just got here.
Besides, you're early.
Well, good to know.
I'm sorry for making you come all the way out here.
I don't mind.
Anyway, let's move on to your request.
I still only have unconfirmed information.
Okay.
Hey, do you want to look at some paintings while we talk?
I want to hear what you have to say,
but I don't feel like going to your office or a cafe.
Sure.
I found out several things.
Where should I start?
You don't need to be conserved about the fact that I'm not the Kuchiki's real daughter.
You already knew?
Checking my family register is simple enough for me to do.
It's just... I haven't told my mother and everyone else that I do know.
I see.
Also, before she adopted you, your mother lived in Kurashiki, Okayama.
I discovered that your biological mother's name is Nakahara Misa.
You found out that much?
Set a thief to catch a thief.
I used to have a wide range of influence in the bureaucratic offices back in the day.
It seems I was right to set my hopes on you, Detective.
You're very welcome.
Still, we were fortunate that there were official files available, despite the chaos after the war.
Anyway,
this is what I've found out so far.
I could find out the rest rather quickly if I talked to your current family.
I'd... prefer you to wait.
I don't remember my birth parents' faces at all, so my foster mother is like my real one.
All right.
Then I'll have to go to Kurashiki and investigate this Nakahara Misa person.
Unfortunately, I can't travel afar at the moment.
Are you talking about your current case?
Yeah.
Sorry, but people's lives are on the line.
I know that.
I'm not in that much of a rush anyway.
I'm relieved to hear that.
By the way, when you said you wanted me to find the real you,
you meant finding your real family and putting the matter of your lineage to rest.
Are you sure you want this?
I really wonder.
I think those are probably some of my reasons,
but I'm not exactly sure what i want to find.
I guess that's why I want you to look for me, Detective.
That's vague.
I am.
Vague.
I'm vague.
Touko says I'm a level-headed person,
but the truth is I don't know who I am or where I stand.
I'm an unstable existence.
But it's not just me.
Everything I look at appears vague, as if they're covered in a hazy fog.
I can't consider anything I look at beautiful.
Even so, you still paint?
What I'm painting is neither a portrait nor a landscape.
I paint what's inside my heart.
Inside your heart.
Yeah, but that's why I can't manage to finish it.
Is that so?
But you seem rather attracted to Mamiya Shinzou's paintings, for a person who can't see the beauty in things.
I see darkness in Mamiya Shinzou's paintings.
The appeal is not the beauty, but the depth of darkness, and magnitude of blackness.
Darkness?
Yes.
These beautiful colors conceal a darkness.
A black color that's not vague.
That darkness exists inside you and me, Detective.
Your heart is enveloped in darkness.
But, there's still a light inside that darkness.
It's faint,
but when that single beam of light pierces me, it feels very hot... and painful.
Also, I sense this painting contains the same color of darkness that exists within me.
This is...
"Girl in the Shell."
When I learned about this painting, I decided to find out who I was.
I wanted to make it clear to myself, that I'm not some made-up figure like the girl in the sh—
Touko!
Touko?
I came here to have a look at the "Girl in the Shell,"
but I didn't imagine I'd meet you too.
Touko, why is...
Don't you remember? He's a detective, Tokisaka Reiji-san.
Touko, why are you with someone like him?
We had some things to discuss.
It was a little, short rendezvous.
Hey, come on now.
Touko, don't be fooled.
You can't be with men.
Tokisaka-san and I aren't in some indecent kind of relationship.
He's not tricking me or anything. It's not like that.
It's not like you to make excuses!
What has happened to your normal self?
Touko, you're dignified and beautiful like this painting.
You have to shine, be more radiant than anything else.
Touko.
This painting isn't radiant at all.
You mustn't look at the "Girl in the Shell" and me like that.
What?
Touko's been acting stranger and stranger ever since she met you.
Touko, you can't hang out with this man.
Touko.
Let's go, Touko.
Please be quiet inside the art gallery.
Stella.
S-Sorry.
Tokisaka Detective Bureau
Come in.
Hey!
Oh, Tojiko?
Yukari isn't here today.
I know.
I'm here today because I want to talk to you, Detective.
And don't call me Tojiko!
Gathering more info?
That's half of the reason why I'm here.
Detective, you're investigating the mutilation case everyone's talking about, right?
Maybe.
Don't hide it!
Yukarin told me.
Yukari's surprisingly talkative.
And so... so...
I thought I'd offer my help in the investigation.
I don't need it.
Come on! Don't say that!
What could a student possibly do anyway?
Don't underestimate my abilities!
Today, I come bearing some very good information.
Shell of
Sheol
What? Does this contain your novel or something?
I'll leave that for next time.
It has one of Katsuragi Shin's works, "Shell of Sheol."
Katsuragi Shin
Shell of Sheol
There's a boy who strives to preserve the image of his late mother.
But to copy his mother's form, he cut off and threw away the limbs...
of the girls he met, or so the story goes.
His mother didn't have any limbs?
I'm not sure.
He didn't write about that part.
So what do you think? It has some connection to the case, right?
Probably some coincidence.
No, it's not!
There's definitely a connection!
Someone who read this novel might have...
Wait.
Katsuragi Shin himself might be the culprit.
That's a pretty big leap.
You writers are always so...
There's no way the criminal would write anything related to his crimes, just for the world to see.
You think so?
In any case, there's a high possibility the culprit is targeting Ooba Girls' Academy students.
Just stay put.
Fine!
In that case, I'll go look into it myself!
Look into it? What do you plan on doing?
I'm going to hunt for information, of course!
Actually, I've already gotten Katsuragi-sensei's address through my connections at the publisher.
I figured I'd be nervous meeting Katsuragi-sensei,
so I wanted you to come along, Detective.
Don't tell me you're a fan of Katsuragi Shin?
Eek!
What? You just want to meet one of the authors you like?
That's not it!
You're so mean, Detective!
Hey. Wait up, Tojiko.
Don't call me Tojiko!
Sheesh.
I don't have enough free time to be hanging out with a schoolgirl.
Shell of
Sheol
"Shell of Sheol," huh?
The boy's mother lay
beautifully in a black shell.
This can't be the case.
That's just pushing it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's gotten all big now.
See?
Gosh. For a police officer, you lack decency.
I'm a diligent person at work,
but I let loose at home.
I cleaned it,
so can you suck me off?
Sure.
Yukiko.
Gosh.
You couldn't hold it in?
Sorry.
But you're still hard.
You can keep going, right?
I still can't believe something this big can fit inside of me.
What are you talking about?
That's where babies come from.
Well, if we do have a baby, let's plan ahead and help it out.
Will you make this place wider with your dick?
Guess I don't have a choice.
Reiji, you're so big!
So what do you think, Yukiko?
Am I making it wider?
I don't know,
b-but I f-feel so good.
Don't!
Yukari-chan will hear us.
She's tired from hanging out with her friends.
She went to bed a while ago.
She's still a kid.
You can be as loud as you want.
Reiji! Reiji!
Reiji, oh Reiji!
I feel so good!
I'm...
I'm going to...
Yukiko!
That... felt... great.
Yukiko.
We should get married soon.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll protect you forever.
Touko!
I'm happy, Detective.
So you'll protect me.
Yukiko.
Where's Yukiko?
Yukiko!
Reiji.
You promised to protect me.
It was a dream?
I understand.
I'll help out as well.
Yes.
Sorry for the trouble.
Nii-san, something terrible has happened.
Apparently, Tsuzuriko didn't come home last night.
What did you say?
I'll go take a quick look around.
Wait, Yukari.
It's dangerous for Ooba Girls' Academy students to walk around alone in this situation.
But...
Give Uozumi a call.
I'll get him to leave some officers here, so you stay home.
Everyone's aware of the case,
so the police won't search for her as if she's just a runaway.
Okay.
"Shell of Sheol."
Katsuragi Shin.
Katsuragi Shin
Shell of Sheol
Investigation First Division
Why are you calling so early, Reiji?
What?!
Another student went missing?
There's something I want you to look into right away.
A writer by the name of Katsuragi Shin.
There's a big possibility that he's connected to this case.
The guy you told me to check out.
Katsuragi Shin is his pen name,
and his real name is Mamiya Shinji.
Mamiya?
Is there a chance he's a relative of Mamiya Shinzou?
Yeah.
I heard that name before. Some painter's son, I think.
The public doesn't seem to be aware of that though.
So, I found out that he owns a workplace in Shimochi.
It seems he's using the studio he inherited from his father.
Shimochi?
Did the crimes take place around that area?
Now that you mention it...
Hey.
Don't tell me... this is actually him.
That's what I'm going to find out now.
Hey, Reiji!
Don't do anything reckless before I get there!
Tsuzuriko.
Tsuzuriko!
Damn. I can't wait for Uozumi.
Tsuzuriko.
A... girl in the shell.
So I guess it was because of the patrol cars that came flooding in.
Katsuragi Shin.
Mamiya Shinji didn't come back.
Also...
he's now wanted by the police as a suspect in the serial killings,
but Mamiya Shinji's whereabouts are... completely unknown.
I heard what happened...
to Yosomiya-san.
That was awful.
It was my fault.
If only I had taken her suggestion seriously...
Touko.
Tokisaka-san!
Tokisaka-san.
What's the matter, Tokisaka-san?
Touko, don't you ever leave me.
Tokisaka-san?
You won't ever become a girl in the shell, right?
Girl in the shell?
Of course I won't.
Hurry up and find the real me.
Tokisaka-san!
No.
My uniform's going to get wrinkled.
No, not there.
It tickles.
Tokisaka-san!
You're wet.
Do you feel it?
Come on.
You're not supposed to say those kind of things out loud.
No, you can't.
I'm going crazy.
There's so much of you inside me, Tokisaka-san.
Touko, will you be all right if I start moving?
Do it however you want.
It feels better for guys that way, doesn't it?
Touko.
Touko!
I can feel your cock so deep inside me. I feel it all over my body!
I can't hold on.
My mind is going blank.
Touko!
Tokisaka-san!
Mamiya Shinji
The trembling wind reaches out and brushes my cheek
like a baby rebelling against the silence.
I held it in my arms, keeping it close,
but the cage simply crumbles away.
Moving past confined time and space,
the azure bird pointed out a sign from the stars.
Even if darkness turns its back on the moon,
it still looks beautiful to me.
As the thread cracks and frays,
it starts to look bent out of shape.
I'll keep my cries that fall on deaf ears
locked away in my heart.
You slip through my outstretched palms,
yet you don't even remember.
The body I've thrown away is lost in hesitation.
What drifts on is a lingering miracle.