No!
Jeez!
What the...?
No!
Hospital
I was really surprised when they brought you to the hospital where I work.
I'm sorry.
That aside, you're such a careless person, Tomohisa-kun.
Really?
But even if you say careless...
...I never thought that I'd end up like this.
Tomohisa-kun.
You haven't had a bath, have you?
I'll give you a wipe down.
What is it?
Why are you making such a strange face?
Eh, no...
Well...
Do you want to do something indecent again?
Oh my, that's a little rude.
If that's what you're going to say, then maybe I should go~
I'm sorry, Senpai.
I didn't mean it!
Please do it.
Jeez.
It can't be helped.
Okay then, I'll give you one.
Translation: Mizuho-sama
Are you all right?
Isn't that too hot?
No, it's fine.
You can leave the front. I'll do it myself.
It's fine.
I've already started, so I may as well do it.
Senpai...
You smell really nice.
Oh?
Me wiping your body is getting you all excited.
This is, well...
We haven't done it since you were hospitalized, right?
It's unbearable.
I'll make it all clean for you.
But... you hate when a girl does such naughty things with you, right?
That's not true.
You're getting hard, Tomohisa-kun.
It jumped out of your boxers.
I'll lick it.
Hey.
I don't have towel, so I can't clean up.
It's fine. Your smell is turning me on.
It was so thick it clumped up.
I'm sorry.
Just once isn't enough.
Senpai.
Oh no.
Wait!
Slow down a bit!
His tongue's going inside me. It feels so good.
I'm going to...
No, not yet!
Hold on a bit more!
Look.
Your semen mixing with my juices is getting me so wet.
Tomohisa-kun, do you want to put your dick in my pussy?
Yes.
I want to put it in.
It makes me a little happy to hear you say it so honestly.
Look, it's so wet that it'll slip right in.
Senpai.
It hurts.
You're injured, so stay still.
Wow!
It's so hard.
It's reaching deep inside.
If you do it so hard, I won't be able to keep quiet.
I'm sorry, but it's so good that I can't stop.
Senpai, you're really squeezing down on me.
Your dick is going so deep and it's so hard. It feels so good.
I'm cuming!
Yes, give it to me!
Cum inside me!
Together...
I'm cuming too, so...
let's cum together.
Tomohisa-kun.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Did something happen?
I came because I heard a scream.
No, I think I just had a strange dream.
It's good that you're healthy, but this is hospital so please calm down.
Yes.
I will stay calm.
She noticed.
Senpai, this is bad.
Hey, can we do it one more time?
Hot springs?
Yeah, I found a good place nearby.
It's the weekend, so I think we can go.
You mean just the two of us?
Of course!
In a few days it'll get busy.
So I thought that we could stay there for the night.
You don't want to, Endo-kun?
It's not like I don't want to... but...
Then it's been decided!
I'm looking forward to it~
It's great that the train isn't very busy.
It is, isn't it?
Maybe it's because of Tanabata.
Those potato chips are delicious!
You should try some too, Endo-kun!
T-Thank you.
So? So? They're delicious, right?
Yeah, they're delicious.
I know, right?
I wonder why Mom left those potato chips.
Mikura-san really is cute.
What's wrong?
Why're you staring at me like that?
Maybe you already noticed...
You know... I haven't been wearing panties since this morning.
W-Wait!
This is bad!
If you make too much noise then someone will notice.
Somehow this is really exciting.
Look!
You're already this hard.
It's so hot and it's moving.
I'm getting a little...
Hey, maybe we should do it here?
Endo-kun, it's amazing.
It wants to jump out of your trousers.
No...
The trousers are tight, aren't they?
You're so naughty, Endo-kun.
No way.
I'll lick it directly now.
It's so big, Endo-kun!
Mikura-san.
You dick is twitching.
You want to cum.
I will now be doing an inspection of the train.
Thank you very much.
I will now be checking your tickets.
Please cooperate.
Mikura-san!
Sir.
Could you please show me your tickets?
Here.
Thank you.
Nimei-sama is it?
Is that customer all right?
Yeah, she's fine.
Understood.
If something troubles you then please contact me.
Thank you very much.
I'm so-
I'm fine.
Thank you for cooperating.
Maybe she didn't realize?
She realized.
I see.
Well, nevermind.
And it's still so lively.
This and that are a different story.
We'll arrive at the station soon.
So, let's continue this later.
Yeah.
You're right.
Kouryo House
It's so beautiful!
Awesome!
It's such a picturesque sunset.
Endo-kun, come and see it.
Endo-kun?
No...
This is...
Maybe it's because of... this!
I'm sorry.
We were right in the middle of it before.
Then...
let's get down to the hot springs.
Yeah.
No one said that there would be mixed baths.
Endo-kun, come join me in the bath.
Give me your dick.
I'll clean it up for you, 'kay?
Will you cum here?
Or here?
Or maybe... in here?
No, no!
Now I'm super horny!
I'm full.
It was delicious, right?
Yeah, it was delicious.
Well...
It seems like a real trip when we do these things.
Is that so?
I'm a little excited.
You really don't wear underwear, Mikura-san?
Why?
No, well...
Do you want to check?
Mikura-san.
Endo-kun.
Check out here.
Because... the room's a little plain.
Mikura-san.
It's okay for you to check.
Be gentle.
Endo-kun.
Did you finish checking?
Mikura-san.
I can't take...
anymore.
Fine.
Let's do it.
Put your dick in my pussy.
Your dick is so hot, Endo-kun!
I can't wait anymore, either.
Put it in!
Y-Your dick is so hard
and so stiff.
Your pussy is soaking.
Endo-kun, it feels so good!
Ah, no!
I'm cuming!
I'm cuming.
My nipples are so hot.
It's so hard.
No!
I'm cuming!
I'm cuming~!
Endo-kun.
Are you relieved now?
Yeah.
Then why do I still see something flapping about there?
No...
This is...
Well...
Erm...
We're all sticky now.
Next time when it's like this let's make tempura.
Preliminary
Announcement
Stringendo.
The private lessons of Angels.
Act 10 is planned to be on sale in summer of 2011.
Summer 2011
planned to be on sale
Next Time: We will continue our indecent adventure at the hot springs and we'll also show Sylvia-san's story.