Me and Endo-kun went to a hot spring for the weekend.
When Endo-kun gets excited, my heart really starts to pound as well.
Why're you staring at me like that?
Might this be the reason?
And we became more daring than usual.
My nipples are so hot.
It's so hard.
The open-air bath truly is the best of the baths at this hot spring.
Womens' baths
Some of it's still inside me.
Don't look at me like that, Endo-kun.
S-Sorry.
You had your way with me just a little while ago.
It's so hot!
Mikura-san.
I can see you... down there.
Endo-kun, you perv.
But...
There's still some of your semen down there.
That's...
So hot.
It feels great!
Endo-kun,
you still aren't satisfied yet?
That bid swollen dick looks painful.
Even though we've done it so many times today. You really are perverted.
M-Mikura-san...
It'll be fine.
I'll make sure that no one notices.
We really shouldn't...
If you raise your voice too much, they're bound to notice.
But...
Your dick is so hard.
Do me, too.
Mikura-san.
No one will notice, will they?
That we're doing such dirty things.
They really will notice if you keep being so rough.
Sorry.
Seems I've interrupted you again.
If you'll excuse me.
She didn't notice at all.
Hey, Endo-kun.
Let's go somewhere further back.
Mikura-san.
It's twitching.
Mikura-san!
I...
Your dick... it's so hot that it's bulging.
If you keep going like that...
Does it feels good?
The hot springs have made my boobs silky smooth, let's give them a go now.
Seems you're being a little more raunchy than usual.
Really?
You might be right.
I'm staying here at this inn with you;
it's a lot different from where we do it usually.
You're boobs are making me harder, Mikura-san.
It's bulging so much!
You came a lot.
Sorry, I got it all over your face.
Make me cum this time, too.
Your dick is so hot, Endo-kun.
It's amazing. it's reaching so deep inside.
I think we might be being watched.
but don't stop.
Hurry up, Endo-kun.
They're watching us.
I'm sure that those women over there are watching us.
It's so embarrassing...
but I think it's turning me on.
They're watching us.
I can't take it...
It feels so good.
I'm going to cum.
Me too.
I'm cuming.
I'm cuming!
That was amazing.
Let's come to the hot springs again some time.
Stringendo.
That's strange.
They should be here already.
Well then, thats all for today.
I'll see you tomorrow.
There they are.
Oh, Tanabe-kun?
Don't recognize me?
It's me.
Shibuya-san? How come?
I'm working over winter vacation. I'm here to deliver this to you.
This is...
It's pretty suspicious that you were waiting out here for this.
Let's see...
It says it contains PC parts.
Oh, isn't this...
It's just a massager.
Recently my shoulders, hips, feet, nose, eyes... you know...
Oh? But still, this is no PC part.
No...
That's just...
I've seen these before.
These can be used to do dirty things.
Amazing!
It's vibrating so hard!
This is how you use it, right?
You sound so cute.
It's that good?
Shibuya-san, stop it.
If you keep rubbing me there...
You're getting a hard-on already?
It really feels good?
Shibuya-san, please stop that.
Stop it already.
No way.
You came.
I told you to stop.
Sorry.
I never thought you'd cum so quick.
Shibuya-san?
Hey, can you try it on me?
Don't you want to see how good it makes me feel?
Here I go.
Okay?
Yeah.
It feels kind of strange...
How to put it... it's not quite tickling...
Hey, want to try it out?
Yeah.
S-Sorry.
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
I was just a little surprised.
Do it some more.
This really has potential.
My nipples are tingling.
If you start making noises like that, I'm gonna get turned on, too.
But I can't help it,
it just feels so good.
Try it down there.
Use the massager on me here.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm begging you, Tanabe-kun.
Give me all you've got.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Please, don't tease me.
Use it on my pussy.
Okay.
Amazing.
I can feel the vibrations through my whole body.
They're even shaking me up inside.
Y'know, it has an even higher setting.
What is this?
T-This...
Oh god!
N-No.
Don't rub my pussy with it so hard.
It's starting to go numb.
I won't stop.
You didn't let up for a second.
No...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
Hey...
I made such a mess,
will it really be okay?
Well, nevermind.
You have to take responsibility until the end.
Your dick got pretty big, didn't it?
See?
Look at how hard it is.
If you're going to do it so rough, th-then I...
Wait.
You want to do it here?
That's right.
I won't hold back any longer.
Plough into me with your hot rod.
Shibuya-san.
Hurry up!
My breasts are so hot.
My boobs feel great, so does your dick.
It's so good.
You're so hot and wet down there.
That's because you kept on with that massager.
No.
Don't come this way.
Wait.
Stop.
What are you doing?
I can't keep quiet.
Hello? Is someone there?
I'm sorry.
I-I fainted for a minute.
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
I-I'm fine.
Please be careful.
Jeez.
Why didn't you stop?
You squeezed down on me so tight, I just couldn't stop.
What are you saying?
Besides, it kinda turned you on, right?
That's not it.
That's not true.
Don't say weird things.
No.
If you start doing that now...
But you're getting tight again.
No.
No!
If you do that at the same time then I'll...
I'll go crazy.
I'll go crazy!
Wow,
I'm feeling it too.
I'm gonna do you harder.
No.
It's already too much for me.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cuming.
Feeling better, Tanabe-kun?
Yeah.
Look.
I'm still all sticky down here.
I'll have to take a bath when I get back home.
S-Sorry.
I'm going to borrow this for a bit.
I want to experiment a little more with the massager.
I see.
Maybe we can do something fun next time, too.
I'm looking forward to it.