Do your best at work today.
I will, Nanami.
Tonight we'll be celebrating our wedding anniversary.
We're meeting at the hotel at seven, aren't we?
Yeah.
I can't wait!
I'll wear something nice for you.
All right, I'm off.
Have a good day, Darling.
This is where it gets good.
Her lewd pussy is getting wet.
Here we have the innocent housewife, Honda Nanami.
A beautiful married woman in a public lavatory.
I love her face when she strains!
I can see that naughty slit of hers plain as day.
And what a soundtrack this performance has!
Such a beautiful expression!
Excuse me, it's Mrs. Honda.
Oh, Kamata. Hello.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm quite busy today.
It's all right.
Holding back is bad for your health.
I've been waiting for you.
I-I'm sorry.
I want to talk with you about the neighborhood association.
It smells kind of like a bathroom out here.
N-Not really...
Please, come inside.
I'll make some tea and we can talk.
Come on in.
What are you doing?
I want to show you something, Nanami.
What are you after?
Take a look at this.
As the building manager-
No.
—watching the security cameras is an important part of my job.
No way.
What is this?
No.
Stop this.
It came out nice, didn't it?
No!
Stop it!
Look, it's really good.
I'm begging you.
No!
No.
Don't you sound just adorable?
I've been watching you the whole time.
No.
No!
I recorded all your embarrassing parts.
Please let me go.
I beg you.
It's your fault, Nanami.
I just can't take my eyes off you.
No.
I can't hold out anymore.
I want to become one with you.
You came all the way to my room after all.
No way!
Don't do it!
That place is for my husband alone. I beg you...
Stop...
It went in...
It hurts.
It's too big!
It hurts!
I've done it.
You're completely mine!
A dick that's not Shuuichi's is inside me...
Help me, Shuuichi!
This is as good as I'd hoped!
Your pussy's really squeezing my dick hard!
Please, take it out.
I'll break.
I'm going to break!
No!
I beg you.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll pretend this never happened.
I'm also taping us having sex.
So stay quiet and listen to me.
No.
That's...
No!
You're so tight when you bend back like that, Nanami!
I...
No...
You still don't have any kids, Nanami.
I'll help you have one!
No!
No.
You can't!
Don't cum.
You mustn't cum inside me!
No.
I'll do anything you want,
just don't cum inside me.
I'm cuming!
No!
No.
No, I don't...
It's my wedding anniversary today, so I have to hurry back home.
I have to get ready and meet Shuuichi where we agreed.
We'll celebrate this day together.
I'm really glad we can celebrate our anniversary today.
I'm being too loud; it's embarrassing.
It's all right.
They won't hear you next door.
That's not it.
I'm just worried that you might think you have an indecent wife.
I'd never think that of you.
You're my darling wife.
That's...
You're a little more forceful than usual.
No.
Don't say things like that.
It's embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing.
It's hitting deep.
It's hitting me deep inside!
We've been together for three years now. You want kids, right?
No.
Don't say that.
It's embarrassing.
You still don't have any kids, Nanami.
I'll help you have one!
This is as good as I'd hoped!
Your pussy's really squeezing my dick hard!
You're so good, Nanami!
I'm cuming!
I love you, Darling.
I love you.
I really do.
I really love you!
I'm going to cum inside you.
Cum, my dear.
Please!
Please fill me with your cum.
I beg you.
It's coming.
Your juice is spreading inside me.
I love you, Nanami.
I love you too.
Today's the day we celebrate our first fuck.
We'll be doing it a lot more from now on.
It's all right,
we'll keep it a secret from your husband.
Nanami?
You were right on time.
You must really love my dick!
O-Of course not.
You went for a drive with your husband in this car today, right?
Try to remember the great time you had with your husband while I jam my cock in you.
You're so cruel.
Hurry up and get it over with.
Darling...
save me.
It's impossible.
It's too much.
No more.
You're moaning like a whore.
You really do love my dick!
No. I...
I'm sorry, Shuuichi.
I'm sorry.
Darling...
You're still thinking about your husband even though you've got my dick inside you?
Stop it...
I'll break.
I'm going to break.
So, how does it feel to sneak out to fuck me after sleeping with your husband?
No!
Darling.
I'm sorry.
That's good. You're getting excited.
I'm going to cum inside you again.
No.
Outside...
Please cum outside.
Haven't I already filled your womb with my sperm a whole bunch?
No!
I really will get pregnant.
Please, stop it.
As long as you keep fucking your husband, he'll never know it's mine.
No!
I have to be up early tomorrow, so could we...
I'm sorry.
I'll do the moving, so please!
I want to feel connected with you.
What happened, Nanami?
You've been acting strange recently.
I'm sorry.
I'll move.
I'll do the moving!
Darling... more!
Let's do it more!
Darling,
it feels so great.
Darling.
I want you to cum inside me.
I want your sperm inside me.
So please, cum inside me!
Over here!
Wait up.
It's impossible.
I can't do it while someone is watching me.
What are you saying?
Then we'll have wasted all this effort.
You can do it at any time.
Use your anger to force it out.
No.
I don't want to.
I'll go mad.
Then let me give you a hand.
No...
No.
You've got such a great expression while you let it all go.
Why are you doing such cruel things?
The video is going to be great.
Since you're all freshened up, let's fuck.
No way!
No.
To have sex after that...
Your ass was just calling out, "Sex, sex"!
No.
Stop!
Fucking you bareback after filming you do that is great.
No, no, no!
I beg you.
Let me wipe myself.
I love smelling your stench while I fuck you.
No.
I'm sorry, Shuuichi.
I'm so sorry.
Oh?
Looks like you're leaking a little.
No!
You want to take a shit when you're getting fucked, right?
You're such a filthy bitch.
No!
That's not true.
Stop it.
You're a pervert that loves skirts, right?
No.
No!
Darling.
Help me.
Breathe in that stench of yours!
Here!
Here.
Take it!
I'm cuming!
Take in all of my sperm!
No!
Don't cum inside.
Thank God. I'm not pregnant.
I'm sorry, Shuuichi.
Hey, Nanami, you pissed yourself again?
This isn't a dream.
I wonder how long we've been doing this.
I can barely remember half of it.
We've been doing it so long. I'll cum soon.
You came again, Nanami?!
You really love it bareback, don't you?
I wonder what Shuuichi is doing right now.
Oh look, Nanami, there's a call for you!
Who is it?
Yes?
Hello.
Nanami? It's me.
Yes, Darling?
I just got back to the hotel.
Thank you for working so late.
Yeah.
I think I'll be back tomorrow evening.
I'll be waiting for you.
Hey, Nanami?
What happened?
I'm all right.
I-It's nothing.
Nanami?
Nanami!
I'm... just not feeling... well.
But I'll be okay.
You're really okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
So please, keep working hard.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be waiting for you at home tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll get back as soon as I can tomorrow, so don't push yourself too much, okay?
I'll be waiting.
I love you, Darling.
I love you too, Nanami.
I'm so sorry, Darling.
I'm so sorry.
You really did well, Nanami!
Darling...
Seems like talking to your husband really tightened you up.
What?
What did I just swallow?
Medicine that'll let us have even more and more fun!
Let's fuck a whole lot more before your husband gets back from his business trip.
Okay, Nanami?
No...
My body's so hot.
I can't...
It feels so good.
Oh? What "feels so good"?
No...
That's not it.
My body just suddenly...
It feels good.
So good.
It's so good!
What is it that feels good?
Dick.
Your dick feels so good.
You really love sex, Nanami.
You're more a whore than a wife!
No.
My body...
My body is...
I can't stop.
I can't stop!
I'm about to cum again!
No.
I'm going to black out again.
Amazing!
It's so good!
Hey, Shuuichi, I want to be your wife forever.
But it seems I've already embarked on a path of no return.
So, Shuichi,
will you still love me, nonetheless?