T-Teacher...
Chemistry Preparation Room
Teacher, someone might see us here.
Fear not,
no one will see us here, no matter what we do.
Not... in the open...
No!
Teacher!
If you're so intense, my pussy might lose it!
Someone's probably looking up here.
N-No... It's so embarrassing.
I wonder how a real high-class girl tastes.
Teacher...
you're pounding my womb.
I'm gonna cum! Fill my womb with your man-milk!
I'm cumming!
Your semen's going to fill me.
She's been well cared for,
no doubt she's still a virgin.
Looks like this'll be interesting.
Teacher...
How is it?
It's fantastic!
I'm so glad.
I love you!
Just swallow it like that!
That's right.
That's a good girl.
Vol. 1
Ideal High-class Girl
A traditional school: Sakuratani Private Academy.
Students must be from a respectable family and pass a rigorous interview to be admitted.
It is an academy for true high-class young ladies.
Schol policies, huh?
Don't make me laugh.
Teacher, I don't understand this one.
I want you to teach me too!
Yes, yes. One person at a time, okay?
Okay!
It's like taming a pack of bitches.
Hey! Pay attention!
Sorry about that.
Kirihara's always been like that, huh?
It does seem that way.
I guess she's got a lot on her plate.
Oh, that's right,
isn't Kirihara going to you for counselling after school?
What? Sounds nice.
I want to go too!
Now, now. You know I'm busy preparing for exams.
Your next class is Phys Ed, right?
Shouldn't you girls be changing by now?
Yeah...
Someone sure killed the fun.
Come on, let's go.
Kirihara!
You're looking sort of depressed.
Is something troubling you?
N-No. I'm fine.
I see.
Well, if you do have any issues, feel free to confide in me.
I will! Thank you very much.
Her attitude's totally changed since then.
I've got this in the bag.
Pretending to be a competent teacher sure isn't easy.
Come in.
U-Um...
I'm sorry about yesterday!
Are you all right?
You're quite light, so I'm fine.
I'm so sorry!
It's okay, Kirihara.
You don't need to worry about it.
More importantly, I'm glad you aren't hurt.
I'm glad that you aren't hurt either.
If anything comes up,
I'll help you however I can.
Okay!
By the way, about the upcoming exam,
are you studying for it?
Yes!
I always study the subject before class, and review afterwards.
You're a perfect honour student!
An honour student?
That's...
Someone who excels in their studies and consistently scores above average.
If that's what an honour student is, then what are you?
B-But...
I'm not comfortable being called that.
Ah, is that so?
Sorry.
Oh no! It's not like you have to apologise or anything.
I suppose people calling you an honour student puts a lot of pressure on you, right?
Teacher...
Such a nice aroma!
This way of making it is the best at bringing out the aroma.
Well then, let's try it.
It's getting late, so after you drink that you should go home.
Um... I don't want to go home!
Hey now, what are you saying?
I-It was a joke.
O-Oh, I see.
It was a joke.
I really am grateful to you for listening to me.
I see.
I'm glad I've been of some help.
You almost seem like a big brother!
The coffee you made me was delicious.
Thank you.
It was to your taste?
It has such a mild aroma.
H-Huh?
I-It feels like my body is getting lighter...
She definitely said it:
"like a big brother", huh?
That's a true high-class girl for you.
But regardless, a woman's body is made for serving men.
Magnificent.
Worlds apart from the common trash!
You're a high-class girl, but... what a saucy rack you have!
Teacher? Is this a drea—
Teacher, what are you doing?!
I'm sorry, Kirihara.
I just can't hold back anymore.
No!
Teacher, don't do this!
Kirihara...
You're so beautiful, Kirihara.
Time to get a taste of this flower!
Your flower is blessed with beautiful petals.
And it seems it has yet to be plucked.
May I, be the one to do so?
What are you trying to do?
No!
It hurts!
Please don't move anymore!
Kirihara! It feels so good!
Please stop...
Your pussy feels so absolutely wonderful!
Please don't say things like that.
I'm almost at my limit...
Teacher... please stop...
This is unfair...
But your pussy whispers such indecent verse.
Please don't say things like that.
It's desperately milking me, hungering for my seed.
No! Don't do it...
Please don't be so rough.
It's flowing inside me...
What a tight pussy!
It's squeezing out every last drop!
I've raped the Kirihara Group's princess.
Looks like it's over.
Teacher, why have you done this?
Kirihara, I've loved you for so long.
But as student and teacher, we aren't allowed to get into a relationship.
Then when I saw you, slumbering, adorable, I couldn't control myself.
I'm really sorry!
Teacher...
I am a failure as a teacher.
I will have to leave this institution.
Don't say things like that!
You're going to forgive me, even though I have wronged you so?
U-Um. It's... fine.
Thank you, Kirihara.
I truly love you!
T-Teacher...
To believe that kind of lie;
that's a genuine high-class girl for you.