I'm so mad at you!
What's with that?
You said that you hate your Sagimiya blood too.
You said "I won't lose to my Sagimiya blood"!
And "I'll try hard".
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry, Nee-san.
I know that you've given in.
You don't have to apologize,
because I'm yours completely.
Your semen is on my hand.
Don't suffer alone.
Because I'm all yours.
Inraku no Ketsuzoku 2
FFFappers presents
Are you going out?
What are you saying?
I just got back.
I-I see.
Besides, you...
were doing it with Kagu-nee, right?
You knew?
I can tell from how you reek.
What is it?
Do you have something else to say?
Not really.
So filthy...
What's filthy?
You-
No!
Don't get any closer!
You're disgusting!
Don't look so damn miserable.
I'm not going to lose to my Sagimiya blood!
You said it too...
That's...
It's really nothing bad.
If you decide to just accept it, then I won't say anything.
Just...
I'm saying that you're nasty and disgusting!
Wait...
Why are you so sad?
Sagimiya blood...
I also have it in me...
It's disgusting!
Only getting turned on by blood relatives...
Gross!
Shun, my twin brother.
I've cared about him since we were children.
Just...
stop already!
I don't want to feel it anymore!
Leave it to me.
If you master your body then you'll accept it too.
No!
I'm not going to lose!
I won't!
You can see all of me...
You can see them...
My breasts are tingling so much.
It's amazing!
It's so good!
My pussy is getting soaked from you touching it.
No!
There's a hard dick going in me!
It's going in!
A dick is going in my pussy!
I get it now!
I know what it feels like to be shaken up inside!
I can feel you
and how hard you are!
It feels so good!
Push!
Push it in deep!
Even though we're doing it like dogs, it feels so good!
It's driving into me!
Brother-sister sex feels so good!
I really don't want this.
It's so bad, but...
it feels so good!
Your dick is getting even bigger than before!
Brother-sister sex feels good.
So good!
This forbidden incest is great.
I'm cumming!
It feels so good!
Let's finish.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
It's coming out...
Semen is...
Semen is flowing deep inside me.
What is this?
It's too good, Onii-san.
What kind of dreams was I having?
Being violated by Shun like that...
I won't lose to my Sagimiya blood. I won't!
Oh, Misaki.
If you're doing laundry, then we could do ours together.
I'll do it myself.
It's fine.
Really...
Did you happen to see, Shun-kun?
Did something happen to him?
He's been locked up in his room since yesterday.
Maybe he's worried about something?
I don't know.
He's probably just worried about something stupid.
He'll come out when he gets over it.
You shouldn't worry about it.
Jeez, Misaki. You need to get along well with Shun-kun.
I'm saying that you're nasty and disgusting.
It's not like I'm worried about him or anything.
That's right, I'll just apologize for what I said.
It's me.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
You want something?
You know... everyone's worried about you.
So...
How to put it...
That is...
Well...
I'm sorry.
That I called you nasty.
Why's that?
I said something horrible to you...
Ah, I see.
So that's why you were worried.
Idiot!
I wasn't worried!
I just thought that I should say sorry.
Right, so why-
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry, Misaki.
You mustn't get near me right now.
So could you...
So that's what you were doing
You were jerking off all night.
Hmm. I see.
For once you've really tried hard.
W-Was it because of me?
I see.
So you were fighting too.
To not have to rely on Kagu-nee.
Hey!
Well...
I've got in the way,
of your...
That's why...
I'll help you out.
Help?
Hurry up and take your trousers off.
Misaki!
Quickly!
W-Why is it so big?
Such an amazing shape.
And it's quivering.
It's such a strange feeling.
Move your hand, Misaki.
Like this?
Does it hurt?
No.
It feels good.
Can you carry on?
Yeah.
Could you move your hand faster?
Like this?
It's hot.
And fits so well in my hand.
Do it faster.
Faster?
I really have to do it faster?
You're kidding... Like this?
Faster!
No way.
Much faster?
Jeez, what a pain!
This is no good at all.
What's that supposed to mean?
Masturbation for men is a real nuisance.
Jeez. So what should I do?
Well...
Can I touch you?
Touch...
That's...
You're kidding, right?
You can't!
You absolutely cannot!
This is just foreplay though...
Foreplay?
Jeez. Fine!
I said that I'll help you.
So you can a little.
Just a little.
And I really mean a little.
No, Shun is groping my boobs.
No...
It's getting bigger.
Misaki.
It's really good.
If you rub that much...!
My boobs are getting rubbed like this by Shun's hand.
His dick is bulging and quivering like it's gonna burst.
Don't grope so hard!
Misaki, soon I'm going to...
Semen will shoot out of Shun's dick.
No.
He really cums that much?
No, don't cum more!
Jeez. What's with that?
It smells so amazing.
It's making me smell indecent.
No.
You mustn't.
Hey!
No, I don't want this.
I can't lose to my Sagimiya blood.
That's...
You mustn't!
It's different...
This is different.
It's so different from when I touch myself.
No! Don't!
Don't look!
You can't!
What?
You came a lot just a while ago, so why is it so big?
N-NO!
No way!
Such...
Such a thing...
It feels really good.
So good!
Would it've been like in my dream?
Will it feel weird when I pee?
It's bad.
This is really bad.
I have to get out of here quick.
If not, then we'll do something wrong.
Something I'll regret.
You don't have endure it all the time.
You can always consult your sister about it.
What's with that?
I did all that just a while ago,
and in case I couldn't he called Kagu-nee?
I helped him because he was working hard.
Is he saying I'm not good enough?
I'm holding myself back so much.
But he called Kagu-nee just in case.
I see... so he did that...
he's the sort of person who would do that...
Misa-
Shut up!
Don't raise your voice so much, idiot!
You don't ask for help from anyone, so it's your own fault.
I tried hard, really hard, and restrained myself...
but what about you?
If you can't do it with me, you just run for help from Kagu-nee.
Don't screw with me!
Misaki.
Wa-
It's so hard.
It stinks.
You're a pervert for making me lick something that stinks so much.
Forcing your little sister to suck you off....
and do embarrassing things.
Don't mess with me.
I'm always imagining this.
I've become strange.
I try to satisfy myself,
but I can't calm down at all.
I can't help you like Kagu-nee does.
I thought that I should leave before I become strange,
but I turned strange anyway.
That's why...
However you...
You...
I'm sorry, Misaki.
Unforgivable.
It's unforgivable.
You have to always... always do it only with me.
Because you're mine!
Should I put it in?
You want me to, don't you?
It's already trembling so much.
You're ready to cum..
You're lusting after your younger sister.
But... for putting my pervert brother's dick in me, I'm the one who's the most...
Per-
-verted.
It hurts!
It's all in...
my pervert brother's dick.
Are you okay, Misaki?
You want this, right?
You're happy to be having sex with your younger sister!
You can do what you want with my breasts.
My nipples are so stiff.
I'm really feeling it.
It's hot.
What is this?
Amazing.
It feels really good.
So good!
Brother-sister sex is fantastic!
Cumming.
I'm cumming!
I can feel it deep inside my pussy.
Your hard dick is forcing me wide open.
Great! It's going so deep inside.
I can feel something amazing coming!
My brother's dick is great.
This forbidden incest is great.
Your slippery dick is going inside me.
It's going inside me!
Even though it's my first time, it's really good.
It's great.
It's so good!
Oh, no.
No.
You're driving me crazy.
Ah, yes!
This is bad...
If you carry on making me feel so good...
No more...
I...
It's good...
because we're siblings...
because you're my brother.
I'm cumming!
Amazing!
Your semen is spilling out.
It's so good...
I can't think about anything.
It was so great...
No...
If I carry on feeling like this...
Why?
You just came a lot, right?
No!
Wait!
Hey, you can't do it any more.
Hey!
No!
I won't be able to stand feeling so good.
Hey, Onii-chan. Wait!
Stop!
No!
Stop it!
It's too good!
I don't want this...
Please, it really hurts..
No!
I'm begging you, please!
Listen!
I don't want this.
Your dick feels too good...
It's stirring me up inside.
No.
I'm cumming again.
Save me!
If you come inside then I'll get pregnant.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, Onii-san.
Your semen is filling me up.
Idiot!
Pervert!
Brute!
Rapist!
Sister lover!
I ask you to do it once, but then you go and rape me.
Jeez, you totally overdid it.
Idiot! Idiot!
I hate you!
I'm sorry.
Well...
I'll do anything.
So...
So?
Then it's a promise.
From now on...
you have to always... always do it only with me.
Okay?