Hard and...
Big!
And it's so hot...
Oh, yes!
It's inside my...
My pussy...
Arihara-kun's cock is inside of me!
How...
How can she say things like that?
Harder, fuck me harder!
T-This is...
N-No!
I'm coming!
I could never say that!
Kanna,
become an eroge voice actress.
Alright, here's the script.
Do I have to say perverted stuff?
Yeah.
With... my voice?
Yup.
No way, no way, no way, no way, no way!
What the heck, Onee-chan?!
I can't do something like that!
Don't worry, you're perfectly capable.
I'm still a high schooler!
I know that. I waited until you turned 16 to ask you this.
I've actually wanted you to do it since you were in 8th grade.
We're a local company, so we work on a small budget,
and we can't afford a professional voice actress.
You get that, right?
My own sister is making eroges...
I still can't believe it!
It's not like I hid it from you.
You just never asked.
T-Then...
Those eroges I saw you playing at home all the time...
Those were all for work?!
Onee-chan!
Pretty much.
Anyway, training a voice actress who's close to me is the best option.
Okay?
No way.
What's the big deal?
It's not like I'm asking you to strip or something.
No way! It doesn't have to be me!
Who else can I ask to do something like this?!
No!
Never in a million years!
Shut the hell up...
and do it!
Absolutely not!
Hey!
Good grief!
Onee-chan is out of her mind.
Kanna! You headed home?
Are you on your way to the night shift, Mom?
Yeah. Sorry, I can't celebrate your birthday with you.
It's fine! I'm not a kid anymore.
I thought you were visiting Yayoi's company today.  Why isn't she with you?
Yes... Well...
Yayoi really cares about you.
I'm sure she has a very surprising present ready for you!
That she did...
Like "Become an eroge voice actress!" out of the blue...
She's doing everything she can to save for your college fund, ya know.
Life's been pretty hard ever since your father passed away,
but she said that shouldn't be a reason to limit your future.
Onee-chan said that?
She works really hard, and she says it's all for you,
even though I told her it's not a big deal since I'm saving for you, too.
I never knew... she cared so much for me.
She's taken care of me for as long as I can remember.
What's a bit of embarrassment compared to what she's done for me?
I'll... give it a shot!
I-I'll be an eroge voice actress!
I see.
Thanks. You're a lifesaver, Kanna.
Well then, let's get right to practicing.
Alright, try saying these.
These are the basics of the basics.
It's impossible to become an eroge voice actress without being able to say these.
W-Wait a second.
I need to prepare myself...
P...  P...
There's no one around, just the two of us.
R-Right.
Pu... ssy.
Say it clearly.
Pu!...ssy...
I can't hear you!
Poo...ey...
I said clearly!
Pu!...ssy...
I still can't hear you!
Clearly pronounce each syllable! Loud enough to be a shout!
Pu...
PUSSY!
I'm back!
What was that screaming just now?
Kanna, let's go home together!
Wanna stop for some cake on the way?
It's our treat.
We still have to celebrate your birthday.
Sorry, I'm going to my sister's studio.
Studio?
Yeah.
You mentioned helping out your sister earlier.
A game designer, was it?
What kind of games? What are you helping with?
S-Sorry, I'm in a hurry... so sorry!
She's in a rush, huh?
She's hiding something.
Okay, let's begin.
Start from page 4, line SA-0001.
Hey! Wait, Arihara-kun!
You're the only one who hasn't turned in his homework yet!
What do you mean, "Shut up"?!
She's amazing!
If you don't want to get yelled at-
Okay, fine!
I'll give you a private lesson next time, then!
I'm being drawn into the world of the story.
What?! You don't want to?
How amazing. It's like I'm really there.
That's great!
It's... pretty hard.
And... it feels hot.
It... It's getting bigger!
I... I can see it!
I've never even seen one before, and yet... I can sort of see what it looks like now!
Is... Is this okay? It doesn't hurt?
Want me to rub it harder?
Should I be impressed?
Does it feel good?
But...!
What's up? Want a retake?
Nope, it's nothing.
Incredible! It's inside me!
Am I going to say that?
Arihara-kun... you're inside me!
Words like that are going to... come from my mouth?
Somehow... Somehow, I'm...!
Please come!
Shoot a huge load of cum inside me!
Oh, no...
I'm...
Good job, Fumika.
You did great.
Really?
All you have to do is look at Kanna's face.
Looks like she got pretty turned on, too.
O-Onee-chan!
I'm so glad my performance turned you on!
Nothing less from our star actress, Warasono Fumika!
Aoyagi-san...
Are you really going to turn your sister into an eroge voice actress?
Without a doubt.
But... a high school girl... isn't that bad?
In the worst case scenario, you will say that you were told she was 18.
Age fraud is common in this industry anyway, right?
Don't say things that'll get us in trouble...
W-Well, we can just keep her age a secret. It's not like we're going to show her face or anything.
Yeah, that's right. You're just being a blockhead.
I'm being criticized when I'm the only one saying anything ethical...
Let's do our best, okay?
O-Okay.
If I'm going to do this, I want to be just like Fumika-san.
I want to become the type of voice actress that can make people visualize a scene with just her voice.
I don't know how long it'll take... but I'll give it my all now that I've made up my mind!
Pe... Pe...
Penis!
It's great that you can finally say it, but put some more emotion into it.
But it's embarrassing!
You can't afford to waste time.
You only have a week left until we start recording.
A week?
That's insane!
I can't do it!
This industry runs on ridiculous schedules.
But, still...
This is just too awful, isn't it?
I-I can't really do anything about it...
I feel for you, though.
So, it's not the time to be struggling from the start.
Say this one next.
This is the toughest word, but it shows up often in eroges.
But then again, if you can say this one, saying the rest will be a cakewalk.
By "often"...
How often?
Let's see, about 90% of the time?
That's pretty much the whole time.
Come on, say it.
C-C-C-Co...
Co...
Fumika, show her how it's done.
Okay.
C-o-c-k!
You got it? That's it!
So erotic!
That's your homework until next time.
It'll be okay, all you need is practice... I think.
Um...
How can you say something like that so easily?
Well, it is my job.
Isn't it embarrassing for you, though?
Well, of course it is! But when I'm acting, it's like I'm taken over by the character.
Taken over by the character?
The person who's talking and doing all those perverted things... it isn't me. It's the character.
I think you'll find it a bit easier if you think of it like that.
It's all about using your imagination and concentrating on completely becoming your character.
Imagination and concentration?
Have you ever played an eroge?
Of course I haven't!
Alright, make sure you play this.
It's what they call a "fap game".
W-Why? No way!
Don't you think it's strange for an eroge voice actress to have never played an eroge?
I can't believe I'm playing an eroge on a Sunday morning...
It starts with a dirty scene!
Good morning, Master.
Your cum's so thick
and tasty in the morning, Master!
She's licking it...!
Why?
It's "thick"? Does it taste different?
He's putting it in her butt!
How?! Why?! Wait, does it even fit?!
Ah, Master's cock's going so deep inside me!
The pictures are intense, but so are the words...
I can picture the scene again...
A voice actress said all these lines, huh?
I don't think I can say things like this...
It's all about using your imagination and concentrating on completely becoming your character.
This isn't the time to give up!
Imagination and concentration...
I am that girl. I am that girl.
That feels so good.
That voice... sounds like it feels really good.
Does it really feel that good?
I... want to do that too...
Yes, I want more...
I want you to stir up my pussy with your cock!
I... want you to... stir up my pussy... with your cock!
It's inside! Your cock feels so good!
Your cock!
Your cock, it feels so good...
Master, you're the best!
Master...
I can't hold it in anymore!  I'm coming!
Oh, no! What? No way...
No... No, no!
A text message?
It's from Onee-chan...
Got it.
No way! I almost came without even touching it?!
I'm never playing an eroge again!
Kanna-chan! Long time no see!
Eh?! Hioki Onii-chan, why are you here?
Do you two know each other?
Nagatoshi is an old friend.
I've known Kanna-chan since she was born.
She'd say, "I'm going to marry Onii-chan when I get older!" when she was little.
I'm so glad that Kanna-chan's going to help us out with our games!
Nagatoshi's the one who wrote the scenario for that fap game I gave you.
That means... I almost came from a scenario written by Onii-chan?
Telling from the look on your face, you must have really enjoyed that game.
Onee-chan, you idiot!
I guessed correctly?
Anyway, being compatible with his writing is a good thing.
The next game you're voicing is also written by Nagatoshi.
Here you go.
Make sure that you study the script carefully and practice.
Why don't we give it a go?
You had homework, too.
No way?!
Wow, that's great!
I want to hear Kanna-chan's performance too.
Okay, this one.
This... This is pretty harsh...
Well, you were going to say this sooner or later.
B-But...
Listen up. Say it like you really feel good.
With a smile.
O-Okay.
Alright, try it!
Your cock...
It's so hot... and hard... and it feels so good...
Wow, that was excellent! I know you're embarrassed, but you can do it!
O-Okay.
The last hurdle she has to clear is that.
Oh, that ?
"That"?
What's "that"?
Slurping noises.
Slurping... noises?
In a fellatio scene, you have to make it sound like you're really sucking a penis.
Naturally, you can't read it like a normal line.
To elaborate... Fumika.
Okay.
Dewicious.
Really perverted!
We can't use sound effects, so the voice actress has to make all the noise herself.
If you don't learn this skill well, you won't qualify as an eroge voice actress.
Is it... like this?
That's not it.
I need to use more saliva.
Then it goes in...
and out...
and I lick around the top and the sides...
What are you doing?
It seems pretty indecent.
Hey, hey! What was that?
N-Nothing!
Don't worry about it!
It just doesn't sound right.
I wonder what I'm doing wrong?
It lacks eroticism.
Sure, you're making some noises, but it doesn't give off the feeling that you're really sucking a cock.
Well, I've never sucked one.
Want to go try it out on Nagatoshi, then?
I guess that won't fly.
Come on.
I've thought of a different method.
Here, suck on this.
I think you can get a better sense of what's needed by actually sucking someone else.
If his cock is unacceptable, his finger should be fine, right?
Is it really okay, Onii-chan?
It's going to get all sticky with my saliva.
I don't mind if it's you, Kanna-chan.
O-Okay...
Onii-chan's finger is warm... and thicker than it seems.
Hurry up and start practicing the slurping noises.
Pretend it's a cock.
Watching this is a bit exciting.
Kanna, ask him if he likes it.
Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels amazing.
I'm so glad...
Onii-chan is able to feel good because of me.
I didn't think this could make him so happy!
This feels embarrassing, but...
I want to make him feel even better!
Looks like she's gotten the hang of it.
Kanna-chan is incredible, isn't she?
Once she gets passionate about something, she becomes completely absorbed into it.
I can't wait for the recording.
Breathing life into a character...
Can I accomplish something like that?
Just make sure you stay calm.
If you do what you practiced, you'll be just fine.
Start from line YA-0001.
Y-Yes sir!
O-Okay. You're checking this out?
Alright, please use this card to write your na-
Okay, from the top.
Say "take two" before you start.
Take two.
O-Okay. You're checking this out?
Y-Y...
Okay. You're checking dis bout?
Sorry...
Take four!
W-What am I going to do?! I keep screwing up!
Wow, she's really tense.
Well, that's to be expected.  It's her first recording.
Kanna, you're too tense.
Relax all that tension in your shoulders,
then say "pussy" ten times.
Why?!
Just say it!
O-Okay.
Pussy... Pussy... Pussy...
Your voice is too low!
Pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy, pussy...
Louder!
PUSSY!!!
Okay, go back to recording.
What was that for? She just felt like making me say that?
Um...
O-Okay. You're checking this out?
Alright, please use this card to write your name, year, and class.
I said it!
Looks like she calmed down.
It just takes time for her to get into the groove.
Alright, so far so good.
Now, I need to use my powers of imagination and concentration to become my character.
W-What, Katayama-kun?
"Why?" you ask?
I'm the librarian, after all.
Yeah, you're right.
Wow, not only did I just feel like I could see the scene, I even heard his voice!
That sounds pretty good!
Her acting skills still need a lot of work, but she's really working hard.
However, the real part starts here.
Yeah, there's the masturbation scene after this.
I-I can't control my fingers! They just can't stop!
As we expected, terrible.
Well, we never got to practice this part.
It looks like we're going to have to try the other strategy.
Kanna, we're going to take a break.
O-Okay!
Um... I changed my clothes.
Go run for 30 minutes.
I don't really get why, but...
I'm going, then!
What's the meaning of this?
After she gets back tired and out of breath, her performance should be more captivating.
Such a crude method...
Kanna was on the track team, wasn't she?
Yeah.
She specializes in mid and long-distance running.
Oh, that must be why she didn't seem exhausted after recording for such a long time.
I practiced so much, and yet I'm still so embarrassed.
I'm having a really hard time.
But...
I've gotta give it my all!
I'm back!
Okay.
O-Onii-chan?
Nagatoshi is going to sit there, so perform while looking at him.
Let's do our best, okay?
Uh, okay.
That feels good...
You can touch it again if you want...
My... pussy...
To be saying such embarrassing things in front of Onii-chan...
Katayama-kun, let me touch yours, too.
I want to touch yours, too!
Your penis...
Her voice is way more erotic now.
If we add that finger fellatio we tried the other day, it'll be perfect.
The fellatio scene...
Whenever I think about what happened before, I get so turned on!
Does that feel good?
Katayama-kun... so big...
Tasty...
This is what it tastes like?
It's so delicious!
It tastes so good!
She sounds really turned on all of a sudden.
The finger fellatio turned on a switch inside of her.
It's so hot... and hard!
It feels so good!
Amazing!
There's something wrong with me...
I felt so embarrassed saying this until just now.
More... Fuck me more!
It's making me quiver!
My mind's going blank!
Oh... Oh no, stop!
I'm going to... I'm going to come!
Oh no, not again...!
No, this is worse than last time...
I can't! I need to stop, everyone's watching me...
I can't stop!
You came so much...
There's so much...
cum inside of me!
You made me feel so good!
Good work!
Kanna, you did well.
You were great, even though it was just your first time.
Onee-chan...
Thanks. Keep up the good work!
Okay!
By the way, you definitely had an orgasm earlier, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
Come on, it was so obvious.
That's pretty intense.
Hioki-san, you didn't touch her, did you?
Nope.
It's usually impossible to do that just with your imagination, isn't it?
Impossible for sure.
But, that's really amazing!
Yeah, I've seen all sorts of voice actresses, but never one who can do that.
You're doing something not even Fumika can do, Kanna.
You should have more confidence in yourself.
Being an eroge voice actress just might be your calling.