I... I'm coming!
I'm...
Oh no, this is bad!
Is every guy in the country going to hear this?
Oh my God, I've done something unspeakable!
Th-There's my name!
I wonder if anyone will find out?
Good work, people!
Great job!
I believe Kanna-chan is our MVP, isn't she?
Of course she is!
Really? Little old me?
She's right!
They said you weren't acting during the climax scene!
Wh-Wh-What?
God, that's so hot!
Hey, be more sensitive, Natsumi!
Still, we completed our project thanks to you, Kanna.
Onee-chan...
Good morning everybody!
Hey!
Good morning!
Sakanami-san!
Ah, sorry for being late!
So you're Kanna-chan? Yayoi's little sister?
Ah, yes.
Nice to meet you. I'm Aoyagi Kanna.
So you're really a high school girl?
Yeah.
I love that school uniform! You're sixteen?
My cock salutes you!
Hey!
We're being watched.
By whom?
A boy is staring this way intently.
A boy?
He was looking, wasn't he?
You do attract a lot of guys, Hazuki.
I thought so too at first, but now I think he was looking at you, Kanna.
Why?
He was eying you differently.
How so?
Eighty percent of the time, people look at me like some sort of cute animal.
The other twenty percent are creepy lolicons
Onii-chan, I feel funny! I'm scared!
who want to molest me while I call them "Onii-chan."
You lewd girl, you're already dripping wet.
Yuck, gross.
With Hazuki, about a hundred percent of them are mentally undressing her,
Yes, come on me!
stroking their you-know-whats between her breasts until they give her a facial.
They are?
I'm starting to lose my appetite.
There are guys who look at you, Kanna, but not the way Kaizu-kun does.
How do they look at me?
As a spunky girl.
Maybe Kaizu-kun likes you.
Maybe he's wondering if you're available.
I could see that.
That can't be true!
Why not?
It can't be!
I don't attract guys.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Man, did that break your glasses?
I'm sensing a thing between you two!
Tell us if there are any developments.
Stop him, Motoki!
What if...
they're right?
But I like my Onii-chan, Hioki.
Still, I guess I don't think of him romantically.
If Kaizu-kun really does really like me...
Wh-What am I thinking?
Jeez, it's all because Hazuki and Kotori were giving me weird ideas.
K-Kaizu-kun!
Aoyagi-san, are you going home now?
Yeah, I just got done with practice.
I-Is that so? I've just finished my class rep work.
Good for you.
Thanks.
This is awkward.
I can't stand it!
B-Bye!
Oh, wait!
Huh?
U-Um, do you have a minute?
Wh-What is it?
This is really difficult, but I have to ask you something.
I may be putting you on the spot, but...
Oh my God, is he really...
Aoyagi-san, do you by any chance...
work as an eroge voice actress?
H-How did you know, Kaizu-kun?
Ah, so it was you, Aoyagi-san.
I've been meaning to ask you.
He knows! He knows! He knows! He knows! He knows!
Onee-chan!
It's over! Someone in my class found out!
What's going on?
Now it'll spread throughout the school!
That's not going to help.
I can never go back to school!
I can't bear to see Kaizu-kun again!
Oh, his name was Kaizu?
Yeah.
You don't need to worry about him. He's not going to tell.
Why not?
Perfect timing, actually.
Can you come to the office after school tomorrow for a meet-and-greet?
Huh?
Okay.
This is the president of the firm that's going to collaborate with us on the next project.
I'm Kaizu of Studio Kaizer.
Nice to meet you. I'm Aoyagi Kanna.
Kaizu?
Mr. Kaizu here has worked with Nagatoshi and me ever since we started out.
Good morning!
That looks like... Kaizu-kun?
H-Hey.
So there you have it. He's Mr. Kaizu's son,
and he helps out at work, just like you.
Oh.
So you're in the same class as Motoki, eh?
Um, yes, sir.
Now I get it. You heard about me from your father.
Yeah.
However, I heard it first from your sister.
She didn't mention your name, but she told me to be nice to her little sister, the voice actress.
You had the same last name, so I started wondering.
Onee-chan! Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Sorry, I forgot.
I should've known.
I see. So that was why you kept looking at me.
Oh, sorry.
It's okay. Actually, I thought...
Thought what?
Oh, forget what I said!
I almost forgot to tell you.
From now on, Motoki will be your rehearsal partner, okay?
Onee-chan, you idiot!
Cum tastes so good!
So good. So yummy!
I want to drink more! I want more cum!
Th-This is really extreme.
Mr. Kaizu's firm specializes in extreme titles.
By the way, cum is another word for semen.
Am I supposed to say that? In front of Kaizu-kun?
Yup.
I can't!
I feel for her.
Yes, you will!
My cock just got hard.
Where's Onii-chan?
Nagatoshi has to stay at the library and write another script,
so he won't be coming for a while.
But it's totally embarrassing to recite eroge lines to a boy from my own class!
I'll also be seeing him every day in school, not just at work!
He'll think I'm some pervy girl who says X-rated lines like they're nothing!
I can't deal with that!
I'll simply die!
L-Look, Aoyagi-san.
I'll never think of you as a pervy girl.
I respect eroge voice actresses.
They always soldier on, despite having to saying those embarrassing lines.
It may be their job, but they still need a lot of courage to say them.
But Aoyagi-san, you're doing it even though you're still in tenth grade.
I think that's fantastic.
So don't worry. I'll be very happy working with you.
Okay.
I'll do it.
I'm so moved!
Cum!
Fill my mouth with your load!
You came so hard! Your cum tasted awesome!
I think that's how it should go.
Have you got the character down?
I know what she's all about, but...
But what?
Ask me if you're unsure of something.
Okay, I'll go ahead and ask.
You know how the girls are a-always sucking penises?
Oh, you mean blow jobs?
Why do they suck on them?
Are you actually serious?
High school girls are supposed to know that!
Now, now...
Kanna-chan, the thing about blow jobs is...
a mouth feels ten times better than a hand!
Hell, I'd suck myself off if I could!
But alas, my body isn't built for that!
That's why I need someone else to suck it for me,
but another guy would disgust me,
so I need a girl to do it!
Understand?
Completely.
Any other questions?
Yes, one more.
Oh, ask us anything.
In this game, the girl sucks penises, swallows semen, and says it's delicious, correct?
That's right.
Does it really...
taste good?
Th-Th-That's...
That's an excellent question!
I know this'll be unbelievably embarrassing, but I'll let you suck my cock-
Don't!
Yeah, technically, cocks taste salty, just like fingers.
I can't really describe how semen tastes. You'll have to find out for-
Yayoi-san, that's going too far!
But that's the only way she'll know.
Yayoi-san!
Let me handle this!
What are you going to tell her?
Kanna-chan, you see, semen...
tastes just like condensed milk!
That's because semen is white, just like milk!
Shouldn't you stop her? She's giving her bad information!
I guess it is...
Plus it's very sweet and delicious!
Nah, I think this may work with Kanna.
And because of that, won't cocks taste sweet too?
If you suck on them, that sweetness keeps coming!
This girl climaxes just from fantasizing.
If you tell her it's delicious, she'll act that way, right?
Yeah.
Kaizu-kun, when did you begin helping with your dad's work?
Uh, in seventh grade.
What?
It was weird growing up around eroge.
I know.
People would freak if they discovered our line of work.
It'll be our little secret.
Yeah.
Aoyagi-san.
Huh?
I was actually kind of happy to find out it was you.
I couldn't talk to my classmates about this until now.
If you don't mind, can I keep on discussing it with you?
Oh, I was thinking the same thing!
Actually, this is my first time touching a boy's hand.
Thanks. I'm glad we met.
I'm also glad I met you.
What do you think?
Something has definitely happened between them.
And I think I know what.
Hazuki, Kotori, do you want to get some juice?
Congrats!
Congratulations!
What?
Oh, you've finally bagged one, Kanna!
So how did he ask you out, you she-devil?
Ask me out?
Kaizu-kun asked you to be his girl, and now you're dating him, right?
No, he didn't!
Huh? But you were just having a deep conversation with him.
We were just-
Today's rehearsal is supposed to start from the sex scene in the library, right?
Yeah. Page 52 in the script.
Sakanami also said we're doing the oral scene in the classroom afterwards.
Oh, okay.
W-We were just...
So something did happen.
Nothing happened, I swear!
But you've never spoken to Kaizu-kun before.
If you're not seeing him, then what's going on?
I can't really say.
You've been can't-really-saying a lot lately.
You're guarding more secrets than the KGB!
I simply can't tell them.
I love drinking it straight from your cock.
Because this is what I'm doing.
Aw, man...
An actual high school girl is fighting her embarrassment to say those X-rated lines.
My cock got hard!
Hey, cut that out!
That's sexual harassment, Senpai!
You are such a major league dunce.
What did you say?
A hard cock is the greatest compliment ever!
And Kanna's sex appeal got my blood flowing
and made my cock rock-hard!
You can't be...
Motoki, you're popping a boner now, aren't you?
Uh, I'm not really affected anymore.
What? You need a pill or something at your age?
You're wrong!
Then what's wrong with you?
It's not that at all.
I know this hurts the voice actresses, who put a lot of work into saying those dirty lines,
but I'm not turned on by them.
You're so upright, Motoki-kun.
Still, you worry too much.
Oh.
I started out in eroge,
but even though I'm also doing anime, I'm not going to quit eroge.
Why not?
Eroge is where it all began, of course.
I'll continue working in it, with pride.
I see.
I understand your position, but...
All right!
Fumika! Kanna-chan! Give Motoki a hard-on with your acting!
Huh?
Eroge voice actresses are supposed to make a guy hard!
Now show your pride, and give him a boner!
This is really stupid.
But if that's how you're going to be...
My pussy feels so good!
More... More... Make my pussy wet!
I'm com- I'm coming!
Um, sorry, it wasn't really...
Sakanami-san, I'm outraged!
Yeah, you should be.
I really thought you were a total idiot for making me do this,
but thanks to this, I've learned something very important!
See, I told you! You still deserve a beating later.
You're up, Kanna-chan!
Even though Fumika-san failed?
Trust me! I'll even tell you a killer trick!
Okay...
Listen...
What?
I can't say that!
Relax. Just think of it as another line.
Now do it!
U-Um...
I can't do oral scenes very well because I don't have any experience.
So I was wondering if you'd let me suck your penis for practice.
And if it's all right, can I taste your semen?
Huh, what's wrong?
Are you hard? Didja pop a boner?
Just because she asked me that...
doesn't mean I got an erection!
Motoki-kun, give me another chance, just one more chance!
Give me a break, will you?
N-No... What's wrong with me?
Why did I feel happy about that?
Because of rehearsals, we have to walk between school and the office every day.
We should take a breather now and then.
Here.
Thank you.
Time to eat.
Oh no!
Wow...
What?
Actually, the thought of practicing with you made me embarrassed.
But now I'm going to do whatever I can, if it will help you out.
Kaizu-kun.
Huh?
I can smell the prime of youth.
No! You've got it all wrong!
And it's sweeter than honey.
All right!
Let's do that scene.
Do we really have to?
Who else is going to do it?
Come on, get on with it!
A-All right...
O-Okay.
Will it work?
Are you ready, Kanna?
H-Hold on.
How about you, Motoki?
Uh, yes, I'm ready.
So many people.
Don't worry about them.
Just do it like we rehearsed, and we'll be fine.
Y-You're right.
We've been practicing a lot.
Now all I need to do is make my powers of imagination and concentration work for me.
I'm ready!
We're starting from line WA-0001.
If you please!
Good morning, Momoka!
Hey, stop hitting on Momoka!
Christ, she has a mouth on her.
Ah, I can see it!
So does this mean I'm completely focused now?
Come on, he's not as bad as you think.
Momoko doesn't go out with hoodlums like you!
Me?
I'm Fujisawa Wakana, the hall monitor!
What do you think?
I think it's great. I can really feel the scene.
We still have a ways to go, though.
Can Motoki put her into a trance state?
Why are you unzipping yourself?
You're not putting that in my mouth, are you?
A-Are you stupid?!
The moment of truth.
Even at that...
Kaizu-kun is watching me suck.
This is embarrassing.
Still, it sort of feels different from Onii-chan.
That time I felt a bit happy.
All I feel now is embarrassed!
It's no use. She's not entering a trance state.
What's that?
Once Kanna gets in a certain mood, she falls into a trance.
In order for Kanna, who has no experience, to do sex scenes,
she has to enter a trance state, or else she's useless.
It went well when we had her suck on Hioki's finger, but now...
I see.
With Motoki as her partner, we'll need to change the conditions.
Yeah.
For now, I'll send Kanna out running,
while we focus on improving her chemistry with Motoki.
Nagatoshi was her childhood friend, so their relationship is already at the maximum.
Her chemistry with Motoki doesn't need much improvement, just a little bump-
Um, Yayoi-san.
This isn't a dating sim, you know.
I know that!
But you say our chemistry needs a bump.
I'm not saying it's bad. She has no problem sucking your finger.
All that's keeping her from sucking your cock is sheer embarrassment.
I think you're getting off track.
In that case, she can suck my...
Nobody asked you!
I'm back.
Come in.
How about you get a good feel for Motoki's cock?
How about I don't?
Okay, how about you see a cock up close?
No way!
All right, how about smelling a cock?
You can always try getting boned by a cock!
Not going to happen!
Do you have any ideas, Fumika?
Well, what if they kiss?
I can't do that either!
Jeez, you're so fussy.
Fine, how about just hugging?
I guess I can do that.
What? Are you sure?
Squeeze her tight, Motoki, before she changes her mind!
Here?
O-Okay, are you ready?
Y-Yeah.
I... feel really close to him.
I can even smell him.
Oh no, I must smell sweaty!
Um, Kaizu-kun, I...
Motoki, you're not hugging her tight enough! Do it harder!
Uh, right.
This feels different from being with Onii-chan.
I can feel his heart beating.
His breathing... His scent...
Is this how it feels to be hugged?
Looks we got her into a trance state.
Really?
Yes, let's begin recording.
Oh, this is nothing like before.
A blow job from a high school girl!
My cock got hard.
Motoki, take it out.
I never thought I'd actually use it.
It's sweet. Just like condensed milk.
Condensed milk...
The taste of semen.
So this is how semen tastes?
I want more!
Oh yes! Stroke my pussy!
Fill up my pussy with your cum!
So good...
Ah, it's coming again!
Oh God...
I-I can't stop it!
I'm com- I'm coming!
I came again, this time in front of Kaizu-kun!
Aoyagi-san!
Hey, Kaizu-kun?
I'm so embarrassed, I can't even look at him!
Kanna, do you have a minute?
What is it?
K-Kaizu-kun?
What?
We'll be leaving.
Buh-bye!
Um...
Uh!
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Sorry because I kept running away from you.
I've never been hugged by a guy like that.
I got embarrassed.
Oh, don't worry about that. I know it must be embarrassing.
I also want to apologize,
for how extreme that project was.
But you were really great! You worked hard, and it showed.
I owe you yet another apology.
That hug put you off, didn't it?
Why should I-
Don't say that.
Because of that, I was able to perform well.
I want to become even better. I'll do my best.
A-All right.
I want you to teach me more.
Sure.
Shoot, we need to let go, Aoyagi-san.
We're being watched.
She hugged him.
She's really taking the bull by the horns.
Y-You're wrong!
I wonder what will happen after this?
I can't wait!
You're wrong!