Front Innocent
Urushihara Satoshi's
First Directorial Production
When I grow up I'm going to become Big Brother John's wife!
We're not siblings, so you can call me John, Fey.
No, Big Brother John is Big Brother John.
When I grow up, I want to leave this village and become a doctor.
Then we'll help you!
Right, Sophia?
We're both going to marry Big Brother John, right?
I...
Hmm?
I will serve you my entire life, Miss Fey.
Enter.
Sophia.
It is time.
Another Lady Innocent
Sophia, you don't have to do this...
Sophia, I have a favor to ask you.
While I'm gone, I need you to take care of John.
Yes, Miss Fey.
Sophia...
I promised Miss Fey I would.
Besides...
I really don't mind...
...because Miss Fey loves you, Master John.
Sophia, if you do that, it is going to come out.
You can let it come out in my mouth, Master John.
It feels so good...
Master John.
Please do exactly what you do to Miss Fey, Master John.
It's inside me. It's inside me!
Master John is inside me.
I'm going to come...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
No!
Please stop!
Let me go home!
Stop thrashing!
Take her away.
We're not done with you yet.
Is that...
She is back at last.
That's enough already, Aine.
No, sir.
This is part of my job.
However...
...this happens at all of the manors.
Eichel, say something to her.
It is part of our job, sir.
Do you not like us, sir?
No, that's not it.
Then look after me well, sir.
Oh, do as you like.
Yes!
Oh, Master!
This feels so good!
More, more!
Sir, I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Welcome home, Miss Fey.
Where is Father, Bill?
He is in the study.
Diana, Ruby, Josie, Priscilla...
...Stella, Ann, I'm home!
Oh, Miss Fey!
She hasn't changed a bit.
Master!
More! More!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Father!
Fey!
Fey...
I told you not to come in here!
But I've been studying at Aunt Martha's for two months!
Oh, I think it is okay, Uncle.
Fey is old enough to know what happens between men and women.
Sister Jane.
Welcome home, Fey.
How was it?
Everyone was kind to me...
...but all I could think about was home.
Oh, I love the way you smell, Jane.
I bet there are a few people you can't wait to see.
I bet they feel the same way.
Where are they?
I haven't seen them for a while.
I think they're in your room.
I'm home!
I'm home.
Miss Fey!
Miss Fey! Miss Fey!
Welcome home, Miss Fey!
I told you to call me Fey when we're alone.
But...
I'm home, Sister Sophia.
Welcome home, Miss Fey.
Now.
Welcome home, Fey.
Big Brother John.
Big Brother John!
Fey.
Big Brother John.
I'm going to be Big Brother John's wife!
Fey.
I'm home...
...where I belong.
Big Brother John.
Fey...
Miss Fey.
Sophia.
You're beautiful, Fey.
Big Brother John.
Fey.
Brother, I love you, I love you...
Fey...
Brother...
You are beautiful.
Big Brother John.
If you touch there...
...it makes me crazy!
I...
You're so wet, Fey.
No! That's dirty!
I've been traveling since morning, and I haven't had time to bathe.
There is no place on your body that's dirty.
But...
Big Brother John.
Yes...
No...
It feels so good...
Big Brother John.
I want it...
Big Brother John! I'm going to come!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Go ahead Fey, come.
I want you to come...
John, John!
I'm coming!
I'm coming again!
I love the way you smell, Big Brother John.
Big Brother John!
The horse that Miss Fey was riding went wild, and Master John saved her...
But in the process...
He's going to be fine.
I'm going to take care of Big Brother John.
I'm going to! I'm going to!
You do that, Fey.
I'm sure that will make John happy.
Fey.
Big Brother John.
I'm sorry.
I'm so glad you weren't hurt.
My sister and I...
...were sent from place to place until we came here.
Just when I didn't think I could trust anyone anymore...
...you let me into your life with a smile.
Ever since then, I...
I decided to live my life for you.
What is wrong, Fey?
Big Brother John.
I love you.
Master John!
Don't look!
No! Don't look!
Master, don't look!
Don't look!
Don't look at me!
If you don't stop, I...
He's going to see me come!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Yes, Yes!
John!
I'm coming!
Fey...
Sophia, come and eat with us.
Come on!
I am your servant.
But...
Please, let me serve you, Miss Fey.
Fey, why don't you let Sophia do as she pleases?
But...
By the way, where were you?
I, um...
Were you looking around the grounds?
Um, yes, that's it...
Was everything okay?
Yes, it was!
I see, I'm glad.
Miss Fey.
Sophia.
Are you sure?
Aren't you tired?
I promised, didn't I?
My nights belong to you.
Miss Fey!
I love you. I love you so much!
Fey!
Sophia, say hello to Fey.
This is Sophia. She will be looking after you from now on.
Nice to meet you, Sophia.
I'm Fey!
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Miss Fey.
Since that day, my heart has belonged to you.
Sister...
Sister Sophia...
Sophia, I want to climax with you.
Yes, Miss Fey...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Me too...
Miss Fey.
Sophia...
Sister Sophia...
Won't you tell me?
What is it, Michael?
Aren't you going to accept it?
It is an invitation.
That's right, John.
If you say no, we can no longer live here.
We have no choice, John.
It is so different from our house.
Yes, it is.
I'm looking forward to it.
Welcome to my home.
I hope you enjoy tonight's party.
Wonderful!
No!
Front Innocent