Why don't you just give up?
Though I want to see how a
serious girl like Shirakawa-san pees.
You haven't done it once since this morning right?
It's because you people didn't let me!
What defiant eyes.
But she's been really restless for a while now.
It looks like she's just about at her limit now.
N... No! I don't want to pee myself in
front of everyone in a place like this.
I don't want to let it out!
Don't waste our time, just hurry up and show it to us.
I'll help you out.
Please don't do something like that!
I'll really let out a lot.
Let's have you show it to us more clearly, huh?
Sto-Stop it!!
In this sort of position... I look just.
Just like a dog right?
Shirakawa-san is doing her best isn't she?
Her anal and pussy and in plain sight.
Well then. Lets have her pee even if we have to force her.
Ok.
No!
I... I'm feeling weak.
He's rubbing it...
I can't... Even though I need to hold it in.
Come on, come on. Its fine, ok?
Come on, just let it go.
It'll come out... It'll come out! It'll come out!!
Ohhh~! It's coming out, it's coming out.
It looks like you're feeling good, Sumire-chan.
I guess the amount of pleasure is different in a place like this.
It came out huh.
Huuh?
It looks like a different sort of liquid is coming out though.
That's no good.
We have to properly wipe it up.
This is quite the problem. If you wear
your panties like this, they'll get all sticky
I took something from you, so how
about I give you something in return?
This time. Let's see.
Why not do it inside the train again?
Come Shirakawa-san. Hurry up, hurry up!
If you don't do as we say.
The everyone will find out that you were
talking your boobs out in a train the other day.
Come on, start sucking!
S-So dirty...
Like I'll lick some place that pee comes out from.
If you don't hurry up, the people
around us will notice you know.
I... I get it already.
Shirakawa-san, you need to lick it like it's something tasty.
You can study and everything but, you're
completely useless at this sort of stuff aren't you?
Just shut up would you?
Being able to lick this well isn't something to be proud of.
It's just lewd.
I guess there's no helping it.
Here! This is how you do it!
That's good, suck more tightly!
W-Why...?
Even though I'm being used like a toy.
My body is becoming hot.
Have I changed?
Well, it's because until now, you've been
experiencing the most extreme of the situations.
You might not remember them but...
Your body is reacting as if it did.
Your pussy is so sensitive that it gets
completely wet just by the smell of a dick now.
It feels incredibly good, Sumire-chan.
Your skin is so soft...
that just from rubbing it like this.
I'll cum right away.
What is this...
Is this... again?!
Dream...? Is this a dream?
Shirakawa-san, you're totally into it now.
You're acting like a sex doll, or should I say a mouth pussy?
That's good. Come on, make him cum with your mouth pussy!
I... If it's a dream.
Then hurry... hurry up and just end already!
Please... Just... Stop already!
I'm about to cum soon so.
Make sure you drink it all!
Idiot... Just what the hell are you doing?
Take it all in with your mouth!
You're all sticky with semen.
Just how do you plan on going home like this. Shirakawa-san?
This is semen?
So hot and sticky.
Its alright.
I'll properly wipe it off before you open up your eyes.
That's right!
I guess I'll leave some on your forehead.
After the semen dries.
After all, it's a place you can't even smell by yourself.
Ehh~? That definely means he was inviting you.
You should have just tagged along.
No, no. There's no way.
Besides his purpose must be just doing it all along.
Even though they were doing
something like that to me yesterday.
Today they're ignoring me?
Just what does this mean?
As I thought. Was that just my.
Just a dream all along?
But.
But then exactly why does.
My that place feels so fidgety?
Something troubling you?
Sumire-chan.
We meet again huh.
Can you please stop referring to me as if you know me?
I believe I told you the same thing before.
Please don't call out to me inside the school.
Ah~ My bad my bad.
Well you see? I just heard a strange rumor.
A strange rumor?
They say that you're being bullied by the girls in your class.
Even if I look like this, I am the school counselor.
I can help you if you want.
No thank you!
Besides, it's not like I'm being bullied or anything.
For example, what if I told you
a way to get back at those girls?
So... Something like that.
Well it's not too hard to pull off.
Just look at this for a second.
W-what are you doing?
Whatever... Just look at this carefully.
Huh?
What? Just what is this?
What...? Just what is this?
Its alright... You can just leave everything to me.
Ever thing will happen after school, ok?
We'll start from that girl.
Actually, I've already put a subliminal
suggestion in that girl's head.
Now all we have to do is pull the trigger.
H... Hey...
Ju... Just what am I doing?
M-My body is... moving... all on it's own.
Please stop... Don't... do something so lewd.
I-I'll look like I'm a pervert.
I... Its alright?
So girls like you really do exist!
I'm surprised.
Please stop... Just stop it!
Don't do any more dirty things to my body.
I have to get off on the stop after
the next one, so I'll make it quick.
Hey... stop it!
You're kidding right?
Really? Here?
Its so tight!
For a girl who fools around with guys all
the time, you have a really good pussy.
No...! Stop it!
I... Its wrong.
I... don't... f-fool around...
You wanted a dick really bad right?
Your pussy is all wet and slippery.
Why?
Even though I don't want this.
Why... is my body feeling good?
Please don't be... so rough!
If you do it anymore than this.
I... I...
Oh no... I have to hurry up... or else.
Its fine to let it inside right?
No... Don't... not inside.
Please not inside... outside.
I've never felt like this before... What is th...
Don't... Don't!!!
Nooo!!!
No way!
A... Amazing!
How about it?
Do you feel a little better now, Sumire-chan?
No... not really.
I've left the other girl to an acquaintance of mine.
By telling her that she's been
scouted for a model in a magazine.
I had her taken for an interview.
Of course that's all just a big lie.
Well then, could you change clothes?
Right here...?
Yeah that's right.
We don't have any changing space in the studio you see.
But, thats a little.
It's fine it's fine.
We're used to this sort of stuff.
You don't have to worry about anything.
U-Um...
I'll change really quickly.
So could you just step out for a bit?
What, are you embarrassed?
Should I lend you a hand?
Wha... H-hey!!
It's fine it's fine.
Pl-Please stop this!
I-I can do it by myself.
Huh?
This is a cute bra, isn't it?
So I guess down there is also.
A matching one?
P-Please don't touch me!
I never heard I'd be doing something like this!
I'm telling you, it's completely fine!
Didn't we say that we'd be doing a swimsuit photoshoot?
Underwear is pretty similar to that right?
Eh? Hey! Why are you recording a video?!
Ohh~? Thats just film making. Making.
While we're doing it, I guess I'll have you show us everything.
N-NO!! Don't take it off!!
Noo!! Stop iiitt!!!
Please stop it! This is not modeling at all!
No! NO!!
Pl-Please no more. Forgive me, please forgive me!!
Come on come on! Don't cry. I'll be sure to make you feel good.
DON'T!!
Huh? Even if you say that, you're nipples are so erect.
Did you start to feel good?
T-T-Thats wrong... That isn't possible.
I'm...
That's good that's good! Start feeling it a lot more.
I'll make sure to record it perfctly.
I-It hurts!
The pussy is really stiff for some reason.
Could it be your first time?
Thats right, so please stop this.
Let me go!
Oh no, that's quite the problem!
You'll have to throw away your virginity immediately.
That's right that's right, to still be a virgin at your age...
That's a little embarrassing isn't it?
You're kidding me right! No way!!
B-But... I'm...
So tight...!
It hurts! No!
That's a great expression. Look over here!
N-Noo!
Please don't film.
This embarrassing self of mine.
Its alright, you'll start feeling good right away.
Please don't just decide that on your own!
Just take it out! Take it out!!
No no! We're just getting started after all.
Help me...! Someone please help me!!
Ook! I guess I'll do it more roughly now.
NO!! NO WAY!!
I'm losing it!!
Don't!! Noo!!
W-Why?!
Even though I'm just watching... my body's getting so hot.
I guess that was too much of a stimulation for her.
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
You seem to have started to feel it.
So let's end this with making Sumire-chan feeling good.
Huh? This place is?
Shirakawa.
What are you looking around so anxiously for?
Ku... Kurahashi-sensei?!
Just when did you come back?
What are you saying Shirakawa?
You're acting strange.
W-We can't do this sensei.
Didn't we decide together?
We'd hold off doing this...
Until I graduated.
That's why I waited until this day.
Look carefully.
Hu-huh?
Is this... me?
Hey, hey, get yourself together.
Hasn't it been years since you went to that school?
Is... that right...?
Then that means.
I... I am.
Se-sensei!
I've been waiting for this day to come for so long.
Thats why... right?
I see... Today with sensei... I...
With Sensei... I'm doing it!
I'll let him do me.
Shirakawa's boobs are so soft and feel so good.
N... No... Please don't say something like that.
Shirakawa, I'll strip you now, ok?
I-It's embarrassing!
No! Please don't do that!
If you rub it that much.
Th-That place is...
Shirakawa's place down here, has gotten so hot already.
Why?
Even though he just teased me a little.
This... To think that it feels this good.
I...
Do I really... have such a lewd body?
It's fine even if you become more and more lewd.
I... Is that alright?
Even if I become lewd?
I'm... already feeling strange.
Amazing... So big... So, this is Sensei's dick...?
Shirakawa, could you do it with your boobs?
Y-Yes.
It's my first time doing this so, I'm not
sure if I'll be able to do it properly.
H-How is it sensei?
Does it feel good?
Yeah... It feels really great.
S-Sensei's dick... is really hot and stiff.
Shirakawa's has also become so hot.
On top of that, its dripping wet.
It feels like it's going to melt inside.
Please... don't look at it so much.
Just because I was teased a little... I'm already!!
Eh?! Why... did milk came out from my boobs?
Isn't that good Shirakawa?
Now you can have my children whenever you want!
Kids... Sensei's and my baby!
Come on, don't rest.
Make me cum a lot with your boobs.
Yes!
Oh no! What's this!
My boobs are so slippery... It's even making me feel really good!
It's really tasty!
I'll bear it!
Sensei's and my healthy baby... I'll bear it!!
You don't actually have big tits so
we can't actually do a boob play.
But this is also pretty good.
Se-sensei...
I... I'm... already.
I get it.
I'll put it in.
Yes, sensei... put it... please put it in!
Shirakawa, are you alright?
Yes, I'm alright.
Sensei... P-please move.
I'm alright now.
Sensei's is going... inside.
So much!!
It's stirring me up!
Shirakawa! Shirakawa!! Shirakawa!!!
I wonder what happened to me?
Even though it's my first time.
It doesn't hurt at all.
To think... to think that sex felt this good!
It's touching me.
Sensei's thing is so deep inside.
It feels really amazing! Shirakawa's pussy is the best!!
That makes me happy.
More...! Please do it to me more!!
Feel more with my pussy!!
Shi-Shirakawa! If you move that much...
I'll...
It's fine, make me all sticky with sensei's fluids!
I'm going to cum!!
Yes...! Please...! Give it to me!
Finally... With sensei.
L-Let's cum together!!
She's making such a happy face.
Well, I guess it's fine.
Until Kurahashi comes back from his transfer,
I'll have fun with you, Sumire-chan.
Kurahashi... sensei...