Wouldn't it have been fine without the apron?
T-this outfit is embarrassing enough.
Huh?
This is it!
When you're talking about hospitals its got to be a nurse's uniform.
Its fine if I make it like this one right?
Thats right! Please do.
Kyaa!?
Noooo...
W-what does this mean?!
T-to forget the skirt... How embarrassing.
That was my bad.
Good good...
Oi! Its pointless without the top.
I can't make two parts at the same time.
Buu.
Kyaa! Hey! What are you doing?!
Wait for me! Shiinchi-san!
Nooo! This skirt is way too short.
– This is standard siz...
– SHUT! UP!!!
S-sensei... Sensei's dick...
Amano-sensei put it in.
Please rough up Sayako's place here.
Sensei... Me too.
Its amazing... Amano-sensei.
Huh...?
Maybe it wasn't this way...?
Um... Shiinchi-san...?
Are you here...?
Haa... will he notice if I leave the desk I wonder?
Hm?
Kyaa?!
Ah! I-I'm sorry.
U-Um...
Eh?!
Ahh...?!
N-Noo!!
NO!!
Noooo...
What happened all of a sudden?
Sto-Stop it please...
Ah... A-Ah! Noo...!!
Wait! Don't! Doooon't!!
It went in...
I let him in...
It just went in...
Fo-Forgive me Shiinchi-san.
The butt-hole that even Shiinchi-san had yet to violate... I...
E-Eeh?!
Eeeeeeii!!
Ahhhhn...
Yah!!?
Noo...!!
No!!
That's enough Saya-chan.
Wai...! No!
What-What is this...?!!
That's terrible! Lying to me about overtime.
You shouldn't interrupt the fun times of your husband you know.
Ma'am.
S-something like this! You must have
done something to my husband right?
Oh my... what makes you think that I wonder?
See?! Aren't you holding something like that?
What I want to say is.
Why do I have to have you suspecting me of an affair with him?
Because we are a married couple.
Then shouldn't we have fun together?
NO!!
Wait...
Shiinchi-san!!?
Che!
Making it troublesome.
– We can't just leave it be
– Kyaa?!
– We can't just leave it be.
What did you do that for.
That technology is not from Earth.
What does that mean?
Anyway, let's chase after them.
Of course!
Yoisho!
Hurry up!
What greed...
Their faces show desires that they
normally keep hidden deep inside them.
Its beautiful isn't it?
W-why are you all angry...?
No way! Is that thing controlling them?
There wasn't just one of them?
Its not them. Or more like, its not even a life form.
EH?!
But...
That's the ancient life form that lived on this
planet long before we outsiders came here.
That is...
An Alien!!
– Shiinchi-san?!!
– Their life energy have been extracted for now but
I can to restore it.
More importantly.
It would be troublesome if that girl takes us for enemies.
What should we do?
W-why...?!
Should I put up a defensive barrier?
Please do that without me needing to tell you.
What happened to your duty of
protecting me with your psychic ability?
Even this outfit is not perfect you know.
Whyyy?? Aren't I going out of my way
to wear somethin this embarrassing?
Coming here wearing something this risky.
Did you feel like getting in on the fun, Ma'am?
Since you're wearing that beautiful outfit.
I'll drown your body in pleasure.
Ok! Its a perfect situation.
I didn't think the people of this planet
had the ability to control us aliens.
I let my guard down.
I have to to save Shnnchi-san quickly.
Noo!
I-I can't muster up the power. Please do something Furuu-san.
T-This is...
The life energy caused by sex has taken on a counter force.
This woman possesses negative emotion related to sex.
Oh no! I can't control the flow of this negative energy and life energy.
The damage is piling up.
We have to find her weakness somewhere.
Preparation complete.
Mika-san...
Mika-san please fight.
We will recover while she is waiting. Please lend me a hand.
What do you plan on doing?
Halt her movements.
How do I do that? Don't you have some sort of weapon?
Well I can procure something blunt.
Anything is fine.
I will have to punish her for doing anything mean to Shiinchi-san!
Just what the hell is this?!!
Its a good match.
Here she comes!
YOUU!!! Take this!!
Mika-san...? Violence is not good you know... violence.
A... Angel...
I will have you learn the sin of taking one's husband.
Say... If they are aliens then that can't be the last of them right?
Uhh... That's how it is.
Then does that mean... this could happen again?
That's what it comes down to.
Eeeeh?
How many times do I have to deal with people like them?
At most seventy or so I think.
Sevent?! I don't think I can deal with that many in this lifetime.
It seems like we'll have a long relationship.
Please look after me in the future as well, Mika-san.
You don't say... It won't be as bad as this every time right?
Who knows.
In any case, capturing the escaped prisoners comes first.
We will take the most stubborn ones, one at a time.
Its fine you know. Even if you turn it on.
Angel you know... I saw one.
It looked just like you Mika.
A cute angel.
Huh?!
Its amazing, Mika!
You look like an angel.
Waiiit... Ahnnnn!!
Good...
Amazing! Its amazing Mika!!
Its like I'm having sex in a dream.
Nooo...
T-today... Together... Lets cum together today, okay?
Cumminnnngg!!!
Me too... Ahhhhnn!!
Such bliss...
That was the best, Mika.
That goes for me too.
Just when did you put it on? That apron.
Sorry. I'll take it off quickly.
It feels best with that bare skin action after all.
Huh?! Mika?!!
Eeeeee?!!! Goshh...!
But... I think I might like it. Ahh!!
If we could teleport, then dealing with that
sort of problem would've been easy right?
I'm sorry... I forgot.
Eeeehhh?!!
Madam is...
Mi-cha-e-l?