S-Sen... Sensei... We can't...
We will be seen here...
It's fine. No one comes around at this time.
Besides, we won't be able to see
each other for a while once I transfer.
It's alright. Even if you transfer, didn't
you say that you'll be back in 2-3 years?
Do-Don't do that sensei. You can't, I mean it.
I-I can't wait that long Shirakawa!
By your graduation, I... I'll already be.
D-D... Dear...
The last train will arrive shortly on Track 1.
Please stand to the side of the white line.
Sensei, I'll be waiting...
until sensei comes back.
Shirakawa!
Actually... before we are separated...
I have a favor to ask, Shirakawa.
W-what is it?
Tonight... I want us to masturbate together.
Tonight at exactly 10 O'clock.
While we're thinking about each other.
Compared to your normal masturbation,
it feels much more exciting right?
Even if you tell me something like that...
I don't even masturbate normally that often.
F-from sensei?
Um... "It's almost time isn't it, Shirakawa?"
"I'm already set up and just waiting over here."
S-Sensei is... waiting?
I-I wonder if I'm doing it right?
I can't really tell but...
S-Sensei is also... M-masturbating... Right now...
While thinking about me...
I have to play with myself down here as well.
F-For some reason... It feels a lot
better than when I usually do it.
W-why...? Even though I'm not
supposed to be such a lewd girl.
T-This is... Strange!
S-Sensei?
Right now... I'm masturbating while thinking about you.
It feels amazingly good.
If you start to feel good as well... Then
masturbate while being naked.
N-Naked...? No way!!?
What is it...? This feeling?
It's like electricity just ran through my body.
T-This is masturbation?
S-Sensei... I'm also masturbating right now.
While thinking about sensei... I'm
playing with my breasts and that place.
It's sensei's fault you know.
E-Even though I wasn't such a lewd girl.
It's because Sensei ordered me...
I-It's amazingly hot...
I think I might like it.
M-My body feels so light.
I'm starting to feel good.
I can't stop myself.
Sensei... Are you imagining this embarrassing side of me?
Are you masturbating to this lewd side of me?
I... I... already... I can't hold it anymore!
My body is going crazy!
I am starting to lose it!
Se-Sensei.
If I continue to do this.
I-I'll turn into.
A lewd girl.
Yo~ Sumire-chan.
It's been a while.
Have you been well?
I'm sorry.
Who might you be?
I see...
So you don't remember me.
It's a shame isn't it, Sumire-chan...
I remember you really well though.
Reeeally well.
Um. I really don't remember anything.
Can you please stop referring to me in as if you know me?
Ahhh... I apologize for that.
Well then.
Won't you drink coffee with me in the counseling room?
I'll say it again.
Won't you drink coffe with me in the counseling room?
I placed a subliminal suggestion on you.
When you hear these words, you'll
fall back in to your hypnotized state.
Ah! S-Sensei...
He's telling me to do something through a text again?
Huh?! S-Something like that!
Shirakawa, take off your clothes on
that train and show your boobs.
T-Take off my clothes here?
I-I can't do that!
Make sure you're properly standing while you strip.
Then take a picture of your boobs and send to me.
What if I get seen by someone...
B-But... I have to do it.
Because... it's an order from sensei.
Hurry up.
If I don't hurry up, we'll get to the next station.
Please... Don't let anyone notice.
Please don't look this way!
O... Ok!
My heart's beating really fast.
I can hear the beating of my heart.
I... I'm taking out my boobs inside a train.
This... This embarrassing appearance.
Next is Tsukiyushi station... Please exit to the right of the train.
I have to hurry... The picture!
Sensei will see this embarrassing appearance of mine.
What are you doiing? Shirakawa-san?
Getting naked in a place like this?
Could it be that... Shirikawa-san is an exhibitionist?
T-That's not it!
This is you see... just...
To think that the quiet honor student
Shirakawa-san was such a pervert?
That surprised me.
I have to tell everyone.
Please! Don't tell anyone about this!
Well its fine with me.
But in return...
I guess I'll have you listen to whatever we say.
What...? Just what do they plan to do to me?
Heh? Shirakawa-san, your appearance, it really suits you.
Come on! What are you hiding? Didn't
you promise to show us everything?
Hurry up! Show us everything!
I'm being looked at!
So small.
Small breasts are so cute.
This embarrassing part of me is being seen by all of them.
Didn't I tell you to show everything?
Turn around and show us your pussy and anus.
G-Getting ahead of yourself.
I won't forgive you!
Hurry Up!!
Stick your ass out and spread your legs.
The stocking is being sucked in!
You serious? You can see everything!
Damn...
Black tights on top of being naked. That really turns me on!
I... I have to endure. I have to endure!
I don't want to lose to this embarrassment!
I can't keep it in anymore!
Wha-What?!! Please stop! Noo!!
Just watching alone is no fun after all.
No... No way!
Didn't you promise to only watch?!
This smooth sensation... I can't get enough!
I'll try licking them.
To even have your legs
licked... Shirakawa-san, aren't you popular?
Stop... Stop! Stop!!
Even sensei didn't do something like this to me.
Well then... I'll be going ahead and use it.
The black tights are rubbing against me. I can't stop!
I... It's touching me.
This guy's hot and stiff thing is...
It feels so good!
You perverts. You perverts, perverts perverts!!
Ahhh... Everyone became so serious.
At this rate Shirakawa-san will be raped won't she?
Isn't that fine?
After all, she's a pervert who takes pictures
of herself while being naked in a train.
I see... Then she must be feeling good even like this right?
It looks like some sort of juice came out.
W-Wrong...! I'm not feeling...
I'm not feeling... good!
I absolutely won't become... W-what you guys want me to!
You're hanging in there quiet well aren't you, Sumire-chan?
This is... as I thought, the result of the experimenting until now.
Or could it be... That this isn't enough for you anymore?
What is this?!! Sto...!!
What is this person doing here?
It's no good. No matter how hard you try.
You can't run away anymore.
It's fine you know. Come on, just cum!!
Do-Dooon't!!!
It'll come out! The pee will come out!!!
It's not enough... I'll let you have much more.
Wh... What? Train?! Just when did I?!
Did't I tell you that I'll let you have more?
Well it looks like Shirakawa-san likes doing it inside trains.
So I thought that this way was better.
You can't let your voice out. Do you want everyone to notice?
I... I-I won't let you have your way like this forever.
You seem to be resisting a little but... This is acting right?
That's right. Shirakawa-san is a
pervert and an exhibitionist after all.
Of course she's just acting.
T-That's wrong... Don't just make stuff up like that!
For real? Then I guess I'll strip her.
T-That's wrong... Its not like that... Please forgive me!
We can see everything now! Let's do her!
Come on! Come on! Shirakawa-san! You want this right?
Come on, give it to us straight.
Let's take your stockings off and get started.
Wait! Stop! Stop it, please!!
Shirakawa-san, take care of this too, please.
N-NO way!!?
Shirakawa-san you're dripping wet already.
It stinks... So dirty.
No!... I've had enough!!
Here I go!
OOHH!! It's so damn tight!
It's also so tight here that my dick is throbbing.
There are big things inside down
there and my mouth... Amazing.
I beg you! Please don't be so rough.
Or I'll... I'll... Cum!
It's amazing! I'm already about to cum.
It's going deep into my throat.
Here, it's reaching my womb!
I beg you! Please don't be so rough!
Or I'll... I'll... Cum!
I... am starting to... starting to fee good!
Good... I'm cumming...! I'm cummmg!!
It's coming in. He's just doing whatever he wants.
It's also going deep in my throat.
I-Is it over now?
It's not over yet.
Everyone is waiting so hurry up and do them as well.
No-No way!!?
Please... Someone... Someone help me!
Sensei... Kurahashi-sensei.
Sumire-chan? It's alright.
So... Something like this... Can't be happening.
It's... It's got to be a dream.
This is all... A Dream!!
Thats right.
This is all a dream.
It was a dream right?
That's right. Something like that can't have happened.
Why am I in my uniform?
Th... That can't have happened... right?
It's alright. They're still on.
Wha... Whats this?
Thi... This is...?
Se... Semen? No way! It wasn't a dream?!
Just what the hell happened to me?!
Everyone's bullying towards me got even worse.
But you won't be able to look each
other in the eyes if you keep doing this.