I can see it!
I can see it thrusting in and out of me!
I can feel it reaching all the way to here.
Deeper!
Mina-san, I need to reach
all the way to your womb!
Huh? My womb?
You can't go all the way to there!
But...It feels so good, Akitoshi-san!
Please thrust it deeper
and deeper inside me!
Right there, Akitoshi-san!
That's my...!
I reached it!
I reached your womb, Mina-san!
Now I can just need to thrust it in there!
That's... That's my special technique!
It's pouring out!
You're cumming inside me!
It's so wonderful!
It's making me crazy!!
Mina-san, we did it!
Thanks to your special training.
I mastered my special technique!
I'm taking every last drop of
your special technique!
Huh?
Akitoshi!
What have you DONE!?
Hi-Hitomi-nee!
I'm never gonna have your baby!
This is a free fansub not for sale, rent or ebay.
Ane-Haramix
Volume 3
Brought to you by Haramix-subs
I guess this is what they mean by
"paying for your mistakes", huh?
But there are only a few days
before the date set by the shinigami.
Translation:
SaHa
Even after all that sex, it doesn't seem
as though Hitomi-nee's gotten pregnant at all...
Timing:
Timgorden11
At this rate, my life will be...
Akitoshi.
Y- Yes?
You want Mina-chan to have your baby
instead of me, right?
Onee-sama hates me, now...
I can't go on living...
A shinigami can't even make a baby with a human...
I feel like I'm completely useless to everyone!
I'll just kill myself now!
Huh!?
W-Wait a minute!
It's ridiculous for a shinigami to die, isn't it!?
Then what should I do?
Hitomi-nee and I need to get back together!
Well, yeah...
What Hitomi-nee doesn't like is the fact that we were doing it all by ourselves.
I get it! So she's jealous, right!?
That's right!
That's why we just need to invite Hitomi-nee to join us and it'll all be okay.
And how exactly are we supposed to do that?
First, you'll need to deepen your relationship with Hitomi-nee a LOT more.
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Well...
I'll explain the details later.
In any case, the keywords are...
hard work, friendship and victory!
I-I'm not sure I really understand,
but I guess it's all about
hard work, friendship and victory, right!?
Just like how you and I worked...
to perfect my Secret Technique!!!
I- I see!
And so...
I see. Understood, coach!!!
Um...
Is this really gonna work with all of this stuff?
Don't worry!
Even though you're both girls,
if you make can make her feel good,
she's bound to be happy.
Are you sure?
But... first of all...
is onee-sama really...
going to let me have sex with her?
No.
Which is why we're going to start
by forcing her a little bit.
We don't have much time, so we've gotta do this right!
I'm pretty sure they were in here...
Found 'em!
First...
We'll start by giving Hitomi-nee's body
pleasure with these!
Giving her body pleasure, huh!?
And her heart will follow after that!
Go, Mina-san!
Roger!
So...
What's this about a way
to make Hitomi-nee fall asleep?
Just leave it to me!
I'm still a shinigami.
So using magic to make a human fall asleep
is the easiest thing of all!
Ah...really?
Well then, here I go...
Huh!?
Y-y-you really did take her down,
but was that really...a magic spell!?
Oh, yeah! I "spelled" her good!
Wait a minute, Akitoshi!
What's going on here!?
Did you really think it was a good idea
to do this to your big sister!?
We want to talk to you, and clear away any misunderstanding you had about us.
So that we can get out relationship back on track -
You call this talking!?
Quit babbling on about nonsense,
and untie me right now!
It's not nonsense!
We genuinely want to get along with you, Hitomi-nee.
You- you've gotta be kidding me!
Why should I listen to a cheater like you!?
I realize that you're the only one
I can really depend on, Hitomi-nee.
And...
that's why I want us to get along.
So...
Let's all feel good together.
You idiot! You idiot! You IDIOT!!
My ass...
My clitoris...is going numb...
That's amazing, Hitomi-nee!
You're already soaked!
Th- that can't be true!
You think so?
Look at how honest your body's become, Hitomi-nee.
We both want you to be honest.
W-what are you saying...?
I still love you, Akitoshi.
But there's no way I'd forgive anyone
for doing something like this to me!
Guess there's no way around it.
Stop it!
Make it stop, Mina-chan!
Onee-sama...
I've never seen you look so naughty and pretty...
It makes me so happy!
You're both acting crazy!
They're going numb!
My nipples, my pussy, my asshole!
That's amazing, Hitomi-nee!
Hitomi-nee, you're totally soaked!
Amazing...
You're so pink and your juices are leaking out like crazy.
Don't look at me! Don't look at me!
Akitoshi...
Just let Mina-chan take your soul...
and die...
I want to make up with onee-sama...
That's why I'm gonna serve you with all of my heart!
Wh- what are you saying, Mina-chan?
Huh? No! Stop it!
I've researched all of your erogenous zones, Hitomi-nee.
Just a while ago, Akitoshi showed me a video of two girls getting along just like this.
And they looked like they were really feeling good!
I want to make you feel good too, onee-sama!
I'll try my very best for you!
You too, Mina-chan!?
Stop! Please stop!
Don't rub my nipples like that!
Onee-sama, my nipples and my pussy are tingling, too...
It's starting to feel so good!
It's delicious!	It's so delicious!
Akitoshi's dick!
In that case, shall I let you swallow my cum!?
I'll swallow it! I'll swallow it!
Give it to me!
Here we go, Hitomi-nee.
You're stretching me out!
Akitoshi, I can feel you inside
and even my ass is turning me on!
You're squeezing so tight, Hitomi-nee!
You want it, don't you?
I want it!
I want your dick, Akitoshi!
R- right there!
This is it!
This is the entrance to your womb!
I'm gonna pour my cum inside!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
If you pour that much inside me...
That's exactly why we're having sex, isn't it, Hitomi-nee!?
Akitoshi-san, you're the only one who did it!
That's no fair! I can't hold back, either!
Mina-chan!
Good! That's so good!
Onee-sama, you're shaking so happily!
I can feel it in my pussy, too!
Akitoshi's in my pussy and Mina-chan's in my ass!
Your dicks are rubbing against each other inside me!
I can feel it! It's reaching all the way to my womb!
It feels like I'm melting!
Me too! I think I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
O-Okay!
When we cum, let's all do it together!
J- just do what you want!
I'll do anything you ask, Akitoshi!
... the rubbing ...!
With this, I'm gonna make you pregnant, Hitomi-nee!
Onee-sama!
Do it! Do it, both of you!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
I'm gonna get pregnant with your baby, Akitoshi!
I'm gonna cum! More! Make me cum more!
I- I'm gonna cum!
How many are we up to?
How many times are you planning
to make me cum, Akitoshi?
I-In any case, we don't have much choice but to do it!
My life's on the line!
Akitoshi, don't! I can't go on!
I feel like I'm breaking to pieces...
I've been waiting so long for this...
H- Hitomi-nee?
Akitoshi, you've made me a woman!
H- Here it comes!
I-I'm gonna cum again, Hitomi-nee!
Are you really gonna stick that inside me?
My pussy and my ass feel so full...
It's gonna overflow! It's gonna overflow!
I'm gonna make sure my dick reaches your womb, too!
And then, I'll cum directly inside you!
It's hitting it! Your dick is hitting my womb, Akitoshi!
So please make sure you get pregnant
with my baby, Hitomi-nee!
Akitoshi...
I'm gonna get pregnant with my little brother's baby!
It's okay, Hitomi-nee.
Please get pregnant.
It's okay, Akitoshi.
As long as you promise not to do this with any other girls...
Then...
I'm yours, Akitoshi, and you're the only one for me...
I'm gonna cum!
Your dick's... so warm... and big!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I love you, Hitomi-nee.
I love you too, Akitoshi.
It's so strange...
It looks like such a bright and beautiful day.
This past week that I've spent with Hitomi-nee
and Mina the shinigami...
Those memories were priceless.
I've run out of time to try
to make a baby with Hitomi-nee.
I've made up my mind.
The Sunday of my fate has come.
If onee-sama is pregnant, you'll automatically escape my scythe.
But if not, you'll be... sliced.
There's no need to think about it, just do it.
Don't lose heart, Akitoshi-san.
Even if you die, I'll let you become my familiar.
Mina-chan, I'm sorry...
but I'm not letting you have Akitoshi.
Well then, here goes!