Well then, here goes!
Translation:
SaHa
Timing:
Timgorden11
I'll be on my way...
That's right. Akitoshi's not here, anymore.
This is a free fansub not for sale, rent or ebay.
Ane-Haramix
Volume 4
Brought to you by Haramix-subs
Looks like it's gonna be another scorcher, today.
He waited for me!
You're late, Hitomi-nee!
Hitomi-nee, if you run like that...
I'll be fine!
I'm in perfect shape!
That's so good, Akitoshi!
I can feel your warm dick and the cold water going inside me...
Club activities are gonna start soon. We should take a break.
I know that...
It's a shame, but I guess I won't be able to enroll in the athletic meet, huh?
Do you regret it?
Hmm? Of course not! Not when I can feel this good!
Is that what you're thinking about!?
Hurry up! Akitoshi, you're such a meanie!
Alright!
Oh?
Hitomi's here early.
Huh? She's here with her little brother, today?
We can't lose to her. We'd better hurry up and go shower!
Yeah!
The interhighs are coming up!
You'd better loosen up muscles, Hitomi.
Oh? What's the matter, Hitomi?
Um... Well...
He's just massaging me a little too hard...
You haven't been practicing too often lately, Hitomi!
That's right!
You took the entire summer break off.
W-well, that's only because it's bad to exercise
during the early stages of pregnancy.
But I never knew that your little brother can give a good sports massage.
Looks like it was a good idea for me to train him...
You're so lucky...
Say, do you think he could give me one next time?
Uh... Go right ahead. If you don't mind him giving you one...
Sure thing! I'd be happy to!
If you don't mind letting me do it, I'd be honoured!
Alright! Well then, let's go do some stretches over there.
In that case, I'll be counting on you!
You can't ask your child's father to spend time with them, can you?
S-sorry... But...
I'm not listening to your excuses.
If I don't cum before those two get back, things are gonna get pretty ugly.
Akitoshi, you're so mean...
It won't be long before I can't even get into a pool, anymore.
I need to train while I still have a chance.
You're just having lots of fun, aren't you?
Does it really matter!? Just hurry up and start moving, Akitoshi!
Yeah, yeah...
So good! Deeper! Give it to me deeper!
Does it feel good? Does your pussy really feel that good?
Nee-san!
It's good!
It's good! My pussy feels so good! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Onee-sama sure is lucky...
She gets to do something that feels so good...
I wish he'd do that to me, too...
Geez! How could a proud shinigami become
so infatuated with a mere human!?
I don't ever remember raising you to be such an obscene girl!
You need to be sharp, alright!? Sharp!
But I can't help it...
It feels so good...
Well, it's not that I can't relate to seeing
a human with my grand-daughter...
Back when I was young, I used to be pretty popular.
The young ladies were all lining up for me.
In my true form, I was considered the
most handsome shinigami around!
Boss...
For some reason, I really want to eat something sour...
This position shouldn't be too rough on your belly.
Are you sure you're okay?
Deeper! Stick it in even deeper!
Okay!
It moved.
Huh?
The baby moved!
Really?
Yeah.
You're right!
It's moving.
Our baby...
It's happy.
It means he can tell what his mommy's feeling.
I-Is that so?
So make sure you do it a lot harder, Akitoshi.
Okay.
T-That's incredible, Hitomi-nee!
Even though it's incredibly soft, it feels like
I'm melting and being sucked inside you!
My milk came out...
It's still too early for that, Akitoshi...
Come on... Drink it...
Otherwise, it'd be such a waste. I want you to drink my milk.
Sure.
Well? Is it delicious? Is it, Akitoshi?
Your breasts are so sweet, and delicious, Hitomi-nee...
You're big...You're so big.
My belly feels so full!
Geez!
They keep doing it every day, non-stop!
Can this guy really become a father!?
Not to mention he got Mina pregnant, too!
I'm gonna punish him severely for this!
Wait right there, Boss!
Akitoshi-san isn't the only one to blame!
You were responsible for tricking me too, boss!
You told me that shinigami can't have babies with humans!
I wasn't lying!
It's never happened before!
M-Mina-chan, please don't stare at me like that...
But... But...
I'm... I'm...
Don't give me that! Who ever told you it was
alright to fuck a human like that!?
I never raised you to be such a slut!
I'm not a slut!
This was all the result of my doing my duty as a shinigami and going through with Akitoshi-san's training course!
It moved! Boss! The baby inside my belly started moving!
Really?
Let's see...
Ohhh! What a lively child! Now I'll be a grandfather!
That really fills me with an indescribable feeling!
You did it! You did it! You really did it!
Give it to me! Give it to me, Akitoshi!
Hitomi-nee, you just came, didn't you?
I didn't cum...
I didn't...didn't...cum!
Even while pregnant, you're not very honest, Hitomi-nee.
In that case, I won't hold back. I'm cumming inside you.
Wait! If you cum right now, I'm...!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming so hard!
Hitomi-nee, you're already completely enchanted.
Hitomi-nee, it's not over yet.
This time, I'll make you cum with your ass, and then you're really gonna be broken down, Hitomi-nee.
Still... I can't believe it...
I can't believe a human and a shinigami were able to make a baby.
In my 1000 years of...
Um... I mean... I'm a little frazzled, but I never knew it could happen.
Oh! I just remembered!
I never wanted to get in their way now
that they're getting along so well.
But maybe I should ask Akitoshi-san what
he thinks about a name for the baby.
I wanted to call him "Akira"...
That's right!
According to shinigami law, it's always
best to think of a name for a boy...
But it's still so unfair...
Onee-sama's the only one getting any...
Mina...
Can I really rely on you?
It's been so long since you've given this to me, Akitoshi-san.
I'm only lending him to you, okay, Mina-chan?
I know that.
But it's not so bad to share him once in a while, is it, onee-sama?
So big... It's getting so big...
Isn't it about time for you to let me stick it in? Mina-san, Hitomi-nee!
No way... Put up with it a little longer.
Isn't this great? I can't believe I was able to actually get pregnant.
B-Being a guy sure is tough!
No... D... Don't!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm Cumming!
No! Akitoshi! Drink my milk, too!
So good!
Good!
It's so good!
Akitoshi, my baby and your dick are filling me up inside.
They're bumping against each other!
Me too!
The baby in my belly is moving around so happily.
I'm gonna cum!
But first... Akitoshi-san, I need a name for your baby...
Geez! I keep telling you to drink my milk, Akitoshi!
I'm gonna cum! A name! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
Drink it!
No! No!
Alright!
If it's a boy, it'll be "Ikuya".
If it's a girl, it'll be "Miruku". How's that!?
Whaaaat!?
B-But w-what if they're both girls?
W-Well...!
O-Onee-sama.
I... I'm gonna cum!
I'm almost there! I'm almost there!
I'm gonna cum!
It's no use...
I'm...
I'm gonna cum!
M-Me too! Me too!
Me too! Me too!
Me too... Me too...
Me too... Me too!
If only I had a body!
That's right... Tonight's Christmas eve, isn't it?
This reminds me of that night 2000 years ago...
Well then...
I wonder if they'll give birth to an angel or a devil?
Or maybe even a shinigami?
Well, I guess we'll find out when it grows up...