Please forgive me, boss!
No way!
You freed a human whose soul
you were supposed to hunt.
And for that, you're getting punished.
And for that, you're getting punished!!
But... But, those two are...
Translation:
SaHa
Don't you talk back to me.
I already understand the situation.
Timing:
Timgorden11
If you don't eat your meals as a Shinigami,
I have to go hungry, too.
If he does get her pregnant, rules are rules...
However!
For deciding such an important thing
without consulting me first,
you need to be punished!
Please forgive me!
I'll do anything!
This is a free fansub not for sale, rent or ebay.
Ane-Haramix
Volume 2
Brought to you by Haramix-subs
Akitoshi, use your hands properly!
Harder! Do it harder!
Amazing!
It feels so good, Hitomi-nee!
Geez! Why do I have to do everything!?
Akitoshi, don't just lie there - move!
So good!
So deep! It's too deep!
I can feel you touching my womb!
Hitomi-nee, I can feel your womb...
...throbbing as if it's begging for me!
It's stroking me inside.
Akitoshi, your dick is pressing
into the opening of my womb!
It's getting even bigger!
And warm! It's so warm!
I'll do this for you... let me do this for you!
Do it! Do it!
Akitoshi, fill your big sister with your cum!
Hitomi-nee,
I can still keep going.
Huh? Still!?
Geez...
Please help me, Akitoshi-san!
The boss!
Boss said he'd punish me again
if I didn't do this!
I don't wanna be punished! I don't wanna!
Mina-san! If you do that while I'm this sensitive, I'm...
Crap! I'm cumming!
Geez! Where do you think you're cumming!?
That's not where it's supposed to go
and you know it!
Are you telling me you're satisfied no matter who you're doing it with!?
Geez!
No! No! No!
Give me a break!
That was so uncool!
Akitoshi-san, could this be...!?
That? That's called a can Oden.
Th-These are really famous
among the Shinigami of my world!
The can Oden of Akihabara!
I...I must try one no matter what!
Say... Akitoshi-sama...
A-Again?
So, about this special mission...
Did you really need to come to
Akihabara to get it done?
It's one of the most important things
for all Shinigami to accomplish.
Hey, this is really delicious, huh?
But I don't really know a lot
about the human world,
so you're the only one
I could count on, Akitoshi-san.
Well, if it's just a matter of
showing you around, then...
Although, even if we're in Akihabara,
your outfit really stands out
a little too much, Mina-san...
Akitoshi-san, those clothes!
I really want to try those on!
Yes, master.
That's called a "maid"
Then again, a maid outfit would probably make
more sense than a Shinigami outfit.
There sure are a lot of incredible
cosplay outfits in here...
Oh!
This one should look great on Mina-san.
What the heck's this!?
4L?
In men's sizes!?
Excuse me, Akitoshi-san...
I'm not really sure how to
put these clothes on...
Okay!
Just leave it to me, Mina-san!
I've always been good with clothes like that.
After all, Hitomi-nee would force me
to help her out with her own clothes!
Whoa... Mina-san isn't wearing a bra.
Oops...
Looks like you're having some trouble, huh?
Well, yeah...!
Hmm... Let's see where those buttons are...
A...Akitoshi-san?
If I massage your breasts a bit
to soften them up,
it won't be so tight anymore.
Ah! I think I get it.
That's no good, Mina-san.
If you let your nipples get stiff,
it'll get even tighter.
B-but, I can't help it...
I'm gonna do it!
Are you sure you're wearing a pannier?
("pannier" = petticoat)
Mina-chan, that's no good.
You're gonna get a nasty stain
just from putting on some clothes.
You'd better take those off
so that it doesn't happen!
H-Heh!?
We can't have you going around
without maid underwear.
Let's see...
There we go! This'll do.
Okay, Mina-san. Go ahead and try these on.
No way...
It's nothing but a string!
These are much better.
This way, you won't stand out.
This is part of being a maid!
Akitoshi-san, that's not the right place!
It feels good, but...
How about...HERE?
It feels so strange!
Nooo!
Come on.
I'm not even touching you there
and you're getting drenched!
Look at that!
Amazing! Amazing! It's coming out!
Look at the way it's pouring out
and soaking you.
While we're at it,
I may as well try this, too.
On no! No!
Don't stop!
They both... They both feel so good!
Oh no!
Alright! It's almost time.
Hey... Are you done, yet?
I'd like to get a look in the mirror...
I was wondering what that
special mission of yours was supposed to be,
and it turns out all you had to do was
buy some "Bibiruman" DVDs?
That's right.
Boss told me that these are
part of a Shinigami's rites.
And he also said...
Do you understand?
You need to get your hands
on those special anime episodes.
If you happen to pick up live-action by mistake,
you're gonna get punished even more!
After all, the only thing that can
shake my soul is anime!
And if it's an initial run,
it'll really make my soul happy.
This is the most important thing
you need to take care of!
You'd better make sure you're successful.
That's what he said.
Bibiruman is part of a Shinigami's rites, huh?
You don't suppose your boss
just wants to watch them?
The boss is really terrifying, you know!
He told me that if I failed,
as soon as I return, Akitoshi-san...
he'd harvest your soul!
Huh!?
Is this mission really that important?
But how can you measure my soul
against an anime DVD?
Isn't that a little too mean?
That's just how scary he is!
Ever since I started attending Shinigami school,
he's had me under his thumb!
Shinigami school, huh?
Wouldn't it have been better if
it was a regular school?
No, but if Mina-san had never come along,
this situation would never have happened...
What's the matter?
N-No! It's nothing!
More importantly, Mina, couldn't you do something
about that scythe you're carrying around?
Of course not!
A scythe is a Shinigami's life!
Ah!
Let's go to this shop next!
More?
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
That's no good, Akitoshi-san.
You can't let me take
your soul already, can you?
That's not exactly what I meant...
After all, you're like an apple
ripe for the plucking, Akitoshi-san.
You've gotta make sure you
make a baby with Hitomi onee-sama.
Now stand up!
Just like Bibiruman!
That's right. I have a mission.
And even though I'm feeling dizzy,
I've got a boner just thinking about the fact
that I can't lose to Bibiruman!
Oh, that's why...
I've been running around so much today
that I haven't done it at all...
Th... That's right!
Now that I think about it,
if I just need to get someone pregnant
it doesn't really have to be Hitomi-nee.
Mina-san would be just as good.
No! This isn't the time to worry about that.
This is so that I can keep myself alive!
This is definitely an emergency!
It's time for some special training, Mina-san!
Eh?
It's not enough!
I need a technique!
I need a so-called secret move!
Please, Mina-san!
No! Coach!
Please give me a sure-fire technique!
C-Coach?
It's got such a pleasant ring to it...
I am Akitoshi-san's coach!
I acknowledge your resolve!
Follow me until the end!
Ahaha!
My strategy is a success!
I'm like a devil even against a Shinigami.
So, um...
How exactly are we supposed to train you
to learn a secret move?
My actual training will be...
THIS!
A-Akitoshi-san!
This is training!?
That's right.
Mina-san, as my coach, you can train with me
to learn a new technique
and maybe I'll be able to please Hitomi-nee!
I-I guess I'll have to take responsibility.
Now that THAT'S decided,
we're really going all-out!
Huh? Then, does that mean...?
That's right: this is sex training.
Coach, you're the one who said
you'd help me learn a special technique, right?
You didn't lie to me, did you?
Of course I didn't lie...
A Shinigami isn't allowed to lie.
But I don't have any experience.
I might not be too helpful.
Even if you're a virgin, that's okay!
In fact, that's even better!
After all, if I can satisfy a virgin like you,
my secret technique will work for sure!
No! Is that really how it goes?
No! Noooo!
Don't look at me!
Please don't look, Akitoshi-san!
We can't have that!
After all, this my training!
I've gotta make sure I know
what my target is.
Is that so?
I guess you're right.
This is training, right?
It's so warm!
Our special training begins!
Go slowly...
Don't move!
This is special training!
I need to train to endure
your incredible pussy!
Okay! I'll try!
I'll try to put up with this special training!
Don't show it to me!
Please don't show it to me!
I can see your dick going inside me!
Take a close look, Mina-san!
My special technique is almost ready!
I can see it!
I can see it thrusting in and out of me!
I can feel it reaching all the way to here.
Deeper!
Mina-san, I need to reach
all the way to your womb!
Huh? My womb?
You can't go all the way to there!
But...It feels so good, Akitoshi-san!
Please thrust it deeper
and deeper inside me!
Right there, Akitoshi-san!
That's my...!
I reached it!
I reached your womb, Mina-san!
Now I can just need to thrust it in there!
That's... That's my special technique!
It's pouring out!
You're cumming inside me!
It's so wonderful!
It's making me crazy!!
Mina-san, we did it!
Thanks to your special training,
I mastered my special technique!
I'm taking every last drop of
your special technique!
Huh?
Akitoshi!
What have you DONE!?
Hi-Hitomi-nee!
I'm never gonna have your baby!