Translation:
SaHa
Timing:
Timgorden11
Akitoshi, make sure you guard your big sister properly!
It's your fault that we're late and we had to get on this crowded train.
I'm trying!
This is a free fansub not for sale, rent or ebay.
Ane-Haramix
Volume 1
Brought to you by Haramix-subs
Will you cut it out, already!?
I-I told you I'm trying!
Hitomi-nee's always like this.
Even though she's quiet and an incredible beauty,
she's always selfishly working me to the bone,
and ends up hitting me anyways.
Hitomi-nee... She smells so good.
The real Hitomi-nee can be pretty cruel,
but the one in my dreams is so kind, and sexy.
Hey, Akitoshi...
What's the matter?
Damn it! You smell so nice, Hitomi-nee!
I'm not going to forgive you if you let
any other guy get a whiff of your scent!
Hitomi-nee, you're mine!
There's only one thing to do with an unfaithful girl like you...
Punishment!
Take this! And this! And this!
I'm gonna pinch these stiff little cherries!
There! Do you give up, Hitomi-nee?
Akitoshi!
I know...
Hitomi-nee, you get turned on really easily
with your nipples, don't you?
'Shi...
Huh? Hitomi-nee?
I-Is this... real?
No, but.....
Hasn't she realized what I'm doing?
Normally, she would have punched my lights out.
What the hell are you doing, Akitoshi!?
Even so... Her breasts are incredible...
They really are...
Has she really been able to walk around
with things like these?
But why isn't she getting angry?
Could it be that Hitomi-nee is sexually frigid?
Could it be the same down here?
Hitomi-nee...
Could it really be that she didn't notice anything?
She didn't get angry at all...
But I sure am glad I did that!
I can still feel the sensation of it!
Crap! I got a boner...
Hmm... This ought to be the place, right?
Huh?
Hitomi-nee...
Heh heh... He hasn't noticed me at all.
He's got that stupid look on his face and
he doesn't even know what fate has in store for him!
But I've gotta say that expression
on his face sure is stupid-looking...
I kinda feel sorry for the guy...
Huh?
H-Hitomi-nee...!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
I'm gonna kill you right this second!
C-Cosplay girl pervert!
What's with all the ruckus, stupid Akitoshi!?
Huh? A pervert!?!!
Hitomi-nee, go away!
Wh... Why? How can they all see me!?
What are you doing dressed like that,
you damn pervert!?
S-She's flying! She has wings! Look! Look!
D-Damn it...
I'm gonna have to silence
the two of you permanently!
DON'T FUCK WITH US!
So...
"Mina-chan, the shinigami", right?
Yeah...
I'm a first year shinigami.
This is actually my debut as a shinigami.
So why are you hunting for Akitoshi's soul?
You've got it all wrong!
It's not as if a shinigami tries to
steal the souls of healthy people.
Our job is to lead the souls of people
who are near death towards the afterlife.
And I still want to know why
you're going after Akitoshi?
Well, that's because
Akitoshi-san is going to be dying very soon.
Heh?
M-Me?
Yeah! It won't be too long before
you're met with a sudden death.
It can't be.
Whaaat!? It c...
You've gotta be joking!
I know Akitoshi is a stupid, unskilled idiot,
but I did work hard to teach him
to worry about others!
There's no way I'm handing him over to you!
If you really want someone's soul,
I'll just give you mine!
Huh?
Hitomi-nee, could it be that you...?
What? Don't get the wrong impression.
But...
I'm so moved! I'm so deeply moved!
Just the idea of a big sister sacrificing her own life
to save that of her brother's...
I'm so deeply moved! Please let me help you!
To put it bluntly, there is a way out of this.
Hitomi-nee's really going along with this
a little too easily.
Even though a shinigami's trying to take the soul
of her cute, little brother...
What's wrong with her!?
If Akitoshi manages to create a new life,
his soul will be spared for a little while.
In other words, he won't die for the time being...
if he gets someone pregnant!
Geez... What's with that cosplay pervert?
Even if she tells us that...
Hey...
I know this might be a little direct,
but do you have a girlfriend, Akitoshi?
I don't! Of course I would never have such a thing!
Really?
I never knew.
So a shinigami can put on
and remove their wings at will, huh?
Well, yeah...
It would be quite a problem if they got all wet
when we take baths, after all...
Wow... That's really surprising.
I can even have these wings pop out
in all sorts of places.
Here! It's out! Or look at this!
Look! I can even pop it out from here!
You're a little stupid, aren't you?
Please, Hitomi-nee!
Think of your one and only cute, little brother!
You're the only one I've got, Hitomi-nee!
If you don't do it, I'll really die!
Damn it!
Fine! Just forget it!
In that case, if I die,
it's gonna be your fault, Hitomi-nee!
Geez! What's your problem!?
You've got no respect!
Fine...
I'll make a baby for you, Akitoshi.
Onee-sama, your big breasts
really are wonderful, aren't they?
Huh?
Aw, come on! Don't stare at them like that...
Anyone would fall in love with those.
See? Just look at Akitoshi-san over there.
Huh?
Akitoshi!
Geez... That stupid Akitoshi.
Even though Mina was with me,
he had his eyes fixed on me.
Just a little more...
I said I'd give birth to Akitoshi's baby...
Wouldn't that mean I'd have
to have sex with him?
But, how...?
Hitomi-nee.
Hitomi-nee?
Is this... my chance?
Is she trying to tempt me?
Hitomi-nee...
You're gonna catch a cold.
But please don't wake up!
Gently...Gently...
Hitomi-nee's...
This is a miracle!
This is a present from god, isn't it!?
Isn't that right, Hitomi-nee?
Uh oh! B-But I can't hold back any longer!
Huh? It won't go in!
Why isn't it going in?
Shit!
I'm gonna cum!
I did it! Hitomi-nee really swallowed my cum.
Huh?
What's this?
Oh?
Akitoshi!
I-I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Please forgive me!
At this rate, I'm gonna die!
Hitomi-nee!
Well, I did promise you.
Then...!
I don't mind doing it with you.
But I feel sorry for you, so I don't have
much choice but to have your baby.
I don't have any experience either.
The truth is, I don't want this,
but I don't have a choice.
Hitomi-nee...
I'm digging in!
Hitomi-nee, your pussy's all wet.
Y-You're wrong!
Well... Maybe not, but...
I'm sticking it in, Hitomi-nee...
W-Wait! Make sure you do it slowly, okay?
You'd better not mess up doing what I say
the way you always do.
I-It's going in... Akitoshi...
It's tight. Hitomi-nee...
This is... Hitomi-nee's pussy.
Don't say that! It hurts! It hurts!
Sorry, Hitomi-nee...
I'm starting to move!
Huh?
Your nipples are getting stiff, Hitomi-nee.
Oh no...
My nipples are getting hard...
Even though my little brother's doing this to me...
I'm having sex with my little brother...
... so he can make me pregnant!
Please save my life, Hitomi-nee!
Make me a baby!
Akitoshi-san's dick is going inside
onee-sama down here...
It feels so strange...
No!
Akitoshi, my hips are moving!
Hitomi-nee...
You really are a pervert.
You... you're wrong!
It's so strange...
I feel so strange!
You're not strange. Hitomi-nee...
From now on, have sex with me every single day!
Every day?
That's right.  Morning and night.
After all, you're not gonna get pregnant
after a single time, right?
I'm gonna have sex with you
every day, Akitoshi...?
You're gonna make me do this
with my little brother again and again?
Do it! Do it! Akitoshi!
Make your your big sister pregnant!
I... I can feel it!
It's so deep!
I can feel you so deep inside me, Akitoshi!
I'm gonna cum, Hitomi-nee!  I'm gonna cum...!
Do it!
Give it to your big sister, Akitoshi!
Your cum! I want it!
I want my little brother's cum deep in me so bad!
Akitoshi...
I'm sorry.
Hitomi-nee, looks like I got the order all mixed up.
Hitomi-nee, you're all mine.
Yeah... Akitoshi.
So...
Akitoshi!
I'm making this mine, too!
No way! Stupid Akitoshi! That's...!
I'm not wrong!
But you can't make a baby from there!
It's too late!
I told you, didn't I? You're all mine, Hitomi-nee!
Y-You dummy! Pervert! Sicko!
How could you want to stick it in there!?
At least go slowly!
It's no use! I want to fuck you so hard, Hitomi-nee!
It... It can't be!
It's strange! For some reason,
I feel just like those humans...
My ass! You're gonna break my ass!
Amazing! Hitomi-nee, your ass is swallowing up my dick!
Akitoshi! Your dick is going into my ass!
Hitomi-nee, I'm gonna cum inside your ass!
So warm... Akitoshi's cum...
I feel so warm down here... I wonder why...?
This is quite a problem...
You were clearly ordered to carry that boy's soul to the afterlife, Mina.
You'll need to be punished for this!
Look forward to part 2!