Mizushima Contractors
D-Don't do it this way.
It's too tight.
But you like it, don't you, Asa-chan?
What?
Because... it feels amazing.
I feel like I'm being caressed inside.
And it's deep inside me.
It tickles.
No... Hajime, you meanie.
This isn't fair.
All the places you do feel good.
Could this be... how it feels to do it?
I feel a bit frustrated...
It's frustrating,
but I'm starting to like him.
Ah, he was right, the door is unlocked.
Excuse me!
No, you're kidding me.
We'll come in then.
It saves us the trouble of having to go all the way back to our clubhouse. Lucky!
I wonder if the swimming club has no activities now.
Actually, it's just the two of them.
Saisho-kun made it sounded like it was "open to public."
Hajime!
It's fine, right?
It's thrilling.
No, stop it...
Actually, isn't it amazing?
Even though there're so many girls here, you seem to stand out the most.
So, does that mean that I'm the best?
I can't get mad at him, if that's what he meant...
Since my heart is pounding so fast, he'll think I'm enjoying it.
This towel...
"Mizushima Contractors"?
Mizushima... the transfer student?
This must be hers...
Right?
But... no one is here.
But... there's no one here.
Speaking of the transfer student, I wonder how it's going between her and Saisho-kun.
I bet he's being ignored, as usual.
Probably.
That's right.
I thought he was nothing but a nuisance at first.
Two months ago
I'm Mizushima Asa, I just transferred here.
Nice to meet you.
Mizushima-san!
W-Wait up!
Mizushima-san.
Hey.
Wait.
Saisho-kun!
You're chasing girls again.
You might as well just hang out with us.
Today is an important day for the members of swimming club.
Oh, right...
And you've already forgotten what you promised?
Mizuki, captain of the tennis club.
Cool blue is cute.
No way! You saw it?
As for the karaoke queen, Kanami-chan...
Mint with lace, as expected from a rich girl.
No!
The librarian, Youko-chan, surprisingly has a pink one. So daring!
As for Nagisa-chan, with her tight ass...
No, you're kidding me!
Virgin white, just as I imagined, good.
I have them properly noted down, so don't worry.
Bye.
Geez, you perv!
So... did I upset you?
Did I step on a mine by talking about other girls in front of a lady?
But, that's okay!
My favorite is still striped.
It's without doubt, the best.
Oh!
B-But, you see...
You didn't try to hide it at all.
Saisho-kun...
You're annoying.
Oops.
Why are you so cold toward me?
He's really the worst.
Come on, we're teammates in the swimming club...
Open the door... Look, we should get along.
Our times will improve too. Hey, come on.
Teammates?
Because my mother decided to divorce,
I transferred here for just one summer.
And still Hajime is so persistent.
As if that's a very natural thing to do.
Hey, don't take pictures of such weird places.
He started to take a place in my heart.
What, so you can smile after all.
Actually, you look much better with a smile.
Definitely.
I didn't even consider it.
That I would end up liking him.
Liking him...
So much.
Are you serious?
I didn't know that at all.
Hurry up, let's go!
Hey, wait a second!
Hey, hey, let's go shopping, shall we?
Oh yeah...
That's right, I heard about a delicious cake shop which just opened in front of the station, let's go there.
Ah, I want to go!
Let's go.
As expected from the well-informed girl.
What, did you say something?
Nope, not really.
Let's drop by the cake shop on our way back then.
Yeah, let's do that.
Hajime, you're going to come, right? You're coming.
You're coming, it's coming out.
I-It's coming, i-it's coming.
I can tell. I can tell.
It's coming inside me.
It looks like a close call.
Idiot.
I'm sorry, Asa-chan.
Look, they're at it.
I won't do it again.
Yeah.
You're right.
Poor Saisho-kun.
Forgive me.
I'll think better about the location.
So forgive me, okay? Please.
Please? No?
You can't?
Look this way.
Thank you.
Eh? Please, forgive me.
Geez, he's really too blunt.
This is really nice.
This chest...
And this tan.
No!
H-Hey, I said no.
No, don't!
Ah, not there!
Tears of joy are flowing out of there.
How dirty.
Ah, you perverted old man.
This old man is persistent.
I will make you my plaything for the rest of your life.
N-Not for the rest of my life...
It will feel too good to me.
Were you thinking of something perverted?
N-No, I didn't.
One. Two.
Wait, no...
No way, we just did it...
One. Two.
minamo wo wataru yuuutsu na kaze
A gloomy wind crosses over the water's surface
If I left the girl I like alone while she looked like she really wanted it, I'd be useless as a man.
toikakete mireba mou natsu no owari
By the time you try to ask it a question, summer is already over
I'm not wanting it. I didn't demand it.
One.
Two.
No, it feels weird.
shizun de yuku yuuhi mo higoto
The evening sun still sets every day,
It's too deep inside.
Y-Your hot thing is going all the way inside.
SUPIIDO mashiteku shuuiro no kumo
with increasing speed, with autumn colored clouds
No...
It's tight...
Don't push it in further. Don't push against my uterus.
kono hoho ni fureru sono kami ga
That hair that touches my cheek
M-My pussy... is getting tighter and tighter.
totemo itoshikute totemo setsunakute hanaretaku nakatta
So lovely, so painful. I don't want to leave it.
I-I can't... anymore...
nee sagashiteru mitsuketai
Hey, I'm searching for something, I want to find it
No!
katachi no nai nani ka wo
Something that has no appearance
I'm coming!
I'm coming! Please, together, together!
hito wa "katachi" wo miseru no ga tokui nano
People are good at keeping up their appearances
tooi kioku aoi haha no you ni
Like the distant memory of an inexperienced mother
I'm coming!
I'm coming, coming! I'm coming!
nami no nai ohisama no naka madoromu tori no you ni kaerou
In the sun without waves, like bird dozing off, let's go home
I'm coming!
I felt great.
I was completely squeezed dry without a single drop left.
It's warm inside.
You made me really happy.
I'm happy too...
That I can have you, all to myself.
I will take yours all for myself too.
Ah, w-wait.
It's your fault.
You made me want more.
It's unfair of you to keep him all to yourself.
The promise we made during the summer, that we would be rivals...
I hope you didn't forget about it.
Me too.
Me, Mizushima Asa, and her, Sorayama Natsume, made a promise this summer
that would definitely be unbelievable, if thought of normally.
I have always liked Hajime-chan.
I have liked him ever since I was a kid.
I like Hajime too.
I definitely don't want to give him away to someone else now.
There's are two loves but only one target.
So we have a problem, needing to share the time.
It will be way more painful if we can't be together.
Asa-chan?
Nacchan?
You can take away our virginities in any way you like.
In exchange,
take both of us together.
From that day on,
our secret summer began.
This is all because that Hajime rubs them too much.
But, I wonder if this is what it's like to do it with a guy.
I'm becoming less and less able to resist it.
I'm becoming a pervert.
Right now Nacchan should also be...
That's unfair.
Don't tease me by invading both places at the same time.
Your clothes will get dirty, you should take them off.
You did it with Asa-chan with her clothes on, right?
I want you to do it the same way with me as you did with Asa-chan.
No,
I want you to do it in a more perverted way with me than with Asa-chan.
I'm really becoming more and more dirty after all.
Because Hajime's dick makes me come every day...
I'm starting to like doing dirty things.
Nacchan... Nacchan must be, too...
Your dick is really hard, and really big.
It's turning inside of me like in a dream, it's pushing against my uterus.
You shouldn't make such loud noises.
What?
Everyone will hear you.
Eh?
You're so perverted to do it while you watch other girls change.
I'm not looking at any other girl.
Just you.
Me too. You're the only one I see right now.
Only your dick...
Your hot thing... is going all the way inside.
Oh no, this feels even more amazing.
Your dick is so tight inside me, I can even tell the shape of its veins.
I can't... anymore.
Please...
Together... together...
No!
I-I-I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
The end of summer is approaching.
It's hot.
It feels like it's burning inside, but I'm really happy.
The painful time for us to separate is also approaching.
Because I don't want to let it end...
Because I can't forget about it...
As I'm remembering my first night...
I want to be taken.
OAV, Sora no Iro, Mizu no Iro, Volume 2:
"I will... do it for you too"
Please look forward to it.