And so, the participants in the movie training camp are:
Katou Yasuyuki,
Yamagishi Yuu,
Igarashi Tomomi,
Takeuchi Shinya,
and myself, Saeki Hitomi.
Except for Tanaka-kun, it's great that the five of us can participate, isn't it?
Then I'll be sure to report this to our advisor, Shindou-sensei.
I'm glad that Tomo-chan can join!
Yeah.
Though it's a bit of a shame that Yuuji can't make it...
Yuu-tan can't make it because he's caring for his mother in the hospital.
I also wanted to be there for him,
but Yuu-tan told me to participate by myself.
We'll be together for a while, but this might be my last chance to camp with everybody.
That's right, next year Tanaka-kun and Tomo-chan will be graduating.
But I'm still jealous of your support for each other!
Right, Hitomi-san?
N-not really!
I'm not interested in that sort of thing!
A student's duty is to study!
To go out with a boy is just...
And so, it just kept growing and growing...
That's just ridiculous!
Now then, from here we'll be screening three movies.
There are more than twenty two of them,
but these three can be called the masterpieces, so they'll be good study material.
In between each movie, we'll break for about ten minutes.
W-what is this?
The remote.
Where's the remote?!
Does someone have it?
Hurry and stop it!
That's Shindou-sensei, right?
N-no!!!
You're kidding.
I can't believe a teacher had a dirty voice like that...
Even teachers are women, so of course they'd have sex, right?
Ooh, scary.
What now? Sensei's left us.
Let's go after her.
T-that's right!
Then I'll go and get her.
You will?
Yes, me and Yasuyuki will.
Me?
But,
after something like that, seeing guys might...
But she's already lost it,
and it's best not to have women wandering around, right?
This is something best left to the men.
Right, Yasuyuki?
Okay, we'll leave this to Katou-san and Takeuchi-san.
However, please don't do anything weird to her.
Weird, like in that video?
Like I thought, guys like you-!
Whoops, let's hurry up and go, Yasuyuki.
Katou-san!
Please... be careful.
Yes, I will.
Yasuyuki, what're you doing?
Ah, sorry!
I'll show this to you, Yasuyuki.
What? Proud of your new digital camera?
Wrong, it's not the camera, but what's inside of it.
I want to show you the video data.
Although from its latest showing, the picture is pretty good, isn't it?
Huh? So you're really just proud of it, aren't you?
This is-!
S-Shinya!
Since it came to this, I really wish I was with Yuu-tan.
Why don't we watch some TV?
We should get a signal in here.
"This just in. A mysterious virus has all of Japan in a state of panic."
"I'm still on air!"
No!
Stop!
Let go!
Stop, I'm not even wet.
Theres no way it will go in!
Is this real?
I don't think the news would lie.
Yuu-tan said the TV news isn't limited to just reporting.
So you're saying this is fiction?
Who knows....
S-sensei!
..c..cock.
Katou-san?
Takeuchi-san?
Shindou-sensei?
Where did the three of them go...?
Somehow, this looks really serious.
It's like a state of emergency.
Shouldn't we regroup with Shindou-sensei as soon as possible?
Then let's split up and look for them.
Ehh?
I agree!
You know...
Instead of getting scattered, shouldn't we go together?
You were the one that said the faster the better, Hitomi-san.
That's true, but..
So we'll split up and search.
Then come back here whether we've found them or not.
That'll work, right?
I guess I've no choice.
Walking around the school in the dead of night by myself.
If something unexpected pops up,
what shall I do?
I'm...
I thought I'd be okay at a time like this...
Oh, you've woken up.
Look, this is awake and excited too.
Now then...
It should be ready.
I'm putting it in.
Wait, Sensei, sto-!
So good!
How does it feel to lose your virginity to your teacher?
Sensei was my first time too.
We're like butt brothers!
Our first time was with the same woman.
We're really close friends now!
You're the one that attacked me, Takeuchi-kun.
Well, how does my hot pussy feel?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Sensei, please stop, this is-
Don't be afraid.
When I was raped and my virginity taken,
I wanted to die.
But now I really love this kind of sex!
No way, Sensei was raped...
Sensei's first time was being raped...
It's gotten so big inside of me!
You're quite excited, aren't you?
Do you want to hear more about that time?
That's... that's...
Your dick is trembling,
did you imagine my face in tears?
When I was like you,
I had never done it before.
Not even with my fingers!
And during periods I didn't even use tampons!
Sensei, stop, I-
Cumming!
Your virgin dick is filling my insides!
There's no such thing as a Hanako of the Toilet, right?
I'm glad I made it in time.
I haven't showered today either.
I have to make sure it doesn't smell...
I have to hurry and find Katou-san and the others.
The lights to the sports shed are on?
Who could it be at this hour?
Could it be Katou-san and the others?
You're always showing off that huge rack of yours.
N-no!
No!
Sensei, what are you doing?  Stop, please!
Such cute panties.
Back then I wore panties like this too.
Oh? A stain..
No, don't look!
It smells like urine.
Aren't you a little kid?
That's not true!
Going nude is pretty cold after all.
Wait, sensei, my underwear-!
Well?
It doesn't suit you at all!
Give me my panties back!
What's going on, what are you doing, Sensei?
Hey, look over here, Yuu-chan.
No, no!
Alright then.
I'll just have to show you.
Hey, wait, what-!
Oh, a sports bra?
These are Yuu-chan's bare breasts.
So soft!
They're supple too, different from an older woman like Risa!
Shut up, fatass.
Sen-
Sensei...
What are you doing...?
Oh, you don't know?
I'm masturbating.
With your used underwear.
I'm sure the department will never forgive me for this.
But to commit such a taboo...
Feels... so... good!
So dirty, and you're still so happy.
I can't look anymore!
My student's underwear is so sticky with my lewd juices,
it's the best!
No more, it's so good!
I'll make you feel good too.
So soft, every girl is a different sensation!
No, it's gross!
It feels good to me!
Say, I've never had a titty fuck before.
No!
It hurts!
So good! Yuu-chan!
W..What?
What are you doing?
Good!
Masturbating in front of my students feels so good!
No... no!!
Yuu-chan, I'm cumming!
Noooo!!!
Looking at my cute students face covered in such dirty-looking cum.
I'm going to cum, I'm-!
I can't, any more, I'm cumming!
Noooo!!!
Hey, lick it clean.
Wha-? What is this?
Katou-san!
I'm so glad I went to the toilet earlier.
This could've been dangerous.
Katou-san, we need to hurry up and call the police!
You might not believe what's happening in there, but they're being raped!
Katou-san?
Katou-san, if we don't hurry, Igarashi-san and Yamagishi-san will...
Huh?  That's just as the news said.  It's a panic!
Katou-san,
Right now Japan is in serious trouble!
Could it be that Shindou-sensei and Takeuchi-san have been infected with the virus, like in the news?
Who cares about that?
Who cares about...
Are you serious, Katou-san?
Right now I just want to convey my feelings.
Could it be... a confession?
The truth is, I also-
Lets fuck.
Lets fuck!
K-K-Katou-san?
Let's have sex, Saeki.
I haven't even had my first kiss,
and yet I'm already sucking a man's penis!
An honors student smells no different than a slut!
Though as long as this can be used, who cares about the smell.
First, in this hole-!
Wow, at least be able to drink that much.
Even with the person I like,
I can't possible drink that!
I give up already.
Do what you want.
but please, at least kiss me just this once.
Why do I have to kiss a mouth that's dirtied with my own cum?
That's-!
Now then, you'll let me do what I want, right?
Now, for here...
Katou-san, that's-!
Saeki, I'm putting it in.
It hurts!
So you were a virgin? I'm glad, Saeki.
Now we've both been raped for our first time.
Katou-san, it really..
hurts.. please, hurry, hurry and make it stop!
Okay!
Saeki, your insides feel so good!
The student council president's pussy is quite the honors student!
It hurts! No more, hurry! Hurry!!!
Hang on, I'll let it all out soon.
But inside, if you cum inside...
A baby! I'll have a baby..!
No more, if you cum inside,
if you cum inside a girl's pussy-!
I'll be impregnated with your sperm!
No, no, if you cum inside, I'll.. I'll..!
My anus feels so good from Katou-san's penis!
Even your asshole is an honor student, you're amazing Saeki!
Having a penis in my vagina or my anus feels so good!
It doesn't matter where, just do me harder!
It's here!
Another penis is here!
I really hate you Takeuchi-kun,
but I love your penis!
So please stick it inside of me!
From now on I'll be raped by more than just Katou-san's penis.
But Katou-san, I only love you!
No matter who rapes me.
No matter who disgraces me.
So please keep having sex with me!
Forever and ever!