Many centuries ago, there was a
battle between light and darkness.
Two; Dragon User
The light was the Souha Jougenshuu,
while the darkness was the Noroitou.
Following their respective beliefs, the battle between the two sides endured.
In order for the Noroitou to realize their ambitions in a future that the Jougenshuu couldn't interfere with,
they weakened the Jougenshuu and performed a ceremony to transcend time.
However, the Jougenshuu had passed down their powers all the way to the present,
awaiting the Noroitou that would eventually appear.
They cooperated with the one who had also transcended time,
Haruka-san, a Blade.
However, she has fallen into the hands of the enemy.
In order to save her, Narika has now decided to become a Blade.
Jougen Ninja Skill...
Power of the Dragon!
Transform, Heaven Phoenix!
How unsightly, Jougenshuu.
Being ejactulated at by males... you must be excited.
No, I'm not!
You are  excited.
At this rate, I fear that the other Jougenshuu might be in depravity as well.
Stop right there!
Noroitou, this place shall be the end for your evil deeds!
Who's there?!
I shall be the crescent whose moonlight cleanses the endless darkness dyed with sin!
Blade of the Souha Jougenshuu, Narika is here!
Bastard of the Jougenshuu,
how dare you break the barrier and trespass!
N-Narika-san...
I could say the same. How dare you persecute our precious Haruka-san!
In the name of the moonlight that I bear, I will kick your asses!
She's just a kid.
K-Kid?!
Hey! Take that back!
I've just climbed the stairs of adulthood, you know!
Although it was a little painful...
Narika, what are you saying?!
Ah, Takamaru.
You don't have to make small talk with the enemy!
S-Sorry, I don't know what I should do since this is my first time.
Enough with your opening speech. Hurry up and save Haruka-san!
Ah, right!
All right, Noritou. Here I come!
What?!
Takamaru, make sure you support me, okay?
Got it. I'll keep a close watch on the situation.
You're better suited as a kid.
Stop saying that I'm a kid!
Well then, how about a piss-stinky slut?
Isn't that even worse?!
Narika, don't let them provoke you!
Saving Haruka comes first, doesn't it?!
I know that. You don't have to shout.
Haruka-san, I'm coming now!
Out of my way!
Here comes my next one!
Heat Wave!
Got you!
Now's my chance!
Haruka-san?
Where are you? Where?
Narika-san has been lost!
We've lost contact with both of them!
Damn, is it the barrier again?
Haruka-san? Haruka-san?
Where'd you go?
I'm here.
Haruka-san!
Eh? Haruka-san, what's the matter?
Your breasts are still that of a child.
You have to let Takamaru-sam rub them.
Haruka-san... what are you-
Don't!
Hold on!
Takamaru's dick had just entered this spot, didn't it?
How does it feel to have your hole swallow a man's dick for the first time?
Hold on!
I can't... I can't do this.
Doing it with another girl... I don't swing that way.
Hey... stop it...
But you're already wet.
Shall I confirm that?
No! How could I let a female touch it...
Wait! Hold on!
What are you doing?!
No... Don't touch it!
You are wet, Narika-san.
You are totally soaked.
Don't say that out loud... What happened to you all of a sudden?
Let me go!
No, let me give you some guidance about Ryuurinko.
Even if you don't, Takamaru will-
That's why I have to polish you up as a woman for Takamaru.
No, don't polish me...
I can't hold it in anymore...
You're being weird, Haruka-san!
What are you trying to do?
It hurts...
You can't win against me when I get serious, Narika-san.
Let me lick it for you.
What are you doing?!
No! Don't lick it!
Wait a second!
You can't, that place is for Takamaru...
Not there!
I beg you, don't remove my panties!
You are embarrassed, aren't you?
To have that wet place licked by me.
L-Lick?
Haruka-san, don't tell me you're going to do that?!
Yes.
To let Takamaru's dick penetrate in, I have to make your lewd hole sensitive.
Why do you have to do that?!
Stop! Just not that place!
If you lick that spot, I don't know what’ll happen to me!
Well then, it's fine.
No! Don't take off my panties!
No!
Narika, this flower bud is quite petite and beautiful, isn't it?
D-Don't look...
Don't... It's really embarrassing...
No, let me have a clearer view of it.
It's cute. It's twitching and making lewd sounds.
It isn't! It isn't!
Please don't cry.
I'm going to give you ecstasy.
What a cute clitoris.
Don't suck on it...
I beg you Haruka-san, stop this!
I beg you!
You're already getting wet, aren't you?
My dick is getting hard too.
Haruka-san, why do you... You're joking, right?!
It's all thanks to my technique.
This is quite the spectacle.
Stop it... Wait!
No way! There's no way something that big will fit inside me!
Let me put it in.
I also want to feel good and climax.
I want to use Narika-san to let me cum a lot.
I don't wanna, that'll break me!
It will only hurt in the beginning.
You will get used to it quickly.
I don't want to get used to it!
Wait a min-
It hurts! Stop it...
You just need to hold out for a little longer.
See, even the end is completely swallowed!
I'm going to start moving now.
Wait! Don't move yet!
I beg you! Wait until I'm used to it!
Have you changed your mind to accept it now?
Yeah.
I understand.
I will do it slowly.
It hurts...
Hang in there. Just a little more.
It feels good!
It's so small that it's squeezing me!
It's going in... it's going in...!
W-Wait! It won't go there!
That's wrong, that's my butt hole!
I will let you be sensitive here too.
No! Don't do it! It won't work! It can't go in!
It hurts! It won't work! Don't put it in!
Please relax.
If you accept all of this, you will become a woman who is loved by Takamaru-sama.
It hurts! It really hurts!
Don't, Haruka-san!
Don't put it in any more!
It's all right. I will put it in to prove it!
Nooo...!
It went in. It has gone in, Narika-san.
It feels good. It feels good, Narika-san!
That can't be...
It feels good.
It went in so deeply!
Haruka-san, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
I'll cum! I'm cumming!
I can't hold it in anymore!
Forgive me, Haruka-san. I can't...
Good! It feels good!
Narika-san, I'm going to cum too!
I'm going to cum!
Me too. I'm going to cum again!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming. Alright, Narika-san?
I'm going to cum inside of you.
Inside?
Bear a baby with my seed!
A cursed baby.
No! Don't! Stop it!
I can't hold it in anymore! I'll cum inside!
No!
Please stop! Don't cum inside me!
Save me!!
HARUKA-SAN!
Haruka-san.
Takamaru-sama...
Please wake up, Haruka-san.
The barrier is broken!
Ah! They're gone!
Damn! They escaped, huh?
In any case, it's great that you're alright.
I'm really sorry.
I was under an enemy's spell.
I placed Narika-san in danger...
No, it's just because the opponent is a troublesome one.
Still, even if...
Even if you are a Dragon User,
to be able to break the Noroitou's barrier and establish a spiritual link...
No, to be honest, I don't really understand it either...
I was just absorbed in wanting to save them.
Thanks to you, the other team of Jougenshuu were successfully able to save them.
A Dragon User seems to be able to reveal Michi's powers.
Well, we'll figure that out later.
Putting that aside, you two should sleep for now.
We don't have much time.
You must recover your battle powers while you're resting.
So, Ikusabe.
Do you understand?
Y-Yeah.
Well... I never thought that it'd turn out like this...
Do you really want to do it together?
Yes, we don't have much time...
B-Because if we do it individually, you won't be able to hold out, right?
No... If it's a twosome...
Takumaru-sama...
You don't have to strain yourself.
Today, we will be the ones comforting you.
Comfort?!
Anyway, just hurry up and lie down in front of us!
B-But if you two are comforting me, will you be able to receive H-power?
Don't worry about that.
We just have to receive your semen, so we can convert it to H-power.
A-About that... Since when were you able to do that?
After we knew that we were connected with Takamaru-sama through our hearts.
Our hearts?
Anyway, let's end the theory talk!
Hurry up and take off your pants!
Uh, fine, um-
Ahh, you're pissing me off! We'll take them off for you!
Hey, w-wait-
What's the matter with you two?
It's our thanks for saving us.
Thank you very much for helping us out.
Well... you're welcome.
Narika-san, don't do that...
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum-
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
I can't hold out any more...
I'm about to cum, too.
Takamaru-sama, please cum together with us!
I'm cumming!
That woman hasn't degenerated yet...
I won't wait any more. I'll do it.
Orochimaru, you bastard...
Nope, it's pointless to stop me.
It's finally time to break the Jougenshuu's barrier with my power.
Go if you must, Orochimaru.
Bring the Jougenshuu into your Kingdom and wipe them out!
Damn right!
W-What's that?!
Is that the Noroitou's Kingdom?
Akira-sensei, the Noroitou are...!
Look at this, Ikusabe.
The enemy this time is a big one.
This is...!
Haruka-san, that is...!
Seiryuu...
It's Orochimaru's Kingdom...
Jougen Ninja Skill, Power of the Dragons!
Transform, Heaven Phoenix!
Haruka-san and Narika-san have successfully entered the Seriyuu Kingdom.
I'll leave this to you two.
What's this? No one's coming out...
It could be a trap.
Narika-san, let's go.
I'm always okay to go!
Orochimaru!
We've found you! Prepare yourself!
You took the bait, eh?
Come out!
I won't let you escape this time!
Let's continue from where we left off.
Eh? It's that barrier from last time!
Just as we predicted, huh?
Ikusabe!
I'll leave this to you.
I shall bestow...
No! Why is it my butt hole again?
Why?!
So that's your retort?
W-What?!
Takamaru...
It's okay to cum!
W-What?!
Takamaru-sama, you came for me?
My power is...
Haruka-san, Narika-san, H-power recovered.
They have broken the enemy's barrier!
Did they do it?
Dammit...
What was that? I didn't hear about it!
Orochimaru, you can't run from us anymore!
That's right.
Resign yourself!
Not just yet!
Here I go!
Here I come!
Me too!
We defeated him, right?
No, more enemies lie ahead.
Let's go.
This Kingdom which has lost its owner will no doubt disappear.
Yeah.
Hey!
I'm glad you're both safe!
I have returned, Takamaru-sama.
I'm back, Takamaru.
Yeah.
Welcome back...
both of you.