It's the Noroitou!
Help! Help! Help!
That's as far as you go, Noroitou.
I’ll be the crescent whose moonlight cleanses the endless darkness dyed with sin.
Blade of the Souha Jougenshuu, Haruka is here.
You low-ranking Noroitou ninja soldiers.
Evil machines who have destroyed the city and caused the people sufferings.
The extent of your sins are no longer forgivable.
In the name of the moonlight that I bear, I shall destroy you with my ninja skills.
Are you alright?
Yes.
Haruka-san, thank you for your hard work. You were great.
Yes, Takamaru-sama. Thank you.
Alright!
It's the Jougenshuu.
Haruka-san, you better retreat before the uproar.
Yes, I understand. I'll retreat immediately.
Thank you!!
One ; Twin Dragon Wheels
Subaru!
Don't bother about me. Just go, Haruka!
Subaru...
You're too late. The ceremony to rewrite the present has begun.
Haruka-san, are you alright?
Takamaru-sama...
The low-ranking soldiers last night who broke through our Jougenshu seal last night,
were merely junior combatants.
But in due time, the high ranking Noroi warriors will appear, won't they?
Each of you should remain vigilant.
Sealing is more effective on the stronger ones, right?
On the other hand, the weaker ones can break through the seal easily.
Haruka, you must be tired. We'll end this meeting early. I will finish the remaining work later.
No, I'm alright.
No, not that. I leave her to you.
Eh? Leave what to me?
You fool. The Ryuurinko.
That's right...
Listen up.
When Haruka is dispatched, her H-power has to be replenished.
Only you, Ikusabe, the one who inherited the blood of the leader can do that.
Somehow, when she saids it like that, it's a bit...
Takamaru-sama
What is it?
Do you hate me?
No, I don't. I thought you were really beautiful, from the time you first transferred schools here.
Then, please touch me.
Are you fine with this, Haruka-san? Even though it's a mission, still...
What is wrong with that?
Because this is normally done by those who feel for each other... something like love or like...
I love you. I can risk my life fighting because I love and believe in you, the leader.
Life... Sorry, it seems that I've taken the burden you bear too lightly.
Please don't apologize, Takamaru-sama.
You're the important person that gave me my powers.
Haruka-san...
I beg you, please touch me.
Can you feel it, Haruka-san?
Yes, it feels... ticklish.
Is this not good?
Where should I touch?
T-There.
But it is better if I grip harder, right?
Yes.
The Ryuurinko will not work if the girl isn't excited, right?
How about this place?
That is...
The Ryurinko is the contact with the dragon, sexually exciting their body and soul
to turn on the spiritual switch, Souryuurin that is sleeping within the user's body, to activate it's power.
It's called H-power.
For generations, only the leader of the Jougenshuu can activate Souryuurin.
When Haruka ecstatic pleasure from bodily contact, extraordinary abilities is retained in her.
Haruka-san, you're really wet.
Takamaru-sama.
Let me feel good as well.
Yes.
Feels good, Haruka-san. More...
I'm going in, Haruka-san.
I'm prepared.
Does it hurt?
No, I'm alright, please continue putting it in.
Haruka-san, is this your first time?
Yes, but I've already prepared myself. Please go deeper inside me.
Takamaru-sama, please don't mind me and continue.
More, more, Takamaru-sama.
Takamaru-sama, Takamaru-sama.
Amazing, Takamaru-sama.
Takamaru-sama, please give me your essence.
I'm almost there, Takamaru, it's coming, it's coming.
I can't anymore, I-I'm cumming.
It's just a matter of time before we break the Jougenshuu's seal.
Woo-hoo! I can't wait to wreak havoc outside.
Don't be impatient, Orochimaru.
Before that, we have to annihilate the interfering Jounin who outnumbers us.
Eventually, the woman who will take this era to the next shall become useful.
Let go of me.
I won't give in. Let go of me! S-Stop it!
Akira-sensei.
Is it Noroi?
Noroitou appeared at two different places at the same time.
Two places at the same time?
I'll set out immediately.
Akira-sensei, let me take care of the other place.
Hold on Ikasabe, Narika has left for the other place.
Narika did?
Please support Haruka as usual.
Okay.
Jougen ninja skill, Power of the dragons
Transform, Heaven Phoenix!
Bestow appropriate punishment to the sinners, it's all for our Nogoi.
Come forward you sinners!
Your evil deeds ends there.
I’ll be the crescent whose moonlight cleanses the endless darkness dyed with sin.
Blade of the Souha Jougenshuu, Haruka is here!
You say Jougenshuu?
Member of Nogoi, to seek out sinners you've destroyed the city with your evil deed. The extent of your sin is unforgivable.
In the name of the moonlight that I bear, I shall destroy you with my ninja skills.
You're merely a female ninja.  If you obstruct me, I shall deliver my justice unto you.
I won't give in to your threats.
Arrogant brat, I will let you taste my special punishment.
Here I come!
It's begun, battle support standby.
Check bypass -All signal. Chakra gate release confirmed.
Haruka-san, do your best.
Jougen ninja skill, strike. Thunder Needle Strike!
One slash punishment!
Evil power response, 40% decreased.
That will do it! Thanks to Ikusabe's Ryurinko.
I'm not done yet.
Give up, member of Noroi. You don't have a chance of victory.
Are you sure of that?
I'm Takimura's kindred spirit. I'll get him out of this bind easily.
Reinforcements?
If the battle drags on, Haruka-san will...
Haruka, retreat for now. It is disadvantageous to fight too many opponents.
No, it's fine. Please let me do this.
Yo! Narika-sama has returned. I could handle it alone...
You're not as powerful as you say. When we cooperate, you don't stand a chance at all.
Now then, I should give this girl a special punishment.
Alright, I'll join you.
Ninja skill, teleport skill.
Haruka-san.
She is lost from the battlefield.
They got us. They've gone to the place we can't send help.
Takamaru.
What? Are you serious?
I have to save Haruka-san no matter what. Please give me H-power too.
I trained until this day to become a Blade.
Takamaru, please. Embrace me.
Narika, you're like a younger sister to me. How can I embrace you?
Just say Yes! I've always held on to the thought of becoming Takamaru's partner.
How do you think I felt by giving you to Haruka?
I'm the only one who can save Haruka right now, right?
I understand.
Takamaru...
I'm not ready, don't look yet.
Yeah, I know.
It's alright now, Takamaru.
Geez, stop staring at me.
Sorry.
Narika. You're cute.
Do you know, Takamaru? I feel, for Takamaru...well, never mind.
What's that about?
Just embrace me quickly.
Don't move.
No... D-Don't look.
No, n-not there.
Takamaru, if you do this...
Does it hurt?
N-No, don't talk to me.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry, I'm just embarrassed.
Narika, I'm putting it in.
Is it here?
You're close.
Ah, that place.
Alright, I'm going in.
It hurts!
Endure it, Narika.
I'll endure it, do it.
It's starting to feel weird.
Takamaru, I...
I feel it.
Is this Ryuurinko?
It's coming. Something is coming, Takamaru.
Be quiet. I am cumming soon.
There, I'm cumming too, I'm cumming!
Takamaru, I've reached my limit.
Me too, let's go, Narika. I'll cum inside you.
Come, Takamaru, Come.
Give me Takamaru's... Give Takamaru's hot thing to me, fill me up inside.
Don't come any closer.
You've lost already. We can do whatever we like to you.
No!!
Please...stop...
No, stop it.
How about it everyone? Delivering the sinner's punishment together?
I can see everything. I can't hold back anymore, too.
No, please don't look.
Well then, let me put it in.
No, Stop it.
Despite all that, you're wet enough for me to enter.
That's true. He got it in so easily.
Even though she was fighting for us, she did lose. This can't be helped then.
No, everybody. Please don't look at me.
I can't move, let me go.
Why don't you just have a taste of my mushroom?
Girl, use your hands to masturbate the surrounding people.
No way.
Don't you think Jougenshuu has to apologise to the citizens?
Enough already, just do me, here.
Over here, too.
How can this be?
It feels great, getting worked on by a female ninja I admire indeed.
Service us properly, you lost after all.
Suck on this with that small mouth of yours.
No, forgive me.
Forgive you? Then who will take the blame for losing?! Shut up and just take this!
Cumming, Cumming!
I'm... I'm cumming...
Foolish Jougenshuu. You've gotten used to this already.
It's almost time for me to use my ninja skill to transform your body.
Takamaru-sama.
Jougen ninja skill, Power of the dragons
Transform, Heaven phoenix!
Narika, I leave Haruka in your hands.
You can count on me!
To be continued