I'm coming.
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Oh Yoshimi, you should be on your break!
Where were you?
I was just checking on the patients,
silly girl!
The patient in room 308,
the one that was in an accident....
Is he still unconscious?
I haven't made my rounds there yet.
I don't...
mean to be nosy,
but I don't think it's right.
Huh?
We can't verify that patient's identity.
It's strange that he didn't have
any kind of ID at all on him!
Oh Yoshimi, he seems like
a really nice guy.
The really laid-back type, I think.
I'm just guessing,
since he's still unconscious.
It's not like I know for sure, but....
I need to get out of here soon.
I need to make sure my things are safe.
I know you're awake!
What do you think you're doing?
I'm not....
You've been seducing my co-worker!
Did she say that?
She wanted it just as much as I did.
Liar!
I'm not lying,
I know you were watching us.
Wasn't she enjoying it?
How did you know?
I'm just helping her out, you see.
It's not something you would understand.
It's a noble thing
to be dedicated to your morals.
Just understand that people
have different moral standards.
You just might want to learn something
from your co-worker.
Maybe you'll see her point of view.
If I sleep with you,
I'll see her point of view?
Maybe.
''Maybe'' isn't really a confident response.
I can't guarantee anything; it's up to you.
What do you say?
All right.
This isn't because I like you or anything.
I just want to see if there's
any truth to what you said, that's all.
I know, I understand.
Let's see.
What a cute little pussy!
You get wet very easily!
Your equipment's nice and tight!
You don't have to tell me....
Don't lick there.
No.
You should make better use
of this cute pussy.
It's good to act on your desires.
Stop doing that.
I'll come.
Did you enjoy it?
You can receive pleasure; from your
patients.
You don't need a reason to have sex.
Please, I want you inside me.
If you want to.
Relax, ok.
You're so deep inside me....
I like it.
Wait, not like that.
Oh yes...
Deeper, more, more.
I like it when you moan like that, Yoshimi.
I'm going to come...!
I can't hear you!
Come inside me!
Oh yeah!
I'm going to come!
Yes, Yes!
I can feel you coming inside me.
Fill me up....
So, what did you think?
Stop it.
Don't get a big head, okay.
Take this!
I'm kidding!
Oh my god Yoshimi!
Calm down, is there something wrong?
The patient in room 308 is gone!
The head nurse will kill us....
Don't worry.
What?
Let's go for a drink after work.
We can talk about him.
Okay.
Great!
Only 12.
This has never happened before;
I can't believe one of us is dead!
A fatal accident like that....
With all respect to the deceased,
this causes a lot of problems.
I agree.
I don't think we'll get an answer
with just 12.
You think?
I think we can overcome this problem
if we try.
I say we need to re-plan
this whole operation.
It's planned with thirteen people in mind.
I don't think so!
We've already spent a fortune.
Just because a person died....
I see, arguing already!
Cruz....
I don't....
Yes. I understand....
Yes. Bye bye.
Oh well....
Godzilla's here!
Darn it, who the hell are you?
What on earth are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
Didn't I tell everyone that
talking to strangers is a very bad thing?
He was the one talking to us!
We didn't do anything wrong!
His name is Godzilla!
You have to leave, please!
Die....Godzilla!
I see.
I always wanted to be
a pre-school teacher for a long time.
I'm hoping that this place
doesn't close down on me.
I wouldn't know what to do, then.
It can be hard,
keeping up with your dream.
That's great!
It's no big deal, really.
People are so jaded now, it's really sad!
You've been really inspiring!
No, don't!
I can't express it in words....
Maybe my body will do a better job.
Stop joking around.
If I wasn't inspired,
I wouldn't do this after just meeting you!
See, you're soaking wet already!
Just be very quiet, okay?
I'm putting it in.
Like it?
Of course, what do you think?
I want you!
I want you right now!
Here you can make all the noise you want.
I want it.
Did you say something?
I want you, your cock inside me.
All right.
I'm...I'm coming!
Me too!
I'm coming!
Come on me!
I want to see.
Oh yeah.
Yummy!
Bye bye!
Yumiko, keep following your dreams!
Sure!
See ya!
Bye bye!
Of course.
Shisui, how many times
did Cruz get away?
I can take over, if you'd like.
Is that the boss' order?
Or are you asking me?
There are those who think
you won't be able to catch him.
They think you're letting him go
on purpose.
After all, he was your partner.
Everyone wants Cruz back, or dead.
Six people have left already, so
we can't expend more people to hunt Cruz.
Shisui, why don't we become partners?
What?
I'll make sure you forget about Cruz.
What do you mean?
I know....
I'm a much better lover than Cruz.
More.
You look like you want a lot more still.
All right.
I'll prove that I'm
much better than Cruz right now.
I wonder what he's up to by now.
You'll never be my partner!
You must be joking!
I don't need a partner!
Your job is to keep
the project moving along.
I'm going to get Cruz myself!
Nobody will get in my way!
I've already set a trap!
I'm going to get you, Cruz!!
Is that a girl?
Hey, can you give me a ride?
Fantastic!
She's probably still in high school.
She's probably jail bait.
Shit, shit, my bag's been stolen!
Oh my god, I can't believe this bag
is stuffed with all this money!
Maybe drugs?
Shit!
This is heavy.
I can't hang out here too long.
I need to get out of here!
Stop, please stop!
Get out of the way, kid!
What the hell are you doing
out here alone?
Please, could you give me
a lift to the next town?
Maybe?
I'll pay you.
Hop on in.
Thank you!
Shit!
Learn to drive, mother fucker!
Watch where you're going, asshole!
What an asshole!
Yeah?
Well....
Let me go, damn it!
Hand it over!
Be quiet over there!
Wow, I've never seen so much cash!
Looks like there's at least a million yen.
That's my money, don't you dare touch it!
That's right.
She knows what we both look like.
We should kill her
and dump her somewhere.
No, no, you can have the money
if you'll let me live!
Who the fuck are you?
No, no, no, don't touch me, don't kill me!
Hi!
Where are they?
They had to attend to an emergency.
I didn't mean to steal your bag, you know.
It just happened....
Wait, you're taking it all?
What did you think, you little thief?
You're going to let me come along,
aren't you?
Take me with you!
Come on, I'll do anything.
I don't care to hang around
with little thieves like you.
I don't like people that I can't trust.
Being a kid isn't going to help.
You really want to come along?
You did say you would do anything, right?
You know what you meant by that, I hope?
You're awfully quiet all of a sudden.
Cat got your tongue?
Well, what about over here....
Are you getting weak in the knees?
You shouldn't bite off
more than you can chew.
Do you think you're so hot?
My boyfriends are all better in bed
than you!
I was kidding,
but you're going to get it now!
Huh?
You've seen it before, right.
Do you know what you're doing?
Seems you've never given a blow job!
Okay.
You don't have
a whole lot of hair down here.
Can't you forgive me?
Now you suddenly want forgiveness.
Don't think so.
Get on all fours, now.
You're definitely not experienced.
I can tell that you're still a virgin!
So tight!
I don't know that I'd fit!
We'll just have to see.
Just remember that you asked for this.
Okay. I'm coming in!
Now!
She passed out.
I was just gonna scare her!
You did it, right?
I'm not going to tell you!
Let me come with you!
You must be kidding.
Hurry back home, kid!
Here, a gift for you!
Really?
Bastard!
I'll track you down!
You'll pay for this, asshole!
I'll get you, for sure!
Where should I go now....
To be continued