No.
You can't.
Nagisa.
I want it too.
Please don't stop.
Quickly!
How do you like it, Your Ladyship
Moeko? Feels wonderful, doesn't it?
You can enjoy everybody's true
nature to your heart's content.
No! I'm not like that...
Please, no need to worry about
others whispering about you.
As you see, each of these ladies...
...has been reduced to a dirty bitch.
I'm sorry.
I said no biting!
Asami, watch.
Well, well... Contrary to your
performance in the classroom...
...you're quite an excellent student down
there.
How can I stop him?
It's no use. He took them all away.
Besides...
Are those mine?
Everybody's wearing
yours. His orders.
So he strips me and I'll obey?
I came to give these back to you.
I washed them clean.
He ordered that too?
No, because I promised you.
Take me...
...to that man!
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Shusaku the Letch
Replay
The fourth Night:
Eri Takabe
It was fun. I want to go there again.
Shall we begin dinner?
No, I don't want to go back there!
Ms. Fujima is not
the only one suffering.
Unless we stop
him now, more will surfer.
I don't want to!
No! I have a platonic
relationship with Kenji!
Platonic?
I see.
How did you...
After all, I am the manager.
It's my duty to watch over every
aspect of all your ladyships' lives.
Give it back to me!
It's no good to be this noisy for so little.
No, you can't!
No!
How did you get this?
Unfortunately, subpar picture quality.
After all, it's an amateur video.
He tapes the girls he
picks up, then sells the video.
What a sleaze.
No way! Kenji
wouldn't do such a thing.
He was so proud
when he sold me this tape...
...telling me how...
...he took away...
...your virginity.
In such detail...
...and with a memento.
No!
How can you...
...show the other young ladies this?
How about a trade...
...Your Ladyship Moeko?
How did this happen?
Don't give in.
Ms. Fujima.
You can say that
because you haven't been hurt.
You have a cute little butt.
Ms. Fuiima?
Eri, could you fight it if he does
something terrible to you?
I don't know.
He might debauch my body...
...but I won't let him spoil my heart.
No way! You won't be saying that!
I can fight it.
If you can't believe my words...
...you can do to me
what has been done to you.
I just might do that.
As you wish.
You're being stubborn.
It's your call.
He might debauch my body...
... but I won't let him spoil my heart.
Take it in deeper.
Your body stands in
for hers. There you go.
How do you like it, Eri?
No!
But I...
What is this?
I can see...
I don't know why...
...I can see everybody's
suffering heart.
You can see our hearts?
Ms. Maejima is suffering.
She's fighting to save
her heart from debauchery.
Ms. Maejima is...
I have to go.
Tell me where he is.
I can't go with you.
Fine.
No, not there.
Gotta keep your asshole shiny clean.
Ms. Maejima, raise your rear end.
Ms. Minami, you mustn't do that.
Where is Mr. Kato?
What's happening to all of you?
Nothing.
We're just being honest with ourselves.
I discovered...
...I've been mean to Ms. Minami
because I wanted her attention.
It's all his doing.
You're wrong, Eri.
He did hurt us...
...but we don't hate him.
Right. If not for this,
I wouldn't have known...
...my feelings for Chiaki,
my own desire.
Ms. Kurihara!
Chiaki, clean me up.
Ms. Takabe.
It's better not
to know the human heart.
Once you do, it may go out of control.
Now that we know...
...there's no turning back.
But you must!
As I said, it's better not to know.
The only way to end it all...
...is not to go back,
but to go forward. That's his message.
Mr. Kato is waiting for you
in the dining hall.
End? How do you mean?
I just figured out how to stop him.
You saw how it's going to end, right?
What?
I'm beginning to sense it a little.
This won't look good.
Ms. Fujima?
I give you this
because you lent me your bloomers.
This is against school rules though.
Pink. Is that my color?
We'll see.
Go now.
Well, well, Lady Eri.
Is Your Ladyship hungry too?
If you could wait a few minutes...
...I will fill you up like this.
How far will you go?
It was for dessert.
Yours truly mixed
the aphrodisiac carefully.
But maybe it was too strong
for these innocent ladies.
Haven't you had enough?
The game's over!
You're kidding.
In the face of this solid reality?
You know it too, don't you?
Ever since I met you,
I've always wondered...
...how could I see through your plans?
Are you saying you're clairvoyant?
It all became clear to me.
Because you expected me to be...
...because I am...
...an illusion born of your reason!
Oh, well.
What a clown I have been.
I have prided myself on
living free and greedily...
...following my desires,
doing what my instincts tell me.
But now to find out I was nothing
but a character in a game...
...a cheap object to be manipulated.
Each human heart wages a conflict
between reason and desire.
I am the reason.
You are the desire.
You're not the only one
who's been manipulated.
Me too.
Morning.
Good morning.
What are you doing here, Ms. Fujima?
You forgot?
They kept me out after curfew.
Guess I forgot to close it.
It's cold!
Can I go back to sleep?
W-Well...
Not that!
Wait!
Just affirming our friendship!
Shall we continue where we left off?
No.
We don't have time!
You gotta be kidding! Eri, the shower!
Ouch.
My life is back.
No. My life that exists only
in my memory has come.
I'll be right out. You want to join me?
Just kidding. But you can take a peek.
But it is a little different from before.
I still want a knight on a white horse.
Okay, keep dreaming.
But I really do.
Waiting for the bathroom too, Eri?
No, I...
She says that she is
a princess waiting for a prince...
...but she wants me
to do something for her.
I can't do it by myself.
Then why not do it now quickly?
Okay.
But you'll do it to me later
when we go back to our room?
We'll see.
You mustn't wash your
underwear in the machine anymore.
But...
Let me wash them by hand.
But they're a little soiled.
I know. I did it to you last night.
Could you do me tonight?
Then I'll wash your
underwear tomorrow.
Moeko, you're taking
your time this morning.
Kaori, you'll be late too.
Don't worry.
I'll have them start
the class late for me.
Start the class late?
What did you say?
Ms. Minami!
Just because you're the school
board chairman's granddaughter!
Words are not enough
to get through to you.
Oh no!
Please stop!
Everybody's watching!
That's why it's so good.
I cannot tell if our life now...
...is good or bad.
One thing I know for sure, Mr. Kato,
is that you're wrong on one count.
Only we girls are the game characters.
And you probably are...
Let's go.
There's more fun waiting for you.