Heave-ho!
I'm off, Miss Sayaka!
Yeah.
Um...
See you.
Since that day, things have
been weird between me and her.
Shin! More!
Pound me harder!
My husband...
Make me forget about my husband!
Miss Sayaka!
We're not even lovers,
and something like that happened...
I've always liked
Miss Sayaka, so it's fine...
...but I'm sure she feels
horrible about her late husband.
This is all for today's delivery, right?
What's wrong, Shin?
You're not cheerful.
That's not true...
No, Shin you're being weird.
You don't have that usual
beastlike glimmer in your eyes.
What do you
mean by beastlike?
I don't want to see you like this.
If it'll cheer you up, I'll do anything.
What do you mean by anything?
Of course, even if
it's something perverted.
If you wish for it.
Miss Mari...
Then could you
put this on and help me?
What is that?
As time goes on, it will eventually...
Wow!
Dirty Laundry
Episode 2
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Asai Cleaning!
Please consider us.
Please.
Thank you for your help.
This isn't me taking advantage
of Miss Mari's offer to help.
Please.
Please consider us.
Asai Cleaning.
Please.
Please consider us.
Asai Cleaning...
Please consider us...
Shin...
I can't hold it in anymore...
Miss Mari, it can't be helped, huh?
Then why don't we have
sex in this shopping town.
That's what I'm talking about.
Look, if we do this...
...no one can look
in from the outside...
...but from inside, we can see out.
It's clear.
It feels like we're being watched,
and it turns me on so!
I want yours, Shin!
Wait!
I want you to take this out
without using your hands.
Okay, wait a second.
Shin, if you're going to be happy...
It feels like what's inside
is going to come out too!
You're right.
With all the love juice,
l can see the pink petals inside...
It's coming...
It's going to come out...
Shin...
Shin!
Miss Mari...
So then!
It feels so good...
That's amazing...
It's Miss Mari's ejaculation.
It's pouring out like
a waterfall, and it won't stop!
Then put a cork into
my fountain with yours.
I want yours, Shin!
If it's my customer's wish,
then l have no choice.
Hurry! Hurry!
Put it in!
More than happy to.
Shin! Shin!
The real thing is the best!
This is good.
You're shaking the car so much
that all the ladies are watching.
Then let's show off our
loving to those lonely women!
No problem, Miss Mari!
Use your imagination.
These are things you do at night too.
Look, look!
You too!
And you too!
It's good!
Well? Are you satisfied, Miss Mari?
Not yet...
Come on, hit me
like you usually do, Shin!
This is good.
It's become tighter.
Here, here, here.
Hit me more.
Hurt me more!
Ah, Shin!
This way you're going
to be turned on more.
Oh, Shin!
It hurts!
Miss Mari! Miss Mari!
Come on, I'm going
to hit you till you come.
More! Hit me harder, Shin!
Shin! Shin!
Shin, you shot so much out.
Here's the continuation...
Miss Mari, wait...
Come on,
you're young! You're young!
Miss Mari...
Miss Mari!
Man, doing this alone is hard...
I should've done it with Miss Mari
after we finished handing these out.
Please consider us!
Please consider us.
Ouch!
Hey, you!
I'm very sorry!
Hey, if you're going to hand out
fliers, then keep your eyes open!
I'm sorry.
You're not hurt, are you?
Gosh, my hair is messed up.
My skirt!
Oh man,
I'm sincerely sorry about this!
This is my favorite...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
We handle your
laundry with our full effort!
Please!
Asai Cleaning Shop
Shinji Ouhashi
You're a laundryman?
Asai Cleaning?
Yes! On us, of course!
Really...
You're a laundryman, huh?
You're coming with me!
W-Wait a second!
Um...
Miss Igarashi, why did you
take me to a place like this?
To get you to do the laundry.
Do you understand what l mean?
W-Wait!
Call me Yuko...
Come on, you sit down too.
Y-Yes...
You work for
a laundry service, right?
Uh, yes.
How's your shop doing?
If you ask...
It's not that great,
but somehow we get by...
Really...
Hm... Please do not worry.
We'll definitely clean
your skirt, Miss Yuko.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I think I've seen
your face somewhere before...
What? What?
Is it some kind of
old-school pickup line?
Or maybe we were
together in our past lives?
My gosh, it's hot.
Oh, it's hot in this room.
I definitely saw you somewhere...
Maybe I should just take it off.
It's hot...
Heave-ho!
So it seems your
shop isn't too popular...
...but how many
employees do you have?
Um, it's just the two of us,
me and my manager...
...but why are you
concerned about such things?
And about not being popular...
My gosh...
...it's just curiosity.
H-H-Hey!
Miss Yuko!
Even if you don't
have that many customers...
...isn't it hard running it
with just the two of you?
That's...
Or is your pay really good?
Miss Yuko...
...please stop!
Or does the widow manager
give you these kinds of services?
Widow...
About Miss Sayaka...
How did you...
Oute Cleaning
President
Yuko Igarashi
I remember now!
What is it?
I saw you on TV before!
Yuko Igarashi!
The president of
the Oute Cleaning franchise!
Oh, well, you found out.
What a shame.
I wanted to enjoy it
a little while longer.
Speaking of...
...I heard there's going to be
a location opening by the train station.
If you're spying like this...
...you must be planning
to get rid of Asai Cleaning.
You don't say.
It's not like that.
I've collected info about other
stores before setting the location.
Then...
It's because I met you by chance.
I thought it'd be nice
to get some insider info.
What's with that attitude,
after you tried to deceive me?
Are you making fun of me
because you're the president of Oute?
Huh?
It hurts!
Let go of me!
That hurt...
I was just playing with you a little.
You don't have
to get all serious, okay?
Don't underestimate a laundryman!
Get back here!
No, let go of me!
Let go!
No!
Let's see if those breasts are
good enough to deceive people!
Hey, stop it!
What's this?
It hurts...
How could you think of deceiving
me with those sagging breasts?
That's horrible...
I'm used to having my dick being
sandwiched between boobs like this!
Stop it! Please stop!
Look how hard your nipples are.
You're turned on,
aren't you, Miss President?
That's not...
...true...
Are you sure?
Are you turned on because
I'm being rough with you?
There are many perverts
among the rich, huh?
That's classism!
You're totally soaked
down here already.
You whore!
It's all soaked already
Normally you hate on men...
...but the truth is you want
a guy's dick so badly, right?
That's not... true...
Okay, I'll give you a man's!
No no no no!
Say what you want.
It's going to keep on coming!
Look!
All of it's already in!
Here here!
No, no!
No!
Even if you say no,
your pussy's sucking...
...me in and won't let me go!
Please forgive me already!
I'll try not to take
your shop's customers!
That depends on ability.
There's no need for deals!
Shin the Laundryman is a man!
I can't anymore!
If you go any rougher than this...
...I'm... I'm...
Me too...
Come on, check
the whiteness with your own eyes!
No...
For a big company president,
you're pretty clumsy.
You pig woman!
Well, if you act all high and
mighty, then men wouldn't want you.
You were able to do it with me and
finally felt like a woman again, right?
Then why don't you
actually act like a woman...
You better not think you were
able to make me come with that.
What?
Preach about being a man
after you make me come.
Come on, you have to get bigger...
...or you won't be able to satisfy me.
Good boy.
If you do it any more
than that, I'm gonna...
Not yet...
You're not allowed
to come with only this much.
If you're going to come,
you have to come inside me.
Hey, what happened
to your energy from before?
You need to use your hips too!
Miss Yuko...
Yes, pound me!
Pound me more!
That's right!
Yes, there!
I'm at my limit already, Miss Yuko...
Please let me come...
Not yet! Please hold it in!
A little more...
Just a little more...
I'm about to come!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
Thank you for your business!
It was just getting started...
Man, did I do too much?
What should l do if she comes
tying to close down Asai Cleaning...
No! I'm going to save
the shop with Miss Sayaka!
I've decided!
Please wait for me, Miss Sayaka!
Yutaro...
It's been six years
since you passed away...
l smelled another man's scent...
I'm sorry...
It's someone with a scent like
yours that calms one's heart...
...but I don't have
the courage to rely on him.
I'm back!
I just returned.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll separate them later,
so just leave it there for me.
Yes! Um...
I wonder what
happened to that voucher...
Miss Sayaka... Miss Sayaka!
Shin...
Let go of me...
Why are you running
from me, Miss Sayaka?
I'm not running from you...
Then would you listen
to what I have to say?
O-Okay...
I could only give
you something like this, but...
T-This is...
Would you marry me?
Shin, I'm really happy you're doing
this for me, but l have a husband...
But your husband
isn't here anymore!
Do you hate me?
Then why?
I can't just betray my husband...
It's not betrayal!
I'm sure your husband
wishes for you to be happy too!
But...
Miss Sayaka!
The scent of lots of sweat...
I feel like I'm going
to go crazy again...
Shin...
Today, it's my turn
to mess you all up.
Shin!
This is the last time...
Miss Sayaka...
Miss Sayaka!
I'm so happy l could
become one with you.
Shin!
Shin, yours is getting harder...
It's proof that you long for me.
Miss Sayaka, I love you...
Miss Sayaka...
Shin...
Miss Sayaka!
Miss Sayaka,
I don't want to let go of you...
Shin...
I want to walk together deeper...
This scent...
I don't think I can go on
without your scent, Shin...
Miss Sayaka...
Don't let go of me...
Shin, don't let go of me!
Miss Sayaka...
Shin!
Shin is coming inside me...
Maybe I should become
a little more honest...
Yeah...
Miss Sayaka...
Then...
Hey, is no one here?
Just because there
aren't many customers...
Not having anyone watching
the shop is so careless...
Welcome...
...Miss Yuko?
What did you come here for?
Don't make that face...
...darling!
D-Darling?
You've become my favorite.
Huh?
I didn't know having a guy
be rough with you felt so good.
So I've decided to make
you my significant other.
What?
Shin...
Who is she?
Um, she's...
Someone special to him of course.
What...
Really...
I'm the manager of this place.
We've vowed
to share our future together.
Miss Sayaka!
Darling and I have vowed
to share our future together too!
No, I didn't promise that!
Shin!
I couldn't wait any more
and brought the laundry!
My gosh, are you
all fighting for Shin?
Could you let me join too?
Miss Masayo, you too?
Um... it's...
I was embarrassed but thought
you'd be happy, so I worked hard.
I came twice before I got here.
Hey, Shin,
what's the meaning of this?
Darling, could you explain?
Uh, it's...
I just thought I should make
the customers happy, so...
Miss Sayaka...
Shin, you idiot!
Lecher! Pervert!
I hate you!
I thought my feelings for Miss
Sayaka were beyond saving, but...
Eight months later...
Heave-ho!
Please don't push yourself
too much, Miss Sayaka.
I'll be fine.
That's right.
The sex we had that night
hit the bull's-eye, and...
Well, she got pregnant.
It became official that we're
going to be married next month.
Miss Sayaka, I'm off!
Good luck...
...Daddy!
I'll work hard!
That's right.
Use your hips more, Shin!
Yes, leave it to me!
It's good! Shin, that's good!
It's kept secret from
my love, Miss Sayaka...
...but to keep the shop running...
...and in exchange
for canceling the rival shop...
That's right...
Clean it well.
I'm working hard on
servicing our returning customers.
Blindfolds make me...
...feel like I'm being
violated, so it's amazing!
When you're coming,
come in my face!
More than happy to!
Shin...
You've improved your skills.
Thank you very much.
It's thanks to your support.
I've got others to do, so I'll be going.
What?
You're leaving already?
Miss Masayo, I'll give
you some special service.
What?
This is way too much service!
But it's good.
So please keep on
favoring us, Miss Masayo.
Shin, you're the best!
Being a laundryman is hard work!