Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Excuse me....
Well, I need money right now.
I thought....
Did you hear that?
Are you selling yourself to us?
Sorry sweetheart.
Not interested.
We have the right to choose, too.
You should try someone older.
God damn it.
This isn't working.
What should I do?
That hurts!
Are you okay?
Can you answer me?
Hey, hey, are you all right?
I--I'm starving!
Thank you for buying me food!
This is my first good luck today.
My stupid motorcycle ran out of gas earlier.
And nobody would let me hitch-hike, either.
And to top it off, it's raining like mad.
You can always call a cab,
and buy an umbrella at a store.
With all the cash you're carrying....
I don't think you're really broke.
Is it stolen money?
You saw it?
All right, then.
I'll tell you; this money is
for spending on girlfriends, period.
What the...?
You know,
girlfriends are so damned expensive now.
You know, gifts, dinner, stuff.
So this cash is reserved strictly
for those kinds of expenses only.
In that case, would it be possible
for you to spend the money on me?
Hey, now little girl,
you shouldn't joke around like that, okay.
It's okay, I understand.
I'm not worth your time or money.
All right, if that's what you really want me to do.
You can take as much as you want.
But, this isn't going to be just a simple date.
You won't be able to walk upright tomorrow.
Don't you want to know why I need money?
If you wanted to tell me,
you already would have done that.
I'm really clumsy and ungraceful and not pretty.
Kids pick on me so much at school.
It just keeps getting worse and worse...
and now they're demanding money from me, to....
Your name was Emi, right?
You don't have to put up with that.
Huh?
But...
You shouldn't let others affect
your self-confidence.
It's important to take care of yourself
and your needs.
It's your life, live it how you want to.
Besides...
I immediately thought
you were very pretty when I met you.
So, what do you want?
What?
It's your decision, Emi.
You can go home if you want to.
You want to stay?
Are you sure?
Your tits are so nice and firm,
they feel good.
And you have pretty, pink nipples.
Right there.
It's so warm and soft down here, too.
Just relax and enjoy yourself.
Wow!
No, stop, it's embarrassing!
Very nice.
You have such a pretty little pussy, you know.
I didn't know.
Well, you know now, baby.
I'm getting really hard.
Can you make him happy?
You know what I want, right?
Okay, we're done with foreplay for now.
Please, be very gentle.
I think...
something is changing inside me.
Y--Yes!
Yes!
I can feel it inside.
My confidence is awakening inside me.
I can feel...
my brand-new self.
Yes, yes!
Please!
More, harder, faster, please!
I love it, yes!
I'm coming right now!
Yes!
I'm coming, too!
Are you sure you don't need money?
Let me at least pay you for dinner.
No, that's all right.
I think you gave me the strength
to become a stronger person.
To control my life.
That's good.
Someday, maybe we'll see
each other again, huh?
Yeah, maybe.
Later!
Maiko, that really tickles!
Stop it, you know you need
to apply sunscreen.
Yes, but...
Be still, I'm almost finished.
But....
I don't tan there.
Just let me worry about it.
It's hard to apply it here by yourself.
Oh, stop!
And you need plenty right here.
Oh, Lori, you're so adorable.
I think...
Maiko, I want....
W--What?
What was that?
Who is he?
No idea.
I'm outta here!
No, are you really serious?
You brought that guy's bag over here?
You know he almost killed the both of us.
Oh come on!
That doesn't mean you can just take his money
and spend it.
I don't plan on spending all of it, by all means.
He's probably looking for his money like crazy!
Of course I am!
H--How did you get in here?
The window, on the fifth floor?
I want my stuff.
Oh, the money, you mean?
Of course I'll give it back.
Did you spend any?
Of course not!
I'll be taking off now.
Wait a minute!
Oh, don't be in such a hurry.
At least stay and have a drink with us!
Want to?
Maiko!
Cheers!
Hey, we should have some fun.
Huh, what?
Get naked.
I'll take off my clothes, too.
Just be quiet.
You like it?
I fucking love it!
Your tits are firm and large and soft!
It's absolutely fantastic, I think.
I'm glad you like it.
So, does this mean we get to have sex?
Your name was Lori, right?
Do you have any cool tricks, too?
Can you hold on a minute?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Maiko!
Shh, he isn't getting really shit faced
like I planned.
I thought we could tire him out.
You really want that money that badly?
What do you think?
Come on, help me out, please, please!
All right, I'll be right out.
Yeah?
What's she going to do?
No idea.
I think I'm ready now.
Here.
What's so special about that?
A kitty. Meow!
Ouch, come on, have a sense of humour!
That just was not funny, period.
Wow!
I thought that was hilarious!
Huh?
C--Coming!
I'm coming!
Damn it, you're done awfully quick.
I haven't come yet.
No worries!
I can keep going!
What?
I'll make you both come.
All right?
I want your cock, too.
Be fair, okay?
I'm coming!
Bad hangover.
That guy could drink like fish and fuck, too.
He fucks like the Energizer bunny!
It was definitely worth it, though.
Hey Maiko, there is something fishy
about this money.
Huh?
Thank you for waiting.
So, what's the verdict?
These are not counterfeit bills.
Are you one hundred percent sure?
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.
There is one peculiarity.
The bills are in numerical order.
Are you sure about this?
Of course!
The bank even verified that it's legit cash;
besides, it's probably stolen, laundered money.
He probably stole it from somebody.
This is stealing, you know.
It's perfect, really.
That means he can't go to the police about it.
All right!
I'm starting to feel really giddy!
I can buy Prada, Gucci, Hermes....
Wow, I'm going to go shopping!
I'm going back to the hotel.
Wait a minute, Lori!
This whole thing just isn't right.
I'm not going back with you.
Maiko.
Come on, you're supposed to be
my best friend, right?
Don't you want money?
I swear, we'll never get caught!
We didn't tell him our address
or anything like that.
We'll never have a chance like this.
We can have so much fun with this!
I'm sorry. I can't.
Lori!
Shit, damn it!
What am I supposed to do by myself?
Hey.
I want to talk to you about the money you have.
What are you talking about?
Who the hell are you?
I need to talk to you right now,
so come with me.
He's gone.
Welcome back!
You're back awfully early!
You're here!
I shouldn't be?
I get it!
You thought I would be freaking out
to find you both gone, right?
I had no worries.
I knew that you'd be back, Lori.
You're one of those really nice people.
You don't want to hurt Maiko's feelings,
so you don't say no to sex with her.
What are you talking about?
You don't need to be responsible
for other people.
You try to take care of everyone and everything.
People expect so much and depend on you
because you are so responsible and dependable.
In the end, you end up feeling overwhelmed.
It looks that way to me anyway.
I didn't....
I thought I saw a glimpse
of your true personality during sex last night.
Am I right?
I didn't come here for this.
We can talk about all you want later.
Doesn't this feel really good?
Take a deep breath and relax.
You're getting so juicy down here.
S--Stop it!
Oh yeah, it's really tight and pink and pretty!
Don't, just don't look down there!
You're really getting wet and juicy!
Stop it!
Please forgive me!
No, this is something you want, right?
Be honest with your needs, okay?
Wait! Please!
I want to suck on you, too.
So big!
I can't wait!
I want your cock to fuck me really hard.
Right there, feels good!
I love it!
Now you're being honest
This feels so good!
Yes, I'm coming!
What?
Nothing.
I feel like I'm floating on air right now.
That's really good.
Cruz.
How many satisfied customers do you have now?
Shisui, how did you...
You know that if you spend any of that money,
we can track you down right away.
Right?
Money?
Oh, shit!
Did you spend the money?
You might as well give up
because I'm not letting you go.
Awake now?
You've been taking these.
So, how many girls have you fucked?
Where are they?
Just let them go.
You think?
What should I do?
Those two don't know anything.
Do you care about them?
Maybe if you cooperate and come back with me,
I'll let them go.
Should I trust you?
You want to try?
Please. I want...
I want to feel you inside me, fucking me.
Yes!
Yes. I can feel you.
Your hard cock's pulsing.
Untie the rope for me.
Don't worry, I won't run.
I think you want me to fuck you hard, right?
I know you want all of me.
You're the best fuck ever!
Shisui, you know you've changed.
You've realized it yourself.
It's not just you, I know.
It's everyone in the group, myself included.
Please, come on me!
I can tell I've changed, Cruz...
but there's anything I can do.
We can live here, even together.
That´s impossible.
Cruz, run now!
You need to make it out of here.
Don't be stupid. Yourself!
They've made a bad decision.
They've gone totally insane!
I can't believe we're killing each other!
Yourself....
W--We have to stop them somehow.
Don't talk, okay!
Go now!
You're the only opposition left now!
Don't let them catch you, all right?
Take this.
Keep it safe, Cruz.
Now, go!
All right.
H-Hurry.
Yousuf!
Awake now?
Where? What the hell!
At least you're honestly surprised.
Well, now I feel like it was kind of worth it
chasing after you all this time.
You've been looking for me all this time?
Oh, yeah, I looked everywhere
for your stupid ass.
I hear you flew into a shack with your motorcycle.
I heard you totally wrecked
the wooden shack and fled.
That must have been you.
Only you could pull off doing something
fantastically stupid like that.
Did you see anyone?
You mean that woman?
She was in the lobby,
talking to some scary looking guys.
So, give it up!
Huh?
Cash, money!
You can't leave the hotel in your torn-up jeans.
Everything was stolen, I swear.
What!
You need to start thinking more positively.
Huh?
At least you're still alive,
so you should be happy.
You can pay me back later, so wait right here!
The keys are already in the ignition.
A trap?
Oh, well.
We need to get going real soon.
You don't want to get caught again, do you?
Wait a minute, what makes you think
you're coming along with me?
Of course I'm coming!
A couple in love on the run from the mob!
You're not serious!
I'll have you know
I do have a proper name: Mihono.
So what? That has nothing to do
with you coming with me.
All right, pay me back the money
I lent you right now.
That's not fair!
You should be thankful
that I lent you money in the first place!
You know I can't pay you back now.
Pay me back right now, damn it!
Are you going to let him go?
Don't worry about it.
I've got everything under control now.