What?
Nothing.
Just missed it.
This feeling, this warmth.
Like how?
Like this...
This softness, this plumpness,
this warm wetness.
Cruz....
I want you to take me again.
Don't you want me, too?
Come on...
I want your cock.
Inside.
In and out of me.
Feels good...
I want it in deep, I want it hard.
Thrust harder.
Shisui.
I'm... I'm about to come.
Suck on it harder.
Just like that.
I can't hold on anymore!
I'm coming!
Now, you can smile for me...
See... You have a pretty smile.
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
It's all gone, everything in the safe!
Don't look for me
Are you sure it's everything?
Everything, even the cash!
Who would have...who could have done this?
Cruz did it.
Are you sure?
Did he go nuts?
I don't care why, we need to catch him!
We can't let anyone see what he has got!
Where is Shisui?
Right here.
I know you were especially close to Cruz.
Do you think you can handle this job?
Just have him back
and bring the whole loot.
Otherwise, kill him.
Yes.
Shisui....
Cruz, I'm not going to ask you why.
Everyone wants you to come back
and to get the stuff back.
Look, see, if you come with me,
my body is all yours.
Cruz!
I'm going to catch you!
Is he crazy?
Oh well, time for a new motorcycle.
Why, why did you save me, you bastard?
You know that this doesn't mean
I'm not coming after you.
You'll never catch me.
This late at night?!
Who is it?
I need shelter.
Eh?
Oh, well, it's a bad storm; come inside.
Were you travelling in this rainstorm?
I don't have much here, but I'll bring you
something warm to drink.
Are you alone?
Yes, so I don't have anything dry...
The electricity!
What?!
No, what are you doing!
Let me go!
Please stop!
No, don't, stop it now!
Please let me go!
Do you know what you are doing?
Can't you see I'm a nun!
I can't do this!
God forgive me!
No!
Please stop!
He didn't leave after the storm passed.
Instead, he brought TV's inside the church,
and watched it endlessly.
It seemed like he was just
absorbing information.
He was not holding me as a hostage here.
I decided not to run away.
I don't know why;
there was something about his eyes.
Nooooooo!
No more, please!
Not right in front of
St. Mary and Jesus, please!
What are you doing this to me?
Why do you torture me like this?
What can you possibly
get by doing this?
Dear god...
He kept taking me whenever he wanted.
At all times of the day....
There was something
very childlike about him...
Enough already!
How long do you think
you can keep doing this?
Y...Y...Yes!
No, I can't give in to the pleasure.
I've given my body and soul to god....
But my body wants more.
Much harder and harder.
I want you to fuck me harder!
Old memories.
I thought I've forgotten....
It's coming back to me.....
No!
No, No!
Stop!
I should have forgotten this by now...
My past and present memories are
coming together into a confusing mess!
I'm coming!
I want you to come all over me, please!
This reminded me of something
from my past.
It was something I tried to forget.
At that time, it was very traumatic...
Strange, I can accept what happened now.
Why didn't you run away from me,
from here?
I have nowhere else to go.
I thought maybe I can save you,
but I think you saved me.
Saved you?
Yes, you saved me.
That was not my intention.
The first time I met you, I felt something.
There was something about you, your eyes.
I can't put a finger on it, though.
I was relying on my position to prevent
myself from becoming close to others.
I didn't want to get hurt.
Are you afraid of getting hurt?
The soul is a weak thing.
People like hurting others.
I think they think
they can be happier that way,
but that's not the way to
bring happiness, you know.
People try so hard to steal your happiness.
But it's something
that can't be stolen, only shared.
I don't know
why I'm telling you this right now.
Wait, let me go get something for you;
I hope you can use it.
Do you like it?
It looks very good on you.
Next week,
we're going to have baptisms here.
It won't be a lot of people,
but there will be a small crowd.
Would you be interested in this at all?
No...
You don't have to answer me right now.
Think about it.
I will never see him again in my life.
I was very sure.
I didn't feel any sadness;
my heart was filled with peace.
I need to wrap this up...
I'm getting hungry, and it's getting dark....
Hello!
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you like that!
I'm just travelling through this area.
I was just wondering
what you were doing with this.
U.F.O.
Huh?
I'm looking for UFO's to photograph.
I saw this last year.
Wow, I've never seen one.
See...
I really want to meet an alien....
People from around the world
have already met them,
and some even visited their planet!
Really?!
I'd bet they have a perfect,
advanced utopia, unlike here.
I want to ride in a UFO,
even if it means I can't come back.
You know it's not that bad here; you
should look at the bright side of things.
Besides, just because they're advanced
doesn't mean they'd be nice.
I'm going to sleep now.
Okay...
I didn't need a lecture from him!
Rain...
I hope he took off already.
Shit!
What are you doing here, still?
Come inside!
Just don't get any weird ideas
or try anything funny, you understand!
Got it?
ls she asleep already?
Slowly slowly.
Quietly quietly.
Slowly slowly. Uh...hi....well.
ls she awake?
I think you're right....
Do you think the earth is just very lonely....
ls she awake or is she sleep fucking?
No, more!
Wait....
Wait , what are you doing?
Coming, I'm coming!
You're leaving today?
Do you remember asking me
if the earth was lonely?
I do.
The galaxy is full of different aliens,
and I'm actually one of them.
You should have come inside me, then.
It would be cool to have an alien child!
Wanna go for it?
Absolutely!
Just kidding.
Not fair.
Later!
Thank you!
The bitch is back...
I told you I'd come after you!
It's  too quiet tonight.
This area is usually still busy at this time...
this is really kind of creepy.
Maybe there's been a vicious murder!
We might come across a headless body!
Stop it.
You get scared easily!
Whatever.
Ow ow ow ow!
Tomoko, you're not hurt, are you?
I'm okay...but what happened?
I'm not sure.
I thought I saw someone come flying.
Will you radio this in for me?
Anybody's hurt?
Don't think so.
Help me!
What's wrong?
Are you okay, are you hurt?
Help me, help me!
I'm scared.
Just calm down and talk to me!
Misato?
I need an ambulance right away, Tomoko!
Are you sure
you're not hurt anywhere, are you okay?
This crazy woman was trying
to run me off the road,
and I was trying really hard to escape.
She caught up to me, and threw me
off the bridge over there!
A crazy woman?!
I hope you're ready.
What?
I told you I'll come after you.
Hand it over right now!
Come any closer,
and I'll have to arrest you!
Don't move!
Mind your own business!
Don't come any closer, otherwise....
What!
What's going on?
Duck right now!
Unbelievable!
This way!
Wait!
She's coming!
We need to go to the main street,
into the crowd!
You don't want a pile of dead bodies,
do you?
We need to find a place to hide, now!
I think we lost the crazy woman.
She's becoming a royal pain in the ass...
Maybe I'll get lucky...
Are you okay?
Don't worry, I'm right here...
Just let me handle things...
Just lift your hips...
Wait a minute.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm an officer of the law!
This isn't working...
Let's change tactics....
No, Stop, Stop it now!
I said stop!
If you don't stop...stop, or I'll arrest you!
What do you mean by arrest me,
my dear policewoman!
I know that you really want me.
You're a liar...lies!
Then please explain why
you're so wet down here?
Shut up.
No!
Don't worry, I'm an excellent lover.
Honestly, you want me, right?
Deeper, please.
I love this!
Yes, yes, you're so big!
Coming, coming coming!
I want more, more, come deep inside me!
Really?
I want you to come inside me, fill me up!
Oh yeah, give me more!
Still scared?
No, of what?
Ouch!
Touch me again, and I'll really arrest you!
This is a change of attitude!
I need you to come to the station
and file a report.
I'm outta here!
Don't move!
Hand over that bag right now.
You're coming back with me.
Otherwise, I'll kill you right now.
All right, if I give you my bag,
will you spare my life?
You know as well as I do I can't do that.
As long as you know the secret,
I can't let you live unless you come back.
Come back, or die.
Aaargh, I was a dumb shit!
Let me pray to god before you kill me!
Cruz, stop fucking around with me.
Decide, now.
You know, I was intimately acquainted
with god through one of his servants...
I was just trying to make
this wreck of a life more righteous
by literally connecting
with god through his messengers.
Cruz!
The messenger of god had
a beautiful countenance,
like the woman
in the poster right behind you.
Cruz!!!
Cruz?
I'm such a lucky bastard,
finding that bug spray!
Cruz!!!!!
Shit!
Let's see how long I can keep this up!
To be continued