Good morning.
I looked closely at the woman
with heavy make-up...
...and I could see her beard.
It was a transsexual!
Mr. Kato!
I have to tell you something.
I don't know why you've been lying...
...but it's all over.
I have the evidence.
Anyway, I'm reporting all this
to the school board on Monday.
Prepare yourself.
Strange. I feel like
I've said all this before.
What a creep.
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Shusaku the Letch
Replay
First night:
Asami Kurihara
Why don't you stop this?
You may think you
have it all fixed up...
...but you've already made a mistake.
I found this in the bathroom.
I remember everything.
Ms. Minami?
Ms. Takabe?
What is this, Ms. Takabe?
Why would you tape
something so dirty?
It wasn't me! It was Mr. Kato.
It seemed like you were giving it to him.
If you checked Mr. Kato's ''computer...''
There must be some evidence.
I have found evidence.
One thing is for sure.
The answer is in here.
I really don't know.
Really?
Maybe your camera
is taping me even as we speak.
l wouldn't do anything like that.
Until we know for sure,
you are not allowed to leave this room.
You got that?
Why?
What if it's his trap again?
Why do I have to do this too?
Because we're breaking curfew.
And if she saw those cute panties,
she'd confiscate them...
...Kaori.
Me too.
True friends break rules together.
I can't believe it.
Nobody else wears
plain white underwear...
...at my age.
Hey.
Eri...
...are you listening to me?
I'm sorry.
What you wear
can be used to judge your life.
What does that mean?
You want students to behave
like good students?
She'll confiscate them anyway,
so why don't you just take them off?
I'm tired of your oppressive education.
My teacher says each student
should interpret the rules on her own.
So your teacher is the problem.
Don't involve him.
You're sidetracking her.
Hey! Stop that!
I can talk to your
grandfather, you know.
Do as you wish.
Cheap stuff looks good on you.
There's really bad
blood between you two.
Before you worry about me, how
long are you going to stay like that?
Eri, can I borrow a pair of yours?
I got them.
Do I really have to give them to you?
I'm taking them off right away.
He wants me to give this to you.
Will you give me back the tapes now?
But why not? I did as you told me to.
I can't.
I see. That bitch. She said that?
I didn't do anything suspicious.
Of course, I believe you.
Would you listen to me?
Actually...
I am going to sleep
here to observe you.
All right?
It wouldn't surprise me
if she confiscated them.
Everybody wears them short.
Idiot, only Kaori and I do.
Frills don't work for you.
But Chiaki gave them
to me. A matching pair.
Have you gained weight?
That's a little tight.
No! I've been on a diet.
People who worry all
the time tend to gain weight.
You're so mean.
Do nothing and
stay beautiful. That's cool.
Speaking of ''diets''...
I never heard of anything like that.
It's true. I heard it from someone
who's doing it.
But ''enemas...''
Enemas to lose weight?
I heard it's surprisingly quick.
You're kidding.
You sound like you'd like to give it a try.
Don't be ridiculous.
Tough-looking girls like you...
...especially, turn out to be masochists.
Don't say things like that.
Could be too big.
You need to go on a diet.
Stop that.
You wanna try it? I've got something.
You have what?
That feeling of holding it
for the bathroom...
It can grow on you, don't you think?
Don't touch me there!
No!
It's cold.
Close it now!
Sorry, I was in a hurry.
Moeko.
Japanese-style toilet.
How inconvenient.
I have to ask Grandfather
to do something.
Every day I have
to assume this position.
I can't stand such debasement.
No! Stop!
No, no, no!
No.
Stop. Stop it.
Bathroom...
Please.
Let me go to the bathroom.
l can't hold it.
Not inside!
Not inside.
Don't look.
Give it back to me.
My tape.
You promised to give it back to me.
Don't.
Please. Stop it.
Ms. Nagumo.
No, no.
No.
Ms. Kurihara.
Please don't, Ms. Kurihara.
Please don't.
Mr. Kato.
Make her stop.
Please.
You promised.
No.
Please stop, Ms. Kurihara.
Please.
No.
You can't.
Anything wrong?
I heard voices.
Just your imagination.
Eri, you're too quick.
I meant to surprise you.
Off I go.
Ms. Fuiima.
You don't need to wash them.
Please give me back...
...my bloomers.
I'll bring them to you later.
Strange...
For him not to come as ''promised...''
Very naughty to come all
the way dressed like that.
You're all exposed too.
You surprised me.
I just remembered...
...you were going to give them to me.
So cute.
How do I look?
Put something on
or you'll catch a cold.
See?
Moeko!
Don't worry. Be still.
Don't.
You mustn't. Stop.
Let's continue in my room.
I'll be waiting.
How long will I be under supervision?
Don't misunderstand.
I'm not expecting...
Moeko?
Who are you?