The demons shall be reborn.
Beasts from the lowest circle of hell...
Rape! Rape! Rape them!
Embrace all that is debased and
carnal, and build a new hell on Earth.
Who goes there?
Dancers of celestial raiment,
the Tenjin Watchers!
We slay foul beasts in God's stead!
Demons, begone!
We are the Twin Dolls!
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Twin Dolls
Legend of the Heavenly Beasts
I-I yield.
How can she be
so graceful and beautiful?
It's more like dancing than fighting.
It's just a prissy girl's moves.
That was Saeko Takamochi.
She's just jealous.
She's the one who went from the
naginata and bow to the kodachi...
...because Mai and Ai came.
Pride wouldn't allow it.
She was the naginata
and bow champion, right?
There's no way she can beat them,
so she prefers not to compete at all.
It's one weapon only till second year.
At lead a kodachi
doesn't compete with them directly.
Mai's cute...
...but her twin sister, Ai, is gorgeous!
Yeah, I really admire her!
Oh, Ai... I just want
you to embrace me once.
See you later!
Ai!
Mai! Look this way!
Hi there!
Sis, wait up!
Don't act so frivolously.
Frivolously?
If you're going to flirt so shamelessly,
do it away from me, okay?
What's with that? It makes me angry.
I used to be the center of attention till
those twins came to Tenjin Academy...
The boys used to wait
in groups to see me walk by...
Then they had to come to this town...
I'm losing my rightful position!
My appearance
isn't inferior to those girls.
My figure...
...isn't inferior either.
My body should turn on guys more!
All right...
W-Who?
You know you like it.
You know you want more!
No!
Stop it!
Man, it tastes great!
She's getting numb!
No!
S-Stop it!
Somebody!
You know you want it!
You want it licked more!
No! No!
Stop it...
Her nipples are
getting harder, my brother.
Oh, yes, and her juices
are flowing down here.
You want me to put it in?
You want me to, right?
Stop, please...
No!
My horn has so many bumps!
No! Stop!
No! No!
Stop... Stop...
Please stop...
Saeko, do you hate those twins?
M-Master Hakumouki!
Who are you?
I am one who hates
the Amatsu sisters as much as you.
Feel the love nectar flow,
gushing from your trembling vagina.
You want this?
Do you want me to take you?
Spare me... Please...
Stop... Stop...
No!
Well? Do you want it now?
If you do, ask for it.
I-I want it... P-Please...
Your true colours show at last, eh?
Cry and beg for it. Say, ''Please pound
me. Pound me hard and stir me up.'
P-Please, pound me.
Pound me as hard
and deep as you can!
Like this?
Does it feel good?
I-It does...
More... More...
You like it, eh?
You are truly suited to be our servant.
Like this?
Yes!
I am Hakumouki
prince of demon beasts.
My lord...
You are my minion from this day.
Yes, I will do anything
you say. So please...
Please what?
Please, don't stop!
Stir me up like crazy!
Like this? And this? And this?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
This is the baptism
of the demon beasts.
Looks like a storm.
Mai.
Do you feel a chill?
Yes, you too?
In this season... It's no cold either.
Yes?
The headmistress is calling for you.
Grandma?
You called, Grandmother?
Be seated. I have much to tell you.
I had planned to tell you this after you
mastered our secret priestess dance...
...but the time has come
for me to tell you your mission.
Mission?
Correct. Have you felt
the strange chill in the air?
Yes.
You felt it too, Grandma?
It is a foul premonition that only heirs
of the Amatsu school can sense.
Grandmother!
What are you saying will happen?
The world
of demon beasts will open!
World of demon beasts?
What's that?
Before I tell you...
...I must first reveal the secret of
the Amatsu school's priestess dance.
Our priestess dance...
...is a dance of celestial raiment, which
was handed down the head family.
Raiment?
A celestial maiden's?
Correct.
It was documented in Oumi during
the seventh year of the Yourou.
Eight celestial maidens descended north
of Biwa Lake to bathe in Lake Yogo.
Taiyu Kirihata was hiding and watching,
entranced by a beautiful one.
He hid her celestial raiment and courted
her. In modern terms, he proposed.
Oh...
No fair.
Don't interrupt, Mai.
The celestial maiden could not
return to heaven without her raiment.
Eventually she opened up
to his kindness and married him.
Three children were born, and
the older two were twin daughters.
The third was a boy and was much
loved and coddled by his sisters.
He was smart enough
to be called a prodigy.
A noble named Koreyoshi Sugawara
heard of him and adopted him...
...and his name became
Michizane Sugawara.
The chief calligrapher named him
head keeper of imperial archives...
...and young Emperor Uda
promoted him to minister of the right.
But Tokihira Fujiwara, an influential
person at the time, was envious.
Charging Michizane with
a groundless plot against the emperor...
...he demoted him
to virtual exile in Dazaifu.
Michizane died in bitter exile
and became a vengeful spirit...
...that cursed the capital
as the embodiment of thunder.
The fearful Fujiwara clan...
...deified him as Tenjin and
suppressed their resentment.
They feared Michizane as
a blood descendant of gods.
The celestial maiden died of grief,
and her body became a clear thread.
The surviving sisters
wove that into celestial raiment.
Those sisters were
the ancestors of the Amatsu family.
Since that time,
whenever twin sisters were born...
...our family has passed
on the secrets of the art.
I never knew we were
descendants of a celestial maiden.
As heirs to her blood, the head family of
the Amatsu school of priestess dance...
...lived to protect Tenjin's line
continuously for 1100 years.
We are also called Tenjin Watchers.
Tenjin Watchers?
All keepers of the dance
are her descendants.
Grandma, so Tenjin
has descendants somewhere?
Correct.
Where?
I don't know.
But we shall see it soon.
The threads of destiny decree it.
Grandmother, what about
the demon beasts you spoke of?
Regarding that...
Demons that lure mankind
into carnality
and corruption taking advantage
of the ensuing chaos.
That is what demon beasts are.
So this chill in our flesh is...
A sign that they've
returned once again.
Just what is this world
of demon beasts?
An evil world sprung from
the same heavens as ours.
The same?
If we are descendants of the light,
they are ones of the dark.
They seek Tenjin's descendant
in order to take over this world.
What was that?
Grandmother?
Those were imps from the beast
world. They were spying on us...
How ominous!
Could it be the revival of
Oniyasha Doji is upon us?
Everything is set, master of
our world of demon beasts...
...Oniyasha Doji.
Be reborn and lead us
to a debauched hell!
I knew Tenjin, the god of scholarship,
was Michizane Sugawara...
...but I never knew our
ancestors had a connection to him.
Though Sis doesn't seem
too surprised about this.
I wonder what kind of person
Tenjin's descendant is.
Maybe he's like Shining Genii,
noble and valiant.
I gotta pee.
Again, young master?
When nature calls, nature calls! Idiot!
You gonna come too?
I'll stay here, young master.
This is the treasury of female bodies!
There are so many
mangos and papayas!
A kid did this?
What are you doing? I won't take this!
Come with me.
Ouch!
Hey, if you're peeping at your age,
you'll grow up to be no-good.
I'm in love!
You're perfect for me!
What are you talking about?
No way! He's aroused!
It's decided!
Take it easy! Get me off!
I can't take it anymore!
What are you doing?
Get off me, you pervert!
I said let go! Let go of me!
Young master. Young master.
Please behave yourself.
Let go! Let go, you rude guy!
Please excuse him.
As you can see, he has been
raised in ignorance to society's ways.
Would you please
overlook his actions?
That costume and how
you speak are kind of off...
If one lives deep in
the mountains away from society...
...one would not know how
to live amongst modern folk.
We will be leaving now, so once
again, please accept our apologies.
By the way...
...do you know where the Amatsu
family of priestess dance is?
Amatsu is my family's name...
Tenjin must have guided us together!
Young master!
Young master! Rejoice!
Gosh, what was that all about?
I'm in love, Dekunobou!
I'm going to make her my mistress!
We came from the mountains of
Kumano without eating for nine days...
His name is Onimaro, is it?
Dekunobou, thank you
for your caretaking up till now.
No, this is my task. I was told
by the oracle to leave the mountains...
...and bring him
to the Amatsu household.
You may relax, because from
this day forth, we Tenjin Watchers...
...will assist you in protecting him.
I'm grateful.
Master Onimaro, I am Genshu Amatsu
of the Tenjin Watcher head family.
Please remember my name.
Young master!
Now that Master Onimaro
is here, take proper care...
...not to neglect the barrier that goes
from this house to Tenjin Academy.
Certainly.
Damn them!
A barrier of celestial raiment?
Saeko, you must destroy this barrier!
Saeko!
Junko, you want me to do you?
I've always felt you looking at me.
You want to have sex with me, right?
Saeko...
How does it feel?
I feel like I'm going to melt!
Now you are a slave
to Master Hakumouki too.
Lure Mai out.
Understood?
Hey, Sis, tell me. This guy...
...the one we'll protect,
is Tenjin's descendant, right?
I guess.
What kind of person is he?
Young? Handsome?
I'm sure he's gallant.
You're better off not knowing.
Jeez, you're so mean!
Change quickly and
come to the training hall.
Grandma?
I have to give you girls something
while Master Onimaro is sleeping.
Yes.
Master Onimaro? That's his name!
This is the celestial raiment
passed down our family...
...and some of Tobiume,
the plum tree that flew...
...from the capital to comfort
the adrift Michizane in Dazaifu.
Both these things possess
the mysterious powers of Tenjin.
Take these and perform the priestess
dance you've practiced up till now.
Right!
Now, show me the dance.
Breathing out, in, and stopping!
Unite your hearts
and do not lose control!
Ai! Mai! Dance without fear!
Right!
You did it! That's the first
Tenjin celestial raiment dance!
Excellent!
We did it!
Do not forget that
timing of your breath.
Eventually, if you continue training,
each part of the dance...
...will become a method of protection
against those filthy demon beasts.
Your awareness powers
can reduce its size.
From this point on,
keep them with you at all times.
I'll tie mine around my wrist.
It'll be my hair ribbon.
When you perform
with the celestial raiment...
...recite, ''Rise, Tenjin. First Dance.'
Rise, Tenjin. First Dance.
The scent of young women!
I never cared for practice before,
but this secret technique is exciting.
Your breath control is still a problem.
I refuse to end up in an unknown demon
world due to your lack of technique.
Yeah, yeah, I'm an inferior little sister.
I'm sorry, okay?
Let's get out.
I will as soon as
I warm up a little more.
I'm in love!
Mai!
You again?
Uh-oh, he's going to drown!
Oh boy!
I-I'm crazy for you...
It's big!
How big is it?
Ai, Mai, what did you
do to Master Onimaro?
Master Onimaro? No way.
He's totally not what I had in mind!
He's also extremely perverted.
Please don't say such things.
Young master, are you all right?
He is Onimaro, the one that
the Tenjin Watchers must protect.
And this is Dekunobou, his protector.
Thank you for the hospitality.
We'll be staying awhile.
So he's staying?
I've got a bad feeling.
Master Hakumouki...
Everything is ready.
Tomorrow, lure them
out here into our hands.
Yes, as you wish...
It's fitting that our old enemies,
the Amatsu sisters, be sacrificed...
...at Lord Oniyasha Doji's resurrection
ritual. Lead them outside the barrier.
I will. I've already ordered
someone to lead Mai out.
Once we have Mai
it should be easy to lure Ai out.
How crafty, Saeko!
And a damn good screw too. I like it.
Then please pound me harder!
From the front or the back?
Do you want me to pound every orifice?
Yes! Yes, Master Hakumouki.
Please pound me in every orifice!
How's this, you slut?
Yes!
Like this, huh? Like this? Like this?
Right there!
I'm in love! Ai! Mai!
I'm so happy!
Touch!
Don't be mean!
I'm just a poor little guy!
Ouch!
Master Onimaro, are you okay?
Ai's cold, but you're kind, Mai.
Boys aren't allowed at school,
so please stay here and behave.
No no no! I want to go too!
Even if you say that...
Let me touch you!
Then I'll hold it in for today!
I'm off!
Ai! Mai! Wait up!
Young master, what are you up to?
It's all your fault!
Let go! You think you can
do this to your master?
That really depends on the situation.
Mai, want to grab some tea?
We found a really swell place.
I'm waiting for my sister.
Ai has special training for
the championships. She'll be late.
Sisters or not, it's impure
to do everything together.
It's not like that.
Let's go!
You should go out with us once in
a while. You'll lose friends otherwise.
There's a tea house around here?
It just opened.
It's a nice atmosphere.
And it's elegant.
I'll lift up all their skirts.
Dekunobou,
are you going somewhere?
Oh, Mistress Genshu.
We cannot be caught unprepared...
...should imps from the beast
world intrude upon the estate.
It is possible that Mai and Ai
could be attacked at school.
In thanks for the free boarding,
l will at least escort them.
You have a strong sense
of duty. You needn't fuss.
Mai...
Sis...
I'll meet my sister after all.
What's wrong, Mai?
I'm just...
That won't do, Mai Amatsu.
You're Takamochi
the student-council president.
What does that mean?
That you'll never return.
To the academy or your own home.
What the hell? You're...
I'll have you come quietly!
Mistress Ai!
Where's Mai?
She has yet to return to the house.
Then this premonition was...
This way!
What happened to Mai?
Let me go!
What happened to you guys?
An incubus from the beast world?
Good guess.
Indeed, I am Hakumouki
of the beast world.
I've come to drag you two
into a debauched hell.
Sis, don't come!
They're twins, so they're linked.
True, that saves some time.
Looks yummy!
We'll enjoy you as much as possible!
No! Stay away!
Hands off my girl!
Master Onimaro, run!
What was that? Onimaro?
Tying to run?
I won't go easy!
Don't be cheeky!
Stay away! Stay away!
Master Onimaro!
Mai!
Sis!
So you've come,
demons of the beast world!
Mistress Ai, use this!
Mistress Mai!
Ai! Mai!
Young master!
Throw down your weapons.
Or else I'll be forced to let
Onimaro feel a bit of earthly pain.
Master Onimaro!
We have no choice, Mai...
Dekunobou!
Before we abduct you, I'll give your
bodies a taste of debauched ecstacy.
Do it.
You've really done it.
I'll go till you're wheezing in pain.
I'll pay you back till I'm satisfied!
Be silent!
You'll scratch your
pretty face if you move.
Just descend body and soul into
a debauched hell via these wicked imps!
No!
Stop! No...
No... Stop!
Your nipples are getting harder!
This sweet love juice...
So this is how a virgin tastes.
You may say no,
but your body speaks the truth!
Your virgin pussy drips with lust!
Hang them up! I will rape them
to my heart's content now.
Sis!
Don't give up. Got that?
But...
Fool.
Spread your legs.
And raise your crotches.
Or else I'll split you from
belly to head with my claws!
Beast!
Scream! Howl! Cry out!
That pride will also
be covered in my sperm!
Spread your legs!
No!
Mai, do as they say for now.
No way! That's so embarrassing...
How nice.
Now then, on to the next plan.
Shall we open the cauldron of hell?
Do it!
I've been saving this just for you.
How does it feel to have your
bottoms practically fried? It hurts, eh?
Shall I cool them off with my tongue?
Or will you put the fire
out with your own honey?
Stop it!
You're already this wet.
How do you like this wetness?
The body is an honest thing.
Especially this part.
So this is a virgin's honey of love?
Your virgin pussy is quivering.
Show me!
Let me see it better. Deeper inside!
You beast...
No! No!
Magnificent...
It's magnificent, Master Hakumouki.
Do you want my fine specimen?
If you want it that much,
then I'll thrust it in!
Lower them!
Now, I'll let you feel
this to your heart's content.
What?
Dekunobou!
Escape now!
You bastard!
Mai, time for
the dance of celestial raiment!
Right!
Rise...
...Tenjin!
First Dance of the Celestial Raiment!
W-What?
Demons of the beast world
who pollute the land!
The Tenjin Watchers and the Amatsu
Celestial Raiment Dance won't let you go!
Damn you!
We'll defeat evil in heaven's place!
Evil will be destroyed!
First Dance, soar!
Here we come!
Don't be impudent!
We did it, Sis!
Indeed.
I'm glad that nothing
happened to Master Onimaro.
He's actually cute when he's asleep.
When he's asleep.
I'm falling in love, Ai, Mai!
Oh, you're safe!
I was worried about you two!
Hey, Sis! No fair!
I love you! Love you! Love you!
Oh well... At least he's feeling better...
It is a far cry from his earlier state.
I'm such a poor little guy!
Sis!
Remember, Ai, Mai...
Oniyasha Doji of the demon beast
world will be born again into this world.
Surrounded by the ocean breeze...
...I ran off with bare feet.
With innocent laughter,
you were there soaked...
You call for me.
It's the same as that day.
Coincidentally,
there's a crescent moon.
I kissed you teasingly
and ran off from you.
Hurry, try to catch me.
Tonight is moonlight.
Written on the sand...
...are words that won't be taken
away by the waves, "I love you."
This feeling that won't
fade away will go so far.
I pledge that I love you.