Ai and Mai Amatsu,
students at Tenjin Academy.
These twin sisters, as Tenjin Watchers
in this world of light and dark...
...are tasked with protecting
the descendant of Tenjin, Onimaro.
And presently,
guiding humans to debauchery...
...and the world to disorder
are the demon beasts.
The demons are after Onimaro.
The twins defeated an incubus with
the First Dance of Celestial Raiment...
...but the greatest demon beast,
Oniyasha Doji, will soon be reborn.
After 1000 years, the heirs
of light and roots of darkness...
...are once again about
to start their fated battle.
But the twins have yet to master
the Amatsu school's priestess dance.
The demons shall be reborn.
Beasts from the lowest circle of hell...
Rape! Rape! Rape them!
Embrace all that is debased and
carnal, and build a new hell on Earth.
Who goes there?
Dancers of celestial raiment,
the Tenjin Watchers!
We slay foul beasts in God's stead!
Demons, begone!
We are the Twin Dolls!
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Twin Dolls 2
The whistle that blows
when the lecherous king comes
That's all for now.
Thank you.
I've had more to look forward to since Ai
and Mai started training in the mornings.
Sis...
The Tenjin Archery
Tournament is coming soon.
Yes...
Hotshots from all over Japan
will gather there. You up to it?
I'm not sure. But I don't
want to lose to a boy at least.
Smells good...
This one is Ai's, and this one
is Mai's... Oh, what a nice feeling!
Young master! Young master!
I'm getting out.
I'll be out in a minute.
Young master, where are you?
Not again.
The underwear thief.
Again? Jeez, I just
bought that one too!
I know who it is. I won't let
him get away with it today.
Hey, you little pervert!
Come out and show yourself!
Master Onimaro?
Bring out everything you've stolen!
W-What are you talking about?
l have no idea...
Ouch! Ouch!
Look at this! And this! And this!
And this! Do you
still want to play dumb?
I'm shocked.
What are you doing? My treasures!
Quit being so annoying!
No! Ai hit me!
l cut my hand! Oh, the blood!
Master Onimaro...
Forget him, Mai.
Young master! What happened?
Ai's bullying me!
She'll abuse me and drive me out!
You're one to talk.
What are you doing?
There's one missing.
Ai's going to rape me!
I'll do way worse if you
ever do something like this again!
Oh, this feels good...
Will you spank the front too?
Is he a pervert or something?
You can't set my loins
on fire and just stop!
Young master, what do
you think you're doing?
Is something wrong,
Master Onimaro?
Granny!
Ai's been bullying me!
So cold...
You're so heartless!
I'm in love with you!
Mistress Genshu, I apologize for
the young master's chronic affliction...
There is no problem as long as
he behaves around Ai and Mai.
It's your fault!
I don't want you grabbing them.
Young master, it's shameful. Guests
at a house must restrain themselves.
Headmistress! It's Tenjin's vessel!
What?
Ominous...
Can it be that the demon world's
Oniyasha Doji has begun to revive?
Strengthen this estate's
Tenjin's barriers!
We must never allow the demon
beasts to abduct Onimaro!
Yes, ma'am.
Dekunobou, do not let your
guard down for an instant.
I will not, mistress.
Tenjin Private Academy
Good morning!
Good morning.
Ai, do your best to win this
tourney for Tenjin Academy.
Sure, thanks.
The word is that
Houoh Academy is strong.
Houoh Academy... That new school?
Right, a Shinto school for boys.
I've heard a lot of them are handsome.
Yeah?
Some of us are going to spy on their
training session. Want to tag along?
I'm not interested in things like that.
My sister is always like that with boys.
Students coming to Suitengu Shrine
to dance in the Shinto offering ritual...
...must purify their minds,
such as with cold-water ablutions.
Also, anyone dancing for Tenjin must
not have any underwear marks.
This means you can't wear
underwear until the day of the dance.
That's embarrassing.
Can't be helped. It's for Tenjin...
Headmistress! Headmistress!
Don't lose your composure.
Calm down... Please calm down!
Mistress Genshu, this is...
Tenjin is angry.
He curses the demon-beast blood
that has mixed with our flesh.
It can only mean that
Oniyasha Doji has revived.
As I thought.
But...
As long as this Tobiume continues
to bloom regardless of season...
...Tenjin's light of purpose
will protect the Tenjin Watchers.
Exactly what is this Oniyasha Doji?
You know of Tokihira Fuiiwara, whom
demoted Michizane Sugawara to Dazaifu?
Yes.
Tokihira, who spoke ill of Michizane
to the emperor and had him demoted...
...also saw him off from the capital
with an earthenware container of sake.
Though Michizane doubted Tokihira
once, he wept over his kindness.
There is traditionally salt in such
containers, but it was actually poison.
Unbelievable...
Reaching the limits of his bitterness
in Dazaifu, his place of exile...
...Michizane became thunder's
avatar, cursing the capital.
Tokihira used arcane chants to draw
on the dark power of the beast world.
The voices of darkness told him that
Michizane was of celestial blood.
Tokihira, fearful of heaven's wrath,
deified Michizane as Tenjin...
...in order to escape that wrath.
But the filthy demons
summoned from the darkness...
...possessed Tokihira and dragged the
court into a world of demon debauchery.
Michizane's seed flowed in one
of the next emperor's mothers...
...so for the glory
of the Fujiwara house...
...Tokihira subjected his own
bloodline to demon-beast blood.
Oniyasha Doji was one of Tokihira's
descendants who fell to the demons.
He isn't oft his world.
And this Oniyasha Doji has revived?
In chaotic times, he always comes
dancing out of hell to lead people astray.
Now once again, he wishes
to take Tenjin's descendant...
...Onimaro, whom from all
appearances is a child but is in fact 18...
...and drag him into a debauched hell.
Quite twisted.
Speaking of the young master...
Dekunobou,
you must not leave his side!
Yes! A-Apologies!
Break Tenjin's barrier!
Destroy the magic field
of the celestial raiment!
I smell young females.
I must offer one as a sacrifice
for Oniyasha Doji's revival.
All priestess-dance participants,
please gather in the training hall.
Oh, and please be sure
not to wear any underwear.
What? They can't wear underwear?
It's Mai! Mai!
If she's not going
to wear it, I'll just help myself!
It's been so long, Mai.
I'm so happy!
I wonder what
this bitter sweet smell is.
It's indescribably wonderful.
Welcome.
S-Someone, help me!
So you were drawn
to this scent, you slut?
Show me your spread legs!
Show me your
throbbing, wet insides!
No! This is so embarrassing!
It's wet.
So wet!
It's like a choking garden of roses!
Master Sekimouki, it looks
like she can't wait any longer!
You want this, eh?
Do you want this?
I'll give it to you. Be sure
to feast to your heart's content.
That's it. You're very good at this.
Keep going.
Kotomi? Miss Sugi? Where are you?
Strange... I thought
she left the locker room.
A quality specimen. You're so cute...
Struggle! Struggle harder!
Enough to be worthy of violating.
That's the way.
Soon, like your friend, you won't
be able to live without our torment.
Kotomi...
I will give you the baptism
of the demon beast world!
A baptism worthy of our
demon beast world, one of blood!
Now your agony
will turn into pleasure!
King of our demon
beast world, Lord Oniyasha Doji.
Revive now from
the debauched darkness!
Guide us,
your servants of debauchery!
There's the response!
Take out the sacrifices!
Let us have a feast worthy
of greeting Lord Oniyasha Doji!
Lift your rear ends high
toward that vagina rock!
Higher! So that Lord Oniyasha Doji
can see them well...
...and with your own hands spread out
your lips so he may look deep within.
Are you wet now? You are, eh?
Gasp. Please yourselves.
Give your invitation to Lord Doji
with the sound of your throes!
Yes, stroke your beckoning clits.
Pour your overflowing
honey as an offering.
Rape them! Rape them!
Rape them as much as you desire!
Our king! King of the demon
beast world, Lord Oniyasha Doji!
Appear before us!
I am reborn.
Now we shall change
this world into a debauched hell.
Come, servants of debauchery!
I will have Tenjin's descendant. It is
time to restore the demon beasts.
Sekimouki, where is Tenjin's
descendant that I might have him?
His name is Onimaro, but he's in
the hands of the Tenjin Watchers!
What? Them again?
We must first deliver death to the
Amatsus' sisters of the celestial raiment.
Leave it to me.
It is my duty that crosses with those
descended from celestial blood.
Arisa...
Sorry.
You just disappeared.
We were so worried.
To tell the truth, I went to spy on
Houoh Academy because I got a hot tip.
A really handsome guy is
transferring in from another school.
Want to go look, Mai?
He was incredible. I was speechless.
Let's go! You'll regret it if you don't.
But I'm...
He's going to enter the upcoming
Tenjin Offering Tourney too.
He'll be Ai's greatest opponent.
But even so,
there's a glimpse of victory.
Let's scout the opposition for Ai!
True, if it's for my sister...
Houoh Academy
His name's Mitsutoki Fuiiwara.
Mitsutoki Fuiiwara...
Say, didn't you feel
he was looking this way?
It's me!
And me! What should we do?
Mai? Hey, Mai.
What's wrong?
It's nothing...
Damn it, let me go!
Let me go, Dekunobou!
I told you previously
not to go to the academy!
Mai, what kind of erratic
breath control was that?
I'm sorry!
We can't train like this.
Grandma, let me try again.
Enough. As you are, you cannot
master this no matter the training.
Without matching breathing...
...the Tenjin Celestial Raiment
Thunder Dance could take your lives!
There's something
wrong with you today.
I'm sorry, Sis.
Got a fever or something?
Nothing like that.
Let's try rehearsing on our own later.
Okay.
A break in focus can kill
in the celestial-raiment dance.
This evergreen will protect you
as you compose your soul.
There's something wrong with me...
Mai, I'd love to see your lovely skin.
What's wrong? Do you hate me?
Then open your shirt and let me see...
Beautiful...
How magnificent.
Will you rub those mounds for me?
Come on, don't be embarrassed.
What a lovely colour.
Your nipples are getting firmer.
Rub your nipples with that evergreen.
It will feel good.
Gulp!
Your heart is pounding.
It's like your heart-rending
agony is reaching me.
You should stroke deep down
your pants with that evergreen.
It should make you feel even better.
Come on, don't be ashamed.
I'll watch over you.
Lucky, lucky, lucky...
Mai... Yes... Yes... Here it comes...
We came together...
That's the way.
With this, you are mine.
The next time I see you,
l want to ravish you senseless.
Mai...
Your body is so beautiful, Sis...
Mai?
It almost looks divine.
Like a celestial maiden's.
Silly. Yours is exactly the same too.
Here.
We'll definitely win
today's tournament, right?
Only Tenjin knows.
Oh, by the way, Mai, don't mess up
the priestess dance before the match.
I'll be fine. It's not
the celestial-raiment dance...
...and there's
no scary grandma watching.
True.
If you have any worries,
talk to me, whatever they are.
Sis...
We're twins, after all.
I can tell when something is wrong.
Don't get worked up all by yourself.
Thanks, Sis.
Suitengu Shrine
There's sure to be
a lot of spectators today.
In any case,
Tenjin is the god of exams.
Those who rely on God only
during hardships will find no boon.
You said it.
You're finally more like yourself.
Let's go to the waiting area!
Yeah!
Mitsutoki, look over here!
What's this... What's this feeling?
Strange...
I hate men but just like that,
l feel attracted to the core.
Young master, this festival honours
our ancestors. It gladdens me.
Is that a guy or a girl?
Are you wet already, Mai?
It feels like he's ravishing
me with his gaze...
The Tenjin Offering Archery
Tournament will now be held.
Everyone, the shrine office
is on fire! Please evacuate!
Will you run too?
No, I'll settle this.
As expected of
the Tenjin Watcher head family.
And a grandchild
of the Amatsu school.
Who are you?
Well now, who in
the world could I be?
Don't play games!
I'm already aware of your true identity!
I'm amazed.
You're a debauched demon
from the beast world, an incubus!
You called?
Sekimouki of
the beast world has arrived.
Ai Amatsu of the Tenjin Watchers!
Spread your legs and
surrender to the demon beasts!
Who would?
Sekimouki is good at entertaining too.
I enjoy violating strong-willed women.
Hold on! Don't touch my girl!
I do believe this is Master Onimaro.
My lord, join the demon beasts.
W-What?
Master Onimaro,
don't let him fool you!
It feels so good!
He will belong to Tokihira Fuiiwara.
I shall welcome Tenjin's
direct descendant as my own.
Ai!
Master Onimaro!
You don't know your place.
l shall teach it to your body!
What?
Don't touch me, you filth!
Sis!
Mai!
All is ready.
The Amatsu sisters are both present.
W-What the hell are you?
A man or a woman?
Why don't you check?
N-Nothing!
How about here?
The petals are all wet!
Look to your heart's content.
It's wet and soaked!
That idiot.
I won't be deceived anymore!
I wonder about that.
Kotomi!
Arisa too?
This is unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
And what can you do but say that?
A beast-world barrier has sealed
away your celestial raiment's power.
What was that?
I can't move!
Strip those two!
Without the celestial raiment's power,
the Amatsu sisters are just women.
Stop!
Her nipples are getting hard.
The taste of a virgin
is such a delicacy!
Your body is so honest.
It's becoming soaked!
How does it feel to be violated
in crimson flames, Amatsu girls?
Young master!
Mistress Ai! Mistress Mai!
Stay back, lackey!
Gee, he's got both parts...
Dekunobou, save Onimaro!
You damn lackey!
Mai, the Tenjin
Celestial Raiment Dance!
Right, Sis!
Tenjin!
Rise!
First Dance of the Celestial Raiment!
What?
Demons of the beast world
who seek to defile this one!
The Tenjin Watchers,
Amatsu dancers, will make you pay!
D-Damn you...
We'll slay the wicked in God's stead!
The wicked will be destroyed!
First Dance, soar!
Here we come!
l am Oniyasha Doii
of the demon beasts!
Rise, demons!
Hope Rend!
Mai, Tenjin's secret technique!
But we still haven't...
We can. We can do it!
Match my breath and come with me!
Rise, Tenjin!
Tenjin celestial raiment!
Mai...
Mai, I want your body.
And I want that heart of yours.
Mai, don't look into his eyes!
Mai, come on!
Right!
Rise, Tenjin!
Celestial raiment
secret technique, Thunder Dance!
Demon, begone!
We did it, Mai.
What were we doing?
I am immortal.
I'll change my face, change my form,
and come back over and over again.
How sad.
It seems he received
a tremendous shock...
Young master... Young master!
Please regain consciousness!
Mai, there's no choice but that.
I have to?
It's the only way.
Mai!
Mai, wait up! Mai!
Please excuse us!
Mai!
We came together!
After the rain on a moonlit night...
...I took you out.
I want to feel tomorrow's happiness
right now rather than go to sleep.
The pah at midnight.
Time started to stop.
You're forcing yourself to smile.
Your sleepy-looking eyes...
I kissed them saying, "I'm sorry."
Tonight is moonlight.
Being protected...
To the gently
shining stars, I love you.
To the shimmer
the rain left behind...
I pledge on a ring that I love you.