Thank you for your purchase!
I hope to see you again soon!
What's going on?
My god!
What on earth did you do, Cruz?
Well, I just tripped, that's all.
That's okay, Cruz.
Everyone makes mistakes sometimes, right?
I'm really sorry about this.
My brother can be so clumsy.
Will you excuse us?
You dumb shit,
we finally landed a job with free rent!
I'll be going back up front!
I think Mihono is such a nice girl!
You think so?
Yes, I'd like to have her
as my daughter, even.
Why don't you get married again?
I don't plan on doing that.
Besides, what are you two going to do?
Do you have some place to go to?
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Good morning, Kazuho!
Morning. Are you getting used
to the early hours?
Well, kind of.
Owning a bakery is a lot of work.
Yes it is.
So, you and Mihono
aren't really brother and sister, are you?
W-What makes you think that?
Of course we are.
Don't worry.
It's really none of my business either way.
At her age, I think it's important
to have a solid,
secure place to grow up in instead of drifting around.
Yes, I think you're right about that.
But...
I don't think this is the place for Mihono.
I think you like having Mihono around
here because you are lonely.
Life can be tough when you're by yourself.
It can be really lonely at times.
I understand that you want someone
around to stifle your loneliness.
But in that case, you're not thinking
about the other person.
I think you're just trying to fill that space
with Mihono's presence.
That's not fair to....
Damn!
I'm really sorry about this.
I'll wipe it off.
W-What?
No stop, we can't do this.
Stop, just please let me go!
Please take your hands off!
Stop, no, don't touch me down there!
Stop!
N-No, not there!
No!
I know your body gets very lonely too.
I thought I could help you
in that department.
Your body won't be so lonely now.
I can't. It's just not right!
Your body seems to think otherwise.
Just be more honest with yourself.
It's not that difficult.
Yes.
You can be louder!
Don't be shy, okay?
Yes!
I like it!
More!
I'm coming!
You're right.
I think I was selfish
about wanting to keep Mihono with me.
Well, actually...
I think she really needs stability
in her life right now.
If she can stay with you,
it would be for the best.
But what will Mihono think?
I think that would be the best thing
for her right now.
I really don't know how much longer
I can take care of her.
I'm taking off.
Right now?
I need to get going.
Take care, both of you.
Later!
Hi Mihono!
Good morning!
Asshole!
You should know by now that you can't
just leave and take off without me!
Gimme!
What?
My money.
I can forgive you for this,
but I do need my share of the pay check.
Shit!
You are so stupid!
All right.
Just shut up, okay!
So, where are we going?
We're going to go see an old friend
of mine around here.
Okay.
Nothing has changed.
Nothing looks good to eat in here.
Hey, did you find her?
Nobody here.
She probably went shopping.
Gross!
Tastes downright nasty!
Where's the light switch?
She hasn't moved a damned thing!
She's not here.
She won't be back.
Nif!
What are you doing here?
I had some business with the nun here.
What did you do with her?
When did you switch sides, Nif?
I've always been neutral.
Neither party interests me, really.
What I'm interested in is...
you, Cruz.
You've changed a lot, really.
So has Shisui.
Even Shisui's against eliminating you, Cruz.
So, what is it about you?
I'm dying to know.
I might follow you around, too.
So this is what you want.
I think it's very important
to get to know people well.
Your friend's passed out in the kitchen.
You always plan thoroughly.
You'll tell me where she is, right, Nif?
Sure, if you can make me
come really hard.
ls that all you really want?
That's all?
Can you make me come
while thinking about that?
I guess I'm going to have to concentrate
for the time being.
Right there, baby!
This feels so good!
Didn't expect this!
Let me suck on your cock more.
Wow! You're getting even bigger!
I am concentrating.
Don't make me wait!
Fuck me!
I'm calling the shots here.
All right, then.
More!
Harder!
Yes! Your huge cock...
is fucking me hard.
You like it?
Yes baby!
Dear god, I love this!
Right there!
I'm coming!
You promised.
Where is the nun?
You have no manners, do you?
You could at least let me
enjoy the afterglow.
But I did make a promise.
I'll tell you.
She's been taken to the vacation house
along with all the other women....
so you'll return the key.
This was Shisui's orders.
But the nun had nothing to do with this!
What do you mean by ''all the other women?''
In Shisui's opinion, if you slept with them,
then they're involved.
What are you doing?
You're conscious already?
That was fast.
Let's go!
What, go where?
What was that all about?
That was the nun?
I was going to leave you there,
but we have a change of plans.
I have no clue about what's going on!
No more running away.
Make sure we can get started
in another two hours.
Yes, ma'am.
You seem all excited.
You like your job that much?
Nif, what were you doing slacking off
and disappearing like that?
So you found out.
Yes, I went to see Cruz.
I have no intention
of interfering with your plan.
I just wanted a small piece
of what was left in him.
Just helping with the recovery process.
Nif, what are you....
It's not like I didn't leave enough
for you or anything.
You want him?
You want him back?
Feels good....
You like it very much.
Shisui...
The plan is in its final stage.
Ramon said anyone can go
after Cruz and capture him now.
T-That can't be.
They know...
what you're doing, you know.
Even if it means betraying everyone...
I want to know why
you are so obsessed with Cruz.
I like to hear you moan.
I want to hear more.
Do you like it?
Oh, yes!
No!
You are so adorable,
and also so, very pathetic.
You're panting with lust right now...
and moaning in pleasure.
Your body is responding so much.
You shouldn't be able to think straight now,
am I right, Shisui?
But your heart is so silent...
like the bottom of a deep ocean.
Come for me.
I know your body really wants to come.
Are you about to?
Come for me! Do it!
Yes, I'm coming!
You're serious, Shisui?
Of course I am.
Shisui, you....
It's time, ma'am.
Yes.
All right, please throw this woman
in with the rest.
Shisui!
Nobody is going to come any closer to Cruz.
No matter who they are.
Not here?
There is nobody by the name
of Misato Sasaki.
That can't be!
That girl.
Hey, wait a minute!
Where is Misato?
What? Misato?
Your partner!
I don't know a Misato.
You know, your patrol partner here at work.
I don't know a Misato. You must be
mistaking me for somebody else.
I'm sure of it!
Come on, where is your partner, Misato?
Excuse me, I have to get back to work.
This is weird!
What's going on here?
Shit!
I told Mihono to stay close
to the motorcycle.
Things are getting really strange
around here.
Cruz?
That's not me.
Oh my god, you don't recognize my voice?
What?
Wow, hi Misato!
I was looking for you!
Well, you've found me.
Follow me, okay?
We'll be okay here.
Nobody will see.
It's a temporary storage area
for wrecked cars and impounds.
Cruz, I missed you!
Wait!
What's wrong?
You were looking for me?
Yeah.
To see if you were all right.
So you're planning to leave already?
I just wanted to drop by.
That's too bad.
But you're not leaving just yet, mister.
Wait a minute...
You've become more assertive, Misato.
It's all your fault.
So, you want to, right?
It's so weird!
Nobody knows about you here.
Not even your patrol partner.
You remember me, right?
Of course.
Well then, we're set.
It's just the two of us here.
Here, you're sweating,
let me lick the sweat off of you.
You're cock is so hot!
My body's nice and cool, don't you think?
You know who I am.
That's what matters most.
Will you eat my pussy, please?
Yeah!
Please, put it in.
Go in deep.
You've changed so much!
It's kind of scary!
Why do you...
say that, Cruz?
My pussy is totally filled...
with your big cock.
More! Go deeper.
Much harder.
Just like that!
Yeah!
I'm gonna come!
What are you doing?
Mihono!
Let me join you guys.
I was watching you two...
and I couldn't take it anymore.
So you want to join the fun?
That's fine, I'll fuck you like I always do.
Turn your ass around, baby.
All right, close your eyes.
Take this!
Tsuruia.
How did you?
You know it's not that easy
to fool me, Tsuruia.
Mihono would not react like that
to this situation.
Tell Ramon when you see him.
I'll make him pay if he hurts any of them!
Mr. Ramon, may I?
Yes.
They are still unstable.
It's usually impossible to exist
under those conditions.
But they seem to even get enjoyment
out of the instability!
Ramon, you've changed.
This planet is too young.
It's surely affected everybody.
So, their action from the beginning.
Don't bring that up!
You should be satisfied.
They may be capable of a lot, but....
The vote has been decided.
Three years ago, 13 people came down here
to vote on an important decision.
But, one died in an accident.
We split into two factions after that,
six people on each side.
We've been killing each other off.
So I decided to just take off
with the most important thing.
What is that?
A key.
Nothing happens without the key.
Let's see.
I guess my ID code is no longer active.
Let's go.
We'll find our way in.
Cruz!
What did you do?
I just put my hand where you did.
What's going on?
Well, now it's open.
Let's go.