Bosarre is a small country
with a population of under 1000.
The independence of Bosarre
has always been precarious...
...as it is situated between
the Rohan Empire to the north...
...and the Geild Empire to the East.
At the age of 20,
Isiodore inherited the Bosarre throne.
At that time, he was still unmarried.
As a result, both the Geild
and the Rohan empires...
...have sent one of their princesses to Bosarre
for Isiodore to choose as his queen.
The Rohan Empire sent
Princess Bellecher as their candidate.
The Geild Empire sent Princess Ariel.
Both empires want to possibly
forge an alliance...
...or even acquire Bosarre altogether.
Isiodore has been given
a month and a half to make his choice....
Under the threat of military action
by both empires...
...and with his country's
independence on the line...
...Isiodore was able to get intimately
acquainted with both princesses.
This stone is called Charmstone.
A mysterious alchemist, Myslandia,
half elf by blood...
...spent his last years within this country
during my father's reign.
On his deathbed,
he presented my father this magical stone.
Placing the stone in front of your eye
while doing a specific activity...
...allows me to cast a spell on the person.
That specific activity must be sex.
As both princesses are here to compete
for their place as my queen...
...they should not refuse my advances.
lf they refuse, it is possible to become part
of either country and remain in a royal position.
In fact, it would be a much easier life
to give up my position as king...
...and live without worries
while retaining a royal title.
Failure could be acceptable.
However, victory would be sweeter.
Victory is worth the risk.
Kokudoh Oh 2
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
It is common practice for most places
to bar unmarried women...
...from participating in official,
state or trade meetings.
Since Bosarre has
such a small population...
...we allow any persons
with a royal Bosarre title...
...of either gender, over 15 years of age,
to participate in state and trade meetings.
As candidate for queen,
learning the etiquette and rules...
...observed during these meetings,
is essential.
Ariel and Bellecher
will be expected to learn them...
...even though neither are
officially the queen of Bosarre.
Who is it?
Isaac, your Highness.
Please enter.
How are they doing?
So far, I have no complaints
with Princess Bellecher.
Do you have any particular
concerns at the moment?
I really would like to do something
regarding Belle's temper and arrogance.
I don't think that's an immediate concern.
You might be right.
I think I can take care of it myself.
If I could be of any assistance.
I'll let you know.
Will you send for Belle?
Of course, sir.
What is it?
I am planning to have an important meeting
over dinner with my mayors.
I was thinking about having
either you or Ari as hostess.
I could do it for you.
That would be great!
It can be very difficult.
I'm not sure that you'll be able to handle it.
What are you implying?
You don't think I'm capable?
Possibly.
This is unbelievable.
Are you sure you can do this?
Of course I am.
Well, then, you can be hostess.
Great!
Listen very closely.
First, it is custom for them
to bring the food.
Irene will do the cooking.
All we have to do is to sit down
and enjoy the meal.
That pretty much covers it.
That's easy!
Not a problem!
I did mention that they
would be bringing the food.
It is considered offensive unless one of us
eats from every dish that is presented.
They will most likely bring
something called Salsoon.
As you know,
it is basically specially fermented fish.
I was never able to acquire a taste
for that particular food.
It especially develops an unacceptable
texture after fermentation.
You can eat that entree.
Uh, sure.
The Salsoon we get here
is imported from Stolon Bay.
It is one of your country's delicacies.
Yes, I know, but, it's for peasants.
I mean, it's a commoner's delicacy,
so I'm not sure...
It's considered a delicacy
in most places in this region.
You mean you're not able to do this, then?
I didn't say that!
Great! All right, I'm counting on you.
Of course, you can count on me.
That will be all.
Wait... When is this dinner?
I haven't set an official date yet.
It could be tomorrow or next week.
Don't worry, you will
be notified in advance.
The dinner meeting is a lie.
I'm also very aware that Belle
hates Salsoon more than anything.
I just wanted to see how she would react.
I just wanted to tease her a lime bit.
I think I'll tell her the dinner
got canceled tomorrow.
Nobody has come to get me for lunch yet.
I got a bad feeling,
so I headed toward the kitchen.
Mealtime is one of the few pleasures
I have here.
With only Irene and Isaac to help me,
I use my mealtime to eat, relax, and enjoy my day.
In a rush, your Highness?
Kind of.
Have you not had your meal yet, your Highness?
Not yet, Isaac.
In that case, I will have my wife
bring a proper meal down right away.
Oh no, that's not necessary, Isaac.
Good day, your Highness.
Isaac is extremely proud of two things in his life:
his wife and his four-year-old daughter.
While it is expected for a man to love,
and be proud of, his family...
...I have yet to see a man equal
Isaac's fierce devotion to his family.
If I had his wife bring my meals, he would
go on forever about his wife's cooking abilities.
I've heard him tell me 1000 times already...
Your Highness, lunch will be ready soon.
It's taking a long time.
I'm really sorry.
I know it's not your fault Irene.
Do you mind if I enter the kitchen to observe?
Please.
Hi, Onii-sama!
What's going on?
I told her I would help,
but she didn't want me to...
How is it going?
My question just got answered.
If things were going well,
it wouldn't take this long, I guess...
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault!
I know, but...
I heard that.
Oh no, excuse me.
Hi, Isio!
Belle, I hope we can eat soon?
Just wait a bit more.
I swear, it will be done soon.
Sure.
It is important to know how to cook.
Hopefully, she will learn from experience.
I'm counting on you.
Don't worry, I'm following directions
from the recipe exactly.
I hope you're adjusting the ingredients
to the number of people.
I believe Irene's recipes
are only for one or two.
Math was one of my very best subjects,
in case you don't recall.
Just making sure.
I hope it won't be too much longer?
I'm almost finished with the sauce,
so it'll be soon.
All right, I'll be in the dining hall.
Wait....
Wait what?
I think the sauce in the pot is burning!
I know you're new to this,
but will you please be more careful...
...and try not to torch the meal?
I think you will agree.
I'll be more careful.
That will do. It's too late to start over now.
And, Belle...
Yes?
Even if you can't handle
other housekeeping chores...
...please learn how to cook well.
That is, if you want to be my queen.
I'm really sorry, Isio.
Isio, are you not coming over tonight?
Ariel is trying to get on your good side.
I will not be the loser here!
Yes, coming!
I think I'm starting to want his company...
But this whole transaction
is first and foremost a political one...
He is not someone
l should really trust right now...
Good evening, Belle.
Come in.
Thanks.
How should I act?
What is that?
This is your punishment.
I apologized for the lunch disaster...
This is not for that...
It's for your attitude
during our first night together.
I had not punished you for that yet.
Punishment?
Yes, any disobedience against me
results in a punishment.
My word is the law.
What is it?
Using this, I am going to have you shave off
all your lovely pubic hair.
But...
Are you going to refuse?
No, I'm not.
I am under strict orders.
I am not to lose to that girl, Ariel.
I wanted to do something
about her arrogant attitude.
I'm also getting back at her
for ignoring me during school.
There's everything you need.
Do I really have to do this?
I can't believe I'm doing this!
At first, I found Belle's pained expression
amusing, but soon I became extremely aroused.
I'm done!
I want you to stand in front of the mirror.
How degrading.
Please, not like this!
Not after that!
I thought I could handle this,
but I really can't!
Please, be gentle with me.
N-Not there!
Ouch...Please, don't be so rough!
I am slowly unfolding
the lips of your bare, wet pussy.
Stop, I can't take this!
It looked like you were admiring
your bare pussy in the mirror.
This feels so good,
a lot better than playing with myself....
Why, because a man is touching me?
Is it because I am bare down there?
God, my god!
More, more!
The very first meeting between Isiodore
and General Hellin is scheduled for this morning.
Under his king's orders...
...General Hellin has his army of 6000
stationed at the Rohan-Bosarre border.
General Hellin is married to
Belle's oldest sister...
...so he is Belle's brother-in-law,
in addition to being a general.
He is also fifth in line for the Rohan throne.
Although he is brave and skilled...
...he almost lost his life many times on
the battlefield due to his temper and impatience.
He had tried to embarrass Isiodore
with a debate during a gathering...
...while Isiodore was still a student in Rohan.
Isiodore easily beat him, causing General Hellin
much embarrassment in front of his peers.
Consequently, he had a grudge against Isiodore.
Damned Isiodore!
Excuse me.
How did things go last night?
All right.
General Hellin of Rohan
is scheduled to arrive shortly.
I am sure he would want
to talk to Princess Bellecher.
A positive reply will be forwarded to the Empire.
And a negative one would affect our relationship
with the Rohan negatively.
Correct.
I can't really say. It's up to Belle.
I see, your Highness.
Isaac, wouldn't too good of a response
from Belle alienate the Geild Empire as well?
I agree.
Well, I still have over a month left.
What about bribing both generals for now
to maintain some stability?
An excellent idea, your Highness.
General Hellin, I would like to present you
with a gift from the king.
Let's see...
It is called Heart of Illusion, and it has been
in the royal family for generations now.
I had heard about it,
but I have never seen it before.
A mystical heart that a brave warrior acquired
from the spirit world, general.
If I lose my life in battle, will this heart
bring me back to life, as it has been rumored?
Yes.
This is for me?
His Highness did not want to upset you
and ruin the meeting by showing feeling ill.
He would like to postpone the meeting.
This gift represents his apologies.
If you insist, he will meet with you.
That's all right for today.
He will be grateful.
I will gladly accept his gift.
Would you like to speak with Princess Bellecher?
Is she well?
Yes, she seems very happy,
and is doing extremely well.
I’m glad to hear that.
Please give her my greetings.
Of course.
To the king, as well.
Thank you for coming.
Over the years, Bosarre has acquired treasures
from merchants that passed through its borders.
These treasures have been
an important tool...
...in maintaining the country's
independence and alliances.
The country's fate rests upon
the wise use of these gifts...
...during the time that is left
before Isiodore makes his choice for queen.
To be the queen, your hostessing skills
must be impeccable.
There were numerous meetings and dinners
with merchants and ambassadors...
...as well as local meetings to host.
For those without experience, even
hostessing the smallest dinner or meeting...
...was met with a lot of work
and an incredible amount of stress.
Is Ariel still stressing out?
Yes.
It is taking so long,
so I was thinking about helping her out...
...giving her some suggestions.
As a candidate for queen,
l think it is essential that she be able to...
...handle these tasks
on her own, your Highness.
On the other hand, Belle probably wouldn't have
had as many problems with something like this.
I think Princess Bellecher
would find this task an easy one.
She always did have the best score
in political science classes.
She could run the meeting and come up with
the answers before any of us could get started.
I think it's best if we stop comparing the two,
and let Princess Ariel solve this task...
...on her own.
I understand.
Please send for Ariel.
Immediately.
Onii-sama, may I come in?
Ari, sure.
Have you come up with
a solution to the problem?
Not yet.
I asked Belle, but she told me
to figure it out on my own.
Why should she help you,
unless you expect...
...to keep Belle as your advisor
if you become Queen?
I don't think so.
See, don't depend on others for answers.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you more time.
Yes.
Do you want to give up?
No, no, I'll try harder.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Hey Ari, were you aware that our library has
extensive references and records on the subject?
A suggestion.
Thank you!
I ended up helping her...
Your highness, having armies
camping out at both borders...
...must be making trade more difficult.
It must be hard for your country.
Yes, that's why I wanted you to come...
...first to discuss the tax for merchants
using the trade routes within my borders.
I am honored by the invitation...
...to be chosen as the very first merchant
to meet with the king this year....
I will also have this meeting later with
all the other merchants as well, as you know.
I want you to do me a great favor.
Your highness, I’m guessing that
you are planning to increase the tax, correct?
As you can see, this country's independence
is in a very precarious state.
The trade slowing down is really hurting us.
Will you help me?
I see.
Political instability, choosing your queen...
you're a busy king!
This is Princess Ariel of Geild,
one of my candidates.
An innocent, very beautiful, young princess!
I'm so sorry! Oh, my gosh, what do I do?
You may be excused.
I'm really sorry, I am!
My deepest apologies.
I am responsible for instructing the princesses,
it is my fault.
Please forgive me.
I apologize as well, Sir Kato.
Oh, no, a princess is usually
not used to performing these duties.
Shall we continue?
No, I must get going now.
I would love to meet privately at a later date.
All right, thank you.
I will guide you back.
Onii-sama, may I come in?
Come in, Ariel.
Don't worry about it.
Everyone knows it's not your fault.
But....
Isaac and I will handle it from here.
I'm really sorry, I really am.
I said don't worry about it!
Okay, but was Isaac upset about this at all?
No, I don't think so, why?
It seems like I'm always causing him
problems like this...
Isaac is not easily upset about anything.
Does that worry you?
Kind of.
Ari, listen.
Have some confidence.
Yes.
Look at Belle,
and confident she is at all times.
She's excessive, but you know....
But....
Someone will always be watching you.
Even if I'm satisfied, Irene,
Isaac and others will not be.
Try to build confidence.
If I try, do you think I really can?
Yes, but you have to try first.
We're going to do something different.
Yes.
Straddle my face. Just like that.
Y-Yes.
Yes, what do I do now?
So big. I can't believe this fits inside me!
I will do anything Onii-sama wants me to.
I'm not sure if I can
satisfy him this way, though.
This feels very strange.
My mouth is being treated
just like another sexual device....
But it makes me very happy
to think that parts of my body...
...can be used like this to bring Onii-sama pleasure.
I feel much joy just to be able
to bring Onii-sama pleasure.
I almost bit Onii-sama
when I gagged for air, but I didn't.
This is kind of difficult
since I can't breathe well doing this...
...but I know refusing would upset Onii-sama.
Hey, what's wrong?
I want to go home!
Where's home?
I don't know.
What's your name?
Call me Ari.
Ari, let's see.
That's a real common name.
I don't know if I can help!
What's your name?
I'm Isiodore.
Idisodore?
Isiodore.
Isiodore?
Right. Isiodore.
Call me Isio.
So, what does your daddy do?
My daddy is king!
Hey, what does Oni-chan's daddy do?
My father is a king as well!
Really, same as my dad!
Yes, looks like we're in the same boat.
I think both our parents
sent us here to Anglemarr.
There's lots of kids just like us here, you know.
I'm from Huberburg.
I'm from Bosarre.
I don't get it...
Since we're from small countries, our parents
sent us here to a big country to prevent wars.
Does that mean we're both from small countries?
I guess so, but we take turns,
so you should be able to go home soon.
What about you?
Eventually, sure.
Will you come back home with me, then?
I can't do that, we just met!
Onii-chan's been so nice, come back with me!
We're not given a choice, Ari.
But, why?
Because we're both only kids, you know.
That's not fair!
I don't think so, either.
I think he liked it when
l tried as hard as I could...
...to be able to accept
more of Onii-sama's manhood into my mouth.
I didn't mean to stop....
I'm glad, I'm glad you liked it!
When my face got sprayed
with Onii-sama's ejaculation...
...I really felt like
I succeeded in pleasing Onii-sama.
I really want to stay here.
I felt that I really wanted to stay here,
to serve Onii-sama day and night.
What is this?
This is a small gift from the king
to show his respect.
I see.
Could this be the legendary moonstone?
Your impressive educational background is
apparent, General Samaroon. I am impressed!
Taken from the frozen piers
of the dangerous northern cliffs in the north city.
I did not know that you were in possession
of this legendary stone!
I hope you like it?
Yes.
It is your gift.
P-Positive?
Yes, direct orders from the king himself.
Is he not able to attend the meeting?
He has been with Princess Ariel since last night.
In that case, I will accept his gift gladly
and be on my way.
Please tell him that choosing Princess Ariel
for his queen will be a very wise decision.
I will tell him.
Good morning!
Hi Ari...
I didn't sleep well last night,
so please, let me go back to sleep.
Please wake up!
Good morning, Onii-sama!
Ari?
May I give you pleasure?
I wanted to relax and let her please me
with her inexperienced technique.
I felt like I would not be able to
control myself much longer.
Ari!
I’m going all the way inside!
So...tight!
Please make it quick...
I'm coming!
Please come inside me!
I want to absorb every drop!
Coming, I'm coming right now!
King Isiodore has a month left
before he chooses his queen.
Will he be able to have his way
with the princesses...
...and keep his country safe
at the same time?