At the age of 20, Isiodore inherited
the Bosarre throne after his father's death.
The Rohan empire to the north,
.and the Geild Empire to the East...
...have sent their princesses
to Isiodore to choose one.
Both Empires are eager to forge
a strong alliance with Bosarre...
..which posses important trade routes
and a fortress-like geography.
The Rohan Empire sent
Princess Bellecher as their candidate.
The Geild Empire...
...sent Princess Ariel to possibly secure
the position as a Bosarran queen.
To maintain Bosarre's
independence and safety...
...Isiodore must be extremely careful...
...with this delicate
decision of choosing his queen..
If the princess feels slighted...
...her army is waiting at the border to wage
a military campaign against Bosarre..
Isiodore must choose his queen
within a month and a half....
A month has passed already...
...leaving only two weeks
for Isiodore to come to a decision...
This stone is called Charmstone.
A mysterious alchemist, Myslandia,
half elf by blood...
...spent his last years within this country
during my father's reign.
On his deathbed,
he presented my father this magical stone.
Placing the stone in front of your eye
while doing a specific activity...
...allows me to cast a spell on the person.
That activity is for me
to sleep with the princesses....
However, an urgent message was delivered
to Isiodore that would change everything.
This sudden event would challenge
Isiodore's ability...
...to control the decision
of choosing his bride.
Kokudoh Oh 4
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Your Highness, this is urgent.
Isaac?
Yes, your Highness.
I suppose this couldn't wait?
It seems that the
Emperor of Geild is dying.
Are you sure?
From a merchant with close ties
with the Geild royal family.
All right....
There is only two weeks left
before I need to choose my queen....
If the Emperor dies before then...
...things could easily
get complicated very quickly.
Yes.
Regarding this situation,
I hear the heir to the Geild throne...
...had previously asked Princess Bellecher
for her hand in marriage some time ago.
What, Bellecher?
Yes.
Under these circumstances, if
your highness is to choose Princess Ariel...
...I am sure that he will re-propose
to Princess Bellecher.
I see.
By choosing Ariel,
Bellecher will likely end up in Geild.
That would be a favourable outcome
for the Geild Empire but...
...that would not benefit
the Rohan Empire's interests.
Especially for General Hellin.
Yes, General Hellin is the second
in line to the throne...
...being married to Belle's oldest sister.
Yes.
His interest lies in Princess Bellecher
being chosen for queen here...
...so he can start a military campaign
against the Geild empire.
If I choose Bellecher as my queen....
There would not be anything here...
...to keep the new Emperor of Geild
from trying to take us over.
Oh, well, whatever.
Either way, this was a difficult
situation to start with.
Do you think Ariel knows?
We have not received any messages.
I would presume they want to keep...
...this information secret from
the Rohan Empire.
I will talk to Ariel later to see
if she knows anything.
Make sure to keep your ears open
for more information.
Absolutely.
This is Ari.
Please enter.
How are you?
Not well, due to the difficulty
of the studies.
There is only two weeks left
until I have to make my choice.
There isn't much time left.
I'm sorry, I'm not very good
with my studies.
I know this is difficult
...but your father was the one
that insisted on this deadline.
Yes... I'm sorry.
I just want you to keep trying hard.
Isaac means well.
Does he really?
You're surprised?
Yes. Well, he gets so frustrated
trying to teach me.
He might be a harsh teacher,
but he knows you are trying very hard.
Just keep trying, and don't give up.
Yes!
Her expression brightened
with some encouragement.
I don't think she's aware
of her father's condition.
You may go back to your studies now.
Yes.
Have you seen Irene today, by the way?
I just spoke with her.
She said she will be cleaning
the bathroom.
I have an important meeting
with a Shandalar merchant today.
I hope Irene hasn't forgotten
that I had asked her to help Belle...
...with preparations as Belle
will be attending the meeting.
What are you doing?
They were naked and fondling each other....
Are you sure he would like this?
His Highness would be delighted.
Belle seems to be enjoying this.
Irene seems to be enjoying herself...
...and pleasing Belle instead of just
giving instructions on bedroom techniques.
That feels really good....
Irene had an expression of lust and joy...
...an expression
I had ever seen her show before.
I could not stop watching them.
Wait.
That tickles...
I'm ticklish there...
Please stop it, no more...
It looked as they both came.
They were still fondling each other.
I think Irene forgot about
her cleaning duties.
I wanted to continue watching,
but I still had to prepare for my meeting.
I hope Belle has not forgotten
about the meeting.
The only problem with having
Belle hostess is her arrogance.
She always seems like she is
looking down on everybody in the room.
A small country like Bosarre
is dependent on the taxes...
...paid by various merchants
using our trade route.
Regardless of her status as a royalty...
...I cannot allow her to show
any disrespect to the merchants.
Come in.
She was prepared in time for the meeting.
She had a dreamy expression
from her lesson from Irene.
I am prepared just in time.
I did not respond to her.
I wanted to make sure
that she would not display...
...her arrogance
during my important meeting.
Isio, what's wrong?
Let me see your breasts.
What?
B-But, what for?
It's a lesson to improve
your hostessing im my presence.
Yes.
Like this, your Highness?
Come over here.
How does this feel?
It feels good...
Lift your dress up.
Yes.
Is it cold?
Y-Yeah.
Not yeah, say yes.
Yes.
Do you like the cold knife?
Perfectly smooth.
Yes...
I've been shaving it
just like you told me to.
That's good.
We're just getting started.
All right. We need to get going.
Like this, right now?
That's correct, your dress
will hide everything.
The meeting with the Shandalar merchant
is going very well.
For a small country like Bosarre...
...it can be more important
to have a strong alliance...
...with the merchants
as it is to have one with large empires.
Having lime military capacity,
out trade in goods and information...
...with the merchants
is often our only weapon.
Belle is being a great hostess...
...beaming with a graceful smile
and conversation.
She might be learning...
...but she is probably just too preoccupied
for her arrogance to rear its ugly head.
She shows no sign of
the depraved pleasures...
...she must be experiencing
under her dress.
I think this lesson
for Belle was especially successful...
After the meeting,
I went to see Ari in her room.
I had a lesson prepared
for her just like I did with Belle.
If Belle's downfall was her arrogance...
...Ari's downfall is
her dependence on others.
It was also for my benefit as I wanted
to be able to stifle my overwhelming feeling...
...of sympathy towards her.
Yes, Onii-sama.
I assume you are ready.
Yes, just as instructed.
I was waiting, wearing the costume
just as he had instructed.
I was wearing a chastity belt...
...with a ring that was framing
my delicate asshole.
Onii-sama, is this to your satisfaction?
Yes.
Show me your ass,
and use the chair for support.
Yes, just like this?
I can see you very well, Ari.
Oh, no. This is embarrassing.
That's really cold.
It's coming inside.
I can feel something cold and hard
coming into my exposed asshole.
At first it was uncomfortable,
but now it is easily sliding inside.
It feels so big inside.
He just continued to insert
the anal beads inside me.
My muscles were responding
to this uncomfortable sensation.
I don't know how much
was inserted into me.
I think he was finally done.
No!
Ari, did you like that?
F-Felt good....
A message from the Geild Empire
was highly suggestive.
The heir to the throne wrote
that he was highly impressed...
...by the beauty and intelligence
of Princess Bellecher.
What should we do?
I think it would be wise
to observe the situation carefully...
...instead of letting one's emotions
cloud the picture.
I see.
If I show preference to Belle,
I will feel heat from the Geild Empire.
I'll hint to Belle to not openly
show her desire to be chosen as queen.
I concur.
Lately, it seems like I am
unable to relax at night.
At first, I was only fulfilling my obligation
to my country as their princess, but now...
...it seems like I want him
to come see me at night.
Yes.
When I hear him coming, I can feel
expectation rising inside my body...
...as my doubts disappear.
Y-Yes?
Did you like your lesson?
It seems like you enjoyed it.
Uh, well...
Tonight, I thought maybe
we should continue along that line.
Follow me.
W-Where?
Just follow me.
Somehow, his words started
to excite my body.
Was I going to experience
those delicious sensations?
Look. Look at my slutty pussy, look.
In the dungeon, I was a sex slave,
asking him to watch me masturbate.
Spread the lips of that pussy wide apart.
Yes.
Fuck me!
Hurry up and please fuck me!
I was fiercely begging with words
that have never escaped my lips.
P-Please, now. I can't wait anymore!
Listening to myself say those words
excited me even more.
I can feel his thick, hard, lusty,
flesh hammering me ruthlessly.
Like it?
Oh, yes!
More! Much harder!
I can feel my mind cloud
in the fog of this fleshy pleasure.
I can feel what was pain
slowly turn into rapture.
I can feel my nipples pulling hard
as he pounds me fiercely from behind.
All I can feel is my approaching orgasm.
Oh, I'm going to cum so hard!
This has brought out
the sadistic nature of his personality.
Pulling my nipple strings harder...
...he continues to ruthlessly
pound me from behind.
I never knew that pleasure
and pain could coexist.
My body responds willingly.
As I drifted away from consciousness,
I was suddenly besieged with this feeling.
I felt that I would not be chosen as queen.
Today, General Hellin will be
here for a meeting.
It will be a good opportunity to see...
...if he knows anything
about the Geild Emperor.
King Isiodore, I think it is about time
that you decide and tell me...
...who you will be
choosing as your queen.
There are still two weeks left.
There is still much unfinished
evaluation on my part.
I cannot afford to rush this process.
Yes.
Incidentally,
have you had
any news from the Geild Empire?
No, other than General Samaroon, no.
Why do you ask?
I heard that all ambassadors from Geild
are being called back to their country.
I am sure that something important
is happening there.
I'm sure we'll find out sooner or later.
If you don't mind, I would appreciate it
if you would forward any news to me.
Of course.
Apparently, General Hellin is unaware
that the Geild Emperor is dying.
If it is possible...
Yes?
I was wondering if it was possible
to speak with Princess Bellecher.
Absolutely.
I believe she's in the courtyard.
I will guide you.
It seems like General Hellin
is especially concerned...
...about the wound on her neck.
That was from the choke collar
I used in the dungeon.
I hope nothing bad comes out of this.
General Hellin.
He has just left for his camp.
He seemed concerned about the wound.
Did he say anything?
He did ask me about it, yes.
Did Belle say anything?
How did you reply?
I had already asked her to say
that it was from a royal Bosarre ritual.
Very wise.
Was it all right?
That was helpful.
If the general thought
she was being abused...
...he would surely send his army
charging into our borders immediately...
Did he respond?
He asked if the Geild princess
participated as well.
All right.
I was preoccupied with the Geild situation
that I was not thinking clearly last night.
I need to go thank Bellecher
for not telling the General the truth...
...and make her feel
that I truly care about her well-being.
Belle, it's me.
What is the matter?
I wanted to apologize about being rough.
As soon as I saw him,
all questions and doubts left my mind.
I'm so glad I did not tell
General Hellin the truth.
Besides, I was a willing participant
last night...
...I was mad at myself
for my whorish actions.
Oh, Isio.
Does your neck hurt?
N-Not anymore.
All right.
Is it all right if we have sex?
He suddenly started to caress my body.
He was fondling me like a common whore.
I could feel my nipples hardening,
and a warm wetness spreading.
No, stop.
Not like a vulgar whore.
There's nothing wrong.
Just give in to the pleasure....
I could not help but
give into the sensations.
I could feel his tongue lovingly
exploring and penetrating me.
He licked my juices
like he was licking honey....
Don't lick me there, it's dirty.
Deep inside, I wanted him to continue.
I wanted him to make me feel good.
He started penetrating me harder
with his tongue like he read my mind.
Feels good?
Feels great.
Soon, all my reservations melt away
as I revel in the pleasure.
There is no need to resist anything.
I'm just going to enjoy the ecstasy.
I drifted into a fog of lustful gratification.
It was important to treat both
Ari and Belle equally.
It was also to pacify Hellin.
This situation is getting so complex...
...that an invasion from either country
would not be a surprise...
...thus every step
I take must be carefully planned.
I can't crawl anymore.
All right, then.
If you can satisfy me,
I'll let you return to your room.
I am blindfolded, and I am enthusiastically
sucking on his hard, hot manhood.
I am afraid that someone might see me...
...but I continue my unskilled efforts
to please him.
Finally, I felt the wet, warm,
ejaculation on my face.
You did well. We're not done yet.
Yes.
That hurts. Please don't move.
I'm not used to receiving him yet,
so it still hurts a lot when he's inside me.
Every time he moves inside,
a sharp pain shoots through my body.
Moving slowly, I try to get used to
having him inside me.
I want to satisfy him.
You can move more now.
When he starts to move, it still hurts a bit.
It's getting less painful each time, though.
It makes me really happy...
...to think that I am getting used to receiving
and pleasing him down there, as well.
Please, can, if you want to...
You're deep inside.
I-It's hurting... Please stop!
I understand.
I don't think I can satisfy him.
I felt as I was letting him down.
I didn't want to be queen
for myself or my country.
All I wanted to do was
to serve and please him....
I felt a deep wave of depression.
The day of the meeting
with General Samaroon arrived.
So far, both generals agreed
that Isiodore was handling things fairly.
Also, it seemed...
...that both Ariel and Bellecher loved
Isiodore as much as he loved them.
However, fate, not Isiodore
would decide his choice for queen.
Whatever happens will happen regardless.