No!
Who are you?
Don't come any closer!
No! Don't!
Enough!
Stop!
No!
Pull it out!
Please stop.
Someone might see us.
You'll forgive me if I do it here?
Promise you won't film me?
I'm sorry. Don't hit me.
I'll do as you say.
It's so late. Nobody's watching.
Don't!
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Shusaku the Letch
Replay
Second Night:
Moeko Fujima
Please stop, Shiho!
That's it, right?
Where are you?
What are you doing?
That hurts.
Please don't.
I won't fight.
Ms. Takabe.
I'll just be a minute. Please wait here.
I'm sorry, Ms. Minami.
Kaori?
Kato? Moeko?
You're mean.
What?
You're so mean.
That...
Kenji is my boyfriend.
No, Moeko. He attacked me.
Kenji wouldn't have strayed
if you hadn't seduced him.
No.
Come on in.
Ms. Kurihara?
Didn't he tell you a slave greets
her master with sucking?
What are you doing, Moeko?
I have to. You know that, don't you?
Please stop, both of you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Ms. Minazuki?
Don't look at me like that.
No! Please stop!
Get a hold of yourself!
Ms. Minazuki!
Ms. Kurihara!
No!
Do as he says,
or he'll send out the tapes.
Maybe I really am a slut.
But so are you, Kaori.
I am not a slut.
Don't lie.
You're thinking slutty thoughts...
...and you end up hard like this.
Kato. What are you doing?
Stop the camera!
No! You promised no nasty stuff.
No.
Moeko.
Enough is enough, Kato!
I won't tolerate any more!
Let me go!
Stop!
Please stop!
That hurts.
Don't be so mean!
No more.
I'm going crazy.
Don't look at me.
Kaori, don't look!
No more.
I can't...
No!
No more!
Mr. Kato. Forgive me.
Kurihara.
I'm sorry, Moeko.
Now we're even.
No.
No!
No way! It doesn't feel good.
Stop. I can't take any more
of that. Please, Kurihara.
No, no!
No, please!
Stop it!
Not inside. Please don't!
Not inside.
I can't hold it. Bathroom...
Let me do it properly...
...in the bathroom.
No!
I can't hold it!
Don't!
Don't look at me.
Please...
...don't look at me.
Professor.
No!
Mr. Kato, please stop. It's too mean.
Don't.
Don't! No!
Don't destroy Kenji anymore!
Please forgive me.
No, I don't want it!
We're both women. You can't fight me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Don't look at me, Professor.
Ms. Minami.
Look here.
Everything Mr. Kato is plotting.
Wrong, Ms. Takabe.
What he's trying to do is...
...to educate us.