This is Bosarre, a small mountainous country.
Isiodore, at just 20 years of age,
is their new king.
The population of Bosarre is under 1000.
The royal residence is more like
a large mansion than a castle.
The royal staff consists of just two people,
a single maid and a single advisor.
The advisor's name is Isaac.
The maid's name is Irene.
Your highness, the guests will be arriving soon.
Thank you.
His visitors are two princesses.
Bosarre's independence is politically
and geographically precarious...
...being bordered by two
large and powerful countries...
...the Rohan Empire to the North,
and the Geild Empire to the East.
Both empires are sending a princess...
...for the unwed Isiodore
to choose as his new queen.
The best thing I can do
under this circumstance...
...is to choose a princess which would...
...most likely guarantee
the safety of my country.
Both countries require
that Isiodore live with...
...and choose his queen
within a month and a half.
This stone is called Charmstone.
A mysterious alchemist, Myslandia,
half elf by blood...
...spent his last years within
this country during my father's reign.
On his deathbed, he presented
my father with this special stone.
Placing the stone in front of your eye
while doing a specific activity...
...allows me to cast a spell on the person.
That specific activity absolutely must involve sex.
As both princesses are here
to compete for their place as my queen...
...they should not refuse my advances.
If, both princesses refuse to be my queen,
it is still possible to become...
...part of either country and remain
in a royal position at least as a duke.
In fact, it would be a much easier life
to give up my position as king...
...and live without worries
while retaining a royal title.
Failure could be acceptable.
However, victory would be sweeter.
Victory is worth the risk.
Kokudo Oh
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
I have convinced both armies
to retreat to their borders.
Well done. Thank you, Isaac.
I have already directed the princesses
to prepare in their respective rooms.
They should be available soon.
Yes, I understand.
I have already met Bellecher
from the Rohan Empire.
It is customary for princes to study
in the royal court of other countries.
Until just two years ago, for five years,
l studied at the Royal Academy of Rohan.
We were classmates then.
During my stay there, I was always second
in my academic standing...
...as her scores always managed
to beat mine.
Throughout my academic career there,
she never acknowledged my presence.
Although I was considered
her academic rival...
...she consistently ignored me.
I would be curious to know how she feels
about this change of circumstance.
I cannot recall meeting Princess Ariel
from the eastern Geild Empire.
I was told that I had met her ten years ago,
when I spent three years in Anglemarr.
I have tried to remember,
but I cannot recall anything about her.
Generally, most royalty are
selfish and arrogant...
...leading a sheltered, coddled existence.
They end up an arrogant,
shrew of a caricature like Bellecher...
...or become an empty shell,
more appropriate as a decoration.
Your highness,
presenting Princess Ariel of Geild.
She may enter the court.
Your highness, it's been a long time.
Oh, yes.
It's been ten years.
That's right. You're right.
Is everything okay?
Yes, you must be tired after travelling.
You should go rest now.
Irene, Irene.
Yes, your highness.
Please guide Ariel back to her room.
Wait...
Yes, go ahead.
Please, if you will,
call me Ari like you used to.
Ari? Wait, you are really Ari?
Have you forgotten about me
so soon, Onii-sama?
If you would have introduced yourself
as Ari I would have known.
My legitimate, official name is Ariel.
I'm sorry about this.
I was not aware that you
belonged to the Geild family.
We will have to talk when I have more time.
I still have to meet one other person.
Yes.
I see. She is Ari...
She has grown up.
Your highness,
presenting Princess Bellecher of Rohan.
I suppose I should say
it's nice to see you again.
Yes, I already remember who you are.
Apparently, we were
at the Academy back home together.
I'm really sorry.
Unfortunately, I really can't remember you at all.
I see.
I have this bad habit
of not remembering things...
...that didn't interest me, royalty or not.
Don't worry, I am well acquainted
with your personality already.
Well then, but you don't
have to worry about that.
We're getting married, right?
That is, if you decide to choose me.
I'm aware.
Well, Bellecher, why don't you go and rest
as there is much work to do tomorrow?
I appreciate your kindness.
If you so desire, I prefer to be called Belle.
With your permission,
could l call you Isio instead of Isiodore?
Acceptable.
Irene, please guide her back.
Yes, your highness.
Well then, good night, Isio.
Good night, Belle.
Well, well.
The borders of this country are so close.
It feels like I can almost touch...
...both the Eastern and Northern
border from here.
The accompanying army for the princesses...
...have both stationed just past the border,
your highness.
If I start playing favourites, the scorned
princess' army will come invading.
Correct.
I have to be very careful
with this delicate situation. Day or night.
Correct.
I hear that generals from both sides...
...are wanting to meet with me
every other day to discuss any progress.
Correct. We will have plan our actions
very carefully regarding this situation.
For right now we'll use appropriate bribery
when necessary to maintain peace.
A very wise suggestion.
Historically, this country's independence
has depended on the wise use of bribery.
It's been our choice strategy.
The trade toll we collect
on the main trade route...
...passing through our country
makes all of this possible.
Bosarre had been sharing the profit...
...of the toll on the main trade route
between Rohan and Gilde...
...with both countries to insure
its importance and independence.
Isaac, with your skill and cunning,
you should be able to handle the generals.
Your highness, I don't think...
Don't be modest.
I am counting on your skill, Isaac.
You are too kind, my highness.
Irene!
Yes, highness.
Irene, Isaac can handle the generals,
your job is to handle the princesses.
Yes.
We will all be busy, day and night.
With one small mistake, I could
very well end up being the last king of Bosarre.
What, Irene?
It is Ariel.
You may enter.
What is it?
Well...
Yes?
I thought I would sleep here.
Okay, you're sure?
Yes, well, I even brought my pyjamas.
Are you all right?
I didn't mean to be rough.
Oh, no. I was just startled.
An expression of concern escaped my lips.
I want to present myself
as a ruthless master...
...but that facade is falling apart...
Is it because of my fond memories?
Ari...
Her female part is quivering
underneath her panties.
Covered with downy, soft hairs, her tightly closed
womanhood was not what I had expected.
Tonight, I am going to turn her
into a real woman.
I-I'm embarrassed...
Every time I touch her womanhood,
it quivers violently and uncontrollably.
As I had slowly and gently prepared her, a
warm, wetness started to flow readily from within.
Right there, right there...
Ari...
I can no longer wait...
I swear, you will be all right.
While Ari may have wanted me mentally,
her body was trying hard to keep me out.
I felt sympathy,
but I continued nevertheless.
Please stop!
Her secret passageway was very tight.
I continued to thrust
my member inside her.
But the tightness was finally
starting to wear me out...
...and I was not sure
I would be able to control myself.
I was surprised to be able
to withdraw at the last moment...
...but I felt this lingering feeling
that I had violated her.
I was unable to feel any satisfaction or joy.
Ari, are you hurting?
I'm all right, thank you.
Onii-chan, is your country
far away from here?
About the same distance as your country.
Opposite directions, though.
Opposite directions...
Why, is there something wrong?
I'm really happy to be able
to go back to my home.
But I don't want to be away from you, either.
You get to go home.
It was common for royalty to send their family
to different countries in ease of a war.
For safety, they did not have everyone in
the family in the same country at the same time.
Isiodore was old enough...
...to understand that her family was probably
sending someone in her place.
So, when are you leaving?
Really early, tomorrow morning.
That soon?
Yeah.
Will you promise to never forget me?
I promise.
You promise?
Yes, I promise.
When I grow up, I promise
I'm going to be your bride, okay?
Don't ever forget me!
A dream...
I am becoming emotional
after this seemingly fateful reunion.
Whether I can keep that promise
from long ago...
...depends on politics more than anything else.
Ari, can't sleep?
No, I had a sad dream.
Sad dream?
A dream about when I left you long ago.
I was unable to do anything
about it at that time.
But now....
This time, I'm not leaving you, ever.
Do what you like.
I had no choice but to act cold and distant.
Your highness,
did you and Princess Ariel...?
Yes.
Tomorrow, the general for Rohan
will be here for a meeting.
I suggest that you do the same
for Princess Bellecher tonight.
I understand.
This is already like a battleground.
Actually, I was trying hard
to decide who to spend the night with first.
I was not expecting Ariel to volunteer.
I thought for sure
Belle would be the first one.
Which points out that Belle's very
obvious pride may be getting in the way.
This could get complicated quickly.
It could be a political problem for us.
But for Belle, who was sent
to be my bride by her country...
...this could be trouble for her
if she fails her mission.
Good evening.
Yes, Belle.
Yes.
The door is not locked.
Are you in a rush, my lady?
I-I'm in no rush at all.
All right. You can be much quieter
when opening and closing the door...
...at least in this country.
Isaac should give you a lesson
on manners in my country.
Custom and manners of this country
will not be optional for the new queen.
I will expect both you and Ari to learn it.
As a queen, it is unavoidable.
T-There is a beautiful moon out, tonight.
Really, I have not had the chance
to look at the night sky recently.
It is a beautiful moon.
Is that the reason you're here?
Well....
See, the stars are beautiful.
If I recall, you earned
top scores in Astronomy as well.
I was never able to surpass your score.
Well done, that was an accomplishment.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, this country has no need
for such subjects as astronomy.
No need for lectures on astrological positions...
No need to lecture me on it.
I made sure I was very sarcastic.
Good night, Belle.
On your way back to your quarters...
...will you please tell Ari
that I am requesting her presence?
Compared to Ari, Belle is smarter
and has had a better upbringing.
However, she is not used to being slighted.
Her pride forces her to prove herself.
What's wrong?
I hear Ariel spent the night last night with you?
Yes?
Then I can't leave until I spend the night.
All right.
I'm right, aren't I?
I understand.
Let us take a bath, first.
That's fine, please go first.
No!
You're taking one with me.
I suggest that you undress.
Unless ladies in your country
insist on bathing with their clothes on.
Are we going to do it...here?
We don't have to.
It doesn't matter, I suppose.
She was extremely responsive.
Apparently, her virgin body
was especially sensitive.
Maybe she was used to playing with herself?
That feels good...
She was especially sensitive between her legs.
When I had slipped my finger inside,
I could feel that she was wet and ready.
I could feel that her juices
were warmer than the bath.
Are you sure?
Yes, very.
All right, just like this, no problems...
That hurts...!
No!
She was in much pain.
I want you to stop!
And tried hard to stop me.
But once I had already started,
l was not willing to stop.
It's not like she didn't know
what she was getting into.
Her fleeting sign of virginity
slowly stained the bathwater.
The noble, haughty, princess Belle.
The test results have been posted!
You did very well.
You're in the top two again.
Top two again.
If Bellecher wasn't here,
you would be the top student.
Maybe.
In my life, grades don't really matter to me.
When I go back,
my profession is already chosen for me.
Look there, Bellecher's looking at us.
You're imagining things.
No, see, again!
She's just looking in this direction.
Do you think she's looking at us?
I can't imagine why.
Why do you say that?
I've my reasons.
What? You can tell me!
Last month, as I was walking
around the campus in the morning...
...I thought I would bid
my academic arch nemesis a good day.
What happened?
She absolutely ignored me.
I'm sorry I asked!
She seems to ignore everyone,
especially us males.
Wait a minute, in that case...
What is it?
If you couldn't get her attention,
l probably don't have a chance.
You're always full of fun ideas.
You never know,
you should try just in case.
I'll hold off.
Wise decision.
Asshole!
Why did you have to do that
when l fell asleep?
You're sleeping happily all by yourself.
I think you were having
those dirty dreams!
Smiling too much to be otherwise.
So, you've been staring at my sleeping face?
What, of course not!
Do you remember,
that time back in school...
...when you flat out ignored me?
Did I do that?
I could have done something like that.
Why did you ignore that?
Well...
You scared me.
I didn't know how to react at that time.
All I did was greet you.
Is that so surprising?
That was the first time ever
that a boy said anything to me.
Especially since it was you.
What about me?
T-The conversation's over!
You need to go to sleep.
You have a busy day ahead.
You're the one that woke me up.
You should have stayed asleep.
Whatever...
Belle and Ari, I just want you two
to listen well.
From now on, until the announcement
of my choice for queen...
...we will all live here together
for a month and a half.
We do not have enough staff.
As such, I expect you
to be available to attend...
...various public announcements
and meetings...
...as well as the hostessing
and housekeeping.
A-Are you saying that I have to clean?
Yes, we consider housekeeping ability to be an
important ability that my Queen should master.
Please remember that as your King,
your first duty is to submit and serve my will.
Is the willingness to submit
one of the requirements?
It's a very important one.
It's equally as important as learning
the customs and manners of this country.
I would like to know what criteria
you are going to use to choose your queen.
I will explain in detail, princess.
Learning the manners and customs,
housekeeping ability...
...also your skill and willingness to please
your king in the king's private quarters.
Your ability to submit and sacrifice
yourself to him is very important.
Madness!
All these factors will be calculated
and used to choose the new queen!
Well, if this is what you really want...
...I'm sure you can learn a lot from
and be able to tolerate this whole process.
This is so my chosen queen will not be
an embarrassment to my throne and country.
As part of the queen selection process
a strange, forced, cohabitation started...
...amidst a very volatile and delicate
political situation.
How am I doing, mistress?
Apparently Irene is training Ari
in some bedroom skills.
Ari is learning to orally please me.
They almost looked like sisters.
Ari was whispering something
that I couldn't hear in Irene's ear...
What did you think?
Do you think my king
will enjoy my new skill?
I believe you are doing very well,
my princess.
Did Irene know?
She was aware that I was watching
and didn't care at all.
I have been given just a month and a half
to choose my queen.
With the fate of my kingdom in the balance,
l wonder how far I can go for my pleasure.
All kinds of fantasies and ideas
are flooding my imagination.