I made a stain on the carpet with juice...
You think it'll come out?
First off, I need to see how it is...
Excuse me.
Um... Where's the stain?
I don't see it...
Over here.
What?
You think this love-juice
stain will come out?
This is...
It's not possible?
No worries.
You want the special
stain-removing service, right?
I'll leave it up to you.
Then...
You are so good.
Seems like the stain
is going to spread more.
Then let's take this o_
before it becomes any dirtier.
You are good at taking it off too.
I'm a dry cleaner.
Not allowed.
Miss Masayo...
No rushing.
We'll continue this in bed...
Miss Masayo...
I was right.
Young ones are so good...
So it's rough.
Their dicks are powerful...
There!
Right there!
Cleaning all the way to the back!
That's right...
Strong...
...and intensely...
Miss Masayo, the best
cleaning feeling is inside you...
I'm not going to lose
to those girls around there.
Then I will suck you
dry with my techniques.
Miss Masayo...
If you move like that,
you get a lot tighter, and I...
You're young,
so you can just let it all out.
Is it easier to let it out this way?
I like it better ''as is''...
So...
Miss Masayo...
I was right, as it is so much better!
I'm going to...
It's fine to come inside me...
Please fill my insides
with your pure, white semen!
Miss Masayo...
Come inside...
Please come inside me...
Miss Masayo!
The young semen is bursting!
My name is Shinii Ouhashi.
I'm a part-timer at Asai Cleaning.
Everyone calls me...
Shin!
I've got a few things, so could
you stop by on your way out?
Ah, yes.
I'll be waiting.
Thank you for all your business.
That's right... Everyone calls me...
Shin the Laundryman.
Dirty Laundry
Episode 1
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
It's been a month
since I started this job.
My youth and looks makes me
popular among the frustrated wives...
Asai Cleaning
...but there's a person
I can't clean yet...
I'm back.
Thanks for your hard work.
It was hot outside, right?
There's some barley tea
in the back, so take a break.
She's Miss Sayaka, a widow who's
run the place alone till l started.
Thank you very much.
Also, change your shirt
since you're covered in sweat.
That was my husband's, but I think
the size is right, so please use it.
Ah, yes.
It's an old thing,
so maybe it won't suit the young?
No, thank you so much!
I'm glad.
Even now, her deceased husband's
shadow leaves a stain in her heart.
I want to clean her heart and body.
Miss Sayaka...
No...
You can't, Shin...
Your feelings make me happy,
but my husband is inside me...
In here, Yutaro still lives...
Shin!
But your nipples aren't saying that.
They're this hard. You want it,
don't you, Miss Sayaka?
Please forgive me, Yutaro...
No...
That's...
You're this soaked...
How long were you vacant?
Dummy...
I kept it vacant for you.
So you can let him in.
Miss Sayaka... I...
Oh, Shin!
I was so lonely, Shin...
Don't leave me...
I don't want to be alone anymore!
I'll always be next to you.
I'll always stay by you.
Stay close to me...
Come deeper... deeper into me...
It feels good...
This feeling...
This is the feeling I wanted...
Pound me more...
Pound me up more!
Make me forget
about him from inside me...
Make me yours!
I can't get enough of it, Shin!
Give it to me more, Shin!
It's amazing, Shin!
Shin!
Shin?
Ah...
Is something wrong?
Ah, um...
Does it look good on me?
Shin, you're so funny.
Yeah, it looks really good on you.
Miss Sayaka...
Here.
Please take this next.
Um...
I'm rooting for you, Shin.
Miss Sayaka...
Asai Cleaning
When she makes that smile,
I can't say anything anymore...
But when I think about her...
No no! I can't just push her down...
I need to hold back...
Shinji, hang on to reason!
Holding it in no good.
Underwear going to stain.
M-Miss Mari!?
Miss Mari, this is...
Oh, Shin!
Here, this is your job, Shin.
Ah, yes.
Job, huh...
Miss Mari still doesn't
get what laundry services do.
Miss Mari, how is everything?
Are you finally getting
used to Japan a little bit?
Isn't it hard coming
to Japan as a bride?
Yeah, there's lots of things
you don't know here.
I'm sure. If there's anything
I can do, please tell me.
I'll help you out.
Thank you, Shin.
So about what you
saw in the car before...
...I want to ask you
to pretend you didn't see anything.
If this is found out
by the shop, I'm going to be...
I don't know many
things about Japan...
...but perverted things are universal.
What?
Shin, please hit me with that.
I knew that you were a masochist...
...but this doesn't mean it's universal.
Hurry!
Miss Mari...
Here I go. Are you ready?
Hit me, hurry!
One, two...
It...
It hurts...
Then you want
me to stop, Miss Mari?
No, the pain feels good...
Miss Mari...
...if you stick out
your butt that much, I'll...
Shin, you're holding your dick.
You want to do it with me, huh?
Well, that's...
Holding it in is no good.
Stop hiding it and show me.
Japanese person's dick...
Shin, your dick...
Miss Mari...
More than happy to!
You hit me and is turned
on as your dick grows big.
Our compatibility is perfect.
That's my bad once again.
I like people being honest.
Miss Mari...
How is it?
Does it feel good, Shin?
It feels good, Miss Mari...
Then next I'm going
to do something like this.
Miss Mari...
Come on, Shin!
You move your hand too.
Let's feel good together.
Miss Mari!
Evey time I hit her,
she puts it deeper in her mouth...
It feels so good...
Hit me harder!
Miss Mari! Miss Mari...
It's being wrapped
by the back of your throat...
I'm going to...
Miss Mari!
Shin... Shin...
Next, with those.
We're going to have
fun using those, Shin.
Those, huh...
Shin, hurry!
It hurts so much that it feel so good!
It feels like my nipples
are going to rip off!
Miss Mari...
It's going to rip off,
and I'm going to die!
I want one here too!
Shin!
Come on, use the one in
your hand and torture my clit.
Then we combine together!
Miss Mari...
It feels so good!
Put it in!
Miss Mari...
It's in...
It's coming in...
Can't get enough of it...
Such a pleasant feeling!
It feels good... Miss Mari...
It's wrapping around mine...
Shin, you're becoming harder
and harder inside me...
So happy...
Shin... Mess me up more!
Miss Mari...
You have a husband,
so why do you do this with me?
He doesn't understand
a woman's body!
No matter how
good a husband he is...
...if there's too big a break,
a woman's body can't hold it in.
This is universal too.
It's so good!
Shin, your dick is so good!
Miss Mari, I'm already...
I'm at my limit!
You can let it out, Shin...
Pour it all into me!
Miss Mari!
Shin...
Here, Shin.
Thank you.
You wash it for me so even
if I stain with having sex, it's all good.
Well, please don't overdo it.
Shin, come back soon.
A woman's body
always needs a man.
Shin...
A woman's body is always in...
...need of a man.
There is no way that's
the case with Miss Sayaka...
...I hope.
I'm back.
Huh?
Miss Sayaka?
Is she out?
But she left the store as is...
That's not safe...
I'm sure it's just that she's
in the bathroom or something.
Yeah, I'll go around to the back door.
What?
Miss Sayaka is crying?
ls she...
...thinking of her late husband...
...till this day?
Miss Sayaka?
No, she's not crying...
She's comforting herself...
Look, I told you.
A woman's body is in need
of a man all the time...
Shin...
It's the scent of a man...
He's sweating this much
and working for me...
No... I can't get
enough of this smell...
That's the shirt...
...Miss Sayaka said
she'd wash for me.
Shin...
Shin!
Miss Sayaka...
Shin's scent...
A man's scent...
Oh no, my underwear
is going to get stained...
S-Shin?
O-Oh no!
Watch out!
Ouch...
I-I'm sorry!
Ah!
This is...
He's erect...
M-Miss Sayaka?
It's been a while
since I saw a man's penis...
It's length... It's warmth...
Since he died...
Miss Sayaka?
Oh no, I...
I'm sorry!
The scent of men is my weakness...
Since my husband passed, I've
been comforting myself on my own...
When I was
smelling your shirt, Shin...
...I couldn't hold it in anymore...
I became a woman...
I'm really sorry...
Even though I know it's wrong,
my body just throbs...
Shin!
Miss... Sayaka...
I can't hold it in anymore
if you show me this.
A real penis!
It's pulsing, and it's so manly...
Penis... Shin's penis...
It's not fair
if it's just you. Miss Sayaka...
I want to enjoy you too...
You can...
Miss Sayaka...
Please get me wet for real, Shin.
Don't tease me. I want it directly.
Please roll it around
with your tongue, Shin.
Yes...
Wow, this is Miss Sayaka's...
It's pink and so pretty...
Shin, there! Right there!
Roll it around with your tongue more!
Shin, I can't hold it in anymore.
Please give it to me!
Please put your penis in my pussy!
I want it too, Miss Sayaka...
Oh, Shin...
I'm so happy.
Shin...
It's coming in!
It's so good!
Then I'll turn you on more!
Oh gosh, it's been so long
since a man handled my breasts!
Do it more!
As I thought, a real one is better!
A penis is better!
Shin, please mess me up tonight.
Miss Sayaka...
That's good, Shin. It's amazing...
Right there... totally turns me on...
Miss Sayaka...
Shin, you are turning
harder and harder...
Shin, when we come,
we're going to come together.
Miss Sayaka!
That's right... More...
Pound me harder!
Shin...
A broad back...
A man's back...
I'm so happy!
A penis is so wonderful!
It's in all the way to the back...
It's good...
So good!
I can't anymore...
Miss Sayaka's whole
vagina is squeezing me!
Come inside...
Come inside me!
Shin, I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Miss Sayaka...
Not yet.
I want to feel you inside me
for a little while longer...
Shin...
You're still pulsing inside me...