At the age of 20, Isiodore inherited
the Bosarre crown after his father's death.
The Rohan empire to the north...
...and the Geild Empire to the East,
have sent their princesses to Isiodore to choose.
Both Empires are eager to forge
a strong alliance with Bosarre...
...which posses important trade routes
and a fortress-like geography.
The Rohan Empire sent
Princess Bellecher as their candidate.
The Geild Empire sent Princess Ariel...
...to possibly secure the position
as a Bosarran queen.
To maintain Bosarre's independence
and safety, Isiodore must be...
...extremely careful with this delicate
decision of choosing his queen...
If the princess feels slighted...
...her army is waiting at the border to wage
a military campaign against Bosarre...
Isiodore must live with, and choose
his queen within a month and a half.
Isiodore has already become
intimately acquainted with both princesses.
It is important at this stage...
...to treat both princesses equally
both in and out of the bedroom.
This stone is called Charmstone.
A mysterious alchemist,
Myslandia, half elf by blood...
...spent his last years within this country
during my father's reign.
On his deathbed,
he presented this to my father.
A magical stone.
Placing the stone in front of your eye...
...while doing a specific activity
allows me to cast a spell on the person.
That specific activity
absolutely must be sex.
As both princesses are here to compete
for their place as my queen...
...they should not refuse my advances.
If they refuse, it is possible to become...
...part of either country
and remain in a royal position.
In fact, it would be a much easier life...
...to give up my position as king and live
without worries while retaining a royal title.
Failure could be acceptable.
However, victory would be
sweeter in my case.
Kokudoh Oh 3
Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
The most difficult aspect of training...
...to be a queen is the complete
mastery of Bosarre's customs.
Also required is the mastery
of religious rituals, history...
...and geography of Bosarre as well.
Even foreign ambassadors take
several years to learn all the information.
It seems nearly impossible for the princesses
to master in the given time frame
of a month and a half.
Apparently,
Ari is having a very difficult time.
Ari is not good with
memorization and the like...
...I am sure Isaac is having a difficult time.
Isaac, are they advancing in their studies?
Princess Ariel is having difficulties.
She is trying very hard, however.
All right.
How long do you think she would take,
going at this pace?
Yes.
At this pace, it would still take her
about 5 years for full mastery.
Five years....
How about Belle?
Princess Bellecher is an extraordinary case,
as you already know.
She would only need about two years.
All right.
By the way....
How did my mother do during her training?
Well, I heard from my late father...
...that her circumstance
was very, very different.
Her country, Shandalar,
had different customs and language.
lt must have been very difficult.
My father, who was assigned as her tutor...
...first learned about Shandalar's various customs
and its language to facilitate the learning process
for your mother.
As a result, my father was able to
better correspond with...
...Shandalar merchants
and ambassadors to further our trade
and political relationship with them.
A large percent of Bosarre's
current wealth...
...comes from that favorable
alliance my father helped build.
Yes, I already know.
Could you please send for Ari?
As you wish.
It is Ariel.
You may enter.
Ari is apparently very nervous.
She thinks she is in trouble.
She is trying to remember if she did
anything wrong to warrant punishment.
Are you doing better with your studies?
Oh, yes.
She seems relieved that I'm not upset.
I know it is difficult to learn
so much information.
Take your time and master
the information thoroughly.
Yes.
You are probably stressing
about the speed of Belle's learning.
Comparing yourself to others
does not help anything.
I understand.
That is all.
I'm counting on you.
Thank you, your Highness, but....
What is it?
I promise that I won't let you down...
You'll be confident in choosing me.
Just give me time to prove myself.
Please.
Of course.
It's lunchtime. To the dining hall.
Yes!
Ari seemed to be
encouraged by my words.
Her large gap in progress...
...might make it seem like
I am favoring Belle.
It won't be good if the Geild general,
Samaroon, gets that kind of impression.
I might have to ask Belle to slow down.
Eating should be
one of the pleasures of life.
However, Belle made a faux pas
in her manners during dining.
Is that not bad manners, Belle?
What?
I know, I was just testing you.
Belle, come with me.
Where?
We need to talk.
Were you aware of your bad manners?
Of course I was aware.
Tell me.
If you don't know,
all you have to do is ask me.
This is going to take some time.
Belle has serious issues with being able
to say that she doesn't know.
Used to having the highest scores academically
she has a fierce pride of needing to know all the facts,
all the time.
Her intellectual prowess
does not come to her naturally.
She is just very dedicated to her studies.
There is nothing wrong with
admitting that you don't know.
I know the answer.
Then, tell me.
This could go on forever.
I know that Rohan has a dish,
basted roasted pheasant's head.
Yes, it's Kizin.
Yes, we have a similar dish called Bollo
that is customarily eaten after a funeral.
Yes, I knew that.
I'm sure then,
that you know whether Bollo is eaten
with a spoon or a fork?
Yes.
Which is it?
A spoon is used for Kizin...
I am asking about Bollo.
With a blind guess, your chance is 50%.
I'll say spoon.
So, you did know.
Of course I did!
One more question.
Bosarre has no dish called Bollo...
...so you've been bluffing
the whole time, Belle.
You tricked me! Not fair!
Well then, is it fair to lie
about what you do and don't know, Belle?
I will not have you lie to me,
you understand?
I will be sure to warn Irene and Isaac.
If this happens again,
you will receive a harsh punishment.
Punishment?
I need to show you
an example of a punishment.
Bring Ariel and Irene.
Answer me!
Yes, your Highness...
I just want you to become more honest.
It's very important
to be able to admit fault.
I can't deal with this kind
of fault and arrogance.
If I try...
If I change, will you choose me as queen?
I'll think about it.
Now, bring Irene and Ari.
Yes.
Please, both you and Ari
change into a maid's uniform.
Maid?
I need to make sure
that both Belle and Ari...
...are aware of what
punishment consists of.
It's not as if Irene
has any faults to require punishment.
I'm just using her as an example.
Are you prepared for punishment?
Yes.
I am prepared.
I had asked Irene...
... to wear this harness to make the punishment
look severe, make this session more effective.
The punishment starts.
Harnesses, chains and such are tools
to effectively give an air of brutality.
Please punish me.
Irene was well prepared.
She was already wet and moaning.
I plowed Irene with my manhood
to show them an example of punishment.
I could not tell whether
she was really enjoying this or not.
She had no problems accepting me
as she was getting wetter.
They both seem very shocked.
They've probably never seen anyone
forced to submit like this.
Let me warn you both that a mistake...
...could result in harsher
punishment than this...
Apparently, the spectacle
has driven my point across.
No one is allowed to object
to any punishments handed down by me.
Even if you think of your
punishment as being unreasonable...
...I'll have you know...
... my authority here is absolute
and I will not hear any complaints.
Please...
...have...
...Mercy.
I unleashed a large load inside of Irene.
I want you both to get serious.
Any problems will be dealt with
swift punishment.
Keep that in mind.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
I will not be the one to call on
either one of you at night anymore.
It will be whoever comes
to my chambers first.
I guess Isio will not be
calling for me this evening.
Could he possibly be with Ariel right now?
Isio?
I will tolerate this for my country,
my family, and my reputation.
What is...?
This is enema equipment.
An enema?
I explained myself earlier.
This is your punishment
for your insolence during lunch today.
You will not object.
I wanted to show Isio that
I could tolerate his punishments...
...that I could tolerate them
better than Ariel.
Are you prepared?
No.
The reason I am here is to help...
...develop an alliance
for my country with Bosarre.
I was prepared to sacrifice my virginity,
but I was not prepared for this....
You don't seem sure.
No, please, do with me as you wish.
All right then, remove your dress.
Oh, yes...
Is this all right, your Highness?
To receive an enema, what part
of your body do you have to expose?
Oh yes, right here.
Where is here?
M-My asshole.
Stand in front of the mirror.
Yes.
Not like that.
Face your ass towards the mirror.
Like this, right?
Turn your head around
and take a look at the mirror.
Yes.
I thought Isio might have been
just kidding...
...but he seems intent
on going through with this...
I can't believe this is happening to me!
Please... Make it quick.
Is that tube going inside?
All that fluid going inside?
Please be gentle with me!
Isio has some lubricant
on the tip of his fingers.
He's preparing me
so my body will accept the tube.
No!
Please don't put that inside me!
Ignoring my pleas,
he continued to insert the tube inside.
I-It's cold!
It's cold!
After this, you will learn some techniques.
T-Techniques?
Yes, so you will be able to
please me completely.
Do you object?
As you wish, your Highness....
How long has it been since
I was brought to the dungeon by Isio?
I was naked, and restrained
around the neck and both nipples.
Isio! Where?
They're becoming really tender.
So red, just like rubies.
As I was trying to ease
the pain in my nipples...
...I started to feel a strange sensation.
I started to shamelessly,
enthusiastically masturbate.
Oh, Isio!
You seem to be doing well.
No...
You weren't watching...?
Wait!
I can't believe he saw me masturbating
in the dungeon...
...with restraints,
under these circumstances!
I can feel you inside.
I can't believe I am so wet already.
My pussy is hungrily
consuming Isio's cock.
How did I become such a whore?
He's pounding hard.
I can feel my pussy wrapping tight
around his cock as he plows me.
Ouch!
If I lower my torso, I'll choke.
No, don't pull the collar!
My nipples will tear off!
The pain was somehow turning to pleasure
and my pussy was getting wetter.
I'm cumming....
I think Belle's had enough in terms
of lessons and punishment for one day.
I will need to be
kind and understanding tonight.
I want her to understand her faults.
Torture is not the point of this.
Oh, Isio!
I hope you have learned
your lesson today?
Yes, I think I understand now.
We have time.
I want you to know how important it is
to learn from your mistakes.
Yes, you're right, Isio.
Oh, don't.
These must be rather sensitive tonight.
You're being mean.
Good, Isio.
I am done with Belle for today.
Oh, Isio.
I hope she doesn't say
anything negative to her general....
Good morning, your Highness.
Good morning.
I heard you spent a lot of time
with Princess Bellecher last night.
Yes, I hope she learned her lesson.
Knowing her,
this will probably take a while.
Make sure to keep her in line.
Absolutely.
I need to spend some time with Ari
before the meeting with her general tomorrow.
I agree.
Since I punished Bellecher
I need to punish Ariel as well...
...so, has she made any mistakes lately?
Yes, small mistakes
during housecleaning duties this morning.
That's it, Isaac.
Mistakes during housekeeping.
Housekeeping is supposed
to be her strong point.
Yes?
I need to have her aware and on her toes.
Yes.
Tell Irene to carry out
spanking as Ariel's punishment.
Right away.
Ariel had apparently been spanked
by Irene for a while.
Wearing a chastity belt like I ordered...
...the sight of her getting spanked,
in tears, made me feel guilty.
I did not look her in the eye on purpose
to see her reaction.
Irene will carry out all
of my orders promptly, efficiently...
...and perfectly, without a single
word of complaint.
As I watched,
Ariel was obviously getting very wet.
Is she getting excited
because I was watching?
I think she was embarrassed
as she refused to look me in the eye.
Although Irene did not seem to mind,
she was probably getting tired by now.
Although she is trying to contain it,
her moans are showing hints of pleasure.
This is enough.
Irene, that will be all today.
Yes, your Highness.
I hope you have
no objections to your punishment.
Yes.
I felt a sudden sense of guilt after
looking at her inflamed bottom...
...and accidentally offered
a word of sympathy.
You did very well.
T-Thank you.
Ari?
This must sting quite a bit.
I will bring something for it tonight.
Thank you very much.
from her reaction this afternoon...
...Ari must be expecting me
in her chambers tonight.
I will postpone my meeting
with General Samaroon until tomorrow...
...and make sure
to take care of Ari tonight.
I don't want him to get a negative impression,
or have to offer any more bribes.
I have been learning from Irene...
...about different techniques for
orally pleasing a man, especially Isio.
Irene is so pretty,
and she knows so much about this.
I admit I get a lime jealous when
I think about Irene pleasing Isiodore...
...like she taught me to.
The best I can do is
to learn as much as possible.
I am trying everything I learned
on him right now...
...while I move my head up and down
like I was taught to.
I can't believe I am sucking on this,
wanting to do something...
...that I used to think was reserved
for whores in dim men's books.
I can feel my body getting hotter
as I continue to suck on him.
I can feel my small nipples
getting hard and erect...
...as I stroke my nipples
from above my bra.
I am scratching my nipple with my nail...
...as I revel in the feeling of pain
and pleasure course through my body.
I can't even cry out in pleasure
since my mouth is occupied with Isio...
...so I just make incoherent noises.
As I continue pleasing him...
...I can't help but play with myself
as well by vigorously stroking my breast.
Right after I started to suck,
I started to feel a warm wetness flood...
...between my legs, so I spread the wet lips
wide apart to make them glistening wet.
I wanted to please him
using my lower lips as well...
...but right now I would like
to practice sucking more.
I could feel his cock harden
and start to vibrate...
...so I prepared myself, to receive.
No, I wanted every single drop of Isiodore.
As he exploded in my mouth...
...I can feel my throat getting
bathed in a sticky haze.
It tasted bitter,
but I greedily swallowed every drop...
...in my throat like a lost traveler
in the desert finding a lush oasis
I am not done with him yet.
Please, let me clean you up.
I start at the head, and slowly lap up...
...every drop of cum
that dripped out of my mouth.
I am not done until
it is licked entirely clean.
I am done cleaning.
I hope you liked it.
You did well.
Irene taught me that,
the job's not done until you ask how he liked it,
and to make sure that he is licked clean.
I don't think I'm as experienced
or as skilled as Irene...
...when it comes to things
like pleasing a man sexually.
I hope he doesn't send me away
soon as a result.
What's wrong?
Well...
I felt strongly that I wanted to stay
and be his queen.
Stay and serve him well.
What's on your mind?
Will you please,
choose me, to be your queen?
I'll consider it.
T-Thank you!
Oh, Onii-sama, you're hard again.
It's for you, Ari.
Oh, thank you so much.
I think I'm cumming, yes, I'm cumming!
The day after tomorrow...
...Isiodore will be meeting with both
the Rohan and the Geild generals.
They are both very eager to know...
...the progress their princess is making
to becoming the new queen.
Both generals, to protect the reputation
of their empire and princess...
...have their army on alert at the border...
...to wage war on Bosarre should
they feel they have been slighted.
The young King Isiodore
is between a rock and a hard place.
The threat to his country remains...
...as the deadline for him
to choose his queen draws near.