Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster
for www.world-of-hentai.to
My Wife is a Schoolgirl
I remember those times back then.
I know, really.
Back then, you were a schoolgirl like Mika.
And you were my teacher.
People around us opposed us, and you ended
up running away. That was a hard time.
I know. I don't want her to suffer like we did.
Yea, let's bless their departure.
Yes, I want them to be happy.
Mika, I will never forget the
time we shared together.
Yesterday's Memorial sex.
Yosuke, more!
Mika, Mika, I love you!
Wow, Yosuke!
I love you too.
Wonderful, Yosuke!
Can you see where we're connected, Mika?
I can, I see it!
Your cock is pumping in and out.
How's this?
Good! The best!
More, more!
Wow, it's going in deep.
No, more, stick it in more!
It's tightening!
No, I'm cumming!
Tighter... I'm cumming!
Yosuke!
Mika, are you really sure?
Sure of what?
Marrying your teacher.
Hey, I'm really happy right now.
What? Then what about me?
You'll always be my friend, Yosuke.
Man, you...
Hey Yosuke, by the way, come
to my wedding, promise me.
What the hell, being stuck to that little girl.
I want him to light my body on fire!
This is no fun.
Wow, you suck so good.
Good, good, you're good, professor!
You're really tight down there.
There, curl your legs more.
It feels so good professor!
Is it good?
Good! It's very, very good!
You have such a nice body.
You're exciting too professor.
Fuck me more! Fuck me more down there!
Like this? This?
Wow, professor! More, more,
professor! Wow, more, more!
Can't hang on..
You're good, professor.
Professor, are you really going to
marry that girl tomorrow?
Ye..., yeah...
Then it's over for two of us.
I thought I was going to be with you.
Well...
I can't...
It's not like everything's over.
But...
We're in a good relationship.
We don't have to be paranoid about marriage,
and we can see each other again.
We work at the same place, so
let's still be good partners.
Cheer up!
You're right.
Come over here.
Hold me tight.
You're so cute.
Professor.
I won't forget about yesterday.
Mika.
Professor.
Mika, I love you.
Me too, professor.
Mika!
It feels good, professor.
Me too...
Professor, professor, I love you.
Mika.
I love you too.
Oh, I'm cumming, cumming.
Professor, I'm cumming, cumming!
You're cumming? Good, good,
you cum first, okay?
Cumming!
Hey, what's the matter? Did you cum? Huh?
No, again...
You're cumming again?
It's embarrassing, I, I again...
It's okay. There, it's okay.
Professor, cumming, cumming again.
I'm cumming, professor!
I'm cumming with you.
Cum, cum!
Cumming!
On my face professor...
That was great.
Are you sad, Yosuke?
Not really.
Really? I'm sad.
You're a strong 18 year old.
Naw, but I'm sad honestly.
I know.
I'll give you a ride Yosuke.
Come in my car, Yosuke.
Professor.
It's okay. Be quiet. Come on.
Yosuke.
Professor.
Good! Good, good!
Professor, I'm almost going to cum.
Cum all over my breasts.
Really?
Yes, really.
Professor, I'm cumming!
Okay, Yosuke.
Cumming!
Good, cum Yosuke!
Wow, I am surprised at
your cooking skills, Mika.
I gave my best, hoping to
make professor happy.
Thanks Mika, I'm happy.
But let's not use professor.
Oh yes, then my dear.
Little embarrassing, but it's nice Mika.
Our honeymoon is during summer break?
Yea, almost.
Starting from Copenhagen?
Yup, then England, Germany, Switzerland,
France, Spain, and finally Rome.
Wonderful, I can't wait!
But before that, you have final exam.
Aww, meanie! You spoiled
my daydreaming, gosh.
I see, and then on top of your daydream,
let's go experience the good dream.
Oh dear, no, there!
Right there!
What about here?
You made me this way, Professor.
Don't use professor.
Dear.
Mika.
Mika, feels so good.
Wow Mika!
Your cock is big.
How is it Mika?
Wonderful, dear.
How is it when I do this?
Dear, it's great!
Mika, it's getting tighter!
It's so tight, Mika.
Cumming! I'm cumming!
How are your days as newlyweds, Mika?
It's excellent, I'm very happy.
Wow, and where you going
for your honeymoon?
Europe.
Oh wow, not Hawaii?
Amazing.
Three weeks during summer vacation.
For three weeks? That's wonderful.
Yes, wonderful.
You appear to be shining right now Mika.
Come on, Mika.
Yosuke.
Mika, Mika.
Great, Yosuke. Great!
You're great, Mika!
Yosuke, Yosuke...
Fuck me harder Yosuke!
Mika, Mika, you're the best milf, Mika.
Good, Yosuke, good!
It's the milf special!
Professor, it's great!
Me too.
Professor...
Oh, good! Professor, it's okay for us, right?
Yup, this is good for us.
Professor!
Your breasts...
More!
I did well on my test.
That's good. Good, good.
Dear, just because I'm still young, that
doesn't mean you can cheat on me.
Hey hey, what are you saying so suddenly?
I wouldn't do that.
You're popular with the other boys, so don't
cheat on me where I can't see you.
Oh my, I wouldn't do such a thing. Gosh.
Really?
Really!