Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
Meeting with Geild's General
Samaroon arrives once again.
To this point, Isiodore has treated both princesses equally.
The love that Ariel and Bellecher has
for Isiodore is also on the same level.
However, the crossroad of fate
is coming near for Isiodore.
Hmm, what's to come?
Only god may know.
I have an urge to see Bell.
It's not just because of the reason I
have to see General Samaroon, it's also
because I'm worried that Gerald's
new emperor might ask for Bellecher.
If that's the case, Bosarre´s new queen will be Ariel.
But that's not on my own will.
No, I think there's a feeling within me
where I don't want to let go of Bellecher.
I can't wait for the night.
I think of it every day.
When night comes, Isio
will teach me some lessons!
People might say I'm a slut.
But I can't resist the lust.
Isio!?
I'm coming in, Belle.
Isio!
What is it, Belle?
I'm sorry, but I couldn't wait.
You're already wet.
Give me...more....
I beg for Isio with my dress on.
I didn't take it off because it turned me on more.
Underneath the dress, Princess
Bellecher has a different persona.
I like the immoral values of it.
lsio...lsio....!
I'm becoming a sex doll in front of Isio.
I want him to do more.
I thought to myself, but I blurted
out words meaning the opposite.
Forgive me, forgive me!
You're so wet, Belle.
Meanie...I can't....please Isio.
I don't think I can live without Isio!
Only this land's king treated me as
a woman, and not a person of royalty.
The times I spend with him doing erotic
things are the happiest moments for me now.
Cuming, cuming!
Weddings are an important ritual for Bosarre.
As a kingdom of trade, people from
different cultures live in the town.
As a king of such land, I have
to get to know each tribe's ritual.
It is very important for a king to visit the weddings.
Each group of people has their own unique living.
There are different types of weddings as
well, and as royalty you must know them.
For lesson purposes, I brought Ariel with me today.
It's probably not an easy thing for Ariel to understand
But she does know it's a moment of happiness.
Ari, did it help?
Yes, I never knew each culture
has their own style of wedding.
Yes, even holidays are different
depending on your culture.
But no matter where, the
brides are always beautiful.
I hope I can become a beautiful bride too...
Onii-sama, how is my butt?
It is very wet.
It's embarrassing...
You know what to do, Ari?
Yes, please look.
The toy's beads slowly gets pulled
out of my butt, giving me pleasure.
I can open this wide now...
To accept his manhood, I play with my butt.
That embarrassment makes my body heat up.
To make him happy, I'm about to do
something even more embarrassing.
I'll push it out.
Please...look.....
The embarrassment of showing a loved one this.
H-how was it?
Please untie me!
I don't want this!
Onii-sama is very tough today.
Was he not pleased with the show?
This strange feeling made my body stiff.
The small hole above the usual one.
The one for urine....such a place!?
W-why am I!?
It starting pouring through
the tubes against my own will.
I don't know why he is making me do such a thing.
Please forgive me...
Onii-sama.
On the day to the crowning for
the new emperor of Geild
War broke loose between three
princes, all wanting to sit on the throne.
This war would later be known
as the 7th War of the Kings.
This would have been to an advantage to Rohan
However, at the same time, a group of nations
raised war against Rohan for independence.
General Hellin and his troops were called back.
A civil war and a rebellion.
Big nations have their own problems.
Correct.
What do you think will happen to the two empires?
I hear that the 1st Prince has
the advantage for Geild.
Rohan, the damages are big but it's close to finish.
It won't damage the empire too much.
Looks like it was General Samaroon
doing, but it was only a waste of time.
So our relationship hasn't changed too much either.
Correct.
Irene, how are the two princesses doing?
Yes.
They are just as they always are.
Then lets keep up with the lessons.
Yes Sir.
lsaac, what are the status of the borderlines?
Yes.
For Gerald, General Samaroon's right
hand man is still there with few troops.
As for Rohan, General Hellin retreated
with all his troops back to the empire.
What will become of the meetings?
I don't think you need to be in it.
I'll take care of it.
Alright, I'm counting on you.
Understood.
Irene, that idea is a bit unusual.
Are you not pleased?
No, it sounds great.
Elaine's idea was very feminine.
Her idea was instead of punishing them
like I always do, do the opposite of it.
And you'll be the guinea pig?
Yes.
You're saying that Sadist and Masochism
are two different things but also the same.
Yes, if they can enjoy the sadist side of it, they'll
learn to enjoy the masochism side even more.
Lets try it, your contribution means dear to me.
Such unneeded words, anything for you Sir.
Are you two ready?
Yes.
Lets start, Irene.
Yes, your Highness.
No need to hesitate, please go on.
What are you two doing!
This is part of your lesson!
Take off Irene's clothes!
Y-Yes!
Irene let us take off her clothes without hesitation.
Even when touching her, she showed no resistance.
I can not tell if she's enjoying it with the light moan.
Irene, does it feel good?
Ones who can't give pleasure
can't experience pleasure.
His words made us realize something important.
It wasn't directly, but he was
implementing that this is a waste of time.
So big...
I stuck one end of this tool inside myself...
It felt strange, as if I became a man.
Listening and looking at Irene
stirred something inside me.
It made me want to thrust this thing inside of her.
It made me want to fool around with Irene.
That's...
Maybe it's because she's experienced in anal, but
soon as I touched it, it started to open up.
Irene...
Looking at Irene and Belle started to turn me on.
Oh, from both sides!!
Belle, it's not finished yet.
Isio!?
Now you try pleasing Ari.
Irene, what are you!?
Obey my orders.
Belle...
I felt Belle's sadness.
If I wasn't here, Onii-sama would've been all hers.
That's what I felt.
Eyes that show hatred and sadness.
I want to accept Belle for who she is!
This is what I truly felt.
Don't worry about me, do as what Onii-sama says.
Belle...
Ari?
I'm sorry, Ari...
Ari...
You're so wet...
I don't need to hold back.
The pleasure of two women becoming together.
This is a different pleasure than the one with Irene.
Two pitiful princesses are bonding...
Onii-sama...?
Now you please Belle, Ari.
Isio!?
Irene, what are you...!
As the king wishes...
Belle, forgive me.
So deep...
Feels good...
I didn't want Isio to see me
enjoying being violated by Ari.
What I want is you, Isio!
I can't hold it back any more, I want Ari to go on...
More, more, give me more Ari!
As my breasts sway, I let out dirty words.
Ari's breasts swaying against my back and her
penetrating me is giving me one big pleasure.
Sir, how was it?
You did well, Irene.
Come to my room later.
Understood.
Highness!
Finished?
Good job.
You'll get your reward as promised.
Geild's army has retreated
and this is the end of Samaroon.
Sir, are you going out?
Yes, as a king I can't miss the festivities
that celebrates our ancestors.
Who will you take?
I think Belle.
Depending on Geild's decision
she might go back to Rohan.
By the way, Geild's army that resided
at the borders have retreated.
Some unknown group has killed Samaroon's
right hand man and set fire to the camp.
That's really daring coming from you.
No, people of Geild are saying that the
cause of war is due to General Samaroon.
Either way, the ones who did this
will probably be treated as heros.
And you're making them the heros I see.
If things are settled with Geild
the problem with Rohan still lies.
Actually, it seems that they have
full control of the rebellion now.
That means I need to choose my queen.
Although it depends on Geild.
Correct.
My breast is burning....
I scream but he continues regardless.
It was painful at first, but it soon
began to overwhelm with pleasure.
Hot!
Please...give me....more......
It's as if he's stamping the kingdom's
emblem on my nipples to mark that I am his.
The thought of it made me proud.
The wax may be gone the next day
but this ritual will be in my heart forever.
I want to be with Isio forever...
Onii-sama, where are we going?
Giving Belle her last punishment, I
also need to do the same for Ari.
Confirming Belle's love, now I have to confirm Ari's.
Onii-sama punishment is especially severe today.
A slight movement, even just the
fingers, runs pain through my body.
But that pain soon becomes
pleasure I dare not want to end.
It's because only I can experience this.
It's going to rip!
Onii-sama!
Cuming...
Cuming!
I squirt very hard, almost looking like I was urinating.
Today is the day for Isiodore to make his decision.
Geild's civil war has ended.
The first prince is now the new emperor.
Rohan has also succeeded in calming the rebellion.
I am not able to come to a
decision on who to choose.
A king who can't make a decision
is not needed for Bosarre.
I am going to give up my
position and become a traveler.
Just like Mithralandia.
You two have served me well for a long time.
Thank you.
Sir, at least take me with you!
No, a fallen king doesn't deserve servants.
Sir, you need to rethink that.
Isaac?
Messengers from Rohan and Geild will
be here shortly, both wanting your help.
Both Geild and Rohan needing my help?
Yes, as long as Bosarre stays neutral
war can be avoided from both nations.
Isaac, what did you do?
Lets just say I want both empires
and Bosarre to prosper in peace.
It also means if you marry both princesses
you can beep the balance between the two.
That's unbelievable.
Correct, it's thanks to our
ancestors protecting over us.
Thanks to Isaac's political
strategy, Bosarre was saved.
Having marrying to both princesses
Bosarre earned its independence.
Ari, your big butt is in the way!
Your butt won't fit on that chair!
Sit on that chair!
You're in the way!
With those two dumbbells
you have, the chair will brake.
Why don't you sit on that chair!?
Hey, that crappy chair looks perfect with you!
That extravagant dress and the
crappy chair will balance it perfectly!
What!?
Alright, you can have that chair then.
OK, I will.
Isio, excuse me!
Hey Belle...
Onii-sama, excuse me!
Ari, you too...
You two are heavy, get off!
Heavy!? How rude of you!
Onii-sama, you're so mean!
There's no point of arguing here.
Lets go to the bedroom.
That's a good idea!
We can satisfy you together when it's on the bed.
That's right, come on Isio.
Lets go.
Hey!
It's still noon!
What are you saying, you're the one who
taught us the pleasures day in and day out.
Yeah, lets all have fun together.
Irene, Irene!
You too!
Currently, Bosarre is the most peaceful
and prospering nation on this land.
But my private life is another issue...
Hey Isaac, help me out!