No!
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Shusaku the Letch
Replay
Third Night:
Ayaka Minami
No!
I'm sorry.
I didn't want anyone to know.
I won't tell anyone.
Ms. Fujima says...
...she wants you to have them back.
I never thought you'd really loan them to
her.
I should have loaned her underwear...
That's not what I mean.
What about the smell?
Who would enjoy the smell?
Don't look at me like that.
What?
Don't look at me like that!
None of that cheap stuff in my mouth!
Please, no more.
No. If you don't go for
a walk, Mr. Kato will be upset.
What's wrong?
Why do you listen to him?
You have to listen to him.
You'll soon find out.
Your body will listen to him.
Please put an end to this.
Do you want to pee?
Come this way.
I don't want to, not here anyway.
You do it like this.
Don't be ridiculous. That's just like...
You have to be a bitch.
Please. I just can't. I just went.
Don't!
Your resistance is futile.
That wine you had...
We drugged it.
Why me?
Once you get used to it, it feels good.
I don't need my bloomer back.
I'm not special.
Just because I'm a teacher
doesn't make me any different.
You need to talk to me?
It's personal.
I see.
I'll visit you in the dorm after school.
This is her memory?
Nagisa confided in me.
She said she fell in love with a man.
Since then, I've felt weird.
Before, we just talked
and I felt close to her.
Now, I need to be with her all the time.
Even when we're alone together...
...I feel something is missing...
...and I desire Nagisa.
It happens at your age.
But not only Nagisa. My eyes
are straying to Kaori and others!
Your heart cannot
keep up with your body.
It's nothing to worry about.
It's like a fever. You'll come out of it.
I read in a book...
...if you suppress your lusty nature,
you'll end up with unnatural desires.
Hey!
Ms. Minami...
You're dripping.
Ms. Minami?
What are you doing? Ms. Minami!
Ms. Minami's memory again?
Is she looking at me?
My smell?
I desire Nagisa.
Your heart cannot
keep up with your body.
...if you suppress your lusty nature,
you'll end up with unnatural desires.
I'm not suppressing. I'm not unnatural.
Then what are you doing?
You imagine your students being
naughty, and you're doing what?
No, no!
What are you doing?
Ms. Minami!
Every heart carries contradictions.
I'm not brave enough
to look inside my true heart.
He debases not just
their bodies, but their hearts too.
Please, no more!
To the bathroom, quick!
You promised to hold
it until Mr. Kato agrees.
I can't possibly.
Don't be so mean.
At this rate, I...
I'll soil myself.
Let me go!
Let's end it, Mr. Kato.
You're a coward, through and through.
Oh my...
The way you're looking
at me, you're turning me on.
Just to clarify, I'm not a coward.
I'm a bastard.
I have customers waiting.
I can't do that.
That's not nice.
What you borrow, you must return.
Just when Ms. Moeko
wants to return it to Ms. Eri.
It was you! Not the students!
What do you think?
Don't come inside, please!
Stop repeating yourself over and over.
I gave you a double helping.
Make sure it doesn't leak out.
Excellent.
It's a rare item, isn't it?
Take it deeper.
The fragrant smell
of Her Ladyship Eri.
Your body will stand in for hers.
How does it feel to have your
insides spoiled for another lady?
Do you like it, Eri?
Are you ready for yours truly?
Forgive me just this once!
A bitch who cannot follow orders...
...deserves to be punished.
Please don't!
It's cold.
No!
You're something else, Ms. Minami.
Ms. Kaori gave up after only one.
You shall be rewarded
with a second one.
No, no more! You can't!
No, Ms. Minazuki!
Please, no more!
I've never tried a double myself.
It'll be fun.
Please! Let me go to the bathroom now!
Only the main guest,
Her Ladyship Eri, can grant you that.
I can't hold it. I'm spilling!
I'm spilling!
You two let go together,
it will smell so clean.
It will just be a bad odor.
That would be just fine for yours truly.
Because...
...shusaku means making bad odors.
It should be fine
for Your Ladyship Eri too.
My room?
It must smell nice.
Ammonia...
Enough!
If you want me...
...why don't you debauch me with
the aesthetics you're so proud of?
What's the matter?
You like this, don't you?
Do anything to my body. I won't give in.
What a misunderstanding.
I just want to release
their Ladyships' dirty desires...
...their female instincts!
I can't hold it.
Everybody has secrets.
But they don't define...
...the whole person.
I can't hold it!
Please, not here!
Not here!
It's coming, coming.
Immoral is the term.
When people step outside
the bounds of morality...
...they enjoy the supreme pleasure.
Then why have morals at all?
So we can devour the pleasure.
The more restrictive the morals,
the greater the pleasure.
It's human nature
to gorge on pleasure.
It is unnatural to resist it.
Don't you agree, Your Ladyship Eri?
You're not listening.
It's all too much
for the innocent lady to watch.
Why not finish with
the high-strung bitch?
Train her, will you, Ms. Minami?
So much humiliation I want to die.
Truly, a bitch's body
is the source of all sins.
How vulgar!
What a lusty body,
always enticing men.
Your very existence is a crime.
I will not tolerate any more humiliation.
Ms. Maejima, don't resist him.
What?
Do you want to be punished?
He'll punish you severely.
Punish me?
Yes, this.
No more enemas! Forgive me!
''forgive me?''
Forgive me, please.
I'll do whatever you say.
Then do it now.
Lusty bitches.
They know how to use their fingers.
Yes, I am. I'm a bitch.
You two make a wonderful duet.
The one who fails to suck
me off will be punished.
Move aside!
My boobs belong to Sir Kato.
Please enjoy them to your heart's
content.
No!
Sir Kato, let me swallow it.
No, let me swallow it.
Does it taste good?
Give it to me too, quick!
It's so good.
Don't pull out yet, please!
Not yet!
Tonight I will rape you
until you can't live without it.
Enough is enough!
Well, well. I see you're awake.
I said do it to me!
Or is my body too skinny for you?
That hurts!
What happened to your
gentlemanly aesthetics?
Raising a hand to a girl.
After all, you're...
You're so stubborn.
Your tour through hell has just begun.