Encode by Jan55 and QC by redrooster for www.world-of-hentai.to
It feels like we're walking in circles.
It wasn't like this before.
Looks like they remodeled it.
I hate the dark!
W... what's this?
Yumiko!?
Misato!?
Sister and Yoshimi!!
Are they dead?
No, they are OK!
Now what!?
Nif!?
I did it!
Cruz?
You are here?
I should start off with a thanks?
Nif, what's all this?
Oh, you brought her here too?
Sheesh, you didn't notice?
What do you mean?
She's Shisui.
To be exact, a copy of Shisui.
So you really didn't notice.
I noticed right away.
I thought we can change bodies only once?
Yes, only once, but not quite.
Besides, didn't she feel...unnatural?
Now that you mention it...
I, I am...
Welcome back, Cruz.
Back in the jar again...?
Yes, she is me.
That's why I was able to find you easily.
You were always within my reach.
I... I don't know anything.
Mihono!
You!
Just as I thought, but what now?
Let's see.
Well, you did have a long journey, so how about
some fun?
I'll get the rest of the key out of you, Cruz.
I'm sure they are happy to see you again.
You may have thought it was a
good idea, but it was just too simple.
You really thought I wouldn't be able
to find it if you hid it inside their bodies?
Well, to be honest, I did panic a bit.
Because of it, I had to create this room.
It's not easy to create by using earth's technology.
E...everyone, wake up! Snap out of it!
Stop, let go!!
Don't...
Don't move around.
Nif, who's side are you on!?
If you fight it, they might just chop it right off.
Shit, now that you mention it...
So, how is that thing?
That thing?
Oh, that.
I would say 98%.
It can be ready at any time.
Amazing...
Anyway, for now, let her do what
she wants and wait for the chance.
Besides, you should enjoy this situation you're in.
Damn, you're straight to the point which makes you boring!
Then, you better let it all out.
C...cumming...
Cumming!
Me too!!
Looks like there's still plenty left.
Get every single drop out.
Get all of it.
Go on.
Continuing on the retrieval process.
We've entered final stage.
We can't wait, open him up if you have to.
I have already got part of it, more will follow.
Then bring those over now.
Roger.
I'll be back soon.
Cruz, now is your chance
You say that, but...
If Shisui can control these girls
She could do it too.
That's it!
Mihono, can you hear me!?
Stop this party now!
I...  I can't do that.
Just pray strongly with your heart!
You can do it, I beg you!
You're not a copy of Shisui!
You are yourself!
Remember travelling all over, well that was you!
Mihono, only you can stop this!
Almost....we can go home.
A world where law and unity is the only existence.
I may be...afraid of what's to come.
Why?
Nothing...
How's the ship?
It's ready.
Soon as it starts, we'll escape.
Unlock code entered.
Boot up sequence initiated.
How far can we go with the given codes?
The procedures can be taken to the final stage.
However, it would need to be done manually.
Come save us from this dreaded world!
Purify this world!
Good job...
Why did you put them to sleep?
What else is there to do, how
am I going to explain it to them?
Nif, please transfer them to safety.
Alright, I'll take them back to their places.
Mihono...what about you?
I'm going to stop them!
Hey, if you don't hurry, I'll leave you behind!
Wait up!!
Hurry!
Ramon's trying to explode it in this state!
This is all your fault, Shisui!
It's because you didn't finish him!
Can it be done?
Yes, this is what we waited for.
Initiation switch...
W... wait, if you're going to do
this, let me leave this planet first.
Count down.
You're all crazy!
T... that's it, Vote...lets vote again!
Lets end this!
It's Cruz...
Ramon, I know you realize...
...that this is not a big deal anymore!
We changed since we came here.
Hate, Anger, Jealousy...we're no
different than the beings of this planet!
We're part of it now!
We are now Earthlings!
Final safety lock, disarm.
What's wrong with you now!?
It's also part of life!
More reasons why this star is dangerous!
I'll kill you with my own hands.
You and me had the same answer.
Different aspects, however.
I realized when people started
doing things on their own!
That's how we got plagued by this star.
You can't do anything about it...
It's the end.
I won't let anyone kill Cruz!
Shi...Shisui!
Shisui!
Shisui....
Cr...Cruz....
S... start the explosion!
Final command accepted.
180 seconds left until execution.
It's the end now...
No, it won't be a black hole
until it reaches max capacity!
We'll move it to the other side before it starts!
It will eat itself up if we do!
Impossible, no matter where we
move it, it'll head back to the center!
It's worth a try, help out!
....it shrunk?
It's compressing the energy,
we don't have much time!
Cr... Cruz...
Where's the moon?
Hey, where is it!?
Don't shout, I'm looking!
This might....just...work....
If I can use the....moons gravity....to move it......
Did you hear!?
I'm trying, why don't you try!?
Give me the controls!
30 seconds until execution.
Mihono...
I'm sorry...but one day you'll....understand.
You...will....
10 seconds until execution.
5....4....3....
Enter data!
2....1....
It's OK, it will be OK.
We're going home.
Although only two are left.
You're taking Shisui back too?
It's the best for her.
I see...you're right...
Lets see...
What are you going to do?
Lets start off by eating a ramen.
I know a place.
OK.