Don't pull on it...
Ouch!
P-Please stop...
N-No...
No...
Why did you let me into your room?
Weren't you hoping for this to happen?
It's because you had those photos...
Those photos?
Are you talking about these?
N-No...
Stop...
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Wife Swap Diary
Episode 1
Please stop...
...I beg you.
I'll do anything...
My fingers are covered in your flowing love
juice.
This time, suck my penis instead of my fingers.
I-I can't...
You said you'll do anything.
B-But...this...
Kanako, it seems to me you are really looking
forward to this...
That's right...
...looking forward for me to pound you...
That's not true!
There is no way!
You are letting out a abundance of fluid from
the Bartholin's gland.
Oh I made a mistake.
In recent studies they found out it's
not just fluid from the Bartholin's gland.
Seems like you want to say I'm filthy but...
...as we can see, you're wet so you aren't you
filthy too?
Weak, weak...
Your resistance is weak!
Why does your tongue wrap itself around me?
I wonder what Koichi would think if he saw this.
Kanako...
You are being teased by Kimihiko and you're
breathing hard...
It's so dirty, it seems like you're not yourself...
You're so cute Kanako...
Help me...
Koichi...
Koichi, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
You're saying that but your vaginal walls are
tightening!
There's no way!
But your body is agreeing with my words!
Kanako...
P-Please take it out...
Kanako, you just need to get off me, right?
Oh what have I done?
I raped my friend Koichi's wife...
I must have been moved by something evil!
If you...stop now...
Kanako, please stop thrusting your hips on top
of me...
If you don't move soon I'll go to hell for
adultery!
Seems like I'm possessed by something evil...
...as well, so I have to finish quickly...
Your dick is getting bigger.
No no no!
You can't come inside!
I'm sorry...Koichi...
Kanako...
You are beautiful...
You and I both...
...are possessed by something evil...
And you mean me, too....
Hey Koichi, I'm thinking of you as a close friend.
Also I believe our connection is deeper than
family in a way...
That may be true.
I'm trusting you and opening up about
something.
What is it?
What do you think of my wife, Sachie?
How...
Well...
I don't know if I should be saying this in front of
you, but...
...she is a beautiful person...
It's not just that.
If Kanako is the sun then she's the moon...
It's not in a bad way, she just has this ambience
that makes men go crazy...
What are you making me say?
It's embarrassing to rate other people's wives.
It's not that I'm fine with doing it to Kanako
either, but...
Yeah...
She's...
Sachie is a woman with something that makes
all the guys have a hard on...
A couple of guys who was said that, actually...
...no, I'm sure there is a chance.
Kimihiko, aren't you a little drunk?
I'm not drunk at all.
I can't get drunk with this amount of alcohol.
No, the only thing that could make me drunk is
sexual pleasure....
Koichi!
Y-Yes?
You're always thinking you want to have sex
with Sachie...
Isn't that right?
Gosh, both of you are drinking beer already.
Why don't you go swimming?
Um...Kanako...
...why don't we rest for a little too?
Ummm...
If you want, I'll go grab something to drink.
Then I'll go too.
That's impossible.
Are you sure?
Koichi, I know you were imagining Sachie's
body weren't you?
I'll make your wish come true.
Kimihiko, please calm down.
What has happened to you?
Koichi, I haven't had sex with Sachie for the
past couple of years.
Not just that.
It's not that I don't desire my wife...
Also, I've found out it's the same for you.
Yes, I have became independent from Kanako
sexually...
So in my thoughts, you have sex with Sachie...
...and in exchange, I have sex with Kanako.
B-But...
But?
Do you think our wives would agree?
Agree?
What are you saying, we're not going to
convince them.
We are going to handle this differently...
We are in need something to energize us.
And this is for them, too.
You don't need to use any kind of strategy with
her.
You just need to tell her you want her body.
Then her fire will light...
She's that type of woman.
I can't think of anything for Kanako...
Does Kanako love you?
She...
...definitely does.
Then...
...I'll rape her.
Don't worry.
If Kanako loves you then she will not tell anyone
she was forced.
B-But...
But your thing is hard now because you
imagined Kanako being raped.
A toast to our ''swap'' being successful!
Swap
I'm sorry for this...
...Kimihiko was the one that invited you...
Don't worry about it.
We are both busy so...
Oh, please wait a second.
missed call
Kimihiko
When I ring your cell phone once, start.
I understand...
No...okay.
I'm sorry, he's not going to be able to come
back tonight...
So meaning if anything happens, Kimihiko isn't
going to know about it.
Koichi, flirting is...
Please stop.
Stop...
Flirting?
I'm serious.
I'm going to violate you now.
Violate...me...?
You have a young, cute wife named Kanako.
But the person who's in front of me right now is
you.
You shouldn't be joking about such a thing.
No...
We are just seeing the same dream.
Dream?
Yes!
A dream that will become just a disappearing
fog...
A dream you'll wake up from...
Stop with the hand jerking now and do it with
your...
...breasts please?
Hey Sachie, aren't you giving too much extra
service?
I've never...had Kanako...
...do things like this.
Is that...why it's...me?
Kanako doesn't have an interest in sex...
...more so...
...not much.
It's like she's still a green fruit.
That's why my eyes always went to your body...
Koichi's penis is stimulating my breasts...
Even though it's a dream it's so exciting...
I-I'm coming!
It has more body than Kimihiko's so it's sticking
to my throat...
But if I spill it the floor will get dirty...
Sachie, what woman you are, opening your
body up that easily!
Don't move yet.
Don't say that.
You want to move, huh?
Sachie, you are so dirty.
This is a dream.
It's a dream so I, I...
If it's a dream you don't have to be
embarrassed.
You should ignore what I say and you should
just move.
I can't.
Koichi your dick is different from Kimihiko's...
It's new so my hips are thrusting!
It's new sex so I have to move my butt!
Ah, no you can't mark me!
The dream won't end...
dirty mine with yours, Koichi.
Please rape me.
Please give me the fantasy ofviolation!
I'm a pervert!
I'm a pervert that enjoys being violated in my
vagina...
...so Koicihi, more...
More!
Please pound me harder!
That's right.
You're Kimihiko's wife...
...but you've accepted my dick so I need to give
you dick torture!
Y-Yes!
I'm going to die with your dick torture!
Y-Yes, I'm a pervert who loves dirty dicks, so it
feels good to have my...
...reproductive organ pounded!
It's too good!
Here I come.
Today is your safe day right?
Y-Yes...
It's safe, easy...
...safe fertilization day.
Come inside me!
I...!
I'll have all the semen poured inside me, I'll
come and become a animal!
This is great Koichi!
It's more than I thought!
Even with that easy big breasted Sachie!
More!
Come inside me!
I can't...
If I keep this up, I won't be able to interact with
normal society.
Trying to energize myself like this is backwards.
If you don't want it, please do something about
it.
Then I will...stop.
That's a unfair way to say it...
But I felt that our feelings connected in that
moment, Sachie.
Is it my misconception?
Or is it my lonely perceived notion?
I don't know what you are talking about...
Oh that's right.
Because it was a ''dream.''
T-That's right, this is a ''dream.''
A dream is something you see at night...
But...
...there also is a thing called daydreaming.
Sachie!
It's the same dream I saw that time.
The feeling is exactly the same!
All the way in the back it's tingling.
Why am I seeing the same dream again?
That's because you want it.
Y-Yes, I do want it.
Why...
Why?
That's my question...
It's obvious you want it but...
...somehow you are trying to restrain yourself.
I'm scared.
I'm being pounded by you and it's coming in
WaVeS.
I'm scared!
I'm scared I'm going to be turned on more than
with Kimihiko...
Don't worry.
Weren't you that type of person from the
beginning, Sachie?
You're just going to go back to how you were
before you met Kimihiko.
Why do you...
I know because I was always watching you.
Yes, so you're going to be late again tonight...
It's fine because you are working hard...
Please...stop...
This...is...horrible...
Kimihiko...is going to find out...
Oh I'm sorry.
I wasn't listening...
N-No, I just felt a little dizzy...
Ah...yes...
Bye.
Mean...
You're so mean...
What a sneaky guy....
I'm having such a horrible thing done...
...but he's doing that so...
I'm really...
...really turned on!
No...
You can't...
I'm going to come...
I'm going to come with a dick other than
Kimihiko's dick!
Kimihiko!
Kimihiko was saying he's going to rape her or
whatever...
But it seems like he hasn't done anything yet.
...but I've done it, I've done it with Sachie.
I...I beg you.
I'll do anything...