Hey, Aiko, did you see how that thing is?
For sure! I have a little brother after all.
Wow, is it true that it becomes really hard?
That's right, and it's really
amazing when it moves!
Incredible! If only I had a little brother too.
Finished...
Hey, Yuka, are you leaving?
Of course. If I don't hurry, the class will start.
Wait a bit more.
What? Stop it.
It hurts...
No! Stop! What are you doing?
1... 2!
No...
No way... please...
Lolicon Angel Part 1:
Watashi-tachi Shoujo Tanteidan
(Our Girls Detective Team)
Lolicon Angel Part 1:
Watashi-tachi Shoujo Tanteidan
(Our Girls Detective Team)
Who will check whom?
Draw it! Draw it!
The incident happened after school today.
Excluding the ones present at
the time of Physical Education...
The suspects are Mari-chan,
Akihiko-kun and Grandpa Youmai.
Let's decide by draw who will investigate whom.
Science Lab
Are you saying that I stole money?
That's not what I said.
I'm just asking because you were the only
one to study during Physical Education.
Then you accuse someone without knowing?
You shouldn't do that!
What a noise! Can't you make a bit of silence?
Teacher!
What's happening, Mari-chan?
Help me, Aiko is bothering me!
I did nothing, and she called me a thief!
Alright, I understand.
Hum, I...
You! Mari is an honest girl.
To accuse others of theft is bad.
This child will receive from God
the punishment she deserves.
Stay in front of the table with both hands on it.
Yes...
No!!!
Now, you have to prepare for this.
I will show you!
Be prepared for it.
How is it? Makes you think
a little about what you did?
I will climax soon.
Teacher, stop with these perverted things!
W-what? You call this "perverted"?
You don't even know what "perverted" is.
Good, let me give you a lesson now.
Mari-chan, you will be my assistant.
Yes, professor!
Be a good experimentalist.
Why are you doing this to me?
We'll start the "perverted" experiments now.
Yes, professor!
First, I'll see how much voltage she can withstand.
Professor? I think this is a good value.
Increase a bit more.
Stop... no...
Stop... I did nothing... please...
Hey, hey, don't make it violent,
you want to flood the classroom?
Teacher? Should I increase the voltage again?
No, this is enough.
Let's move to the next experiment.
Can we continue with something like this?
Hmm, a test tube... Well, why not. We have
to do a series of experiments anyway.
What?
What are you doing?
What is this strange feeling?
Professor? We also have this one.
Let's try, give it to me.
Stop, not with this...
Don't use it, I beg you!
Chilly...
No...!
That hurts.
I have such a strange feeling...
Somebody help me, I'm gonna die!
How cute.
Professor, I love you.
Feels good, I can't stand it anymore...
Thief!!! Thief!!!
Wait!!!
Why am I a thief?
Don't play innocent! What were you doing at
my desk at the time of Physical Education?
This is a misunderstanding!
You still pretend to be innocent?
Oh my, it will never stop.
No way! This is a love letter?
No way!
No way you need all these "no way".
My bad, it sucks being called a thief.
You don't have to laugh.
It's just that...
Huh? What?
You know...
I really like you, Akihiko-kun.
Really?
Akihiko-kun...
Ah, you have been hurt!
Right, I did not even notice.
If you got a wound, let me lick it to heal.
You don't need to, Yuka-chan.
Oh, there's something moving here!
It must be hurt... poor you...
Hey! It's not what you're thinking!
Stop it, patients must receive care!
Oh oh, let me handle it.
Wow, what a problem!
Look! It left a sticky thing!
Yuka-chan...
This is serious, it's still hard!
Hey, don't you know Yuka-chan?
The thing that you are licking...
Yuka-chan's place...
Put it in there to have a good feeling.
Didn't know that.
Want to try?
Yes.
Enough already.
Here I come.
What a strange feeling.
It's because you have to take off your panties.
Alright...
So, let's go.
No, it entered!
It went inside...
Yuka-chan, I feel so good.
Me too, it's the first time I feel this way.
Ueda Apples
Looks like I have found another kind of criminal.
Then, Akihiko-kun should have done it after all.
You saw it...
My secret...
Hum, I...
Kaori... you are Kaori?
No, I am not...
I knew you were alive! Thank God, thank God!
No, you are mistaking me.
No no, don't lie to me!
You wanted bloomers so much
but I never bought any.
I know that you felt rancor because of that.
Ah, you know...
Until now, your daddy was stealing bloomers
every day, hoping that you would wear them.
That's why...
I see. He confused me with
his deceased daughter.
It would be awful from me if I won't play her...
Father, now I remember.
Kaori was looking forward
to put these bloomers on.
Really? You remembered now?
Kaori, you have to remove
everything to put bloomers on.
Take off your panties.
Hey? But...
Ah, that's right.
This is the first time I'm putting them on.
I didn't know that, sorry.
How is it, dad? Did I do well?
You're as beautiful as your late mother!
Come closer so I can see your face better!
Such a long time since we were separated.
Your breasts became bigger, let me see better.
Both nipples are equal to
those of your late mother!
Father... feels good...
Really? Are you pleased? Listen, Kaori.
I will make the merry-go-round
carousel that you liked so much.
Goody goody, I'll take off your bloomers.
How cute!
Father, what are you doing?
Doing what? I'm building the
central part of the carousel.
Without this it will not turn.
Oh, right. Sorry to forget this.
It's ready, come over here!
Alright, do we start?
Everything ok? I will turn now.
It's the merry-go-round carousel!
More, more, faster!
Feel it! Feel it!
Kaori, Kaori!
You had fun, right?
Yes, a lot! But it seems that I became dizzy.
I got tired because you were quite heavy.
But there's one thing you're still forgetting.
That is?
You are not yet through with this pole.
Oh, yeah, but how do I come to the end?
Put all your love in it until "water" comes out.
Like this, father?
This is it, Kaori! So delicious!
Father, it's not out yet?
Make it a bit more.
It's not out yet...
I cannot hold any longer,
the water is about to come.
Ok, I have to go faster.
Huh? What are you saying?
Liar!
It's the truth, look what I found.
I didn't notice, but the
money was in my wallet.
Well, well...
The last one is the priest's wife!