Senpai's breath is like reachin' deep inside my pussy!
Rubbin' it up my ass! Feels good!
It's still puny...
Grow bigger! Grow bigger!
Grow bigger!
Senpai! Don't grab my ass that tightly!
Nooo!!
Noo!
Don't caress it so much!
I'll get hornier!
Yummy!
It's so big now...
This yummy dick's so cute...
Ya're rockin' hard now...
Ya must be feelin' real good, huh?
Yummy juices are startin' to come out, Senpai...
Noo!!
Senpai's mouth is eatin' my pussy!
Senpai, go for it!
Get harder!
Keep suckin' it!
Fu.. taba...
Don't!!
I'll lose it!!
Amazing!
Your dick's so yummy!
Senpai... Ya're so yummy early in the morning!
My pussy feels so fucked up!
Your dick's so fuckin' hard too!
Hold on!
To be continue next time, okay?
Oh, Sis!
Senpai's awake now!
Breakfast is ready.
Senpai, you're gonna be late!
Ya can't hold it anymore either, right, Senpai?
A lotta 'em are comin' out...
Futaba's pussy can't hold it anymore too...
She was rubbin' her pussy with her ballpen all day during class...
Futaba-chan, we shouldn't be doing this here...
Class is gonna start soon...
And besides...
Jeez...
Your dick's twitchin' so much,
and I know you want me bad.
Oh, no...
My pussy's kinda stuck on the head part!
I want it more!
Futaba-chan!
I'm serious...
Ya still got the balls to act like a wuss 'round me?!
I'm the one raping you again!
Senpai...
It's Futaba's pussy that's eatin' Senpai's dick!
Senpai's dick is so big, I think it's gonna explode soon!
Futaba-chan! We shouldn't!
My womb is Senpai's semen's disposal, you know.
My wet pussy feels good, right?
Ain't ya a man enough to say no to that?
I know my boobs ain't as big as Sis's, but they're still good, ya know.
If you don't cum inside me, I'll...
Senpai! Slow down!
It's hittin' my G-spot!
No!
It feels so good!
Senpai's dick is fuckin' my pussy like there's no tomorrow!
I want ya to fuck me more!
No!!
People might see us from below, you know!
My boobs are hittin' against the railings!
It's fuckin' cold!
Senpai! More!
No!
That's the spot!!
I want Senpai to shoot every drop of your fuckin' semen inside my pussy!
Fuck, yes!
Senpai! That's fuckin' good!
Fuck me harder!!
It's fuckin' way beyond the G-spot!
Your dick's too fuckin' hard!
So, let it out already!
That's it!
Senpai's dick is still squirtin' a lotta semen out...
Is this...
Y-You know, Futaba-chan...
How should I say this...
This kind of thing...
We shoudn't...
This kinda thing?
Futaba-chan... I'm sorry...
We can't go on like this...
I can't be your bitch anymore...
God damn it, Senpai...
Didn't we go over this already?
Till Sis recovers her memories back...
Besides, I'm not some dirty hoe...
Not Futaba...
Later, Senpai!
I'll grab some condoms on the way home.
Go ahead home!
For show, Sis's doin' it by herself at home again.
This is bad...
Am I getting delusional?
Ushio-kun, I came...
Miharu?!
H-How's your body doin?!
U-Um, it's... kind of okay...
O-Oh, noo...
It's... okay now...
Thank God, you had some spare clothes.
Sorry 'bout that, Miharu...
Some asshole forgot to put that bucket away.
Nah, it's fine...
It's all good...
This shit's never gonna end, right? That bitch!
It's stupid training every day! It's bullshit!
That was a close call...
You know, Miharu, you didn't have to hide with me...
Yeah...
I... guess you're right...
But, this might...
U-Ushio-kun?
It's hard!
Don't...
D-Don't, Ushio-kun...
Not here...
Don't worry...
Just keep your voice down...
I told you to stop...
No! Ushio-kun's... is so big...
No way! No! That's my butt!
If he's gonna put it there, I'll...
Don't! Ushio-kun!
No!!
Huh? What's that?
Did ya say somethin'?
Huh? No...
I didn't say shit...
Really?
A whatever! Let's roll!
Yo! Wait up!
Bitch, you're slow...
U-Ushio-kun! That's... That's my...
Miharu, I'm gonna put it in now...
What?!
T-There...
In my butt?
Do you prefer the other hole?
Huh? N-No...
I... I don't want it inside my butt...
It'll be fine.
No! It's too rough!
Ushio, don't!
M-My pussy's filled...
By Ushio-kun's dick!
Noo! U-Ushio-kun, that's...
My butt!
Noo!
Don't!
I'm starting to feel weird!
U-shi-o-kun...
Hey, this is weird!
I-diot...
No, not like this!
Ushio-kun!
Don't! Don't! Not like this!!
Ushio-kun, I wanna see your face...
I feel... it's coming really deep!
Noo!
Ushio-kun! I can't... take it anymore!
No more!
I will...
W-Will it... really fit?
Don't worry.
I always watch anal sex porn.
I don't like this...
This is weird...
I-Is it all the way in already?
No...
I-It's only halfway in!
It's in now!
T-This feels really weird...
I-It'll soon... feel good...
Really?
It will, it will.
N-No!
Wait!
T-This... doesn't feel right...
Don't!
My butthole's gonna go inside out!
Getting used to it already?
That's not true...
How can I get use to this kind of pose?
It feels so weird!
Ushio-kun's... reaching my stomach!
Noooo!!
Ushio-kun, it's soo weird!
Even my butt... It's... It's...
No more!
It's weird!
I feel... really weird!!
Ushio-kun!
My butt!!
My... butt's cumming!!
No way!
My... stomach... is full of semen...
Oh, no...
My butt...
I...
H-Huh? Miharu, is that...
Oh, this?
It was inside the pocket of my school uniform...
It kind of bugged me, so I...
I'll put it on someday.
If I wear it now, would it look like I'm already hitched?
You're too wishy-washy sometimes...
Is this gonna my engagement ring or some fashion ring?
It'll be up to ya by the time we graduate!
C'mon, Sis!
Hurry up and take a bath!
Be sure to put your uniform
next to the washing machine, okay?
Now that Sis out of the picture takin' a bath...
Should I let Senpai lick my feet squeaky clean?
Huh? Senpai?
Ya prefer ero-manga?
Fu-Futaba-chan?!
Since Sis's in the bath, Senpai...
I'll make ya cum...
Sorry...
Like what I said this afternoon,
we shouldn't be doing it anymore...
Right, Futaba-chan?
Quit... Quit jokin', Senpai...
What's up with the drama?
I had enough...
Huh?
I don't want to make Miharu depressed again...
Even for you, Futaba-chan...
It'll only make things harder for you...
W-What are ya gettin' at?
Ain't ya a virgin like a few days back?
And now... Ya're schoolin' me?
Seriously...
I'm being unfaithful...
I'm two-timing the both of you...
Say whatever you wanna say...
I'm really sorry, Futaba-chan...
Senpai...
Ya meanie!
Wha-?
Futaba..
Pervert!
Freak!
Lecher!
PERVERT!
UGLY!
PIPSQUEAK!
PERVERT!
LOSER!
SQUATTER!
PERVERT!!
NYMPHOMANIAC!!
VIRGIN!!
PERVERT!
NEEDLE DICK!
PERVERT!!
UNCIRCUMSIZED!!
PERVERT!!!
MAN WHORE!!
PERVERT!
WORTHLESS SCUM!
PERVERT!!
VIRGIN!!
PERVERT!!!
FAILED SOCIAL CLIMBER!
PERVERT!!!!
PERVERT!!!!!
Wow, is that all you can say?
Senpai, ya're a WORTHLESS DICK!!
Am I really a worthless dick?
Ushio-kun...
Miharu?
This is...
The ring that Miharu begged me to get her...
She said I was too wishy-washy...
That's why I've decided...
May I?
Sure...
That's weird...
Ow-Ouch!
Damn!
It's in...
Miharu, now we're...
No...
I said that...
IT HURTS!!
Fuck!
It hurts, but you still forced it in!
You, animal!!
Miharu, you're...
Jeez, what's up with you?!
Now, what?
Senpai, ya ANIMAL!
PREMATURE EJACULATOR!!
UNLESS 2-INCH DICK!!!
:P
Ushio...
You better explain this shit...
What? Amnesia?
How did I... get it?
It was when you fell and hit your head.
I fell? Me? How?
You tripped...
That's bullshit!
No way that could've happen...
I-It's no bullshit...
No wonder...
It doesn't feel like I've missed your dick, even though I forgot everything...
Don't use that as a reference!
Nevertheless, you were makin' out with Futaba too!
Yes!
Ushio, your dick's so good!
By the way...
How many times did this dick
go inside Futaba since I had Amnesia?
Ow, ow!
That hurts, Miharu! It hurts!
Be a man and take the pain!
Jeez, doin' my little sister behind my back...
It's not my fault!
Blame it on your slutty sister.
She's not the kinda girl who'll give in that easily, ya know...
Futaba! How fuckin' long are you gonna hide there for?
What?
Didn't Futaba-chan just leave a while ago?
Futaba-chan?!
Congratz, ya found me...
Fuck after you've recovered...
So much for the recovery party...
L-Look who's talking!
You're such a slut!
Hmph!
Ya talk a lotta shit for a slutty hoe yaself.
Anyway, mind if I give him a go too?
You ain't touchin' my wallet!
Ern... I mean, my boyfriend!
Futaba-chan's a crazy bitch too?
Does it run in your family or something?
W-Why don't you just shut up and just keep humpin'!
This dick... only belongs... to me, bitch!
Well, it ain't gonna be yours alone for long.
Yes!
No!
Amazing!
Ushio, your dick is soo goo-ood!
Nooo!
Senpai's pokin' his nose up my pussy!
That's it, Ushio!
Fuck my pussy up with your giant dick!
Sis!
Ya should know it was me, Futaba...
who trained this dick well, ya know?
W-What stupidity are ya talkin' about this time?
No! I'm about to cum from this!
Ushio's dick is makin' me cum again!
Futaba too!
I'm gonna cum from Senpai lickin' my pussy!
Suck 'em good!
N-No!
I'm...!
Let's cum!
Sis!
Futaba's cummin' too!
Noo!
It's way too good!
No, I'm cumming!
I'm cummin'! I'm cummin'!
Noooo!!
This dick, I love it!!
I cumming!!
I cummin'!!
C'mon, Futaba!
Hurry up, bitch!
Jeez, fuck you, Sis...
Futaba wants to drink the first semen of the day.
What the fuck are ya talkin' about? Stupid bitch...
Who gives a shit!
I'll just rape Senpai again at school!
If you keep talkin' shit like that,
I'll have JPz Records & Masurenai gang rape you.
Sorry for the wait!