Nice to meet you. I'm Mirano.
We finally can be together openly.
Starting from now on, I'm looking forward to seeing you every month.
I'm leaving you in my care.
Recently, my friend, Nana-san has become very pretty.
She and her husband are close and happily married.
At least, that's what I thought.
But she seems to be having an affair with another man...
What's more, the man is her beloved husband's friend...
You see... They did something they shouldn't have done...
B-But she said she wasn't fooling around...
She was hugged by that person forcefully...
And then... s-she couldn't resist his overwhelming dick...
I asked her to share the feelings that she felt...
Then she said, "Ah, it's very awesome..."
I... had to bear the loneliness by myself...
My husband always works late...
So, in order to fill the loneliness, I...
I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing to go on.
B-But...
But...
Please let Mirano cum!
Mornin!
Jeez...
When someone says "Mornin!" to you, you should say "Good Morning!" back.
What are you doing, Fubuki?
Sorry, Shinichi!
I couldn't avoid Momose-san's request.
Although I didn't have to ask around, I already knew where you were at.
How many years do you think I've known you?
Although today's a holiday, don't just slack off.
At least, do some exercise.
It feels good to be under the sun.
The same usual morning
Jeez...
What an emotionless face...
That sullen attitude is starting to piss me off!
Now that I mention it...
Isn't it normal for me to wear partially exposed panties like that?!
I just got a glimpse of it.
My bad...
But I guess it was only me who got lucky...
I know he noticed it... for sure...
Idiot! Moron!
At least... give me a little bit of a chance...
A normal scenario
What an enviable guy you are...
You got the "Madonna" of Sakuragaoka Academy all to yourself.
She's only like an older sister to me.
Dumbass!
She knocked down each and every numskull who confessed to her like a catapult.
Go for her, if you want.
No one's allowed to peep, you two pervs!
All these seem to be a distant past
Shinichi...
You still dunno how popular I am with the girls, right?
I'm quite notorious when it comes to quickly getting girls to bed, you know.
Just leave her to me then.
Yeah, yeah...
~ Little birds in the darkness ~
Brought U By JPz Records & Masurenai
More... caress me more...
It's coz... I... belong to you...
That's why, caress me more...
I wanna make you feel good as well...
Don't! No... That place is embarrassing...
Perv!
Fubuki, aren't you quite a pervert yourself?
It's so broad...
It can do anything...
Just by looking at it makes me horny...
I want it...
Hurry up and become one with you...
If it hurts, we could stop, Fubuki.
I don't wanna!
That's coz I'm so happy.
Although it hurts, it's the pain of becoming one with you.
I wanna feel you more and more!
You're inside of me!
It's reaching in... inside of me...
It feels so good!
Again?!
So good! So good!!
Go ahead! Do whatever you want with my body!
More! More, damn it!! Cum inside of me!!
I know... I know you wanna!!
It's getting hotter! It's getting bigger! It's gotta be...
You're cumming, right?!
It's okay! It's okay to cum deep inside anytime!!
I want you to fill me with a lot of it!!
Umm...
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
Was it just a dream?
Um... I'm Senju.
I'm Senju Mizuha.
I'm grateful that you caught me from being injured...
But...
Oh... S-Sorry...
Kawahara-san, if you weren't here for me, I might have fallen down the stairs.
I would have been...
You've saved me once again...
I guess, you have already forgotten, have you?
I was a little shocked.
You're planning to let Senju-san, who's like a princess, wash your dirty clothes?
To let the only daughter of the Senju Zaibatsu
become a cheerleader and wear skirts that expose her panties, you think I'd allow that?!
Umm... Well, I...
H-Hey!
Wait!
If there's something in your mind, don't hesitate to speak up.
Y-Yes...
If you wanna become more self-reliable, why not participate in a sports club?
But don't pick volleyball!
Because there's a devil inside.
I still remember it like it was yesterday.
Senpai 「先輩」 is how a lowerclassmen address his or her upperclassmen.
It's Senpai's words that gave me a lot of courage back then.
The reason why I'm wearing this uniform till today is because of you, Senpai.
I got a little too emotional.
I apologize.
It's pointless to relive thoughts at a time like this, right?
Shinichi?
Shinichi, is that you?
Takaaki!
Shinichi!
Fubuki...
Shinichi...
Let's make this our base.
It looks sturdy, has a lotta space and is easy to rendezvous.
Listen. Remember to groups in pairs, okay?
Before we met up with you two, we went through several places, and...
That's the exit that leads outside...
I've always been in love with you...
A brief moment of serenity
Fu-Fubuki...
Don't say that as if our lives are about to end.
I don't wanna have any regrets...
If we're gonna die, I wanna die with you in my arms.
It's full of sweat and stench... Since it's yours, you should be able to stand it, right?
I'll make you forget about it...
The only thing you'll feel in the inside is my dick.
It's moving...
His... is moving and reaching deep inside me.
The pain I had earlier was just like a lie.
Senpai! Senpai! Senpai!
I want to forget!
Please make me forget about it!
Jam it deep inside of me!
It's all the way in! It's coming! It's coming!!
My womb can feel your...!
What is it that you feel?
What's coming all the way in?
Your... It's your...!
If you wanna forget, you should follow what I say.
If you do so, you'll be able to forget about it.
It's resounding... the voice of a strong man...
My womb... can feel it your...!
Your dick! Your dick is touching my womb!
I'm going crazy! I'm going out of my mind!!
Senpai...
Sen…pai…
Oh, this?
It's what I left in the club room.
What's in it?
I-It doesn't matter!
Anyway, it's just a necessity for girls...
Huh? The two of them aren't here.
Takaaki! Senju-san!
Sorry, I overslept...
The princess is still sleeping.
It seems like she isn't feeling well.
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine... Sorry to have made you worry.
I was a little anemic, but I'm okay now.
It's pretty!
It's cute and warm.
See? Isn't it a necessity?
Well, I'll leave the rest to you, Takaaki-kun.
Please don't threat...
I, Tsumura Takaaki, promise to serve full-heartedly as a knight.
Let's hope that the knight won't turn into a wolf.
Trust him. He's my bestfriend after all.
Sure.
Sorry, Takaaki...
I'll rest first.
Go ahead.
Shinichi!
My bad...
I accidentally fell asleep...
Let's split up and look for her.
Senju-san!
If you're there, please respond!
The two disappeared? What do you mean?
Sorry... Maybe "disappeared" is not the right word it.
When he and Momose-san went out, he confessed to her.
After they rendezvoused, Shinichi had...
No way! That's impossible!
No way...
Even I don't wanna believe it myself.
Just then, he took the chance when she went to the toilet.
Although I've already found Senju-san...
This time, he and Fubuki disappeared.
I said, don't, Takaaki-kun...
Stop... Doing something like that at a time like thi...
Stop... I...
I won't let you say a word after this...
I'm happy...
...that you responded to my kiss.
That's not true...
It's coz you inserted your tongue inside my mouth so forcefully...
But you accepted it...
By wrapping around back with your tongue...
How cruel of you now to make that as an excuse.
Do you hate me?
Asking a question like that...
You're the one who's being cruel.
No!
Don't...
Touch me there!
No...
It's starting to get stiff down here, Momose-san.
Don't... We really shouldn't do this... Let me go...
Takaaki-kun...
No, no... His kiss is sucking up my saliva...
My saliva... is being sucked...
Although I don't want this...
My tongue is being tangled up...
Saliva is leaking out of my mouth...
What's this? It's amazing...
I feel... so numb...
This time, saliva is flowing into my mouth...
It's roughly flowing into my mouth...
Shinichi's kiss...
It's completely different from this...
No... No!
By kissing... you seem to be getting horny, right?
Gotta question, did you kiss Shinichi?
I wasn't getting horny!
Compared to the first time, you've gotten good at it.
The first time?
Fubuki and Takaaki?
I'm begging you... Don't say such a thing...
But don't forget...
The person who taught Momose-san the true pleasure of kissing... was me...
More! Do it more!
Momose-san, stick your ass out more!
No!
I can feel... Takaaki-kun's getting turned on... It's getting harder...
I'm already hard down there. Can you feel it?
N-No...
It feels... uncomfortable...
P-Please... don't caress me like that...
D-Don't grope my breasts!
I already knew...
You were moaning like this a while ago.
A while ago...what?
Were Fubuki and Takaaki always doing this kinda thing?
I'm happy...
It's that time, right? That guy on the rooftop...
Don't look at it!
Was it coz the stripped panties were tainted by me?
You're well-prepared...
But this one will once again be tainted by me.
T-That's why I told you not to grope my breasts!
No! You're groping it too hard!!
I can feel it!
It's hot! No!
Shove it right between your thighs.
Momose-san, I'll make you hornier...
N-No...
Coz I can't have promiscuous relationships with another guy.
No...
Don't squeeze them too hard!
Takaaki-kun's so big... It's like it's gonna burst...
If the person Momose-san is now is seen by that guy...
No... N-Noo...
Don't mention that guy right now...
Oh... Coz right now, you belong to me...
To think it could be this big... It's so hot!
Takaaki-kun's... is soo hot!
You wanna put it in?
Yeah...
It's okay to put it in...
Damn!
Did she lie to me?
That confession too...
Fubuki, that bitch... was with Takaaki at the very beginning...
Anger makes people stray far away from the truth
You wanna put it in?
Don't... That you absolutely can't do...
I... I'm... a virgin...
Are you still thinking about that guy?
Please... don't bully me anymore...
Sorry! I got no plans of making you cry.
But could you at least do it with your mouth?
It's okay, right, Momose-san?
Um, sure...
It's okay to do that...
Only if you let me go after doing that...
Takaaki-kun, why in this posture?
It's very embarrassing...
It's okay to at least let me enjoy the view of this embarrassing position, right?
It's in exchange for preserving your virginity.
What an awesome smell!
So this is the smell of a man...
Is it coz it wanna rip through my hymen?
I better do it fast or else this thing will ruin my virginity.
Do you love that guy that much?
He's the kind of guy who would always think of another girl.
Y-You're wrong!
When he's with you, he's always thinking of that princess.
A while ago, in this toilet, she must have been raped by that guy.
No... That can't be...
No... Even I want to do it now...
Don't! If I keep smelling this disgusting thing, I won't be able to stand it!
Amazing...
It's swelling up in my mouth...
It's getting horny even more...
I mustn't... I have to suck it in...
Otherwise I'll lose my virginity...
No, I'm...
Already...