Brought U By JPz Records
Takanashi Yumi: While studying at her house, I will be taking her virginity
Sensei, I finished the printed test paper.
Then, let's see if you got em all correctly.
Let's see.
Hmm, they're all correct.
Well done, Yumi-chan.
Yumi-chan?
Is something wrong?
You don't look well.
If you feel stressed out with your studies, you should rub your shoulders like this.
Don't worry, nothing's wrong.
Sensei?
What are you doing? Please let go of me.
Yumi-chan, you're so cute.
I have wanted to do it for so long.
Don't! Please let go of me!
No... Stop it, Sensei!
Somebody! Somebody help!
You're wasting your breath. No one's gonna come.
This strange force must be the work of the DreamNote.
Why are you doing such things to me?
I've always trusted you, Sensei...
It's not just today, you know.
I've always desired to do this.
No way...
Don't you notice?
I've taken the time to study you naked in my mind during the study sessions.
This is amazing, Yumi...
These majestic breasts of yours are well-formed.
No! Don't look at them!
It hurts!
Sensei, please have mercy!
Looks like you're starting to like it.
No...
What now? Do you still want to be rubbed?
No, please stop it already.
You're not being honest, you know.
Next will be down here.
No, not down there!
Gosh, You are so wet already. What a nasty kid.
Jeez! Just by looking...
Yumi, you've been quite a pervert.
How cruel... I'm not a pervert.
I wonder...
You are so wet, I guess it's okay to put it in, huh.
N-No! Anything but that! Please have mercy!
I have no experience in this kind of thing.
Guys get more excited when they hear lines like that.
Yumi, it's time for your lesson.
No way...
Stop! Noooo!!
I'm going in now.
Yumi, how does it feel to become a woman?
It hurts... Pull out quickly...
Don't worry... It will soon feel good.
It really hurts! Stop!
Although you were just a virgin a while ago,
you're starting to feel good, huh, Yumi.
That's not true.
But why?
Soon you'll feel the ecstasy of pleasurable sex.
N-No way! This is so intense!
I'm about to cum!
I'm gonna cum inside, Yumi!
Don't, I beg you please!
Anything but that, so stop!
Don't cum inside!
NOOOOO!!
No... You actually came inside...
I will be pregnant...
I will be pregnant with your baby...
Yumi, listen...
Don't tell your family about this.
You wouldn't want them to know, do you?
It wouldn't be a smart idea, right?
Oh Sensei, leaving already?
Was Yumi having a good time with her lessons?
Yes! Yumi-chan's enjoying her lessons, so everything's fine.
What the hell! You came again?!
My, my... Shiori, you're as mean as always, huh.
Wait a sec, don't get all friendly by calling me by my first name!
It's Miss Shiori to you, got it?!
Stay away from my big sister!
I'm sure you look at her with those perverted eyes, huh?!
Arrogant bitch...
I bet she's still a virgin.
Shiori, you're being rude.
I'm sorry, Sensei.
No, no... I don't mind.
Then, I'll take my leave now.
Shiori-chan, see ya later.
Yes, Sensei. Please come again.
You're not supposed to ask him to come again!
As always, the same arrogant bitch.
I'll use the DreamNote to punish her.
Let's not forget about Mrs. Misako the mother as well.
It seems things are getting interesting from now on.
Takanashi Shiori: Fuck her at the Center for Emoticon Games in the photobooth
Well then... Shiori, over here. Let's hurry to the photobooth.
Yes, I know.
Shiori, can help me set the machine?
Sure.
It's because of the DreamNote's power you have become very obedient.
She is too boring this way.
Huh? Why am I here?
The hell do you think you're doing?!
What are you saying? Obviously taking a photo, right?
But an ordinary photo is too boring.
I wanna take a photograph of your perverted side.
No way! Let go! Let go of me, I said!
Although I'm not really forcing you, I know you want it.
As a matter of fact, you seem happy, right?
Stupid, of course I  don't!
W-Why?! My body's moving on its own...
W-What's happening?!
T-This can't be!
Figured you wanna do it after all.
No way!
Noooo!
I-It hurts! Pull it out!
This feels great. You're acting like you want me to continue.
Noooo! I don't wanna do this!
Noooo!
It hurts!
Pull it out! Have mercy!
Your body is saying something different though.
Y-Your dick is moving inside me!
I guess you're starting to feel good now, huh?
Why are you moaning like that?
N-Noooo! Even though it's bad... Even though it's embarrassing...
It feels good and hot inside!!
You want me to do it harder, Shiori?
You want me to take more disgraceful photos, right?
It... can't... be... helped... b-but I can't take it anymore!
If you want it that much, I'll give it to you hard!
You've now become a perverted woman who gets fucked in the hole!
NOOOO!!
Soo deeeep!!
Your dick... is pounding me nonstop!
No more! Don't take pictures anymore!
It's embarrassing!
Don't take pictures with my legs open anymore!
You're about to cum now, right?
Go ahead! I'll come right in the hole!
Noo! Don't take pictures when I cum!
D-D-Don't!
No! Don't push any farther!
If you do so, it'll break me into pieces!
It... It's filling me inside... filling me up with so much semen...
I-It's hot...
A lot of sticky semen came out...
I guess this should be enough for you.
Fertilize and become babies, my children.
Takanashi Misako: Do her in the living room, while taking a phone call with husband
Oh, is that so.
Work seems to be tough, huh?
So when are you coming back?
Yes, I understand.
No possibility you're coming back by Saturday, right?
Eh? Oh, I see...
S-Sensei, what are you doing?
Hmm? Is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing...
Stop it, please...
Good Evening, Mrs. Misako.
I was just passing by.
Can you relieve me with your mouth?
There's no way I'm going to do a such a thing!
Hello? Are you there?
I-I am sorry... Something just fell...
Then, please do the honor.
Please no... Not now...
Resistance is futile.
You know the only way to fix this is to make a man cum, right?
But...
Is there something a matter, Misako?
I-It's nothing, my dear.
The drama on TV seems to be in a climax.
Come on... Do it already.
No... I can't do it...
I will yell out if you don't do it.
Oh no...
I'll do it...
What are you doing? I can't hear you.
I'm sorry... I am eating a popsicle at the moment...
Forgive me for being too loud, my dear.
That's the way to do it, Mrs. Misako. You're terrific.
It's too deep...
It's fine! I'm about to cum!
Drink it all and don't let a drop spill please.
Just now it sounded like something was not right.
I'm sorry. I was feeling a bit cold at that moment.
No... Stop...
Please forgive me... I don't want to do this...
You're already this wet. Do you really want me to stop?
Having oral sex while on the phone with your husband is not enough, huh?
I-I didn't wish to do this kind of thing.
I'm sorry, my dear.
We were talking about your business trip, right?
No more...
I'm gonna to cum inside.
No, stop it!
Don't... Don't!
My moan... My moaning will be heard...
Forgive me! Forgive me!
No... no...
I... I screamed because he came inside my womb...
Forgive me, my dear...
He came inside my womb...
Takanashi Shiori: Exposed her in the park during a walk.
Shiori, listen to me well and do as I say, got it?
Yes, Master.
Take off the coat while you play in front of me.
Yes.
Good. How do you feel now?
Yes. I feel embarrassed, but feel good being naked at the same time.
Then go ahead. Pee on the roots next to that tree.
P-Pee on that tree?
I will, since Master desires it.
What an interesting landscape.
Show your pussy a bit more, Shiori.
Yes.
This is embarrassing...
My fingers are moving on their own...
Hey, hey, who told you to masturbate without order?
I-I am sorry...
Really now, masturbating in public...
You really are a hopeless bitch, aren't you?
I am not a  bitch...
Really now, as expected you would cause problems to me whether I fuck you or not.
I am sorry that you had to repeat yourself because of me...
I understand.
Hurry up and pee already.
Yes!
My pee... It won't stop coming out... It feels so good!
I can see that was an interesting show there, Shiori.
Peeping in public...
While people are watching, you're satisfied?
Are people watching me?
I don't care if people are watching me pee...
All I wanna do is pee to my heart's content...
Well then... For obediently following your Master's orders, I'll give your reward, bitch.
You're giving me my reward? Master!!
Well, I'll fucking give it to you now.
So then, does it feel better than peeing?
It's amazing! It feels better being fucked inside!
If you keep moaning so loud like that, we're gonna be seen for sure.
I don't care...
Although this is so humiliating, I feel ecstatic!
So humiliating, but it feels so good!
You are one messed up perverted bitch.
You really can't wait for me to shoot inside you, huh?
Shoot everything inside of me! Turn me into a Mommy!
Please give me...
My Master's semen!
Shoot it all inside of me!
I understand. I'll give you your favorite semen!
I-It's coming inside... inside my pussy...
Semen... is filling up my pussy!
This is amazing...
In public... I was... being impregnated...
Takanashi Yumi: Fuck her again in the public swimming pool.
It's inside! You're fucking me again!
Surrounded by all these people!
Screaming with that lustful voice, who wouldn't hear us?
But they come out on their own!
Oh, I see. You wanna be seen that badly, huh?
Noo!
Don't look at me!
Take a look. All the boys here are looking at you.
They probably wanna see you masturbate right now.
N-No... That's a lie!
Don't look at me masturbating!
I'm sure they want to see it.
They wanna see your lustful self being excited.
There's no way... I can be that perverted...
Then, listen well, Yumi. Place your hands at the side of the pool and face me.
Yes...
They're looking at your lustful face.
You're one horny slut!
Go ahead!
I'm... about to cum!
Well, do it in front of all these people!
Don't! I can't! Noo!!
In front of these people, I'll fuck you till you're pregnant!
No! Don't look at me!
Don't look at me! Being impregnated!
You came...
You made me pregnant...
In front of so many people... You gave me your baby...
Let's get out of the pool and get into the showers.
Yes.
Yumi, if you moan any louder, we're gonna be found out.
No! To be seen like this... They'll think I'm a pervert!
No! It feel too good that I can't help moaning like this anymore!
We'll be found out! We'll absolutely be found out!!
You really wanna be seen, right?
To be honest... I want someone to see me being violated by Sensei!
I want people to see me become pregnant!
Fine! Let me impregnate you!
Impregnate me!
With lots of your sticky semen! Shoot it all inside of me!
IMPREGNATE ME!!
I'm so happy... I'm pregnant with Sensei's babies!
Yumi has completely turned into my mindless sex slave.
Next will be...
are those two...