Still not gettinn' up...
After doing this much to wake you up...
You're finally awake!
Miharu!
Jeez, and I took the trouble of waking you up with a boner.
Can't hold it anymore, right?
Hurry up and cum already.
You came a lot so early in the morning.
You!
Noo!!
Jeez...
Nooo...
You're so wet this early in the morning as well.
Your breath is blowing on my ass.
I only get horny in front of you, Ushio, you know?
It's coz of you, Ushio, that I get horny.
No...
Hey, Ushio... I want it...
Oh, c'mon...
Ushio, stop being a meanie.
It went in...
Ushio's dick went inside my pussy so early in the morning.
It's so intense. Ushio!
Right there...
No... Rubbin' it against my pussy...
That feels so good!
Amazing... It's reachin' all the way inside...
Hitting my womb like that, it feels so good!
Yes, keep knockin' me down!
Ushio!
I'm about to cum!
Let's cum together...
Ushio, I want to cum with you!
No! No more... I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!!
You came so much inside my pussy...
Jeez, what the hell were you doin'?!
We're gonna be late, late!
Jeez, just coz your parents ain't home, you've fucked me like crazy!
Watcha mean, "Fucked you like crazy?!" Miharu...
You came so much inside of me, I might be pregnant!
You don't have to declare it to the entire world...
Nobody's listening to us anyway.
Even if that's the case...
Nobody would believe that you didn't stand out at all in the past if they saw you now.
Who gives a fuck about the past?!
What's that suppose to mean?!
You sayin' you're not satisfied with the way I am now?
N-No...
Then, let's drop the topic!
I don't want you to see the old me...
From those times...
I don't wanna go back to the old me...
It's coz of the 'me' now that I was able to meet you, Ushio.
S-Sorry...
It's fine...
Even if we're this close now, there are times when I don't want you to hate the old me of the past.
It's nothin'.
Let's get going!
Miharu!
Miharu, are you okay?!
Miharu?
Hey, Miharu!
MIHARU!!!
Amazing! Awesome!
Can't hold it anymore, right?
Stay still for a bit.
It's getting bigger and it twitches.
It went in.
Just a little more, it'll go inside.
H-Hey, Miharu.
What's your problem?!
I suck coz I'm a virgin?!
B-But you made fun of me being a virgin as well...
Like it matters, right?
Anyway, I gave my super valuable virginity to you.
Use it to make me feel good as well.
Don't, no touching!
If I didn't push you down,
you wouldn't have the balls to fuck me.
I'm not gonna let someone like you touch me.
It's me who's raping you,
so I call the shots on what we will do.
D-Don't! No!
You're thrusting me up with your hips...
No, this is... my first time, but I feel so good...
No, I'm cumming...
It's my first time, but...
I'M CUMMING!!
Ya're so pretty, like a Sleeping Beauty.
She is sleeping.
I was just wonderin' if Sis became a heroine of a tragic drama.
Quit posing to be cute.
Ain't I not cute?
Damn cute, I guess.
Your girlfriend's unconscious...
And yet, ya're hittin' on other gals.
Futaba-chan!
Note:
Senpai = An Upperclassman
Unfaithful as ever, ain't ya, Senpai?
Since that dick of yours ain't a virgin anymore...
Why are you being so mean?!
It's been a while since I've seen Senpai's cute side.
Still a wuss as ever, ain't ya?
Your words are hurting me badly, you know?
Fu... taba...
S-Sis, ya okay?!
Miharu!
I'll go call the doctor.
Where am I?
It's okay.
Ya just hit your head and lost consciousness,
so ya were brought to the hospital.
No way... How?
It happened while ya were goin' to school.
School?
Since when did I...?
Futaba, why do you have that uniform on?
Amnesia?!
He said that it's only temporary, but...
What should we do if she never recovers her memories?
No way... She'll be okay...
I guess, ya're right.
She'll be okay...
Oh, Senpai, let's call it a day,
since our parents are comin' over soon.
I'll contact ya about her condition later.
Ya should rest for a bit.
Ah, okay.
If Senpai collapses too, that'll make things even worse.
You're right. I understand.
And so, Sis and I are here!
The hell do you mean "And so"?!
You didn't even bother to explain it at all.
Jeez, ya spare too much on the minor details, Senpai.
Like I say, in order to restore Sis' memories, the best place to do so would be here.
You're not explaining it at all!
Well, I kinda understand a bit, but...
Will she be physically okay?
It never was a severe physical injury to begin with.
She just gotta rest to be back to normal.
It was kinda tough...
Sis was bein' all shy about comin' here.
Took me a lotta effort to drag her ass here,
although she's the kinda person who'd always make trouble.
Oh no, I...
Well, she was like this before she entered high school.
Come on, Sis, say hi to Senpai.
C'mon, quit showin' your ass in front of others.
Jeez...
Oopsy!
Come on, ya shy gal.
Are you okay, Miharu?
Mi... Miharu... Miharu?!
Irifune-kun is calling me, Miharu!
Jeez, that's all ya do.
C'mon, say hi to him properly.
Please take care of the both of us!
Both of you?!
I'm...
I'm really here at Irifune-kun's house...
And, he's my boyfriend?
It looks like she lost all her memories
startin' from when she got into high school.
So she totally doesn't remember bein' your girlfriend, or the lucky draw...
Being dressed like this...
Dating Irifune-kun...
Then, that means she doesn't remember me?
Am I really?
That's why I thought if she stays with Senpai,
maybe she could get her memories back.
Well, that's what I think...
I can't believe your dad agreed to this.
That part was a piece of cake!
E-Even so...
Ya musta heard about what she used to be like, right?
She was always a loser.
So, I heard...
We were at that topic this morning.
She said she never ever wanted me to see her old self.
Although she has shown it already...
Well, Sis's still pretty adorable this way, right?
She's the complete opposite of how she usually is.
It's kinda refreshing...
No, no, no!
We gotta hurry and restore her memories back.
Rushin' things won't do any good.
N-No, Futaba...
You're having too much fun talking to Irifune-kun...
This kinda stuff requires timing...
So we shouldn't rush things and look after her together.
I... I wanna talk to him like that too...
Together?
Ya, we'll do it together.
No... You shouldn't, Futaba...
You're even holding his hand...
We gotta gal here who seems to be havin' a lotta fun fantasizin'.
I-I see...
Well then, now that ya know Sis' true color...
True color?!
All that's left is to go to sleep with her.
So, this is...
Your family's in the middle of an overseas trip, right?
I just thought maybe I could be some use to ya... like a SEX SLAVE...
Don't say 'Sex Slave', Futaba-chan!
She was so embarrassed just a while ago...
N-No way, Futaba...
I really can't s-sleep like this...
I fixed her up with some tranquilizers, so...
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm pretty sure I gave her more than enough.
You shouldn't be saying that...
Anyway, Sis's fast asleep...
Senpai...
W-Wait... W-We shouldn't!
Oh my. When your dick was still a virgin, I could do whatever I wanted with it...
C'mon, Senpai...
Please fuck me...
Futaba-chan...
Ya're thinkin' 'bout it right now, right?
Stuff like, "Futaba-chan's so slutty." and...
"I wonder if I should fuck her on the spot?"
That's right.
The one who really wants Senpai...
is the slutty Futaba-chan...
It's gettin' hard...
It's been a long time since I touched Senpai's dick...
So good!
It feels so much better than doin' it by myself!
Senpai's hand... is so warm...
Senpai's smell too... It's been so long...
I'm gettin' really horny now!
Senpai, please stay still, okay?
Coz it's me who's raping Senpai this time...
Let's check out how Senpai's dick has grown.
Still hyped up, I see, though it ain't very faithful.
It responds as good as always, right, Senpai?
It's makin' me wanna tease ya a bit more.
Wait...
Ya like me being kinky, right, Senpai?
Amazing!
Senpai's dick is so hot on my knees!
No, I thought doin' this was weird,
but I'm gettin' even hornier!
Senpai, ya're gettin' sticky down there!
If this keeps up, are ya gonna cum soon?
Lookin' at Senpai's face is gettin' me excited...
But it's a no-no...
It ain't no fun if Senpai's the only one gettin' it all good.
Make my pussy feel good as well.
Your girlfriend's right next to ya...
And your dick's about to go inside her little sister's pussy, Senpai.
Ya're givin' me that weird look on your face...
I wonder what Sis would think
if she sees that face of yours...
Ya're makin' that kinda face,
even though ya're about to cum inside of me...
Senpai's dick went deep inside of me!
Although I've stuck a lotta things inside of me before, Senpai's dick is the best!
All those kinda things...
I'll tell ya more next time, okay?
Oh, no!
It's been too long!
So hard!
I can't!
If this goes on!
I'll cum!!
Senpai's dick feels so good!!
No! I... I'm cumming!
It's been a long time since I made Senpai's dick cum!
So good, Senpai!
I'm cumming!
Futaba... is cumming!!
A lotta came inside of me, Senpai's semen...
While Sis's still sleepin',
Senpai's semen's fillin' up my pussy...
It's still fillin' me up...
There's so much...
Senpai, I know I can't be Sis' replacement...
But let me try till Sis gets her memories back, okay?
Wow, it's leakin' out!
What a waste!
I wonder if this smell can get her memories back.
I guess Sis's slutty to begin with, don't ya think, Senpai?
Sis, be sure to rest properly, okay?
Avoid any strenuous exercises till your memories recover.
Kyaa~
W-We'll be back as soon as we can.
Take care.
It's so refreshing!
Since ya came so much semen inside my pussy last night, I'm full of energy!
Futaba-chan!
If ya can't hold it anymore,
ya're free to stick it in my pussy anytime...
Even during class time.
Please wait for me!
It's like a dream...
Being able to be with Irifune-kun like that...
Before, all I could do was look at him...
All this stuff about us being boyfriend-girlfriend...
It's all true...
Going together to school, becoming lovers...
Even I, myself had changed...
The person who's had no friends and is a coward...
is together with him...
Even had sex with him...
It's embarrassing!
Really?! We did those things?!
It's as if I'm a different person...
But this smell is the real deal...
It's his smell...
Ushio-kun's smell...
It's weird...
It's the smell that makes me feel kinda heavy...
While smelling it, it makes my body really hot, and I imagine Ushio's face...
It's so embarrassing!
It... is like Ushio-kun making love to me...
I can't do this...
No...
Don't!
Doing something so embarrassing...
I can't stop myself...
Don't! Don't!
Doing such embarrassing things inside Ushio-kun's room, I...
No... I... I'm... about to... I... I'm...
This can't be true...
I did such an embarrassing thing...
Ushio-kun...
Miharu...
Uh... U-Um... Um...
Uh... Um... Uh... Uh... You see...
Umm... Ushio-kun... You see... Umm... I...
Miharu...
Ushio-kun?
No way, I'm kissing Ushio-kun...
How can I put it? This doesn't feel like it's my first time.
It feels so nostalgic.
I feel like I've done this before...
Don't, Ushio-kun!
Um... I, you see... hey...
It's all right since it's Miharu...
Don't!
It's embarrassing, Ushio-kun...
T-This... is my... first time...
I... umm... have had sex with you, Ushio-kun before...
S-Sorry, I rushed things...
M-Me too... I showed you an embarrassing side of me...
But...
This position...
It's going in?
It doesn't hurt...
No...
It's... coming... inside of me... Feels nice...
Amazing... Does it feel this good?
Don't... I won't be able to resist it...
No! So good! Amazing!
Ushio-kun... Amazing! So good! Stay like that...
No... It's... rubbing deep inside...
What to do?! Amazing! Feels so good!!
Ushio-kun's... feels so good!!
Ushio's... rubbing inside of me!
It's driving me crazy!!
No!
Ushio-kun!
No more!
Amazing...
I had no idea it would feel this good...
Ushio-kun...
Senpai, ya're a meanie!
Bailin' on me during lunch break...
Sorry, I only came back to get something I forgot.
Then I had something else to attend to...
Jeez, ya should've at least contacted me!
I was searchin' everywhere for ya.
M-My bad...
Even someone as nice as me would get mad if ya do somethin' like that, ya know?
I... I'm going back to my room.
Did ya have sex with Sis?
So ya did, huh!
Havin' no memories, ya forced yourself!
I... I didn't force her.
W-What is it?
Senpai, I wonder what punishment should I give ya.
Punishment?!
I'll make sure that your dick won't want anyone but me.
Well then, time to take a bath.
Senpai, wanna take a dip with me?
I rather take a hike!
Ushio-kun...
Miharu!
I thought you were asleep.
I was going to do that, but...
I heard Futaba-chan and you talking...
You and Futaba seem to be getting along quite well...
I-It's natural, right?
S-Since she's the younger sister of your girlfriend, right?
W-What am I saying?
Miharu...
Umm... I'm sorry for saying something weird...
Feeling jealous?
W-What? Why would I be jealous of my younger sister?
I'm sorry, forget about it...
Miharu...
You're cute...
Don't...
Senpai...
He actually had sex with the old Sis from before...
This declares war, doesn't it?
Hey...
If we do it here, Futaba will...
Even though you say that,
it turns you on, doesn't it, Miharu?
No, doing this... we'll get caught...
That spot... It's going all the way...
No! That spot... rub it more! It feels so good!
Ushio-kun's... really... feels so good!
Hey, do this only to me...
I'm sorry...
I'll sure I'll remember the old times...
That's why...
This...
Belongs only to me...
Only to me!
Miharu!
Don't! If you do it so violently, I'll cum!
Ushio-kun, I can feel it!
Make me feel more like a slut!!
Ushio-kun's... Give it to me!
Inside my cumhole! A lot of it! Shoot it!!
Amazing! It's... so... full!!
I feel the same way for Senpai...
Same as how Sis feels...
I love him...