The Oda Big Event that operates in the shopping square is known as a convention.
Since it's crowded and open at all hours,
Cam and Scott-senpai have teamed up to watch over the square.
Brought U By JPz Records
Cam, hurry up!
'Kay!
Jeez, this place is loaded.
Furthermore, I gotta feeling the cameras keep shooting at us for a while now...
Why??
Oh, it's coz...
They think Senpai and Cam are Yuzetsu cosplayers.
Yuzetsu?
It's currently a popular series on the TV, where Yuzu gets kidnapped and is full of despair in the animé.
Senpai is mistaken as a character called, Kiryuu...
And Cam is a character named, Asagi.
Well, ya see...
Kiryuu and Asagi are lovers.
They fight together against the evil forces that threaten the Earth.
I see.
So if we continue to pretend to be cosplayers,
We'll be less conspicuous as we investigate the area.
T-T-This is like a spy operation in disguise, right?
The basic principles of spy operation is...
To blend in within the environment.
Yes! Cam will blend in!
This way fags!
Okay, first we should...
Ah?! Cam??
Ah, Senpai...
Senpai!
Se-Senpai, did ya get lost?
Ca-Cam should ask for help!
Cam mustn't!
If Cam did that, Cam won't be able to blend in...
Don't worry, Senpai.
Cam is now a cosplayer.
As the replacement of my lost Senpai,
Cam will complete the spy operation successfully by herself!
Woah, check that chick out!
It's a Yuzetsu cosplay!
That's the hottest Asagi-tan costume I've ever seen!
That's somethin' ya don't see out of the blue!
Yeah, got that right!
We got ourselves a target, my fellow fags!
YES, YOUR HIGHNESS!!
Hey, miss...
Ya're cosplaying Asagi-tan from Yuzetsu, right?
It's awesome! Ya're like Asagi-tan in real flesh.
Oh, ya think so?
Did ya hear that, Senpai?
Cam is now the ultimate cosplayer!
Well then, Asagi-tan! Strike a pose!
A pose?
Like this?
That sucks! Ya need to look more like Asagi-tan...
Ya dunno much 'bout Asagi-tan role, do ya?
What?!
What should Cam do?
If Cam fails to do a pose,
the spy operation will be mission failed.
Well, to be honest, this is the first time Cam became a cosplayer...
WHAT?!
Today is your cosplay debut?!
CHANCE!!
If that's the case, we, fags, will teach ya how to strike a proper pose.
To commemorate your first day as a cosplayer,
we'll help ya out with your Asagi-tan pose.
Ya really will?
Thank you very much!
Note: "Moe" is how Japanese fags address something as cute.
MOE!!
W-What are ya doin'?
That tickles...
What're we doin'? We're helpin' ya with your character, of course!
When Asagi-tan is attacked by monsters,
she poses elegantly, ya know!
Oh, really?
Nooo!
Those are my boobs...
Woah, that's one hell of an expression ya got there!
Very much like the real Asagi-tan!
Is Cam now.. actin' like a real cosplayer?
Here's a better way to make ya even more like a cosplayer...
Pucker up!
My mind... is starting to go blank...
Cam is starting get really horny...
Cosplayers must be very horny people...
Here ya go, Cam-chan!
Now it's time to be even more like Asagi-tan.
That tickles!
This is great!
Cam-chan, ya're good at armpit jobs!
Ya're probably the best cosplayer this square has ever seen!
Ya really think so?
Cosplayers do armpit jobs too?
Here!
This one too!
This is awesome...
Your dick keeps throbbing more, it's hot...
Cam's body is also gettin' really hot...
That ain't good!
We must relieve your fever right away!
Even if ya make Cam fondle your dicks...
or poke Cam's nipples with your dicks...
Nothing will come out from Cam's boobs...
They don't have any milk...
Cam-chan, ya gotta pay more attention...
I'm about to cum!
Cam-chan, are ya ready for our cum?
Yes...
C-Cam is ready...
A lot of dicks are gonna cum...
That's a lot...
A lot came out...
There are a lot of dick milk all over Cam's body...
Good!
Let the real fun begin!
This will be the best image-play, once I put it in!
I'm puttin' it in!
I'm puttin' my monster dick inside Cam-chan's pussy!
But, that's...
This is Asagi-tan's greatest pinch!
Ya shouldn't move an inch or lose your shiny elegance,
if ya wanna continue lookin' like Asagi-tan!
This is awesome!
Both dicks are comin' in-n-outta of Cam's pussy and butt!
Cosplaying is so awesome!
It feels so good!
Cam is full of dicks right now!
Cam is goin' crazy mode!
CRAZY MODE!!
Cam's butt...
Cam's pussy too...
Even Cam's mouth feels great!
Great job!
Cam-chan's acting is the best!
The best cosplayer ever!
That's right...
Cam is a cosplayer...
A one hell of a horny cosplayer!
I know Asagi-tan doesn't give up on round one, right?
Even Cam's throat...
This thick dick is goin' all the way down Cam's throat...
Cam-chan, ya're cosplaying's so intense!
It got my dick rock hard!
I'm almost there...
Almost there...
It's cumming!
Here it cums!!
Cam's mouth... is full of boys' naughty juice...
Cam's full of cum...
Here more, Cam-chan...
Accept my cum too!
Okay!
Okay, up next, let's cosplay in this position!
With pleasure!
It's Cam's first time cosplaying after all...
Your dick... I want it...
Ya got it!
Sweet, Cam-chan's squeezing me tight!
If ya continue to squeeze me like this, I'll cum right away!
Yes, please cum!
Please cum inside of Cam!
Please fill Cam with cum!
Please flood Cam's inside with a lot of your cum!
It's so awesome!
Cosplaying is so awesome!
Cosplaying with dicks involved...
It's makin' Cam go crazy mode again!
CRAZY MODE!!
Here, here, here it comes!
I'm gonna smash your cosplay body with my Gundam!
Cam can feel your Gundam entering me!
GUNDAM FIRE!!
Your Gundam came in so violently...
I'm totally messed up!
Cam's pussy and butthole is being carved into a slutty shape by your dicks!
Once you take it from the back, no turning back!
Ya're cosplay like a pro, ain't ya?
Ya sure want the inside and outside of your body to be like the character, right?
Cam-chan!
Be sure to savor the flavor of tons of our semen, okay?!
I will!
Please...
Please gimme cum!
Please let Cam eat all your semen!!
I-I-It's spilling all over the place!
Cum-milk... is spilling all over Cam!
Okay, for the final character building stage...
Let's fire Cam-chan with all our semens combine!
Cam is so full...
Cam is so full of cum...
All the cum on my body make me look like a vanilla ice cream...
Ya did one hell of a job, Cam-chan!
Ya totally have captured the character by heart!
It even brought out the villains inside of us, fags!
Now, give us your final smile!
What a relief...
With this, I won't be a nuisance to Senpai,
and our spy operation will successfully be mission complete...
Hey, Cam!
Oh, it looks like your partner is coming.
Thanks for taking pictures with us, fags!
That girl was great.
She totally made me think of becoming a rapist.
That's gonna keep me satisfied for half a year.
Thank you very much, Mr. Rapists!
OH NO!!
WHAT?!
What are those fluids all over you?!
What on Earth are you people doing?!
We were just practicing how to cosplay properly.
Thanks to that, Cam and Scott-senpai were able to arrest Mr. Rapists who threatened this convention.