Welcome back! It's Mirano.
The season when everyone's dicks are hot has arrived.
I bear a secret which shouldn't be told to anyone, and yet I told it to everyone.
It's a secret that my husband is very perverse about.
Although I know that I shouldn't do it, I couldn't control myself...
About the secret that excites and inflicts pain to my body...
With that, my shameless self... told my husband, "I love you."
But I knew it was futile up till now...
I use his secret to pressure him for sex.
My body doesn't listen to me...
Even today, I'll use this secret for my pussy more...and more!
Till I shake like crazy!!
Don't!
I can't control myself!
Doing this shameful thing...
He saw my shameful side as woman...
But!
I can't hold it anymore!
M-Mirano...
Permission to eat now!!
Where have you guys gone to?
Where have we? Well...
I'm returning the princess.
It's strange though...
If you have time to rest, you should use it to protect her instead.
When I woke up, Shinichi, you weren't there.
I was really worried...
Even Takaaki-kun, he... well...
H-He said that wondering alone is dangerous...
So he accompanied me...
Fubuki, were you...
Before we ran into each other, were you together with him all along?
With Takaaki...
Well... you see...
But Shinichi, you as well...
After being affected by the earthquake, when I woke up, I found her unconscious next to me.
Nothing else happened.
Same as I...
~ Little birds in the darkness ~
Brought U By JPz Records & Masurenai
How was your search?
Half of the building is flooded in water.
I guess it became a waterfront.
Is the main building safe?
The sooner we get outside, the sooner we'll be rescued.
I-Indeed.
Aren't you gonna bring Fubuki-chan along with you?
I'll let her sleep for a bit more.
She seemed like she couldn't sleep last night.
I...
So Takaaki, I will leave the two to you.
Roger that, my bestfriend.
B-Being alone could be dangerous...
That's only what I thought...
And once you two are alone, you'd jump into his arms?
Because I'm afraid of boys...
I hate that...
Did he touch you?
P-Please stop it!
I'm already...
Was it Shinichi who made you this wet?
That's...
I wasn't careful enough at that time.
I thought everyone was sleeping already.
However, I didn't expect Kawahara-senpai would...
I-I was shocked!
He was silently...
Peeping at me...
Before...
He was your unusual kinda guy.
He must be following you.
I... see... No way... Why?
He probably intended to peep at you, don't you think?
How come?
I-It was embarrassing...
Although I told him to wait outside...
I didn't want to be seen by anyone...
That's why he wanted to peep at you.
No!!
Boys...
are scary...
I hate this!
Are you still afraid?
However, it's warm...
Feel it more!
More, more!
What should I do?
Today... Senpai's...doing it a lot again!
I feel it a lot!
So intense... It's more intense...
It's more intense than yesterday...
Today, even the shape is...
Is it big?
I wouldn't know!
I can't compare it either!
But I love it!
It's so ecstatic...
It's scary, but it makes me feel very warm inside...
I... Senpai's... S-Senpai's...
My?
My... what?
That's... umm... D... D...
My...?
Dick...
I didn't hear that quite well.
It's Senpai's dick!!
It's so good!
Senpai's making me feel so good!
I love Senpai's dick!
You went out alone again, Shinichi.
Could it be that he hates me?
Fubuki, were you... Before we ran into each other, were you together with him all along?
With Takaaki...
I shouldn't think of such things.
He'll hate me even more. I must forget it...
You gotta treasure your memories...
For girls, isn't the first kiss an unforgettable and much cherished event by them?
That's coz you forced me into it!
That first time was your first time.
Although I do my best during practice, it's not something for anyone to see.
Did you notice that someone praised me that I'm feminine?
What exactly am I doing anyway?
Jeez, maybe I should ask him out to go swimming,
And let him stare at my body while I'm wearing a swimsuit!
Why the hell must I be the one to ask him?!
On the first place, isn't it the guy who's suppose to ask the girl out?!
Jeez, and I just bought a sexy swimsuit!
It will surely make him nosebleed till he collapses!
But I'll need a model's figure though, right?
W-What the fuck, Tsumura-kun?!
What the fuck? Isn't that a charm for waking up a sleeping beauty?
Stop fucking around! What the hell happened here?!
I didn't expect that we'd encounter this kinda situation again.
Thank God you're safe.
Although I say it was also my first time, I guess you wouldn't believe me either.
No way... It's coz...
It's coz...
T-The fuck do I know!
Fubuki-chan!
It's unfair, doing something like that...
He's totally different from Shinichi.
It's definitely a lie, saying it's his first.
Fubuki?
It's true! We can use it!
Can I try it out?
Maybe I'm just being a bit paranoid.
But I guess it's Shinichi after all.
Surely it's all bullshit!
For Shinichi to behave that way, there's no way!
Sorry that I doubted you at the last minute.
But that guy...
...is a failure as a knight, right?
Ta-Takaaki-kun!
No!
Jeez, stop this...
Kissing me right from the start... It's unfair...
Making my mind blank so that I couldn't resist against him...
This makes my second time seeing Fubuki naked again.
Stop this, Taka-
Say, tell me...
Do you also masturbate everyday?
Asking so suddenly...
I only did it once...
At night?
On the bed?
Just stop this...
Shouldn't it be your boyfriend who's suppose to satisfy you during such times?
D-Don't say anymore...
Please, don't!
No more!
No fair...
Since you're quite experienced with masturbation, I'm sure you can't hold in anymore, right?
Don't... Shinichi... is there for me, you know...
But he is also with Mizuha-chan...
It's the end for you and him.
C'mon, I'mma stick it in now.
I really don't wanna do it...
If you say you really love me, you'd let me go...
Better embrace it firmly...
Or else that guy's gonna hear us.
So mean...
Looks like being fucked in the pussy makes you so happy that it makes you cry.
Fubuki-chan, your inside is so warm.
So rough!
You're so sensitive when I grind it inside of you.
No... T-There's no way...
No! Takaaki-kun...
Don't! Don't do it anymore... He'll hear us...
No!
No! I'm scared! No!
Takaaki-kun!
Hug me! I'll never let you go!
Fubuki-chan, do you see it?
It keeps coming... inside of me...
Takaaki-kun's dick is getting bigger...
I'm so happy that Fubuki-chan kissed me herself.
No! I...
Don't! Takaaki-kun, I beg you!
Stop this, Takaaki-kun!
Your body can only feel me!
No! Takaaki-kun, I beg you!
Takaaki-kun, please!
Takaaki-kun...
Takaaki-kun!
Fubuki?
S-Shinichi...
S-Sorry...
Wait for a bit longer...
Okay?
S-Sorry, I fell asleep...
So nothing happened?
Umm... Yeah! Don't worry... I'll be done in a jiffy.
Don't... I shouldn't...
I wonder what will happen to us...
Don't worry about it... We'll surely get outta this place.
Don't worry. I'll protect you no matter what.
You're sure as the same as before.
Right, right...
We were busted big time at that time too.
J... J-Jeez! You don't have to recall those kinds of shit from before!
Shinichi...
I...
It hurts...
It's okay... Be more gentle, okay?
Sorry!
I don't intend to disturb, but...
The other princess is getting worried.
Also, she got something to say to us.
Ah, okay... Sorry...
Momose-san, are you wet?
Yea... coz I just got out from a shower...
Did it feel good?
The drainage system?
Yes, if it's still intact, we could...
However, I'm not sure if it's still intact.
Since the showers are still working, the internal waterway tunnel should probably be undamaged as well.
T-That's true...
Anyway, let's go and check it out.
The sound of the waves... We're getting close to the sea.
It's true... I can hear it!
It came from that trap...
Could that be... the way out?
Fubuki-chan!
Fubuki!
Senju-san!
You, okay?
Ta-Takaaki-kun?!
This makes it my second time waking you up, Fubuki-chan.
You, okay?
In this position, we won't be crushed...
S-Shinichi?!
Takaaki-kun, where's Shinichi?!
When I tried to call out to him, there was no response.
It seems he was trying to protect Mizuha-chan, but...
He tried...
T-There's no way...
Shinichi...
Takaaki-kun?
I wonder if I'm as determined as he was...
N-No way...
Takaaki-kun, say that!
I'll cheer you on!
Don't worry... I'll protect you no matter what...
Really sorry, Fubuki-chan...
I know a simple apology ain't gonna let me off the hook...
Fubuki-chan, I've made you have those perverse thoughts...
But really... All this time, it's only you... that I love...
Although I say it was also my first time...
Can you... listen to my final wish?
W-What is it, Takaaki-kun?
Since I'm gonna die anyway, let me be one with you...
No, no way... Even if you say that...
I don't care if that guy is still in your heart, Fubuki-chan...
But only now, let me be the only one in your heart, okay?
I can't move at all, so...
Fubuki-chan, use your hands...
Please...
Takaaki-kun...
It's hot... It's so hot, Takaaki-kun...
No, Takaaki-kun...
Fubuki-chan, you rubbin' my dick... Makes me feel better again...
Takaaki-kun...
Please...
For this only moment...
Can you be my lover?
Sure...
Fubuki-chan...
Yes...
Takaaki-kun, fuck me...
Fubuki-chan!
Takaaki-kun's hot dick is fucking me!
Fuck me all up inside, Takaaki-kun!
It's fucking me deep inside! Takaaki-kun's...
More... Show me more of your horny face!
Since it's gonna be my final one...
This perverted side of me... is only for you, Takaaki-kun to see!
I can't let Shinichi see this side of me!
The tip of your dick is... Noooo...
My pussy's so fucked up by Takaaki-kun's dick!
No! It's so fucking me up!
Fubuki-chan's pussy... belongs only to me!
Only yours! My pussy... belongs only to Takaaki-kun!
This fuckin' dick...
It's not Shinichi's, but Takaaki-kun's dick that makes me so fuckin' horny!!
Yeah!
It's so good!!
I love you! Takaaki-kun! I love you!
I love you!
Fubuki-chan!
Give it to me! Takaaki-kun's semen!!
Give me all of it!
I'm also...
Takaaki-kun! Takaaki-kun!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!