Really, your sister had too much to drink.
Akane is too slick,
I also want a boyfriend like Asato.
Um
really...
Asato-kun
I want you to take care of me too.
Look, this place is getting all swollen up.
onee-chan
Asato, is mine though, *pout x2*
That accident really shocked me.
I though that Akane would never wakeup again.
Onee-chan
but I didn't expect that the call of the prince would actually wake you.
It was so great.
Both learning and work are doing well, I feel at ease.
Go chase your dreams.
Ok.
If you run into difficulties come to me, I'm just next door anyway.
Ayumi-san
Thanks, work hard at work.
Although it's troublesome, I entrust her to you.
ok
But it's hard for someone single to bear.
Don't do it too roughly.
If I heard ecchi noises every night,
My body would...
A Ayumi-san...
Just joking!
see ya
Onii-chan was...
It was very much in line with Ayumi's character.
Asato, sorry for making you wait.
No,, this is for the dream of two people.
No, Asato
Was thinking of waiting until marriage...
but it's alright now.
a lot happened after graduation
to be with Asato now...
I feel very happy.
Because of my stubborness,
you've had some lonely memories
I'll never leave you again.
I'm so happy.
So, don't worry about me.
It's alright, I want to become Asato's.
I want to be filled by Asato.
Who is that?
Is it Onii-chan?
I'll go take a look.
It's probably Ayumi-san.
K Kyou-chan
What happened?
Hmmn?
Kyou-chan?
Kamisaka Kyosuke
Akane, what...
A-Asato...
It's my childhood friend.
Hey, what happened?
Kyou-chan...
Please!
A month, no! Just 2 weeks!
Please let me stay here.
Sorry.
But I have a way to repay the debt.
So until then, please.
So Kyou-chan was working as a host.
2 weeks...
Asato, if it's just this...
hey
But living here, Akane...
Don't worry.
This place hasn't been discovered.
Since we're child friends,
and has also helped me a lot.
I would like to also do something for him.
Although it's at a time like this.
Can I, Asato?
Ok but only 2 weeks, no more.
And, you must pay attention when you're going in and out.
Sawamura, sorry.
What happened?
Nothing, was just looking for something.
Oh really.
Akane is really stubborn eh?
She didn't want her childhood friend to see the bad side.
Well, it wasn't all bad.
Good work today.
Akane, today's bento was great.
Thanks.
This is?
That's Kyou-chan's.
Sorry, I'll change it.
It's ok, I'll do it.
Is this also Kamisaka's?
Here.
Eh? Is that my shirt?
Akane
Do it, do it harder.
Kyou-chan, we can't.
Let's stop.
I still have to go to school.
This is too wierd.
Hey, Kyou-chan.
It's fine now right?
Ah, sorry.
Akane said she'll help so I was willfull.
This kind of thing.
It'll be done in a sec.
I'm not boasting,
but I'm quite fast.
Hey Akane
This is also for Sawamura.
Although he's wearing a condom,
I can still feel it,
It's a different shape from Asato's
Akane, I'm almost there!
Kyou-chan
Wow, so much.
No, we can't continue, so..
Akane...
Asato...
Hey, let's continue what we were doing before.
Akane, wait.
I guess we can't if you have the morning shift.
Work hard at work.
No
I'm becoming more and more ecchi.
Kyou-chan
Hey, what really happened.?
I want to help.
We're childhood friends after all.
You can rely on me a a little.
That and cheating  someone's onii-chan.
with this opportunity...
was the first person who could make me feel at ease
really.
you still feel for her.
That's complex, I'm surprised.
It's been years.
So that was real love.
Maybe playboy Kyou-chan doesn't understand.
Really.
But even though it's like this.
To be with Akane right now.
Puts me at ease.
Akane I want to forget about her.
Like this, even if I repayed the debt.
Ok, I'll do whatever I can to help.
Kyou-chan
Ah, sorry about that.
Only Akane can do it.
Nobody else can.
Letting me see this so suddently.
I was unprepared for it even though we were childhood friends.
And
the first time.
Asato couldn't get big and failed.
Kyou-chan said it like it was my fault that he couldn't get it up.
If I become ecchi.
I can make Asato happy.
For Asato, I have to work hard too.
There is nothing to be ashamed of.
Ok
Does this really feel comfortable?
Sawamura will definantly be happy.
No!
You can't go overboard.
Unless your Asato, you can't.
I shouldn't be doing this.
This is bad for Asato.
This is just a message.
Like a real vibrator.
It's just a prop, it's not betrayal.
Yeah, but.
A vibrator like this,
although it's my body,
think of it as just a prop.
But you really can't go overboard.
You absolutely can't.
Only Asato...
I hate this.
It feels kind of....
Akane, good, continue.
Do it harder.
You can't, Kyou-chan
You can't touch that place.
There's so much sperm.
Such amazing momentum.
Akane should also cum.
You can't, Kyou-chan.
No! You can't do this.
Ah? Asato-kun.
Ayumi-san
Are you going now?
Yeah, today's a bit later.
Eh? Asato just got back now?
Aren't you a little early?
No, there's no rules so sometimes it's early, sometimes it's late.
So that's it.
Invite me over for a drink some time.
Onee-san feels lonely when single.
Ok
You're really not straightforward.
Well, since you're with Akane.
Not really.
But it's tough to be single.
Even if you start doing this during the day,
You have to control your voices.
See Ya!
During the day?
Akane, how's school?
What Asato?
Eh, ah, nothing.
Ah, we ran out of...
I'm going to the convenient store.
Ah, I'll go with you.
I was just going to buy something.
No, I'll go, Kamisaka you,
The owner of the house is here, you can't leave me alone here can you?
It's alright since it's night time.
You must be tired, right Sawamura?
Akane, please!
I can't hold it anymore.
No!
In this kind of place, what are you thinking?
Kyou-chan!
Stop this kind of thing.
Sawamura came home early.
One more time!
Hey, please!
What the?
I don't understand at all.
If I'm late Asato will...
I'll be done in a jiffy.
No!
We, can't
Absolutely not raw.
Hey, Kyou-chan.
Didn't we promise?
So.
Let's go buy it at the convenient store.
Shit, why wasn't there any.
I can't sleep like this.
Hey, please!
You can't Kyou-chan.
Akane's been also looking forward to this right?
No, Kyou-chan.
Didn't we say that kissing is off limits?
You can't...
Control your voice stupid.
Someone will hear.
Then stop this.
It'll be alright.
See, you're already wet.
Kyou-chan.
I beg you.
Shhh.
Hurry up.
People will come.
You can't hold it right?
You're like this.
This is only message.
One touch won't matter.
Shit, another.
Hurry.
No.
It's slippery.
Can't, like this.
It's shivering.
I shouldn't touch this but...
Why?
Akane
It feels great.
Kyou-chan
It feels more than usual.
This is semen.
It's Kyou-chan's smell.
They should be home by now.
Akane
Really, what am I thinking?
Maybe I'm too tired?
Shit
Ah?
This can't be real.
She went straight to sleep.
I couldn't hear anything.
Oi! Sawamura.
Today, I'm likely to have some overtime tonight, sorry.
Washing clothes right now? (I understand)
Kyou-chan's taste.
Today, he hasn't,
You can like it slowly tonight.
You should do it carefully.
I hate this.
If we continue this.
It should be only Asato.
Akane has become very skilled.
I'm jealous of Sawamura.
Asato will be happy?
You're great Akane.
Can you hear me?
No!
You can't.
If I'm too loud, I'll
Don't worry.
I won't touch it directly.
If you can bear it.
Kyou-chan
no
If this continues.
I'll be come more ecchi.
can't
Kyou-chan, aren't you coming yet?
I still can't make you comfortable like this?
Is it coming? Are you coming Kyou-chan?
So much!
Such momentum.
But it's less than yesterday.
No, if you touch there.
No Kyou-chan.
You can't.
Coming.
I'm coming!
No!
Why?
I shouldn't be doing this.
Is it because Kyou-chan is too skilled?
We shouldn't be doing this.
We absolutely can't, continue.
Asato has overtime again tonight.
Can't continue this.
Ky-Kyou-chan
No!
This is me and Asato's place.
Even if it's Kyou-chan
You can't.
Really.
Even though you've came so many times.
What are you saying now?
A no is a no!
Get out!
It should be alright right?
Forget about Sawamura.
What are you saying.
My only boyfriend is Asato!
What? It can't be.
We're kissing.
No!
Kyou-chan
We can't kiss.
We shouldn't.
Why Kyou-chan.
This is too much!
Why?
It's because I like you.
Like?
I love you.
Compared to him I can't forget about you Akane.
Kyou-chan.
But this kind of thing.
My boyfriend is Asato.
Kyou-chan is only a childhood friend.
Hmph.
Childhood friends don't give blowjobs.
They also don't do paizuri.
No matter how you see it, we're man and woman.
But Kyou-chan said it was just a massage.
You really thought that was a massage.
This, you had this in your mouth.
Got wet from a pervert.
Really lame reason.
Even Sawamura won't forgive you.
This kind of thing.
These erotic breasts.
Weren't they pleased to hold it?
No, Kyou-chan.
Stop it!
No!
What do you mean by no?
You're spilling all over.
No you can't!
I don't want this.
That place to be seen.
No!
Weren't you looking forward to this?
No! I was never looking foward to this.
Just being looked at and I'm so shy.
No!
You can't use your tongue.
No, Asato!
Being looked at, tongue's entering.
No!
You can't!
My mind's going blank.
You can't, I'm becoming wierd.
I'm being force, why is it
that my body's feeling good.
No, this is getting out of control.
I'm become very ecchi.
It should be only Asato.
Only Asato.
No! Stop sucking!
I'm going, coming!
You came gorgeously.
You're body has become perverted.
No!
Something's coming inside me.
You can't!
If I kiss with kyou-chan.
We can't do this.
We're only childhood friends.
What? Something large is coming in.
Kyou-chan's dick.
It hurts, kyou-chan stop!
why?
You can't.
You really can't.
It'll be done in a flash.
It's only a brief moment.
No
can't have sex with Kyou
only with Asato
Only this you absolutely can't.
No, No!
Absolutely no!
let me go Kyou
Ne, you can't.
No!
You can't continue Kyou-chan
Hey do you get it?
Kyou-chan
Akane
Do you really hate having sex with me?
Kyou
sorry
but I can't...
I'm Asato's
Really...
All the more reason not to stop!
It's a lie! It's in!
It's inside me!
Dick
Congratulations woman, it's mine!
No! no!
Liar, this isn't happening.
It hurts!, Kyou-chan!
Who gives a fuck.
Look, I'm going to cum inside!
No!
Kyou-chan, why?
Why are you doing this?
Shut up.
The sperm is flowing in.
This is a dream right?
Why isn't it Asato.
Ah, what?
I really liked this.
shucks.
Just a bit and more for the next train.
I'll use something else.
Akane!
That, hurts!
Ayumi-san!
Ah, it's Asato-kun!
Are you alright Ayumi-san?
really...
I'll lend you my shoulder.
Wait, Ayumi-san!
I can't breath.
really!
Who's fault is it?
That child too!
She was so loud at that time.
I didn't expect that.
Really.
You're going overboard.
You did it so many times.
So I'm going to get a drink.
Next time it's on you!
Ayumi-san, when was that?
When?
It was like that for the whole night!
really...
Akane! Where are you.
She couldn't have left so early in the morning.
It started last night.
Then what Ayumi-san heard might not have been this place.
No, but.
Shit
Where did she go.
No, let me go!
Wait Akane.
Akane? A fight?
It's my fault.
But try to understand my feelings!
Liar.
I'm different from the girls around Kyou-chan.
Asato's my only one!
How do I tell this to Asato?
You're so cruel, Kyou-chan.
But, I'm also.
Stop, kyou-chan.
I don't want to keep anymore secrets from Asato.
Don't worry.
There isn't anymore things.
Kyou-chan.
Translator: Kureha. K1 Productions http://kureha.gotdns.com/k1