Be more gentle.
You must not do this to Miyu...
I know.
Only I have to suffer something like this...
You just want to hog it all to yourself right?
Don't be silly
on this kind of level?
What a slutty expression
If an idol puts on this kind of expression, the fans are going to be disappointed.
No...
No!
You can't...
my ass...
What a pain
you feel it in your ass already?
As expected from a top idol
That's nice Leina
You've become experienced
He's about to cum
In my mouth again?
It's better to cum inside the mouth than on the face of an idol.
What an boring old guy.
Isn't this enough?
This is a Kureha One release: http://kureha.no-ip.org/k1/
Ep2: I......did it.
Miyu, was that real?
Why won't you tell me anything.
Do you dislike me now?
Ryouta-san wait a bit longer ok?
It'll be finished quickly.
Miyu, are you really ok?
Ryouta-san, I'm fine!
Didn't I say it yesterday too?
Yeah
Ryouta-san I'm going to change so could you get out for a min?
Um, Ryouta-san?
I'm going to change so could you leave like usual?
Ah, sorry, wait a sec.
Miyu
You're alright right?
Yeah, Miyu is full of energy, Ryouta-san
Miyu and Terada... with me at the end...
No
No, our fit is so comfortable.
There must be a reason.
Miyu
This might be annoying, but are you really fine like this?
Eh, Ryouta-san It's really fine.
Miyu won't tell me?
Um Miyu.
Miyu wha...
Nothing
I have to go shake hands with my fans early tomorrow so I'm going to sleep.
oh
Ara? Tendou san? Does it start today?
Yeah, today's shaking hands with the fans, and phase 2 comes next, before that...
Really hard eh?
Tendou-san are you tired?
I'm fine, I just slept late last night.
Ara, thanks for the hospitality.
Showing off your married life to me.
No, no, you have it wrong.
Leina I don't mean it that way.
It's no that.
Tendou-san?
Oh no, it's time.
See you next time Leina.
Yeah
Are you going to use this hand to shake with your fans?
What a great idol.
You're the one that wanted this.
I'll wash my hands properly.
An idol leaving all those people to give someone a blowjob during resting time?
Don't talk about it.
You should just do it with him, he'll be relieved that way.
How could I do such a thing.
You're the one that made me a woman.
You're about to cum right?
Cumming so much...
I still have to go shake hands with my fans.
I'm going to wash it.
Isn't it better to have a bit of semen? To those guys...
That would be too disrespectful to the fans.
They finally have a chance to come.
No!
In a place like this.
The firm is next door, they will hear you if you're loud.
Please stop.
This...
Miyu-san, it's almost time for the next thing, please get ready.
Ok, I'll get ready
I'll be waiting for you at the place earlier.
Ok, I understand, see you later.
Your talking voice wasn't right, you're getting excited from being seen aren't you?
That's not true!
Cum quickly!
I'm about to cum Miyu
He came inside again.
Miyu
greetting everyone in the shop?
Today's Miyu's handshake event right?
Yeah, she's so small and cute!
But I think she's acting too much.
I talked to Miyu during rest time.
Eh? Really?
but it was just to tell her the place.
That's all?
How boring.
But!
Eh? What? What happened?
There was this wierd smell.
What do you mean?
She was looking for a place to wash her mouth.
Wasn't the wash basin broken?
But that smell, yes it was the smell of that!
Do you mean "that" by that?
Yeah, it's the stuff that males shoot out.
That means it's that guy with the big beard right?
Yeah, I thought it was the manager but he just got here.
Is he from the firm?
Amazing! Idols are just different, to have to take care of feelings in that area.
She must love to do it, that cute face of hers.
Eh? Beard? It must be that guy, I should talk to Miyu about this.
Miyu
Eh? Ryouta-san? What did you want to talk about?
Miyu, to tell the truth...
About Producer Tereda...
Did something happen with Tereda-san?
Um...
I can't say it? Even though I'm already at this point.
Um Miyu
Ryouta-san? I understand.
There's nothing.
I won't let anyone besides Ryouta-san look at me.
Wait, Miyu, I'm not done talking.
Ryouta-san
Miyu
I've been holding it back for Ryouta-san.
I want to become one with Ryouta-san.
Ryouta-san please feel good.
Miyu's technique is so good.
Ryouta-san, does that feel good?
Miyu, um...
Ryouta-san's so good, it's up and hard again.
Ah, it's cumming
Ryouta-san you came again.
Um Miyu, today, um.
Ryouta-san, become one with me.
Sorry, Miyu, I'm tired today.
Is that so?
That can't be helped then, since you're tired.
I'll go wash my hands and go to sleep.
Good night Ryouta-san
When did you become like this? Miyu, you really are...
Is it Miyu again?
Ah, Leina.
She's the only one that can make you look like that.
What happened? You've been like this alot recently.
Miyu looks energetic to me.
Really? Probably...
There hasn't been a scandal or anything...
It's just that Miyu and I llive in different worlds.
We also have times when we feel disturbed.
So we want to use smiles to greet the people around us.
In this world, one can only believe in themselves.
If you who support Miyu is like this, then Miyu can't be relieved either.
Yeah! That's right!
Thanks Leina, I've come to a conclusion.
That was sudden.
Thanks to your blessing, I've found my answer.
I have to be clear with Terada-san.
Terada?
Finally, I have tomorrow off, I'm looking forward to going to school.
I'm not going to school tomorrow.
I have somethings to take care of, sorry.
What kind of things?
I just want to discuss somethings with the producer about the future.
Miyu-san's probably...
Really?
He had his position taken away by your grandfather.
Miyu's trying to protect my position...
Tomorrow is an off day right?
It's better not to tell Miyu about this.
yeah...
So Ryouta-san's not going to school tomorrow...
I understand, Miyu will be by herself.
If I don't clear this up...
Ryouta-san, I love you.
Excuse me.
Ah, Tendou-Kun!
and Leina-kun?
Tereda! I've heard from Leina about Miyu.
You actually did that to Miyu!
Oh really? Leina has already told you? Well that's that.
You grandfather messed me up good.
I'm finally at this position.
But you appeared before me.
You also let me pop an idol's cherry.
You've let me come to a peace.
You became hard when you saw me break her hymen right?
Are you not confident in your cock?
I think she wanted to get penetrated by you for a long time.
That's not true!
Miyu's not that kind of person!
Take back what you just said! Miyu's not at fault!
Don't make Miyu suffer anymore!
I understand, my anger is resolved anyways.
Because of me, in order to stay by me...
Miyu was, by you...
Yeah, if she didn't want to be by your side then this wouldn't have happened to her.
I intend to quit this industry.
So don't disturb Miyu anymore
Ah! I won't touch her anymore.
but you don't have to quit
Miyu became the number one idol thanks to your support.
I still need you two guys take care of my programs
I also want my programs to become popular.
That makes sense...
Miyu wanted to become the best idol.
She finally realized her dream.
I can't break her dreams because of something like this.
Please take care of us in the future... too.
That's nice, a boyfriend bowing to the guy who popped his girl's hymen.
Tendou-san are you alright?
I didn't think it'll become like this.
Ah, I'm alright, Miyu is probably hurt the most, I have to support her properly.
yeah, if you're by her side...
Let's head back to school, we can still make it.
Miyu's by herself too.
Ah, that's probably for the best, I'll just...
Thank you, Leina.
Miyu's feeling great!
Miyu-san you're being too sly.
I'm talking to you!
Ara? Leina-san?
Didn't you go back with Ryouta-san?
Didn't you also hear the discussion we just had?
It shocked me a little.
At the time he even saw it.
But he didn't say anything.
That person.
If he was human he would have been angry right?
His girl was being fucked.
Miyu
but he didn't say anything
He doesn't love me
He's just the dull headed kind of person that doesn't have any reaction no matter what happens to Miyu
I forgot my bag.
I'm going to cum, I'm feeling it to much!
My pussy's going to break.
Then what do you want Tendou to do?
He's...
this feels so good!
He can't satisfy me, the way he is now.
What? Are you trying to say that that cock is yours?
Yesterday, Miyu used her mouth a little...
his limit was only two times! Don't you think he's not fun?
Only this cock can satisfy my body.
So great!
Leina-san this cock is really great!
You can find your own sensitive spots now Miyu, you've graduated.
It feels so great!
I'm getting broken!
Please give me more special training from today on!
That's special training to Miyu?
Leina you should join in next time.
This is Miyu's special training.
It's Miyu's special training to make the trainer feel satisfied.
Ah, no! Miyu's cumming!
Cumming by herself.
no, lets come together
Miyu's cumming from producer's dick
Cumming!
Is that really Miyu?
Miyu...
Ah, It's Ryouta-san, what should I do?
Well, I'll just call back later.