Ahhh, no!
You can't, no, Kyou-chan!
You can't do this.
This is good
That's....
I want to see you doing it in this dress
Not before work
Can't do this?
If you play with that...
The gap in my panties...
It's because I keep blowing.
Don't blow, Kyou-chan
Translator: Kureha
No
Subbed by Kureha One Productions http://kureha.gotdns.com/k1
Kyou-chan's hard and hot.
Kyou-chan you can't do this, Asato's
No! If you keep pushing me...
You want to right?
That kind of thing...
Be more straight forward.
Kyou-chan, no
Oh no, my butts getting wet.
Asato, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
For me to feel like this
Asato's still at work
I'm doing this, with Kyou-chan.
No
As you wish.
I'm home.
Not here.
Come here.
So deep, Kyou-chan, no
To think that Asato hasn't touched you yet.
Thanks to that, I enjoyed the utmost hospitality
The hospitality of Akane's virginity!
No, Kyou-chan
Don't talk about Asato right now.
Did Akane go to work?
I have to say it.
Asato
That was close.
That's why I said no.
We really shouldn't be doing things like this.
Even though you're this wet?
No, no no!
Stop coming in with your penis.
This kind of thing.
So deep, no!
You can't enter that place.
The body is very honest isn't it
I'm picking up the pace.
I maintained it till now for Asato.
I don't want this kind of thing.
Kyou-chan's penis can't come in like this.
Watch me fill you up with semen.
No, I'll have a baby!
No, I'll be come pregnant.
Asato, sorry, I've become a woman.
Stop it, really!
You're completely wet.
Asato's masturbating? No way.
Maybe he's grown tired of you.
Why? Asato, to me?
Even though he's lover is here.
Kyou-chan, no.
Not good, if this keeps up you'll be abandoned.
Become lewd, to the point that he is inseparable from you.
Kyou-chan's dick is kissing my uterus.
Sticking it so deeply although Asato's right there.
I'm going to come in this kind of place, Asato's...
My pussy's being filled by Kyou--chan again.
Shit.
Akane, go sleep with Sawamura.
If you take the initiative, Sawamura will...
But, I'm already....
Close the lights and it won't be exposed.
You've already reluctantly done a lot for Sawamura's sake
What reluctantly.
Because, Asato's my lover.
Kyou-chan is...
What am I doing? I should make sure with Akane.
Thanks to that, I enjoyed the utmost hospitality
The hospitality of Akane's virginity!
Shit!
What, Akane?
Um, hey Asato
About Kamisaka?
Nothing.
No, to initiate it is a bit...
?
It's difficult for Akane if I don't take the initiative?
Akane
Um, no, nothing.
Asato's asleep.
Has he lost interest in me?
If that happens, I'll...
Kyou-chan, please...
Your body's honest.
In situations where you're doing lewd things that Sawamura can't see.
To become satisfied
That's not true, I'm not lewd.
I feel like this because Kyou-chan's strong and hard.
You've had countless sex with me and came countlessly.
You can't do without my dick now.
That kind of thing.
Ah, no! Even though I don't want it.
But to want Kyou-chan to come in me.
To give me a sense of strong and hard.
More!
I feel good! I love Kyou-chan's dick!
Stir me up with your dick!
So deep! The dick is even reaching those places.
The uterus is starting to want it.
Enjoy doing it with me.
No! My uterus isn't listening to me.
It wants to be combined with the semen from the dick.
Even though today is dangerous.
My womb is overflowing with Kyou-chan's semen.
You lover Sawamura is still at work.
What a bad girl Akane is, coming so many times.
Asato, I'm sorry.
Even though you're working so hard for the two of us.
I'm getting feelings like this.
Sawamura is doing overtime still believing that you're a virgin.
But you're being made into a complete mess with my dick.
No! Kyou-chan's dick is entering me.
The uterus tweets continuously.
Your pussy's desire to be fucked is making you unable to leave my dick.
You're dependent on my dick.
No! If you insert it so deeply.
I'll really become inseparable
wanting to have a dick inserted in me.
Kyou-chan these close are weird.
I wonder what Sawamura thinks of your lewd pussy.
No, Asato, that's not it, not it...
I was forced to feel like this by Kyou-chan.
To Akane's superb pussy is not Sawamura's clumsy sperm,
but my thick strong semen that is more appropriate.
Kyou-chan's dick is making my pussy feel great.
My uterus is making a pleasant noise.
Become pregnant with my handsome child, Akane!
Firmly grasp my dick with the depths of your womb!
No! I'm being inserted and making perverted sounds...
Although I only want to bear Asato's child...
Akane's perverted pussy keeps sucking and won't let go,
Watch me inject your womb with semen!
My stomach is getting mixed up.
If I get injected with massive amounts now...
I'll become pregnant with Kyou-chan's baby,
but, I want more!
Wait, wait a bit Kyou-chan.
No! Kyou-chan wait!
Wait, no!
No, I can't stop... no....
Not going home tonight either.
Shit.
Kyou-chan is a pervert, idiot.
Always making me do these embarrassing things
What am I doing? My lover's Asato...
But with Kyou-chan...
This can't continue.
Asato's the one I love.
Asato's also...
But when I'm thinking about Kyou-chan, I...
Asato, what should I do?
Welcome, Asato-kun, come in...
Hey, today's the day that Asato's coming back...
Sensei, now's not the time to be saying that.
Kyou-chan, really!
That's great sensei...
No! Asato's ...
Akane, forget about Sawamura
Kyou-chan?
It should be alright now...
What are you saying?
Lovers aren't like this.
That's because he was busy, now's...
He's probably noticed us by now...
Liar! How could....
He knows... If he loves you...
That guy's got a girl.
What are you saying Kyou-chan? Asato's?
To not touch his lover, and not mind even though there are other guys around.
Going out alone from morning to evening...
Liar! Asato wouldn't do something like that.
I situation is already evident, or he's an idiot.
No! Asato's
For a lover to feel like this for other men...
it's impossible to not notice.
What's not being noticed is something else...
Stop talking about Asato...
It's about time to recognize reality!
No!
That cant be! You're lying!
Kyosuke, you're....
Asato Onee-chan
Akane....
Are you recognizing the reality?
Kyosuke, what are you doing to my sister...
Onee-chan, shutup!
Akane?
Asato, what is this?
Weren't you living at work?
Uh, yeah...
Asato... are you...?
With the lover's sister eh? That's unexpected...
Akane, wait, I just took the metro back.
I had something to talk about with Ayumi so that's why...
So you had something to say... leaving me alone.
It's quite good right? Being with onee-chan.
Don't worry about me.
Akane, you....
Why don't onee-chan comfort Asato?
Akane, wait! It's a misunderstanding!
Sawamura! Leave Akane to me!
Maybe it's too late...
Hey! Don't make that kind of face! There's still time!
And the important part is from now on...
Eh- yeah...
We know that they do it roughly every night.
I didn't expect it to actually be Kyosuke...
So that's why you're making that face...
It's my fault... maybe she was too lonely...
If I tried harder....
Thank you for thinking about Akane like that...
Although it might be a bit messed up right now...
That child still loves Asato.
Right, I still love Akane too.
Ah~ I also want to be love like that by you.
Kamisaka!
Oh? You came back fast!
You could have enjoyed it longer.
but, even now, I still love Akane deeply!
Heh?
I'm sorry, but please stop it.
Akane should feel the same way as me.
Although you wanted to be cool, now's not really the time.
Wouldn't it be better to ask this kind of thing to the person herself?
A kane...
Kyou-chan's so hard....
Akane, your ex-boyfriend says he loves you.
He hopes you'll suck his dick.
Kyou-chan's dick is larger, harder and more reliable.
It makes my pussy feel great!
I prefer this side.
This dick tastes good...
Did you know Sawamura? Akane likes taking it to the root.
During the period that you weren't around...
She's become a woman that loves dick.
Oh crap, I'm going to cum again.
Akane, why are you doing all this for this kind of guy?
Not just the mouth, a lot has been injected in this place too.
My pussy has been changed by Kyou-chan's dick.
It's becoming big again.
With my pussy this time...
Wake up, Akane!
Onee-chan...
That guy isn't the one you love! Asato is!
Don't loose sight of yourself!
I....
It's alright now, Akane.
You wanted to use this child to pay off your debts?
Really, this is really something that an asshole cowboy would think up.
Why do you know... shit!
Akane!
It would have been perfect if you didn't come!
No other choice...
Kyou-chan?
Akane!
Kyou-chan, what is this?
I'm going to make money using you as a prostitute!
That's why I started this with you.
You're a very important commodity Akane!
I've also taken a dangerous step, come with me!
Geez, you're really an idiot, did you think we'll let you run?
Hirobe!
Long time no see! I wasted a lot of effort looking for you.
Asato, sorry, I.. I'm...
Akane, it's all right now, you don't have to worry anymore.
Asato! Asato!
Akane I'm so sorry for making you feel lonely
No, It's my fault for doing so many bad things to Asato.
It's alright, it's just a bad dream.
Asato!
Sorry.
Really.. Onee-chan...
Take your time!
A few months after that incident.
Her smile that was destroyed, came back.
The thing with Kyou-chan was very sad.
But indeed, Asato's the one I love.
Even if because of my body, I can't be satisfied.
As long as our hearts are linked....
that's all that matters.
Ryouta-kun, are you done?
let sensei see.
Ok, that's great! There's nothing left for sensei to teach you.
It's time to teach you other things.
Sensei, I...
Really, Ryouta-kun, if you are like that...
Sensei wouldn't be able to reject.
Leave it to sensei ok?
Great! Your dick's become hard.
Ryouta-kun
Ryouta-kun's dick is great!
It's stirring up inside of sensei!
Ryouta-kun, it's great!
I'm better than Asato nii-chan right?
Asato's always finishing so fast, he's no good at all!
Always finishing once even though it's just started.
I'll love you, sensei!
So intense! Ryouta-kun!
Sensei's almost there!
Ryouta-kun's shot everything inside my pussy.
Asato-kun didn't notice anything.
Akane's dependence on Kyosuke was extraordinary.
In particular, physically.
But, Asato just couldn't satisfy her.
The Akane I once knew is no longer...
Even so, she's still my imouto.
That's great Ayumi-san.
This kind of thing is obvious isn't it?
This is really our last time ok?
I know, I'll give Akane's video back to you.
So...
Having said that, did you see that just now?
It's already recorded properly.
Looked at it properly so that's why...
This kind of thing...
Ayumi-san, I'm going to reveal it, Akane's ero-video.
It should sell for a lot of money right?
I'm sorry.
Do you have anything else to say?
Um when I was watching Akane and Ryouta-kun's video...
I, started playing with my pussy.
You're really sister! Both wanting the cock.
No! This kind of thing!
You've be come sensitive here too.
That's not true!
That kind of place won't have feelings.
This doesn't feel good at all!
I... this kind of thing.
I like stubborn women you know...
What are you saying?
I'm not happy even if you say that.
I'll let you become happy then.
No, Ryouta-kun! Not there!
Not this kind of thing, no I'm coming!
Take it out Ryouta-kun, stop! No! stop!
Ah, Ryouta you came.
Today was at Ayumi's?
Asato nii-chan, welcome back.
Today was studying pro-wrestling and stuff like that with Ayumi-nee-chan
Ayumi-san really gives headaches.
Are you going back? Want to eat together?
Nah, I can't bother you all the time.
Asato-nii-chan is a really nice guy.
Really?
I think so, I'll come back next time.
Ah, be careful on the road.
(Real ultimate debauchery of tutor sisters)
This is great, it'll sell for a lot.
Lucky for me her boyfriend is an idiot.
There are people that are leaving more messages.
Mikami Family Restaurant Manager
Eh, not enough? I'll go for more exclusives next time.