Please Manager!
Let Miyu-chan come along to drink, thanks.
Hahaha... really...
Maybe next time.
You really protect Miyu-chan too much!
You still have to relax sometimes.
Ha ha, we'll go next time we have the chance.
Well, whatever, next time!
Thanks for your hard work.
Translator Kureha
The manager is so strict I can't go out and play right?
So troublesome.
Alot of invitations like this have turned up recently.
A Kureha One Presentation. kureha.no-ip.org/k1/
Don't stare at me like that, I'm getting embarrassed.
Ah, no I didn't mean anything.
Sorry
Part One 「Ineverwantedtodothingslikethis.
Ryouta-san, I'm back.
I'm sorry, it was my turn today.
We have to help each other when it's busy.
But I keep troubling you Ryouta.
This just shows that you're busy right?
I should say I'm happy I could help.
Thanks Ryouta-san.
Although after I became an Idol we don't even have time to struggle together.
Could you give me another special training?
Miyu
Ryouta-san
It's hot, and hard.
Even though an idol shouldn't be doing things like this.
Ryouta-san
So much is already coming out.
Ryouta-san I'll make you feel even better.
Ryouta-san Are you ready to come? It's ok.
Shoot it quickly.
Amazing, you came so much.
No, don't look over here.
Even though you were just so erotic.
I'm so embarrassed/
Ryouta-san
I have a test tomorrow, so we can't be together.
Miyu, I'll always be by your side.
From now and on.
Ryouta-san, I want to be by your side.
Everything will be fine.
Ryouta-san is having his finals.
I need to also give my best.
Dirada-san, thanks for your hard work.
Good afternoon Miyu.
Do you have some time?
Yes
No, nothing.
It's fine like this.
O-ok...
It'll be over quickly.
Ryouta
Do you best on the test
Miyu will do her best too
Hmph, really.
Your nose is long, just like a pervert.
Lena, so you're here today too.
Yes, I finally have time off.
Miyu-san still has some work to do right?
Yeah, recording, because it overlaps with the test, she can't take off.
A manager's job is hard too.
Miyu's giving her best so it's not too hard.
Ahya? So scary.
Wait...
The pure idol Miyu, doesn't have this kind of rumor at all.
Everyone knows Miyu's well protected by her manager.
But still, be careful, Tendo-san
because alot of people have their eyes on Miyu
If you aren't careful in this industry, you'll trip easily.
Well if you protect her as her lover, I think there won't be a problem.
Ah? Your lover sent a message?
Maybe she's jealous of us on the other side of the phone.
Thanks for your hard work.
Ryouta-san...
You look tired, are you ok?
I'm fine.
I feel much better after seeing Ryouta-san.
Then, let's go home
Ohya? Isn't that Miyu and Tendo?
Thanks for your work, Producer Dirada
Sorry, Tendo-kun.
The discussion took a while.
It's alright.
Thanks for having us.
Please let us do a bit of everything.
Yeah ok.
Hey, Miyu greet him.
Thanks for your work.
Although it'll be hard from now on, and further discussions.
We will give it our best!
Then see you next time.
So that's Dirada-san, the one who does the discussions.
We'll be even busier from now on.
Ryouta-san, let's go home quickly.
Miyu, if you don't get some clothes on you'll get a cold.
Miyu, did something happen?
Ryouta-san, I finished taking a bath.
Ah um no, the way you are now...
Ah, no! I came out like this.
Ryouta-san, you can't look this way.
w-wait...
Thanks for working hard.
Thank you, Ryouta-san
This is all thanks to Ryouta-san.
Oh yeah there is still the talk with the president.
I'll be right back.
Ok, I'll be waiting here Ryouta-san
Well the guy who likes to get in the way is gone.
Do you need something?
Please don't be like this.
This is mutually beneficial.
As long as your attitude is good, everything will be just fine.
If you're an adult, you should understand.
Huh? Miyu?
Miyu!
Ryouta-san!
Sorry, I had some important things to talk about so I borrowed Miyu.
Oh...
But, please tell me next time.
I'll notify you in advance next time.
Sorry, Ryouta-san
To discuss while I'm not around, Miyu you're too naive.
Because many people have their eyes on Miyu
Although I think there isn't anything.
But if there is something that I don't know, I won't be able to save you Miyu.
Ryouta-san
Miyu doesn't know about the world.
Lena is also worried about you.
hmmph? Ryouta-san is only worried about me after Lena-san said something?
Huh Miyu! I'm really worried about you.
What are you worried about?
You're only worried because Lena-san said something.
That isn't being worried about me at all isn't it?
What are you saying?
I'm saying Miyu doesn't have a sense of danger.
That's not true.
I at least know a bit about this industry.
Senpai got caught with drugs and was sent to a strip show and things like that.
I know of those dangers.
Miyu I'm really worried about you, stop fooling around.
Don't be nosy.
I'm happy about Ryouta-san's feelings.
I was too rash today.
Miyu, I'm sorry.
To tell the truth, when I see you standing with Dirada-san...
Ryouta-san that means...
Ryouta-san I'm, I'm Ryouta-san I'm happy.
Ryouta-san
wow.
Tendo-san　Miyu-san
How dare you pretend to be not at home when this lady comes to visit.
Did something happen?
Because of that thing earlier
You seemed abnormally bothered by it so I came, but it looks like you're doing fine.
Lena-san thanks for caring.
but wouldn't you be better off worrying about yourself?
I don't think I've been seeing you around recently.
Miyu
Oh yeah, Miyu
I'm don't really have the time to worry about the likes of you.
Then, see ya.
What happened Miyu? Lena came because she was worried.
S-sorry.
Remember to properly apologize next time.
Miyu, this is great, let's go with this.
Ok
Oh Tendo-Kun!
Producer Dirada, thanks for your hard work.
You look more and more like a proper manager.
Thanks for the compliment.
Well, see you at the next meeting.
Yes, thank you.
Miyu, someone will come in here.
Ryouta-san, please let me be like this for a while.
Miyu, it'll be fine, I'll always be with you.
Ryouta-san
Are you alright?
Eh? yes, I've calmed down.
Miyu, your face is red, do you have a cold?
No.
Well, that's good.
Then, I'll go attend the meeting.
Please come back quickly.
Sorry to interrupt.
That's wierd, Dirada-san should be here.
So many machines, so the message was sent from here.
This is, even the backstage has cameras installed?
Not good, someone could have seen...
Oh? This is the wrong place.
Really... tell me properly.
Eh? Why doesn't it open, hey! Is anyone there? hey!
Oh yeah, I'll call Miyu and tell her to come.
Wait.. Miyu, acting? Hey, Miyu! Miyu!
Why, this kind of thing.
Shit.
Miyu, Someone! Someone!
Miyu, why? Run!
Miyu, resist and run away! why?
Miyu
Miyu, pick up the phone Miyu!
Miyu, hurry and pick up Miyu
Oi Dirada that damn bastard.
Miyu
Miyu Miyu Miyu Miyu!
Please stop.
Can't hold it anymore right? I actually have a lot of experience.
I've memorized by heart the method for people like you.
How long can you hold it in?
I can't do anything about it, I have to do it for Ryouta-san.
Oh really? This kind of Miyu is also cute, I'll end this quickly just like you wanted.
What a great view, Miyu.
Aren't you already completely wet?
Hurry up and end it. Ah, Ryouta-san's calling, what should I do?
Why don't you just pick up? What are you worried about?
This embarrassing feeling.
Is this ok?
Please hurry and end this, I want to go to Ryouta-san's side
Miyu, are you a virgin?
So what if I am? End this quickly.
Hahahaha, I thought you've already done it with Tendo.
Miyu turn your butt towards me, it'll be less painful if we do it like this.
No!
Ryouta-san I'm sorry.
This is great! Miyu's insides.
You just lost your virginity and you're already feeling it inside, you're so sensitive.
No! Not like this!
No, No!
No! You cant!
Miyu I'm going to shoot out all that I saved up in you.
No! wait!
No! Not inside! No!
No! No!
No!
It's leaking out of my pussy, I have a secret I can never tell Ryouta-san.
Miyu!
Ryouta, are you finished?
Tendo-kun I think you went to the wrong room.
Sorry, we'll talk more later, see you later Miyu
See you next time.
Ok
The thing between your legs is rising.
Miyu...
Hmmn? Ryouta-san what?
Ryouta-san, let's quickly head home.
I'm really tired today.