Ah, that feels good.
My senses are going crazy.
You become fascinated when you're molested, huh, Kanon?
My name...
Why did you come to where l was?
Because l saw your molesting this morning?
Or is it fate?
Who are you?
Fate?
You say such a funny thing.
l guess because it was decided from that day.
That day?
l'm the existence that showed up to make you fall all the way to the bottom.
You're all going to take the punishment for your crime.
Kanon?
Kanon! What are you doing!
You finally woke up?
Sis, you wouldn't wake up fast enough.
That's why l was having Mr. Kouichi do it to me.
Stop doing such a stupid...
What?
Hold on, what is this?
Hey you, stop fooling around and untie me!
What a loud woman.
Damn it...
l'm not fooling around.
Hold tight a little longer.
Next up after your little sister is you.
l'll make sure you can never talk to me like that...
...by totally messing you up!
You are horrible!
Even if you do such a thing, it's no use!
You already did me so many times.
Regardless of what you do now, it's all going to be the same!
Even though you...
...did such a horrible thing to me!
Something to that degree...
You were actually enjoying that, weren't you?
You want me to do you too, right?
Don't say such a stupid thing!
Don't talk like l'm a pervert!
Hey, Mr. Kouichi...
We're not done yet.
To me too...
Please do what you did to my sis right here too.
All right.
Show it off to your sister as much as you like.
Kanon, do you know what you're saying?
Stop it!
Please don't do it.
Hey Kanon, please...
lt's coming into my butt...
lt's coming into my butt!
lt hurts, it hurts!
Hey Kanon, if you take in what your sister says...
...you have turned into a pervert!
lt hurts, it hurts...
My butt hurts!
More in my butt...
Put it in deeper!
Here we go!
lt's all the way in!
Wh-What is this really...
lt's good...
lt feels so good!
Man, your little sister is so honest.
This can't be...
Kanon, what happened to you?
Why would you ever do this with a man like him?
lt's amazing, Kanon!
Front and back are both mine now! How is it?
Y-Yes...
l'm all yours, so please pound me more!
Okay! Let's show your sister more!
Yes!
l'm going to go crazy...
Sis, can you see the dick?
lt's in my butt.
lt's in really deep.
How is it, Sis?
Hey, Kanon. l'm going to come soon.
Move more.
Yes...
But, l can't take it anymore...
Nothing can be done. l'll help you.
No, no, no!
No, no...
l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
l'm going to come...
l'm going to come!
Kanon...
Let's see...
What?
Don't come near me!
You...
lt happens that you saw your sister and wanted to do it too?
There's no way for something like that...
You did that much to my sister, so aren't you satisfied already?
So how is it?
As l thought, you're a little bit there.
lsn't that right, Sister?
l didn't do the front yet.
Don't.
Don't, don't!
lt's unfair if it's just your sister, right?
Here you go!
No, don't get turned on...
No, not to a guy like this...
Ah, no, it's turning me on...
Hey Kanon, don't!
No.
Sis, it's because you won't reflect on your mistakes that easily.
Seriously...
Here, l'll make you feel better, so reflect on your mistake truthfully!
l understand, l understand.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry, l'm sorry!
l-l'm the bad one, so please...
So please hurry and pour it inside me!
lt's hot!
lt's good...
One like this...
lt's my first time...
Now Nao is in our group too.
Here, souvenir photos.
Hey, button up your shirt. lt's indecent.
Okay!
Oh yeah, next is Kyoko!
But before that, l'm going to go shopping with Mr. Kouichi.
So Sis, you can go home before me!
Thank you very much.
Did you find something you liked?
You want that?
Well aren't you a little nympho...
What are you going to do with something like that?
This is my choice.
With this, your sisters will all be happy.
Kanon.
Yes...
Then l will see you again on the weekend.
l'm home.
Where's Kanon?
She won't be coming home.
Not coming home?
Did something happen?
That guy...
He's dragging Kanon around!
Who do you mean by that guy?
That molestation guy!
Are you serious?
l was...
l was also violated...
lt can't be...
Sis, you're being targeted too.
We need to call the police...
We need to call the police... l'm home!
Sis, l'm sorry.
l'm late.
Kanon, you're safe?
Of course.
l'm fine already.
So Sis, you too...
You!
Good evening, Sister.
You... Why are you here?
Why?
Wh-What is going on, Nao?
l'm sorry, Sis.
l don't have a choice but to do this anymore.
Sister Kyoko...
Sis, you have to pay for your crime.
Right, Mr. Kouichi?
Yeah, that's right.
Sis...
Atonement feels really good.
No!
Seriously...
lf someone did this much to you normally, wouldn't you wake up?
Maybe she was in too much shock.
Right, Kanon?
Most likely...
l guess it's because Sis is excessively nurturing me.
Sister Nao leaves me alone.
Right, Sister Nao?
That looks great on you.
So, shall we start over here too?
What are you doing?
Don't! Stop it!
You finally woke up?
How carefree.
You think you're going to get off scot-free doing something like this?
l'm going to call the police!
How are you going to call them in a situation like this?
Ask your little sisters.
Kanon! Nao!
What are you girls doing?
Why are you both doing something like that too?
l told you before.
You have to pay for your crime.
Mr. Kouichi forgave Sister Nao and me already!
That's why it's yourturn now, Sister Kyoko.
This can't...
So that's the story.
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
You get turned on easily.
What a sister...
Sh-Shut up.
What are you saying?
How is it, Sister Kyoko?
Mr. Kouichi is really good at making girls feel good.
lt's my turn.
l'm going to feel good with Sister Nao.
lsn't this amazing? l found it earlier.
There's a small one in there, but we can leave it, right?
Amazing...
Something like this really does go in.
lt's really kind of perverted, Sis.
l kind of want to do it now too.
So, what should l do, Sis?
They're all excited over there already.
Why don't you start too?
You want me to put it in?
l changed my mind.
Why?
Are you going to forgive me with this?
You got to be kidding...
lt means l'm not going to do it for you!
On top of that, you think my anger is going to simmer down with just that?
l was sued for something that l didn't even do to you guys!
l lost my wife, my job, everything!
That's why l'm going to have you guys experience the same thing.
l'll make you lose yourjob!
And your family! No, your lover too!
What l lost won't come back anymore!
That...
Really?
l don't know anything about that.
That's why it's a sin!
As long as l can have revenge, l don't care what it is.
l am already dead as far as society is concerned.
Then this is punishment for our own sins?
That's right. That's why we're doing this.
Right, Sis?
Hey, does it feel good?
Mr. Kouichi taught me a little bit.
So...hey!
Do you finally understand?
No...
Why?
l put a lot of jelly on the vibrator before that's going to make you feel good.
The truth is you can't hold it in anymore, right?
That's right, it's time for you to pay for your sin!
Sister Kyoko finally understands?
Then l have to do my best too.
Alley-oop.
You think this will go inside me too?
lt's amazing!
lt's opening up really wide!
This is agonizing.
l feel like something is going to happen to the inside of my stomach!
How is it, Sis?
How is it?
Kanon! Please forgive me...
l'm about to come.
This fat vibrator is stirring up the inside of my pussy and l feel like...
...l'm going to become stupid!
Me too...
My pussy, my pussy is about to...
Why don't you become honest too, Older Sister?
Here l go at full force then!
lt... lt...
...feels good!
Really, does it feel that good?
What do you want to do? l can stop here if l wanted to!
No...
No, no, no...
No, no...
Until the end...
...when you pour all your semen inside me and it comes out.
Pound me, pound me...
lt's coming! lt's coming!
Something is coming!
Me too!
Me too! l can see something!
Yes, a country...a country of angels.
l can see heaven!
With this...with this, we're going to be forgiven!
l'm coming!
Hey wait, Mr. Kouichi.
Thank you so much.
Why are you thanking me?
lf l commit a sin again, please punish me again.
ls that so?
Yes!
See you again, Kanon.
Master...