lt's almost time.
l'm home!
She's home.
Earlier than usual.
l'm home, Ayu-niichan!
Hi lzuru, welcome home.
The Sex Exchange 2
lzuru, you're going to do it like always, right?
She just got home.
Stupid Ayu-nii and dumb lzuru!
lt's good that the only thing l can feel is your nipples.
What do you mean by that?
Are you saying l have no boobs?
You can't deny it right?
That's not true.
My boobs got bigger because l gained some weight.
You can't tell because you look at them everyday!
Really?
lt doesn't seem like they changed much.
Forget you!
l'm sorry lzuru.
l just didn't want to think you're gaining weight.
Yeah, it's okay.
No Ayu-niichan...
lt's too sudden...
Sorry, l just can't be serious all the time.
But it's okay right?
l'm making you all sticky like this.
You don't hate it, right?
l like it but...
l wanted to feel embarrassed.
Who cares?
lt's not like us to think that hard.
Let's just leave that to Kokone.
Those idiots are doing it each and everyday.
Besides, lzuru and l feel the same way.
lt's wet...
Ayu-niichan...
My cunt feels so good!
lzuru, you can say it out loud if it feels good.
But then again, you're already loud.
Ayu-niichan...
l...l...
l can't hold it anymore! l have to pee!
l...
l have to go too...
Playing with myself like that stupid lzuru...
l'm coming...
l'm coming!
lt's not fair lzuru, you climaxed by yourself.
l want you to make me climax too.
Okay, okay...
lt's big, hard, and amazing.
l'll give you a handjob.
Wait, lzuru, l'll climax quickly if you do that.
Do it with your mouth.
Do l have to do everything for you?
lt's bitter.
No matter how many times l do this,
l just can't get used to the taste.
She made me climax so easily.
Now, now, don't be disappointed.
lt's just that l'm really good at this.
lzuru, you're such a good girl.
Stupid lzuru.
She took it in her mouth again.
Hey lzuru.
Do you want me to stick it in?
Do you?
Hurry up and stick it in.
Oh lzuru!
You're so cute!
Will you just hurry up?
l want it real bad too, you know.
Okay, okay.
Your cock is amazing!
lt feels so tight inside you.
l feel like l'll climax everytime l stick it in.
Don't !
l haven't climaxed yet.
There.
lt feels weird in my stomach...
How is it weird?
Your cock feels so hot inside...
And then...
Yes...
Your cock feels so good!
One more finger...
lf l keep doing this...
...l'll end up stupid like lzuru!
lt's so tight and feels good inside you...
Plus you're moving your hips...
This is what you...
...taught me remember?
You're right but...
But we have to finish with
your favorite from the back...
That's not true...
No!
l...l'm coming...
l'll climax with your cock inside me!
Me too...
l'll release it deep inside you like always...
l'm coming inside...
Ayu-nii... Ayu-nii...
l...l...
l'll climax with your cock!
Hey lzuru.
Don't bother me when l'm reading.
You idiots!
You come home and make all these loud noises!
l have an English exam tomorrow!
l can't study when you people are so loud!
This room blocks out most noises,
so l don't think you can hear us.
l didn't make that much noise either.
Maybe you were...
What is it?
Spying on us by placing your ear against the wall.
You wanna join us? Come on!
Yeah, she can be one of us from now.
Yay! She's one of us!
She's one of us! She's one of us!
ldiots!
She was pretty mad.
Yeah.
Kokone, can l come in?
Hello?
What do you want?
Can l borrow your notes from English class?
l'm gonna study a little.
Hold on.
Thanks.
Actually, the exam is mixed with
the first part and the second part.
And the important sentence constructions are taken from the second part.
Hey Kokone, can l come in?
Sure, l bathed for a good amount of time.
Enjoy.
Kokone, are you asleep?
l woke up since you came in.
What do you want?
Can l sleep next to you?
Kokone, are you asleep already?
l'm still awake.
Are you still angry?
Kokone?
l'm not angry so let me sleep.
l'm glad.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're sleeping like a baby.
Ouch.
Great.
l feel so stupid for doing all this.
Also, about Ayu-nii...
lzuru, does it feel good?
You're so wet.
Feels so good...
How is it?
Wow...
Yes, Ayu-niichan, right there...
You're so wet.
lzuru...
Here l come.
Amazing...
ls it good?
lzuru, it feels tight and good...
You're the best!
Keep moving more...
l'm gonna climax...
lzuru...lzuru...
l'm coming!
lt's not fair lzuru.
l like Ayu-nii too...
l want him to do lots of naughty things with me...
Ayu-nii!
l'm the one who's stupid.
Doing all these things...
l should go to sleep.
lt's almost time.
l'm home!
Are they going to do it again?
l'm home Ayu-niichan!
Hi lzuru, welcome home.
Huh? What the? Why?
Ayu-nii, well um...
What is it?
Where's lzuru?
She's right there.
What is the meaning of this?
You know?
Yeah.
Could it be...
You know?
Yeah.
l knew it!
l heard you masturbating with great
intensity, so we decided to help you out.
Since we're good siblings.
But this is just too much!
You're all embarrassed.
Are you insane?
Now, now.
We now know how you feel.
This guy too?
Looks clean since it hasn't been messed with.
Ayu-nii, stop it...
l feel embarrassed...
Why are you doing this?
Because l wanted to do this.
You knew what was coming when
your lower part was exposed right?
What...
Bon appetit!
No!
Stop sucking that spot!
You're so cute, Kokone...
No...
l'm coming too...
Your nipples are getting hard too.
Are you ready now?
You're not thinking of sticking your cock inside me...
You know l'll do it.
You can do it, Kokone!
Try to relax.
l'm doing this because l like you.
But...but...
l want you to be gentle with me.
Sure.
Kokone, here l come.
Ouch!
Kokone...
But it really hurts!
l see.
Sorry.
lt hurts, it hurts!
Stop it Ayu-nii!
This really hurts!
Ouch!
Kokone, are you ready?
Yeah.
Somehow it feels good.
Ayu-nii, it's starting to feel a little better.
lzuru also likes to take it from the back.
l kind of like it too.
But at times like this, l don't
want you to compare me to lzuru...
You're also a girl after all.
Cute.
lt's going in very deep...
lt's hitting the spot and it feels good...
You're moving your hips on your own...
Very naughty...
Right now, you're all mine right?
Kokone...
Wait Kokone, you're moving too fast...
l'll climax...
But my hips just move on their own!
Your cock is moving deep inside me...
lzuru...
Me too...
But you see...
Look.
Let's switch Kokone.
No!
Come on.
Because of you, l was hurting a lot.
You're too selfish.
You've been doing it with Ayu-nii all this time.
Give it a break.
What did you say?
lf l didn't plan this for you, you'd still be masturbating while Ayu-niichan and l have sex!
Meanie!
That's not a nice thing to say!
Don't say that even though you're an idiot!
Whatever!
My hips are moving...
Somehow l can feel your sensations deep inside...
Ayu-niichan, we love you!
Let's go for round 2!
Sorry, but l have to study for an exam.
Sorry, but l can't afford to
get a failing grade this time.
See you!
Huh?
What the?