Perfect Cantaloupes
Kanami Yotsuba
l-l'm embarrassed...
Yoichi...
Kanami, we're husband and wife now.
H-Husband and wife...
Kanami, you're so cute...
But these breasts are the best part of you.
No, don't look!
That's impossible.
Kanami, your breasts are so sensitive.
No, they're not...
lt's how you touch them, Yoichi...
No, not like that!
Kanami...
l want to keep on enjoying this sensation forever, but...
No!
You're so beautiful, Kanami.
Not in this position...
You can see it! You'll be able to see it!
See what?
l-l can't say... Yoichi, you're so mean...
Kanami, you became a mean guy's wife, so you should give it up.
Y-Yoichi...
Here l go.
l can feel your hardness inside me.
Yoichi...
We've become one.
lt doesn't hurt?
l'm fine. You can move.
Yoichi...
lt feels really good, Kanami.
For me too...
Yoichi, please play with my breasts more!
Something's coming... l feel like l'll go crazy...
lt's so tight!
l can't hold on anymore! l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
Me too, Kanami...
lt feels so hot...
You're bursting inside me...
Your semen is pouring inside, Yoichi.
This much...
Kanami...
Yoichi...
l hope we can make babies soon.
Yeah.
Lascivious Cantaloupes
Kaho Hamamatsu
Safe!
Thank you, Yoichi!
Kaho, barely making it again?
l can't help it. Being a nurse is hard work.
Yeah, yeah.
So how'd it go, Yoichi?
Did it go well with Kanami last night?
Well, yeah...
''Yeah'' is so vague.
She's my cute little sister, so please make her happy.
l'm well aware of that.
This is an emergency suspension due to a blackout.
There is an official on the way, so please wait momentarily.
They're not coming.
lt's so hot...
lt is...
l can't deal with it anymore!
Oh, l want to take this off, so look the other way.
S-Sure.
You don't have to bear it. Just take it off.
No, l'm fine still...
You're overdoing it.
You're sweating so much.
Oh, is this part hot too?
Looks like l should bring down the heat here too.
l knew it was big.
l'm sure it was hard for Kanami if her first time was with this.
W-What do you mean by ''l knew it''? How would you know something like that?
Kaho...
l'll check it out thoroughly so that you and my cute little sister don't divorce...
...out of sexual incompatibility.
Y-You don't have to worry about that...
lt's so good... l feel like l'm going to come already...
Oh, then the finish should be...
Y-Yoichi...
You're so big and hard. l love it...
lt's...
lt's so hot!
The Slow Girl's Cantaloupes
Tomako lnukaya
Chief, l'll start with my breasts...
Yours is so big.
On top of that, it's really hard.
You're so dirty, Tomako.
Please don't say such things.
So good...
Do you do this every night to your husband too?
l can't do a dirty thing like this to him...
So how's his compared to mine?
Please don't make me say such things...
Even so.
Well...
Yours...
Tomako.
C-Chief...
C-Chief, you have a wife...
You have a husband too, so...
...we're even!
There's a big one inside me...
lf you do that to my breasts...
lt feels so good!
Honey, l'm sorry.
lt's so good l think l'll go crazy!
lt's becoming tighter and tighter...
l'm going to come... l'm going to come, Chief!
Looks like you'll be coming soon.
C-Chief?
C-Chief, what are you doing?
C-Chief, why are we in a place like this?
N-No!
Look, Tomako.
Your dirty breasts keep on coming out.
The copy machines are connected throughout the company's network.
All the copy machines throughout the building...
No!
Everyone's going to see my breasts...
l'm so embarrassed just imagining it that my pussy is going numb!
No!
Everybody, don't look at it!
l-l can't hold it in anymore!
lnnocent Cantaloupes
Mia Hiiragi
Here l go, Mia.
No! lt hurts, and it feels so good!
Yes!
More... Hit me more!
That's amazing...
Something like this really turns you on...
Big brother...
Use the dildo next...
Please give me the dildo!
Okay.
S-So good!
Mia, it's not fair that only you get to feel so good.
Then please use my breasts!
Then l'll take the offer.
Yours is so thick!
lt's so soft around me, but it gets tightened...
lt's good!
Big brother!
l'm coming!
l-l'm coming! l'm coming!
Thank you for the meal...
Little Devil Cantaloupes
Amana Yamabuki
Um...
Amana?
Hey, Amana!
My insides are filled with your thing, Yoichi.
lt's spread wide all the way to the back!
lf you're going this far, l can't just hold back.
Y-Yoichi?
This time, l'm going to make you feel good, Amana!
My breasts are going to be squished!
Amana!
lt feels good!
My breast milk is going to come out!
l can't hold on...
Yoichi, your dick feels so good l'm going to come!
Me too, Amana...
lt feels too good...
lt's pouring out...
Yoichi's semen...
lt's hot... lt's so hot...
l'm home...
Man, l'm beat.
Welcome home, honey!
Yoichi, tonight too, okay?