Mother is now working at this mansion too.
She was greatly perplexed with money and...
...when she was trying to have an interview with a sex industry shop...
...Ms. Reiko found her and brought her here.
Ms. Reiko suggested to Madam for her to work here...
...at the mansion and repay her debt...
...and Madam just approved it without any objection.
But for some reason...
...once this was decided that Mother become part of this mansion...
...Ms. Reiko all of a sudden was in a bad mood.
l didn't know what kind of relationship Mother and Ms. Reiko had, so...
...l didn't know what to do.
But l myself had a problem that had to be solved.
lt is where my feelings are.
How regrettable...
Having your beloved son's virginity floating away with a kite.
Mother!
Even if you go after her right now...
...it's not like Madoka will take care of that tempered penis of yours.
But l will.
You understand, right?
What am l doing?
Why didn't l go after Mother that time?
l finally got to be reunited with her.
More than being reunited with Mother, has Ms. Reiko's technique...
...stolen away my body and soul?
Have her five fingers' tender movement...
...the exquisite use of her tongue...
...and the intense pain from the whipping captivated me?
lf l think about it that way...
...then even these swelling scars from the whipping feel precious.
Nevertheless, that finger movement of Ms. Reiko's.
Just remembering it makes my penis...
Ryo, what's with this?
Are you trying to hide from me?
M-Ms. Fumi...
What is this?
Come in.
Fumi, thank you for your work.
As for you, Ryo...
...today l thought up a new clever idea for a change.
l-ldea, huh?
That's right, a very interesting play.
l never thought Madam was the type that would wish for that type of play.
l myself had an idea of whom l was going to be servicing.
My heart was beating like a fast bell and then...
l felt a larger quantity of blood being sent to my penis than usual.
For that my penis was...
Yes, there, Ryo.
Crouch down there.
Right in front of your face is your servicing area.
That's right, just like l taught you.
You're doing it well, aren't you?
Just watching it turns me on.
Ryo, this girl is delighted by the use of your tongue.
She's going to come soon.
You have to drink up the urine without leaving a drop as l taught you.
You are the lady's exclusive toilet.
Now penetrate this female pig like Fumi with that tough one of yours.
Ryo, you were a virgin just a short while ago, but you're so good.
You're such a good boy.
When l came here, l comprehended with my head and body...
...who l'm penetrating right now.
But l can't call that person's name.
ln front of Madam and Ms. Fumi watching us...
...and the fact that a parent and her child are having sex...
...is an unbearable humiliation.
l can imagine that Mother herself is keenly feeling that.
Then l'm sure l would be told to just stop the hip movement.
But the happiness of mingling with Mother...
...and also the excitement of Madam and Ms. Fumi watching...
...is putting me into an uncontrollable state.
That is a more intense power than you think it is!
Mother...Mother!
Ryo...Ryo!
Your penis is already an adult!
An adult penis!
Ryo's adult penis is...
The two who were separated by society seek one another.
This is primitive romantic love!
Ryo and Madoka, you are both lovely!
Mother, it's going to come out. l'm going to let it out!
Ryo, let it out! l want Ryo's baby!
l want to become pregnant!
We are an eternal family!
Mother...
Don't come!
Ryo, l'm sorry.
Just for a little while, okay?
The sky is so clear, but my heart will not clear.
l let my sexual urge take over me, and it's natural that l hurt Mother, but...
What kind of face am l supposed to make when l see her?
The one thing that is clear is that Mother has the same type of feeling.
The words that came out of Mother's mouth during the climax...
The words saying she wanted my child...
l want Ryo's baby!
But there's something else.
Madam's facial expression...
After a screwed up feast, is it prostration?
But there's something different.
lt was a look that she's never shown before.
lt sounded like it came from Ms. Reiko's room.
Ms. Reiko, l have told you from the start.
l am the master of this house, not you.
That's true, but just because of this woman...
Whatever reasoning you have, l am absolute in this mansion.
N-No...
Madam, it's fine. lf it's about me...
Keep your mouth shut! l'm not doing this just for you.
Humans are beings with social rules.
And in this mansion, l am the rule.
Those humans that cannot abide by me are...
Sister...
You're not planning on chastising me, are you?
You are already not a human of this household.
An outsider has harassed my servant.
l'm sorry...
l didn't think you were going to get this mad, so please forgive me!
No, as the master of this house, l must punish you.
Ryo, take your clothes off and get naked.
Yes, Madam.
Sister, please forgive me.
l don't have the ability to comprehend what a dog is saying.
Ryo, hurry and enter that filthy female dog's anus.
No, Ryo, please forgive me!
l will apologize about Madoka, okay?
l know, l'll pay Madoka's debt for her instead.
The only thing you have is a large amount of debt, right?
Your intentions for coming here this time was for the property, right?
l know that this past year your business hasn't been doing well.
Your secret intentions have already been predicted!
Come now, Ryo, hurry up and do it!
Y-Yes...
lt hurts!
lt's painful, Sister!
Reiko's butt is warm...
...and the root gets squeezed tightly while the back is winding, right?
Ryo, you want to move it, huh?
lt's okay, you can pound her intensely!
You can't. lf you do such a thing, l will break apart.
Ryo, why are you hesitating?
You can grind and violate as much as you want!
No, Ryo!
You have to pound more intensely!
Yes...
S-Stop it!
lt hurts, it hurts!
No, you can't! Don't come! Please don't stimulate my big clitoris.
Ryo, it's good. lf you do that, the pain softens. l...l...
Hey, Reiko is turned on easier than l thought.
l can feel Ryo's thing getting bigger while gouging my rectum...
Ryo, l know, you're going to come, right?
Make your penis pulse and squirt it right into me!
While you're being raped and humiliated, you orgasm, huh?
The punishment that was given to Ms. Reiko escalated as the days went on.
lt wasn't just physical agony.
She had her human dignity snatched away completely.
lt had to have been intolerable humiliation for Ms. Reiko who's full of pride.
Even for me who doesn't know her well and only had sexual relations twice...
...l was able to understand that well.
That treatment came everyday...
...and even changed the personality of Ms. Fumi who was participating in it.
Even though being overwhelmed by Madam's fierce vindictiveness...
...that changed everything for the ones that reside in this mansion.
lnstead of criticizing it, l became entranced by it.
Within that, Mother is the only one...
...who continues to gallantly stick up for her.
On the other hand, Ms. Reiko continues to reject her.
Why does she reject her to that point?
Once again today...
Reiko...
l was thinking for a while about why you hate me.
We were friends...
When?
l never once thought that you were my friend!
On top of that, l hate that good-person face of yours!
But l like you, Reiko.
On top of that, l feel that you are my friend.
We were going against each other with studying and club activities...
...but l believe that we were connected somehow.
That's right, you were always like that.
You seem like you are gentle, but your heart is strong or maybe stubborn.
When we were in the executive committee for the festival...
...while everyone was doing stuff separately, you would round them up.
Unlike myself who just pulls everyone along forcefully...
...you would lay the groundwork and everyone worked together.
Everyone adored you.
Reiko...
Despite that...
All of a sudden you quit school.
Do you know how l felt?
l'm glad.
lt seems the two of them reconciled.
Maybe the emotion of hatred towards Mother has melted away...
...by the two bringing their true motives together?
Maybe there was a button that was not put through the right hole...
...in the beginning, but l wouldn't know what that is.
For some reason l imagined that and my penis...
Mr. Ryo, please wake up!
Ms. Fumi.
What's going on?
Ms. Reiko...
A fire!
Reiko...
What happened all of a sudden, Reiko?
Madam, it's really hard to say this, but...
...when l got over there on my rounds, Ms. Reiko had already set fire...
...to the curtain with the candle stand.
ls that so?
But that's not something we can do anything about now.
Please wait.
l can't believe that Ms. Reiko would start the fire.
B-But l definitely saw Ms. Reiko.
S-She most likely was trying to counterattack us and did!
Fumi, keep your mouth shut.
Seems like you have a lot of confidence.
Continue, Madoka.
Yesterday, we were able to deliberately talk and understand each other.
We spit out all of our feelings that piled up over time.
So Ms. Reiko is not in a state where she would go on a frenzy.
That's how it was.
Madoka, l will believe you.
Thank you very much, Madam.
lt's too early to be happy.
From now on, you're going to be watching over Reiko.
She'll most likely require long-term medical treatment.
ls that still okay with you?
Yes, of course.
But l don't have that kind of money.
l'm not looking to have you pay for my sister's treatment.
Also, l'm planning on showing you an expression of gratitude equal to it.
You can repay the debt from that, okay?
Madam...
Ms. Reiko certainly did have the lit candle stand in her hand.
But as Mother said, Ms. Reiko had no reason to start the fire.
One possibility is...
...from that kind of punishment, she could have been mentally unstable...
...and ran to such an unexpected impulse.
Or...
Ryo, please take care of the rest.
Do you think it was okay like this, Madam?
About what?
About Ms. Reiko.
Do you have some sort of complaint, Fumi?
N-No, nothing like that.
Reiko ending up like that was unexpected, but...
...l think them being able to get along and live like that...
...was the best result.
More importantly, what are you going to do with your future plans?
T-That's...
You are finally free from the Yotsuya Family's restraint.
The reason you condemned Reiko more than you needed to...
...is because you were so driven into a wall by Reiko, right?
Madam...
You knew about it?
Something to that degree...
...l predicted it all.
l didn't think that Reiko would break down...
...and l wasn't able to look after her enough...
...so if Ms. Madoka is going to be with her, that is the best result.
Okay, l'm going to take a shower and rest.
Fumi, you can step back now.
To tell you the truth, Fumi is my half-sister.
What?
But Reiko and Fumi herself don't know.
lf Reiko wasn't like that, l knew l had to explain to her precisely.
But l have to tell Fumi that sooner or later too.
She's been living with the Yotsuya Family for a long time...
...and she has worked hard for us.
On top of that, she has a phobia of men and lived a different kind of life.
The mansion burned down, plus, thanks to you, she found her new self.
Now she should be able to live in the outside world.
Madam...
Ryo, you too.
Then what are you going to do from now on, Madam?
Ms. Reiko and Mother are not around.
And if Ms. Fumi and myself leave, who's going to take care of you?
Me?
l have a patron that is more of a multi-millionaire than me.
The mansion is gone, so l will be taken under his care for a while.
B-But...
ls that Madam's wish?
Oh stop it, l wouldn't think in that kind of immature way.
l-l will take care of you, Madam!
Ryo, you're such a foolish boy.
Madam is licking me.
This can't be because servicing is my duty.
lt's only the two of us now, so no more of that distribution of roles.
Once the mansion is rebuilt, we will live a very obscene and inflamed life.
Ryo, you shall call me ''Akie'' from now on.
B-But...
lf you can't call me that, l won't do it for you.
M-Madam, that's good too! No...
Akie!
Such a good boy.
lt's going to come out! Mada...Ms. Akie!
lt's punishment for saying ''Ms.''.
Yes, l'm sorry.
You just need to get used to it little by little.
lf you're that sorry about this, it's hard to do it.
Yeah...
Come on, Ryo, embrace me.
Mada...um...
A-Aki...
Ryo, hurry up and come.
l originally like to be loved in this normal situation.
Yes.
l'm coming in!
Ryo's inside me.
lnside me...
A-Akie...
May l move?
lf you have time to ask, pound me.
lf you can't tell what the other person wants, you can't be a sex expert.
You would be able to be my best partner.
Y-Yes!
That's right, Ryo!
Move your hips up and down. Hit it roughly!
Ryo handles my pussy and l handle Ryo's penis.
Then Ryo is going to pour his special thick penis milk into me!
Ryo, it's so dirty!
Your penis and your testicles are like a dirty engine!
With the woman's body-lubricating oil, it's slippery and pumping!
Ryo, use the head of your penis more and scrape the walls of my vagina!
You are such a dirty boy!
That's right.
Rub your slimy pre-cum into my anus.
l'm not used to using that either.
lt's coming, it's coming!
My butt is coming!
Your butt cheeks are squeezing it so much.
A-Akie, l want to move my hips intensely!
Go ahead, shake your hips up and down!
Pound hard into my butt cheeks!
R-Ryo!
Massage my breasts too, not just my butt cheeks!
My breasts are so good! lt's amazing!
My nipples too!
The nipples will turn me on like a clitoris!
l'm about to come, Ryo!
M-Me too!
One to go...