N-No...
No, please stop.
Then say it out loud and deny it.
l can't do...
...such a thing.
ln a place with this many people...
What do l need to do for you to stop?
Until l ruin you, l won't stop.
Please, forgive me.
Please...
You want my dick?
Yes...
You have to beg me right.
Um, l want it...
Want what?
Your voice is too low.
l can't say it in a loud voice.
That was Miss Ashida the lawyer.
That sort of...
My nipples are hard.
No, l'm going to be late.
l'm going to be late!
No, Kanon. Don't do such a thing.
lt's so good...
lt's so good, so l'm gonna keep going...
More, more...
No...
lt's coming...
lt's really...
...perverted...
lt's coming... lt's coming...
No...
This is wrong.
Stop...
My uterus...
My uterus is wanting to come.
l'm not going to be able to hold it in much longer.
Why don't you hurry up and come, Miss Lawyer.
N-No, not in a place like this.
Forgive me. l'm not that kind of human.
Maybe you know what kind of human being you are already.
No, l'm not.
Every time l move you're drooling.
You nubile lawyer.
Hurry up! Accept and cry!
l-lt's amazing!
The walls of my vagina are eating up his dick!
With this fat dick...
l'm...
l'm going to come!
l-l'm coming!
That's one down.
The next is...
N-No, please stop.
Your resistance is weak.
Did you want the same thing like this morning done to you too?
Even if she was making herself look younger, Miss Lawyer was close to 40.
You can't.
Oh, is that so? lt felt good, huh?
Kanon, l'll make you feel a lot better.
You're not going to resist?
Ah, no, this is...
Ah, that feels good.
My senses are going crazy.
You become fascinated when you're molested, huh, Kanon?
My name...
Why did you come to where l was?
Because l saw your molesting this morning?
Or is it fate?
Who are you?
Fate?
You say such a funny thing.
l guess because it was decided from that day.
That day?
l'm the existence that showed up to make you fall all the way to the bottom.
You're all going to take the punishment for your crime.
Punishment?
What? l don't know...
l...
l-lt's going really deep...
lt feels good. l'm really melting...
l didn't know that you wanted to take the punishment that badly.
That's right. l'm taking the punishment.
This is punishment.
The bottom too...
lt feels so good.
lt's really good...
lt's going to come out.
l'm coming!
Use your whole mouth.
l have never done this before.
Raise your chin more and use the back of your throat.
Swallow all of it.
P-Please forgive me.
l understand that l'm the bad one!
lf l don't, l...
l...
...won't be able to stop.
No help is going to come.
You're soaked.
Does that mean you're hoping for it?
No, you have it wrong.
No.
No, no, no, no!
My hymen is going to be ripped by your penis!
l'm going to go crazy.
What is it? You want me to move?
But you want to rub it, right?
No, not this. lf you move, l...
Every time l pound the back, it gets tighter and tighter...
...like it's trying to inhale it. lt's sucking onto it.
My stomach, my stomach...
The raw penis is pounding my stomach.
You're pulsing right on it. Does it feel good?
l'm g-going to come. l'm coming!
l'm coming!
lt's your first time and you're climaxing already?
lt's coming out. lt's ejaculating.
lt feels good.
Kanon, inside of you is amazing.
No!
lt's your first time, and it was an inner cum shot.
lt's not over yet.
l'm going to pollute your uterus, Kanon.
l'm going to pollute it with my sperm and...
...make it the same scent as my dick.
No, l'll get pregnant!
l'm not even an adult yet and l'll become pregnant.
You're shaking inside.
lt's unbearable when l ejaculate inside you, huh?
Yes...
l became a pervert when he poured semen in me.
l'm coming again!
A second time...
lt's continuing...
My orgasm is continuing...
...even though l want it to end.
Your private part has learned my taste.
l like it. l love it so much now!
l'll do it more to you.
Here you go!
l'm going to become a pervert.
A perv that enjoys having her uterus violated...
So, more, stronger!
The third time... The third time...
lt's coming out.
There's lots of semen coming out.
My pussy can't take it anymore.
l'm home.
Hey, where's Kanon?
She's not coming out of her room.
She's not coming out? ls she not feeling well or something?
Maybe she had her heart broken.
Sis...
Kanon isn't young anymore. Why don't you leave her alone?
That's true, but...
Good morning!
What's wrong, Sis?
Big Sister Nao, you woke up earlier than usual too.
Kanon, are you okay?
Huh? Breakfast isn't ready yet?
Well, it's not like l'm totally pinched for time, so it's fine, but...
Hold on a second. l'll prepare it right now.
l'm off!
l'm going to take a half-day and see how she's doing.
O-Okay, please do.
A school teacher?
No, he's not. He didn't have that kind of aura.
That was...
Yeah, somewhere...
Welcome.
Please watch your step.
Please tell me what floor...
Kanon?
Why are you here?
Hey, why were you following me?
Th-That's because l was worried about you.
l'm trying to compensate for your share too.
You guys should take the punishment too.
You're...
Wh-What!
lf it's your second offense, there's going to be no pardon this time.
Kanon, what are you thinking?
Sis, you still don't get it?
You did this to Kanon too?
Yeah, l was molested on the train.
Even though it was my first time, he violated me like nothing else...
...and he made me come.
No...
This is fate.
He is a herald.
l thought l should make the punishment a little less, but...
You guys are...
Tongue, tongue...
lt's really...
My butt is weak...
l'm going to come!
lt's not enough yet, right, Kanon?
Yes...