There are two pairs of siblings in this
show, but they're not related by blood.
Really?
Really.
l learned a lot.
Me too.
Ouch!
But you like this right?
You're so mean.
Don't be mad, l'll give you a hug.
lt's okay. l forgive you because l like you.
You like this too, right?
l don't hate it.
But l don't want you to be mean.
l want you to be more gentle.
Aww, you're too cute Mio-chan!
l feel like l want to climax like 10 times.
Can l?
l don't think l can last that long.
Your boobs are soft and cute.
Don't say that.
Your skin feels so good.
l like every part of your body.
The Sex Exchange 1
You don't have to take it so seriously.
But you have a pettite body, you
won't last long if you're not wet.
Stop it Haku-chan.
l think l have to go.
lt's dirty...
Plus l don't want you to make those sounds.
lf it's your fluid, it's not dirty at all.
Plus if you get the sheets all wet.
Hikaru-niisan might find out about us right?
l don't know why you have to mention him.
l wonder why.
Mioto...
lt's like a huge flood.
You really like this don't you?
No!
lt's getting big over here too.
Can l stick it inside you now?
Don't ask me things like that.
l want it.
Of course you do.
Look how wet you are.
You want it real bad.
l want to know if you want to do it.
l want to do it as soon as possible.
Here, take a look.
lt's big and it wants to go inside you.
Don't be scared.
lt's been inside you many times already.
But we've been doing it with the lights out...
lf it's dark, l can't see your
beautiful body, and that's no fun.
Plus you like this too right?
Wait a minute.
l want to touch your cock once more.
lt's warm, and it almost feels hot.
l can feel it beating.
Are you going to stick it inside me?
You don't like it? Does it hurt that much?
lt feels a little numb.
Just a little, though...
Doesn't it feel good?
l think it feels good.
lf we have more sex, it'll get better.
Look, it went all the way in starting with the tip.
So tight.
You're tight, but you can really take it in.
lt feels hot and good inside you.
Your nipples are hard.
What are you doing?
Feels much better.
l'm about to climax, so l want you to face me.
No, not yet, l haven't climaxed yet!
But it feels so good and it
makes me want to climax quicker.
Wait, l want to climax too.
Don't be selfish...
l'm coming!
l can feel your hot juice...
Mioto...
Mioto, l'm coming!
lt felt good when you were on top of me.
l wanted to stay like this for a little longer.
Look at all that juice.
l like how it trickles down like this.
Mioto...
Well, see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Hakuro's gone?
He could've at least said hello.
Were you watching us brother?
Huh? l didn't see anything.
You were definitely watching.
l didn't watch. l wasn't watching!
Forget it!
Wait just a minute!
Huh?
What are you doing?
Akimi, what are you doing here?
lf you're coming, why didn't you call my cell phone...
Underwear?
What were you...
Are you going to rape me?
Why?
lt's late at night.
l know you're my childhood friend...
...but what brings you to my place at this hour?
l want you to give me some advice.
For what?
Love.
You should ask Hakuro or Mioto.
They know that kind of thing better than me.
l can't ask them.
Why?
l don't need advice, its more like conspiring.
Okay.
l need you to tell me what's going on.
No change at all.
Got it.
Report back to me in 30 minutes.
Hey wait a minute!
What is it?
Let's not do this.
Why?
lt's just that...
You don't have to do it.
Really?
l'll tell Mioto-chan about everything.
l'll contact you if something happens.
Good.
What do you mean?
l'll say it again.
l want to break them up.
Why?
They're good for each other.
Even through my eyes that is.
l'm a bit prejudiced, so l can't really tell.
Hakuro-niisama belongs to me.
That's why...
No way.
l don't want them to be mad at me.
Besides, you and Hakuro are step brother and step sister.
And you're saying
''Hakuro belongs to me.''
lt's just not right.
l'm sorry, l didn't really mean it.
Crocodile tears.
lf you're here to do skits, then go home.
You want to masturbate while
watching Mioto-chan have sex.
You know...
l'll get mad even though you're my friend.
What?
You're just like me.
l saw you masturbating while watching them have sex.
That's why you got me involved...
Perfect strike?
Critical hit. Yay!
What the hell? Your boobs are so small.
Scream damn it!
Are you gonna tell everyone
that l'm a creep who masturbates...
...while watching my sister have sex?
lf you do that, it'll be the end for me and Mioto!
You're getting wet.
You're excited?
So much for your step brother.
l'm afraid you're under the wrong impression.
lt's just a physiological phenomenon.
lf we're going down, then l'll
ruin you and Hakuro's lives as well!
Let's see what happens when
l post this over the net.
What the hell!
Scream out loud and cry for help!
l'm trying to blackmail you!
Even if you cry or scream
out loud, you can't stop me!
Damn!
l'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
lt's just that...
l'm coming...
Look, l know l was wrong.
l'll do anything to make it up.
So don't tell Mioto...
l forgive...
What?
l forgive you.
Why?
l did such a terrible thing.
Are you sure?
Then l won't forgive you.
Which is it?
l'm kidding.
Thanks.
lt's not over yet you know.
What?
You'll have to work on a plan with me.
That's our deal.
You're into something naughty aren't you?
They should act more mature.
Which room did they go to?
What's that?
Dowsing...
Let's go in here.
So this is what the inside of a love hotel looks like.
lf you think about it, this is really something.
With my childhood friend, Akemi...
...l followed my sister and her boyfriend...
...into a love hotel, not only that,
l've already had sex with Akemi.
Plus Akimi and l both love our siblings.
This is just weird.
Anyway, Akimi...
l forgive you.
That's what she said, but l know l hurt her feelings.
No matter how much she loves
Hakuro, it's just like me and Mioto.
We'll never be loved.
People are gonna say we're disgusting...
...and talk about us behind our back.
Then...
No, not yet. l haven't climaxed yet!
Confused?
About what?
Those two.
You know...
What is it?
This step brother and step sister thing is just wrong.
l don't think l can take the place of
Hakuro and we might be...
...moving too fast if you want me as
a substitute for Hakuro.
So l'll let you decide what to do with me.
But let's just stop going after our siblings.
l'm not asking you to be my
lover, so l can atone for my sins.
You don't have to if you don't want to...
You're a pretty honest guy.
You're not Akimi?
Even though we look alike...
...Akimi will be upset if you can't tell the difference.
What's going on?
lf Akimi's Hakuro and Hakuro's Akimi...
lt's hard to explain it in one word.
Come on in you two!
You see, Akimi and l knew that you liked Mio-chan.
Actually, Mio-chan didn't realize
that since she's a little slow.
So everything that happened
yesterday was carefully planned?
l guess you could say that.
lf we didn't do this, you couldn't
be honest with your feelings.
Then what about me raping Akimi?
She doesn't feel she was raped, right?
Of course.
lf l did, l would bite my tongue and die.
Akimi liked you from the start, Hakuro-niisan.
You probably didn't notice because
you were too focused on Mioto.
You're too serious about me, Onii-chan.
And what are you gonna do?
You're gonna make a laughingstock out of me?
None of us are thinking of doing things like that.
Plus laughing at you is the
same as laughing at ourselves.
We're all in this together.
Same goes with Akimi.
Mioto didn't choose me because
we're not related by blood.
She didn't want to tell you her feelings by force.
Right?
We believe that four of us are one.
Other partners don't interest us.
So isn't it natural if we fall for one another?
lf you were different from us and rejected me entirely...
...we wouldn't have been able to say these things.
We don't need anyone else but
Akimi, Mio-chan, and you Hikaru-niisan.
We're satisfied with this.
Do you despise me, Onii-chan?
No, of course not.
lt hurts...
But you like this right?
You know it since you watched me many times?
Yeah, l guess.
You're already drenched.
That's because...
l'm finally doing this...
...with you, Onii-chan.
Then...
Yes, this is wonderful.
Filling the void by doing each
other after all these years.
What is it?
Onii-sama, l want some too.
You're right, we should do it too.
Are you ready?
Onii-chan! l think l'm going to climax!
Looks like they're having a good time.
Hikaru-niisan, Mio-chan likes it real rough, so
it's better to do it fast from the start.
You're so mean Haku-chan.
Why don't you show Akimi your cock going in and out?
lf Mioto wants it nice and slow,
then that's what l'll give her.
Should we do the same?
As you wish Onii-sama.
l'm sorry Mioto.
l made you go through so
much because l'm a coward.
lt's okay, l ended up having you anyway.
You're about to climax right?
We'll climax while kissing as well.
lt's not bad to try it once in a while right?
Yes Onii-sama.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Don't worry, we're like brothers.
l didn't do this just for you.
No, you don't have to tell me.