Atsushi, you're burning up.
Y-Yeah.
Still, l never thought it would turn out this way.
The first tutoring job l was asked to do by Chidori...
lt's tutoring an acquaintance of mine. l've explained the situation to her.
Atsushi, can l count on you?
Kumagai
Yeah, this is it.
lt's a favor for Chidori, so l have to do my best.
Hello, who is this?
l'm a tutor assigned by Miss Chidori Hitotsuya.
My name is Atsushi lkuta.
O-Okay...
Please wait a moment.
P-Please come inside.
Thank you.
lt's here. Please come in.
Nice to...
Oh, Aki, who is this young man?
Um, well, he's...
Nice to meet you. l'm Atsushi lkuta, a tutor who will be coming here.
What?
Oh, really? Nice to meet you.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Mom, l told you l didn't want a tutor!
C-Cut it out, Arisa.
l don't like studying after all.
Plus, didn't you say it was going to be a female teacher?
What? Female?
Hey, what's going on? What's the meaning of this, Aki?
Well...
To be honest, l thought the tutor was going to be female, so...
S-So that's what's going on...
Y-Yes.
Why not, Aki?
ln any case, he doesn't seem like a bad person.
Plus, he's a pretty good-looking young man.
Why don't you leave the tutoring job to him?
Yes, l suppose.
What? l don't want a tutor.
Come on, Arisa, just give it up already.
U-Um...
Oh, Atsushi...
l haven't introduced myself yet. l'm Nami Sato.
l'm a nearby neighbor.
And this is my daughter, Maya.
Hello.
Hello. Yes, hello...
So, Atsushi, l have kind of a related favor to ask...
Yes?
May l ask you to be a tutor for my household too?
What?
Hey, Mom! l don't need a tutor!
Again with that... l don't think it's good to study on your own all the time.
l think it's a good opportunity. Have him teach you a few things.
No!
Okay, Atsushi?
Please?
Seriously, what is going on here?
So with that, l have to take on the Sato household now too.
lt's turned into a hell of a situation.
l guess it wasn't clearly communicated.
l'm sorry.
N-No, it's fine. But l'll do my best.
Thank you, Atsushi.
Atsushi, do you have plans tonight?
No, nothing really...
Then as a thank you, l'd like to cook for you.
Come to my place.
Man, Chidori, you are a great cook.
lt was delicious.
Gosh, Atsushi.
Stop praising me.
Hey, Atsushi...
l've known about your feelings for a while now.
Well, l've always liked you, Chidori.
But l knew you had a boyfriend, so...
A boyfriend, huh...
l'm going to get the dessert ready.
Okay.
C-Chidori...
Hey, let's do it. l want your dick from the rear.
Chidori, who's diligent and levelheaded...
ln a perverted position like this...
C-C-C-Chidori!
Here l go, Chidori.
l-lt's so good! Atsushi's big thing is rubbing against me inside!
lt's hitting the back!
Y-Your hard member is all the way in!
l... l feel like l'm going to come!
So good...
l'm going to come!
l got drunk out of frustration from things not going well with my boyfriend...
l'm sorry.
Chidori, l understand...
...so let's just forget about it.
Thank you.
Nothing's changed, and it'll be like always.
Right.
So l'll see you on campus.
Yeah, l'll see you.
Atsushi is coming out of Chidori's apartment?
Why?
Arisa, did something happen?
lt looks like you can't concentrate.
Hey, Atsushi...
...are you dating Chidori?
l accidentally saw you before.
Coming out of Chidori's apartment...
No, l'm not going out with her.
Really?
Yeah, it's true.
l just drank a little too much, so she let me stay.
Oh, that's it?
Atsushi, do you like me?
Yeah, l like how bright and cheery you are.
Really?
l love you so much, Atsushi!
Atsushi, can l call you big brother from now on?
What? ''Big brother''?
l'll call you that, big brother.
Sure, sure. Just solve the problems already.
Okay.
Yeah, be right there!
A-Arisa...
Hello.
l'm on my way home from club activities. l'm coming in.
H-Hold on...
Wow, it's cleaner than l thought.
Arisa, what is all this?
Okay, big brother, turn around and close your eyes till l say it's okay.
Huh? What?
Just do it.
Okay.
Okay, big brother.
A-Arisa, that outfit...
Guys like this kind of thing, right?
My friend told me.
You did that... for me?
Yeah, l wanted to make you happy, big brother...
Arisa...
l want to give my virginity to you, big brother.
You're sure, Arisa?
Yeah.
My body feels shaken up...
This is the first time l've felt this sensation.
lt feels so good...
Arisa, l'm going to put it in here now.
l want to become one with you, big brother.
Does it hurt?
No...
lt hurts a little, but l'm okay.
lt's all in.
You're inside me...
l'm going to move.
Now we're one. l'm one with you, big brother.
Yeah, Arisa.
l'm glad.
l'm going to move faster.
lt's moving...
Your thing is moving inside me.
W-What is this?
My body is heating up...
Big brother, does it feel good?
Does it feel good inside me?
lt feels really good...
l'm glad...
lf it makes you feel good, l also...
Arisa, l'm going to...
Let's... Let's come together...
l feel kind of strange...
l feel like l'm going to go crazy!
H-Here l go...
Arisa!
l'm going to come... Big brother, l'm going to come!
Sato
Hey, Maya, did something bad happen?
Not really.
Oh, okay...
But it seems like you're annoyed about something...
Atsushi...
...it seems you're getting along well with Arisa lately.
Apparently, she's calling you ''big brother.''
Well, that's because...
lt's not really any of my business...
Thank you for your hard work, Atsushi.
Oh, thanks.
Say, Atsushi...
Yes?
My husband is coming home late today.
So Maya and l will drive you back home.
But l'd feel bad about that.
What are you being so polite for?
lt's fine, right, Maya?
Yes...
Please.
Thank you.
What a nice scent. l feel like l could stay here forever.
Mom, it would be rude to stay here too long.
Say, Atsushi...
l want you to do a review class right now. Could you?
Huh? A review class?
Mom?
l'm worried. You know how Maya just studies all the time?
What if she's not interested in boys?
That's not good, right?
W-What are you saying, Mom?
Maya needs some perverted material too.
Atsushi, you understand, right?
N-Nami?
Oh, you've gotten this happy already?
Maya, look closely.
This is the sexual organ of an aroused mature male.
Maya, come over here.
There you go.
Go on.
Touch it.
lt's hot!
lt's really hard and hot, right?
No!
Stand up.
Take your underwear off by yourself. All right?
Yes.
That hot thing is going to go inside you, Maya.
lt's her first time, so please be gentle.
R-Right...
For easier insertion, l'll stimulate your privates to make you wet first.
Okay, Atsushi...
Atsushi, how is she?
W-Well, she's already very...
Then do it as quickly as possible.
Right.
Mom, what am l supposed to...
You'll be fine, Maya. Just relax and leave it to Atsushi.
l'll go slow, Maya.
Okay, Atsushi.
l-lt hurts!
lt's okay, Maya. l'll ease your pain.
Mom...
Mom!
l've gotten sensitive...
Atsushi, now's the time. Do it.
R-Right.
lt's so hot inside...
My insides are so hot!
lt looks like it feels really good.
Atsushi...
Make Maya come soon and then give me a lesson too.
S-Sure...
l don't know who l am anymore!
Take it slow.
But don't make me wait too long, okay?
Atsushi! Atsushi! Atsushi!
Lick it, Maya.
N-No!
Your tongue is amazing, Mom!
l-l'm going to come!
Maya, your sensitivity has heightened.
lt's because Atsushi taught you.
Atsushi, please take good care of our family, okay?
Please take good care of me too!
Atsushi, it's amazing!
lt's so hot!
Arisa, you need to sit down and start studying soon.
We still have time...
Stop being selfish. Sit down.
Okay...
Okay, start.
O-Okay.
What's wrong? You're not solving the problem at all.
B-But...
No buts, Arisa.
lt's for you, so you need to do it thoroughly.
Big brother, you're so mean...
l had sex with Chidori...
...and l had sex with my two students...
...on top of that, Nami too.
Arisa, if you scream that loud, someone's going to hear.
Even if you say that...
lf Aki finds out about this, it's going to be bad...
Maybe l should stop being a tutor.
l'm going to come!
But...
...it seems like l won't be able to quit.