lt's getting bigger again...
No! l've got to control it.
Maybe just a little.
What if l get found out for doing this?
lt's so...
No! l can't bring it out here!
Hurry up and end!
l need release...
Kagekiyo... This must look weird, but l'm still a girl...
l can't wait any...
Futaba, you're covered in sweat.
Yeah. But hey, what are they doing over there?
There's this really pretty girl a year below us.
They're excited about forming a fan club for her.
ls she that pretty?
l've only caught a glimpse of her...
...but she was a lot prettier than some awkward pro idol.
Okay...
But if l had to pick, l'd say you were prettier.
You don't have to flatter me.
l'll call you tonight.
lt wasn't flattery...
l can't take it anymore...
Look how hard it is...
l can't wait...
This feels good...
Class is gonna start if we don't hurry.
His lectures are so darn boring.
Don't worry. That last job of ours made some nice money.
Now that's economics, huh?
Hurry and leave...
Fine, l don't care if they know...
Hey, it's about to start!
We both need to hurry up!
They left...
lt's so good...
l had to wait so long for this that it feels so much better than usual!
Almost there...
Getting close...
Here it comes!
l've done it now.
What do l do with so much of it?
l'm a girl, so why should l have to do something like this?
Why do l have this thing at all, when l'm a girl?
Why? Why?
l like you too, Kagekiyo.
ls talking to me fun for you? Really?
Don't you want to talk to your other friends, or a girlfriend?
l can't believe it's this hard after l came so much today...
Hello, Futaba?
ls something wrong? Your voice sounds odd.
No, l'm fine. What was it you said was hard to talk about?
Well, you see...
...there was some guy's semen all over the ladies' bathroom.
That must be mine.
l knew that was a bad idea.
And there's a rumor...
...that you can hear some weird voice from the old school building at night.
l wonder if some pervert's prowling around, peeping and taking pictures.
You don't say.
Futaba, you're breathing kind of hard.
Sorry. l have a slight cold.
l don't want to keep you on the phone long, so l'll get going.
Kagekiyo!
Now l've done it. l wonder if he knows l was jerking off.
Oh no! l just got done masturbating, and it's getting big again!
l can't help myself!
lt feels so good! Too good!
Who's she?
You know...
...the pretty transfer student, Kyouka lzumi.
Futaba.
Who do you think's behind the ladies' bathroom incident?
l don't know. l don't care much about such things.
l'm pretty tired right now.
Futaba.
You need to wipe up after yourself when you ejaculate.
Right?
You're very pretty, Futaba.
But l can't see it very well if you don't move your hands.
Kyouka, please... Don't tell anyone about this!
Oh, come on, Futaba.
Why can't l tell everybody about it?
Look at this naughty thing you've got.
Wow...
You're always hiding that big thing under your skirt, huh?
You've got such a soft body. You really are a girl.
Hey!
Stop...
You truly are naughty.
You get off on being watched, don't you?
Kyouka! Not there!
Not...
Futaba, you have to say what it is you want.
Kyouka, please...
l can't hold out any longer.
You want to come, don't you? You want to squirt white stuff all over.
Yes, l need to let it all out!
You know something?
Most men don't even have one this big.
This part's amazing too, Futaba.
lf you keep sucking...
Yes!
That feels so good! Too good!
More! More!
l can't take any more! l'm gonna come!
Look at all that!
Futaba, you're incredible.
lf that's how much comes out...
...no wonder you covered the bathroom stall.
Take off your skirt.
lf you're a girl, you're free to go.
Excuse me, but what's the meaning of this?
Why should l need your permission for anything?
Everybody's talking.
They say you're the one who messed up the bathroom.
l've always thought you were odd.
You always wear a jersey over your tights in gym and in the summer.
You're actually a guy, aren't you?
You always play so innocent in front of Kagekiyo!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Hey, what gives?
Kagekiyo...
There's no possible way Futaba's the culprit.
Unfortunately.
l stayed over at Futaba's house a few nights ago.
Her body was very, very soft.
Kyouka...
l understand that you're all nervous...
...but don't go suspecting your classmates.
The guy will be caught soon enough.
Okay, Kagekiyo. lf you say so.
Thanks, Kagekiyo.
No, that's okay. l feel kind of embarrassed now.
Got to hold out until l get home...
lt's not far, once l'm through this park...
l can't keep doing this forever. Got to hold out.
What if someone comes by? But l can't help myself!
Why don't we assist you then?
What a nympho, getting it going in a place like this.
What the heck? What's that under your skirt?
No!
Whoa, hey, this chick's a dude.
No, l'm a girl! Stop it!
She's a guy.
No, wait. ls she a girl?
She's got white skin, and she's gorgeous.
Aside from this, she's totally a girl.
Hey, which of these do you get off with?
l bet it's this one.
W-Well...
Tell us! You want us to strip you down and toss you in the street?
You're right. That's what l use.
Okay, then let's see you in action.
No...
No... Come on, get started.
Let us watch. Then we'll let you go home.
Now go.
Yes, this isn't a park. lt's my room.
Nobody's around, so this isn't embarrassing at all...
Check it out. She's really doing it.
Wow, man. She's serious about it.
Oh, gross! lt still feels good with them watching!
l can't hold back anymore!
Me neither!
Watching a girl do this is so hot!
Uh-oh... They've started doing it too...
l'm gonna come!
Say what? You're a girl, but you shoot cum too?
Have some of this, freak!
There's sperm all over me...
Now it's my turn!
What's this?
Hello.
Oh, Kyouka.
Futaba, do you like the present l got you?
What's the matter? You don't sound happy.
Yeah, on my way home today...
l see...
Felt good though, didn't it?
l just knew you were a masochist.
Don't tell me you told the girls in our class...
...and those delinquents about my body?
Come on, l wouldn't do a thing like that.
Just please, hurry and try out your present.
l imagined you being assaulted, and now l'm touching myself.
But l...
First lick the tip, and get lots of saliva on it.
Next stick out your ass, and loosen up your asshole with your finger.
Please stop this, Kyouka...
You're hard now, aren't you, Futaba?
But don't touch it today.
l'll take good care of it tomorrow.
And you know...
l wish l could have seen you covered in cum.
Turn on the switch, and please stay that way until tomorrow.
You did like l asked, Futaba. That pleases me.
Kagekiyo looked like he was worried about you.
Please... l can't stand any more...
You haven't come at all since yesterday.
No! This is so embarrassing!
But doesn't that make it all the more hot?
This is really hard now too.
No, don't mess with that too...
Your girl part's all mushy and wet now too.
lf you don't hold out like you should, you'll shoot it all over your face.
But l can't stop it!
There it goes. Look at it all, Futaba.
l figured you were pent up.
Look how much l have in my hand.
Has your boy part had any experience?
l'm asking whether it's still a virgin.
Have you ever put it inside a girl?
You haven't, have you?
Like l said over the phone last night...
...would you like me to be your first time?
You want to, don't you, Futaba?
Not really...
You're cute when you're stubborn.
You're so mean, Kyouka.
See, this hard thing of yours is going inside me.
Can you tell?
Yeah, it feels really nice and warm inside you.
Something's weird!
My hips are moving on their own!
lt feels good, having yours rub me...
Futaba, that's rough!
Sorry, Kyouka! l can't stop!
Kyouka, if you keep moving like that, l'll finish soon!
But you're so big, and it feels so good.
lt's touching me in my deepest place!
lf you keep tightening on it like that, it'll...
Hey, Futaba, l think l'm about to come. Let's come together.
Yeah, together... Kyouka!
Here it comes!
Me too!
lt's gushing out and filling up my uterus...
Was it good for you, Futaba?
l see...
Well then...
lt's a chastity belt.
l'd like you to wear it during class today.
lt keeps getting bigger inside there...
l want to touch it! l want to come! l really, really want to come!
Got to do something...
l'm...
...about to go insane!