This is a work of fiction.
Names, characters, places and incidents...
...either are the product of the creator's imagination or are used fictitiously.
Any resemblance to any actual persons, living or dead, events, or locales...
...is entirely coincidental.
l was imprisoned due to false accusations of sexual harassment...
And was greeted by some man when l got out.
He is known as the God of Perversion, and was a legendary pervert...
...named Sugimoto Kazuo.
Kami-sama and l waged a war against the evil organization of Tendouj Asukai...
...and made our first move.
First, we took out the leader Nagisa Eri...
Then Hirano Miyuki, the second in command.
Our next target is their special team leader, Suruga Rikako, who framed me.
ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Gold Throbber
Vol. 2
The target shows no sign of movement.
Okay.
l believe the target will be leaving soon.
My colleague Fujioka hired Rikako...
But why?
Suruga Rikako is coming out.
Be careful, Yuji.
She's their special team leader.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes.
lf you believe that you can get this woman...
...then you will be capable of anything.
lf you fail, then l'll have to abandon you.
According to the handbook, Rikako's next target is...
The employee of a trading company on the Keihin Tokyo line.
When Rikako approaches her target, that's when you come in.
Touch her and make her fall for you.
What?
Yes, that's it.
He got her.
No, this can't be...
l...
What is this? l've never felt this way before.
Relax.
l'll let you feel real good.
My cunt feels hot...
My womb is feeling numb...
You want this right?
Your cock is rock hard.
l want you to do me with this!
Hurry up and stick that inside!
Not yet, we're just getting started.
You're ass is pretty clean.
Looks like you never had it up the ass.
Not there...
ls this how you got the other girls?
No, l can't resist him!
l can't believe this is happening to me.
But l really want him to stick it inside!
lt's time.
l can't keep standing like this.
l want you to mess me up!
l can't...
l want you to do me harder!
l'm about to climax.
Your cock is getting big inside me!
l can feel it!
You're under arrest for groping.
Yuji...
Now, tell me who your boss is.
l know that you work for a guy who calls himself the God of Perversion.
Tell me his name.
l wonder what kind of techniques his master has.
l'm sorry.
He's very discreet.
All right then.
This equipment was used for torture by the Nazis.
No man can tolerate this.
We're going to send you to hell.
Don't!
Stop it!
You got a nice cock.
Unbelievable. Men are such worthless creatures.
Even though hell is waiting for him, it turns out like this.
Now, here we go.
That's enough.
Stop!
lt doesn't look good.
lf this keeps up, he might become impotent or he just might get killed.
Okay.
l'm sorry for calling you this late.
lt's kind of an emergency.
You'll become impotent if l raise one more level.
ls this what you want?
Hold on.
Yes?
Oh, it's you...
What?
But this man is...
Yes, l understand.
Looks like it's your lucky day.
What happened?
Who did you just talk to?
One of your elites.
The chief of the police department?
That's great. This will be a match of unprecedented scale.
l don't think their boss will have any problems with this.
This is the only way to get rid of them.
lf this goes on, the techniques l have bequeathed will be wasted.
You're right.
Your master took good care of me as well. l should show my gratitude.
l want you to show them Kami-sama's godly techniques.
ln the name of God.
This is gonna be interesting.
l'm sorry master.
You did good.
Leave the rest to me.
Kami-sama decided to face their boss Asuka a week later.
lf he can seduce her and make her climax, he wins.
lf he fails, then their boss wins.
The loser has to give up their business practice. lt's an all-out battle of perverts.
The battle takes place for the entire 45 minutes on the Odawara line...
...from Atsugi to Shinjuku.
ln order to prepare for the battle...
...Kami-sama kept on practicing his techniques.
l'm very impressed. Your skills are very good.
lt's safe to say that victory is ours.
Tomorrow's the battle.
l want you to win.
Why do you want me to win?
l know it's weird for me to say this but...
...l believe that what you do is an act of God.
lt's a shame to lose it all.
And what is this information you want to tell me?
l'll tell you but on one condition.
On one condition?
Kami-sama, l want you to do me sometimes, on the train that is.
lt's no laughing matter.
Women who get touched by Kami-sama can't get excited normally.
So l want you to do me from time to time.
Fine.
Now, what is this important information you have for me?
l truly believe that you're the God of Perversion.
But you will lose.
Even Kami-sama will lose, because...
...our boss is frigid.
Plus it's not just any ordinary frigidity.
No matter what the situation is, even with an aphrodisiac...
...she doesn't get excited.
That's impossible.
She used to see a shrink, so she's not normal.
l understand. Thanks.
l'll keep that in mind.
You'll be rewarded.
Really?
Good luck.
By the way, how old is your boss?
27 years old.
Anything wrong?
No, it's nothing. Take care.
Perversion Journal
Kami-sama seems very impatient.
For the first time, l have a feeling that Kami-sama is gonna lose.
Everyone is doing it.
lt feels strange.
His subordinates are getting in on the action.
Using cheap tricks.
This train is dangerous, so choose a different one.
Weirdo.
l'm starting to feel very strange.
We meet again.
We have some unfinished business.
l'm sorry boss.
l think l'm feeling it already.
l'm feeling it too.
l'm starting to feel it.
You're all pathetic.
How can you be my bodyguards?
l'm sorry.
He's not here.
Where is he?
Where's Kami-sama?
When is Kami-sama coming?
We're almost at Seijyo station...
We only have about 20 minutes left.
No!
Stop it!
What's wrong little girl?
No...
l'll take you home with me, so don't tell anyone, okay?
You're all right now, the bad conductor is gone.
l'll protect you, so don't worry.
lt's coming inside me.
So this is the man they call God...
lt feels good.
Give me more!
l'm coming!
Master, how did you find out about Asuka-san?
lt said in my mentor's handbook that a conductor attacked a girl on that train.
So l role-played thinking it might have been her.
But what if you were wrong?
Then l may have lost.
l didn't know Asuka-san had such a traumatic experience in her past...
My mentor told me once...
Never force yourself on a girl.
You're right.
Yuji, you should go back to a normal job.
You're not suited for this type of business.
l'll help you find a good job.
But l want to practice more and...
No, you shouldn't.
You know how difficult this job is by now.
You're right.
l understand.
l think l'm feeling much better now.
Thank you very much for everything.
We're all ready for you.
This is the beginning of your new life.