lt's so hot.
Seriously! l wished they'd cancel practice on days like this.
Hey, Akino.
Did you hear the town announcement earlier?
No.
l wonder what it was about?
Who knows? lt's probably that thing again. Photochemical something...
Oh, that warning about staying indoors?
l didn't hear it so l'm not positive though.
Was it ''smog'' or ''sumobu''?
Come on, ''sumobu''? Erika...
Yeah, that sounded like ''sumo-club'' didn't it?
Tightening the sumo belt... With the sumo coaches...
What the hell is that? Stop making weird songs.
Hey, are you guys blowing off practice?
Why aren't you at practice?
Oh, it's Sensei.
We already went to practice today.
We're not blowing it off.
lf we practice anymore we'll die!
Switching topics... Sensei, your boobs are so huge.
Woo-hoo!
Hey! l'm really self-conscious about it so stop it!
Erika?
What... is that?
Where... am l?
What was that light?
What is this place?
lt's like a prison...
Someone! ls anybody there?
U-Umm...
Welcome to our country.
Fools from the rotten land.
Damn whores, full of greed!
Bring her!
What's happening?
Akino!
Hurry up and walk!
This is revenge.
Your people unleashed a wave of violence upon us.
Then threatened us with your financial might. You will not be forgiven.
You will suffer the consequences and we will show no mercy.
You filthy scoundrels will get the death you deserve.
You will experience a tenth of the pain our comrades had to endure!
Sensei...
That woman has been drugged.
She can't fight it.
ln fact, she'll be begging for it.
Do you hear her? She sounds like an animal.
Or... perhaps this is all because a mere human, an animal...
...had foolishly tasted the forbidden fruit.
Perhaps in this moment, humans are able to escape the control of that fruit...
...and can be truly free.
This is the one moment humans can escape the sin they have committed.
Do you agree, girl?
Listen to her! She sounds like she's enjoying it!
...even though she's getting raped by several foreign men.
The only thing she feels, isn't shame or guilt from her sin...
She only feels ecstasy.
Humans are so weak.
Look. She's thrusting her ass on her own now.
Humans are always suppressing their desires, but one dose and look at her!
Beneath your skin... You also have a wild beast called desire...
...locked up inside a cage made of morals.
Although locked in a cage, the beast's tongue is hanging from his mouth...
...drooling, yearning for pleasure.
More...
M-More...
Stop! My student is...
No! Erika, don't look at me...
No! l'm going to cum!
Now, if you confess and join us we can be merciful.
Confess? What are you talking about?
lf you want to play dumb, that's fine with us.
Do it!
Wait! l really don't know what you're talking about!
The other one too!
Please stop!
This drug will release you from your inhibitions. Enjoy it.
What the... My body is getting warm...
l can't think clearly and...
My breasts are also...
They're throbbing, right?
Once someone touches them...
What is this... Why are my nipples so sensitive?
No, don't let go!
My breasts...! My breasts are...!
Then tell us what you know.
l really don't know what you're talking about!
Stubborn woman. You'll regret this.
Do it!
Y-You're kidding, right? Please don't!
Nooo!
Please... Help me... Someone...
lf you refuse to talk...
D... Don't...
You'll just have to submit...
No! Keep touching me!
Do something! Hurry!
l'll do anything you tell me! Please!
You should have said so in the beginning.
Resistance is futile against the waves of pleasure.
My breasts... My breasts too...
l wonder what your boyfriend would say if he sees you like this.
As far as l can tell you're still a virgin, but...
...your body is in heat and won't refuse me.
Well?
Not that... Please don't stick it in...
Anything but that...
J... Just your hand...
Must you be so selfish?
Remember, you're the ones who foolishly reached out...
...without considering the consequences!
l know this is wrong, but...
lt feels so good and...
l can't think straight and...
l don't care what he does to me anymore...
Mizoguchi...
l-lt feels so good, Mizoguchi.
Throw her back in the isolation cell and keep an eye on her!
You can do it! Go for it! Erika! You can do it, Erika!
Have you finished eating?
N... No...
You were taking a piss, eh?
They told me to keep a close eye on you. Let me take a good look...
Hey, hey. Do people from your country not wipe themselves after they're done?
What? Now is my chance to escape?
Knock the guy out? l... l can't do that!
One of the stones behind you is loose. Use that to hit him over the head!
l can't... l can't do that...
Then... you'll just have to stay like that forever.
This way, Miss.
What are you doing? Hurry up.
What? She escaped?
lt's them? They've finally come!
We must catch her at all costs!
That girl is definitely...
This monster is going to kill me...
What's going to happen to me?
Don't lose them! What about the ruin gate?
lt's staying silent.
She has a really high fever.
She might die at this rate.
We have no choice but to go ahead as planned.
But...
That's reckless, Elder!
Her body won't be able to handle it!
Does she really have that kind of power?
Regardless, she'll die in two days time from the air down here.
And... if the prophecy is true...
this girl might guide us, even though we continue to live in disgrace.
Hey, Erika! What are you doing over here?
Hurry up and come here!
Brother...
Bro... ther...
l'm being raped by a monster, but...
...l wonder why l feel so warm.
His dick is so big, but...
My pussy is so wet...
l wonder what's going to happen to me?
lt feels so good.
l can't believe l want this to last forever.
When did l turn into such a slut?
Humans are so foolish.
Erika.
Miss Shimizu.
Mizoguchi...
What the...
What's happening?
What the...!
Damn it! ls it that girl?!
Hey, what's happening over there?
We'll have an emergency meeting. Report the situation!