l doubted my eyes because of this abnormal scene.
What are Madam and Ms. Fumi doing?
No, l can't look.
lf l keep on watching this scene, then l'll be sucked in too.
But l can't look away from it.
l can't look away from these two doing it like insects.
Because of the honey-like substance created from sweat and body fluids...
...the thin layer of fat which covers the round bodyline is accentuated.
Girls about the same age as me think being thin is the ultimate beauty...
...as they try out things like exercise or limiting what they eat.
Also, my classmates pour out their love to those girls, but...
...for myself who doesn't agree with that...
...Madam and Ms. Fumi's figures are certainly like maidens of beauty.
As of right now...
...l'm convinced they are mistaken.
When you think about it...
...since ancient times, the earth was thought to be female.
And works of art which were left in their natural shape were...
...buxom figures like Madam, Ms. Fumi and also Mother!
Once again, my eyes were stolen away by...
...Madam and Ms. Fumi's phlegm-like entanglement.
Then l suddenly realized.
The truth of why l was looking.
Yes, since the moment l came to this mansion...
...no, the moment that l decided to...
...l was pulled into this abnormality.
The moment l realized that, my limiter was taken off and...
...as if my hand had another will, it reached down to my crotch.
My crotch has expanded to the point of bursting as...
...every time my heart beats like a fast-ringing bell...
...l can feel my blood being sent to the erectile tissue.
At this moment, if l even lay one finger on my crotch...
...l will shoot some cloudy, thick milk.
Actually, even before that, due to my underwear...
...and also my pants which are keeping my violent penis held down...
...wouldn't my penis break?
That can't happen!
l wouldn't know how to face my mother who has taken care of me till now.
My body is not only mine anymore.
Even better, one half is my mother's and...
...the other half belongs to Madam, who bought me.
When you think about it like that, there is nothing l could actually call my own.
Then an act of harming it on my own will not be tolerated.
When l think about something like that, my expanded penis will...
...bend against the restriction of my pants and break!
Madam and Mother's precious, precious penis will...
Fumi, l'm envious of your breasts' flexibility.
My bodyline, on the other hand, has started to degrade.
Madam Akie, that's not...
Look for yourself.
My fingers are like springs and bounce back...
...along with the parts that overflow.
l'm jealous.
Ouch!
Fumi, so unladylike...
Madam Akie, l am sorry.
Fumi, you are so lascivious for wetting yourself from overwhelming pleasure.
Madam Akie, please don't say that.
lt's sad that a girl like you doesn't know a man.
No, l have you, Madam Akie.
You were the one that taught me the pleasure of the night.
lf l can be your companion during the night, then l don't need a man.
You cannot say such a thing.
These acts with me are mere child's play.
lf you compare it to sex with a gentleman filled with sexual desire...
But to me...
l doubted my ears.
lf it was possible, l wanted to intrude into the bedchamber and...
...confirm with Madam.
''Madam, what did you just say?''
''Did you just say Ms. Fumi is a virgin or something like that?''
Ms. Fumi's a virgin.
lt's only been a short time since l met Ms. Fumi...
...but l'm able to think of her many wonderful traits.
Of course her appearance and also her efficiency to be able to work with...
...all the things that have to be done in that very spacious mansion.
Her quick thinking that leads me to resolution...
...when l'm perplexed about the sudden change in a situation.
Her intellectual interior and the manner that proves it.
That wonderful Ms. Fumi is a virgin.
That's not right. A wonderful woman like Ms. Fumi...
...that should be worshipped as a maiden is a virgin.
Why?
Your clitoris has become so big.
Even though you're a virgin, you wouldn't lose to a female veteran in the...
...sex industry with this well-played clitoris.
Please don't say that, Madam Akie.
That's right.
Madam was just saying that Ms. Fumi has a phobia of males.
l feel like l'm going to be taken over by my conceited arrogance.
l was going to give my virginity to my mother...
...who has loved me the most in the world, so l've protected it.
But Ms. Fumi's virgin vagina...
No, more to help her get rid of her phobia of males...
That might be the way to return the favor to Ms. Fumi.
But the more l think about it, Ms. Fumi is a wonderful woman.
A guy like me...a filthy, nobody virgin would never be able to save Ms. Fumi.
l need to apologize to Ms. Fumi and to Madam.
Maybe l should just open this door...
...and have them convict me of my conceited thought and my peeping act?
Madam Akie, l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
You can come, Fumi!
What have l done?
l just stained the floor with my filthy semen.
l was bought to take care of this mansion's duties...
...and l just made it dirty instead.
But that means Madam and Ms. Fumi were...
No, l can't! My penis will start emphasizing its youthfulness again!
No, don't, penis!
Please don't emphasize your violence due to your youthfulness!
lf you are going to do that again, then l will not hesitate...
...to use the right hand of the gods.
Oh, Ryo's penis is really emphasizing it's youthfulness, isn't it?
Fumi, listen well.
You have to lick it thoroughly and prepare it.
You are going to turn into a woman with Ryo's youthful and manly penis.
This is an order.
Fumi, your virgin vagina is going to be broken through by Ryo's virgin penis.
Look, Ryo's thing is getting bigger from anticipation.
Look, Fumi! Look at Ryo's anticipating facial expression!
Ryo can't wait to take on the honor of penetrating your virgin vagina.
From the anticipation, his penis is getting larger!
Fumi, it's going to come out. Get ready to drink up the thick milk!
lt's coming out, it's coming out! An amazing one is going to come out!
So, you know where to put it, right?
lt hurts, it hurts!
Fumi, take it. This is something that is necessary for you.
But...but l can't bear through this.
No, move more intensely!
Ryo, you were a virgin, so you might not know...
...but women don't break that easily.
Especially for lascivious female dogs like Fumi!
Mr. Ryo, slower...
lt's going to tear.
Please, don't make it so rough.
Ryo, l won't forgive you if you loosen up your movement.
Fumi, you keep on saying that, but the honey from your crotch is pouring out...
...and on top of that...
Look, your whole body has become really sensitive!
l...l...
l'm going to come, l'm going to come!
lt's the first time, but shamelessly...
l'm going to come...
Coming!
Ryo, listen well.
Just like this, with me...
...and also once in a while with Fumi, it's your duty to service us.
That's your punishment for staining the hall with your filthy semen.
lt's good. Yes, lick all over and clean it up just like that.
Do it diligently.
To service your master like that is an honorable thing.
You're pretty good. Your mother's training was good, huh?
You're so good. lf you do it like that, my body's going to burn up.
Ryo, you lick me so well that l want to urinate now.
Ryo, you're going to take it, understand? Here l go.
Ryo, you are such a dirty boy.
But l love those dirty young boys.
Did you know?
Young boys have this scent like fresh leaves floating over.
l knew that you were one of those dirty ones at first sight...
...so that's why l approved of you working at this mansion.
You already came twice today, but...
...your thing is still full of life trying to get inside me.
My clitoris is being stimulated by Ryo and is getting excited.
Ryo's penis is amazing. lt's emphasizing its youthfulness and pride.
Ryo, use your hips more intensely.
l won't allow you to commit the sinful conduct of just lying there.
Ryo, good boy. Just like that, shake your hips and make me happy!
That is the proof of...
...youthfulness!
That's right.
This is the Yotsuya household.
That fantasy-like happening from last night was reality.
lnside my white briefs is Madam and Ms. Fumi's love juice.
Also, my own semen that shines on my penis is the evidence.
When l think about it, a week ago...
...my mother was cleaning my ears for me like usual.
Then mother secretly smelled my underwear as she masturbated...
...and l would watch her as l masturbated to her secretly.
The usual everyday life.
l'm sorry.
l'm sorry that l'm this kind of mother.
l'm sorry l'm a bad mother that plays with herself while smelling your underwear.
This strong smell.
l'm going to come!
The happenings at that house are like a dream.
Mother would behave as a mother, and l would behave as a real child.
And then the implicit consent to watch each other masturbate.
Since we couldn't step into a relationship, that was our only contact.
Mother enjoyed having me watch her masturbate...
...and l would go along with it.
lt was an instrumental duet we both played.
But that unexpected, sudden catastrophe.
Mr. Ryo, are you ready?
What do you mean, attachment?
On top of that, what did you do with Mother?
Your mother, Ms. Madoka Tatsumi...
...is in debt to Mrs. Akie Yotsuya for a large amount of money.
With the present cram school administration, repayment is impossible.
So while cutting into her time to come home, she's trying to raise money.
As an exchange for this long-term absence...
...we have been holding on to this home's ownership.
Thanks to our master's kindness...
...your residence in this home is allowed.
l was sent by Madam Akie to explain the situation to you...
...and that is why l came to visit.
P-Please wait.
What is it?
U-Um...
ls there anything l can do?
Anything you can do?
Well, l want to help repay the debt.
l didn't know Mother was being run into a wall like that.
Even from this point on, l would like to attend to my familial obligations.
So please buy me!
ls that so?
Unfortunately, l do not have the jurisdiction.
But l will be able to make a chance for you to meet Madam Akie.
Also...
Also?
lt's true that doing all the duties for the mansion alone is too much.
lt seems that your preparations are okay.
The task that we will have you doing today is weeding the yard.
Madam Akie loves gardening, but we don't have enough hands.
Hey, both of you.
Up so early...
Madam Akie too.
Until l was going to wake you up...
l don't know if it's because l got excited, but l slept light last night.
Aside from that...
Fumi, is your crotch okay?
When l got my virgin vagina penetrated...
...the next day it hurt so much that l wasn't able to walk.
Ryo, you also came three times.
Fumi, please bring my meal to my room.
l'm starting to get sleepy now, so l'll eat in my bed.
Yes, l understand.
l'm going to prepare Madam Akie's breakfast.
Mr. Ryo, after you eat, please take care of the weeding in the yard.
Please warm up the soup on your own.
Please don't think that things like yesterday will happen often.
What is up with that innocence of Ms. Fumi?
Even though she's in her thirties, she's like a female student.
There's a freshness unlike the girls my age.
Usually her actions are tame and calm...
...but sometimes her cheeks blush and show an honest, innocent face.
My heart is greatly moved by that appearance.
ls it because we are somewhere isolated from the outside world?
lf l am too, then just like yesterday...
How many times do l have to tell you to contact me before you come, Ms. Reiko?
You're an adult too, so l would appreciate it if you had some etiquette.
Oh, who cares? lt's just us two sisters.
There are times l just want to see your face.
Good manners even between friends.
Plus, isn't your objective to pester for money?
You're wrong.
l just wanted to see your new servant that you just hired.
Because it's been a while since a boy got past your eyes, right?
Ms. Reiko, are you planning something?
No, nothing.
Well, whatever.
l will say it to you beforehand, but l am the master of this house, not you.
Mr. Ryo, you're still young, so you might not know, but...
...listening in on your master and her company's conversation is an act...
...that can be criticized as a lack of common sense.
Hey Fumi, long time no see.
lt might be unpleasant for you, but l will bother you guys again for a little while.
That's what l thought, so l brought your luggage to the usual room already.
How thoughtful of you.
Well, whatever.
So you're Ryo.
Ms. Reiko, Mr. Ryo has tasks that he needs to complete too...
...so please don't keep him too long.
What a mouth on you, even though you are only a servant.
Oh, l get it, do you have some kind of special feelings for him?
So l hit the mark on that one?
What a piece of work you are!
Meaning the man-hating Fumi at that age learned how men are.
You're Madoka's stepson, right?
Madam Reiko!
How scary.
Then l'll see you at night.
What Ms. Reiko said before was all lies, so please don't worry about it.
Ms. Reiko knows about Mother?
When she was saying Mother's name, she showed those eyes of hatred.
Mother incurring someone's hatred? Can't be!
My kind mother?
l can't believe it.
Even if hell froze over, it couldn't be.
Oh no!
Because l was remembering Mother's sweet sigh and her warm, soft thighs...
...blood is flowing into my penis.
l'm coming in without knocking.
Hey, good timing.
Could you just stretch your arms over your head and grab the bed frame?
Young ones are amazing.
You come three times in one day, but go at it again the next day.
l wonder who you were thinking about that expanded your penis.
W-What are you...
My sister? Fumi? Or is it...
Your stepmother Madoka?
Ah, so that's what it is! You guys did have that kind of relationship, huh?
Madoka is disgusting as usual!
She seems like a good person.
At cram school, the parents like her...
...but in the house she's flirting with her stepson?
l seriously want to vomit!
We have to punish you.
This is punishment, Ryo.
You aren't at fault, so think about it as your mother's fault.
l hit you that much with the whip, but your penis is still stiff.
As expected, one that was a virgin is so greedy.
Such a modest, poor man's penis...
lt wants to let its milk out.
Did you stick it inside Madoka like this too?
lt's amazing!
Which one's better, Madoka's pussy or mine?
Since it's her...
...she just laid there, didn't she?
Perhaps you guys didn't have sex?
Then l'm sure Madoka is regretting it so much!
Your penis just got bigger!
Are you getting excited from thinking about Madoka?
No, don't pound me that roughly.
lt's good, it's so good, Ryo.
Ryo's penis is so dirty. lt's so good!
Right, Madoka?
Ryo, l love your dirty penis.
My pussy feels so good.
l'm going to come, l'm going to come.
l'm coming!
l can't hold it anymore!