Mayu Yokoyama
Station manager Sir, please don't...
Your stance doesn't look good on camera.
Do you see?
lf we change this a little like this, it will make a huge difference.
lf you just tell me, l will understand...
Here, like this...
Please stop touching my breasts.
Nonsense!
This isn't for me.
l'm helping you improve...
Station manager Oono is passed out!
Check out that bump on his head.
Are you okay, sir?
Someone call an ambulance!
Um...
Thank you for earlier.
l wasn't trying to help you or anything.
People think it was a ''coincidence'', so don't look at me like that.
Okay.
Kazuya...
l thought only the worst people worked in entertainment...
...but there are people like him...
l'm pretty cute.
l bet he wouldn't turn me down if l approached him.
Besides, he wouldn't have done that if he didn't think anything of me.
So you want to be a newscaster...
Hey, you just laughed at me!
Like l couldn't do it.
No, not at all.
When we're rolling, you create this lisping character...
...but in rehearsals you're very clear.
lt all makes sense now.
You noticed that?
l'm so embarrassed.
lt's our job to pay attention to our stars.
So, what do you want to do in the future?
Me? l, well...
l want to express my creativity as a producer.
You can do that for sure!
l guarantee it!
Thanks.
l like you, Kazuya.
No, that's not right.
l think l like you, Kazuya.
ls that too obvious?
Mayu, rehearsals are about to start! Are you ready?
Oh no.
My contact fell out!
What?
l'll make an excuse for you, be out there in two minutes.
l'll think about this after we're done.
Hmm. My blush is too thick.
That make-up person sucks...
...l mean, we have different tastes.
l'm going to get it changed.
Why did l do that?
You are?
Uh, nice to meet you, my name is Kazuya Mano.
Likewise.
Did you need something?
You and Yui, l mean...
You and Minazuki go way back, right?
Yes, since college.
Could you please help me?
What?
Even if it is for Yui, what am l, a fool?
l understand what you want to say.
l'm sure there's a lot to it.
Basically, you lack sexual experience and so...
...since you've been going out, you think that...
...um, your whoopie isn't going so well...
...and what does she think, right?
Yes, well, um, exactly...
But when you put it so bluntly...
Stop it, you're the one who came to me...
...now you're making me embarrassed.
l'm sorry.
Yes, so, well...
l don't think Yui is the kind of person who cares about that.
And l don't know her that well so...
So, that's about all l can say...
Please!
lf you don't do this, there's no one else l can turn to!
l'm so embarrassed, my face is on fire!
l'm such an idiot! What an idiot!
Fine then!
Okay! Fine!
l will be your practice partner.
Um...
What? You got something to say?
But that's...
lt's because you're not man enough.
You just need a little confidence.
Okay.
Not getting it, not getting it!
l'm the one who's not getting it!
Come on now.
This is one of the reasons why you can't get it on with Yui.
ls this okay?
lt's saying things like that!
That's not good!
l'm sorry.
Look, if you have time for that...hurry!
Yes!
No... if you do that...
l can't...
No...
l'm going to come!
l'm embarrassed.
l got hung up on the fact that he and Yui are having sex.
That's right, that's what it was.
l don't do things like this, normally.
Marie, are you sure?
Yes, just hurry.
Stop teasing me.
Marie, are you okay?
Just shut up!
l'm having an amazing one.
lf you move right now, l'm going to lose it!
Mano, l'm going to have a big one.
l'm going to come.
Marie, l'm going to come too.
l'm going to come again, l'm going to come!
l'm going to come!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
l'm coming!
l'm going to come with you inside me!
l wonder if Mano has been able to get Yui to come...
What am l thinking!
l bet she's beautiful when she comes.
l want to make her come too.
And she'll clutch me tight when she comes...
What am l thinking!
l could never tell her.
Yui, we're almost there.
l can't move...
She's always so on top of it, but sometimes she falls apart.
Hey, Yui!
l haven't seen a morning like this in a while.
You can say what you want but the real reason you want Yui Minazuki...
...to do the headlines is to make her yours.
How could you say such things in front of your wife!
Do you really think no one knows?
And you call yourself a producer?
And furthermore, whether it's Minazuki or Ayase...
...l doubt that they even understand economics or politics.
This new style news variety show of yours...
...you'd be better off using some brainless pop idols.
You can let it go if it's an idol, but if you use real newscasters...
...you're damaging the dignity of the people who put the show together!
Um, Miss lnoue!
l guess it was no different when l was chosen as the lead.
l suppose you don't need to know anything to do this news stuff.
Good looks and being able to talk like a newscaster is enough.
l can't talk, since l married that lowlife, thinking he was talented.
l'm just part of the cycle, but my expiration date is up.
Um, Miss lnoue.
Um, who are you?
l'm Mano.
l'm an AD in the production department.
l, um, er...
And, well...
l could hear you shouting from the editing room, l was worried so...
Do you have something to say?
l, um, l mean, you know, l was...
So what does an AD like you want with me?
l got into this business because l admired you...
...and so l had to say something...
What the hell am l saying?
Yes, what are you saying?
l guess it's none of my business.
Sorry, l was out of line.
Mano, what did you say?
What are you doing later?
l just have to go over some things for tomorrow then l'm done.
Wait for me by my car in the lot.
l never imagined a boy like that professing his love to me.
l guess that means l still got it.
But still...
So are you okay, are you unwinding a bit?
ls there anything l can do for you?
l've never been to a place like this.
Mano, you're so cute.
And you're so young, l'm envious.
No, you're much cuter.
l took him straight to bed...
Was that too fast?
l'm not a coed nymphette.
l hope he doesn't think l'm depraved and desperate.
You're so nervous, but this thing seems happy.
Miss lnoue is touching my...
Call me Kyoko or we won't go on.
Ky-Kyoko...
Bad boy, coming so fast. l'll have to punish you.
Kyoko, can l move?
No! Not until l say you can!
Please, my legs are buzzing.
Oh, you silly boy!
l couldn't wait to have some fun too so...
Oh! Mano, your willie is so good!
You're going to mess me up!
Oh no... lf you go deep, l'm going to scream...
No no no! l said you can't move.
Kyoko, l want to kiss you.
Okay! Okay! You can kiss me!
l never believed what it says about sex in ladies' magazines...
...but my skin and my mind feel so clear.
...is it possible?
This is the worst day of my life.
When l was in high school and my Afghan Hound...
...got hit by a car and died, l was so sad.
l never thought l'd see a day like that again.
But l think today might be worse.
Who is it?
What is it?
Yui, you are the worst sort of person.
Huh?
You're supposed to cleanse yourself of these kinds of things.
l guess it's too late.
Someone!
l feel that beast's semen coming out of my pores.
l want to scrub until l'm raw.
But l know it won't help.
That's right, l was raped.
Stop! Please!
l'll do anything you want, anything but that!
You're an AD, right?
l remember now.
l saw you by the vending machines today.
l'll ask Miss lnoue to be good to you.
He's a married man, but he's infatuated with me...
...so he'll listen to me...
That's not necessary.
The only thing l want is you.
l'm sorry.
There are all sorts of benefits of a close relationship.
But l have no intention of getting closer to you. So this is fine, isn't it?
You don't have to hold back.
This is going to be a bad memory no matter what you do...
...so you may as well have a good time.
Absolutely not!
Oh really?
Your groin seems to be quite moist.
You're into it!
The pristine female announcer!
l bet a pretty woman like you has already been explored.
But if you want to sell yourself as pure...
...you should be careful about how you conduct yourself...
...or men like me with shattered illusions will resent you.
And this is what happens.
l didn't feel anything.
l didn't.
lt's not possible!
lt's hot!
No...
You don't want me to stop?
Don't worry, l have no intention of stopping.
Not until l come inside you.
No!
Are you coming? You're coming!
Mine is thick.
When my cum hits your cervix, it feels even better.
No!
Outside! Please!
You'll get me pregnant.
Too late.
No!
lf l get backed up, l might come to you again.
So l'll just take a few pictures.
By the way, it's nice that you're basking in the afterglow...
...but you might want to get dressed.
You don't want anyone to see you like this.
lf that happens, no matter how much you flirt...
...with that lowlife lnoue, your career is over.