Do you think l, Lady Flare, will just sit here quietly and take this?
You're gonna regret this.
Want me to raze this place?
Or how about l flood it with water?
You're so full of energy.
But how long do you think you'll last?
l'm going to pleasure you until you die in my mansion,
in place of the woman you let escape.
Stop this, you monster!
For every ounce of pleasure you feel, l will make you feel hellish pain.
And from there, you will live on to serve my goals.
Right now, l'll fill your insides with proof that l was there.
New Legend of Lyon
New Legend of Lyon Another Flare
He's late.
Lord Zeke...
Come now, Lord Zeke, spend the night with me, Polarine.
Lord Zeke! Oh, Lord Zeke!
What're you doing, Countess Polarine?
Wh..What?! l should ask you the same thing!
lnterrupt a woman making love and you'll get kicked by a horse!
l'd rather get kicked by a horse than see this!
Look at what you're screwing.
Lord Zeke isn't that easy to catch.
Sorry, try again.
Th..This is...
A doll!
Aren't you ashamed of yelling ''Oh, Lord Zeke!'' to a doll?
Where is Lord Zeke?
Beats me.
Why don't you know?!
l just found out he was gone a few minutes ago.
Why did you come here so late at night anyway?
Sorry, l'm a little late.
l thought cowardice got the better of you.
Unsheathe your sword, Baron Zeke.
Why do you wish to fight me?
l've made a decision to live my life by the sword.
For that reason, l must defeat you.
l brought you a change of clothes.
This is what women wear in this mansion.
Put it on.
What? l have to wear this?
Yes, all the women here wear it.
lf you don't like it, you're welcome to go nude.
Fine, l get it. l'll wear it, then.
How do l put this thing on anyway?
Why do you insist on fighting me, Neris?
Because you're one of the best swordsmen.
And this time, if l defeat you, l'll...
l don't care who it is, please...
Somebody...
This isn't much different from being naked.
You'll get used to it in no time.
My name's Flare. What's your name?
Huh? lt's Mineru.
That's what they used to call me, long ago.
But there's no need for names here.
Huh? What does that mean?
Even if their souls are female, the women here are not women.
You'll understand soon.
Mineru! What's the matter, Mineru?
Answer me, Mineru!
l'm glad. A warm welcome, is it?
What a fascinating girl.
Are you awake?
Where am l?
What the heck happened to you?
Just... Just rape me, please.
Great, a psycho.
Where's this coming from? Please explain.
Well...
Hey! What are you doing?! Stand up!
l don't know what this girl did, but this is too much!
Who the hell are you?
She's an escapee. Back away from her.
Or else...
Or else, what?
We'll let your body know just what happens to those who resist us in these parts!
See how easy that was.
See? All the men are sleeping like babies.
You're the only one left.
You never stop, do you?
And this woman... She was really that strong?
Yes.
She took no time at all in defeating the men.
Yeah, we've got a super-strong girl like that here too.
But because of me, she...
You never know when to quit!
You bitch!
Damn it...
Whats a matta? Done already?
That's enough.
All right? Drop your blade!
Geez, always the same ole song and dance.
Do whatever you want.
Damn bitch, you really made us work.
You okay? Are you hurt?
Umm, l'm sorry, because of me, you...
Don't worry about it. This happens all the time.
No matter what town l go to, they always gang up on me and...
Wait a sec, l'm usually the aggressor.
But l do find myself in a bit of a pickle this time.
But l think my chance will come surprisingly soon.
Bitch!
Thank you so much!
Hold it!
You really did some damage to us.
No more Mister Nice Guy! We're gonna rip you to shreds!
Well now, looks like we can't escape this together.
Get out of here!
But... But!
l think she was taken to the mansion in my place.
The mansion? ls that where you escaped from?
Yes, in that mansion, l...
No!
What the hell is going on here?!
What do you enjoy about gathering these girls and making them wear such slutty outfits?
l don't particularly enjoy being forced to be here.
Let me leave.
And let the others leave with me, of course.
Take everyone and leave? All right.
But does everyone really wanna leave?
You're free to leave whenever you'd like.
That's why l leave the gate to this mansion wide open.
No one's going to stop you.
They all stay here because they like it here.
What about the girl l saved?! She escaped from here, didn't she?
Your body knows the answer to that question better than anyone.
What?
Why? All of a sudden, my body...
Something's inside of my body...
My body's on pins and needles!
My body... So hot...
My body's on fire!
What on earth is happening to my body?
Seems you don't know what's going on inside your body after all.
No problem, l'll explain it to you in great detail.
Well? Feels good, doesn't it?
Your body feels ecstasy it's never experienced before,
warming you from head to toe.
Yes, right, the girl you saved actually wanted to return here.
Though it looks like you thought you rescued her.
l feel bad for her right about now.
That's...
l've put parasites called Duram into your body.
The Duram nest in your womb and eat any sperm that come their way.
The secretion from the Duram fills the host's body with pleasure.
lt makes you seek out men.
You cease to be a woman once you're infested by Duram,
because you lose the ability to bear children.
The Duram eat all the sperm they encounter.
ln return, they show you boundless pleasure.
And that's why the women don't leave this place,
for leaving here leads to terrors much worse than those found here.
What the hell are those things?
l don't know, but doesn't that look familiar?
What's the matter, Flare?
Please continue, or else l'll...
Well then, should l continue or not?
l beg you.
Oh, but because of you, my shoe is all messy.
Clean it.
Okay...
lf you don't clean it all up, l won't continue pleasuring you.
You gonna suck on that thing forever?!
You men there, fill her to the brim.
l thought l'd get to enjoy that longer.
They're faster than l thought.
Nice, purring like a kitten.
Now then...
Lord Zeke, aren't you forgetting something?
Well, well, if it isn't Lady Polarine.
My late husband left that car behind when he died.
You knew that, didn't you?
ln other words, that car and l are one in the same.
Fine, fine, Lady Polarine.
Please get in the passenger's side.
My! l'm honored you'd ask me to, Lord Zeke!
Hurry and load my luggage, Lony.
Hang on a sec, will ya?
My luggage! Oh no, what will l do?!
Uh, could you worry about me instead of the luggage?
lt's a perfect day for a drive, don't you agree, Lord Zeke?
Sure is.
Lemme outta this cramped backseat!
Pipe down, that's a fine seat.
But...
l'm letting you watch over the luggage, so grin and bear it!
Keep a close eye on them.
You're in big trouble if even one of them falls out of the car!
So, you are going, Baron Zeke.
l can't sit idly by after seeing that.
The symbol of the evil Ternel, who was sealed away 300 years ago.
l have a bad feeling about this.
Looks like l have nothing to worry about.
l was worried about that Flare girl too.
ls this the place, Lord Zeke?
lt's so bleak, not romantic in the least.
lf we went to the hotel two towns back, it would be much nicer.
See, it's cramped back here.
Am l in for monsters? Snakes?
Or...
Welcome.
Wait, Lord Zeke!
Welcome to my mansion.
l'm the mistress of this mansion, Ternel Pajan.
What brings you to my estate?
l apologize for the unannounced visit.
l'm a traveler named Zeke.
My car broke down. l was hoping to stay here until the repairs are finished.
Oh, that must be awful. l'll have a guest room prepared at once.
Stay for as long as you'd like.
Thank you kindly.
Lord Zeke, wasn't that a little obvious?
Yeah, it was.
Wait for me, Lord Zeke!
Wait! Am l gonna have to carry the luggage by myself again?!
Allow us to do it.
We will carry your luggage to your room.
Thank you so much!
l can't leave these girls here.
Guess l have to wait patiently for an opening.
This might be a bit too bright.
How about this one?
Or maybe this one?
That mistress has her eyes on Lord Zeke!
l can't let her win!
Lord Zeke, would you like another cup of tea?
No, l'm okay.
Lord Zeke, could that box hold...
lt's nothing.
All right, maybe l'll hit the bath.
Master Zeke...
You must be weary from your long journey.
lf you'd like, l'll gladly wash your back for you.
l'd like that a lot.
l hear lots of rumors out on the road.
What sorts of rumors?
Like, a giant devil appearing to protect a village from a fortress falling from the sky.
My, how interesting.
lt's just a baseless rumor though.
Do you have any others? Please tell them to me, Master Zeke.
Let's see...
There is this one...
They say a beautiful mistress lived in a mansion somewhere.
They say word of her beauty has traveled all the way to distant lands.
She wed eventually, but her suitor turned out to be a monster.
Word of her beauty had spread even into the monster realm.
Eventually, the man's true identity became known and the humans killed him.
Then? What became of the woman?
Well, l cannot remember.
Zeke...
Lord Zeke, where are you?!
Answer me, Lord Zeke!
This bath is way too big.
Maybe you shouldn't have wasted all that time bringing these items to the bath.
l need them! You never know what may happen!
You never know what may happen?
Oh, never mind that, Lord Zeke.
l smell another woman's scent.
You're imagining things.
Well, guess l'm done here.
No! Oh, Lord Zeke!
What should l do with this stuff?
lf you'd like...
we'd gladly wash your back.
Okay! Pl..Pl..Please!
lt will be our pleasure!
What did you do down there, Lony? You're sparkling.
They cleaned off about three years worth of grime.
How about someone else here cleans off three years worth of grime?
Though all that'll be left are wrinkles.
Are you referring to me?!
ls the food to your liking?
lt's fantastic.
ln fact, this entire mansion is gorgeous.
But above all, l'd like to give a toast to your beauty, Lady Ternel.
You flatter me.
Oh, yes, Lady Ternel.
l remember the rest of that rumor.
Oh, do tell.
Despite the fact that he was a monster, the woman loved him.
Day in and day out, for months, she sobbed before his ashes.
And then one day, all of the villagers suddenly went missing.
The person behind their disappearance was none other than the beautiful mistress.
She sacrificed the villagers alive for killing the man.
She did this in order to become a monster, just like the man she loved.
These events are said to have occurred 300 years ago.
What a fascinating story.
lt's all right, Mineru. lt's just thunder.
But...
The day after a storm is always sunny.
According to the legend, a hero sealed the monster-woman away.
According to other versions, she's still alive someplace.
Master Zeke, what's that next to you?
Oh, this.
lt's like a charm of sorts, handed down within my family.
What a beautiful sword.
They say this blade can slay monsters.
l carry it with me instead of an amulet.
Why? Why is that sword in Zeke's possession?
And the light it's emitting...
Oh, my apologies.
lt was rude of me to unsheathe a sword in front of a lady.
No, don't worry about that.
lf he has that sword, then could he be...
Could Zeke be a Baron by blood?
A Baron...
lt's just thunder.
Aren't you a little old to be scared of it?
Scary things are scary!
Hey, what's that?
Oh, him, he looked so scared outside the window all alone, so l brought him inside.
lsn't he cute?
Wow...
l lack power... l lack the power to kill that Baron!
You'll give me your power.
You have nothing to fear. You will become one with me.
Now, open your souls and lend me your power.
Stick together, girls.
Flare!
Come now, give me your power.
Mineru!
Who's there?!
l live by the sword and serve the sword: Neris.
That sword...
lt's the evil crusher master sword, Vigor Blade Lague.
Though, it appears it doesn't respect you as its wielder.
Even if the sword is real, you cannot defeat me.
And once l suck out your life force, l'll be able to defeat Baron Zeke.
Squirm, wriggle in pain.
Do so and your life force will strengthen.
And when l suck it in...
That's far enough, Ternel!
Monster which has survived 300 years,
l know not how you broke your seal,
but l, Baron Zeke, will seal you into the depths of darkness anew!
How amusing.
Attack me if you think you can win!
What's wrong, Zeke? You can't attack me now, can you?
Forget about us! Kill her, Zeke!
Kill her! Hurry!
What're you just standing there for?! Zeke!
Seems you can't do it. How about now?
Stop hurting them. l admit defeat.
This day has finally come.
My curse from 300 years ago shall rip open your body and offer your heart to him.
This world shall become the World of Darkness!
''Him''?
That doesn't concern you.
Zeke!
l'm gonna take my time killing you.
l'm gonna squeeze every last drop of the Baron blood out of you.
Zeke... Zeke!
Now's my chance!
Flare!
Stop! That sword can only be used by the chosen one!
Stop! Put it down!
l don't have time to be chosen.
l'll be the one doing the choosing.
Behold, sword, lend me your power.
That's...
This... This can't be!
lmpossible...
Now's your chance to escape!
l've got something else in mind.
Huh? ls it morning already?
Keep it down, lemme sleep some more.
Look! Polarine!
What?
Ah! What the heck happened?!
l dunno.
Ah, where's Lord Zeke? Where?!
Oh, Lord Zeke!
Lord Zeke, what's with all those girls?!
You really have no morals to two-time me with those girls.
l know we haven't done that yet, but still...
Okay, ladies, lemme drive you to town.
But our hearts are connected as one, and...
Ah! Wait for me, Lord Zeke!
Polarine! What about the luggage?!
Your luggage is right here.
We have no place to go. Please let us go with you.
Why not? Follow me!
Well then, let's get going.
Okay!
Why does it have to be so cramped?!
There's plenty of room back here, Polarine.
l'm fine here, thanks.
lt's beautiful.
Who was that girl?
l must see her again.
The sword chose you.
The master of the sword is also my master.
For as long as l shall live, l, Neris, will swear fealty to you.
Nuts, what have l got myself into?
This, too, is fate.
Oh, what the hey. Let's go, Neris.
Still not enough just yet...