YOU'RE ALL SCUM
You're all scum!
Mirai-chan.
That's what the entire academy thinks about 2-B!
This class is a dumping ground for students...
...who are a bother for the academy and the teachers!
A guy who punched a teacher!
A guy who has ridiculously low grades!
A baseball fanatic that practices from morning to well into the afternoon!
A guy who's too loud!
A guy who refuses to talk!
An otaku!
And an alien!
Nyuririn!
That's why people think it's okay to look down on 2-B...
...because we've all been grouped together!
This isn't just the transfer student's problem!
This is mine, no, it's our problem!
Mirai-chan... l'll do it!
l have a competition coming up, so count me out.
Sora...
What are you going to do?
No way.
l want no part.
Boss! Say something!
You're all scum!
This, coming from you?
Yikes.
Oh well...
ACT II: NAUGHTY YOUTH
l didn't expect you to be so thorough.
Same goes for you. l didn't expect your boobs to be so soft.
That wasn't exactly a compliment, you know...
No bra and no underwear, eh?
lt's getting warmer, so...
...l'm starting to feel...
Stop staring!
Don't stare? You're so excited your pussy is twitching.
N...No...
Come on, stick your ass out more.
l can see everything.
N...No...
You're such a dirty girl... You're soaked.
Don't just stop!
Please...
l didn't know you had a cute side.
Th...That's...
No!
P...Please. Stick it in...
Huh? Why are we doing this, again?
Because you're a guy and l'm a girl.
No, that's not what l mean.
Who cares about that. Be more rough with me...
Now l remember!
l saved you when you got busted
by a professor for smoking.
Oh really?
Be more grateful, will ya'!
Th...That's why l'm letting you fuck me...
Putting that aside...
lt's so good! l think l'm going to cum!
l want you to help out in the match against the Theater Club.
That has nothing to do with this!
You want me to stop?
Don't be so mean!
Are you going to help?
Fine!
Good!
l'm going to cum!
Don't cum inside!
lt's a duel! Transfer student!
What? The ball...
...disappeared! Why you...!
Kshnk!
l lost. . .
l... l won...
M...My ears...
How did you like that? N...Next is...
lf l keep doing this... l'm definitely going to die.
Take that!
How'd you like that!
Why you...!
You little...!
You bastard!
That's it...for...to...day...
Morning!
Hey!
Morning.
Yeah.
Hey. Did you do your homework?
Oh no, l forgot!
Yeah Akina, but. . .
What is this?
lsn't it a masterpiece? lt took me all night to write it.
The climax will be the hot-blooded Mutant Eleven against a mysterious...
...evil alien army. lt's a fight with psychic powers, and the fate of the galaxy's on the line!
What a super-thriller!
lt's such a grandiose story. Sounds interesting.
Doesn't it, Momiji-chan?
Yeah right!
What?
Are you planning on making some B-rate movie? lt's a play!
You couldn't even use this for a manga!
Shock!
Anyway, how are you doing with getting everyone involved?
L...Leave that department to me.
The guys with a flower mark are in.
That's amazing!
This isn't enough. We need the entire class help to do a play.
E...Everyone?
Of course!
Good morning!
What's going on?
She came?
For real?
No way!
So what's going on?
She's taking time off?
Yes. l saw it on the celebrity gossip news this morning.
Oh...
You must be Saku Yoshijiro-kun. l'm Uzuk Amui.
Mirin-chan sent me an email and told me what's going. Nice to meet you.
We're best friends.
Can l help out too?
Oh really?
Welcome, we'd love to have you.
Amu-chan...
ldiot!
OFFICE LADY: KANAKO, 23 YEARS OLD
W...What are you doing here? The campus already closed a while ago.
Sorry. l didn't get any sleep last night. l didn't realize l fell asleep.
You're from 2-B, right?
You're Takano Hijiri... On the library staff.
Perfect timing. Hey...
l can't help out in the play. l'm too busy with my library duties.
Can't you do something?
There's something on the floor.
ls this yours?
OFFICE LADY: KANAKO, 23 YEARS OLD
lt... lt's not mine!
l'll put this back.
l'll help you.
You came here to masturbate, didn't you?
Wh...What are you...
That book... Read it.
l told you. l said l'd help. Read it out loud.
What... No!
Oh, that's right! Let's make this into
a play with you in the starring role.
Okay, l'll let everyone know right away.
W...Wait!
''Kyoko did as she was told...''
As she was told, what?
''She placed her hand on her chest.''
Like this?
Just keep reading.
''The man's hand was on top as if he was covering her breast.''
And?
''He started to fondle her while licking her neck.''
No...
''After the man fondled her breast thoroughly...''
''...he stuck his other hand inside her skirt.''
l see. This is informative.
l don't want this!
l'm just doing what you're telling me to do.
But you told me to read it...
And?
''Excited, Kyoko willingly...''
Willingly, what?
lsn't that enough?
lt doesn't say that in the book.
Stupid Kyoko.
Are we really going to do it?
What does it say?
''Like a dog, Kyoko...''
''...lifted her behind and begged.''
Good girl.
''The man could not hold himself back.''
''After he placed his hands on Kyoko's supple behind, with one thrust...''
Thrust, what?
''His hard, gleaming penis...e...entered...''
What? You came with me just
sticking it in? Kyoko hasn't cum yet.
So what happens?
l can't, if you do that...
What are Kyoko's lines? Come on!
''F...Fuck me more!''
Ahhh... l can't anymore!
What happens to them at the end?
''They climaxed at the same time, and...''
''Th...The man poured every ounce of his lust... inside Kyoko...''
Okay!
W...wait! No!
l'm going to cum!
N...No!
Stupid Kyoko...
This is getting exhausting...
W...What the?
B...Boss...
Why are you sleeping in the classroom?
l had something to do... l forgot to go home.
A young girl shouldn't stay out all night.
lt's fine. l'm on campus.
By the way, your look is a bit suggestive, you know.
My look?
Boss, here...
This one's the real masterpiece!
You wrote another one?
Yeah, l don't want to lose to the Theater Club, so...
What's this?
Your script. l edited it... Read it.
lt's amazing!
She's amazing!
l read it!
l read yours too.
This is way better. lt's different from what l envisioned, but...
...the parts that were important to me are still there.
But then l thought, l want to read a story that you wrote yourself.
l'm sorry. l guess l didn't realize l was running away.
l wished for this to happen somewhere in my heart, but...
You based your second script off of this, didn't you?
Yeah, l found it in the library yesterday.
You had this book too?
l was surprised that you had the same book as l did.
But thanks to that, l've made up my mind.
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
What are you doing with the lights off?
What about you, what are you doing here so late! You scared me!
l had a feeling l would see you here...
That outfit...
l was getting fitted into costume.
l won't be able to wear this to the theater much anymore, but...
...l wanted you to see it.
l got a part in a movie. My manager was like, ''let's find new opportunities"...
l'm playing a rude, vulgar girl with an attitude.
l see... But that part is perfect for you!
That's not a compliment!
l was lying.
l always had a mask on.
l hated coming to school, so l ran away from it...
Now that being a performer is hard work, l'm running away again.
Where do l belong?
Please... be gentle...
ls it your first time?
Yes.
l'm so embarrassed...
They're small, so it's probably not satisfying for you.
Don't worry about it.
l was actually hoping you'd say ''of course they're satisfying''...
Sorry.
That's... No!
lt hurts!
lt's... lt's hot! lt's hot!
lt's so big... lt's inside...
lt's so good... l've never felt like this before.
Amu, you'll only be in pain for a little while longer.
Okay...
My insides... They're hot. lt's coming all the way inside!
l want more...
l'll become a great actress, so that you can be my fan.
l should've asked for an autograph.
Morning, Boss!
What? That was so rude!
Yeah, but...
Here. You can have this.
lf you sleep with it under your pillow, you'll have good dreams.
Come on. Let's go.
More like nightmares...