We're just having a hard time believing it, you know?
Exposing you to the school won't do us any good, anyway.
But just having us watch is enough to get you wet.
l'll say. Just look at how high these are sticking up.
Check it out, her hips are doing the dirty dance.
Don't talk like that...
Just admit you're a pervert already.
That's not true...
Oh, no?
Then what's this?
You're this wet and still insist you're not a pervert?
Well?
Looks like you just couldn't wait to be touched.
No, l just...
You just what?
Say it!
l wish Kyouka hadn't ordered us not to rape her, because l really wanna!
You're lying! She doesn't do things like that!
Man, she still trusts Kyouka.
Touch me...
Touch me more...
Give me a break. How can l when you've got this?
More...
Hey, l can't take it anymore.
Don't hog all the fun, asshole!
lt's too much! l'm gonna come!
Me too!
There it is... That hot stuffs all over me...
lt's all over me...
l want to come...
Keep tormenting me...
Man, she still trusts Kyouka.
lt's a lie, right, Kyouka?
Hello.
Kagekiyo?
What were you doing, Futaba?
Sorry, l wasn't near my room.
l haven't seen you in two days... and l was worried.
No, l was at school. l just wasn't around.
Hey, Kagekiyo. You sound strange.
l-l don't think l do...
Maybe l'm catching a cold.
Thanks for worrying about me. You'll see me again tomorrow.
By the way, it looked like you had Kyouka on your mind.
Are you in that fan club of hers?
l'm not interested in that.
You're the only one l'm interested in.
Come on, Kagekiyo. You're cute.
l'm sure there are plenty of girls interested in you...
...so there's no need to flatter me.
l never expected you to call me ''cute.''
l'm a guy, after all.
Sorry to keep you on the phone so long. l'll get going...
Hey, Futaba.
l've always found you more attractive than you give yourself credit for.
Thanks, Kagekiyo.
Why'd he say a thing like that all of a sudden?
And l wanted to ask him more about Kyouka...
That does it! l can't stand it anymore!
Kyouka, take it off me!
Please...
You're so selfish... Can't you endure it a little longer?
But you said it would just be for one day!
ls this how much you need to release some white stuff?
But l think you need to hold out a bit longer.
But if you keep playing with me there, l won't be able to...
l know you like it.
When you mess with a guy's asshole, their cocks seem to get harder.
l wonder if that's true for you.
lt doesn't hurt. l bet you're used to it.
Stop... l can't stand it anymore...
My hips keep moving on their own!
Please, take it off!
l'll bet it's a lot bigger and harder than usual, Futaba.
lf you put it in now, l just might break.
l'm sorry. l can't help it! l think l'm gonna come!
With your finger in my ass...
You enjoy being tantalized like this, don't you?
After all, you're a masochist.
Look how much naughty juice has oozed through the chastity belt.
Forgive me! Kyouka, forgive me!
You smell pretty strong, Futaba.
You're taking baths, aren't you?
Wow, that's incredible.
lt looks like you like being teased, you masochist, so l won't touch it.
lt's not just your boy part that's sensitive, is it?
This got plenty wet, even though it couldn't be touched.
l don't feel right...
Help me, Kyouka!
You really want me to mess with both, right?
Your boy part's standing tall as a tree.
Come on, touch me there too...
No, today l'm only going to touch you here.
l'll punish you if you touch it yourself.
Please, l'm begging you... Mess with both of them...
Come on, Kyouka! l can't stand it anymore!
You're just not patient enough, Futaba.
lt's about time l make you come.
l can't believe you're doing it like this!
lt's about to come out even though you didn't touch it!
l'm coming...
Wow, Futaba! Look at all that thick juicy stuff!
You're so cute when you come.
Hey!
Kagekiyo...
Futaba.
This rain came out of nowhere.
You'll catch a cold.
You're so kind, Kagekiyo.
What? What's the deal?
l really am a girl.
Even though l have this body, l really am a girl...
You seeing it makes it this hard, but l really am a girl...
l'm not lying.
You stuck up for me...
...but l really was the one behind the incident with the ladies' bathroom.
l'm sorry... l'm sorry!
You're mad because l lied to you so long, aren't you?
But l have feelings for you...
ls that all you have to say?
l mean, l'm definitely surprised.
But no matter what your body's like, you're still you.
Besides, l've always loved you too!
Are you sure you want me?
You're so silly. l do, Futaba.
Your boobs are cute.
Don't lick them too much!
You're gonna get me all crazy if you keep that up...
This is looking amazing too.
Look at how hard it's getting, Futaba.
No, don't rub it!
Wow... lt's wild, what happens to your pussy...
Girls really do get wet.
l wish you'd stop talking like that.
No...
Does it feel good when l stroke this?
Yeah, l think it probably feels as good as it does for you.
l really want you to use your tongue, not just your hand...
But he's a boy, so he'll probably be against that...
You're overflowing down here. Which feels better?
The front or the back?
l can't tell you a thing like that, silly...
ln other words, they both feel great.
l think... l think l'm going to come already!
No, don't watch!
Wow, look at it all!
lt's so embarrassing...
l figured it'd calm down once you ejaculated.
Yeah... ls that how it is for guys too?
Yeah, l guess so.
But yours is up, Kagekiyo.
Well, l still haven't... you know...
Do you want to put it in? l don't mind if you don't.
Do you have times when you want to ''put it in'' too?
Jeez...
Don't ask a girl questions like that, silly.
This is the first time l've ever seen you pout.
lt's cute.
Silly...
You're pretty, Futaba.
You're embarrassing me...
lt's going in...
Kagekiyo is entering me...
That's deep!
D-Does it hurt? Are you okay?
Yeah, l'm fine.
Futaba, yours got big again.
My hips are moving on their own...
Yes...
Play with it...
lt feels good in both places!
l-l love you!
You can come inside me, okay?
l'm about to, Futaba!
lt's so warm!
l'm going to come with you!
l'm coming!
l guess this is a little awkward.
ls it?
lt felt good.
Which part felt better?
Silly.
You're acting differently than usual.
You seem more self-important now.
Do l really? But l could say the same for you.
You're always so strong-willed, ill-tempered, and cynical, and yet...
Yet?
You were really cute during sex.
You really are silly...
Want to go again?
Hey, wait a minute...
Stop... Don't touch me in weird places...
How was yesterday, Futaba?
Kagekiyo has a big one, doesn't he? lt got me going too.
Kyouka...
Your girl part's as sensitive as ever.
lt's already shamefully wet.
Stop... l feel embarrassed...
You know that time you talked to Kagekiyo on your cell phone?
l was in his room then.
You like being tormented this way, don't you?
You're lying, Kyouka...
You're lying so you can mess with my head...
Hey, Futaba, l know an interesting place we can go.
Where?
Somewhere you can enjoy the things you like.
On my face! My face!
More! Give me more!
What do you think, Futaba?
Nobody comes here to the old school building at night.
You can make as much noise as you like.
Please...
What's the matter, Futaba?
Do you want to have guy juice all over you, like me?
Or...
...do you want to shoot hot goo all over from this unclean thing?
lt looks like it's about to burst.
Looks like it wants out so bad that it can't stand it.
Okay, enough teasing! Please, take off the belt!
Oh, but don't you like being teased, masochist?
You're looking rough.
Take a load off her, guys.
Now we can get down to it.
lt sure is a lot of fun hanging with you, Kyouka.
Please, take off the belt!
Hey, don't hog all the fun.
You're right.
Untie...
Untie my hands.
l wonder what'll happen if l do this.
Damn, that's tight...
Here too!
l can't stand it anymore!
Let me let out some sperm!
lt's throbbing.
l wonder what it feels like to come without squirting.
Please, take off the belt and rub it!
l need to ejaculate right now!
Kagekiyo.
Futaba...
Kagekiyo really does have a big one.
l'll let you enjoy it when l'm done.
But l thought you said you loved me...
Kagekiyo...
Far out!
She's still tied up, but she's unloading anyway.
Hey...
Gross!
Look...
Look at my body...
l'm a girl, but l've got this naughty thing...
Oh no!
l'm gonna come!
l'm coming!