Ow! My butt... My butt!
Huh?
Murakoshi...
W-What's that...?
Do you understand now? There are deep places hidden in your heart.
Yes.
Hmm... Looks like this thing is for real.
That's right, I need a trigger word for you...
I've got it!
''Panty-wetting phone call.'' Yes.
When you hear the words ''panty-wetting phone call,'' you will fall into your deep place.
Panty-wetting phone call...
Into my... deep place...
Yes.
Why... am I touching myself at school?
Oh, yes! It feels so good! Why does it feel so good?
Oh, no!
I can't... I'm going to pee!
I can't stop. I can't stop!
I have to keep doing it for the video camera!
I have to show myself peeing. For Murakoshi!
Wha-? What do you think you're doing, you pervert?!
This is the girl's locker room!
What are you doing in here?! Get out, you creep!
Wait... ls that my towel?
Get your hands off my towel!
Huh?
W-What is that thing?
Your breasts are as big as ever.
A little milk girl like you must not have a care in the world.
That's not true... Yuu...
Yuu!
Hmm... Let's talk a little.
I'm the person you can depend on most, after all.
You poor thing.
''Two stiff shoulders.''
Aya, call for this Yuu person you mentioned.
Do it.
STUDENT GUIDANCE OFFICE
What do you think you're doing, Murakoshi?!
Teacher, you are now feeling very relaxed.
Yes. I feel very nice now.
Yes, that's right. You will now answer all my questions truthfully.
Yes. I will answer them.
By the way, you will be irresistibly drawn to suck the thing between my legs.
It will now be your favorite thing to do.
My favorite thing. Yes, my favorite thing.
So, you have this side to you, huh?
Teacher, you like it so much, even I don't know how long you'll keep it in your mouth.
I'm... I'm cumming!
Does it taste good, Teacher?
Yes. This is my favorite thing.
Really? Then I'll let you swallow it every day.
You will? I'm so glad!
And in return, I'll help you to get better at it.
This world's all about give and take, right?
Thank you! But isn't it ''give and give''?
No, give and take.
Of... Of course. If you say so, it must be right.
Oh, listen to me!
''Brazen little me.''
STUDENT GUIDANCE OFFICE
What are you staring at? You're creeping me out!
I have to discuss something with the principal.
I don't know what your problem is, but...
Tell me, Teacher, isn't there something that you want?
Murakoshi, did you hit your head or something?!
I wish you were more honest with yourself.
Oh, forget this! Get out of here!
Oh, is that the attitude you're going to take?
''Brazen little me.''
Please recall for me. What is your favorite thing?
Favorite thing... My favorite thing...
That's right. As much as your head denies it, your body desires it, does it not?
Teacher, you want it so bad that you stuff your mouth with student's dicks after school, don't you?
No! No, I don't!
Teacher, if you do that, even a guy like me who jerks off all day won't be able to perform!
No!
Huh?
What is that?
I've seen it somewhere before...
N-No way!
No way! No way!
No, no, no!!
By the way, Teacher, even though you're a virgin,
didn't you feel the pain of having your cherry popped a few days ago?
Though it didn't seem that painful to me.
''Brazen little me.''
Teacher, you will forget that I've hypnotized you.
Yes. I will not do anything.
Honestly... That sadistic streak of yours is just an act, isn't it?
Your vagina walls are a switch.
Each time my cock goes through them, you will lose all your shame and reason.
You'll get hornier and hornier.
Hornier... and hornier...
Very good. And your nipples are a urination switch.
Urination... I'll want to pee myself.
Oh, I forgot.
Principal, you won't think it's strange to see me having sex with a teacher.
I will not.
Right, you will not. And you'll start masturbating when you see it.
It'll be natural. It'll be just like watching a porn video.
You won't be able to stop with one or two shots.
You won't stop even if blood comes out. You won't stop till you die.
Porn! Jerking off!
Like a monkey!!
Murakoshi's dick is grinding into me.
Teacher, concentrate on my penis, but please teach me as well.
If you don't spread your legs more and show me where they connect, I won't learn anything.
Right! Come into me, Murakoshi!
Oh, my clit's starting to swell, too!
Look! Each time you go in and out, your love juice makes it slipperier and slipperier!
Oh, your dick is great!
Pinch my nipples!
My nipples!
Oh, when you throw my nipple switch...
Murakoshi! Murakoshi! Your dick is so hard!
Maybe I gave her too strong a suggestion.
It'll be no fun if she loses her mind.
I've got it. Say, Teacher?
Murakoshi... Murakoshi...
Teacher, after you orgasm 7 times, you will fall unconscious.
Seven times! Seven times! Fall unconscious on lucky 7!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
Your dick! Your dick! Oh, Murakoshi, your dick...!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! Being a girl is amazing! Yes! Yes! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Here it comes. I'm peeing. It's coming!
It's here!
I'm cumming! My tits... I'm cumming!
It's in me again!
Your fat dick! Your fat dick is in me!
It's so thick! You're gonna cum on me again, aren't you?
Your dick is so big! I feel so dirty!
Here it comes... Here it comes...!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Bravo, bravo, bravo!
Bravo!!
Get away from Aya!
No!!
No, no!
''Two stiff shoulders.''
Listen, Aya... Never cry out again.
Yes. I will not cry out.
Yuu will be the cameraman.
You'll have the honor of photographing her as she gets her cherry popped.
Oh yeah, and Yuu, you will not have a heart attack. You're completely cured of that illness.
I can't have you dying on the sidelines.
Completely cured...
Come on, Aya. We need to let Yuu have a good look at this.
Aya...
Forgive me. l... l...
No! Save me... Yuu...
It's no use! No use, no use! Yuu can't do anything but watch your tits flop up and down!
No! Yuu, Yuu, Yuu!
Yuu!
Aya, forgive me! Forgive me! l... l...
No! No! No! No!
Stop it! Don't hurt Aya!
Your request...
...is denied!
No!!
Stop!!
The popping is complete.
Yuu, shame on you. You should look up to Aya now that she's become a woman.
Yuu, forgive me. l... I love you!
I love you! Forgive me!
Aya!
My insides... My insides are gonna burst!
Stop it! That's enough! I'm begging you! I'll do anything!
I don't have to do anything for a stranger. Because I can make you do anything I want!
That's the sort of country we live in!
Do you understand? You may feel some pain at first.
But soon it'll feel so good that you won't notice. Even though it'll be my dick inside you.
Even though my hymen will be broken for the first time with your thick dick, it'll feel good.
Stiff shoulders. Stiff shoulders.
No! I'm getting off on it! Even though this is the first time my cherry's been popped!
I've been trained!
He's turned me into a pervert!
How do you like it, Aya? How do you like having an orgasm in front of your childhood sweetheart?
No! You're so deep inside me!
Yuu...
Yuu... l... I'm a pervert!
A pervert who likes getting fucked deep!
Harder! More, more!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
TEA CEREMONY ROOM
C-Can I help you, Murakoshi?
l-If you don't want anything, could you please leave?
''Panty-wetting phone call.''
The Kitagawa couple was duller than I expected, but you'll please me, won't you Miss Kurasawa?
Miss Kurasawa, I've been thinking for a while that the tea ceremony club doesn't serve very good tea.
Yes... You may be right.
So, today I've brought some good tea with me.
Oh? What sort of tea did you bring?
This.
This... Yes, it might be very good.
This... could be incredible. I'm sure the tea will be great.
We can't just do this from one direction. We need to mix it up a bit, right?
Right, that's it. Do that and I'll be sure to make a tasty batch.
It really is tasty.
Now, Miss Kurasawa, this time I want you to let me drink yours.
Huh?
My... what?
Your tea, of course.
It's going in! The tea... The tea!
This is good tea ware. The sort of stuff Hisahide Matsunaga would surrender a castle for.
It's moving! It's moving, it's moving!
The tea's coming out! My tea! My tea, my tea!
You're chipping my tea bowl!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming with tea!
Everyone, quiet down.
I know this is sudden, but I'd like to present a new transfer student to you today.
Um, Miss Yano?
Huh? Teacher, that desk over there...
Hm? What about it, Miss Yano?
That desk... I could have sworn someone was sitting there before.
Hey, would you all quiet down?
So, what about that desk?
I said be quiet!
It's just...
So, Midori Yano, huh?
She looks tasty.
How good of her to come from her exclusive school to sacrifice her body to me!