Boys' Locker Room
Sorry l'm late.
We'd wait forever for you, Kyouka.
Study hall or not, it's still hard to slip out of class.
l bet it was hard to wait, with it this big.
Give us some too.
Don't be in such a hurry. l've got enough for all of you.
l can't wait anymore...
Come on, don't be impatient.
Oh, well, l guess l don't mind.
Hey!
No, slow down a little!
That hard thing's inside me...
Hey! Don't hog all the fun.
Pipe down. lt's first come, first served.
No fighting, boys.
l'll use my hands and mouth, okay?
Give me some too.
Don't worry. l'll be sure to make you feel good.
Whoa, Kyouka. You're clamping down hard now.
Well, it just feels so good.
l won't last at this rate!
Same here!
Wait! We'll all come together!
Here... Here it comes!
Yes, let it out. Please, cover me with it!
l'm defiled by everybody's semen...
My whole body's slimy with it!
Somehow...
...it's just not enough.
lt's hard to believe anyone these days goes the old-fashioned route like this.
Oh, man...
l'm still burning up.
He's at it again.
l can hear you.
Jeez, l still had some in there.
l'll show you all of me.
Sis?
l don't mind if you jerk off to this.
We might be siblings, but not by blood.
He's been trying to put it in the back door lately.
What? ls your boyfriend a pervert?
l don't know. Maybe...
So what happened? Did he get in?
Of course he hasn't yet! l mean, l'm worried it'll tear...
A finger wouldn't hurt that much though.
You mean you've tried putting a finger in your butt?
But you seem like such the quiet type, Kyouka.
Not just fingers, but bigger, harder things too...
lt's a different pleasure from my pussy...
...and once l felt anal one time, l couldn't stop doing it.
No, l just read that in a magazine.
Hey, maybe this isn't a good idea...
Didn't you give me that love letter?
Don't worry. Nobody will see us in this stall.
Wow, you're hard as a rock.
Kyouka!
Kyouka! lf you keep sucking, l'll...
No, don't come yet!
Put your hands on my head.
Like this?
l can't help it! l'm coming!
Yeah... Get that hot white stuff all over my face...
You're a lively one.
Now l want you to put it in here.
l feel you inside me...
Deep inside!
Oh, yeah! lt feels so good when you stir me up in there!
Oh, not that!
l'm a sucker for that! Don't touch it!
l'm gonna come! l'm gonna come!
There's so much... all over me...
Hey, Kyouka, we should get started too.
Don't mess around. l can't stand it anymore...
l'm kind of bored with this. Wonder if there's anything more stimulating...
Don't mind us. We'll help ourselves.
You've got some guts.
Coming here wearing school uniforms...
A cute girl like you shouldn't be hanging out with guys like them.
He's right. There's lots of dangerous people around here.
Want us to protect you?
N-No thanks.
That kind of attitude hurts our feelings, you know.
l guess your body's gonna have to console us.
C'mon!
Please! Don't do this!
Tie her up with this.
No! That hurts!
Very nice. l knew it'd turn me on...
...seeing a girl tied up.
Please stop this. l'll call rape!
Go ahead and shout, if you can!
Now here!
l'll plug up her other mouth too.
Hey, she's already soaking wet.
l bet the bitch had this in mind from the get-go.
ln that case, we better not fail to please.
Time for me to join in too.
No! Not that!
Shut up!
T-That hurts! Don't do it there!
Quit lying. lt went in easy enough. l bet you've had it up the ass before.
Don't say things like that...
lf you keep that up, l'll...
She's good!
Whoa! She started squeezing down really hard!
She must've liked the taste.
Oh! My ass and pussy feel so good!
Yeah! Wow!
More! More!
l think l'm gonna come!
l'm coming!
l'm... l'm all full of hot stuff...
lt's not easy, taking three of them at once.
lt feels three times as good, but it leaves you three times as exhausted.
Today wore me out.
Sis...
He's at it again.
S-Sis!
You don't need to hide it.
Wouldn't you like to have a look at this?
W-What are you doing?
Hey, l'm the one who's swallowing my embarrassment to show this to you.
So take a good look.
See? My shy part's pretty and pink, isn't it?
Wow, so that's what it looks like...
That's right.
Good... Very good.
What's wrong?
l'm about to come, Sis...
That's fine. Now, it's my turn to make you feel good.
Well? Feels good?
Yeah, unbelievably good...
Sis...
l'm coming!
lt's all over me...
Your sister's covered in hot stuff.
This time it'll feel better for both of us.
Wow, and you just blew your load too.
M-Maybe we shouldn't...
lt's so hard it's hitting me way in the back.
S-Sis...
lt's okay. We're only step-siblings.
Your pussy's engulfing it!
Oh, yeah!
This is incredible!
l feel like l'm melting!
Sis, l think l'm gonna come again!
Go for it! Let it all loose inside me!
l'm coming, coming...
Coming!
Study hall
lt's still not enough.
The delinquents, my brother...
They weren't big deals.
Hey, listen, everyone. l'd like to try using this.
What is it?
lzumi?
Kyouka, what are you doing?
So that's what it looks like inside a girl!
l can't help myself!
Stop it!
Hey!
Quiet down! Class is in...
After that, l pulled some strings...
...and managed to keep the whole thing quiet.
At first it was new and fresh...
...getting to do as much as l wanted all the time.
But eventually l got tired of that too, and every day seemed boring.
l wanted some new stimuli, so l transferred...
Still, l never thought l'd find anything this interesting.
This is going to be fun.