l knew Erika was interested in him.
But the one he smiled at...
...wasn't Erika.
l wonder why l didn't turn him down?
No, l know exactly why l didn't turn him down. That's because...
l slept with a guy who l neither liked nor disliked.
''Guys are so lame.''
That's what l had thought.
The fact that l got wet from a lame guy touching me...
...made me hate my body even more.
l wouldn't have done it, if that hadn't happened!
l can never beat you!
Just keep on trying and you'll eventually get faster.
l did it! This is the first time l've been able to beat you, Akino!
Bummer! You finally beat me!
l wonder if it's because of my breasts?
When l measured them the other day, they were two centimeters bigger.
l wish l had yours, Erika.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean!
This is not good. My time hasn't improved lately.
l think they've gotten bigger again.
They're nothing but a hinderance when l run.
l think my thighs and butt are getting bigger too.
l hate being a woman...
My time isn't improving at all.
What's wrong, Akino?
Maybe your breasts are too heavy?
Y... Yeah...
l'm kind of tired. l think l'm done for today.
A-Are you okay?
Men... They're all pathetic...
What's so fun about fondling that?
l could care less.
Fondle them much as you like.
Don't you get bored of sucking on my nipple? You're like a baby.
Now that?
Oh brother... What are we, cats and dogs?
Men are all the same.
All they do is fondle, pinch and roll it around...
They get excited when it gets perky.
What are you, idiots?
Hey, where do you think you're licking! You pervert!
This is getting boring.
Come on. Hurry up and cum already.
She's starting to get into it.
l'll take her mouth. Come on! Open your mouth!
Nice... Her tongue feels great.
Then l'll take her pussy.
l'm so wet. l hate myself...
You want to cum, right?
Cum, already! All they care about is cumming.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Erika!
Maybe our friendship was over a long time ago.
Here. This is for your pleasure.
Well? Are you satisfied?
Are you satisfied after squirting your dirty cum all over me?
He's fast.
Erika, what are you looking at?
l was just thinking how fast he is.
Oh, let's see...
Who does Erika have the hots for?
That's not what l mean. Who does Erika have the hots for?
That's not what l mean.
Ew! That foreign guy?
You have bad taste, Erika.
l told you! That's not what l mean.
Did you know it's rumored his country is developing a hydrogen bomb?
Yeah... But... He was really fast...
Are you awake, Miss?
l wanted to taste you again so l came for you.
Nooo! Please, no more!
Are you awake?
l'm Kaiya.
l'll go tell the elders you're awake.
Me?
lndeed. We don't know for sure, but...
...if the gate appeared because you descended to this world...
Th... That can't be...
Anyhow, get some rest today.
Let's think about what we need to do another time.
She's right. Don't worry about what this Geezer is saying!
Who are you calling a ''Geezer?''
Thanks.
All right. l'm going to make the rounds.
Me too! l'll go tell everyone to be on guard!
What? You want to fuck me too?
Oh. You're not like her at all.
Thanks for the food.
My apologies we couldn't give you a more proper meal.
Not at all. lt was delicious.
l see they've left you alone.
E... Elder!
Even if they were here, they'd be helpless against me but...
Long time no see, Falcal.
To think you chose to live after being disgraced...
l'm taking the girl.
l wouldn't if l were you. You know who l am.
l'm sure you haven't forgotten...
The World of Darkness and Flames; you and the others were banished to...
Why, Elder! Why did you let them take her! Elder!
Even if l retaliated, l wouldn't have been able to defeat them.
Damn it! l would have fought to the death if l were there!
We are the descendants of the banished ones...
You can't expect a good harvest from seeds planted in poor soil.
''Banished ones!'' That's all that comes out of that damn Geezer's mouth!
Be careful. Are you okay?
You have to be careful!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Are you okay?
Hey! You have to be more careful!
Hey, Kaiya! Are you okay?
l just remembered... She's...
Welcome back, Missy.
Commander Jan ordered us to teach you what happens when you run away.
You're really going to get it now.
Let's see...
Wait!
l'll take her place.
Don't make us laugh! How is a boring body like yours going to satisfy us!
Come on, give her a chance. Let's find out how much she can take.
Throw the other one back in the isolation cell!
And don't let her get away this time!
You better not think we'll let her go because you took her place.
l...
l'm just doing what l have to do.
What?! She went to rescue her alone?
l'm not certain she went to rescue her but she said...
''l was saved by her. That's why l have to go.''
She was saved by her? What's that about?
l don't know the details either.
Why didn't you stop her!
Have l ever meddled in your business?
But that doesn't mean...
She still hasn't awakened though!
Such small breasts...
Her skin is really soft though.
Look at her, she's wet.
Come on. Spread your legs.
Whoa, stand up!
Feels good, eh? You're sticking your ass out.
You can do it.
You're sticking your ass in my face. What do you want me to do, huh?
Let's get down to business.
We'll let you have the biggest cock first.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
But... That's so...
You bastard!
Damn it! How many men did she get?
Five... No, six men!
Damn bitch!
Hey, what are you going to do?
This is unforgivable. She's going to get a pussy full of cum before l kill her!
Thank you, Sissy.
Come on. Say thank you!
Thank you, Sissy...
Be careful next time, okay?
What is it? Hurry up and walk!
l just remembered...
Hey! Wait!
Damn it, she's fast!
Come on. What's wrong? Say something!
Come on! Come on!
Kaiya!
What is she doing here? Did she run away again?
S... She's...
Kaiya!
Erika...
Yeah, l know.
l have to go... for Kaiya's sake too.
What's wrong? What are you doing, standing there?
Hey Erika! What are you doing there?
That can't be... l'm Erika's...
That girl has left, huh?
You! l won't let you get in the way.
l have no intention of getting in the way.
''Open the gate and a path shall appear.''
Those are the words that have been bestowed us.
''Listen and obey the voice.''
''Thus the gate shall open and the path shall appear.''
lt's rather different from what l was told.
All l know for sure is that the presence of foul bastards like you, makes me sick.
Perfect. l was getting sick of your ugly mug myself.
This looks much harder than training camp back at school.
Erika, you can do it! Good luck! Erika! Go for it!
Erika...
Go!
Do you really think a fallen bastard like you can defeat me?
Shut up!
Even in a situation like this, running is so much fun...
You talk big but l guess it was all bluff!
l already told you. You can't defeat me.
We shall return to the world of light, where we came from.
But seems like you've fallen too.
This can't be...
l have done everything to open the gate...
How could this be...
Why?!
''The one who plants the seeds will harvest its crop,'' eh?
What is this, a reward for working so hard? How considerate.
Fine. Show me what you got.
l...
How could l have said such a thing to Akino...
lt's my fault that Akino...
Akino!
Erika.
Akino, l'm sorry.
l had no idea how you were feeling!
lf l only stopped and thought about it, l would have known!
l was only thinking about myself!
lt's fine. We've known each other for so long.
l knew you weren't being malicious... but l was...
l couldn't take it anymore and l...
l'm the one who did something unforgivable.
We can't go back to how we were anymore.
W... Who cares!
We don't have to go back to how we were!
l just want to be friends with you!
l just want to run with you again!
Hey! We're friends, right?
Erika... You're such a...
Thank you.
Akino!
Akino...
No, let go! No!
Nooo!
Erika... Erika...
Akino...
Come, let's go together...
Yeah.
Wait! Don't leave me!
lt's useless.
You already know.
We have to atone for our sins here.
B... But...
A... Akino...
No!
Who knows when it'll be over...
We have to continue to suffer until our sins have been atoned, Erika.
No... No...
''We will fall with the others. No one is good here. Not one person...''
''This moment, when humans are engulfed by their evil doings...''
Look, Erika. My body is so light here.
Look, everyone's waiting...
Erika! Erika! Erika! Erika!