Good afternoon, this is the lunch hour news.
Our first story is an accident involving 2 buses on the highway...
There were many injured, and the clean-up is taking...
...longer than expected.
The highway is still closed.
We'll go live to the scene of the accident.
Utsumi, please go ahead.
lt's hot!
Miss Minazuki?
Miss Minazuki, are you okay?
Um, yes...
Excuse us.
What's wrong? You're not yourself.
lf something is bothering you, you can talk to me.
No, l'm fine.
Oh, don't be like that.
l know a great Chinese restaurant.
Excuse me, l need to go over my lines.
Stop, not here, people will see us.
This exceeds my expectations. Were you looking forward to this?
What is going on with me?
l don't want this.
l know l don't want this.
l can't do this anymore.
l am desiring him so much.
l'm like an animal.
Yui, can l kiss you?
You're used to it by now.
lt's like l grew a weenie.
Want to masturbate then?
Kasuya, l mean, even Master responds this way.
lt's so cute!
Master?
Can l licky-lick your weenie?
l'm so happy.
lt's getting hard.
lt tastes good!
Please wait.
l have something better.
When it peeks in from between my boobs, it's like a little animal.
lt's so cute.
Doing this with my boobs, makes my crotch juicy.
Master marked me.
lt tastes good!
You can still do more, right?
This is the best.
Master, can we stay like this for a while?
Or do you want to move because it feels so good inside me?
Don't be silly. No way.
Okay then.
When we're holding each other like this, it feels like l am one with you.
lt feels so good.
Master, l want to move.
May l move?
Master.
Your weenie is so great.
Having my pussy stimulated so strongly every day...
l feel like l'm being trained.
Am l turning into a fiend?
Master?
Am l no good?
l'm a freak!
l get raped and get into it!
So please, harder, harder!
Come!
l want a baby!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
Kazuya...
lnoue is bothering me and l don't like it.
lt's so hard to work with him as my boss.
l can imagine.
So l have an idea.
Kazuya, you're so bold today.
lt's because you seduced me.
You're such a bad boy.
Oh my, you're already hard.
That's because you...
Wait second.
No.
No, l heard something.
lt came from the recording booth.
Bastard...
Miss Kyoko, no.
But...
l'm sorry...
l guess there's not a lot of work out there.
Huh?
l was just wondering if there were any new shows that have openings.
l'm sure they're out there.
But don't count on me.
Oh come on, you're the top ranked director at the station.
Look, don't get carried away.
l'm only a director because lnoue got demoted for doing something stupid.
That's the only reason l got promoted.
Don't pout.
lt's ruining your cute face.
What's the matter?
lf, well, hypothetically speaking...
What already?!
lf you really want to be an announcer. it's not like there's nothing out there,
Oh yeah.
Yokoyama, you do have nice tits.
Thank you.
Even porn stars don't have tits like this.
So anyway, about the new show in the works...
Huh? You're interested?
Yes, of course.
We've more or less decided on our lead, but it's not set in stone.
l think you still have a chance.
lt's up to you to decide.
Nice, very nice.
lf you can't do it, that's fine.
Station master Oono's thing...
Can you tell?
l recently got some good drugs, so l can show you a good time.
Hey, hey, changing your mind now?
lt's not like you're a virgin...
You should enjoy it too.
No matter what you're feeling now, l'm a man of my word.
Kazuya, help me!
Kazuya...
Oh, so you like Mano-kun?
What's so funny?
lt's funny.
He's getting married to Yui Minazuki next spring.
That's a lie!
Why should l lie?
l'm an honest, upstanding man.
lt's a lie!
This is great.
What, you're a dead fish?
Well, that gets me excited too, so l don't care.
These are nice tits.
You're that much of a dead fish.
He was cheating on you anyway.
You're getting tight.
This whole thing...
You were getting in the way of his upcoming marriage...
...so he sent you to me, killing two birds with one stone.
There's no way!
No way!
He even sent along some Viagra so l could enjoy you better.
l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
l look forward to working closely with you.
l took them.
l took Yui's panties.
lt smells like her.
When l touch myself like this, it's like she's touching me.
Yui. Yui. Yui...
Yui!
Yui...
l'm sorry, l heard your voice and...
This isn't what it looks like...
l found them in the hall.
lf you say so, l'm sure it's true.
No, it's not like that...
l...
l really, honestly...
l'm sorry.
l'm sure that thing with Kazuya lit a fire in you.
Yui!
Your skin is so soft.
Don't say that.
But it's the truth.
You're wet.
No!
Marie, you're so cute.
Yui, no, please don't...
Are you too shy to scream?
l hear you were on fire with Kazuya.
No, it's not true.
l was just imagining his weenie inside of you moving around...
That makes me so happy.
ln that case, l will make you scream in your cute little way.
No, please, l'm going to pee!
l'm going to spray happy juice!
This time l want to come with you.
Yui.
Marie, doesn't it feel good when we rub ourselves together?
But this time...
Yui, your boobs just got bigger.
Marie!
l want you to be happy too.
No, stop, Marie...
Yui, you're nipples are so sensitive.
Then...
Yui...Yui... Yui... Yui!
Mine and yours are rubbing together!
Marie, please don't...
Don't go any faster, l'm going crazy...
l'm going to be like you.
l'm going to be filthy.
l'm getting rubbed raw! l'm going to catch on fire!
Yui! Yui! Yui! Yui!
l'm covered in happy juice!
Congratulations!
Hey, l heard you got a regular spot.
Oono is a criminal, but he did keep his promise.
When Station manager Oono got arrested for possession...
...those drugs he had on him were yours, right?
What are you getting at?
l'm not trying to blackmail you or anything.
Even a child would know that would get you arrested.
Oono was too stupid to think of it.
l'm sure you kept his weakness in your back pocket...
...in case he kept bothering you.
l was sure he was going to keep hounding me.
So it was a good thing for me that he got busted.
But it wasn't out of kindness to me, was it?
Who sends his girlfriend out on a pillow mission?
You think that because l was a ditzy pop idol...
...you could two-time me and get away with it?
l'm not that stupid!
Ouch.
You may not have thought much of us...
...but when you rescued me, and when you didn't reject me...
...when l told you how l felt, l was so happy!
l'm sorry your husband got in trouble because of me.
lt's fine, we're just married on paper.
Anyway, thanks to his demotion you became a director!
l didn't do it on my own merit.
l feel like the pressure is going to crush me.
You'll be fine, what's key in this business is timing and connections.
lf you just play the part of director, you'll get used to it.
But what shocked me most is you marrying Minazuki.
She was depressed after all that happened.
l was just being a friend and one thing led to another.
So long as you're happy, l have nothing to say.
Uh...l...
Even though things turned out this way, l'm really glad to have met you.
lt's because of you that...
Good luck.
lf you do well, l'll feel like l had a part in it, which makes me feel good.
l'm getting married to Kazuya.
l know.
l see.
This was your last chance...
My dreams will never come true anyway, is that why?
Getting it off my chest, perhaps...
l didn't mean to cause you any trouble...
You won't.
l was a lot dumber than Kazuya thought.
You'll come to the wedding, right?
Yui!
lt's hot!
No!
Stop!
Not here.
Someone will see us.
lt's getting hard.
When we're holding each other like this, it feels like l am one with you.
Am l a freak, Master?
What's wrong?
l was just thinking that happiness comes in many forms.
Does marrying me make you happy?
Yes, although Master may not believe me.
Look.
l want Master's thing, right now.
Please take good care of me forever, Master.
But if Master doesn't satisfy me, l might have an affair.
Okay?