Men are all perverted, uncivilized, low-intelligence beings that can only...
...think with their penis.
Sayuri, you're done with coaching the club, right?
Why don't we go home together?
l'm sorry...
l promised to listen to one of my student's problems.
l can't go home yet...
Then what about your house?
Another time for that too.
l promise to make it up to you so...
l'm sorry...
l guess l can't avoid it...
Sayuri, is something on your mind lately?
There are a lot of times you look depressed...
And, recently we haven't made love...
l'm a little lonely...
Thank you...
Then l'm going to go home.
Hey, Ryoko!
What?
l'm thinking about you first, and l love you!
Hey, your voice is so loud! There are still students left!
Come on!
Music Teacher Haruka Machida (Age 21)
Master!
Penis is good! lt's good!
lt feels so good!
lt's amazing!
Ms. Machida, inside your pussy is slippery and tight, it feels so good!
Slippery and tight, mine is good, too!
More...
Pound me more, Master!
lt gets tiring pounding you from the bottom.
Then this time l will move.
Master, does it feel good?
Me too...
lt's rubbing on my clitoris...
lt's so good because it's rubbing on my clitoris...
My hips move on their own.
My breasts and pussy are small but l love the penis!
l love feeling good!
Where are we...
l was cleaning up the equipment and...
Haruka Machida (Age 21)
Haruka!?
Physical Fitness Teacher Natsumi Machida (Age 21)
Where are you doing!?
Oh, sister.
Hey, you woke up?
What, Kei!?
Sister, you want to do it together?
A teacher and a student can't do such a thing!
Get away from each other!
No! l'm going to feel better!
Okay Haruka, do you want to make your sister feel good together?
Yes, Master!
What, hold on, what are you doing!?
Stop...
Stop it!
This is the thing l use to masturbate.
Sister, you are diligently a virgin and you've never masturbated before...
so this feels way too good, right?
What is this vibration...
No...My pussy is feeling numb and my mind is totally becoming white...
Sis, you came?
She's the woman Shin should train...
You are soaked.
lt's like you wet your pants.
Well with the course of events it ended up like this so l can't do anything...
l guess it felt really good huh?
Plus he did feast on one of mine too so...
Haruka, we are doing next!
Yes!
Ah- l don't want to anymore...
Why do l have to take this guy's thing...
Hold on Haruka, don't lick it...
Haruka's tongue... lt feels so good...
There...
Sis, your pussy...
it's soaked with sweat and juice, it's delicious...
Master, it's totally ready.
Okay, then you can do it.
Yes!
What Haruka, what are you...
This side is Sis and this side is mine.
l'm going to put this on and violate you, Sis.
You will feel good and l'll have it in me too so...
we can come together.
Ready? Hold on...
Wait a second...
l'm putting it in!
Haru...ka...
l put it inside Sis.
lt hurts!
Haruka, pull it out!
Pull it out! lt hurts!
So Sis you were a virgin!
Ready?
l'm going to move it so stop tensing up.
lt hurts!
Stop it...
Ms. Machida, you're at a good age and you were really a virgin.
Haruka, she's in pain so assault her more. Then it feels good.
Yes!
Sis, how is this?
No, what?
What are you doing, Haruka?
When l rub the clitoris like this,
doesn't it feel good?
No, that part is...
No, not there...
lt feels so good...
My sister is violating me and it's turning me on!
Haruka, stop it...
l'm starting to have a weird feeling!
Sis, has it started to feel good?
No, don't pound me that hard!
Mine is good too.
Sis, l can tell your pussy is all tight and soaked!
Pound me gently!
Sis is all turned on, how cute.
No!
No no no!
Ah! Right there!
What are those sisters doing!?
This is abnormal!
Haruka! Haruka! Haruka! Haruka!
Sis! Sis! Sis! Sis!
No, l...
Why am l turned on from this?
l can't...
My hands won't stop...
lt's hitting it!
No! Sis, l'm going to come...
No...
l'm...
These sisters, having incest, how stupid...
Seriously, they are like sex objects.
No, it's kind of weird!
No, Sis, l'm going to come...
lt feels way too good!
l'm about to come, l'm going to come!
Hey, hey, both of you, look alive! What are you going to do with me!?
Haruka, make Natsumi be on top!
Because her virginity was taken by you!
What, what are you going to do?
lt hurts!
No!
Not my... butt hole!
Sis, inside you, master's penis and mine are hitting each other.
lt hurts...
No... They're rubbing against each other inside.
Good...lt feels good...
No, not there!
lt feels a little strange.
No... l can't...
lt's so good inside you, Sis...
What am l...doing... l need to go home...
That was Ms. Kobuchi?
And those voices...
Sis, it's good, really good!
Haruka!
My butt and my pussy are feeling hot!
l can't hold it, l'm going to come!
lt's getting hot and something is coming!
l'm going to come with you, Sis!
Something is going to come!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming! l'm coming!
What? Natsumi is!?
Come over here and explain in detail!
What?
Your cramps are really bad so you're going to call out!?
Ah, hold up, Sayuri!
Kei, you...
Art Teacher Nao Yabe (Age 25)
How is it?
To be violated with the tools you use all the time?
l guess it feels really good.
There's juice dripping from the tips of the brushes...
Say something.
You fight against it but your body doesn't lie.
Look, your nipples are so hard!
So next, we can stick about eight paintbrushes into your butt hole?
Stop it!
Midou... Shin...
The rumors about you raping the female teachers in this school...
they were true...
Well, well, Ms. Hashimoto, it's during class time.
Answer my question. l'll call people here.
Ms. Hashimoto, this is consensual sexual intercourse.
Liar!
Ms. Yabe is scared!
Once she has sex with me, she'll feel satisfied right away...
Even if you think it's a lie, there is videotape for evidence.
So by doing that you have violated as many teachers as you have.
Violating?
l'm just training her to become a female slave.
By collaborating with your cousin Kei?
You've got to be freaking joking!
Who the hell would collaborate with that dick Kei!?
This works out because l don't have to waste time calling you out.
You are forcefully going to violate me?
Well, if you go against me, it's going to be forcefully.
Be obediently trained by me, Ms. Miho Hashimoto.
l'll make you come so many times...
We'll see how that goes...
This woman has fallen too...
Ah, that hurts!
Your nipples are so hard. You're totally turned on, aren't you?
Pinch it gently!
Man, l'm about to come...
What, you're already finished?
As l thought, you are still a child.
You came alone first...
lt didn't even feel good at all.
Don't make me laugh.
Your thing is so small. You need to acquire some techniques or caressing...
...or it's not going to be training at all.
There is no way you are done with just one shot, right?
What is with this woman?
But compared to the other women, she's really good...
Look, you're hard again.
This time l'm going to enjoy it. Shin, you lay on the floor.
l'm going to put it in...
How is it... ...inside me?
Doesn't it feel good?
What is this sensation...
lt feels too good!
lt's totally a different pussy that l was pounding before!
A woman's pussy is a living thing.
Depending on the other person, it becomes good or bad...
lt's still not enough!
l'll make it feel better!
What?
You came already?
And so much faster than before...
You're still young so you can stand up to more, can't you?
Pound me with all your might from the back and make me come.
Your thing isn't reaching all the way to the back of my pussy.
That's right. That's a little better.
Stronger and deeper!
Damn it!
l got caught up in that woman's pace...
What's up with that whore?
Looking at it like that l can't tell who's training whom!
Damn it...
Pretending to be turned on burns you out.
Ms. Yabe, are you okay?
T-Thank you very much.
My gosh, putting scratches on a woman's face and down there...
Don't be scared, it's safe now...
No...Stop...
Ms...Hashimoto...
That part is...
Don't worry.
l'll comfort your body and soul...
Right there...
English Teacher lori Kikuna (Age 26)
No...
No, please stop...
l beg you...
No... No...
Right there...
No... Stop...
Ms. Kikuna, you are really a virgin huh, are you stupid?
You even have a fiance and you're still going through with being a virgin...
Whatever...
Let's go to the piercing show right away!
To have the virginity taken by a student...
No, stop it, not that, l beg you!
... before the man who will be your husband. Just not that!
Kei, no!
There's a lot in life. Eh, Ms. Kikuna?
No, it hurts!
No!
lt hurts! No!
No! lt hurts!
Stop being so tense!
Eventually it will feel good!
From now on, l'll take care of you everyday and teach you the pleasures of a woman!
No, it hurts...
Please stop now...
Board Chairman's Office
Ah! lt's so good!
Your penis is so good!
Kei, seems as Ms. Kikuna is turning out to be good, too...
No, there are still a lot of things to teach through training...
Yes, seems as it's going smoothly.
The Machida Sisters, too...
Mr. Chairman, l really want your penis soon...
Penis...
Going to have it pierce through my pussy...
l'm all set and ready.
No Haruka!
Master...
l would be happy if you can pound my pussy next...
l can't wait anymore...
There's an order, you should get yourself ready on your own.
Yes.
You took one of my women...
You did one of them on my side, too, right?
Now we are even.
The situation is different from that time.
Who cares about such a thing.
Plus, if her first time is with a plain penis like Shin's, isn't it not fair for her?
You have to teach them the man's taste thoroughly.
What was that?
Say it one more time!
Well, don't get too riled up.
lf you are not calm about the competition, you won't win against me.
Plus one of your trainees is not even at school l hear.
With it looking like that, it isn't going to be a competition.
Damn it!
Kei, you started to push it once you found out about women...
Bastard...
Chemistry Teacher Miyuki Kamoi (Age 28)
Faculty Ladies Room Stop it!
Stop it!
No... l can't, l can't Kei...
Master...
My stomach...
Can't take it anymore...
lt's going to come out... Can't hold it anymore...
lf you want it out, let it out and let me see your feces.
No!
Why do you do such a thing...
From today l'm going to train your butt hole so...
first we need to get rid of all the feces.
More will still go in right?
Seems like more will go in.
No! Not anymore...
Okay, one more!
No... not anymore...My stomach...
No...
My poop is going to come out...
Man, how disgusting!
Don't let it go outside of the toilet!
Master, l'm coming in...
Feels so good!
Shin's penis is perfect for me...
R-Ryoko...?
Math Teacher Ryoko Katakura (Age 27)
Penis feels so good!
Classic Literature Teacher Sayuri Kobuchi (Age 27)
You were late...
Sayuri!?
Why!? Why are you here!?
Ms. Katakura, it's fine.
Sayuri is also one of my female slaves.
She's the same as you.
l'm glad.
Sayuri, you're also having sex with Shin?
Master...
Why did you lay your hands on Ryoko...
you promised!
You took off for a week so it's your own fault.
Plus, because you were being slow...
That dick Kei took Natsumi...
But that doesn't mean...
Ryoko...
l really did...
love you...
Who cares, Sayuri...
Thanks to Master, my male phobia went away...
so let's be trained by Master together.
By a guy like him?
No, from the real master...
What?
When l think about that person, l become soaking wet...
Sayuri, you'll know the enjoyment of sex...
the happiness of servicing.
That's wrong!
l don't need the happiness of sex or the pleasure!
l just want you to stay by me...
Ryoko, assault her like you used to when you guys were making love!
Yes!
H-Hold on Ryoko!
S-Stop...
Sayuri, l will introduce you soon.
You body and soul will become Master's victim of love...
Stop...
Ryoko, that part is...
No!
Look Shin, here...
Sayuri is weak here...
Look! Look! Her clitoris gets big and herjuice is overflowing.
No, it feels so good.
lt's been a while since Ryoko has...
Ryoko...
Assault me more!
lt's been three weeks, right Sayuri?
l'll take you to heaven forthe first time in a while.
Let's not worry about this guy and let's make love.
Ryoko...
l love you...
Epilogue
Nurse Mari Nakayama (Age 31)
lt hurts!
Nurse's Office
Stop, stop pulling there...
Ms. Yokohama, don't lick...
A person in the teaching profession with nipples rings, huh?
What a bitch teacher!
This is because of my master and...
Master?
Oh, l get it, meaning your lover is training you in different ways!
You're wrong...
Ms. Yokohama... Not... there...
l'm sorry...
lf l go against him, he'll hit me...
You are the lowest for tying down and abusing a woman!
Shut up...
From today, l'm going to train you, so break up with that lover!
l can't do such a thing...
What!?
Yes...
l'm going to go pee.
Lick all my semen from this woman's pussy and make it clean!
Ms. Nakayama...
l'm sorry...
l don't really want to do that but...
l know, Ms. Yokohama...
More than that, are you going to stay that guy's slave forever?
That is...
Don't cry...
Everything's going to be all right. l'll introduce you to my master...
Okay?
Student Kei Midou and Shin Midou
Sayuri, hold on!
No! Don't do it!
l'm sorry Ryoko...
Thank you for everything...
No! Wait!
Sayuri!
Board Chairman's Office
You idiot!
You drove our important sale item to commit suicide!
lt's no use to say anything to an idiot uncle...
He doesn't understand anything about society at all!
What did you say...
Scary!
The one that screwed up is flipping out?
Kei, you too!
You gave the Machida Sisters drugs!
This abusive gorilla is only able to do such a thing.
How dare you judge other people when you put your girl on a pedestal?
What the hell!
You're flipping out on me when you stole one of my women and ruined her on top of that!?
Stop it, both of you!
l don't care if you guys hate each other or kill each other but...
remember that you aren't even doing your job properly...
Reference Room
What happened? Move your hips more.
Seriously, Kei is a lot bigger.
What!?
The other day, Kei violated me.
''Mine is a lot bigger than Shin's...
...and my techniques are better'' is what he was saying and...
he was definitely making fun of you a lot...
Hey, why are you looking like that, what happened!?
Master...
l...
l was...
l was violated by Shin...
What did you say...
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
That bastard...!
You bastard!
lt's so good, Mr. Chairman!
lt's really good, Ms. Hashimoto...
lt's my first time with a pussy like this...
Right?
By the way, what happened with those two?
The two of them stabbed each other and died...
l have an acquaintance that's...
a back alley ''cleaner'' so l took care of it...
so!
l know.
From now on, l am putting you in charge of training...
The women that you trained are selling at a very high price.
You are totally different from those two...
l have high expectations for you!
Of course!
Don't put me together with those ignorant, crude guys!
Human World Teacher Miho Hashimoto