U-Upstairs...
...Arisa's having a lesson, but l'm doing something like this.
lf Atsushi finds out about this...
Arisa
Come on, Arisa, you have to solve the problem.
J-Jeez, big brother, you're so mean...
l can't like this...
l-l can't...
lf l scream too loud and Atsushi hears me upstairs...
Arisa, you're not allowed to scream so loud.
Aki will hear you.
But...
Atsushi... l-l'm about to come...
B-Big brother!
l'm about to come...
Kumagai
Atsushi, we'll be counting on you again.
Sure, thank you.
Oh, Atsushi.
Hi, Nami.
A lesson for Arisa?
Yes, l'm about to go home.
l see. lt's our place in two days.
Maya and l are looking forward to it, Atsushi.
Um, Nami...
l'm not sure if l should keep on tutoring like this...
Atsushi...
l just thought l should rethink things.
Oh, Atsushi.
l made it in time. Huh?
N-Nami...
Good evening, Aki.
l bumped into him on the way back from shopping...
...and we were discussing Maya's lessons a little bit.
Oh, l see.
ls something up, Aki?
Um...
This is for you if you'd like it.
O-Oh.
l made too much for dinner.
Really? l can have this?
Please eat it at home. l'm not sure if you'll like it, but...
Thank you so much.
l'm sure l'll like it.
Oh, Atsushi.
Mom...
Maya.
Hello, Maya.
Hello, Atsushi.
Heading back from classes?
Yes, kind of...
Atsushi...
Are you going somewhere right now?
Well, nowhere specific...
Then...
...may l come to your room?
Yeah, you can.
Let's see...
juice or...
...but would coffee or tea be better?
Atsushi...
Maya?
Does it have to be with my mother?
lf it's just me...
Don't l have any appeal?
lt's not like that. You are cute and do have appeal.
Atsushi...
l want you to do me alone.
Maya...
Maya, you're so beautiful...
Atsushi...
Big brother!
l'm here!
What is this?
Big brother, what are you doing with Maya?
No, um, this is...
You weren't only mine?
That means Atsushi...
Well, uh...
What?
You're supposed to be mine alone...
A-Atsushi isn't just yours, Arisa!
l really am in love with him!
l-l like him too!
l like him a lot more!
My feelings for Atsushi will never be less than yours!
Hold on, you two.
Your feelings aren't a competition.
The feelings you both have for me are real.
And l also like both of you too.
Atsushi...
Big brother...
So let's all just feel good together and not fight, okay?
All right.
But...
Maya understands.
l guess Arisa's not going to understand?
B-Big brother...
A-All right...
Look, big brother.
You like this, right?
Arisa...
Come here.
Big brother...
lt's amazing...
l can do that too.
Sato
Atsushi...
Please look at me too.
You went that far, Maya?
Arisa, Maya was here earlier than you today, so Maya's first, okay?
A-Atsushi's hard thing is going in me from down there...
Maya, you look great in the bathing suit...
...but let me see your breasts.
A-Atsushi, i-it's amazing!
Amazing, your dick is going wild inside my stomach!
Maya's enjoying it so much...
l can't hold on anymore.
B-Big brother, hurry. l want it too...
My gosh, Arisa... You're so perverted...
l-lt's because...
Atsushi!
l-l-l'm going to come a-already!
Me too...
l-l'm coming!
Atsushi...
Maya...
This time it's my turn...
...big brother.
lt's hitting...
Your dick is hitting the back!
Big brother, stir me up inside like crazy!
lt's amazing!
Big brother!
Arisa, may l borrow this?
Maya...
Yeah, you can.
Thank you.
Maya's really a pervert too.
Arisa, if you move it that much...
lt's because big brother's so amazing!
Let's all come together...
Big brother, l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
Atsushi! Arisa! l can't hold on anymore!
lt's really gotten crazy.
Well, it's my own fault...
Hold on a second!
N-Nami?
Atsushi!
What's with you three being together?
W-We met by chance in front of the station.
l was just walking them back home.
Oh, really?
Then we'll part ways here.
Goodbye. l'll see you at the lessons.
See you, big brother.
Goodbye, Atsushi.
We should head home too.
Okay.
Say, Arisa, why don't you stop by our house now?
We have a delicious cake. What do you say?
A cake? l'll definitely go!
And l want to tell you something interesting too.
What is it?
Mom is plotting something again.
Sato
Hello!
Atsushi, welcome. We've been waiting.
Come on in.
Sure, thanks.
A-Atsushi...
Hello.
Um, what's all this about?
l don't know either...
l think she's here.
Come on, please come in.
Sure...
Excuse me.
Chidori!
Atsushi... What's going on?
l came because Nami asked me to...
Now we have everyone here.
Nami, what's the meaning of all this?
Chidori, Aki...
...how do you feel about Atsushi?
What?
Nami, what do you mean by that?
Meaning do you like him or not?
Nami, what's this out of the blue?
l like Atsushi.
W-What are you saying, Nami?
And right in front of Maya...
Oh, don't worry about her.
She already knows.
Arisa too.
Right, Atsushi?
You couldn't have...
Sorry, big brother.
T-Then...
Arisa was bribed with cake...
l heard everything from the both of them.
The cake worked especially well on Arisa.
Y-You spilled the beans?
You kept the stuff about Aunt Nami a secret too!
What are you talking about?
lt's like this.
Atsushi ate the three of us up.
What?
lt's not just you three.
l also did it with Atsushi...
C-Chidori!
Oh, it's like Arisa suspected.
What a player you are.
So let's go as planned.
Oh, Aki's the only one left now.
Mom.
M-Maya?
W-What are you doing?
Mom, hold still.
Arisa, stop it!
M-Maya, you too...
Jeez.
Aki, just give in and be honest.
l'm not... This shouldn't be happening.
Really... You're not honest with yourself.
The truth is you want him to look at you, right?
T-That's not true...
Maya, give back my panties! Arisa, give back my bra!
But we just took them off.
And what are you going to do, Chidori?
l-l'll do it too.
Me too.
l'm not going to lose!
Maya! Arisa!
A-Atsushi...
Big brother...
Don't rush, you two.
This is a first for someone here. Maybe she should be first?
Right?
N-Nami, you can't! We can't do such things...
Aki, just get honest.
Atsushi, please.
R-Right...
My, Aki, are you that wet already?
N-Nami...
lt's okay. Let him put it in.
l can't do this.
l... l feel bad for my husband.
Forget about that for now.
lt feels good, right?
lt doesn't feel good...
Aki, should l stop?
N-No...
P-Please don't stop...
Then here l go.
lt's... lt's amazing!
lt's hot, Atsushi!
lt seems she's fine now.
Maya.
Okay, come here.
Come on, Maya.
No!
Mom, l-l don't want to do this...
What are you saying, Maya?
Show Atsushi everything and turn him on.
A-Atsushi...
Please look at mine...
l'm watching closely, Maya.
A-Atsushi, i-it's my first time going this fast!
M-Mom!
Atsushi is moving that much...
Big sister...
Let's do it with this...
Okay, Arisa...
Big brother...
Look at me...
Arisa...
Atsushi, are you watching me?
Atsushi, your dick is going crazy inside me...
Hey, Atsushi...
This way, you'll continue tutoring, right?
Don't you think about quitting!
That's right, Atsushi!
l'll help too!
We should just study together!
From now on too, as a family...
lt's a perverted lesson... A family lesson.
That's right!
lt's fine this way!
l-l'm going to come!
Come on, Atsushi.
lt's my turn next.
No! Please do me first!
What? l'm first!
Atsushi, please give it to me too.
l want more.
Atsushi, teach us more!
After that, the perverted tutoring still went on.
The only thing that changed is that Aki and Nami became pregnant.
lt's said to be their husband's kids, but they're both mine of course.
When these kids get older...
Right, Aki?
Yes, Nami.
Atsushi, please give us all some perverted lessons.
Siblings can study together too.
Atsushi, please stay my tutor forever!
l'll help too...
Okay!
We'll have a lesson with the eight of us!
Okay, Atsushi!
The perverted family lesson seems like it'll go on for a while.