l am probably lying about this.
To Yosuke-san, to Kazuhiko-san.
And, to myself...
l'm back, Kazuhiko-san.
Emiko?
Why?
She no longer has a reason to come here.
E, Emiko...
That's when l realized something...
Emiko is much stronger than l am.
l am hiding underneath the darkness and am lost in my own thoughts.
But Emiko, unlike me, is straight forward.
l...can't....
l can't betray Yosuke-san...
l can't...
Mother, Mother, Mother.
Yes!?
Don't think wrong of this, Mother.
Aunt Emiko came here on her own will.
l didn't order her or force her to.
Right Auntie?
Kazuhiko-kun, great!
More, more please!
Sis, l'm sorry.
But l realized something.
My body...it constantly needs Kazuhiko-san.
What l'm saying is that l didn't come here for you.
l came here to take him away from you.
What are you saying, Emiko!?
lf you don't like it, try stealing him back from me!
But before that, you'll have to sort it out with Yosuke-san.
With Yosuke-san!?
Tell Yosuke-san about Kazuhiko-san?
l can't...
l can't do that.
You're so good, you're going to make me cum!
My butt, it's so warm!
You two are definitely sisters, Mother likes this too...
No, forget about my Sister!
She's going to Yosuke-san!
lt feels good, deep, in my butt!
You two like the same thing, act the same way.
Not fair, giving me all the pleasure...
Mother?
Yes!
Hurry.
l'm going to take Auntie back home.
When will you be back?
Sorry Mother, but l won't be back today.
Huh, what!?
Please Kazuhiko-san, don't go.
Come back!
Come on, lets go.
Alright.
lt's Monday.
Yosuke-san is headed for Sapporo to look for an apartment near his new job location.
He'll be back Friday.
And Sunday, l'll fly to Sapporo with him.
After that, we'll be far away from each other and l won't be able to see Kazuhiko-san.
But...
Tuesday...
and Wednesday...
Kazuhiko-san is still not back home.
Tomorrow, Yosuke-san will be back.
lf Only today...
Kazuhiko-san!?
Hey Sis, it's me.
Where's Kazuhiko-san?
Kazuhiko-kun is taking a shower right now.
Emiko has a charm that Mother doesn't have.
My, Kazuhiko-kun is wild!
He won't let me get out of bed.
We were at it all last night.
He came in me so many times.
A cream-pie.
lt doesn't get any better than being with the one you love.
l hope you have a splendid time in Sapporo.
Oh, by the way, you don't need to worry about Kazuhiko-kun.
l will take care of him.
Of course, his ''needs'' too.
Give him back!
That...Kazuhiko-san is mine.
Hurry, give him back!
Emiko, you listening?
Emiko!
Oh Kazuhiko-kun, are you done with the shower?
Yeah, l feel refreshed.
Alright, your aunt's going to take one then.
Auntie, don't worry about that.
Look, l'm hard again.
My Kazuhiko-kun, you're amazing.
After all that...
And you still want more...
You are very naughty.
Auntie, that's because your smell down there excites me.
You sure know how to push your aunt's buttons.
Naughty boy.
l'll suck it out for you.
Seeing you sucking me is very arousing.
Looking very kinky...deliciously having my cock in your mouth...
ls this really that delicious?
Kazuhiko-san, l want it...
Your Mother wants your big thing too!
Alright, l'll lick your sensitive spot.
No, l didn't wash it yet.
You're such a bad boy for making your aunt do this.
Want me to stop then?
Shesh, now you're just being mean.
l want to be held by Kazuhiko-san, l want to feel him.
This smells nice, Mother...
Kazuhiko-san's smell...
This smell...you said you loved me.
Kazuhiko-san, please come back.
Choose me instead of Emiko...
l start remembering about the wonderful days l've had with Kazuhiko-san.
Everyday from now on, once dad leaves for work in the morning...
Promise?
Yes...
Kazuhiko-san...
So cute...
Don't say something weird.
What's weird?
Our age gap is big.
Besides, it's not a thing to say to your mother.
That's not true.
You're so cute that l just want to give you attention.
But...
Don't you want the attention, Mother?
Right here...
l want it...
l want Kazuhiko-san's hot, hard thing...
K, Kazuhiko-san!
P, please give me attention with your big, hard thing!
Use your mouth.
Your cute face...
l want to violate it with my sticky cum.
You made me this hard...
Please, spray...spray it all over my face.
Huh, you're sure?
We're mother and son.
lt's fine.
l am a perverted mother.
Please dirty your mother with this.
Then, lick it.
l am not a good mother.
Doing this to my son...
Give me your cum, Kazuhiko-san.
You're so cute when you keep your mouth opened.
Back then, this is what l was thinking...
lf l keep this up, he'll be mine forever.
l want your cum, Kazuhiko-san
You're so cute when you keep your mouth opened.
That's when l realized something.
Emiko is experiencing exactly the same thing l have and...she just took it away from me.
Oh Kazuhiko-kun, your big thing...it's inside me!
You're...so tight, Auntie!
No, l can't take this much longer!
Deep.
lt's so deep.
Move your hips at your own pace, Auntie.
Deep.
lt's so deep.
Move your hips at your own pace, Mother.
Good, do it stronger!
Kazuhiko-san is no longer mine...
The very thought of it is making me feel lost and driving me crazy.
Mother, how do you like being fucked on the balcony?
Kazuhiko-san, your big thing...feels so good.
My son has opened up the door of pleasures and my feminine lust won't allow me to deny it.
Mother, don't take out the vibrator
A mother enjoying a taboo.
Come Kazuhiko-san, come.
Cum, coat me with your sticky cum!
Give it to me!!
Kazuhiko-san!
Enjoying being covered with a man's sperm, a natural and lustful female instinct.
More, give me more.
l can't forget the time l was under Kazuhiko-san's control.
Kazuhiko-san, hold me tightly.
Don't let go of me!
No, Kazuhiko-kun!
You're going to make your aunt cum again!
No, l can't cum without...Kazuhiko-san.
Kazuhiko-san...
Mother, the phone.
lt got cut off...
Mother, are you not home?
Man, where could she have went too?
Mothe...!?
You're finally back...Kazuhiko-san.
W, what happened, Mother?
You're finally back...
Without you...
Just being in his arms is making me...making me so...
Mother...
l can...only be satisfied by...you now.
But l'm your mother, you're my son, so l can't be your wife...
So l'm moving in with Yosuke-san.
l promised myself to be a normal mother.
l don't want to be apart.
No Mother, l won't let you do that.
Kazuhiko-san...
Mother, you are mine.
Your hair.
Your fingers.
Your chest.
Your butt.
lt's all mine.
Mother.
Mother, who's do you like better?
Mine or my father's?
l, l can't...
l like yours better than Aunt Emiko's.
Yes, you're definitely mine.
Now l realize that l can't continue lying to myself.
Good bye.
Yosuke-san...
So, Father is back tomorrow, right?
Yes.
Lets go to your room then.
You and Father, always in this room, doing...
No, don't say it.
Even your armpit smells good.
Don't.
lt smells good down here too.
Stop, l haven't washed in three days.
Don't worry, l'm not like Father.
No, don't sniff it Kazuhiko-san!
But truthfully you like it right, Mother?
l am a bad mother who likes being sniffed by her own son!
Your smell made me so hard.
What should we do about this, Mother?
Put it in my butt.
Ever since you neglected me, it's been craving some attention.
This hole isn't really meant to be plugged by this.
But since you want it, l won't deny you.
Kazuhiko-san is inside...inside my butt!
Does Father know how dirty you really are?
Yosuke-san will never...do this.
Going in, coming out, going in, coming out.
Mother, don't you love this?
Kazuhiko-san, l can feel you inside my butt!
The feeling of it when it's pulling out, feels so dirty.
lt feels good!
Mother, your ass is so warm as it greases me.
l..l'm going to cum!
l want it, your sticky cum...
Please cum inside my butt!
Mother, c, cumming!
l can feel it, feel it inside my butt!!
l can't waste this valuable sperm.
Don't worry, l can give you more.
lt smells so kinky.
The combination of my butt and your sperm...
lt's your fault, Mother.
Can you clean it?
So big, so hard, so energetic...l want it.
Please, give me.
Please Kazuhiko-san.
So impatient.
Don't keep me waiting, hurry!
Here l...go!
Kazuhiko-san, your thick thing is inside me!
More, give me more!
l can feel your hot thing, l'm, l'm...
Mother,l'll do something that you really enjoy.
W, what?
l'll help you cum with both holes.
This is driving me nuts!
You like it in both holes right, Mother?
lt's so amazing, you're so deep inside me.
l need...l need...you.
Yours is the best, Mother.
l'm so happy, l want to be by your side.
Not Yosuke-san...
Two years is quick, so lets stay as mother and son.
As long as we're mother and son...we can be together forever!
F, forever?
Yes, forever Mother!
K, Kazuhiko-san!
M, Mother!
Together...
Kazuhiko-san will always be mine.
Even if it's a taboo, l have no regrets.
As you have said, l'll go with Yosuke-san.
l'll call you everyday.
l'll come back during the weekends.
No matter what you're doing.
No, l'll go see you.
Yes, l'll be waiting.
Feeling the body of the one you love.
There's no happiness greater than this for a woman.
Did Kazuhiko-kun already go to sleep?
l have something important to tell him.
Right?
l wonder if your father would be happy.
And another woman becomes a mother
l was able to come home one day early.
No one is picking up the phone and the lights are off.
Are they already sleeping?
Hey Misako, l'm home.
Nothing quite beats being home.
But soon, l have to be in Sapporo for two years.
This is Misako's wedding ring.
Strange, she never took it off before.
Mother, it feels great!
Kazuhiko-san!
Hey, lt looks like Misako is awake.
THE END