See you, Yoichi.
Thanks.
Good luck at work.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Will you get to work on time when you're leaving this late?
l-lt's fine.
You're such a rebel employee.
That's not true.
Really? So you're working really hard, huh?
Of course.
Of course he is.
Oh.
You're getting along well.
l-l'm in a hurry, so...
See you.
Okay, the documents for today's meeting are... Huh?
Good morning, Chief.
Morning.
Today's meeting starts at two in the afternoon.
Okay.
Celebrity Cantaloupes
Kairi Tsubaki
Hey, Kanami!
Kanami!
Huh?
Oh, yeah... She said she was going to her sister's place this afternoon...
Um, the security code is...
Miss Tsubaki?
You still had boxes to move?
Yes, my husband's busy with work, so he won't help me that much.
lf you'd like, l could help you.
This really is a big help. You're a man, all right.
Not at all.
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yes...
l-l'm sorry!
No worries.
T-This is...
No!
T-That's, um, well...
lt was a prize my husband won at a party, and...
Wow!
l'm so embarrassed!
Don't be.
lt looks really good on you! lt's very sexy.
To prove that...
What a fine, big carrot...
Please, don't hold back.
What a delicious carrot it is...
lt's amazing...
Miss Tsubaki, l'm...
Give it all to me!
Fresh white sauce on a red and black, delicious carrot...
lt looks a lot more delicious.
l'm going to enjoy it this way now.
What is this? l sucked on it with my mouth, but it's still really hard...
This time, l'm going to cook you really well with my meat juice...
Miss Tsubaki...
l haven't had something like this in so long...
These are the best breasts to massage...
Going in this deep...
l'm already...
Already...
l'm going to come! l-l'm going to come!
Me too...
Pampering Cantaloupes
Kisae Yotsuba
Really. Kanami isn't home...
And l came all this way. lt's a shame that she isn't home.
But seeing as you came all this way alone, is my brother that busy?
lt's business trip after business trip. He's never home.
We don't even have time to make kids.
Oh no, l'm soaked!
Oh, whatever. Yoichi, where's the bathroom?
P-Please...
Yoichi, please come with me.
K-Kisae, why are you making me do something like this?
Yoichi, don't you know?
A woman's aspiration is to get a guy to help them urinate.
ls it?
l'm serious.
Do it with Kanami next time. l'm sure she'll be really happy.
R-Really?
Come on, Yoichi, hurry and make me urinate.
R-Right.
Piss, piss, piss...
To return the favor, Yoichi, l'll help you urinate too.
Come on... Piss, piss, piss...
My gosh, you want to let something other than urine out?
l never thought l'd be in a relationship like this with my brother's wife...
Yoichi, yours is seriously huge.
Sis, your breasts...
They feel good...
lf you want to let it out, don't hold back and just let it out.
Come on, Yoichi, spew out your semen.
Spew out your semen!
Really thick stuff came out so quickly!
Yoichi, your ejaculation is amazing...
Timid Cantaloupes
Mei Hanamizuki
Wow, it's my first time doing this...
...but they really do a thorough community clean up.
Mei?
Sorry, i-it's nothing...
You say it's nothing, but it doesn't look true.
Really, l'm okay...
Let's just rest a little.
Here, this should be good...
l can't hold on anymore!
This is...
No!
l can't...
l can't hold it in anymore!
Please don't look!
Someone will see us here...
P-Please put it in my pussy...
l didn't know you were into this, Mei...
There are a few guys at the apartment complex who lust after you.
l'm sorry!
l'm a major masochist. l don't really want to do this!
But l have to because it's my husband's orders...
ls that true?
Your lower mouth is drooling so much and asking for it.
N-No!
lt's because my body throbs...
...when l'm told to do dirty and embarrassing things in front of people!
My pussy heats up and throbs, and l can't hold it in anymore so l have to!
That's because you're a pervert who feels happiness when playing like that.
Please don't say that!
No... No, l'm not!
Mei, you're a wild and perverted wife.
Look.
You have a dildo pushed up your butt, and it feels good, right?
Admit that a dick other than your husband's feels good, wild Miss Mei.
l'm...
Don't dig into my butt with the dildo!
Anal... Anal is my weakness!
ls your butt your only weakness?
But it feel good!
My breasts, my butt, and my pussy... They all feel good!
They all turned into erogenous zones!
lf you pound me that hard, l'm... l'm...
lf you want to come, go ahead anytime.
You're going to come here, where you never know who might pass by, huh?
No! Not outside...
But...
B-But...
Flattering-in-black Cantaloupes
Suzuka Fuyou
Mom is available, so why do l have to...
Please bring this to the flower-arrangement teacher.
Why do l have to do this on my day off?
But it hasn't changed around here at all.
lt's exactly the same as when l went to the flower class with her.
l wonder if Miss Suzuka is still well.
Excuse me!
ls no one home?
No!
What?
Please stop it!
Father...
Miss Suzuka is a widow, isn't she?
Her husband died, and the son is from his previous marriage.
That means...
Father... And Tomonori...
Please stop!
T-There's company...
No one's going to come. l'm sure they left.
Please...
Not during midday...
Mother, you taste so good.
The juice pouring from your ripe pomegranate is the best.
l'm comforting your inflamed body in place of my dead son.
You should be thanking us.
Oh, gosh...
lt's time for you to suck on it.
As usual, the head you're giving is superb!
l'm gonna...
l'm sure Tomonori's young semen is delicious to you.
Here.
No...
N-No more...
Your butt is like a base for flower arrangement.
Suzuka, do you want flowers arranged in the front or the back hole?
T-The front please...
l see. l see.
The back, huh?
T-That's...
You got it wrong! l said the front!
Oh, really? Sorry, l'm becoming deaf these days.
Not that side...
T-The front...
You want it in the front too? Suzuka, you're so greedy.
l was right, Suzuka. You look good speared by two.
lf we continue this, l think l'm going to go crazy...
That's not good.
So she doesn't go crazy, we have to do it...
...with so much love that it makes up for my son's share, right, Tomonori?
l'm going to go crazy!
l'm so sorry, honey!
l... l...
Please forgive me! Forgive me!
Lonesome Cantaloupes
Chizuru Yotsuba
Yotsuba
l'm home.
Mom, Miss Suzuka wasn't home.
No...
No, stop it!
No!
Stop it...
Oh no...
Yoichi?
Y-You're back early.
W-Was Miss Suzuka doing well?
T-The other day, when l told her that you got married...
...she wanted to see you since it had been a while...
Mom!
Y-Yoichi?
l'm sorry l wasn't able to realize.
You've been lonely, right, Mom?
Ever since Dad died, you've always comforted yourself alone...
Hold on, Yoichi. What are you saying...
Mom, l've always wanted to suck on your breasts.
You can, Yoichi...
Even if we aren't related by blood, you're my beloved son.
Yoichi...
Mom...
Y-Yoichi? What are you...
Mom, you were in the middle of it before, right?
So l'm going to satisfy you.
Yoichi, that's...
lt's in, Mom.
My son's dick is inside me...
Even though l'm your mother... Even so...
Mom, it's so tight inside you.
Maybe it's because no one's been inside you for a while...
No!
Don't say such things...
From now on, l won't let you feel lonely, Mom...
No, you can't...
Yoichi, you have Kanami...
Yoichi...
Y-You've became this impressive...
Your thickness and hardness is better than his...
l'm happy that you're happy, Mom!
But l feel guilty about Kanami.
What are you saying, Mom?
You and Kanami are both precious family members to me...
...so l'm going to make you and Kanami both happy!
Yoichi!
l'm really happy.
l'm so happy that my breasts...
Milk is going to come out of my breasts for the first time in a while!
lt's coming out... The symbol of motherhood is coming out so fast...
That's amazing, Mom!
Yoichi! Yoichi!
Mom, l'm...
Come, Yoichi...
Come inside me!
Mom!
Good morning, Yoichi. Breakfast is already made.
Get up soon, okay?
Yoichi, just because it's your day off doesn't mean you can stay asleep!
Yes, ma'am.
They're all wives so getting pregnant isn't weird, but...
Wait, one's a widow...
lt's so strange that everyone became pregnant at the same time.
l know, right?
Why don't we raise all of them together like siblings?
Yeah.
They might be real siblings.
What do you mean...
Does it matter? Everyone's happy.
Mother, you too?
lt's a secret.