She's late. Probably had all sorts of stuff to do for admission.
Now then, Midori Yano...
I'd like to present a new transfer student to you today.
Um, Miss Yano?
So, what about that desk?
I said be quiet!
It's just...
I wonder what your voice sounds like when you cry out.
Oh, Murakoshi! So this is where... you went.
I was kind of looking for you.
D-Did you want me for something?
No, not exactly....
I still don't know my way around, so I got lost.
I heard you were looking for me, but...
M-Murakoshi, would you like to walk me home?
Huh?!
What's with that girl? I've never heard of a girl like that.
My house is this way, so...
R-Right. Mine's this way, so...
Oh, Murakoshi!
No, never mind.
If you want to say something, you should say it.
Well, you see... Could we walk home like this tomorrow, too?
Wha-?!
Er, just kidding!
S-See you!
See what I mean? He's gross!
So gross! See what I mean? He's gross!
Go to sleep.
Woof! Woof! Woof! Woof!
Murakoshi!
Say ''ah''!
You did it!
Here, have some tea.
Murakoshi, what's wrong?
Yano, why...? I mean, this thing, with you and me...
Maybe I've fallen in love with you.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
I kissed you! That was basically my first kiss!
Oh! I was supposed to try out for the track team today!
Okay... Then I'll wait for you.
''Panty-wetting phone call.''
That's right, I wouldn't be me if I didn't do this.
It feels so good! It feels so good!
Make my pussy feel it more! I want your dick grinding inside me!
In and out...
Your dick feels so good! You make my girl parts feel so good!
I'm squeezing my pussy around your dick! It's so numb, the juices won't stop!
The pulsation of your dick... I can feel it all the way to my nipples!
More! More!
More!
I... I'm ready to cum! Ram me harder!
No way... It's still coming.
Is anyone as good as you? It's still coming out.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
M-Midori!
If we don't hurry, we'll be late for afternoon classes, won't we?
Do you...
Do you have track again today?
Yeah. Sorry.
I-I see. Yeah. You're popular, aren't you?
Shinta, is it possible you're lonely without me?
D-Don't be ridiculous! That's not it at all!
Yano?
Shinta, if you could...
What?
If you could, don't call me Yano.
Use my first name...
I want you to call me Midori.
ACTING PRINCIPAL
You look busy with your work.
But then, you've finally become the principal just like you always wanted, so it must be fun.
I have a feeling it won't be long till they take the ''acting'' off that sign.
So, what do you want? Did you come to use me as a toy again?
Please. ''Toy'' sounds so respectable.
Yeah, you're right. You don't have time to waste with me, do you?
What's that supposed to mean, Mayumi?
There's no hidden meaning. I meant exactly what I said.
You're having fun, aren't you? Playing house with Midori Yano.
I don't know if you hypnotized her or not, but I'm amazed that you want to play such a childish game.
''Brazen little me.''
No, no, no, no, no!
I hate having your dick up my ass!
Then why didn't you raise your hips higher?
But having it in my ass feels so good... so I'm willing to put up with this gross shit!
Then I'll help you, too.
No! I hate it! But... No! This anal sex is weakening me.
If you don't make me feel good, having your dick in me will make me wither and die!
No! No! Don't stop!
I'll die! I'll die!
Ream me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming in my ass!
The principal was thrown out for lascivious acts, so you got the school back... thanks to me.
Why are you still so dissatisfied?
I'm not dissatisfied at all! I just wish you weren't here!
But this is all because of me.
All that aside, aren't you nervous every day?
Dirty little me might say something to drive Midori Yano away from you.
Am I right? Then did you come here because you wanted to distract yourself?
Or perhaps to be comforted?
You make me sick!
I know. I'll tell you a good way to settle this.
Use it on her. Use your little flashy thing on Midori Yano, too! Then it'll all be fine!
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Um, listen...
M-My mom and dad aren't home today.
Huh?!
Y-Yano... Sorry, I mean Midori.
You want to do it with me?
Yes. With you, Shinta.
Should I turn off the lights?
Y-Yeah. Should I turn off the lights?
Y-Yeah.
I feel so shy.
It's okay. You're beautiful, Midori.
Right. If you say it, I believe you, Shinta.
No...!
May l?
Yeah.
You okay?
I'm okay. So, please...
M-Midori! I love you. So...
And I love you, Shinta.
I'll take care of you. I will! So please, please never leave me!
I... I'm glad I met you, Shinta.
No way! Midori? Midori!
Huh? Shinta, what's wrong?
Huh? What's the matter? Why are you crying?
Breakfast will be ready in a little while. Get dressed and come downstairs, okay?
Ah, right.
Maybe I don't need this anymore.
''Before I sent you The Inducer, you couldn't handle your problems.''
''That's why I chose you to test it out.''
''Since that ray gun brought out such strength in you, I figured I'd send you a little gift.''
''So, how do you like Midori Yano?''
"I'm sending you the password to undo her hypnosis.''
"I figured you'd like to see what it looks like when the hypnosis is undone,''
''and a girl sinks into the depths of despair.''
PASSWORD: SKIPPING BRAIN
''Skipping brain...''
No! Stop it! Someone, help me!
Shinta! Somebody, help!
No! No!
Don't!
No! No! No!
It feels so good! The vibrator slipping in and out makes my heart skip!
Anal! Anal makes me shiver!
I'm all right! I got my father's school back, even if it means having to do this!
No, I mustn't! I'm the principal now! I can't overdo this!
But maybe one more time...
Having the vibrator in me makes my heart skip! Oh, it's coming out! Sanae's tea is coming out!
Here it comes... here it comes!
I'm cumming! Mayumi the pervert principal is cumming!
No! No! No!
No, stop!
Help me! Shinta! Anybody!
No!
Shinta, help me...
No! No! Stop it!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
I've made a baby... A baby...
Sh-Shinta...
No...
No!!
As I expected, this is the result when you're thrust into a hellish situation.
Now, tell me what it was like pretending to love me!
Fine, I'll say it.
''Skipping brain!''
Go on, answer me!
It made me... incredibly sick.
You see? Just as I expected!
But, along the way... I started thinking it was sort of nice.
Huh?
Because there was something... Yeah... I thought there was something between us.
Walk in silence, see the danger.
Endless talking, don't walk away.
Don't turn away in silence, my illusion.
Confronts and then dies...
People like you find it easy walking on air.
Teacher?
What is it, Miss Yano?
I was just wondering. Why is the desk next to me empty?
Hm... Yeah, I wonder why? I'll have to ask the principal later-
Oh, wait. I'm the principal now. I'm still not used to that.
Geez, Teacher!