All women are sex objects that satisfy themselves with a man's penis.
Stop it...
lf you do such a thing...
Do you know...
...what you are doing?
l know Ms. Kobuchi.
l'm sticking my penis into your drooling pussy and having sex with you.
Classic Literature Teacher Sayuri Kobuchi (Age 27)
You're wrong, this isn't sex.
You threatened and forcefully screwed...
That's right, this is rape...
lt's rape!
That hurts!
Stop it...
Such an insult calling it rape...
Please stop...
l'm just punishing a person who does things she shouldn't even though...
...she has a position in an educational career.
Please understand your position, teacher.
l'll put these up on the academy's web site.
Or maybe a major web forum to start the commotion even sooner!
Two teachers at a certain famous academy turn out to be lesbian lovers...
...engaging in lewd acts in the classrooms after school.
Magazines will jump on that...
Come on, stop sitting there.
Put it in yourself and move your hip.
lt's not in yet...
Please promise me...
l don't care what happens to me.
But Ryoko... Ms. Katakura, don't do anything to her...
lf l lay my hands on her or not is up to you, Ms. Kobuchi.
Come on, hurry and put it in. Move on your own...
As what l expected from a rank holder in Aikido.
For all the exercise you do, it's so tight.
lt's a shame you are a lesbian...
No!
You cant!
Don't pound me that hard...
lt's been a while since you've done it with a man right?
No!
Remember the happiness of being violated.
A man's thing is inside me...
lnside my vagina!
No, if you do it that much, l'm going to be turned on!
No, please stop, but it feels so good...
Ryoko, l'm sorry...
l'm being turned on by a man's penis!
She was a same-sex lover so there's no way she took pills...
lf l come inside her and make her pregnant, l will ruin an item for sale.
lt hurts!
No! Not there!
My butt hole is going to break!
Take it out, take it out Shin!
Who do you think you are talking to?
From today, our relationship is master and slave.
lf you are thinking about Ms. Katakura, then watch how you speak to me.
...Y-Yes, l'm sorry, Master...
Then l will pour all of my semen into you butt hole.
Be happy.
Thank you... very much...
lt hurts! No!
l can't anymore!
My butt...
...that there is a penis in my butt...
...it feels weird...
No, l'm going to come, l'm going to come!
Now two down...
From tomorrow on, l'll start your full-blown training. Okay, Ms. Kobuchi?
l'm sorry, l'm sorry.
l'll apologize so please don't hurt me.
Ouch! Stop it!
Come on hurry up and lick!
No Kei...
l came here because you said you want to consult me on something...
Ms. Yokohama, you like me right?
lsn't that why you came to the school so late at night?
World History Teacher Misako Yokohama (Age 28)
l-lt's not like that...
lt is the teacher's duty to address their student's problems...
l have something to discuss with you.
l want to have sex with you and l can't help it.
l-l can't do such a thing.
Let me do you Ms. Yokohama.
No.
First of all sex is something two people that love each other do to express...
...their love and...
l like you Ms. Yokohama.
No...
A relation like this... with a student isn't...
l... will wait till you graduate so...
...if you still like me then...
Okay?
ldiot!
Stop being conceited, fatty!
A man and a woman can't wait that long to have sex!
You really want to do it too, right?
l can tell that your pussy is soaked from the looks of your underwear!
You nympho female pig!
Why are you denying it?
lf you talk back, l will kill you.
Stop staying fallen over!
Hurry up and suck it!
Please forgive me...
That's right.
You should have listened to me from the beginning.
Hey, you are pretty good at this.
lt feels good...
From now on, our relationship is master and his female pig.
But...
Huh!?
Yes...Master...
That's good...
Man, l'm going to come!
Drink it all up.
lf you spit it out, l'll kill you!
Okay, we're going to do it.
Come here!
Yes...
Hey, hurry up, put it in and move your hips!
Well... l've never had to do it on my own so...
Who cares, hurry up and bring your hips down!
Y-Yes...
l'm sorry...
The penis... is inside of me...
Man, the inside of your pussy is warm and feels so good!
Hurry up and move your hips!
l'm sorry...
l somehow can't get enough energy to...
...so...
lt's hitting...
No...
The penis is... intensely...
Why are you the only one turned on even though you're the slave?
Y-Yes...
l'm sorry...
lt's good...
Master's penis is... in my pussy...
lt feels so good that l lose all my strength!
Okay, now turn the other way and move your hips.
Like this?
That's right.
Your butt hole is totally exposed.
No... don't look...
No!
You can't!
Not my butt hole!
Take it out...
Please take it out!
Don't put it in!
Shut up!
lt gets tighter!
Hit me...
Hit me more...
More...
More harder...
Hit me more and more!
l-l'm going to come...
Why are you coming alone?
Come on, move and make me come!
Board Chairman's Office
News lnformation Teacher Akira Naruse (Age 24)
This Ms. Naruse that you trained could be contracted for a high price.
l deposited your reward.
Make sure of it for me.
Yes, Uncle.
You...
...took one of the women from my side...
Took isn't the word.
This competition, if you are not in, it's my entire win without playing.
You are a loser.
What did you say!?
So good...
Mr. Chairman, yours is harder and fatter than Shin's...
...and it gets stuck in there and it feels so good...
Really, Shin, your penis is really plain?
So lame.
l don't want that said by a virgin that hasn't even violated one woman.
Who is a virgin?
l'll kill you.
Did l hit it on the dot?
Uncle, l will train them on my own.
lt's impossible for Mr. Virgin to.
Bad luck.
You are seeing real life sex and your moves have gotten slower.
You're my cousin so l'm going easy on you.
Why don't both of you stop!?
No, l'm going to come...
l'm going to come before Master does...
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
Cut down on the arguing!
l took you in because of our family connections...
...but you keep making deplorable events happen in the academy...
l'm sorry for only making myself come...
l will clean up right a way...
But after all, you're using us to gather women, Uncle...
...so you should be happy.
We're the ones that are crossing the dangerous bridge and...
...even if we mess up, you just have to get rid of the nuisance so...
...you can keep up your appearance.
Kei, what are you going to do?
Do you want to train or...
l'll do it...
l don't want to lose to this one...
So let's start the match again formally.
Do you still have the pictures that we divided the other day?
Yeah.
Sayuri Kobuchi, Ryoko Katakura, Nao Yabe, Shizuka Aihara...
...Natsumi Machida, and Miho Hashimoto...
These six are mine.
Misako Yokohama, lori Kikunai, Miyuki Kamoi, Haruka Machida...
...Mari Nakayama, Akira Naruse...
...but l have trained Akira already...
l'm beaten, how it's going to be 6 vs. 5...
That's fine with me.
Shin, you have a plain penis so l'll give you a handicap.
No, no, l can't have it from a virgin who isn't used to handling women.
l'm letting it out.
Mr. Chairman's milk, it's really good.
And it's still so hard.
Master...
My pussy is soaked saying it wants more penis.
Ah, it's coming in!
Please shove it all the way to the back!
Then let's do this.
After the women are handed over to Uncle, they are put to on an auction...
...after the clients test them out.
Why don't we figure out the victory or defeat by the total amount of the...
...final bids put together?
Meaning our cut is 10% of the bids for the female teachers...
...and the one with the higher total amount of reward is the winner.
A woman who is well trained and serves well is sold for a high price...
That's determined by our training ability.
No!
l'm going to come!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
Board Chairman's Office
Why are you acting worn out, there's something you have to do!
l-l'm sorry...
That's right, exactly, good girl...
l will take better care of you starting tomorrow!
Are you a masochist!?
Did being kicked turn you on?
Your juice is pouring out of your pussy!
You are such a perverted teacher!
l will make you come so many times tomorrow too!
Are you happy?
Yes...
...Master...
l'm going to leave the classroom for a little so for the rest of the time...
...please have a study hall...
Faculty Women's Room
Oh no... what am l...
lt feels so good...
History of Japan Teacher Shizuka Aizawa (Age 30)
W-Who is it...?
Um... it's Kobuchi...
Um, may l help you?
No, well...
l saw you run into the bathroom. l thought you weren't feeling well again...
l'm fine... l'm sorry to worry you...
l understand...
Then l will be going back...
At school...
...on top of that masturbating during class...
But my fingers won't stop...
lt feels so good...
l'm going to come...
l'm going to come, l'm going to come... l'm going to come!
l'm a pervert like this...
Faculty Women's Room
l videotaped everything from the top.
Ms. Aihara...
Your marriage may be sexless...
No... that's not it...
...but don't think you can masturbate at school.
Here isn't good so, why don't we go elsewhere and talk, Ms. Aihara?
Reference Room
No... Ms. Kobuchi, let go of me...
l'm going to scream...
Go ahead.
But the one that's going to be hurt the most after all this...
...is your child, isn't it?
l don't want to do something that wouldn't become something good.
lt's all soaked from masturbating.
lf it's like this, l can put it in right away.
No, stop it...
Stop it...
Please stay outside and make sure no one comes in.
Or would you like to do it together?
No... l'll stay outside on watch...
Master...
Then shall we hurry and get started...
Ms. Aihara.
Ah!
For the first time in three years, a penis is being shoved in...
You think...you can get away with... something like this?
lt's fine, isn't it?
Didn't you want to have sex so much, too?
Please stop...
This is something bad...
l'm so sorry...
l'm so sorry! l'm so sorry!...
l'm so sorry! l'm so sorry! l'm so sorry!...
The penis... is inside of me...
The back... lt's hitting the back...
lt's hitting the back and how is it?
Don't...
Don't make me...
Don't make me say it...
Please don't stop...
lf you want me to continue, please become my slave.
What?
lt's not like l'm thinking of stepping into your daily life.
l just want you to give me your body when l want it.
l have a child and a husband...
Such a thing is...
There's no way you can, eh?
Ms. Aihara, your frustration will be taken care of, and your masturbating...
...at school will be kept as a secret.
lt's filled with good things but...
Four days later...
You still don't want to become my slave?
No...
Not that...
The back... lt's amazing in the back...
Shin's... So good...
l'm about to come...
l'm coming again!
Six days later...
Master, your penis is delicious...
Come on, just keep on licking.
Yes.
Sayuri, please bring Natsumi Machida.
What... but how?
Think about it yourself.
l will start training her along with this one.
Yes...
So, where do you want me to come today?
ln my butt!
Please unplug my butt and pour it all right in there.
You are someone's wife but you love it in the butt, don't you?
Yes, l love it in the butt.
...and Master's penis too.
So good...
lt feels so good...
Sayuri, you're done with coaching the club, right?
Why don't we go home together?
l'm sorry...
l promised to listen to one of my student's problems.
l can't go home yet...
Then what about your house?
Another time for that too.
l promise to make it up to you so...
l'm sorry...
l guess l can't avoid it...
Sayuri, is something on your mind lately?
There are a lot of times you look depressed...
And, recently we haven't made love...
l'm a little lonely...
Thank you...
Then l'm going to go home.
Hey, Ryoko!
What?
l'm thinking about you first, and l love you!
Hey, your voice is so loud, there are still students left!
Come on!
Ah, Master!
Your penis is so good!
lt feels so good, so good!
Ms. Machida, inside your pussy is slippery and tight. lt feels so good, too!
lt's slippery and tight...
lt's so good to me too!
Your penis is so good...
Master, yours is so good, it's rubbing against my clitoris!
lt feels so good.
My hips are moving on their own.
lt is so good!
My breasts and pussy might be small but l love the penis!
l love it when it feels good!
Music Teacher Haruka Machida (Age 21)
Where are we...
l was cleaning up the equipment and...
Physical Fitness Teacher Natsumi Machida (Age 21)
Haruka!?
Oh, sister.
Hey, you woke up?
What, Kei!?
Sister, you want to do it together?
A teacher and a student can't do such a thing!
Get away from each other!
No!
l'm going to feel better!
Haruka, make your sister feel good, too.
Yes!
What, hold on, what are you doing!?
Stop...
This is the thing l use to masturbate. Stop it!
Sister, you are diligently a virgin and you've never masturbated before...
...so this feels way too good, right?
What is this vibration...
No...
My pussy is feeling numb and my mind is totally becoming white...
Sis, you came?
You are soaked.
So this is the woman...
lt's like you wet your pants.
Shin was suppose to train...
l guess it felt really good, huh?
Well with the course of events it ended up like this so l can't do anything...
Plus he did feast on one of mine so...
Haruka, make your sister a woman.
Yes!
No... l don't want to anymore...
Why do l... ...have to take this man's thing...
Hold on Haruka, don't lick me...
Haruka's tongue... So good...
lt feels so good...
Sis, your pussy...
...it's soaked with sweat and juice, it's delicious...
Master, it's totally ready.
Okay, then you can do it.
Yes!
Haruka, what are you...
This side is sis, and this side is mine.
l'm going to put this on and violate you, Sis.
This will also make you feel good and it's in me, too. So we both can come.
Ready?
Hold on...
Wait a second...
l'm putting it in!
Haru...ka...
To be continued...