You've gotten really good, Vice President.
Thank you very much.
Yukihito-sama. We're finally alone. Don't call me that.
You're right, Yumeko-kun.
Go deeper.
Yes... Good girl.
Stop! Stop it!
Yukihito-sama...
Hey, give it back!
Don't worry about them. Keep going.
Okay...
l'm sure everyone will give you a warm welcome!
But... Don't get taken aback when you see the classroom door and walls.
Are you listening?
Saku Yoshijiro-kun?
Yes?
2-B ARE IDIOTS
STOP
DUMBASSES
SCUM
GO AWAY
DIE
PATHETIC
I'LL KILL YOU!
TRASH
STUPID
SHIT
IDIOTS
This is 2nd Year Classroom B!
This is really something...
Those bastards!
Aoi-san?
Move!
Whoa!
Captain!
Mirai-chan!
Captain! My bat!
What's with the ruckus?
Hey!
M...Mirai-chan is...
Y...You! What do you think you're doing!
A student shouldn't be fondling a teacher's chest!
l wasn't fondling!
He felt her up!
lt's a misunderstanding!
You touched her five times?
Why you...!
l didn't!
Anyway, what's up with that girl?
l totally forgot about her!
Damn it! The only things l've ever fondled are baseballs...
M...Mirai-chan is going to club them to death!
l bet they're softer than baseballs...
Ge...Getaro-kun was taken away by three strange looking guys!
l saw them from the window!
One of them looked like an alien.
Mirai-chan is probably going to club them to
death before they can ab-ab-abduct him!
l don't really understand what you're saying, but...
l guess it's a pretty big deal...
Ahh...
By the way, who is that guy?
l dunno.
They should just let it be...
ACT 1 : A FIERCE & NAUGHTY BATTLE
This position is embarrassing.
Yumeko-kun, your mouth and pussy are contradicting each other.
What do you want me to do?
Please don't be so mean, Yukihiko-sama.
l don't know what you want. Tell me. What do you want me to do?
Your... l want you to slam your fat handsome cock in me here.
Here? Where do you mean by ''here''? You mean here?
Or are you talking about... here? Well? Tell me.
Put it in... Please...
Fine. l'll stick it in then.
Thank you. l can't wait any longer!
Don't stop!
The guys outside will hear you if you moan too loud.
lt's amazing! Yu...Yu...Yukihiko-sa...
Hey! You guys!
That's enough!
Here she comes... Aoi Mirai.
Yukihito-sama... Yukihito-sama...
Suffer. Suffer... Well? Can you feel it?
Cumming... l'm going to cum, Yumeko-kun.
lt's hot...
lt's coming out...
Hurry up and clean me up.
Y... Yes. l'm sorry...
Good girl...
You guys better know what's coming,
for doing this to a 2-B student!
W...What do you think you're gonna do!
No violence! You'll get expelled!
This...
...coming from...
...you guys?
Stop it, you idiot.
What? Who are you?
l'm the Transfer Student of Justice.
Let go! l'm not going to be satisfied until l clobber them!
You'll kill them if you clobber them with this!
l don't care if l get expelled!
Expulsion won't be all that happens to you!
l don't care, so let go! l said, let go!
Let go! You macho idiot!
What a violent woman!
You should act more ladylike!
How dare you!! Let go! Let...
Owww... Jeez... Don't let go so suddenly! lt's dangerous!
l hate guys like you!!
Wait!
You're abandoning your friend and running away?
H...Help me!
Hey! You should stop...
Stop right there!
How many times do l have to explain to you guys!
lt's not like today was the first time we got harassed!
Even the graffiti in the hallway is...
Stop making false accusations.
There is no way a well-mannered theater
club member would bully someone!
He's right.
You're full of it, you snobby bastard! l saw it with my own eyes!
l saw it too!
What did you see exactly?
To me it looked like you guys were using inexcusable violence...
...against our helpless theater club members.
Saku Yoshijiro... Apparently you have a history of being a delinquent.
l hear you also caused problems at the previous academy you were at.
lt just goes to show that scum will always be scum.
Boss...
Let's decide their punishment.
The transfer student, Saku Yoshijiro, will be expelled.
Aoi Mirai and the remaining students of 2nd year classroom B...
...will be suspended indefinitely.
What?
Hey! Why all of them?
W...Wait a minute please!
Sakamoto-sensei.
lt's the Vice Principal's decision.
Do you have an objection?
That punishment is too harsh.
l won't have a class to teach anymore.
lt's unfortunate for Sakamoto-sensei,
but everyone must take responsibility.
lt's also a good opportunity to improve
the moral order of the Academy.
But...
There have always been a lot of
problems where 2-B is concerned.
How does it feel to be the loser, Mirai Aoi?
Aoi Mirai, sitting right there, is called their ''Captain''.
This is what you get for continuing to disobey me. Feeling defeated?
She has been criticizing this academy's policies for a while.
lf you cry and beg for forgiveness,
l'll use my authority to save you.
lt's about time you submit to me, Aoi Mirai!
No!
Nooo!
We need to take firm action before it's too late!
So, now that things have been decided...
Please wait a minute!
l have an idea.
''Punishment to be decided. Will keep you
informed''? Acting all high and mighty...
Who's that snobby guy in glasses and
the roly-poly one with the mustache?
They control this academy together.
lt's bothering me... What's Yukihiro up to?
Don't you get it? We've been framed!
Who knows what impossible tasks they'll throw at us!
As long as l don't have to jump off
the roof, l'll do something about it.
You're really interesting.
You think?
l'm Aoi Mirai.
What's your name, Boss?
l'm Saku Yoshijiro. The Transfer Student of Justice.
l see... l'll just call you Boss.
Then what was the point of introducing myself...?
l think it suits you well.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
That's the guy from earlier!
Getaro!
Hey! Wait!
Boss!
Yes...
W...What the...
Shit!
More...
Fuck me harder... Yes! Yes! That's so good!
Holy shit... lt's tightening!
She wants me to watch her...
More... More!
l can't anymore! l'm gonna cum!
D...Don't cum yet!
l'll cum on your face!
Jeez...
What the hell. What's with this academy?
2nd Year Classroom B students! Listen up!
l have a very important message.
l'm lost.
Hey! You!
You must be the transfer student joining my class.
Are you in 2-B? Good timing.
Wouldn't you normally run away
if you were caught peeping?
You're the one who kept going even
after you knew l was watching.
lt was such a turn on...
Hey, let's fuck. lt really wasn't satisfying.
W...What are you talking about?
You're my type of guy, so l'll let you cum inside.
Please?
You're not wearing a bra?
l'm proud of my boobs!
Are you okay with cheating on your boyfriend?
Huh? What boyfriend?
The guy you were just with...
Ew, he's not my boyfriend!
Umm... l wonder what his name was?
He said he wanted to have sex, so...
Who cares about that.
Well? Does it feel good?
You're good!
You're twitching.
You can't take it all in!
No!
You're not an ordinary chick...
l'm a natural.
You're unbelievable...
Just kidding. My mother taught me.
l'm not sure how l feel about that...
My mom supposedly used to be the No.1 girl at some bar.
My dad was the No.1 host as well...
So you're a pedigree.
You're amazing! You're already hard!
lt's your fault, so you better take care of it!
Geez...
You're so rough.
l'm coming in.
Stop moaning so loud! lt'll echo!
B...But... lt's so big...
There's no stopping now!
lt hurts!
lt's so big...!
Noooo!
l can't! l can't anymore...!
lt's reaching all the way inside me!
l'm going to cum! l'm going to cum! l'm going to cum!
Nooo!
Hey, don't cum without me. l'm still not done.
l can't... l don't have the strength...
l can't anymore!
No! Stop!
Hey... Stop, please. l'm going to go...
What?
l can't hold it anymore.
Hold what?
l'm going to pee...
Let it out then.
No.
Just let it go. Come on.
Stop! Stop!
Hey, let's do it some place roomier next time.
l don't like perverts.
Finally, l'm here.
l transferred here today. l'm Saku  Yoshiji...
What are you going to do about this?
This is crazy!
How are we supposed to win a theater challenge...
Die! Moron! You piece of shit!
...against the Theater Club in the cultural festival?
Virgin! Dickwad! Cocksucker!
What am l supposed to tell my mother!
lt's over! We're all going to be suspended indefinitely!
You bastard! You monkey! You impotent bastard!
Shut up! Really, all we have to do is win the theater challenge! Let's do it!
Let's show that four-eyed jerk what we can do!
Nyoriiriiin.
You have no right to say that!
Everyone!
You shouldn't blame him. He's one of us!
S...Sensei...
He's not one of us!
Why can't they just expel him?
Yeah! Yeah!
Don't say that. You can do it.
lf everyone gets suspended indefinitely,
l won't have a class to teach.
lf l don't have a homeroom class, l'm going to get a pay cut.
Well, l have to go to my part-time job now, so...
Goodbye.
S...Sensei!
YOU'RE ALL SCUM
You're all scum!
Mirai-chan.
That's what the entire academy thinks about 2-B!
This class is a dumping ground for students...
...who are a bother for the academy and the teachers!
A guy who punched a teacher!
A guy who has ridiculously low grades!
A baseball fanatic that practices from
morning to well into the afternoon!
A guy who's too loud!
A guy who refuses to talk!
An otaku!
And an alien!
Nyuririn!
That's why people think it's okay to look down on 2-B...
...because we've all been grouped together!
This isn't just the transfer student's problem!
This is my... no, it's our problem!
Mirai-chan... l'll do it!
l have a competition coming up, so count me out.
Sora...
What are you going to do?
No way.
l want no part.
Boss! Say something!
You're all scum!
This, coming from you?
Don't move!
That's a great expression.
Um. . .
You said you wanted to contribute to my art.
That's why l asked you to model for me. That's all it is.
How does it feel?
lt's chilly...
Where are you chilly?
Um... My butt, and...
Don't look away.
Yes. l'm sorry...
Um...
Your butt and where is chilly?
D...Down there...
Good! Maki-kun! You're great!
You idiot! You haven't learned anything, have you!
Learn what? First of all, you're the one
who was swinging around a bat...
lt... lt was just an act!
That's so lame!
We need to get them involved. We only
have a month until the cultural festival.
l'll make the preparations, so you get the people involved!
Get them involved? You'd
be better at that than me...
No, l thought about it earlier.
There's no point if l make them do it!
Plus, we won't win this challenge if
you don't get along with everyone!
You said you'd do pretty much anything except jump off of here, right?
Y...yeah...
Then here you go!
What is this?
lt's the personal info on our classmates.
lt should come in handy when you try
to convince and negotiate with them.
Good luck!
Are you serious?
Who's this? lt's the only one with no picture.
Her name is Uzuki Amu.
Uzuki... l think l've heard her name before...
She's a celebrity.
The Amu Uzuki?
Boss, are you a fan?
N...No. l'm...you know...l'm only into western music, so...
Why don't you have a photo?
She gets upset when you try to take a picture of her.
lmage rights and what not...
Oh...
She rarely comes to the school anyway. She can't help us.
Fine! l'll see what l can do!
Boss, give me your hand.
Why?
Just do it.
Hey...
Promise me you'll never be violent again.
This, coming from you?
Promise me... Okay?
Okay...
l'll club you to death with a bat if you do!
lt's a promise... We're going to do this together...
See you!
They were white...