What the?
What?
What's...
What's going on?
The earth is being inv--
Gekikara!
Gekikara Men
Go! Look for women!
Wh-Who the hell are you guys?
No!
No! Don't!
Let me go! Let me go!
Stop it!
I'm kinda jealous.
This isn't the time for this.
Gekikara!
No!
What's this?!
No way!
It's embarrassing.
I don't like this!
Help!
What? It only removes their clothes.
Let's enjoy the show!
What?
Will it happen to me too?
It only affects clothes for women,
but it will melt the whole body for men.
Being naked is kinda embarrassing.
Eh? Why me too?
Hags also melt.
No! I'm not a hag!
How embarrassing!
Get only the beautiful ones!
Wh-Who is it?!
Upholders of cosmos, the maidens of the moon.
Who the hell are you?!
Earth class Korona Angel!
Tokumei Kourin has arrived!
Ryuusei Tenshi.
Primaveil!
Annoying pests!
Go get them!
Let's go, Korona-chan!
Yes, Onee-sama.
This is the resistance we, the Markjin, are facing in our conquest of Japan.
This single Primaveil.
Primaveil Tsukuyo.
Primaveil Tsukuyo
And also the other Primaveil,
Korona.
Primaveil Korona
Ever since we started our conquest, they have suddenly appeared, interfering with our invasion.
Their identity, as you can see, is these normal-looking girls, however their strength is to be reckoned with.
Our forces suffered great losses.
Moongram
The reason to why our plan of world conquest is suffering to achieve results in a timely manner
is entirely due to those Primaveils.
All of our forces have retreated.
General Genesis
Kouron.
What of prince Garland?
During the last battle plan, he went to handle the Primaveils and did not return yet.
Well, honey.
How about we let the prince handle it?
Reporting, Your Excellency.
What is it?
Garland-sama has seized one of the Primaveils.
Garland has, huh?
Your Majesty,
we have wonderful news.
Primaveil Moon Attack!
Primaveil Korona Kick!
Shit!
Take this!
Gekikara Sperm Splash!!
No!
That was close!
This is bad. Even the Saint Costume...
As long as it's hit by my sperm, it will dissolve no matter what it is.
And it will impregnate any woman.
What the heck is with this guy?
Korona-chan, make sure you absolutely don't get hit.
Yes, Onee-sama.
I'm not getting pregnant as a teenager!
You will not be able to get close with this!
Get them, boys!
Get all the women!
No!
Korona-chan, that move!
Yes, Onee-sama!
Let's go!
Korona-chan!
Yes, Onee-sama!
Moon Flash!
Shit!
Looks like they got us.
I'll have to use this last resort.
Onee-sama! There's one left.
Korona-chan! Don't let your guard down!
What the heck is this?
We can't take him on like this.
Onee-sama, let's use the robots against him.
We have nothing like that.
No good! We can't run away!
We have to use the finishing move!
There's no other choice!
Onee-sama!
We have to release the Saint Angel's power.
But if you do that, you will...
It's all right, Tsubasa-chan.
In this town, I have important people, family, and friends that I want to protect.
In that case, I'll...
No.
Tsubasa-chan, you're the sun.
If the sun is gone,
the earth will be swallowed by darkness.
Protect the people.
No, Onee-sama!
This is the end, Primaveil!
Oh, no!
If he fires one that big,
he'll impregnate all women in town.
Onee-sama!
Primaveil...
Moon Flash!
Onee-samaaaaaa!!
Tsubasa-chan...
I will always love you.
Who is it?
Onee-sama!
Onee-sama, where are you?
Onee-sama...
Ryuusei Tenshi
Primaveil
Presented by Killer Maid
http://www.killer-maid.net/
I have brought a Primaveil, Your Majesty.
It is indeed a Primaveil.
Well-done, my little brother.
With this, there is nothing to hinder our plans.
Let us hurry and sentence this girl to a most eloquent punishment.
Thus, striking fear into the humans.
Forcing them to come reeling under our rule.
Wait, Moongram.
This girl still has the amazing power of the Saint Angel.
We must draw out her power and make use of it for our purposes.
But...
I will not tolerate disobedience, Moongram.
Your Majesty!
However, how do you intend to draw it out?
In order to draw out the Saint Angel's power, that girl must be completely violated.
The Saint power will be reformed through the corruption of the body and soul.
And then, by the time she falls to the evil sense of pleasure, the girl's body will change.
Hence, it would be possible for us to take her into us.
I see.
Well then, I shall take the duty of defiling the girl.
No, I will do it.
I shall bring her back a shameless lustful woman.
Your Majesty, this girl is my prey.
Please leave this mission to me.
What are you thinking, boy?!
Know your place!
Very well.
Then, Garland, I shall leave it to you.
However, you shall have only two months.
Until then, you must train this woman in order to successfully capture her power.
But, Your Majesty...
Moongram.
My words are absolute.
Yes!
And I so wanted her...
You Primaveils have caused quite the trouble.
Looking at you like this, you're nothing but a little girl.
Don't touch me!
You're in good spirits.
Still got the strength to resist.
As expected from a Primaveil.
What are you going to do to me?
Nothing much.
I'll just teach you how to enjoy this world to its fullest.
And then, have you at our side.
Hah! As if that'll happen.
I'll never fall to the likes of you.
Is that so?
When the time comes, you'll willingly spread your own legs.
Take a look at this.
Tsubasa-chan!
What are you going to do to Tsubasa-chan?
Nothing.
However, I wonder what will happen to her friends?
What about the other one?
Stop! Stop!
Please! Stop it!
Every time you resist me,
one of her friends will die.
Take your time and think about it.
Prince-sama!
Chiharu-san of the R&D lab is calling you.
She says she has something for you.
You called?
Hold on a moment.
Huh? Who is this girl?
As ordered from high command, I have been assigned as the prince-sama's private secretary.
Private secretary?
You?
I'm Chika.
You may call me Chika-chan.
Pleased to meet you.
From now on, I'm the caretaker of his majesty's daily needs.
In short, it was for my achievements.
Lolicon.
I-I'm not!
Prince-sama is not a lolicon.
Chika is already 20.
Got to take note of it, otherwise...
It sure has been noisy latey, eh?
Who has...?
Here.
Super brainwashing medicine.
This drug is expensive, so don't waste it recklessly.
If I successfully get the Saint Angel power, I'll be a general.
There should be no problem, even if it's the R&D.
Well, I'll be looking forward to it!
Also, I created new combatant models.
Would you like to try them out?
Is there a difference from the current models?
A very grand difference!
Well then, let us explain!
Of the new Command Soldier types, there are models CDR0011 and CDRW0022.
If you apply a photograph to the forehead, they will be able to transform into the pictured person.
CDR0011 can only transform once.
CDRW0022 can transform as many times as desired.
Different from regular combatants, with incredible abilities and special skills,
the high class DVDR0033 type is also available.
That's about it.
I see.
Chiharu, give me a picture of yourself.
What are you going to use it for?
Have the Chiharu combatant in the nude...
Like this!
Like that!
And this too!
How embarrassing!
Do not read into my heart.
You perverted bastard!
That girl is unreasonable.
How would I want her naked?
Prince-sama!
Please use Chika-chan's picture!
What are you doing?!
Enough!
We'll start with your body directly.
I'll make you know that you are mine.
No...
No. No!
Stop it!
Struggle! Struggle!
If you resist me, you can only imagine what would happen.
I beg you.
Stop.
Please stop!
I'm...
I'm still...
You're...
a virgin, huh?
No!
Stop!
Interesting.
Well then, I shall have your virginity!
No! No!
Don't!
No!
Resistance is useless.
Primaveil Tsukuyo.
Is it all right with you to kill another of Korona's friends?
Then stop disobeying me!
You got that?
Yes.
Good girl.
Now, hold out your tongue.
Quite the flood.
In reality, you like doing perverted things, don't you?
N-No, I don't.
That kind of thing...
No.
You actually like having your body get molested.
I'll soon make you realise your true self.
Don't!
I see.
Your cute virgin pussy is dripping wet.
No! Don't say it!
Don't!
Don't! Don't!
Tsubasa's fr~ie~nd~s...
No!
It hurts!
As expected from a virgin.
You're tight!
No!
I feel something moving inside my stomach!
Help me!
It hurts! It hurts!
Please stop!
Pull it out!
Don't! No!
No!
Then let's finish up.
Pull it out!
I'm shooting inside of you!
D-Don't!
You are mine.
Where I ejaculate is my business!
Onee-sama!
Onee-sama...
Where are you?
You should understand perfectly with this.
That you are mine.
How long do you plan on crying?
Make sure to clean me up properly.
Hey!
Your pretty face will clean my dick.
Clean it with your mouth.
Prince-sama!
You already started it?
Is something the matter?
Yes.
Chiharu-san has finished three new combatants.
Bring them in.
Sure.
These guys!
They look the same as the old ones.
Is there anything to test them out with?
Good. That's enough.
Get on the bed and take off your clothes.
It's basically the same as not wearing any with them in that condition.
Which one to use them on?
All right. You are this.
This.
And this.
I see.
This could be useful.
Tsukuyo!
Sit there and spread your legs.
Tsubasa's fr~ie~nd~s...
Prince-sama, amazing!
Spread your pussy.
Spread it!
I'll show you something good.
As developed by our Markjin Empire, no matter what kind of person takes this, they will obey orders.
And afterwards, your sensitivity for pleasure will reach the highest level.
Sensitvity...
You can't mean...
For the experiment, you're going to feel good.
You must be happy.
Swallow it!
No!
I don't want to!
Tsu~ba~sa...
All right!
Get on all fours and raise your ass to me.
Over there...!
I'll take this virginity, too.
No!
It's going into my butt!
Ouch!
It hurts!
It hurts! Stop!
Not there!
No!
Pervert!
I have now taken all of your virgin spots.
Hey! The big one there!
Come forward.
The other two come, too.
Four players!
No! No!
Onee-sama!
Tsubasa-chan? Is it you, Tsubasa-chan?
Where? Where are you?
I don't know where.
I've been captured.
Onee-sama, I'll save you.
At any rate, Tsubasa-chan. Escape!
The Markjin are killing people close to you to threaten me.
Why?
They show me your terrified look, so that I listen to them.
And I also lost my stick.
I can't call out my power.
Then this...
Oh, right. Onee-sama, I don't know your location, but I might be able to give it to you.
You can't, Tsubasa-chan!
Onee-sama's thoughts... Please move!
Not bad.
You!
I'll never forgive you!
Especially you!
Cool!
Prince-sama!
Strong!
No! He's too strong!
With my current strength...
No.
I can't.
Run!
Run, Tsubasa-chan!
Run~!!
Presented by Killer Maid
http://www.killer-maid.net/
Translator:
Dark Master Schmidt
Translation Checker & Editor:
Rengemaru
Timer:
Dark Master Schmidt
Typesetter:
Quality Checker:
Dark Master Schmidt
Encoder: