Sexual
Pursuit
Episode 2
presented by Kira-H
Makoto, I'd like
to ask you something...
Is Miss Kasukabe here?
Is something wrong?
A-Ai!
T-The game made us...
Right, the game forced us into this!
Y-Yeah, the game that I got was...
Game?
Makoto, you snuck in a game, huh?
I hope you don't play it too much.
More importantly though...
Miss Kasukabe isn't here, huh?
Hey, couldn't it be that she can't see
this because of the game's power?
There's no way.
But it said this won't end till we hit the
goal, and we couldn't even turn it off...
Big Brother, the window won't open!
Why you!
Right?
That's true.
Okay, Makoto,
if you see Miss Kasukabe...
...then tell her
to come to her checkup.
If she doesn't...
If she doesn't, she'll have to deal
with consequences that she'll regret...
...forever.
R-Right...
Speaking ofwhich, where is she?
Heave-ho...
Hina?
Man, Miss Naruse is scary.
Right, little brother?
What is it?
You don't want her walking in
on this situation again, right?
She may not have noticed it just
now, but she may the next time.
T-That's...
Leave it to me.
Behold! It's a Columbus-esque concept.
What's up your sleeve?
Well, it seems you're using
this game to plot some bad things.
You've actually done
horrible things to your mother.
So I figured it might
be better if I joined in.
Oh, what a coincidence.
The thought just popped in my head
to protect my older sister from you.
No worries. I'm going to make
it so that it's to your advantage.
Really?
You really like him, don't you?
What's so great about him?
Hey, Yuna, get away from her.
Hina, please don't corrupt Yuna.
You're a walking bad influence.
You were yelping and pounding
your mom in front of her...
...and you call me a bad influence?
Regardless, I'm going to join
the game in your mom's place.
Hina, we're not
on the same page here.
I just have to press this button, right?
R-Right.
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Lesbianism
Yahoo!
There is a God!
No way.
This means I'm under the control
of the game, so don't be mad at me.
Hina?
That's right.
It's me, Hina.
Sis, run!
Yuna?
I don't like it when
you're like that, Big Brother.
Misa, let's do nice things together.
Darn it.
Miss Kasukabe!
What's with your third and fourth
attempts at escaping your checkup?
Miss Naruse...
There's a deep reason for this.
Does that reason run deeper
than my anger right now?
Little brother, help me!
No!
If we close it, we won't
be able to get out again!
Crap.
Makoto... And even you, Yuna...
You want to make me suffer like this?
H-Hold on, Sis...
You want to do horrible things to me
like you did with Natsuki, right?
S-Sis...
I always thought you were a bit
carefree, but I still thought well of you.
Why did it turn out this way?
Whatever, Big Brother.
Let's ignore this uncooperative
sister and finish this game up.
Yuna?
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Lesbianism
I-I don't want this.
Sis, stop complaining
and play with mine too.
Yours is so wet.
I'm sure you got excited when
I was playing with Big Brother's dick.
That's not...
...true.
N-No!
Yuna, please stop!
Well? It's good, right?
I do this kind of stuff every day,
so I know what feels good.
Please stop.
Makoto... And you too, Yuna.
Sis, your breasts
are so big. I'm jealous.
I'm sure Big Brother
likes big breasts like this.
O-Ouch!
Yuna, that hurts.
But my mom's are big,
so there's room for improvement.
To the point that
I can compete with you.
N-No, my nipples.
Yuna, please, stop...
Makoto, you too... This is abnormal.
It's abnormal...
You say that, but you're turned on
because he's watching you.
You enjoy it!
That's not true... That's not...
Your nipple is this hard!
No! No! No!
I know you want his thing.
I-I'm coming!
Makoto's...
No, I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I-I'm coming!
Yuna?
Yuna, your clothes! You're naked!
Your penis is showing too.
That's true, but...
I love you, Big Brother.
I figured you didn't notice.
W-Well, I think you're adorable...
Though I have thought
about you while masturbating...
But you're...
...a sister, right?
But Misaki is one too.
Yuna, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
...so just wait a little, okay?
But Natsuki thinks...
Mom did what
she wanted to do with Dad.
But I don't want to be
told I can't do that either.
Yeah, that's true.
T-That's why I'm going
to be honest with my feelings.
Yuna, are you sure
you're okay with me?
I may be a no-good guy,
just like Natsuki says.
You're not no-good.
After all, you're...
You're a true brother to me.
Thanks.
Yuna, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
If we didn't have this, I don't think
I would have told you my feelings.
So I don't think this is
a bad game like Mom said.
Seems like it.
I-I'm kind of glad I found this game.
That's true.
S-Say, Big Brother...
Y-Yeah?
I couldn't be your first...
...but I don't care about that.
U-Um, so I...
...want to have sex with you.
Y-Yuna, are you okay?
Yeah, but it's a little painful.
Is it okay to move?
It's so tight that
I feel like I'm going to come.
Yeah, go ahead.
Big Brother!
I-I'm sorry, Yuna.
Your squeezing felt too good.
Is my pussy turning you on?
It feels so good inside you.
Kiss me while we do this.
Big Brother, that tickles.
But I thought that doing this
would keep your mind off the pain.
Thanks.
What?
No, it's nothing.
I want to know.
You like big breasts.
But don't worry.
I'm sure mine will grow bigger.
Big Brother...
W-Why are Makoto and Yuna...
Makoto, why does it
have to be Yuna?
And Yuna, why does it
have to be Makoto?
Big Brother, that tickles.
But I thought that doing this
would keep your mind off the pain.
Yeah, thanks.
It's sliding in easier now, Yuna.
Yeah, I think it feels a lot better now.
Big Brother, you're playing
with my breasts again.
If I do this, it'll get bigger, right?
Like you said before, I like breasts.
Just like Sis's?
W-Well, that's...
Makoto's big thing is being
shoved into Yuna's petite body.
Makoto... Makoto...
You were only mine for so long...
My privates are so lonely.
Makoto... Makoto... Makoto...
Just like Sis's?
W-Well, that's...
Makoto!
S-Sis?
Hey, Big Brother.
Please have sex with Sis.
What?
Sis was watching us
the whole time we were doing it.
She most likely realized
her feelings when that happened.
B-But what about you, Yuna?
Don't worry about me. After all, the
most important thing is how you feel.
What about your feelings?
T-Then I guess
the three of us can do it...
...can't we?
You can do Sis first.
Yuna?
I did it with him before,
so it's your turn now.
R-Right, Big Brother?
Y-Yeah.
T-Then here I go.
Okay, I'm going to move.
No, not yet...
Makoto's... Makoto's...
S-Stop, Yuna...
I'm not stopping.
Your nipples are pretty and pink.
Stop...
I'm so happy with your dick
inside me, Big Brother!
I'm so happy!
No! No, Sis...
With his dick and your tongue,
my mind's going to go crazy!
Yuna, lick mine too.
Yuna, your tongue vibrates
when Makoto pounds me.
M-My clitoris and yours
are rubbing each other!
You're so perverted, Yuna.
You're going to make me come!
With Big Brother's and Sis's!
I can feel the body
heat from both of you.
Big Brother, will you come
if we keep doing this?
You're both so perverted...
I'm going to become perverted too!
I-I'm coming...
We're going to come too, Makoto!
We're coming!
We're coming! We're coming!
What a dream...
Maybe they're still younger
than I think they are.
H-Help me, little brother...
Makoto, don't you lift a finger!
Miss Kasukabe isn't going
to get away this easily!
I never thought I'd be murdered
by a nurse during a hospital stay...
Don't joke about things like that!
Hina, you're reaping what you sow.
Huh?