Kiss me, Shun...
Kiss me!
Presented by Kira-H
House of Five Lusts
Part 2
Shun...
Whenever you do it with me...
...I kind of change!
In what way?
Something I was repressing...
In that case,
let's change things up a bit.
Um, Shun?
Say, Miss Shizuru,
there's something I'd like you to tell me.
We'll finish once you tell me.
What is it?
What's inside the outbuilding?
I-I don't want to talk about that bitch...
Well, I guess that'll do.
S-Shun?
Don't worry.
This hole of yours
is twitching in anticipation.
No! It's not!
N-No! No no no!
You put it in my ass...
Are you amazed by
how unnatural it feels?
S-Shun... Pull it out...
Do you wish me to start moving?
No...
I wouldn't do anything
that's not for your own good.
B-But...
So it's time for me to start.
It doesn't hurt at all, does it?
No... It hurts a lot...
S-Shun, it's so strange.
It hurts so much, and yet...
Oh? You're going to come?
N-No...
Even if you can't,
this is all I'll give you today.
Can you stand it?
Come on, don't make that face.
No...
I feel so hot inside...
I think I'm going
to come too. In your ass.
I'd be happy
if you came along with me.
S-Shun! I... I'm going to come too!
It feels good having
you pound my ass!
I'm turning into
a pervert who likes anal!
I guess I was too hasty.
What is it?
It's about the outbuilding
you mentioned before.
It's our mother who's in there.
That's what makes it the core.
She isn't right in
the head anymore though.
So that place is,
in a way, like an asylum.
Asylum?
Having the previous head
of the Jounouchi family...
...locked up inside
a hospital would look bad after all.
Is she really
this family's central figure?
I don't recall when it got this way,
but it was a long time ago.
Then why do you hate her
so much, Miss Shizuru?
If she's the way you say she is.
Because of what she said about him!
She said he wasn't
fit to be a Jounouchi...
If you want to take a look
in there, I'll pass along the word.
I guess I should make sure
nobody sees you go in.
It's unusual for you to get up
this early, Miss Tsubame.
Wrong, I'm just now going to bed because
I reached a stopping point in my work.
I had a feeling that was it.
You look nervous about something,
Shun. That's unusual for you.
I never realized you paid
such close attention to me.
Well, of course I do.
After all, you're important to me.
Yes, very important.
Why, Miss Tsubame,
you were chomping at the bit.
You weren't wearing any panties.
Were you hoping this would happen?
What? Didn't you believe me
when I said I was crazy about you?
You sure are mean sometimes.
Why don't we try
something new today?
W-Who's there?
S-Shun, is that you?
I'm peeing!
You always seem to get
the better of me, Shun.
Uh-oh, you really
do look stressed out.
Don't you ever feel
like you're in danger?
Danger? This estate is
the safest place in the world.
But what if I were to...
Yes, what if I were to let in a burglar?
It isn't impossible.
I bet that idea crossed your mind...
...and that's what got you so excited.
Here's what I want. I want some kind
of unstoppable calamity to come along...
...and thrust me down
into the depths of darkness.
So when you did what you did,
I thought perhaps it had arrived.
You mean the way it's written here?
Let's see... Where should I begin?
The truth is that
our mother wrote that.
The first thing I'll have
to tell you about is our parents.
Things are much better now...
...but two generations ago, conditions
were rather severe in this family.
That family head was hung up on
bloodlines and knew nothing of the world.
Of course coping with societal
changes was impossible.
So we were on a collision
course with our own downfall.
Onto that stage walked
my father, a nouveau riche.
He had a complex about his upstart
lineage, which was typical of such people.
The Jounouchis
wanted cold, hard cash.
They each had
something the other wanted...
...so by marrying a Jounouchi, my
father finally was in the upper crust.
Marrying into your wife's family is tricky
though, even without a class distinction.
Apparently it was
tough times for Father.
Mother was a sheltered beauty with status,
and Father was a lower-class upstart.
Only sex for conception was allowed.
Mother wasn't exactly
passionate, as you can imagine.
That must've been tough on a man.
To alleviate his sexual frustration, my kind
mother had the twisted romantic idea...
...that he should find another
woman who looked just like her.
Accepting such a gesture of love meant
his sex life would get more aggressive.
Since you read that...
...I think you understand
"aggressive sex.'' is just a cute name for it.
There was nothing they wouldn't try.
What was Mother thinking?
Maybe she developed an interest
in a low-class upstart's deeds.
She started spying on those acts
of aggressive sex and taking notes.
So what you read
was their joint masterpiece.
But it seems it was all too
provocative for my sheltered mother.
Watching a woman who looked
just like her being violated...
...in mind and body and slowly collapsing
eventually led to her own collapse.
Locked up inside a hospital...
Now I see.
Shizuru told you
something, didn't she?
I think it was her persecution complex
that ultimately killed her husband.
After all, to forget
your own daughter's face...
...but still remember to make rash
remarks about the ''Jounouchi bloodline''...
I read that when I was still young and
impressionable, so I turned out like this.
But I ended up an incomplete person
who could never truly move beyond it.
What kind of parents were they, to let such
a thing negatively influence their own child?
Sorry if this bored you.
Not that any of it really
matters in the end.
I'll say.
Aha! You thought you'd found
some important Jounouchi secret.
To be honest, yes.
Too bad!
All you have left now
is Rei and Tsugumi...
...though you might have to use
a different approach with her...
...and the Jounouchi
family will be all yours.
That's probably true.
Are you waiting for
the inevitable divine retribution?
That's why you abandoned your beloved
family and live like an ascetic.
It's nothing as profound as that.
It's just what happens to
those entranced by the abyss.
I imagine that's a pious way of thinking,
even if that's not the best word for it.
Yes, I was only taking a stab, but maybe
I'm closer to the truth than I thought.
That side of you is
a sort of messianism.
In other words,
you're hoping for that moment.
But you also fear it,
so you hope it never comes.
So it's messianism
without a messiah?
It's not a destination you're meant
to reach, but one you forever approach.
This place is...
...much worse than you expected?
I had a feeling you'd show up, Tomoe.
It seemed so strange when
Shizuru told me about this place.
Her story and yours
just sounded too different.
It wasn't hard to figure out that
somebody must have been lying.
Don't you have anything to say?
Sorry, Shun.
I don't have time
to listen to your deductions.
I don't want to kill you,
so give me the key and step aside.
Thanks.
I don't know what she's up to, but there's
no gain in letting the old lady live.
If she wants to do
the dirty work, she's welcome to it.
Do you want to go inside?
What for?
Aren't you after
the one who just broke in?
Why would I be?
Whatever.
So even you groan
in pain sometimes, eh?
What's so funny?
I see you're still calm about this.
Then you won't mind if I get rougher.
I'm going to come inside you.
Just think,
not long ago you were a virgin.
Please, I want it.
I want you, Shun.
By the way, earlier Tomoe...
Isn't that yours, Shun?
Shouldn't you answer it?
Hello.
How does she know my name?
W-What have I done? Tell me, Shun!
What are you talking about?
Tomoe?
There's still some secret
in there, isn't there?
What are you doing?
I can't just sit here naked.
After all, I might catch a cold.
Tell me, how much do you know?
The previous family head is in there,
and she's become mentally ill.
Why do you think
Tomoe snuck in there?
For revenge.
Correct. To avenge her mother, who
was tortured and killed by our father.
Then why?
I wonder. Was it really
our mother in there?
A woman who looked like her...
The body double?
Well done.
That's sick, using revenge
to trick her into killing her own mother.
Oh, but it's not like it mattered to us.
But it's what she wanted,
so I let her do it.
That's all.
Wait. Does that mean
the previous family head's still alive?
No. Like you said,
she was the body double.
She switched places with her and was
tortured to death by her own husband.
It's probably what
she wanted. Besides...
...maybe it was
a punishment she deserved.
What's that?
She died as a result of sacrificing
herself for the man she loved.
Even if it was cruel sex, she wanted
the full force of his true affections.
It's enough to make you cry.
She loved him? I heard
she didn't want to marry him.
Feelings that find their way to the surface aren't
everything. Maybe deep down, she loved him.
Then what was the punishment for?
It was for having sex with
an outsider and diluting the bloodline.
I hate the thought that some
outsider's blood might run in our veins.
So, you're the one
who killed Shizuru's husband...
Oh, you're the best.
I think it's very important
that you're so smart!
So will you kill me too? I'm trying
to worm my way into the Jounouchis.
Why? You're the divine
retribution we've been waiting for.
I'd just as soon not get that
involved in your tangled bloodline.
But weren't you after
the Jounouchi family?
Do it, Tsugumi.
Miss Hina, what?
I was trying to make you happy.
W-Well, could you set me free?
No.
After all, you belong only to me.
W-What's that?
A new aphrodisiac.
I was worried whether it would work,
but thankfully it did well.
You dosed me?
Yes, because I wanted
to make you mine.
You're with him again?
You're mine, you know, Hina.
I didn't ask for this.
Shun, that's cold.
See? He's such a cruel jerk.
That's why I'm gonna do this.
Look at how big it's gotten
even though I'm using my foot, Hina.
He really is like an animal.
I'm sorry, Miss Tsugumi.
Your oily feet are just that slippery.
Take that back! There's
nothing wrong with my feet!
I had to run around a lot today,
so maybe I'm a little sweaty.
Yes, that's true.
Well, take this.
H-Hina, look how much it's twitching.
Y-Yeah, it's amazing.
W-Wow, look at all that!
What should I do, Hina?
I-It's no use asking me...
Hina, Tsugumi, this playtime
of yours isn't much fun for Shun.
Is it?
No.
Shun, that's so good...
You really are special to us.
Hey, Shun...
I want to kiss you...
You haven't come yet, have you?
Looks like we can keep having fun.
What are you thinking?
Let's talk a bit about the past.
Our mother had an older brother.
They had a forbidden relationship.
What's your point?
He died young in the end.
Their love was never fulfilled.
Hey...
But some of their fertilized
eggs were cryogenically-preserved.
Tell me, Shun. Do you remember
anything before the orphanage?
Damn...
Haven't you felt an irrational sense
of spite ever since you were a child?
Just stop!
One strong enough to make you vow
to get revenge on the Jounouchis?
Don't say it!
I'm coming!
I wonder if I'll get pregnant... I'm coming!
Welcome home.