I heard, Keita.
The reason your house
is so loud lately...
...is because you're living
with three pretty ladies.
''Living with'' isn't the right way to put it.
They're candidates to be my mother.
They're women who may
become my dad's wife.
I know that. And the fact
you're to choose one of them.
Listen up, Keita!
I, Haruka Mikami, will run
as a mother candidate too!
What?
Episode 2
Why?
It doesn't matter.
I choose to, so it's fine.
It's not. You'd be
a candidate to be my mom!
Are you stupid?
Shut up!
I'll make you
speechless with my charm!
''Speechless''...
Could it be that you
were in love with my dad?
What?
Are you serious, Haruka?
Mr. Taguchi!
Y-You showed up, Dad...
Haruka, is that true?
O-Of course!
Oh, wonderful, Haruka.
I'm welcome to the idea, of course.
Listen up, Keita. She's one
of the candidates now as well.
Get a room ready
for her quickly, understood?
I'm off to work now.
Do your best!
You too, Haruka!
What the hell did he come here for?
Thanks for dinner,
Miss Sawagiri. It was great.
Chiyo, you're a good cook.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry. Haruka just
locked herself in her room.
Please, I'm sure she's tired.
True, she was irritated at carrying
her luggage all by herself.
She's like my dad. She won't
quit once she's gotten started.
I'm sure she'll get bored of it right
away, so please look after her till then.
Right, please leave it to us.
By the way, where's Noriko?
Well, she was
wandering around before...
Did you call?
I was having dinner with Haruka.
A sports player eats
so much. I was amazed.
Anyway, you have good taste, Chiyo.
I sometimes order takeout from
this place too, but it's always good.
Takeout?
Yeah, they listen
to your requests pretty well.
It's perfect for people like us.
Hey, Noriko...
What, Kazuho?
Miss Sawagiri!
Chiyo, we don't care about that...
Huh? Did I do something again?
Miss Sawagiri,
please wait! Miss Sawagiri!
Miss Sawagiri, I don't
care about stuff like that.
I always got takeout
when I was alone.
I'm sorry that I can't be of
any help! I'm completely no-good!
What are you saying?
You're helping out a lot.
Please don't say such things.
Because of you, I...
A blackout?
Yeah, it's a blackout. Miss Sawagiri?
U-Um, Keita, it's dark.
I can't take the dark.
It's okay. It's just a blackout.
No, I'm scared.
I'm scared of the dark.
Where are you? I don't
like being alone in the dark.
Hold on. I'll come to you.
I stepped on something!
Keita...
C-Chiyo, please don't
grab hold of me like that...
Keita... Keita... Keita...
Miss Sawagiri, it's okay.
I'm here.
Keita...
You didn't hurt yourself, did you?
I'm bad with the dark.
I'm scared of it. I can't be alone.
It's all right.
I'm with you now after all.
Thank you, Keita.
I'm just glad I fell on the bed.
What is it?
Didn't you just call me by my first name?
Did I? I'm very sorry.
Don't misunderstand.
It made me happy.
Since coming here, I was the only
one you didn't call by first name.
I didn't like it because I felt alone.
So, Keita, I want
to become closer to you.
Miss Sawagiri, are you
sure you want to do this?
That won't do.
Call me by my first name.
Um... Chiyo.
Right.
No...
Say, Keita...
Please...
I can't wait any longer...
Okay, Chiyo.
Here I go. Huh? It's a little dark, so...
No, Keita, that's my anus.
Then here?
No.
Keita, it's here.
Be nice to me.
It's fine now. Please put it in.
Are you okay, Miss Sawagiri?
You're so mean. Use my first name.
I'm sorry, Chiyo.
No, don't tease it more than this! No!
Don't say that. Let me hear more
of your sweet voice, Miss Sawagiri.
Say it again... Say my name, Keita!
No, you have to be
turned on a little more.
Please don't be mean, Keita.
Keita, I... I...
Keita!
Yes, you're adorable, Chiyo.
Please call me
by my first name again.
Chiyo.
Yes.
Yes!
Chiyo...
Keita...
Well, I'll be going.
Okay, have a good day, Chiyo.
Have a good day!
Keita, you called
Chiyo by her first name.
Did something happen?
Nothing did.
Are you sure?
It seems kind of suspicious.
Come on, it's weird only
calling Chiyo by her last name.
Why did you start today?
That's kind of weird.
Did something happen yesterday?
Haruka!
Nothing really.
Noriko.
After the lights went out, we just waited for them to come on.
Those two are close, aren't they?
As a candidate for his mother.
You're sure?
I'm sure.
Doesn't look that way to me.
You're really sure?
I am.
So what did you want to ask me?
Well, it's not really
something I wanted to ask...
I was wondering if you still
wanted to become Keita's mother.
Of course I do. Why do you ask?
You sure someone becoming his
mother should do something like this?
I was wondering
what you thought about it.
This is from the other
day when Keita and I...
That's right.
What do you think
of my detective skills?
This wasn't like that...
You're mistaken.
I wasn't trying to do that...
Well, I think it would be fine
if everyone became close.
Kazuho, the phone.
Hello, Taguchi residence.
J-Jinta? No, it's nothing.
I'm fine.
Where are you now?
Oh, me?
I'm at the beach.
I wanted to see it on my way home.
It's wonderful. It's like the ocean
breeze is cleansing my heart.
By the way, how's Keita doing?
Has he slacked off all summer break?
No, he's doing fine.
He worries about us every day.
There was a blackout yesterday...
...but it seems he was
looking out for the neighborhood.
Yes, it seems like it.
Hey, Noriko, please stop that.
Just keep on talking.
Hey...
Sorry, it's nothing.
Yes, um... That's right.
Yes.
It seems like it was trouble.
Glad to hear Keita is being helpful.
Yes, really.
Rather than us being mothers to him,
he's taking care of us instead.
Yes, that's not a problem.
Sorry, the waves are loud here.
I'm very grateful to you ladies.
Especially you, for
taking care of the cooking...
...since Chiyo can't cook
too well, despite appearances.
Jinta, you knew?
It seemed Chiyo was
trying to hide it, so...
Yesterday too...
No, i-it's nothing.
It's nothing.
Yes, I didn't know at all...
I just thought she was a cute person
inside. That's what I realized recently.
Yes, that's right.
I hope Keita realizes that too.
Sorry to keep you
on the phone so long.
I'll be back soon after wandering
some more. Don't worry about me.
You should all just get along.
I understand.
Noriko, what are you doing?
T-That's far enough.
Nope, the best part starts now.
Voila! Let's go with this one next.
No, please stop it.
Here you go.
Welcome home, Haruka.
Thank goodness...
I'm home...
Haruka, you should have called or
something if you were gonna be late.
Sorry, I just went back to my
house to get something I forgot.
Everyone was worried about you!
You were the one who barged
in here, so do the proper thing!
K-Keita, you don't have to go so far...
But, Chiyo, she's so self-centered.
But she's home now, right, Keita?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
I apologize.
Why you...
Calm down, you two.
What's up with Keita?
He's all, ''You, you, you.'' What
does he think I came here to do?
If it stays this way, that dumb
Keita is going to hate me more.
Keita, you idiot!
Your tolerance is low,
so why do you drink?
Because it's good.
Let me drink more...
No!
Why not, cheapskate?
Jeez, quit it!
This isn't what you think.
Noriko is drunk, and...
Hey, Haruka...
Idiot.
Keita, I can't get
this off... Undress me...
Jeez! Noriko,
just hurry and go to sleep!
Why isn't anyone home?
Apparently, they all have
something going on today.
A better question is why you
came home on a day like today.
Have you decided
who you'll pick as a mother?
Well, they're all nice. Though
I don't get what Haruka is doing.
You're no good at all.
What am I supposed to do?
So bored...
Yeah.
So tired...
Oh? Haruka.
Mr. Taguchi.
Heading back from
practice? You're working hard.
I know. I'm always covered in sweat.
Plus the shower still isn't fixed.
You're back from work?
No, I have to get going again.
You're going to work now?
It's like you're doing it on purpose.
Maybe.
You talk just like Keita does.
That's because Keita talks like me.
Even so, you're totally alike.
Haruka, you like Keita, don't you?
Yes, I wanted to stay close to him,
so I became a mother candidate.
That's true. You want to be
with the person you like.
Good luck.
But I don't know what to do.
Well, he is dense.
Chiyo, I'm going
to take a shower first.
Shall we take one together?
I'm embarrassed,
so maybe another time.
Keita.
What were you
doing in Chiyo's room?
Who cares. It doesn't matter to you.
Why?
Why are you close with
the others but mean to me?
You get on my case all the time.
It can't be like it used to be.
Plus, you're...
I can't take this anymore!
Keita, look at me!
I...
I like you too, Keita!
Where did that come from?
Put your breasts away, you idiot!
Why do you always call me
an idiot all the time? You're the idiot!
I want to do what everyone
else does with you too...
What's all the shouting about?
Keita, you should think
of Haruka's feelings too.
But I've never done it,
and I don't know how to.
Okay, hold on a second!
I have a good idea!
N-Noriko?
It's okay, Haruka. Leave it to me.
It might not be a bad deal.
Really?
Okay, Keita, come over
here and help Haruka out.
Like I said, why'd it turn out this way?
Keita, I don't mind it like this.
Please, Keita.
You made a girl go so far
as to say that, so just do it.
You really don't mind?
It's fine because I like you, Keita.
Haruka.
Be nice to her.
Chiyo, help them out.
Sure.
Kazuho, you're naked anyway.
Still...
I'll do it to you like the other day.
You liked it so much.
Look, you're soaked
already. Kazuho, you perv.
Haruka, let me see
your breasts again.
Okay, look closely, Keita.
Touch them.
Keita, please her with your mouth.
Having my breasts
licked feels kind of strange.
Hey, Keita, could you
go down there too?
Wait, Keita... What?
No! It's embarrassing this way!
No, no, no!
No, Keita! This is
gonna make me go crazy!
It's rough, Keita.
I can't take this much longer.
Haruka, hold on a little longer.
It'll just get better.
Keita, it's about time.
Right.
Haruka, don't tense up, okay?
Okay.
You're totally soaked.
Keita.
Right.
I'm putting it in, Haruka.
Okay, Keita...
Haruka?
Chiyo...
It's fine. Keep it there for a little while.
You too. Hold on a little longer.
Okay...
It seems you're just about ready.
Voila, here it is again.
No, not that.
It turns me on too much.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here, bon appetit!
Is it okay now?
Y-Yeah.
Please move, Keita.
Right.
Keita, move a little slower.
It's my first time.
I'm sorry, Haruka. I can't stop.
You feel too good.
Really? So have you had enough?
H-How about you?
I don't know.
It feels like the inside of
my stomach is being shocked.
Keita, not so hard!
I-I'm fine. Having it in
deep feels kind of good, Chiyo.
Move it up and down around here.
L-Like this?
Yes, right there.
Please move more, Keita.
Haruka, I can't... I feel like cumming.
Go ahead. You can cum, Keita.
You can cum inside me!
Hot stuff is spreading inside me.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, Keita.
Well, Haruka? Isn't it wonderful?
It gets even better
when you do it more.
I see. It makes me kind of happy.
Now Haruka's one of us too, huh?
What do you mean by one of us?
Now everyone can get along.
Come on, Kazuho, do your best!
Keita, you're amazing.
You're this hard again?
I'll do it for you this time.
Then take care of mine, Keita.
I can't choose a mom like this, Dad!
Forget about all the love games.
It's just me looking away from you.
l walk away without saying a word.
Although my footsteps
create a rhythm for a second.
The image of me
jumping deep in your eyes.
A halation reminiscent
of our promised place.
Someday the distance
between us will narrow.
l believe it, in that promised place.
In that scenery
that doesn't change...
...l looked up, and l can
hear your voice. l love you.
Keita, you're passionate!
Brought to you by Kira-H team