Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Kiyama General Hospital
Sexual
Pursuit
Episode 1
presented by Kira-H
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Massage
H-Hey, that's enough.
Come on, Makoto!
I'm just joking around.
I hate those kinds of jokes.
You should have said so from the beginning.
Well, I couldn't help it!
My body just moved on its own.
It's nothing.
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Massage
Yuna, you're so into your school
activities that I'm sure you're sore.
Big Brother, it tickles.
That proves you're sore.
Let's see how much you've developed.
You shouldn't do that!
I'm just kidding. It's a joke.
M-Makoto!
I-I'm sorry...
Gosh, you're the same
as Daisuke in that respect.
Come on, Makoto, apologize to Yuna.
Yuna, I went a Little too far.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
I don't mind it.
Yuna, what's wrong?
B-Big Brother, your hand!
W-W-What?
Makoto!
Makoto?
I-It's not me!
M-My arm's moving on its own!
Stop fooling around!
M-My body...
What is this? I can't move!
I don't want to do this...
Well, that's not true, but...
Hey, Sis! Natsuki!
Could you do something about this?
We can't move!
N-No, you shouldn't
Big Brother, stop it!
I-It's not like I'm touching
them because I want to.
Is that because
my breasts are small?
Q-Quit joking around.
Small ones are, you know...
Yours has its pros, Yuna...
Yuna, what are you saying?
Makoto! Hurry and let go of Yuna!
Makoto, please don't
trouble your sister, okay?
B-Big Brother, if you do that,
my nipples are going to get hard.
Y-Yuna, you're turned on?
Makoto!
Y-Yell all you want. My hands
are doing this themselves...
It's not me! Sis, it's not me!
What am I supposed to do?
Makoto, what were your intentions?
What you did can't be passed off
as a joke. Do you understand?
It wasn't of my own will.
My body was doing it on its own.
I can't even buy that.
You're just like Daisuke.
They're not even excuses.
You tell such transparent lies.
Mom, just stop!
You constantly compare
Big Brother to Dad and belittle him.
Why'd you get married to Dad then?
Big Brother,
I'll apologize for what she said.
Thanks, Yuna.
Also, I'm sorry.
W-Well, if it's you...
T-Then I don't mind being felt up...
Or rather, I'm happy about it.
Huh? Big Brother?
Jeez!
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
I believe it's my turn...
Mouth to Mouth
I actually have to do this?
T-There's no way.
I can't do something like that.
Here you go, Sis.
W-What, Makoto?
What are you holding?
Vegetable juice.
Sis?
No, i-it's not me!
My body is doing this on its own...
Big Brother...
Huh?
Sis?
No, don't...
Misaki, stop it!
No!
Sis?
I'm sorry, Makoto.
I'm happy that you're
concerned about me...
...but please stay by
Yuna instead of me.
B-But...
We'll put an end to this now.
N-Natsuki, please calm down.
I thought Misaki was different
from Daisuke, but after doing that...
I don't care about me, but please
don't lump Sis in with Dad's name.
I-In any case,
we're ending the game here.
I don't care if it's a free sample.
The joke has gone too far.
I feel that way too.
Yuna, I'm sorry that something
weird like this happened.
No, it's fine.
If it's with Sis, it doesn't count, right?
Come on, Makoto.
Please help me here.
What's wrong?
It won't open!
I wonder if someone
locked it from the outside.
It can't be!
Big Brother, the window won't open!
Nurse-call buttons don't always work,
but why won't the door open?
Why you!
What is going on?
What the heck? They're so loud...
Makoto, what is the meaning of this?
I-I have no clue either.
First of all, you made us
play a lewd game like this one.
Aren't you ashamed?
W-Well, this was a sample...
T-That's right. I was given this...
Yuna, shush!
Even if you have an innocent
face, you are Daisuke's son.
I can't trust you.
Yuna, what's wrong?
Look here.
Sexual Pursuit
"It won't end until
you make it to the goal."
Sexual Pursuit
You've got to be kidding me.
I understand.
At least the fact
that this situation is abnormal.
I'll excuse those earlier events.
T-That's right.
Let's work together to finish this.
Makoto, we'll be tying you up.
What?
This has gotten interesting.
Hold on.
Natsuki, this isn't fair. On top of that,
you've tied me up way too tight.
Natsuki, I don't think
you have to go this far.
I don't like that we're
only treating him like this.
This is something we have to do.
Yuna, you didn't like him massaging
your breasts and such, right?
Well...
That's the verdict,
so please understand.
Natsuki, you're not doing
this out of malice, right?
I... Well, it's not actually my fault...
...but I may have gone a little too far.
Let's just finish this creepy
game quickly, right, Yuna?
Yeah!
I-I didn't think about
doing this out of spite, Makoto.
I'm just thinking about Yuna.
I'm hoping we can
get along as a family too.
Well, what I'm saying...
...is that I never thought of you
as a bad person from the start.
As you can see,
you're about that age...
You're not that far
apart from Yuna, so...
Ouch...
Ow...
Man, how boring.
We should continue.
Here, Big Brother.
Huh?
What's wrong, Yuna?
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Fellatio
T-This is not going to happen.
W-Well, we have
to finish the game, right?
I...
What are you saying, Yuna?
Yuna?
Yuna!
I can...
...f-f-fulfill Big Brother!
Yuna...
Um, it's not that I was thinking
perverted thoughts about you...
It's just, well...
I wanted you to think those things.
It's nothing.
Yuna, don't...
I beg you.
Makoto...
It's hot.
Just look. Regardless
of your pretty words...
...you react when your penis is being
touched. You're just like Daisuke.
No, you can't, Yuna!
Some sticky juice is coming out.
Yuna!
Big Brother, am I doing it right?
Big Brother, what's wrong?
Why are you getting close to his thing?
Why don't you do it with Dad?
I'm not trying to.
My body's doing it on its own!
You're lying. You're just
trying to get in our way.
Big Brother,
make her stop! This is mine!
Even if you say that...
Forget it.
Daisuke... Daisuke...
Uh-oh...
It's the same as Daisuke.
So much came out of Daisuke's.
Mom, you're the worst.
Sis, you don't have
to force yourself to push it.
When the time comes, it'll move.
And you're going to make
me do such horrible things?
You don't have to say it like that.
Aren't I right?
You made Yuna do
such a horrible thing.
I'm sorry.
No...
No... No, I don't want to do this.
I don't want to do this with Makoto...
N-No...
I don't want this.
Daisuke, it's getting so hard.
Your big breasts
a-are making my thing...
I-I'm going to come!
Here, Big Brother.
It's your turn next.
What's wrong, Big Brother?
No, it's nothing.
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
Natsuki
Makoto
Yuna
Misaki
Learn from Elders
S-Sis...s
H-Hina?
little brother shouldn't
be trying to do bad things to Misa.
H-Hina, where did you come from?
I just showed up to save
Misa from your poisoned fangs.
Big Brother, who is she?
So you wanted to watch them
do it while biting your fingernails?
well, um, that's...
I pressed the random button...
...so I don't know if you've
been selected or not.
No!
No, please, stop...
S-Stop!
Makoto, stop it!
No... No...
This can't be... N-No!
I'm sorry, Natsuki.
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Stop... Please stop...
I'm sorry...
B-But it's so tight inside you...
...that I can't stop moving.
Well, if it were you, little sister,
it seems you like him...
...so it would have been fine.
This is something.
N-No, not the breasts!
B-By any chance,
are you enjoying it too?
I'm glad.
It's not that I wanted
to hurt you after all.
Of course it's not like that! Of course...
Mom, you really are the worst.
You had an affair with Dad
and gave birth to me just like that.
You get in my way and
don't even think about how I feel.
Just get lost!
Why are you saying this to me...
If only Daisuke weren't around!
If you pound me that much...
If you pound me with
that same dick as Daisuke's...
I'm going to come...
No no no... You can't come inside!
You've grabbed my dick.
I can't stop now!
Whoopsie.
Yuna...
Daisuke...
That's how it goes, I guess.
It was your first time,
so there's no helping it.
But it was the prime example
of a guy selfishly enjoying sex.
Makoto, I'd like
to ask you something...
No way.
Is Miss Kasukabe here?
Is something wrong?