Those Science Freaks
Kagaku  Na
Yatsu  ra
-
A
Okay, Haruki-san,
next we'll spend some time at a luxurious, fancy café.
I'm okay with that, but, Airi...
I thought you said you needed help with something.
Yes, and what's your point?
So far, all we've done today is go to the movies,
Do I have a good idea?
window shopped,
and had lunch.
What was it you needed me to do?
Uh? Well, actually...
Haru-kun! Airi-chan!
Ayana?!
Are you two going somewhere? Mind if I come along too?
Sorry, but I can't allow that.
We're in the middle of a hot, steamy date.
There's no room for you, Ayana-san.
So that's why we're just walking around?!
This is pretty surprising, though.
I thought you usually spent the weekends at home.
Yes. I was actually sleeping, but I got a phone call and woke up.
My sister said she's coming to see me.
You mean she's back?
I don't like her one bit.
Also,
I didn't have time to change, so I just put something on top of my pajamas.
But nothing on the bottom?!
Hey, Ayana!
This is your own fault for going outside in your pajamas!
Th-That voice...
Oh my, this is where you're most sensitive, right?
My nipple...
If you touch it...
I'm cu...
From my breasts... my nipples!
Geez, this is how you greet us after so long?
Show yourself, Touko-san!
Long time no see!
Do you ever wear normal clothes?
What brings you here this time?
I heard through the grapevine that you two established separate clubs. Is that true?
Mm-hmm!
I made a chemical science club
and Airi-chan made a mechanical science club.
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Chemical
Science
Haru-kun got them mixed up
and promised to join both of them!
Chemical
Science
Mechanical
Of course I got confused!
The Kuzes and Hizukis are rivals,
both seeking to master the abnormal sciences.
That means we need to find out who's better.
As Haruki-san has been familiar with our work since we were kids,
whichever club he chooses will prove to be superior,
and that's also how he'll choose who to marry!
Since when was that a part of this?!
But this is between me and Ayana-san. It has nothing to do with you, Touko-san.
But Ayana's not very assertive.
So I've...
decided to lend her a helping hand!
Look at this! If you join Ayana's club,
the two of us will throw in this special service!
Onee-cha—
U-Use of seduction is cheating!
Double boobies...
Don't fall for their temptations, Haruki-san!
Now I'm mad!
I just can't stand you at all!
Boobies...
Let's go, Haruki-san. Our date isn't over yet!
H-Hey!
A date?
Ayana, she has a huge lead over you!
Yeah, they should have let me come along.
God, you're hopeless.
I guess I'll have to turn things up a notch.
There's no need to rush things. Why don't we go and catch up...
Huh?
Onee-chan?
We should be safe here.
So we're still doing this date thing?
Of course! Got a problem with that?
Nah, I'm all right with it.
Then it's okay if we restart our date.
Why is that schedule so detailed?!
She's serious! She's going all the way!
Got that right! You won't be sleeping toni—
Airi?
Whoa!
Got me a teenager!
Touko-san?
W-What are you trying to do?
Take a hint, will you?
I'm continuing where we left off.
Come on, what do you think?
I know you adolescent boys love these.
Now give in and join Ayana's science club!
U-Um, no.
I'd rather the three of us have fun.
Hmm, you're a tough egg to crack.
I'll just think of something else.
Want a Bocky?
Are you even trying?
Don't you know anything besides maneating?
Oh well. Since I'm an abnormal scientist too, I'll just use this instead!
Touko-san brand drug, Submitacil!
Submitacil
That doesn't sound safe at all!
Just as the name suggests, whoever I inject this with will submit to my every command!
Now that drug even looks scary!
Rocket Punch!
Shoot, so she's awake?
Airi?
How low must you be to knock me out and try to make Haruki-san your slave?
As compensation, you'll hand over that drug!
I'll put it to more effective use!
No! She's totally going to use it on me!
I need to get out of this heat.
Oh, no you don't!
Airi Eye: Search Mode!
Got you!
Taste my Airi Buster!
Hey, watch it! Stop!
God!
Take this!
Darn it! I was careless!
I was going to use that on a certain guy.
Well, change of plans.
As punishment, you're to embarrass yourself in front of this boy.
Y-You're full of it...
What kind of drug is this?
It'll never bend me to your will...
Haruki-san, don't watch!
Uh, it's out of my hands.
Stop it!
I don't remember programming you to do this...
Serves you right!
Th-That was humiliating...
But I feel like I've made a new discovery.
Forget that discovery! Just stay who you are!
What should I make you do next?
There you are!
Ayana!
How could you just leave me behind like that, Onee-chan?
I'm sowwy!
Gotcha!
Payback time.
I'm going to give you a taste of your own medicine!
Wait, that's—
The airspace pseudo-hardener!
Shit, I can't move!
My boobs...
This is just perfect.
Now I'm going to get you back for everything you did to me!
Hey, timeout!
Hey, watch your hands!
Wow, you're holding up pretty well.
I've been through worse.
Very well.
In that case, it's time for Max Power...
Vibration Massage Mode!
No!
This... isn't fair!
Don't, Onee-chan, you're rubbing... against my nipples!
Oh no, I'm going to cum...
Just from that?
Just how sensitive are those boobs?
A-Ayana?
Onee-chan... I can't...
Airi, hurry...
Why do you think you're in a position to give me orders?
Hurry up and molest Ayana with those arms already!
Eek!
This is too much for me!
I can't hold it in!
You're so cute when you're being molested like this!
Onee-chan... Onee-chan... your tongue is...
Onee-chan, I feel a big one coming!
I just came, but this one's even bigger!
Ayana!
I... can't stand it either!
Phew! Kyouko-san's a very happy camper!
Onee-cha...
For now, let's call it a draw!
Let me go...
Later!
She was stringing me along the whole time.
I really don't like her at all.
So what about our date?
Our schedule's all messed up, so let's call it a night.
Not to mention she killed the mood.
Were we even in the mood to begin with?
Hey, did you hear?
There's this new school doctor, and she's got these gigantic tits!
Really?
Hey!
Infirmary
Glad to see you three again!
You!
Onee-chan?
What are you doing here, Touko-san?
Well, I'm the school doctor.
In order to lure a certain boy into Ayana's science club...
I wanted to get up close and personal.
Boobies...
I know you probably used your drugs to become our school doctor, but you're an invisible woman!
Why couldn't you just sneak in and out of the building?
Oh, now that you mention it...
I guess you're right.
There was
no reason
There was no reason?!
This sucks. What am I supposed to do with this position?
You already want to quit?
Onee-chan,
since you're already here, why don't you stay for a while?
Ayana?
I think school doctor is an important job where you get to listen to kids' problems.
After the incident that turned me into this, when I was all stressed out...
I was able to pick myself up thanks to Haru-kun and Airi-chan.
That's what I want you to do, Onee-chan.
Ayana...
Okay, you've got it.
Touko-san will go for it!
Touko-san's Clinic
Solve your problems through drugs!
Touko-san's Personal Advice Office is now open for business!
What are you trying to do?
I'm only helping out kids with their problems.
...with drugs.
That's too much of a shortcut!
And it sounds totally dangerous!
This is stupid. Who'd ever fall for something so suspicious?
There's a ton of them!
Teenagers do have a lot of problems!
All right!
Leave it all to...
Dr. Touko!
Thank you very much!
She's actually providing a good service.
She certainly is my rival's sister.
I can't say much about her personality, but she's an impressive chemist.
Maybe I should sign up, too.
I'd like to get buff without all the work.
I just remembered something. Excuse me.
Uh, sure.
Looks like my business is a success.
Okay, what may I help you with—
You're not fooling anyone, Airi.
No, the transformation of Kuse Airi is perfect...
No! You made me slip up already!
So, what's your problem?
C-Can you make my breasts bigger?
That's a pretty lame problem for someone who brags about her scientific prowess.
It's a normal problem!
Airi, the measure of a girl's worth is not in her breasts.
Haruki-san...
Hey!
The way you constantly drool over Ayana-san's giant boobs is why I'm worried to begin with!
I'm sorry!
I love boobs! I'm a total breast man!
That's too bad.
I've never been dissatisfied with my bust, so I don't know if I even made such a drug...
Are you looking for a fight?!
Oh, wait a second.
I think I did make something...
Touko-san brand breast enhancement drug for girls!
Hey.
Is it working?
I'm not feeling anything...
Airi!
My breasts... my whole body feels hot. I can't move!
Onee-chan, was that the right drug?
Huh?
That's strange.
Sorry. This was for making boobs more sensitive, not for enlarging them.
What did you say?!
Oh well, might as well make the most of it while we're here!
What are you... doing?
I'm disgracing you in front of Haru-kun so that he thinks less of you!
That's low, Touko-san!
This is bad... Stop, or I'll...
cum!
Airi is lactating! Is that a side effect?
It only lasts for a little while. She'll be back to normal soon.
That was horrible.
I can move.
All right, let's liven things up with more of that dru—
No you don't!
Looks like you've turned the tables on me.
There's a lot more where that came from.
You'll be feeling 10 times my pain!
No, stop you two!
Looks like I should exit stage right.
Give it up!
Shoot! The drug hasn't completely worn off yet!
I have to concentrate...
There!
What?
A-A-Ayana-san?
She drank it!
She's the last person who should drink that stuff, but she drank the whole thing!
I'm being aroused... just by the clothes on my breasts!
Are you kidding?
What are we supposed to do?
Why not take off the clothes if they're a problem?
Me?
You didn't have to take off her skirt!
I like the way he thinks.
So, did that help any?
No...
Now it feels like the air itself is licking my nipples.
Ain't there nuffin' we can do?
Touko-san, isn't there an antidote?
Well, I was planning to throw out that drug.
I don't even have the ingredients for an antidote!
This is a total disaster!
It appears the drug is excreted out along with the breast milk, so she'll have to be milked dry.
Wait...
There may be ingredients for an antidote in my clubroom.
So I guess you make some drugs too, Ayana.
She says the ingredients are in a safe in the back...
Ayana's creatures?
I get it.
They're worried because Ayana looks sick.
But we can't get through now.
Ayana-san, tell them to move.
Guys, let us pass.
I have to take some medicine.
Or else, you'll have to squeeze my breasts... and make me squirt a lot!
I know what you're saying, but that came out wrong!
I'm not sure,
but she looks bad.
She says we have
to give her medicine
or squeeze her
breasts.
We animals
hate medicine.
Then let's squeeze them!!
Squeeze them and make our master better!
No! That's not what I meant...
They've got the wrong idea entirely!
Ayana! Talk some sense into them!
Stop! If you stroke my boobs too much...
Oh my god!
I can't... stop the milk!
This far surpasses anything I've seen.
Oh man, I want in on that!
What are you saying, you two?
This woman also looks sick!
We need to squeeze her breasts!
Excuse me.
Such unmanageable breasts. Très bien! So indecent!
Don't!
Let's squeeze her!
M-Me too?
In that case...
Don't come near me, you creatures!
Haruki-san will suck out my milk!
Hey, don't speak for me!
I see stuff oozing out from other places.
And a lot of it too.
That can't be good.
We should squeeze it all out.
Don't... rub me there...
Let me go!
I'm... I'm cumming!
That's three times!
This may be too much even for me!
You're hard!
Still, it's also strangely soft!
I think I might like this!
Y-You think so?
Even small breasts have their charms...
Ayana... your pets are very direct. They might even be...
they might have been molesting us all this time!
I'm cumming!
No!
Infirmary
Gosh, that was horrible!
Taking advice from a rival was a terrible idea!
Sorry! I'll make a better drug next time.
No thank you!
I'll just sway Haruki-san with my own sexiness.
Ah, youth.
Good luck, Airi-chan!
Same goes for you!
Is that right?
I have a feeling she'll be needing Airi's aggressiveness.
Don't you get it, Ayana-san? It's still not over yet!