Presented by Kira-H
House of Five Lusts
Part 1
Jounouchi Mansion
Miss Tsubame, I seem to recall cleaning
this room a mere three days ago.
I don't remember that...
Day and night don't mean much with my
lifestyle. I'm not even sure of today's date.
I can't help...
You can help it.
Oh, Shun. Don't be so scary.
Let's change the subject,
if you know what I mean.
My my, you really are incorrigible.
I could say the same about you.
Somehow it never takes long
for it to get good when it's with you.
It's like I'm a little virgin.
W-Wow...
You're so hard-core on my pussy...
Oh no... Your hand's making me...
I c-can't keep from peeing!
N-No, it's coming... Here it comes...
Here it comes! Here it comes!
You always get
right in up to my uterus.
Just having it in...
No!
Not yet... When you pull out,
the ridge of the head catches...
It's pushing aside my flesh...
I can't pull out or push in.
Just what should I do then?
N-No, I mean I want you to do both.
I... I just want you to wait a little.
After all, it's so incredible that it'd
be a waste if you didn't take your...
Yes, but I don't have
that much patience.
You're so m-mean, Shun.
Thrusting into me so powerfully...
I-If you keep that up...
...we won't be able to talk about love.
Love? What are you talking about?
You're overreacting.
I'm not really after
that either, you know.
I just... I just wanted to see
how you'd react if I said that.
Then shall we get back
to our lust-only sex?
That's what seems to suit us.
If lust is more important than humanity,
isn't doggy style more appropriate?
Y-You might be right...
It's so primitive.
Dogs don't speak using human words!
You don't need to be so strict...
Ow! No...
Stop...
I-I'm g-going to come...
W-Why'd you stop, Shun?
Getting hit makes you pee,
Miss Tsubame? You really are like a dog.
You're such a scoundrel, Shun. I can't
believe how much control you had.
You're liable to discover
a whole new way to orgasm.
I still haven't orgasmed however.
N-No... This time I mean it...
I just came... I'm too sensitive...
No!
Round two!
There's still a lot of yours inside me.
It feels like it'll leak out...
You act cool, but every now and then
I catch a glimpse of your wicked side.
It's not hard to see there's more
to you than meets the eye.
What could you be after?
What do you think?
Let's see...
The Jounouchi family itself?
Bingo.
Sure, why not? You can have it.
But you're not
the family head, are you?
Then will you try
to conquer my sister Shizuru?
You could take her late
husband's place. I'll help you.
Well, well.
What are you after?
I'm not after anything.
I'm just crazy about you.
My work is coming along great thanks
to all the pleasure you bring me.
Helping you is
the best way I can thank you.
That, and I think I can derive
inspiration from your roguish story.
That's the most important thing to me.
You'd ensnare your sister
for the sake of your livelihood?
You're a bad person.
You're going to get tripped up
if you get too carried away, Shun.
Does that mean you'll
demonstrate your loyalty...
...by informing the Jounouchis of
the danger of Shun Daichi, Tomoe?
Don't be stupid. I meant in general.
Just because those five sisters
are this family's core...
...you think things will work out
so long as you control them all?
Wow, you're concerned.
If you become number one, that'll
improve the terms of our employment.
That's why.
Well now, is that really the case?
No, I really need you to work hard.
Yes, very hard.
Good morning, Miss Rei.
Good morning.
That Night...
Miss Shizuru?
Please deep throat me if you would.
Well done, Miss Shizuru.
I'm touched that you're putting
so much enthusiasm into this.
Is this the first cock you've sucked
since your husband passed away?
Don't talk about him.
You were faithful to him, weren't you?
I think that's quite sweet of you.
But you still had to find a way
to satisfy your body's aching needs.
Dear...
I thought someone was watching.
Yes, and it left quite
the indecent impression.
So you felt my eyes upon you?
No wonder you were so slutty.
Now please, move on to the next step.
That's nice.
I fear I'm about to come!
Shun, that's great...
Now that you're inside me, it's again...
You've been loosening yourself up every
day. No wonder it was so easy to get in.
I wasn't loosening anything up...
The... The tip of your
penis is in so deep!
Yes, and I can feel you tensing up.
No, not there!
That's my cervix...
No! No!
Don't rub against it with your big tip...
I-I've never... felt this way...
I see your husband
wasn't very adventurous.
Don't talk about him!
I really did love him!
Yet despite those feelings,
you weren't satisfied!
D-Don't! Don't!
Don't go after my cervix
so much! I'm not used to it!
O-Ow...
O-Ouch...
So you say...
Stop that, Shun... It hurts...
You're so adorable, Shizuru.
But I won't be gentle with you.
This is for your own good after all.
No, Shun! Stop!
I-It hurts!
But doesn't that pain please you?
That isn't true...
Isn't it? Not that I plan
on stopping, either way.
Shun?
You're in need of this kind of thing.
No, I'm not...
After all, if it's not like this,
you'll feel like you're betraying him...
...and you won't be able to come.
W-Wow...
Do it... Blow my mind
with your thick dick...
You're messing up my pussy...
I'm g-going to come...
I feel so hot inside!
Here comes that nasty sticky stuff!
I'm coming! Coming, coming, coming!
Shun...
Yes?
Thanks.
It's not like I'm very young.
That's quite all right.
On Another Night...
The water is cooling
down. I'll brew more.
No! I'll do it.
Did you intend for this tea
to be specifically for me?
I-I had Tomoe teach me
how to make some nice tea.
I really want you to try some.
That's why I asked you here.
Is that so.
If you went to that much
effort, then by all means.
H-Here.
Thank you very much.
So... how is it?
Is it good? I hope so.
Don't worry. It was good.
Oh, you're so mean!
Sorry, I guess I shouldn't
have joked around.
It's okay. I said too much myself.
N-No...
S-Shun...
Stop it...
Don't...
No! I don't want this.
You want me to stop?
But you're quite fascinated
by this kind of thing, Miss Hina.
T-That's not true.
Yes, it is.
Otherwise you wouldn't have
watched what I did with Miss Shizuru.
You knew I was there?
Yes, which is why
I'm going to do it with you too.
I-It's big...
It's okay. Take your
time getting used to it.
O-Okay.
Please begin by grasping it.
It's hot!
That's all right. Please continue.
O-Okay.
Wow, it's twitching.
Yes, that's because
your hands feel good.
Now move your hands up and down.
All right.
You're squeezing a little
too tightly. Try to settle into a rhythm.
Okay, understood.
There you go. That feels good.
Please stop a moment.
Did I do something wrong?
No, it's nothing like that.
I want you to try putting it in your mouth.
M-My mouth?
Really?
It looks like we're done.
W-Why is that?
You can't do what I ask,
can you? So we're done.
N-No...
U-Um, I just need
to ask you one favor.
Which is?
I-I want you to be mine and only mine!
Sure, Miss Hina. If you insist.
Don't be stupid.
Then here I come.
All right.
Shun, it's getting bigger...
Miss Hina, I'm about to come!
That was all of it.
Please swallow it, Miss Hina.
Thank you for swallowing it.
Now it's my turn.
N-No...
It looks like servicing me
got you excited, Miss Hina.
N-No, it didn't...
Oh no?
That's odd.
I guess I need to take a closer look.
No...
S-Stop! I'm too embarrassed!
I suspected this was the case.
No!
Jeez...
Who does he think he is?
Hina belongs to me.
Doesn't he know that?
S-Shun... It's too much...
I-If you keep going,
I-I'm going to burst...
H-Hina, you're so...
Watching you like that
makes my hand move faster...
N-No...
I'm going to... I'm going to...
I-I'm going to pee!
I can't stop it!
Hina just came.
I'm... I'm going to come too...
I'll come together with you...
You're drinking my pee, Shun.
You really belong to me
and me alone, don't you?
Tsugumi, I didn't let you
set up this surveillance system...
...so you could spy on Hina.
Do you understand?
Well, why are we letting
that guy do as he pleases with her?
He'd be in trouble if I hooked it
up to our security system...
You need to understand
the situation. Hina wanted this.
It's not like she belongs to you.
Or shall I inform Hina
that you spy on her this way?
All right!
Listen to me.
This is something we need.
Bear that in mind.
Are they nearly in
the palm of your hand now?
You're not being nice. Don't tell me you're
jealous because I'm neglecting you?
You must be joking. Why would I be?
Maybe you think all you
have to do is topple Shizuru...
...but doesn't that outbuilding seem
like it's the core of this household?
Outbuilding? Why?
What the hell's in there?
To Be Continued