Kitsune
Papillon Rose
Lingerie Senshi
Original Project by
WS
re-edited and integrated by Kitsune
Yoru no tokai Sekai wa nemuri
City in the night The world is sleeping
Zawameki mo sasayaki mo
Rustrle and whisper
Uso ga nurikaeru
Repaint the lies
ILLUMINATION Meikyuu no hate
Illumination At he end of the maze
Maiorita yami no chou
Flies down upon the butterfly of darkness
Hane wo ima tojiru
It now closes its wings
Tada anata wo motomeru no wa
I just want you
IKENAI koto desu ka?
Is that so bad?
Zutto karada no
In my body
Oku de moeteru ENERGY
the energy keeps burning forever
Uchibiru toikisae
Even when I sigh
Anata ni wa todokanai no
It doesn't reach you
Mune tsumaru Ai no yukue
My heart Can't find its love
Kagi wo nigitteru
I will find the key
Anata shidai na no dakara
To get to you soon
Tsubomi's Dream Blossoms in the Night
Lingerie Club
Papillon
Here we go, Sensei.
Well, this is nice.
Alcohol tastes a lot better
when it's from a pretty girl.
By the way, today...
where is that girl?
That girl..?
Yeah, what was her name again?
Um... the one that's always cheerful.
The girl that goes "Kyaa!".
Oh, You mean Tsubomi-chan?
Let's see... Tsubomi-chan is..
Oh Sensei, welcome.
Are you looking for Tsubomi-chan?
Damn right!
Call Tsubomi-chan over here, Master!
Right away!
Tsubomi-chan!
Sensei is looking for you!
Coming!!
Sensei, welcome!
This sensation...
Take this, take, take...
this is heavenly!
Tsubomi is here!
Take...
Take, take...
This is like a paradise!
What's this?
What?
Tsu... Tsubomi-chan!!
What's with the hair?
Where'd come from
this bothersome hair?
Bothersome hair?
Oh...
A wig?
No way...
It's a wig. A wig!
Tsubomi-chan!
Put it back!
But it's a wig! A wig!
Tsubomi-chan?!
What do you think you were doing?
Sensei was mad!
That's not what I intended to do.
His wig just popped off.
At any rate, your attitude is bad!
On top of that, you
were late again today!
That kind of girl...
will be punished!
In the name of the moon!
Master... Forgive her for the incident.
Tsubomi-chan didn't do it on purpose.
As expected, Anne-chan!
My soulmate!
Anyway!
You're paying for this
out of your salary!
Are you sure you want to do that?
I'll tell your wife...
about your adultery whit Anne-chan.
Oh my...
That's fine whit me.
You can tell her.
It's all about the body,
isn't it, Master?
Our hearts don't connect.
A man and woman's love game.
Right...
Master?
Anne-chan... That's not true.
Do you think I can feel your licking?
You worms!
Step back!
Is there any warriors who
can take me to my climax?!
How annoying!
Then, I, Regina Apis, shall have
all the power of male pleasure.
Well? Who shall take
this ecstasy-filled duty?
To go and create mayhem!
For this mission,
leave it to Sister Beene.
Oh, go ahead,
let's see Beene-chan do it.
I doubt this small fry can do the job.
What'd you say?
For an indecisive hag who can't
do anything, you'd better shut up!
That's mean!
Petite-La-chan is still a
young girl's green flower.
Then this job is not for
a mackerel like you.
What's that, you lesbo pig?!
Silence!
Bitch, don't mess whit me!
Perverted hag!
Stop this meaningless fight!
Sister Beene. This time I'll
trust the mission to you.
Yes, Ma'am.
I will collect fresh and
superior rogue energy.
All desire and mayhem
belong to our Dynasty.
Kabuki Butterfly Street
I'm late, I'm late!
That cruel female teacher
wasted my youth and
beauty whit her detention!
That's unforgivable!
Hey, watch where you're going!
What a cool guy!
I can see them.
Huh?
Oh nooo!
Can you walk?
I can't...
Where should we...
take a rest?
Welcome!
Massage Parlor
Pai Panic
Do you want to go in, sir?
Yakitori
The Elegant Bird
It's cheap and there are beautiful girls
Sausages
The Gluttony
Kabuki District Branch
Come on, over here! Let's go!
Restaurant MORITA
This strong smell...
There is no mistake.
She must be close.
Yeeeees!
Oh... yeah!
Ugh... Oh yes!!!
Yes!!! Oh yeah!!!
Oh yeah!!!
Oh...
Oh yes!!!
Th-That was amazing!
I... scored!
I scored!
I scoooored!
The seed has been planted inside you.
A beautiful flower will bloom.
Tsubomi...
A dream..?
Huh, what's wrong whit me?
I see. That was such a
fantastic sex whit Hikaru...
Was that only on my mind?
Kyaa! No way!
I'm thinking too much.
Aniway, Hikaru?
Could it be... A sex-and-run?
Dammit! I should've know!
Thank you very much.
Why do I...
have to pay
for the motel fee?
Oh no!!
What's with this kitty?
Where are you from?
Oh, I just smelled a very
familiar odor in there.
Whoever has that odor is
destined to be an hero.
Aaaa! Demon cat!
Demon cat?
How rude!
My name is Rahma.
And I've finally found you!
Crystal of love, flower gem soldier.
What the hell are you talking about?
Crystal of love? Soldier?
For your information...
I scored!
Is this vulgar girl really
a Papillon Soldier?
What's that?
I'm not a dog. I don't greet
people by sniffing them!
I'm not mistaken, aren't it?
Help me!
Huh?
What was that?
That was the owner's voice.
As I expected from a Papillon Soldier...
Yes... your male energy.
This Sister Beene-sama is so wicked.
I will suck you until
you're dry to the bones.
Hel-Help me!
Feast time!
Stop!
No, don't stop!
That's amazing!
I wanna join in too!
You idiot. What do you
mean you wanna join in?
Fine, fine, you idiot cat.
I was joking. Joking...
You can make jokes
at a time like this?
Well, Tsubomi-chan?
Transform to Papillon Rose!
Papillon Rose?
When are you gonna stop you prank?
Never mind that!
"Rose Orgasm Power. Erection"!
Shout out those words.
Roger! Got it!
Honey Fla...
That's not it, Tsubomi-chan!
Stop being such a low class!
No.! Pervert!
This is no time for jokes!
Fine, fine!
I got it!
I guess it's my bad luck
to fall into your prank.
Well then.
After much consideration...
I'll do it!
Rose Orgasm Power...
Erection!
Oh, what a joy!
If not for the job...
Why don't I get to do
this to a pretty girl?
Being middle-class
management is heart-breaking!
Stop right there!
You think this town is
an oasis in a desert?
You, Dinasty minion!
Who are you?!
I can't forgive anyone who disturbs the pure, righteous and law-abiding citizens.
Who is this exhibitionist?
Exhibitionist?
That's rude!
You're not that different from me!
Dressed in a scantily-clad lingerie...
the fluttering crimson
butterfly in the night!
Papillon Rose!
Papillon Rose, you say?
Tonight I will give you...
all you can drink!
Defying our Dynasty?
Is she brainless or something?
You're quite charming from this angle.
W-What are you doing?!
Thanks you!
But you're a bad one.
Shall I train you to be obedient?
Commence the attack!
What's wrong, Rose?!
Running away won't get anything done!
Damn you...
What do you expect me to do
against that many opponents?!
I'm just a girl passing by!
Your wit...
Use your wit!
Why you...
How dare you make fun of me!
There's no other choice.
Papillon Rose,
use the Pinky Vibrator!
Pinky Vibrator?
Inside your crotch there's a flower gem!
That's your weapon!
Flower gem?
I'm so hot!
My crotch is exploding!
That vibrator will get
bigger as it feels your rage.
Oh my, I feel stimulated now.
How dare you do that
to my cute kittens!
I'll prove that I'm not small fry.
Perhaps a little S&M treatment
is too much for you?
Nooo!
A cute girl should act like a good girl.
Well then!
Where should I start feasting?
I failed again...
Well, well, let's start
from your cute butt.
Good shot!
Th-This is..?
What... That can't be!
You are a lady.
You should be ashamed of
your bad taste in fashion.
Who are you?
I'm the symbol of love in the night.
A nameless beauty.
You are not better than a regular prostitute!
It's not good to be a bawdy woman.
Look at this body...
It's enough to enslave any men.
I am a gentleman and
I know what to expect.
Stop it!
How dare a guy like you...
Your gasp and voice...
to my ears are like my favorite music.
You surely are an exquisite lady.
Papillon Rose, now!
Your ultimate attack!
Use your Rose Pinkish Viagra!
Got it!
Rose...
Pinkish...
Viagra!!
I'm comiiiiing!!!
Well done, Tsubomi-chan!
I mean, Papillon Rose!
Is this Papillon Rose's power?
That's right.
You are the Papillon Soldier
I've searched for.
Our protector from Dynasty's minions.
Nope!
I don't wanna get mixed up
with those crazy people!
Besides, like hell I'm
gonna be your servant!
By the way, where's the guy with the mask?
Wait!
At least...
At least give me your name.
A nameless beauty...
I assure you we will meet again.
You can call me Dandelion.
Thank you for helping me a while ago!
Dande... lion-sama!
Papillon Rose?
That troublesome.!
Anyone who defies the Dynasty...
will be tortured to death!
For this mission, leave
it all to Sister Petite-La!
Well, Sister Petite-La?
Shall we show what you can
do with you IQ of 300?
Hey hey!
Go easy on me today.
I ran out of energy.
I thought you're unbeatable
at having the most sessions in one night.
Cool it.
There are three more Papillon Soldiers.
We must gather them quickly.
It won't be complete whitout them togheter.
Your seed is persistent.
For the sake of that person...
Yes...
Please close your eyes.
Sashi noberareta
I reached out
Te wo nigiri kaeshita shunkan ni
To return to the moment you hold my hands
Just like a dream
Just like a dream...
Minareta senaka ga
A familiar body
Kieteshimau youna kigashite
Disappears along with the spirit
I still believe
Tomaru kotonaku
Even though it's a dead end
Subete wo motometeshimau no ni
I will search everywhere
Anata wa kawaru koto naku
Even though you transform
Oreta tsubasa dokomademo
With broken wings.
tsutsumikondekureru
I shall follow you
Let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel whenever
Sono nukumori ga
I don't want
kieteshimawanai you ni
the warmth to vanish
Let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel forever.
and make me feel forever
Mou ichido dake dakishimeteite
Please embrace me one more time
Notes:
Tsubomi: [蕾] Flower bud
Papillon: [ パピヨン] Butterfly (Fr.)
Rose: [口ーゼ] Rose (Fr.) ... do you expect something else?
Itteyoshi: [いってよし] This is a gamers' term for making a kill (score).
According to the official website:
Dandelion doesn't have a transformation scene, because he just cosplays.