Kitsune
Papillon Rose
Lingerie Senshi
Original Project by
Fans For Fans
re-edited and integrated by Kitsune
Translation: AKofTroy
Yoru no tokai sekai wa nemuri
When the city world falls asleep
zawameki mo sasayaki mo
all the murmurs and whispers
This script has been Pr0nalized and contains inaccuracies for the sake of humor in English. -Shin Newtype
uso ga nurikaeru
turn to lies.
Irumineishon meikyuu no hate
Illumination, the ends of the maze
Maiorita yami no chou
The butterfly of darkness descends
hane wo ima tojiru
and now closes its wings.
Tada anata wo motomeru no wa
Is it just wrong to
ikenai koto desu ka
seek you out?
Zutto karada no
The burning energy
oku de moeteru enajii
from the depths of my body
Uchibiru toiki sae
Even my lips
anata ni wa todokanai no
can't reach you.
Mune tsumaru ai no yukue
This love in my heart
kagi wo nigitteru
where it goes is up to you
anata shidai na no dakara
since you have the key.
Someone has risen up to rule the
ecstasy of those in the sex industry.
The leader of D-Nasty, Regina Apis.
To protect the peace of the sexual paradise, one gutsy woman stands tall.
Her name is...
Papillon Rose
Tsubomi's Dream Opens At Night
Lingerie Pub
Papillon
Open wide, Sensei.
Oh, thanks.
Liquor tastes so much better
when a sexy girl pours it for you.
By the way...
where's that girl today?
That girl..?
Oh, what was her name?
You know, the always energetic one.
That one.
Oh, Tsubomi-chan?
Umm, where is Tsubomi-chan?
Oh, welcome, Sensei.
You're asking for Tsubomi-chan?
I sure am.
Call Tsubomi-chan, Master.
Yes, sir!
Tsubomi-chan!
Sensei is asking for you!
Yes, sir!!
Sensei, welcome!
This...
Take, take, take...
feels so good!
Tsubomi is here!
Take...
Take, take...
This is truly heaven.
What's this?
What?
T-Tsubomi-chan!!
What's that hair?
Where's this hair from?
I wonder WHAIR?
You wonder whair?
Oh...
A wig?
Ewww!
A wig, a wig!
Tsubomi-chan!
Tsubomi-chan?!
What were you doing?
Sensei was pissed off!
What do you want me to do about it?
The wig came off on its own.
Anyway, you have a bad attitude!
You were late again today!
Girls like that...
In the name of the moon...
I'll punish them!
Master, give her a break.
Tsubomi-chan didn't do it on purpose.
Thank you, Anne-chan!
What a great friend!
Anyway...
I'm withholding your pay for today!
You sure you should say that?
I'll tell your wife that...
you're cheating with Anne-chan.
Oh...
Go ahead, tell...
With the Master I just have
a physical relationship.
My heart has been broken...
because of the game of love played between men and women.
Isn't that right...
...Master?
Anne-chan... Don't say that.
You think I feel anything
from such poor work?!
You worthless insects!
Begone!
Is there no one who can
give me true pleasure?!
How frustrating!
If this is the case, then I, Regina Apis,
shall take all the pleasure of the world!
Now, in order to rule all
the ecstasy of the world...
go forth and collect sexual energy!
Then let I, Sister Bien,
have that honor.
Go ahead, Bien-chan, hop to it.
Seems so simple anyone
could do it anyway.
What'd you say, you stupid old bitch?!
That's so mean!
I'm just a young, innocent girl.
Aren't you twice as old I as am?
What'd you say, you fat pig?!
Shut up!
Don't touch me!
You perverted old hag!
No cat fights!
Sister Bien, I'll let you
handle this mission.
Yes, my Queen.
I shall collect some
good perverted energy.
All ecstasy shall belong
to our great D-Nasty.
Sing Dance Technique Butterfly Street
I'm late, I'm late!
That damn female teacher
punishing me because she's
jealous of my youth and beauty!
I won't forgive her!
Hey, watch where you're going!
What a hot guy!
I can see you.
Huh?
Oh no!!
Can you walk?
I don't think so.
Shall we...
rest somewhere?
Message Parlor
Pai Panic
Yakitori
The Elegant Bird
Eat Too Much
BBQ
Branch Kabuki District
Restaurant MORITA
This powerful smell...
No mistake about it, she's nearby.
Yeeeees!
Oh... yeah..!
Oh, yes, yes!!!
Oh yes!!!
Oh, yes!!!
Oh... Yes!!
A-Amazing!!
I'm cuming!
I'm cummmmming!!
I've planted a seed into you...
to create a beautiful flower.
Tsubomi...
A dream?
Huh, what am I doing?
Oh yeah, I had so much sex...
I passed out.
Oh no!
I'm laughing just thinking about it.
Hikaru?
No way, he came and went?
Goddammit!
What a prick!
Thank you for coming.
Why did I have to pay
for the entire hotel room?
Oh no!!
Damn cat...
What do you want in there?!
Oh, this feint, sweet fragrance hidden under all the stench.
And those legs that spread so wide...
MONSTER PUSSY!!
"Monster Pussy"? How rude!
My name is Raama.
I've finally found you, the soldier who
owns the bud that is the symbol of love.
What the hell are you talking about?
"Soldier"? "Symbol of love"?
Are you insane?
Get out of here!
Is this slutty girl really
a Papillon Soldier?
What the hell?!
I'm not mistaken, aren't it?
I haven't had these cleaned yet,
and they're soiled with my love juices!
Help me!
Huh?
What's this old man's voice I hear?
As I expected of a Papillon Soldier...
Now, give me your energy.
I, Sister Bien-sama...
will suck you down to the last drop.
Pl-Please spare me!
Bottoms up!!
Stop!
No, don't stop!
Wow, that's amazing!
I should try it with them, too!
Idiot, what are you talking about?!
I know, you stupid pussy.
I was just kidding. Kidding...
It didn't sound like a joke.
Now, Tsubomi-chan...
transform into Papillon Rose.
Papillon Rose?
What the hell have you been smoking?
Anyway!
"Rose Orgasm Power Erection"
Scream out it!
Roger, sure.
Honey Fl...
Wrong, Tsubomi-chan!
How can you fly around
like that anyway?!
No, pervert!
This is no time to jerk off.
Fine, fine...
I get it.
We'd get caught for
copyright infringement.
Now that I'm feeling better, here I go!
Rose Orgasm Power Erection!
Oh, what a joy!
This may be my job,
but I don't have to like it.
I wish I could be licking
a hot girl's lil' thingie.
Life sucks.
Stop right there!
To protect men who find
an oasis in their desert...
To prevent D-Nasty from
destroying the sex industry...
Who are you?!
I won't forgive those that
disrupt my sexual paradise!
Who's this slut?!
"Slut?''
How dare you!
Like you're any different!
The lingerie wearing
crimson butterfly...
of the night.
Papillon Rose!
Papillon Rose?
Tonight I'll...
Suck you dry.
To defy us, D-Nasty. What a fool.
Now that I look closely,
you're a pretty charming girl.
W-What are you doing?!
Thanks for the treat.
But bad girls
need to be punished
and turned into slaves.
Do it!
What are you doing, Rose?!
You can't just run around!
Look here, you...
How can I fight those freaks?
I'm just a weak girl.
Your weapon...
Use your weapon!
Look here, you...
This is torture!
There's no choice, Papillon Rose, use your Pinky Vibrator!
Pinky Vibrator?
The bud inside of you,
that's your weapon.
Weapon?
I'm so hot!
I feel like I'm about to explode!
This vibrator gets bigger and
harder the more pleasure it feels.
Oh my, this is turning me on.
note: that's an in-joke in the club of tranlator.
How dare you hurt
my cute lil' kitt0ns!!
I won't go down like them.
How about a little S&M on the house?
note: another in-joke.
Oh nos!!
You have to be a good girl.
Now, where shall
I eat you out first?
This time I'm really finished...
My, what a cute ass.
Salty...
I-Isn't this?
N-No way!
I don't want to see a cute girl
being hit with a whip.
Who are you?
Names are not needed
for one night of love.
Mystery is what is beautiful.
You look like you need some attention.
How about I turn you
into a real woman?
Look at this body ravished by only women...
lacking a real man's talents.
I'll drive in deep
what a real man can do.
Stop!
I hate men, I hate men!
Just hearing your
voice makes me hard.
It's music to my ears.
You are a true woman.
Papillon Rose, now!
Hit her with your finishing move,
Rose Pinkish Viagra!
Okay!
Rose...
Pinkish...
Viagra!!
I'm cumming!!!
Good job, Tsubomi-chan.
No, rather, Papillon Rose!
This is the power of Papillon Rose?
That's right.
You are the Papillon Soldier
I have been searching for.
You must protect the sex
industry from D-Nasty.
No way!
I don't want to have to
fight against those freaks.
And I don't want to be your lieutenant.
By the way, where'd that hot guy go?
Wait!
At least...
At least tell me your name.
Mystery is beautiful...
But if I have to name myself...
you can call me Dandy Lion.
Thank you for saving me!
Dandy Lion-sama?
Papillon Rose?!
Impudent wench!
How dare she defy the great D-Nasty!
I'll destroy them all!
Please give me,
Sister P'tit-la, that honor.
In that case, Sister P'tit-la...
show me the power of
your 1,300 point IQ.
Hey hey!
Give me a break today.
I'm going to run out.
That's not something I'd expect
from a guy who can satisfy
twenty women a night.
Don't say that.
There's three more Papillon Soldiers.
We must find them as soon as possible.
It seems like they are already mobilizing.
We need your seed...
for all of her.
Yes...
Please close your eyes.
Sashi noberareta
I was given a helping hand
te wo nigiri kaeshita shunkan ni
the moment I took your hand in mine.
Just like a dream
Minareta senaka ga
I feel like the back of me you saw
kiete shimau you na kigashite
is going to disappear.
I still believe
Tomaru koto naku
I will not stop.
Subete wo motomete shimau no ni
I will still seek everything.
Anata wa kawaru koto naku
You will not change.
Oreta tsubasa doko made mo
You will always
tsutsumikonde kureru
hold my broken wings.
Let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel whenever
sono nukumori ga
so that that warmth
kiete shimawanai you ni
will not go away.
Let me in, wanna kiss
and make me feel forever.
Mou ichido dake dakishimeteite
Hold me just one more time.