Pero Pero
Candy
狐 Kitsune
Caution
Asunaro Private School
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Hey Mom, I will walk with Momoe.
Don't go!
Instead of a walk
better think about how to get into a good school
is a good institution and a good company.
Again began.
Nothing again.
Listen to me
if you will be lazy when you grow up, you will become like your dad.
Then in Kyushu, then in Hokkaido, wears it all the time.
So start your studies. Be diligent, Takeshi.
Sì...
It's your fault, dear.
As soon as Takeshi was born, you immediately left for Hokkaido.
And since then everything is on the road.
Then Tohoku, then Shikoku, then Kyushu.
And everywhere alone.
So you have no time left for raising a child.
I really...
feel lonely.
Do me a favor ...
woman's friend.
No! Need to learn!
Learn!
Le... arn...
No! Do not!
Hello!
This is from the laundry.
Will there be an order today?
Oh!
This voice. Ken-chan from the laundry.
Allora..?
Coming!
Wait a moment.
Takeshi! Takeshi!
Crap!
Oh, you're still studying?
It is harmful to do so much.
From time to time you have to go for a walk.
Eh?
Now you'll be busy preparing for exams all the time, will not you?
And now you have the opportunity to walk.
But, mom, you have just ...
Look!
Momoe also wants to go.
Quickly, go out.
Okay.
Well, here we are at the park.
In the afternoon
there is no place to go.
After all...
There is no such hidden place.
What's the matter?
What happened?
What?
Go here?
But, what's the matter?
Women             Man
Cool!
That's awesome!
No! Someone is watching!
Really?
It's true! Here.
No!
I'm all wet!
Momoe, it's your fault.
It would have be better
if you had warned me.
Eh? Now what?
You saw something at the top.
What is it?
Momoe, nice job!
Already developed?
Next is..?
Home.
What? Enough.
What a beauty!
No!
Oh no!
What a beauty.
However...
such a cutie...
it would be nice...
What's the matter, Momoe?
So...
Your lips...
Ken-Chan, are you already tired?
Now open your legs, madam.
My business... the laundry...
More.
Oh, yes!
Yes?
Ikuyo, it's me, Tatsuzo.
Oh, dear.
Takeshi diligently engaged?
Ah... Yes...
Good.
Everything is alright?
The mood for studying at Takeshi... is very good.
Good.
Are you calm now?
Bene.
I'm working with him now... with enthusiasm.
Oh, yes.
Whit this attitude...
I'll also work with enthusiasm.
Good mood... good... good.
Sì, good mood.
Then, I will finish soon.
Well, try there.
I will try too!
Yes dear, well...
Well, let's go!
Good!
This is not possible.
Ah, it's no good...
Our family is falling apart.
But Mom was so beautiful.
I also want to do it.
If desire could somehow help...
Tomokatsu!
Tomokatsu, where did you run to? What a mischievous.
Oh, you!
Stay away!
Enough, Momoe.
You can't meet him.
Why did you bring me here?
Eh? You want go in?
It's impossible.
I will look like a thief.
I understood. If I come in, will you calm down?
Understood. I need to peek in?
That girl...
Still can not. Be patient a little more, Tomokatsu.
Now you can, Tomokatsu.
Come on!
Why am I not in the
place of that dog?
Tomokatsu,  what are you doing?
Tomok...
Tomokatsu, you..!
Momoe!
Now you can't!
But ... it looks nice.
Momoe...
H-Hello! I-I am Takeshi, the master of Momoe.
And I am Sayuri.
Sayuri-san, I'm sorry. At times lei...
Takeshi-san, everything is fine.
Takeshi-san, let's do it us too.
Faster.
Yes!
With pleasure!
Sayuri-san!
Sayuri-san!!
Takeshi-san!!
Her it is!