Eromame
It's Christmas tonight.
I was lonely, but a genuine Miss Santa came to my cheap apartment.
I'm your present.
I'll try my hardest to make you enjoy it as much as possible.
A-After my precious first kiss, please take my first time.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Oh no!
It's overflowing!
My pussy's staying open in the shape of your penis.
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Santa Society, Japanese Branch
Having sex with a Santa girl?
Did we really approve a wish like that?
Have Santa Clause                                All to Yourself
It's Christmas tonight.
I'm Miss Santa, who delivers presents to all the pure children.
I'm in charge of a branch in the
Santa Society, Itabashi Ward, Tokyo.
In office for the first year.
Or at least that's what I'm supposed to be.
This is the place.
Good evening!
I'm Santa!
Um...
I came to deliver your presents for you.
I'll come in, all right?
S-Santa?
Present?
I don't really understand...
what she's saying.
Who is this girl?
She's super cute!
The Santa Society approved your request,
I'd like to have a date
at my home with Miss
Santa on Christmas night.
because you properly put it in your socks.
Come to think of it, I guess I did do something childish when I was drunk.
I'm still a newbie, but I'll do my best to make you happy.
Here.
Say "ah".
Ah.
U-Um, did I do something I shouldn't?
Man, you're so cute I fell in love with you at first sight.
I can't hold it back any more.
You're so bold!
I'm embarrassed!
Please wait.
I'm not mentally prepared yet.
I can't wait.
After all, this present is only for today, isn't it?
I understand.
Only for today, I'll give you my entirety as a present.
Please use me however you wish.
Your pussy is cute too, Miss Santa!
You're so cute, Miss Santa!
D-Don't stir me up so deep!
Your pussy is so wet already, Miss Santa.
I can put it in, right?
Yes.
I give you my virginity.
Your insides are so hot it might melt.
It feels way too good!
Th-Thank you very much.
I can't keep it up.
Your virgin pussy is squeezing me.
I-I'm cumming.
You came with me.
I'm so happy.
I was in ecstasy too.
By the way, are these presents mine too?
Y-Yes.
The things you're wishing for right now...
I wonder what these are.
Check
Erotic Book
Whoa, they look fun!
Check
Erotic Book
All right, let's play with these!
Check
Erotic Book
O-Okay.
Check
Erotic Book
I-I'm a little scared.
Miss Santa, say "ah".
Ah.
This is how...
the guy who was in me a moment ago...
tastes like.
It's so soft and slippery; it feels good!
I think I'll cum again from your cleansing blowjob.
Pwease ejacuwate inside my mouth.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming while he's ejaculating in my mouth!
Take it out.
P-Please take this toy out.
You came while giving me a blowjob.
How cute!
You want my dick, right?
You give me no choice.
I'm cumming while your thrusting it in.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming through my pussy!
Don't tease me there with those toys!
How fun!
Do your best, Miss Santa.
I've been coming all this time.
I'm going crazy.
Yet I was the one who was supposed to get presents.
This naughty Miss Santa who's been cumming all alone needs to be punished.
That place...
The more I tease your anus, the harder your pussy teases me.
Oh no!
I'm cumming.
I'm ejaculating in the deepest spot of your lewd pussy.
I'm cummiiing!
Your semen is filling me so hard!
Let me shoot my last one in you in a lovey-dovey fashion.
All right.
I'm a happy girl.
Give me a lot.
I want you to burn the shape of your dick into my pussy.
Love you! Love you!
I'm already cumming.
Let's do it together!
I love you too.
I'm cumming.
Please cum inside.
I'm cumming with you!
Miss Santa...
One Year Later
Thanks.
So you called me again.
We're going to be together forever from now on.
I love you!
Please let me have
Miss Santa as a wife.
Be swift!!
Don't wake them up!!
Be careful!!
Huh?
Did we really approve a wish like this?
Captain is so cool!
She sure is.
Uh-huh.
I hope I'll get to do archery soon!
I know, right?
Silence your whispering, Kohinata!
Once first-years finish with their weight training, they go to running.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Love     Bow     Maiden
~How to Melt her by Shooting in her Heart~
No good! No good!
Don't think of anything unnecessary!
Concentrate!
So you stayed to train overtime, after all.
Wh-What's the matter, Kohinata?
Did you forget something?
I was thinking about how I haven't made out with my girlfriend recently.
D-Don't.
If someone sees us...
Everyone went home a long time ago.
Just for a little bit.
Ah, right!
She's just my classmate.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Huh?
I was sure you were misunderstanding it.
You're the only one I love, Yumika.
You dropped the honorific from my name?
No fair, Kohinata.
You're cute.
The complete opposite of how you act during club activities.
You know well that this is a sacred place.
Are you really saying I should stop?
D-Don't...
Don't stop.
I'm begging you, love me to the very end.
To tell the truth, I always thought of you, even when I was doing club activities.
The mere fact that you're talking to some other girl
makes me crazy from jealousy.
If you beg me that honestly,
and even show me your wet pussy,
I can't control myself either.
I really think I forgot it in the clubroom.
For real?
Huh?
The lights are on in the archery practice hall.
Is there anyone here?
D-Don't fondle them!
Sorry, but your breasts almost poked out.
Huh?
It isn't there.
Maybe in the classroom?
Whoa, your locker is so dirty!
P-Please go home quick.
If you don't, my mind will go blank.
I want Kohinata's cock fast!
I want him in my pussy.
Y-Yumika...
You can't seriously want to move now.
It went in!
Deep inside.
More.
I can't stop.
K-Kohinata.
You can't, Yumika.
Control yourself!
You're held in suspense because you couldn't hold back and put it in.
You got what you deserve.
My womb got diswocated.
Your pussy is moving like jelly.
This'll be bad!
Hey, didn't you hear a voice from the archery practice hall?
You check it.
It's scary!
Sorry.
I'll ejaculate.
Oh no!
The club members will see how he shoots it inside me.
Here it was.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Ahh, that was scary!
I guess we shouldn't have sex in the school.
We should probably go home right away.
Yumika?!
I don't want it to end wike dis.
Kohinata, I'm sorry.
I don't sink I can controw myself anymore.
Pwease wet me have a taste of you for a wittle more.
I-If you suck on it that hard,
it'll get erect again.
It's intense.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
You'll suck my semen.
It's dewicious!
I even came twice!
Yumika, did your excitement switch turn off?
He's asking me if my switch turned off?
I-Is it okay if we don't go home?
The smell of a penis and the taste of semen only made my pussy tingle more,
and feel more painful.
Hmm... If you beg enough,
I may think about thrusting you hard.
I-I'm begging you!
I want it here, in my pussy, one more time!
I want you to keep thrusting me with your cock till I collapse.
As you wish, Captain.
I'm not the Captain now.
I'm yours... I'm only yours now.
Call me "Yumika."
Sorry, sorry, Yumika.
You know, your pussy is squeezing hard when I say "Yumika."
You're cute, Yumika.
The virile Yumika who's training...
The Yumika who's embracing my penis naughtily, and never wants to let it go...
I love them all!
I'm so happy!
With your penis loving me,
my pussy can't stop cumming, Kohinata.
Your pussy is so wet and feels so good while you're cumming.
I'm happy.
Stir me up more.
I'm cumming.
I'll cum harder if you keep thrusting like that.
I love you!
I'm about to ejaculate, Yumika.
Cum.
Cum!
I'll take it all in to my deepest spots!
I'm filled with Kohinata's semen!
It feels so hot!
I love you.
I love you!
Geez, I can't stop cumming.
Yesterday, I was here with Kohinata having...
Are you thinking about it??