Karakara-sama's secret: the Goddess from Heaven
Karakara-sama no Himitsu
Ten Kara Kita Megami
Translation: Kuukunen
Translation check: Sonic_Sabbath
Everything else: Kuukunen
#kuukunen @ irc.rizon.net
How, Why & More info:
http://kuukunen.net/karakara/
There!
Crap!
Let me out of here!
You're really lucky.
To have to go through this the time you just happened to come here all the way from Toukai.
I feel sorry for him, really.
Instead of feeling sorry untie these ropes!
We can't do that, Akimitsu.
This is grandpa's voice?
I am sorry.
But this village makes an offering once in a hundred years and today is the day.
Offering?
Yes. You were selected to be the offering.
There is no choice, so please put up with it.
Offering...
What exactly is that?
It is for Karakara-sama.
Karakara-sama is the guardian deity of this village's fountain.
If we don't keep her happy, the water source of the village will dry up.
So that is why no matter what, we have to make an offering.
So what does this "Karakara-sama" want from the offering?
I think he will get his blood sucked out.
What are you saying? Isn't his liver going to get harvested?
Wrong, wrong. His skin will be peeled off.
His brain will be eaten.
Don't say stupid things. It's definitely the shirikodama.
TL note: shirikodama (尻子玉), mythical ball inside the anus that is sought after by kappa
No, no, no! Let me out of here!
So, hang in there, Akimitsu.
Hey everyone!
Whining's useless...
They really did leave me alone.
After being told all that, I really have a bad feeling about this.
Mirror?
What's this?
Karakara-sama?
You are the offering?
Please don't suck my blood!
Please don't harvest my liver!
Please don't peel of my skin!
Please don't eat my brain!
Definitely don't touch my shirikodama!
Please!
That's impossible for me....
I couldn't do anything like that!
Hey...
You...
So you're an apprentice of god?
Yes. Because I'm so clumsy and I always make mistakes,
I don't know what a goddess should do at a time like this.
So after all as a god I should peel off your skin, harvest your liver and take your shirikodama?
Personally I think it would be better if you didn't do that.
So that's it?
This is the first time this girl has come to this world.
So there will be lots of difficulties.
I am Akimitsu. You are?
My name is Moegi.
That's a really good name.
If there's anything you need, please tell.
If you're fine with me, I can help you.
Yes.
Finally you smiled.
So...
What is it?
Can we perform the ritual now?
Ritual? Fine, but what is it?
What are you...
The ritual is that the offering and the god will spend a night together.
Err, do you understand?
No, not at all.
But even so, it's still too early.
I knew it! You don't want to do it with me, right!?
That's not what I mean! Umm...
Rather than mine, it's up to your feelings.
Well, as long as it's you, Akimitsu...
Well... I...
Moegi.
Moegi...
Akimitsu-san...
This is my first time...
be gentle...
Yes.
You're pretty.
Not there!
They're amazing!
N–no!
This, this feeling is the first...
I'm losing it!!
Moegi?
Embarrassing...
You shouldn't be.
Moegi, you're very beautiful.
Really?
Yes. To prove that, look!
Because you're so beautiful, it became like this.
This is Akimitsu-san's...
Is it okay?
It hurts!
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Yes. I'm fine.
Moegi...
Sorry. Does it still hurt?
No... It...
What is it?
It doesn't hurt anymore, but I have a strange feeling.
Could it be, you're feeling it?
I don't know!
What kind of feeling?
Please don't stop!
Moegi...
That's too hard.
Moegi, Moegi!
Don't!
If you do that...
I will feel weird!
Moegi!
Together!
Together...
Akimitsu-san!
Moegi...
I guess Moegi went back to her own world.
Umm...
What is it?
I forgot how to go back to heaven.
It's fine, Moegi.
So what should I do now?
Don't worry.
Really?
This is your home town?
It's pretty ordinary town, though.
Anyway, until you remember how to go back, this is your home town too.
But are you sure I'm not an annoyance?
I don't want to become a burden to your house.
It's fine. Let's go?
Yes.
You look really happy.
Yes, I'm happy that I'm able to see scenery that is different to Heaven.
And...
And?
And being able to stay here with you makes me really happy.
Oh, Akimitsu-kun!
Oh, good morning.
You're not to be underestimated, is she your girlfriend?
No, well...
My name is Moegi. Nice to meet you.
Such a polite greeting. She's a nice girl, isn't she?
Are you sure she's not your girlfriend?
That's right, I'm not his girlfriend.
Oh, was I wrong?
Yes. I'm a goddess.
She's really an interesting girl! Take good care of the goddess.
Yeah...
Who's that? What an eyesore.
She said she was a goddess.
We can't leave her alone.
So here we are.
This is my home.
This is?
Let's go inside.
So this is her home.
What should we do?
We will remove her from our area by force!
You're so violent, Hibiki-han.
This is a good time to start our secret plan.
If she notices us, she might try something.
I guess you could think that way...
That's why we are going to sneak in that way, and attack.
Then I will finish it with my own fists.
I couldn't do anything like that.
Stop nitpicking.
We must not be noticed, so have to go quietly.
Make yourself comfortable. There are currently no one else living here.
What about your parents?
Both of them are always gone because of work.
So I'm just living here alone.
But, now you and me are living here together.
Hm? Yes, that's right.
Hey! What are you doing?
What is it?
Hey! The tail is off-limits!
Stop tickling me!
Hey you! What exactly is this thing?
That's the guardian robot of the house, Shinkichi-kun.
Cute!
My mother specializes in robot engineering, so...
For that reason alone you leave something this dangerous sitting around!?
But it's my mother's hobby.
Hobby?...
Leaving that aside, who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am, just get this thing off me!
So you were demon-san. Nice to meet you.
Sorry for the ruckus.
This is just cheap tea, but—
As if I would drink this!
We are demons, enemies of goddesses. Don't act so casual!
That's right, you followed Moegi through the town.
So leisurely drinking tea is...
Shut up! This is a matter between demons and goddesses! It doesn't concern you one bit!
Feh!
No way! I will protect Moegi!
What's with this guy?
Delicious tea cookies!
Akimitsu-san prepared them.
He really does have good taste.
Hey! What are you doing warmly chattering. Focus on the current situation!
But if demon-san and I will be peaceful, it would be better for everyone in the town. Right?
Well, if Moegi says so...
What about Hibiki-san?
I can't really say anything to that...
You know how to talk.
I'm not in the mood to argue with him.
Kodama, you say something too.
So everyone, let's drink tea and calm down.
Yes, my throat is dry as well.
Hmm?
Moegi!
My body won't...
What did you do?
While everyone were talking, I slipped some drugs in the tea.
Sleep medicine for Moegi-san and some special medicine for Akimitsu-san.
So, let's get started with the fun time.
This person... is good...
What a Kodama-like detestable way of doing it.
Good! More!
When he opened his eyes, he thought you were his lover.
That's right. He drank poison that will make him vigorous like an animal.
After the shock, she will leave the town.
Crap. So that's how it was.
But it feels kind of nice – no – my body is not obeying me, I have to stop this.
You look like you're coming.
Inside! Come inside!
Delicious.
Where are you going?
That's not to my taste. I was thinking about going back.
Service this person too!
You!
I was feeling bad hogging all the fun.
Wait! Stop!
Even if you say that...
Don't! The tail is...
I said don't! I can feel it...
No! I still have my pants on!
Incredible! It's my first time with someone like this.
How is is Hibiki-han? Should we quit?
T–that...
If you don't speak clearly, I can't understand you at all.
M–m–
More...
Honest girl, aren't you. I want my share of the passion too.
This. This is good.
Sorry, sorry.
I can't hold it! Can't hold it!
Hibiki-han! Together. Together!
I'm coming!
What happened?
So you woke up?
You're too late, though. He is already ours.
That...
Yes, that's right. You should leave quickly.
That's... Akimitsu-san is...
What's this? The air in the room is moving.
Akimitsu-san is...
stupid!
What's this?
Oh no, she was a water goddess.
Water goddess?
Goddess who controls water.
You only know the obvious!?
Why did you make her cry? She unleashed her power when you provoked her.
That's why I said it's a bad idea to make her angry!
You're saying that! You're the one who provoked her the most!
In 1959 an elephant from a zoo was washed away in the isewan typhoon.
Like I'd care!
An ark would be nice.
That'd never happen.
I give up!
Akimitsu-san is stupid.
Akimitsu-san!
I can smell something.
This is the smell of a medicine.
It's coming from Akimitsu-san's body. Could it be that those drugged us?
Akimitsu-san! Akimitsu-san!
I'm sorry Moegi. If I was stronger, this wouldn't have...
No. It was the medicine's fault.
It was my fault.
If only I hadn't come to your place... Because of me, those two came here and gave you so much trouble. So...
Don't worry about it.
So it would be better if I wasn't here by your side.
Moegi.
I want to be together with you always.
There might be things to come, but as long as we're together we can manage somehow. That's what I think.
Besides...
I love you, Moegi.
Akimitsu-san!
Moegi.
Akimitsu-san.
You are pretty, Moegi.
Moegi?
Akimitsu-san is mine only!
You're like...
If you do it like that...
I... can't...
Don't go further, Akimitsu-san.
Why?
It's the punishment for unfaithfulness.
Moegi became like this too?
That's...
Your spot is very hot.
Meanie!
How do you want it?
I don't know!
It went in.
It's still coming.
If you don't begin...
I'll start.
It's in. Akimitsu-san is inside me!
It's so warm inside you.
Don't!
Moegi!
Akimitsu-san!
This time, try moving yourself.
You can move as you like.
Akimitsu-san, like this something...
It's incredible, Moegi.
Inside me, I can feel you pulse.
Akimitsu-san.
Moegi, I...
I will...
Akimitsu-san is releasing a lot inside me.
Moegi.
Akimitsu-san.
I love you.
Yes!