So this is the city of Toras.
The sun is setting.
We'll rest here tonight.
Well, Silver? It's been a long time since you smelled the scent of women.
Come! Come on, Silver.
They're waiting for us there!
Hi-yo, Silver!
This is the legendary
knight Takeru Yamato,
an outstanding warrior for good.
He was born as a child of the gods,
but fate has ordained
that he must wander in the human realm.
He himself does not know his origins.
But numerous heroic deeds are attributed to him,
and his name is known everywhere.
The people yearn for his coming.
His appearance is like a ray of sunshine.
There's no one who hasn't heard of Yamato Takeru.
Dragon Knight Gaiden
Oh? That must be the famous cathedral of Toras.
There's quite a lot of activity here.
Stop! Stop that boy!
Stop him!
He's a thief!
Make way!
That scoundrel!
Return the property you stole,
I don't know what you're talking about!
Don't talk nonsense.
Give it back to me now.
I... don't know anything!
We should just kill him!
Wait!
What's this? You don't just hit children.
Don't get bent out of shape, stranger.
We just want to get back what this dirty little rascal stole from us.
I see.
Stay still,
Trying to fight me is suicide, buddy.
Hey, if you stole something, then you'd best cough it up,
or I'll leave you with these friendly gentlemen here.
Here. I take it you're satisfied now?
If not...
No, it's all right now, stranger.
Yes, yes. The priest has...
You fool. That's nobody else's business!
We're leaving.
Let's split!
You stay here!
Give me back my coin purse, immediately!
You noticed?
Of course. You've probably just started in this line of work?
Was I really that bad?
Yes, if even I noticed.
If you go on like this, you'll lose both your hands for sure.
You're probably hungry, huh?
Yes. I haven't eaten anything for three days.
Well, I'm inviting you to dinner.
You mean that?
Yeah.
But you have to promise me something.
Sure! Anything you want.
As long as you're with me, no thieving.
If that's all, then your purse is safe from me.
I mean everyone's purses. Got it?
All right, I promise.
What's your name, by the way?
My name is Jodi.
I'm Takeru.
Oh man, that one's hot!
Takeru, when are we finally going to eat?
Oh, come on, that can wait a little while longer.
Oh! But that one's sweet too!
Takeru, how long do I
have to wait for food?
I see women!
It's been so long since I've seen a woman!
Master Leonardo...
Priest, obey me!
Toras still needs more women.
I understand. Thy will be done.
Soon this city will be transformed into a swamp of lust, Great Master.
Let it be done.
You can count on me.
Who's there?
It's just us, Priest.
Oh! It's about time!
Here, Priest!
Bring these women to Venezza the moneylender right away.
Good quality.
We understand.
Something's missing!
Impossible. We counted the money twice.
Moron! Who's talking about money?!
This purse also contained an important drug that I must have.
Important drug?
It was the little guy!
Seize that thief!
And because he probably knows about it,
it'd be better if you disposed of him.
We don't need a confederate!
Go at once and get to work. Every second counts!
You appear quite desperate.
Th-That voice... I know it!
Shade? As always, your appearance is very theatrical.
Leonardo likes me to keep an eye on his subordinates, my friend.
Then you understand that I have to find this drug soon.
At any cost, this city must not discover who I really am.
Leonardo has not yet been informed about this little mishap.
Can't you assist me in retrieving this drug?
Of course. But I'm doing it my way.
I'll leave that to you.
Now I'm really in trouble.
You have an amazing appetite!
That's enough for the next two or three days.
Those portions were for three grown men.
Say, is it true...
that you lost sight of your sister when you entered the city?
Where could she be?
She can't have left the city already.
All right! I'll help you.
What?
By all accounts, this city is very large,
but there must be a reason why she hasn't shown up yet.
Maybe someone kidnapped her and is holding her captive?
You think so?
So tell me. Is your sister really pretty?
C-Can you please think about something else?
Just kidding!
I saw through you before you invited me to dinner.
Then we understand each other, kid.
Well, you're not exactly ugly,
so I thought that perhaps your sister is good looking.
And if she's not pretty, then you won't help me?
You mean to say...
she's as ugly as sin?
What nonsense!
There's no better woman than my sister in the whole of Toras!
It's all right.
But if you find her, I can't even reward you for it.
Don't worry, kid. Your sister will be responsible for that.
Thank you, Takeru.
But are you doing this from kindness or from greed?
Come on, trust me, okay?
I've observed how you helped this boy.
You're very adept with your sword.
Oh! It's nothing special. I'm just lucky.
No, I've got some skill myself.
You're a very good fighter.
I'd like to ask for your help with something.
I'm very sorry. I already have a job.
Then I'll ask you another time.
Sorry.
My name is Yurius.
Mine's Yamato Takeru.
Yamato Takeru?
Are you the one who broke the curse of Strawberry Fields?
You must be confusing me with someone else.
I can't be him, can I?
You might be right.
They say he's very large and quite strong.
Allegedly, everyone who meets him
respects him just because of his appearance.
And every woman who crosses his path
supposedly wants to give herself to him.
You're right. You can't be him.
That's actually pretty rude of you.
What's the matter, kid?
You look like someone I knew, eerily similar.
But unfortunately, that man has already died.
Such things happen sometimes.
There are people who say
that every person has a double in the world.
Could be... but...
So, Takeru, will you help me after you've completed your job?
Yes, I'll be in touch.
So I'll be leaving now.
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for a place to crash.
Oh, and what if you run into the guys from before?
But...
Innkeeper!
Yes, what is it?
We'll stay here for a while.
Here.
Very well.
Thanks very much, sir.
Please find something else for the boy to wear.
It should be easy to find
something better than that.
I still have a couple of pieces of clothing from my son.
Now, wait a moment!
I'm not going to sleep in the same room as you.
There's nothing to be worried about.
I have no interest whatsoever in that direction, boy.
Come on now.
Let go! What's this?! Takeru!
The room is located on the second floor, sir.
Just come with me, Jodi!
Jodi?
Then they're hiding in here?
What should we do now?
We'll wait until they're asleep.
Otherwise it's too dangerous.
I hope this is gonna work.
Once they're asleep, they won't stand a chance against us.
Immediately to the right is the bathroom.
Make yourselves at home.
Jodi, you can bathe first.
B-But I don't want to take a bath.
Once you get cleaned up,
no one will recognize you.
Also, it's not exactly pleasant for me
to sleep next to a little stinker.
B-But it's all right. I can...
Don't argue, buddy.
Come on, get undressed!
I-It's all right! Let go of me! I can do that myself!
Let go! Let go!
Then get going.
But the door is to remain remain closed. Is that clear?
I have no desire to look at you, idiot!
No education is also an education.
Acting like a girl...
Good evening.
Hello.
Do you perhaps have a room available?
If possible I'd like a room next to those two.
Yes, that can be arranged.
I'll show you.
Who's there?
It's me. I've brought fresh clothes.
Just come in.
These are rather modest items.
That's all right.
The main thing is that they're clean.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Yes, thank you.
Jodi!
Your clothes.
You... You... You...
Get out of here, now!
Y-You're a girl?
Get out! What are you looking at?
A girl? I don't believe...
Takeru!
Is everything okay?
Takeru! Say something!
Takeru. Takeru! Takeru!
Are you all right, Takeru?
B-Breasts!
Oh my God, Jodi!
I'm so glad. I'm so glad!
I thought I'd killed you.
J-J-Jodi, calm down.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm very sorry!
It's okay, Jodi.
You have to get dressed now, or you'll catch a cold.
Please, put something on quickly, Jodi!
Take me, Takeru.
But you can't just say something like that. It isn't right.
It is!
You saved my life.
Jodi, that doesn't have anything to do with it.
And you want to help me find my sister.
That's what I promised.
I told you... that my sister is a beauty.
And?
I don't want her to take you away from me.
That's just unfair!
That girl tricked us pretty good, boss.
If we'd caught her right away, then we'd be in his place.
Just look at that. She's quite pretty.
You're right!
Do you like that woman so much, guys?
Shade!
So this bitch has the drug?
Yes, yes.
Who's that man?
He seems to be a traveler.
But he has the strength of a bear.
Takeru, please! You can't just stop like that!
W-Wait a minute, Jodi. I can't breathe!
I'm sorry.
You probably regard me rather badly, right?
No, that's not true, Jodi.
Tell me, what's your real name?
Jodice.
Jodice, huh? A beautiful name.
Jodice, I accept this down payment for my work.
Huh?
We'll start looking for your sister tomorrow.
So make sure you rest.
But...
Have you ever heard of soldiers receiving
their pay before completion of their mission?
But...
They only get a down payment, right?
So that's it.
You don't like me!
Don't talk nonsense.
Of course I like you, Jodice.
Really?
Yes, of course.
After we've saved your sister,
I'll take my reward, Jodice.
You're so mean!
Not at all.
You know very well that I love women, right?
But I don't like it
when they indulge me only out of gratitude.
Do you understand, my darling?
Don't you think that the advance was too small?
More...
If you really want it...
Kiss me, Takeru!
I love you, Jodice.
I love you too.
Takeru! Takeru!
Takeru!
What a lovely sight.
That's true.
Begone!
That's just what I wanted to say to you.
If you don't keep perfectly still, I'll cut the little one's throat.
Have I made myself clear?
Jodice...
Takeru!
What?! Takeru?!
Put your sword aside. Otherwise...
Oh, no!
W-Wait!
I'll do it.
Very reasonable. Nice and slow.
I understand, but don't hurt Jodice.
Takeru!
Now you're finally silent!
You, close the door.
Sure.
Hmm?
What was all that noise?
So, little one,
give back what you stole yesterday.
Or do I have to cut your ears off?
Please don't hurt me. I don't know what you're talking about!
Or should we start with your cute little nose?
Oh my... God!
You still haven't found anything?
No, not yet. But what's left to search here?
Hello? Is everything okay in there?
Why now? We're leaving.
Take the girl and her clothes.
Yes.
Quickly!
Hey!
Wake up! Hey!
Where the hell can they have hidden it?
It's still a bit early to cry.
Have you finally found something?
Okay then.
I'll probably have to take care of you in a special way.
And now?
Th-That hurts! Please stop it!
Then spit it out!
Wh-What do you want?
What do you want me to say?
Are you finally willing...
to tell me where you hid what you stole from the priest?
But I returned everything.
Did you take anything out of the bag? Be honest, or else...
That hurts!
I swear! I didn't take anything! Please believe me!
Hmm, you're pretty tough.
But don't worry. This won't leave any scars on your skin.
Please... don't do that!
I'm afraid!
You're extremely sensitive, aren't you?
Now try not to faint again.
That would spoil all of my fun.
I'm going to give your sweet little behind a good thrashing.
How do you feel about that?
Please don't...
Please let me go. I don't know anything.
Please don't!
After I've rested a bit,
I'll transform you into a really lewd woman, my darling.
That girl knows nothing.
Why is Shade continuing?
Shade clearly wants to turn the girl into a toy.
When Shade's finished with her, she'll be given a spoonful of the drug.
The girl will get so turned on that she'll obey blindly,
despite all the perversions.
But I think Shade's being
particularly cruel in this case.
There's probably something about the girl.
I bet that the priest won't be allowed to touch her yet.
He battered the last girl pretty badly.
Thank God our bosses have different preferences.
That's how we can earn our bread, right?
Hey, that's true.
My head is buzzing horribly.
W-Water, please.
But that's... Takeru!
D-Don't shout so loud!
I've got a headache.
And where's the water?
Wh-What is this?!
Where the hell did you
get this stuff? Speak!
You'd better tell me where Jodice is.
How did you obtain this forbidden drug? Answer me!
If I don't like your answer, I'll kill you!
Forbidden drug?
From the mandrake plant.
If you give a woman just a single spoonful,
she'll automatically become a slave to her desires,
and she'll do everything she's told, no matter how perverted it may be!
That is a ultra-mega-cool thing. Very handy.
I didn't really mean that.
This isn't the work of man.
What does that mean?
Are you really that stupid?
It means that demonic forces are in town to party.
Yurius, tell me where Jodice is! I must find her quickly!
We will.
I have a hunch.
Hey, Yurius!
Why did I need to dress myself up like a lady?
We can't simply demand that Jodice be returned.
That's not what I meant!
Why are you the posh girl and I'm the younger sister?
Just look in the mirror for once, boy!
Hmph! I feel discriminated against!
Try not to behave so conspicuously!
I'm sorry, but are you sure that Jodice is hidden in the cathedral?
Most likely.
The new priest here belongs to some obscure religious order.
He's a very strange guy.
It's best to go have a look around and behave as if we want to pray.
This is the least conspicuous way.
Yeah. You're probably right.
There's no other way.
What do you want?
Yes. We've lost our parents to a terrible disease
and wanted to ask the priest to pray for their salvation.
That way, the evil afflicting our family may be lifted from us.
My goodness. Not bad, Yurius.
Oh, my sincere condolences.
Then I'll take you to the priest at once.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you, sir.
Oh! How beautiful! You are welcome in God's house!
I will pray for you.
Shade will accompany both of you to the prayer hall.
Shade?
Follow me.
But you're...
Shade? So you as well?
What's going on?!
I guess it's my turn next!
P-Please stop!
Your body and your mind already belong to the demon!
What the hell are you waiting for, Shade?
Kill them! Kill them!
No! I can't!
Oh, right! You can't kill me! Sorry!
Die!
What are you doing, Shade?
Yurius, leave it to me!
Try to get the priest to tell you where they're hiding Jodice!
Stop!
If you want to fight me, I won't spare you!
Hey, you beast! Show yourself!
You beast!
I knew it! You must be the legendary Takeru Yamato.
I'm not telling you!
I've got you figured out!
Oh, really?!
Die now!
Are you looking for me?
I'm right here!
What?
Now you'll get it!
Yurius!
Priest, where's Jodice?!
She'll soon be handed over to Master Leonardo.
I want to see her, Priest!
The poor little thing has no strength left to speak anymore.
But before you can see her, I'll have to give you to Master Leonardo.
Take her away!
Yurius!
Oh, what's that? What have I done?
Takeru!
Ah, right.
He's to blame,
Now it's your turn!
That's really horrible.
J-Jodice...
Jodice, I'm sorry I'll never see you again.
Maybe she was Jodice's sister?
How did it come to this?
Master Leonardo will atone for this.
Jodice!
Takeru?
Now everything's all right, Jodice.
Takeru... at last!
Jodice, what's the matter with you?
Take me, Takeru!
Please, take me.
Jodice, what's wrong with you?
Pull yourself together. What have they done to you?
You have to do it with her, or she'll go crazy.
What are you saying?
It's the effect of the mandrake.
Jodice, they poisoned you?
Please, I can't take it anymore!
I'll wait outside.
Almighty!
What kind of hell did that girl go through?!
Jodice...
Takeru...
Please! Hurry!
My whole body's on fire!
I'll do it. Soon you'll feel much better.
No!
S-Sorry. Did I hurt you?
Not at all.
Please put your hand there.
Did you come already?
I don't know, Takeru.
But it feels great. Touch me there again.
Oh, yes!
You're all wet.
Oh, yes! Continue, please!
You taste so sweet.
Takeru! Hurry! Put it in quickly.
Are you ready?
Takeru, I love you.
Please come to me.
Oh my God!
Are you all right?
It's wonderful.
Takeru, please, don't stop.
Oh my G-God!
Jodice...
I'm glad, Takeru, that finally...
That's good, Jodice.
Great! This is so wonderful!
Yes, more... faster!
Yes! It feels good! More. More!
Takeru, please...
I'm about to come! Oh, it's wonderful!
Takeru! Takeru! Oh God!
Please, let's come together.
Oh my God, Takeru! Faster! Harder!
I'm coming.
Takeru... I'm... I-I'm coming!
Take care of Jodice.
Has the effect finally abated?
Yes. My work here is done.
Now I can go.
Then come with me! I need to go to Rona.
I'll have to take care of Jodice first though.
What is your answer?
Rona, huh? Why not?
Take care of her.
I'll get Silver and go on ahead.
You are Her Highness, aren't you?
Yes. And you're the daughter of the Guardian of Rikyuu, correct?
Yes. I'm glad you remembered.
Your sister suffered terribly,
and unfortunately, we were too late to save her.
But because that nefarious priest is dead, this city is safe again.
Feel free to remain here for a little while.
And you, Your Highness?
I intend to leave immediately.
Because, as you saw, there will be no peace
as long as Leonardo is still alive.
Where is Takeru?
He's already left.
We will fight Leonardo together.
I understand.
Thank you.
The freedom-loving, swashbuckling, legendary warrior Takeru Yamato
continues on his journey.
He ventures further,
and he doesn't know where and when he will learn the truth about himself.
Takeru Yamato is marked by the star of destiny.
He continues to look for romance and adventure.
He's the last of the true heroes.
Takeru Yamato travels further on his erratic way.
Where will his journey lead him next?
English translation & timing
M74
Editing
Collectr