I'm really happy.
Just by breaking the earth and digging a hole, I feel a transient kind of happiness.
This act, every shovel, all of which connects me to you.
Ah... it's snowing.
Presented by Masurenai Fansubs
First night
Indiscriminate murder
Ueno Serial Mutilation Murder Cases
Whereabouts of the criminal is
If that incident hadn't happened, I wouldn't have gone to Zushi.
7 years ago
Zushi
That girl actually came to such a place all alone.
That's true...
Let's go.
Are you alright?
My name is Takashiro Shugo.
I came to see a doctor in this town to get my chest ailment treated.
Even so, people in this place are really horrible.
They didn't lend a hand even when seeing you in hardship.
That's because I... that's why...
Eh?
It's nothing. Thank you very much.
Well then.
That was when it all began.
Excuse me!
Kohzuki  Keiichirou
This is Takashiro. I've been referred here by Police Inspector Arishima from the Metropolitan Police Department.
No one's home?
Are you a detective?
Yes...
This way please.
Have a seat.
Um...
The master will be with you soon.
7 years ago, I fell in love with Yura here.
But now...
T-Thank you for traveling such a distance here.
Yura?
It must have been difficult traveling in the snow.
Did you manage to find this house immediately?
Coming from the city, the location of this house was unexpected and missed many times.
No matter how wealthy they are or how big the place is,
I think it's meaningless if it can't be found.
Don't you think so?
Ah, please have some tea.
Um...
You're a detective, right?
I've been waiting for you at the entrance.
Ah, I shouldn't do this.
I didn't introduce myself before I started talking.
My name is Kohzuki Kazuna.
Kazuna?
I thank you for coming over today for my sister's sake.
Come to think of it, I did hear that Yura had a younger twin sister.
Um... is there something on my face?
N-No, it's nothing.
Without delay I would like to hear more regarding the request...
Speaking of that, I'll take over from here.
Father.
Kohzuki Keichirou-san.
Kazuna, please leave us.
But-but, this is an important discussion concerning Onee-sama...
For this reason, I must speak of the details with this person thoroughly.
Kohzuki-san, since she's her younger sister, her presence here should be...
Isn't that right? Isn't it?
Leave us!
Well then, even though you were referred by Police Inspector Arishima, but...
My name is Takashiro Shugo.
Regarding your daughter who had gone missing...
Can you keep secrets?
Eh...
No matter what you hear, can you maintain confidentiality?
That's... required of my job.
Very well.
You're right. The one I want you to find is my eldest daughter, Yura.
She's Kazuna's twin sister.
She went missing 5 years ago.
Moreover, she disappeared without even stepping out through the door of her room.
As if she was spirited away.
Furthermore, her eyes were wounded in an accident.
In short, it was impossible for her to move by herself.
Then, could she have been kidnapped?
No, since then we have not received any threatening letters or ransom demands.
I have used all means to find her,
but halfway through, the war began.
She went missing 5 years ago.
And, she couldn't be found even with the influence and power of Kohzuki family.
Furthermore, there was the chaos that occurred during the war.
That's the situation.
After all this time, why are you asking me now...
Something happened recently,
and we've received information that my daughter was seen at Ueno.
Ueno?
That's right.
That's the place currently flustered with the bizarre serial murder cases.
Of course, Yura wasn't one of the victims.
Kazuna made a fuss about it, saying that we definitely must find her sister this time.
She's afraid that if it continues, Yura might become a victim, too.
Even though that's just some groundless assumption.
That's where you come in.
Will you accept this?
I understand.
I shall put in my utmost effort.
Very well.
But this job isn't really that difficult.
What do you mean by that?
Actually...
My daughter, Yura...
...has already died.
That means your job is just a farce.
A farce?
To us, Yura is already an existence of the past.
But...
Listen carefully,
Kazuna is the only person in the entire Kohzuki family who wants to find Yura.
If we don't do anything about this,
Kazuna will definitely leave for Ueno to find Yura on her own.
I can't let my daughter to do such a dangerous thing.
That's why I hired you.
Then, is there conclusive proof that Yura-san has passed away?
None.
Eh?
You only have to completely deceive Kazuna.
And you will receive your reward.
There isn't an actual need for you to go out of your way to find Yura.
Because Yura has already died,
on that day 5 years ago.
Shugo-sama, I'm Hatsune.
Would you like to have a bath now?
Ah, I should do that.
Ah, pardon me.
What are you doing?
I-I'm sorry, I'll clean this up immediately!
You're really clumsy.
Do that and the water will stain the wood.
I'm sorry.
Geez, it's not just this, the customer will be made to wait for his sake now.
Pay more attention to your work!
You're really useless.
I'm really sorry.
You better clean it up properly.
I do know about you, hanging around that freeloading good for nothing sensei's place.
Just let it go at that.
Ujaku nee-san.
Hatsune didn't do that on purpose.
But that detective has been waiting a long time for his sake to be served.
I'll go and apologize to him.
Is that so?
If Nee-san says so...
I'm really sorry!
Don't bother with this already, return to the kitchen.
Um...
My my, just as I was wondering who it was, I never thought it'd be you, Master.
Have you finished your work?
Don't be so sarcastic with me.
Geez, I'm not being sarcastic, you make me sound so mean.
Master has taken care of me so well, too.
That was a long time ago.
Anyway, you said that a detective is here.
Seems that it's related to the investigation of those serial murders.
So, he's not really here as a customer then.
No, absolutely not.
Have another drink, Detective.
My, my, I'm really grateful to you.
Geez, you're really impatient.
This is embarrassing.
It's really hot.
Master...
Master, I'm feeling it.
Master!
Master... Please be more gentle...
Master... Hurry up and do it...
I can't bear it anymore...
Master, I'm going to cum...
I apologize for the other day.
Even though this was originally my job...
Is it regarding those mysterious serial murders?
Yes, the victims were two prostitutes.
Although, they were just cheap prostitutes.
Seems that the murderer's methods were quite unusual.
After mutilation, the bodies were disemboweled.
And that's not all.
Upon examination, the external wounds were made before their deaths.
That means...
The victims were subjected to brutal torture before being killed.
Moreover, there is something that hasn't been announced to the public.
According to an autopsy,
There was a striking loss of body parts from the corpses' abdomens to their genitals
It was the characteristics of those wounds that were unique.
Unique?
Yeah, it was as if they were bitten by sharp fangs.
So you're saying, they were eaten away?
I hope that you'll keep this a secret.
I understand.
So, were there any clues left by the murderer?
None.
The person didn't leave any trace, not even a single fingerprint was found.
There weren't any witnesses as well.
This sequence of events happened in the neighborhood of Ueno.
Moreover, despite putting myself in the victims shoes,
the murderer's motives remain ambiguous.
If the victims were subjected to such a brutal torture,
one would think that the murderer held an intense grudge against the victims.
If that was the case, then the similarities between the victims were too few.
The first victim was a high school girl.
The second and third were drifting prostitutes.
And the fourth victim was a housewife.
They are not connected in any way.
It was as if women who were simply passing by were attacked without discrimination.
But there was something odd.
Something odd?
New wounds were made on the corpses and feathers of crows were stuck in them.
As if they were wings.
Who would do such a thing...
What is this?
This prediction was correct.
Remember in your heart. Obey the Emperor's child's prophecy.
If not, just like an angel that holds black wings, more tragedies will befall upon you.
Senri Shrine?
I guess I should return to my original duty.
Yura, you were a woman whom I once loved dearly and betrayed.
I never thought I would get myself involved again because of that incident.
But Yura is no longer of this world...
Yura? It can't be...
Like I said, I'm looking for someone who looks like me.
Err... But I don't mean me.
You are!?
I found you!
Eh?
Geez... I looked around for you!
I went all the way to the address you left, but isn't that Yukishiro place in the red light district?
Geez... you should write your address properly!
Err well... actually I do live there.
That means, could you possibly be a bodyguard who fights bad people?
I'm just a freeloader.
Long ago, I worked for the mistress over there, so she gave me her support.
Is that so?
Um... Detective...
My name is Takashiro Shugo.
Err... Shugo-san.
Well, actually I've a request for you...
No you can't.
I haven't said anything yet.
This isn't a place for a rich girl like you.
You do know, right? That something is going on here...
Yes. The Ueno mysterious serial murder cases, right?
After mutilation, the bodies were disemboweled.
If you know that much, return to your house obediently.
Your father must be worried.
Oh, if that's your only concern, that's not a problem.
I'm living with someone else.
Eh?
My mother lives around here.
I want to find my sister no matter what.
Let me look for her with you.
Is your father aware of this?
Detective... He said it was fine if I stayed with Shugo-san.
What if we can't find her?
We'll definitely find her!
Until then, I beg of you.
Being a female, I'll do anything, even serve tea.
Ah, if it's necessary, I can even stay in the same residence as you...
I won't allow that.
I'm left with no choice then. So, I'll decide the conditions. Is that alright?
Yes! Thank you very much.
First: You must absolutely listen to my words.
Second: You must never take your own actions.
Yes!
Lastly, if we can't find her after exhausting our options, we'll give up.
Okay...
Is that alright?
Um... the final condition can't be possible, can it?
I understand!
Please take care of me from now on!
I'm dead tired today...
Shu-san... Pardon me.
Rin...
My customer for tonight suddenly said he couldn't come, you know.
Even so, isn't this a bad idea?
Don't worry. I've locked the door.
I don't mean that...
You seem really exhausted.
Yeah, many things happened.
Shall I soothe you?
H-Hey...
See, you're already having a reaction.
If you hold it so strongly...
Then, I shall do it gently.
I-It'll be troublesome when I return.
Shu-san, are you already married with a child?
That is none of your concern.
See, as I predicted, you can't resist, right?
Shu-san, what's the matter?
Hey, Rin. Do you know of Senri Shrine?
Senri Shrine?
It has something to do with a prediction.
Yes, come to think of it, I heard this from a close client. Apparently she's currently a really popular hostess.
Hostess?
Some of her predictions have proved to be accurate though, but...
See. There's that fearful incident that the authorities are panicking about, isn't there?
Apparently, she had predicted that a long time ago.
Could it be a coincidence?
I wonder. I'm not too sure about that either.
Rin, I have a request for you...
Yes, I'll do anything should Shu-san wish for it.
There's only one thing, I'd like it if you'd inform me of anything you hear about the Senri Shrine.
Yes, I understand.
I'm sorry for that.
In return...
Eh?
I want to stay this way tonight.
Just this time, alright?
Yes.
Rin.
It's fine, for Shu-san.
Does it feel good?
Yes...
Shu-san.
Rin...
Rin... That's my...
Shu-san.
Shu-san, you have such a...
I want it quickly.
Rin...
It's great, it's great.
Rin, I'm going to...
Shu-san. Let's cum... together.
Nee-san, it's Takashiro.
Ah, Master. It's all right, just come in.
I'm sorry for calling you here so early in the morning but...
Y-Yeah, I understand but that was really the first time, and it wasn't on purpose.
I was the one at fault and Rin is not responsible for any of it...
Master? What exactly are you talking about?
Eh? Like I said, about last night...
Or it doesn't seem so...
Actually, Master. We haven't been able to find Otoha since morning.
Otoha?
Well, I reprimanded her a little the other day because of the incident with Hatsune...
I don't think she's such a weak woman who would run away from that.
Could she have gone out to buy something?
That is Hatsune and the others' job.
Master, I'm worried about her.
You see, with those mysterious incidents, we've been warned by the police the other day, to be careful as single women are easily targeted.
So, a young woman must be accompanied when she goes out to buy things.
But Otoha seems to have gone out on her own.
I understand. I'll search for her around here!
Ueno Aoi Street
Otoha is a strong-willed woman, I doubt she would be lured in by suspicious people.
You are already too late.
It's not possible to escape from the fate of destruction.
You are?
Believe in predictions.
I'm sorry but I don't have a habit of fortune telling nor depending on gods.
Unlike Benten the goddess, they'd have black wings yet unable to soar to the heavens.
It can't be...
Hey, you mustn't go in.
Stand aside!
Otoha...
To be continued