This act, every shovel, all of which connects me to you.
7 years ago
If that incident hadn't happened, I wouldn't have gone to Zushi.
Zushi
Are you all right?
My name is Takashiro Shugo.
My name is Kohzuki Kazuna.
Kazuna?
I thank you for coming over today for my sister's sake.
Regarding your daughter who's gone missing...
You're right. The one I want you to find is my eldest daughter, Yura.
She's Kazuna's twin sister.
She went missing 5 years ago.
Moreover, she disappeared without even stepping out through the door of her room.
As if she were spirited away.
Furthermore, her eyes were wounded in an accident.
In short, it was impossible for her to move by herself.
What are you doing?
I-I'm sorry, I'll clean this up immediately!
You're really clumsy.
Do that and the sake will stain the wood.
Geez, just let it go at that.
Ujaku nee-san.
Hatsune didn't do it on purpose.
But that detective has been waiting a long time for his sake to be served.
I'll go and apologize to him.
Master... Hurry up and do it...
There was a striking loss of body parts from the abdomens of the corpses to their genitals.
It was the characteristics of those wounds that were quite unique.
But there was something odd.
Something odd?
New wounds were made on the corpses by crow feathers stuck onto them.
As if they were wings.
Shu-san... Pardon me.
Rin...
You seem really exhausted.
Yeah, many things happened.
Shall I ease your stress?
H-Hey...
See, you're already having a reaction.
Rin...
Yes, right there.
I want it quickly.
Rin...
It's great! It's great!
Rin, I'm going to...
Shu-san. Let's cum... Together.
Actually, Master. We haven't been able to find Otoha since morning.
Otoha?
Well, I reprimanded her a little the other day because of the incident with Hatsune...
I don't think she's such a weak woman who would run away from that.
I understand. I'll search for her around here!
Otoha...
Presented by Masurenai Fansubs
Second night
With that, this makes five victims.
Indiscriminate murders which don't have any relationship with one another.
The only clue is the crow feathers that were left on the crime scene.
Damn...
Otoha, I will definitely find out who's the murderer.
Master.
Nee-san, I'm sorry! I will leave immediately.
It's fine. You can take your time.
Since that kind of thing happened, we have already closed for the day.
U-Umm...
Is it all right for me to keep you company?
Eh? B-But...
When one is depressed, they'd want to be together with another person.
Does that not apply to you as well, Master?
I was happy.
That you are able to pledge sincerely in front of the policemen that you will catch the murderer of Otoha.
I suppose that even a girl like her would have someone thinking deeply of her.
At the very least, please let me show my gratitude.
N-No, there is no need to thank me-
What I am able to do now...
...Is only this much.
Nee-san...
It has become really big.
I also wish for the warmth of a man.
Nee-san...
Master, does it pleasure you?
I am very happy.
N-Nee-san...
I'm going to cum soon.
It is all right.
Allow me to be soiled with you!
Nee-san, this time it's my turn...
Master, it feels good...
This time, allow my lower mouth to taste yours.
Master!
Nee-san's pussy is moving around and is getting really tight...
Nee-san's pussy is awesome...
Harder... Please pound me harder!
Master's hotness feels so good...
Amazing, Nee-san's cunt is sucking me so hard...
Nee-san...
Master!
Such a thing has really happened?
Geez....
I've really made Otoha suffer.
So, about the job this time...
It's all right, I understand.
Eh?
You are going to capture the hated killer who murdered Otoha-san, right?
Well... it is like that, but...
Please rest assured. I shall assist you as well.
It's not that. Before I finish this job, you... well...
Can you please stay at your mother's place obediently-
You sure have guts to sneak away!
Okay, I see.
A beautiful woman of Shugo's tastes, huh?
But since you already have me, I won't forgive you for dating other girls this early in the morning.
U-Um... This person is...
I'm Shugo's lover.
Eh!?
No, she isn't!
She's...
...My idiotic little sister!
Shu-san!
This way!
Ahh, it's delicious.
Say, Shu-san. What kind of relationship does that girl have with you?
I heard that she was his little sister.
Right, Shugo-san?
Y-Yeah...
He's my elder brother, yet girls are all over him, huh?
M-More importantly, what happened to your schooling?!
Some trivial stuff came up.
More importantly, I'm interested in that incident.
Dissecting the bodies and then disemboweling them.
You're quite an admirable person, aren't you?
Hey now...
There should be some clues, right?
All there was were crow feathers left on the crime scene.
Actually, I'm rather intrigued by that.
You're going to start talking crap again, right?
Have you heard of the book "Love Prison" before?
"Love Prison"?
A book pertaining to curses?
It's the prophetic manuscript of the Senri Shrine.
It speaks of humanity's destruction and rebirth, as well as salvation.
The extreme fictional contents seem to have affected a large branch of humanity.
Moreover, the whole incident this time seems to have been predicted.
That's absurd.
Takashiro-san.
The police have contacted me.
Oh, damn!
Umm... who are you?
I am an instructor at Kayou Academy. My name is Fukamizu.
Then you are Nana's homeroom teacher...?
My apologies. I'm Nana's elder brother...
Well, about the police...
I received information that she left the dorms last night without permission and drank wine all night.
And so, I'm here for her.
I can't believe you!
Now Shugo, I'll be waiting for your report on this case.
I'm sleepy.
Geez...
Is something the matter?
N-No...
Shugo-sama!
Is that you, Hatsune?
Yes.
There is a letter for you.
Ayasaki?
Takako-chan!
Shugo-sama!
Long time no see, huh.
Wonder how many years it's been.
You've really become a lady.
You're the same as ever, Shugo-sama.
But that was a surprise.
You're actually Nana-chan's classmate.
I was surprised as well.
You were actually Nana-san's elder brother.
I couldn't hold back, so I sent you a letter, and...
I don't mind.
Really?
Of course.
So cold...
I am getting married.
What?!
My fiancé is the only son of a former financial clique.
Though it was actually my father's selfish decision...
Well then...
I'm sorry. This doesn't have anything to do with you, right?
Ah, it's already this late...
You have a curfew, right?
Yes, my school has very strict regulations.
I'll walk you back to the dorms.
All right, thank you!
That incident has become the topic of the dorms.
Really, even for such a wealthy ladies' school?
Of course.
Especially for Nana-san, who's all excited about it.
She even went to the crime scene of the incident to do some detective work...
You should never get involved with her!
We didn't make it in time, huh?
It's all right.
Over here.
We can get in through here.
Nana-san told me about this.
Maybe you should reconsider your friendship with Nana-chan for your own sake.
Shugo-sama, this way!
T-This is...
Shugo-sama, hurry up!
We're safe now. No one will come in here.
Say, Takako-chan.
Yes?
I don't think there's a need for me to come in too...
Well then, I'll be off.
Takako-chan...
I don't understand.
Eh?
I don't know whether or not I should just abide by my father's orders.
I feel worried.
Takako-chan...
At the very least, I want to be with you for tonight.
Please save me...
Please save me.
Yura...
Shugo-sama...
Yura!
No, I'm Takako.
You're beautiful.
I'm happy.
No...
It feels good...
Shugo-sama... Don't do that...
Don't!
Shugo-sama's... Is so manly.
I actually wanted to do this more skillfully...
Shugo-sama, what should I do to pleasure you?
T-Then...
Well, can you suck on it deeper?
Yes!
I'm sorry, I seem to have licked it a little too deeply.
Is this really fine, Takako-chan?
Yes.
Since I can give my virginity to Shugo-sama...
Are you all right?
Yes.
My body... My body is...!
Shugo-sama...
Something... Something is coming out!
You're really beautiful.
It's embarrassing...
Amazing... You're amazing, Takako-chan.
It's so tight.
I'm really happy...
Draperies
Oh, Rin! About selling yourself... won't you consider it?
No, Master! I will be scolded by the landlady.
I want to have a baby with you.
Geez, Master. Please stop doing this.
With that body of yours, having any number of babies won't be a problem at all!
You're Rin-san, known as "Snow White", right?
You're Nana-san's teacher...
Takashiro-sama is waiting for you.
Y-Yes?
Master!
What happened, Nee-san?
Rin has...
Rin hasn't returned after going out for a house-visit!
Thank you.
Geez, where did she go?!
"Bizarre Murder Case: Mysterious Corpse with Unnatural Cause of Death"
Don't tell me... Rin, too?!
Even if Rin was taken away by the murderer, this place is too conspicuous to be the scene of the crime.
She must've been murdered somewhere else before being brought here.
But how did he do it...?
Moreover, what exactly did those black crow feathers left in the crime scene signify...
It couldn't be...
Whatever the case, this place is too...
Anyway, I have to check it out.
This is...!
This smell is...!
Rin!
T-This is...
A corpse...
No way... This is too...!!
Where am I...?
This is troublesome...
This place is supposed to be restricted to uninvolved people.
Why?!
Why are you, an ecclesiastic, doing such horrible things?!
That mark is...
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
How cute!
I have injected you with a specially concocted medicine.
From today on, you will live only to comfort me.
It feels good! Really good!
Stop it...
I can't hold it in anymore!
From now on, you shall forever attend to me...
W-What are you going to do?!
For that, I shall cut your legs-
Damn!
So you did this, killing Otoha and disemboweling her!
This is for the sake of "The Rebirth"!
What did you say?
You wait there!
Rin!
The moment I entered the carriage,
I already knew who the murderer was.
A faint smell of blood was left on the carriage.
That's the evidence of it transporting corpses.
But, why? To think that such a model citizen could commit serial murder...
Fukamizu's body was infertile.
She had an endometrial cyst when she was young, so it seems that she had her uterus removed.
From that point on, feelings of malediction against young women started to build up in Fukamizu.
Moreover, she was under the impression that if she ate the uteri of young women,
she thought that she would be able to have babies.
That is the ceremony known as "The Rebirth".
Although the police seem to have linked all the serial murders to her, I don't think that that's the case.
What do you mean?
Fukamizu was a believer of Senri Shrine.
It means that the case will continue, Kazuna.