So hot...
My body...
Is burning up...
Why is this happening...?
Inside there... is semen...
Hot sticky semen...
No. I have to get a grip.
The water's so cool and refreshing.
Hey, girl over there!
Your face is all red, what's up?
Maybe it's sunstroke.
You should let us take care of you.
It's nothing!
If you're really fine you should have spoken up earlier then!
No, stop it, I'm--
No!
It's all ready.
Here I go!
No, stop!
I'll be taking dat ass.
No! My pussy and ass at the same time...!
Take them out, please!
Take them out!
Why does it feel so good when I don't want them to...?
Don't! Don't!!
No!
Don't play with my nipples, they're too sensitive~!
I don't want this... I don't want to be raped by men I don't know!
But why, why does it feel so good?
Huh... where am I...
S-stop!
Don't! Don't!!
Stop it!
Sui...
It hurts!
Don't touch my breasts!
It feels so wiggly and gross!
No! Save me, Takeru-chan!
Sui!
They're pushing into my... womb!
My womb is being raped...
Takeru-chan...
It hurts!
No!
It's peeing, it's peeing inside me!
So hot, my stomach's so heavy...
I'm going to burst! Please, let me pee!
I came while peeing...
How could this have...
happened to us...
- MeiohSubs Present -
Translation: Barbar of Damascus | QC/Timing: EchelonV
Inyouchuu
Shoku
Volume 1
Alright! Fun island vacation, here we come!
You know very well we're here to work, so don't forget it!
We're on official Kuroneko Brigade demon extermination duty.
Come on, don't worry so much!
It's summer after all!
A little job like this'll be nice and easy.
That's why we brought Sui along with us, isn't it?
Eh? But I'm not nearly as strong as Takeru-san or Mikoto-san.
I'm not an exterminator or a warrior...
That's true, but your spirit-sensing ability is the best, Sui.
We're counting on you!
Correct. There have been a number of disappearances on this island since about a year ago.
This island completely depends on the tourism trade,
so if this kind of thing gets out to the public, the island's economy will be ruined.
I see.
So this is what we were called out from Tokyo for.
Understood. We'll be taking your case.
Oh! Thank you very much!
It would be an honor if you were to stay in my guest house.
Okay, let's get going!
Why do we have to go in the middle of the niiight~
Ookami-san is sleeping!
Shh, that's exactly why.
There's something odd about this job.
So we can't let our guard down, even if the job seems easy.
That's how it goes.
Everything is according to plan.
What is it?
Mikoto-chan, I feel horrible.
Are you okay?
Such a strong demonic aura...
There's something very wrong with this island.
It's coming from over there!
That's...
Mikoto-chan, something's inside the shrine!
A barrier?
IT'S A TRAP!
I, Shiratori, call to you.
Answer my command. Appear before me,
Vanquishing Blade, Raitou!
It regenerated?
How about that?
Takeru, are you okay?
I'm fine, Mikoto.
More importantly, we have to find the core.
Core?
If we destroy its core, it should stop regenerating.
But how do we...?
That's... up to Sui.
Me?
Sui, you understand, right?
Your spirit-sensing ability is much higher than mine or Mikoto's.
Hurry up and find the core!
I'll try!
Takeru!
Sui! There's no more time!
Found it!
That one!
Alright!
Takeru, are you okay?
Unnhh... mostly.
Mikoto-chan, let's go back.
Okay, let's retreat for the time being.
Mikoto-chan, is Takeru-chan okay?
She's just a little dazed from the demonic energy.
All she needs is some rest and she'll be fine in the morning.
No good. I can't stop at all.
Is this because of the pollen from those demonic flowers?
Gonna cum...
Takeru-chan was perfectly fine the next day.
We decided to spend the day acting like we were just having fun
just to throw off anyone that may have been watching us.
Itadakimasu!
Here I go!
Mikoto-chan, over there!
So good~!
Uhm, you ARE just acting, right, Mikoto-chan?
Takeru, are you okay?
Yeah.
I should be able to resist the demonic aura with this.
Okay. Let's do it!
There doesn't seem to be anything here now.
Really? What a bust.
Be that as it may, make sure not to let your guard down.
Let's go.
What the hell?
Are these the girls that disappeared?!
No. These girls are just bait.
So we were right about you.
Bait? For what?
There happens to be a shortage of girls with strong spiritual power.
So at the command of the Master, we made up this whole "disappearing people" story.
This way, we can attract the attention of people with strong spiritual power.
People like you three.
"...The Master?" And who is this "Master?"
You'll see for yourself soon enough.
Sui!
Save me, Mikoto-chan!
Takeru, what are you--?
Your little sister sure is easy to manipulate!
Mikoto~!
Sui!
Little lady, weren't you going to "not let your guard down" when you came in here?
That's not what...
It's okay, there's no need to hide your desires anymore.
You can take off these troublesome wards.
But if I do that...
Then you can have what you really desire!
Sis, I'm sorry, but I can't take it anymore!
Takeru...
Go ahead, tell her how you really feel.
Yes...
I'm a perverted bitch who loves semen and fucking...
Really...
Please...
Please... violate me...
Very well. Come here.
Takeru, what are you--?!
STOP IT! DON'T TOUCH THAT!
Shut up.
It smells so good, so delicious...
Takeru...
I'm cumming!
Semen... so delicious...
I want more, please...
Ahhh, I'll give you more. This time it'll be inside you!
Hurry! Hurry!
Please give me semen!
Here you go!
It's good! So good!
It feels so good!
Takeru...
Good... so big... pushing on my womb...
So good... my womb feels so good!
Sis. Sis.
Sis!
How do you feel, Sis?
How do you think I feel?
What, I can't move...
I'll make you feel good very soon.
Stop it! Get away from there!
Your pussy has such a delicious smell, Sis.
And it's so soft and pink like a baby.
Don't say such embarassing things!
And here... a tiny cherry blossom bud.
It's such a shame that you can't see it.
It's so cute and adorable.
But we need to get ready.
I've got something really good to give you. Bear with me, okay?
Takeru? That... what is that?
No! Takeru, stop it!
No! Something's moving down there!
What's happening to me?!
Amazing. What a wonderfully perverted thing!
N-no!
It can't be! This can't be happening!
Nooo! Nooooo!
Nooooo~!
Stop it!
Takeru...
Don't!
With this, Sis, now you belong to me.
I'll never let you go.
I love you, Sis.
No! No! No!!
Don't touch that place!
Go ahead and cum in your little sister's hand, Sis!
No! Something... something's happening!
No! This isn't right!
Nooooo~!
You sure came, Sis.
Takeru, I'm a girl...
But I'm not a girl anymore... not like this...
Sis, it's okay, you just came with your manly parts.
I'll make sure to make you into a woman, Sis.
Nooooo~!
Sis, I'll finally get to be inside you.
Don't push in there!
I'm so happy!
It hurts!
Y-YAMATO!!!
This is... what Sis feels like on the inside.
So warm and tight, I'm melting!
Takeru... Takeru...
I'm cumming!
So good...
I... I... I don't care anymore...
Takeru...
Sis...
Delicious... Takeru's penis is so delicious!
Takeru... Takeru's pussy feels so good!
So happy... Sis' penis is filling me up inside!
Deeper!  I want it deeper!
I love you! I love you!
Sis!
Takeru... Takeru, your penis is all the way in my womb!
No more!
My breasts feel so good!
My nipples are so sensitive!
I'm inside you, Sis.
Takeru, it's so good!
So hot and slick.
I can't stop. I can't stop!
It's so good...
My body won't stop!
Fuck me!
Fuck your sister's pussy with your penis, Takeru!
Takeru, you feel so good!
Melting... Melting...
I can feel it in my womb!
Sis...
So good, I'm gonna cum!
Alright, I'll let you cum, but on one condition
you belong to me from now on, Sis.
I'll do it, I'll only belong to you, Takeru!
Please, fuck me!
I'm so happy. I love you so much, Sis!
Amazing, your penis is pushing up so far in me, Takeru!
It feels so good! So good!
So good!
Your pussy is so great, Sis, I can't hold it anymore!
No more!
I'm cumming, Sis! Together with you!
No! I'm cumming!
So amazing!
Takeru! Takeru!
Sis! Sis!
Sis...
Takeru...
No!
What is this?!
Mikoto-chan, Takeru-chan, what...
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN TO US??!