Wait for me, my little darlings...
I'm bringing something tasty for you...
I'm home!
Just a moment more, I've brought food for you!
So much semen is coming out of my womb!
Eat up! I've brought you all semen!
Go on and eat your semen, everyone!
It's coming out of my ass too...
There's a lot of semen in my ass, uh...
...still coming out.
It came out.
Semen.
It... all came out...
Tugging on my breasts...
I want you to touch more than just my nipples...
Put it in me...
Put all of it in me!
Too much!
Womb! In my womb!
Cumming, gonna cum!
My womb, fucking my womb!
Translation: Barbar of Damascus | QC/Timing: EchelonV
- MeiohSubs Present -
Inyouchuu
Shoku
Volume 2
Dammit...
Stop it!
It'd be best if you stopped resisting.
I never thought that the brainwashing would wear off after only one day.
But you know, your sister gave birth to these slugs.
That means they're your nephews and nieces.
Mikoto?
What have you done with Mikoto?
She should be giving birth to more bugs right about now.
Tugging on my breasts...
Put all of it in me!
Too much!
In my womb!
Cumming, gonna cum!
My womb, fucking my womb!
I'm giving birth again to so many babies...
She's raped by tentacles every night, and gives birth in the mornings.
And then, during the day...
No... don't take pictures...
She collects the semen that the bugs eat.
That is her purpose now.
How could you...
How could you be so cruel!?
"Cruel?"
What about you? You're the one who brought her into this kind of life.
That was because... the demonic aura...
Was it? Or was it just your true nature?
It... it... it might be...
But I don't want those bugs. I just want this.
Please, take this hard throbbing cock...
and fuck me.
Ohhh? You sure are honest.
I am... always honest...
Not!
A kid? In a place like this?
Listen, this place is dangerous. I'll take you to a safe place.
The exit!
They've gotten so big...
There's no way I can go back to living a normal life with these...
Ehh? Sui, have your breasts grown?
Huh? Us being captured, and all those things that happened...
They were all a dream!
Of course! Things like that can't possibly happen!
What are you mumbling about?
Come on, cheer up!
I've been wondering about this since I saw you in your swimsuit...
Uhm, that...
this... it's a little...
actually, my cup size did go up.
Ahhh! M-Mikoto-chan!?
How unfair, Sui! You...
M-Mikoto-chan!
Sui!
Don't, don't touch those! We're both women!
Exactly. It's okay because we're both women!
Mikoto-chan!
Not there!
It feels like your boobs are getting softer, Sui.
They might be getting even bigger too!
That sort of thing isn't possible...
Will milk come out if I squeeze?
Of course there won't be any milk!
Mikoto-chan, it feels weird!
My boobs feel so hot...
No way... I don't even have any babies...
But milk is coming out...
Sui, your milk is so warm.
And!...
It's so sweet and rich, so delicious!
No! Don't, don't drink my milk!
Takeru-chan, help me!
Oh, for goodness sake, Mikoto.
Are you really going to keep something as sexy and delicious as this all to yourself?
Takeru-chan!
Stop it, you two!
It's so delicious.
Isn't it?
Don't wanna stop...
If you keep suckling my boobs won't stop growing!
So much milk is coming out!
Mikoto-chan, Takeru-chan...
Stop it! Stop it!
What the?!
Nooooo~!
Looks like you woke up.
That voice, it can't be... are you...?
Indeed!
I am called Meioki!
"Meioki?"
[Translator's Note: Meioki = Hell-King-Demon]
You do seem pretty strong, for a fake oni.
But you're far off from calling yourself a king of Hell.
As expected from such a strong demon hunter.
Thanks to you, I've lost my most important minion.
Minion?
An earthquake unsealed me many years ago.
Since then, all the residents of this island have worshipped me.
So all those stories about the disappearances...
Indeed. It was all a trap to lure in fools like you.
So that I may consume your power,
in order to become a true oni!
Do you think I'm going to let myself be eaten by you?!
Oh, it seems that you've misunderstood.
People with your pathetic level of power are only good for breeding bugs!
What the hell?!
Now, you sisters will become my bugs' incubators!
Where did he?
Takeru... Takeru!
Mikoto!?
Mikoto, you're okay!
Were you worried about me?
Mikoto, what are you-
Sis...
What's wrong, Takeru?
Sis, those are...
These children were worried about you too.
They came along to comfort you.
Sis, stop it.
Why? These children are so cute and obedient.
Hey, don't crowd.
We have to make Takeru feel good first!
Takeru, don't be afraid. Just leave it up to me.
Stop it, Sis!
Your body doesn't seem to agree.
Amazing, Takeru.
Your pussy is clinging so tightly to this child when it slides out.
And your clitoris is so erect, just like a little jewel!
So good! I can't think!
That's right. We don't have to think about anything anymore if we stay here forever!
These children... so good!
So many inside me!
Feels so good!
The child... in my womb... is also inside Takeru's womb!
Sis, we're about to have babies together. So good!
Ahh! It's cumming in my womb!
Sis, I'd like some semen too...
Takeru, I'll give the semen in me to you...
Come closer to me!
The semen is pouring into me!
Take it! And then!...
Give birth to lots of babies!
Mikoto-chan... Takeru-chan...
There's no way I can lead a normal life now.
Not with breasts like these...
Indeed!
You will spend the rest of your life here.
Oni?!
I've been waiting a long time for a woman with strong spiritual power like you.
What do you mean?
The disapperances were all a trap that I set.
Then... what happened to Mikoto and Takeru?
I have no interest in fucking those demon hunters.
Now they belong to my bugs.
How could you...?
But you're different.
I must violate you in order to obtain your power.
Now, let me satisfy you!
It's poking at my pussy!
What's going on?!
My power is to make women aroused.
Why?
Why are there two penises!?
And they're so big...
So big, there's no way they'll fit!
But, something this big would certainly feel good...
Hahahaha. I'm going to fuck your organs!
Burning! I'm burning up! Stop it!
So big! Digging so deeply inside me!
They're rubbing together inside me!
Amazing!
Feels too good!
Excellent. Your power is entering my penis.
A most splendid power!
Good! So good! Feels so good!
My insides are burning up!
Here we go. Take it all!
Hehehe, and now that you're all used up
it's time for you to take your place with the others as a bug incubator.
Tentacles... wiggling...
...wiggling inside my tits!
Breasts... breasts... feels so good!
Delicious... tentacle semen...
Delicious...
My stomach is moving...
They'll be born... they'll be born soon!
We're giving birth to more babies!
I've given birth again! Our little babies...
Healthy little babies, come get your milk!
There's alot of milk, so don't fight over it!
Cumming again!
Yes! Yes!!
Is it time to be impregnated again?
That's not the right hole!
So rough!
You're shooting so much again
Semen is going up my ass!
Please continue...
More... make me feel good some more!
I can't think anymore!
Cumming~!!!!
- MEIOKI WINS -
(Good end?)