Kibun Kibun
Kibun
Presented by MOT
It's only been half a year since we've started going out.
But...
Everyday...
as I come to cook breakfast
I become more accustomed to...
his apartment’s kitchen.
This kind of thing makes me happy.
Hey, it's morning, Kenji-kun!
Ouch, that hurts, the chopsticks are sticking into my stomach!
I-I'm sorry, Kenji-kun!
It's sticking in!
Um, my name is Nojima Nami.
Ah! The chopsticks!
In case you didn't know I am the main character, hope we get along well together.
Chopsticks!?
I'm sorry!
Then, I'll be leaving first. You'd better hurry up.
Hurry up, huh? That girl doesn't understand a thing.
That won't ever change.
Good morning!
Look, he's late again.
Geez...
Hey Nami, he lives alone and spends all his time at his part time job right?
I bet you're at it every night.
No, what are you saying, stupid.
Was I wrong?
Umm, well, about once a week.
You're so young but it's only once a week?
I see.
Well, if I was able to I would, but...
He always just jumps on me suddenly.
He doesn't even try to get me into the mood.
His apartment is in this neighborhood right?
Why don't you go there in the morning so you can go to school together?
That should be fine but...
But?
Well, if we're seen leaving together it will just look like we're coming out of a Love Hotel.
But you know, it may be harsh on you but,
If you ask me, Kenji Owada doesn't suit you.
That's not true!
I think you should definitely change horses.
You think?
Is there really a person who suits me better than Kenji-kun?
We were kidding.
Late again today.
What's wrong with you guys?
Damn it! Only if you didn't exist!
She may be a rarity who you'd want to protect but...
Good luck, Kenji-kun!
Do your best, don't lose!
Really, what's so good about this slow poke of a girl?
Kenji-kun!
Well, whatever the case, she's made her choice.
Yahoo~ Kenji-kun. Are you still alive?
Kenji-Kun, don't you dare lose.
But of all people, why him?
What? Did you say something?
Nothing at all!
Level change!
How boring.
Just when you get a day off work, all you do is play games.
There's hardly any time for the two of us.
Didn't I say we'd meet again tomorrow?
Well, yeah, but I was thinking about well, more like...
Oh that's what you meant? Why didn't you just say so?
W-w-w-wait!
No! Not this suddenly!
Why do you always resist when I get to this part?
Hey, just stay calm.
They'll hear us.
Don't!
Oh, sounds like trouble.
What is it? Again?
Kenji-kun, you idiot.
If it's so sudden I can't really tell if he likes me or not.
I don't think he suits you.
I wonder what I mean to Kenji-kun?
Nami, got a minute?
What is this?
I failed.
I'll be redoing the test today after school.
No way!
You idiot, what about our date?
I'm sorry! We'll have to do it some other time!
Geez...
But I'm glad it wasn't during my part-time shift.
The boss would be furious.
Due to unforeseen circumstances, please wait.
She's the type who can protect herself, huh?
Hello everybody, I will now hand out the test papers.
Kenji-kun!
Hey~ Hey~
Looks like you're feeling better.
You're heartless!
That's what you get!
The angry one is me!
Good luck~
Mister Owada, sit down.
Yeah.
Later.
Nami!
You idiot! You wanna die?
That was close, geez...
Oh? Kiku-chan?
At least look at the traffic lights.
Anyway you're always...
Kenji-kun, why are you here?
"Why" you say? You know...
Oh, her panties are yellow today.
Ah, Kenji-kun!
Ambulance! Ambulance!
I'm sorry Kenji-kun.
About what?
Kenji-kun got hurt because I was daydreaming.
You've always been inclined to daydream.
You were worried about me, right?
Enough to jump from the second floor.
That made me really happy.
What's up?
I love you.
Can we stay like this a bit longer?
Good morning.
Good morning, Nami. You're cutting it close again today.
That's because I go visit Kenji-kun every morning to cook him breakfast.
Kenji-kun is running late again this morning, geez...
If he's eating it after Nami made it then...
I really do think Kenji-kun and I are made for each-other,
and one day we'll be able to support each other’s weak points, I think it's wonderful.
Ow.
It's just a matter of waking up 10 minutes earlier!
You're going to ask him to wake up 10 minutes earlier?
If Nami gets even slower and starts waking me up later, I'm a goner.
Tomorrow is already the start of summer vacation,
this means I'll have a lot more time with Kenji-kun.
I'm home.
Welcome back!
Nami,
I thought I told you to use the fan when you're alone.
I thought it would be better if the room was nice and cool when you returned!
You idiot, idiot, idiot.
S-sorry.
When the room is this cool, I don't really want to go to my part time job.
Then why don't you take a day off?
I can't do that!
What the heck are you doing?
But, you're always so busy and we don't have any time to meet up.
Kenji-kun, do you not like this?
It's not bad.
What a boring reaction.
Even though it's summer vacation, you're always at work,
and I come every day, I just wanted a bit more...
Hey you!
Honestly, you're so dirty!
What are you expecting from me?
Um, well.
For Kenji-kun to gently hold me from behind,
and in those arms I lie lovingly,
not understanding whether this time of happiness is a fleeting moment or eternity.
And then both of us turn to face each other,
lips ready, we slowly close our eyes...
Wow! Romantic!
But we're going to do it after that right?
That's not the point here!
But you're teasing me now right?
I am not!
Is this...?
Just as I thought, you're not wearing a bra.
Umm, well, it was hot.
Don't make excuses, you really were teasing me.
I said I'm not!
There was no need to make you wet.
Can you raise your legs yourself?
Yeah.
More, more.
No, I... want Kenji-kun's....
Alright.
Hurry...
Why did you stop?
I forgot that my job starts at 8 o'clock!
Sorry, just finish yourself off.
I don't care anymore, Kenji you idiot!
Die!
Damn!
That Nami, not answering me since then.
You lost your temper.
Kayama-san?
Did you have a fight with your girlfriend?
Umm, well, a little one.
Hmm, same as me.
Hey, Kenji-kun, with us both being so sad, why don't we comfort each other?
S-stop joking!
My girlfriend is the sad one, probably.
You're just trying to look cool even though you're feeling down.
I bet your girlfriend isn't sad at all.
He-Hey!
I was half joking at first but...
What do you think? I'm confident in my looks,
plus you're kinda my type since you look like my boyfriend so...
And...
You're already like this, it doesn't matter what you say now, it's not going to convince me.
Well, that doesn't have anything to do with it.
This thing getting hard is like a reflex, I don't intend to justify myself every time it happens.
Also...
Also?
If I'm going to do it, it's best with her.
Yes, hello.
Shinichi!
Can we meet? When?
What? Her boyfriend?
Idiot, you could have at least called earlier.
I wonder if she also cries because she's lonely.
Huh? Kenji-kun welcome back.
Yeah.
Do you have to go to your next shift soon?
Huh, yeah.
I didn't use the air conditioner.
Really?
Thinking about it...
If you can barely afford your living expenses, why is it you have an air conditioner?
That's because...
I took almost everything that was in my room when I moved out of my parent's house.
I also took off the air conditioner.
I sold all the unessential stuff, then combined it with my savings and rented this flat.
And with that the mystery of why you don't have a bath is solved.
It's a bit bothersome after sex.
Sorry...
It was just after I moved in here that we started going out,
I would have got a better place if I knew you would be here.
NO!
That would mean you would have to work more than you do now, right?
Which means we wouldn't be able to meet even as much as we do now.
I don't want that!
Hey Nami, show me your eyes!
No...
Nami!
No, stop, don't you have work Kenji-kun?
I don't want to be left halfway through like you did earlier.
Don't worry, Kenji Owada is off sick today.
I'll call in later.
Sorry, but you know, you weren't the only sad one.
Kenji-kun.
Nami.
It's been a while so you'll have to show it all to me.
Open them, Nami.
No, it's so embarrassing.
What are you saying? The more embarrassed you are the better it feels.
What!? That's not true.
So, what's this then?
That's...
You're starting to feel good, right?
Say it!
Yeah.
You're already so wet, how dirty.
Hey, Kenji-kun, I want it.
Yeah.
Fire!
Hey, this apartment is on fire!
Is there anyone inside?
That room's lights are on.
Fire!?
It's good that it was only a small fire.
Yeah, but it still ended halfway though.
Hey, is it okay to hold hands?
Huh? Yeah sure.
Kenji-kun, look, the stars are so beautiful.
You're right.
Hey, Kenji-kun.
Nothing.
Kenji-kun's taking his time.
Kenji-kun!
I-I-I'm sorry!
What happened?
I, um, sorry, Kenji, no, Owada-kun was supposed to be working today so...
He suddenly took today off.
Why don't I know about that?
Saying such things so suddenly.
Well speaking to me won't help.
Thank you very much!
Wait a minute!
You wouldn't happen to be...
Kenji-kun! Why did you take a day off so suddenly, I waited for you!
Hey Nami! Perfect timing,
I was just having some trouble finding my textbooks for the summer homework.
Don't tell me...
You took a day off just to do your homework!?
You can't make time for me but you can make time for homework!? Is that it!?
Kenji-kun you idiot!
These are...
My textbooks?
I thought you would be busy at work, so I did them all for you.
You'll spend the rest of the holiday with me, right?
Of course I will.
So huge, so pretty.
This is the first time I've been to a pool in a hotel.
I was harsh towards Kenji-kun earlier, so take this a token of my apology.
We'll have to thank Kayama-san.
But of all places, I didn't think it would be here.
Did you say something?
No, it's nothing, more importantly, how long are you planning on wearing that?
Well, it's embarrassing.
Huh?
This will be my first time in front of you in a swimsuit so...
Don't be stupid, what are you all embarrased about?
You've shown me much more embarrassing poses naked.
You're the stupid one!
That's like a whole different thing! Won't you learn already!
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Huh? Kenji-kun?
Kayama-san?
What? You came here so quickly.
Hey it's Kenji-kun.
Thank you very much for the tickets.
Don't worry I got them free.
What are you looking at?
Just as I thought, this girl is really cute!
Right, right?
So this girl is Kenji-kun's girlfriend, right?
Such a waste, for a guy like him.
But from my point of view she's an idiot.
She's so slow all the time, and the way she's quick to sulk is such a pain.
Only an idiot would praise her as being cute.
W-wait up Nami-chan!
Well, he's the real idiot here.
It's obvious at a glance.
What are you doing?
Well, anyone would get self-concious of their breasts if talked about like that.
I wonder why it's like that with Kenji-kun.
He's goes so far as to tease the girl he likes, he's not gown up at all.
I think I understand why he does it, but...
Hey, Nami-chan, I wasn't going to say anything but...
It was just a joke so don't be angry, okay?
Well, a little while ago, Kenji-kun and I...
Kenji-kun.
W-what do you think of my swimsuit?
W-what do I think...?
What's wrong?
Kenji-kun, I heard you refused Kayama-san.
So you really do like me?
What? Could it be that you heard this from Kayama-san?
Yeah.
No, don't run!
I know you're embarrassed, so just answer me with "Yes" or "No".
Is what you said to Kayama-san true?
Yes.
And my swimsuit?
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
All Yes.
Answer me properly!
This is my answer.
W-why has it gotten big?
It became like this when I saw you in your swimsuit.
Well, it's like...
I know it's better to tell you all the details no matter how small they are.
But you know, well, give me a break here.
Well, I'll let you off, but just today.
We're getting out.
This way.
They left, I wonder if they managed to make up?
This place doesn't get used during the week.
Kenji-kun, why do you know that?
This window is a perfect magic mirror, it just looks like a mirror from the other side.
Have a look, you can see the pool down there.
Nami, why do you think I chose this place?
I wanted to see how you responded in a place where it feels like we're being watched.
Wow, it's running all the way down to your ankles.
This is great.
It'll slide in if you're this wet.
No way, it went in so easily.
Nami you're off balance, stand up straighter.
But, my legs are feeling so weak.
Press up against the glass.
More.
Kenji-kun, my eyes met with someone below.
You're just imagining it, it's a coincidence.
This magic mirror is perfect.
Or not, if I remember correctly there is one place where you can see through.
No way, is it possible someone is watching us do it?
No.
That's just, don't look, it's embarrassing, no, I'm going to cum.
Kenji-kun hurry, you'll be late for school.
In the end, the rest of the holidays were spent doing homework.
It would be too obvious I did it.
I wonder why?
Door and windows closed.
Alright, shall we go?
The self I didn't even know was inevitably revealed to me.
I never knew I was so...
Dirty.
But I think it's fine just the way it is.
There are many things which haven't chaged but everything feels right.
That's why...