With this, the reaction should work, but...
...a-ara?!
What was that? Geez...
It won't work like it used to.
Wh-whoa!
Why did this have to happen at a place like this?
Eh?  “Since I’m here, I should show them a little more service?”
I-I got it already...
H-Here.
I don’t want to do it, but it’s fine if you look.
Really, this is so immoral.
Huh?
I wonder what this could be...
I didn’t see this before the explosion.
Huh?!
Wh-what is this?!
Could this be?
A love potion?!
Hatsu
Inu
This is a free fansub. Not for sale, rent or auction.
Strange Kind of Woman
~again~
Sample.2
F-Fujino..
I-is it okay to eat this?
Funjino's breasts are delicious...
Somehow... it's even harder than usual...
Eh?
This too... it's alright to eat it?
F-Fujino... I'm already...
A-amazing! The cream is so slippery.
It's the first time it's felt like this.
C-crap, it feels too good...
I can't... hold on... like this...
It's finished!
This potion, if Fukaya drinks it...
Ahhhh... Really, I think we overdid it a little yesterday…
Anyone who drinks this love potion would have to fall in love with me.
Now Fujino won’t have a hold over him in bed!
Alright! With this, Fukaya will be mine!
Ara?
It's no good.
I just don't have an appetite today.
This is strange...
I didn’t expect for anything weird to happen, but…
Eh, Fujino?
H-hey, this is bad.
Sorry, Fujino.
I’m just a little tired today.
D-don’t worry!
If I rest tonight, I’ll get my energy back.
Why?!
Why is it...?!
After watching all these “young gentlemen” videos…
Why?!
Could it be...
I really can’t get it up anymore!?
Hmmmm...
There are a lot of things it could be, but...
None of them really show up.
How's it going over there?
A-ah, sensei...
Somehow my body’s gotten hot, but…
Here, how about this?
S-sensei!
This here is a special service.
Five minutes of this and I only get a nosebleed.
That hurts.
W-What are you doing so suddenly?
Still, I have no clue what the cause is.
You didn’t eat anything strange, right?
Huh?
Hm?
Mita!
Ah!
And what are you doing at a place like this?
Eh?
N-nothing, I was…
That is...
So it was you again?
Really, you’re giving us only trouble.
I-I was only...
I didn’t really... Fukaya, that is...
I didn’t think it would do that to his penis.
That should be obvious! You always screw me over on purpose!
So, is there any way to fix him up?
I mixed the love potion, but it worked out differently.
I don't know what happened.
Fixing it so soon is a little…
Tha-that can’t be…!
W-what, Fujino?
It can’t be helped, right?
It had such a strong effect!
I-I got it already...
I’ll take responsibility, so there’s no problem, right?
Huh? Responsibility?
How do you plan to do that?
Very well, Fukaya just needs to perk up, right?
Eh?
Alright!
Now that it’s come to this, I’ll teach Fukaya’s penis to stand with my body!
Ehh?!
You’re helping too, Fujino.
H-Hey...
Just what are you planning to do?
Be grateful! We’re giving you a little bit of service.
S-service? But that’s...
Fujino, are you ready for this?
Wait, just what...
Right now, we’re going to show you how we masturbate.
Pay attention!
Ehh?!
Look, h-how is it, Fukaya?
Watch. You’re watching, right?
Stop it, both of you. This is...
No, watch me properly!
I’m suffering this embarrassment for you!
Fujino...
Mita...
Oh no! “That place” is already so drenched.
I think that Fukaya watching is somehow getting me excited...!
A-amazing...
Look, Fujino – Fukaya’s penis is waking up.
Fujino?
I didn't think it would feel this good doing it in front of Fukaya!
Oh no, this is... really good!
I just can’t help feeling good!
Fujino...
You don’t need to... go there...
Just watch... our perverted bodies... and get that penis big!
Fujino!
Can’t hold on!
Fujino, isn’t Fukaya’s dick hard yet?
S-sorry...
Fujino?
I’m... becoming strange.
The grinding back there is making me hot...
Fujino, that’s fine.
You’ve already done enough.
Fujino...!
Fujino...
Mita...
For my sake, they’ve done so much.
Why?
Why can’t I answer those efforts?!
Fukaya!!
Oh my!
Huh?
What is this place?
Why am I here right now?
What’s going on, Fujino?
Those clothes are...
Well, I suppose I can’t say much about clothes...
Fujino...
It’s fine already...
Really, I’m probably already broken.
Fujino?
I want sex only when you and I want it together.
Eh?!
Fu-Fujino?
A dream, huh?
Ah! Th-this is...!
Huh? What?
Right now, when I woke up, this was...
Ehhh?!
W-what does this mean?
I also haven’t the slightest.
I see.
I wonder if the effects didn’t just wear off.
Huh?
I made the medicine,
but it was incomplete and I kinda’ failed...
So that was just a temporary side effect! Definitely...
That means... possibly, that you had no idea what you were doing?
W-well, I suppose you could say it like that...
Wait, Fujino.
Anyways, today isn’t the time to be talking about that.
Yesterday was our service, so today you’re going to make us feel good, right?
You don't mean...?
Here, Fukaya.
Our holes, shove your penis in and make us feel good!
Mita...!
Fujino...!
O-oh crap, amazing!
My clitoris... the grinding is making it sensitive...!
H-hey, Fujino!
Don’t just start moving…
...like that!
Oh, crap...
This feels so good that I’m about to come!
That’s alright!
All over our bodies...
It’s alright to shoot a lot!
No, I can’t hold on!
My hips keep moving!
NO!
Fukaya’s penis has gotten so big, and it’s twitching!
That’s an amazing amount that came out.
Sorry I was so sudden.
What are you talking about?
We’re not anywhere close to finishing this, right?
Well, does it feel good, Fukaya?
Amazing!
What do you say about this...?
You’ll make me come!
It’s completely different from last night.
Two women working me – what is this good feeling?
Fujino... there again?!
Ehhhh?
Fukaya lets out such a cute voice when his ass gets touched.
N-no good...
I... can't hold... like this!
Well then, that’s my cue to give it to you.
It doesn’t look ready to quit.
We’ve also been holding out for this.
It's going in!
I was gunning for this...!
Mita... going so suddenly...!
That’s because... I had to hold it all yesterday!
My pussy or anything, just don’t stop it!
N-no...
I’m letting out such a strange voice…
I’m really feeling it...
Until now... like this...
With Fujino... with Mita...
I didn’t think I’d be having a threesome!
Neither did I!
You can’t just do what you want anymore!
Feels good, it feels good!
I’m becoming strange!
Fujino, do you feel good?
You’re feeling good, right?
Such a lewd face...
Doing this with your boyfriend as you watch…
Is making me really horny!
This… can’t take it… almost there…!
I-it’s fine!
We’re also... about to come!
We’re...
...gonna come...
...together!
Yes!
So...
In the end, you all had a threesome yesterday?
H-hahhh. Well...
Really now. If you don’t show some constraint, you really will break it.
Y-yes, I’ll be careful.
Speaking of which, what’s Mita doing right now?
Eh?
Huh? That’s strange. She was here just now, but...
That was just cooperation because of the last potion.
If we reverse my hypothesis,
then this potion will make his penis energetic.
With this love potion, definitely...
Just you wait, Fujino!
I won’t let you do what want!
IT’S NOT OVER YET!
I'LL CONTINUE!
Seems like, after that, everything’s back to normal.
Fujino!
You were waiting for me?
Again?!
In the end,
I don’t know what to make of Fujino or Mita,
Those strange kinds of women.
Translator: necoyama
Editor: refinder
Timer: hom-chan, refinder
Typesetter: einlanzer
Quality Checkers: einlanzer, refinder, hom-chan
MOT Subs