Hello? Kenji-kun, are you there?
You're the one calling me.
Nami.
Huh?
Am I really good enough for you?
As I am now.
What should have I done?
Get a grip! I'm really angry at you right now!
If you keep saying "Stop this" and "Don't do that" I'll...
I'll just have to break up with you.
I see...
Yeah, you're right, then shall we break up?
K-Kenji-kun...!
Kibun Kibun
Kibun
Presented by MOT
I'm sorry!
Kenji-kun...
Are you here?
So, shall we break up?
There's no way I would say something like that and mean it.
Geez, stupid Kenji!
Where did you disappear to?
I love Kenji-kun so much, so, so much.
Kenji-kun?
Who is... that?
"Who?" It's you, isn't it?
Hey, that's my...!
W-what do you want?
Hey, Kenji-kun...
There, there, I'll put it in now.
Stop it!
This is wrong!
What's wrong about it?
Whenever we did it,
It made you so happy.
How is it?
You feel good, Nami?
There's no way I could be happy, this is weird.
That's me there, but it's not really me.
Do it with me.
Look I've gotten so...
So wet.
Don't do it with that me, make this me feel good.
I don't want to.
We broke up, right?
Well, that was a joke.
Did you think I was joking?
A dream?
Yes?
Hey Nami, you and Owada weren't in school, what are you doing?!
What time do you th...?
Nami...
Are you crying?
I wonder if Kenji-kun hates me?
Welcome!
Table for two.
In the smoking area.
Sure, right this way.
He quit?
So Kenji-kun won't be coming anymore then?
I thought it was a strange phone call.
Kayama-san do you know anything about his whereabouts?
I do.
Hey...
Huh?
What the hell is this?
This is the easiest way to show you what kind of man your brother is.
A pervert?
You wouldn't understand.
This is how I'm fighting...
Against dad.
Pointless.
Are you running away again?
What did you say?
As long as we produce good results, dad will let us do whatever we want.
What I do is none of your business.
No, Kenji-kun.
Let's have fun together.
Right?
Kayama-san!
H-hey...
You wouldn't be cheating if it's just my mouth.
It's gotten hard.
S-Stop this, please!
What a lewd woman.
Huh?
You seduced Owada?
That's...
I see.
Kenji-kun was cheating...
He said that he wouldn't have sex with anyone but me.
You're wrong!
We forced him.
Also he didn't want to either.
But, I guess I'm just making excuses.
If you were just going to make excuses,
wouldn't it have been better not to say anything?
Kenji-kun didn't even tell me that.
That he was cheating.
Hey, Nami!
Kiku-chan, you keep out of this!
Yes.
Listen! He wasn't cheating!
He did it with someone else, is that not cheating?
Kenji-kun's always...
When it comes to sex, Nami is the best.
Nami...
Oh yeah,
Then I wasn't hated by him.
What do you mean?
Um, are you alright with that?
There's no way I could be alright with it.
Um well, do you want to slap me once?
Are you sure about that?
I'm not going to hold back.
Come on then!
I won't be able to let this go just because you let me hit you.
But thank you for telling me.
Are you okay?
It hurts...
I'm so bored...
What's with this grade?
That's easily high enough.
I thought I told you to get more than 90% in every subject.
I tried my best.
Tried your best? That won't get you anywhere in society.
What's important are results.
Look at Shinichi, he always produces good results.
You trying your best is what's called a "pointless effort"
Damn it. Not again.
It's hot~
It's already nearing the end of August but...
I'm going to run out of money soon.
I'm so hopeless.
What the hell... am I doing?
Nami, I want to see you.
It feels like I'm in real trouble.
Nami...
I left home in order to run away from my dad.
But that doesn't mean I'd find an answer simply because I left home.
I wasn't expecting anything.
Not of school,
Or anyone.
How pretty!
Something rare happened.
For me to...
fall in love at first sight.
Nami...
Hey, hey, I'm here, here, here
There's a good boy.
That's dangerous.
Here, look, it's over there, go get it.
You're such a good boy, here.
That's dangerous.
You're so cute.
He wags his tail to get his owner to like him.
That dog, is like Nami.
And I always got mad at her for being like that.
So of course she'd hate me.
You're scary.
You're going to tell Owada how much you love him right?
With my fists.
We're in too far at this point.
Get out here, Kenji!
Nami?
What's with me?
I'm so happy.
This means that I'm that dog.
Just stop it already, Nami.
Shut up!
That Kenji! I'll beat him until he's nothing but bumps and bruises.
You know, Owada's had a really bad influence on you.
You're right! I have to get Kenji-kun to take full responsibility.
Responsibility?
He'll probably be more than happy to.
Nami!
Nami...
Owada, this is really bad timing!
Ken... ji...
Nami!
I'm sorry, Nami.
I'm just a little bit... jealous of them...
Oh, this is a superb view.
Geez~ Idiot.
It feels good.
Don't do it so fast.
Hey!
What's wrong?
I'm tired...
Not yet!
Let me rest a little.
Not a chance!
No!
I'll cum again.
No... don't...
I'm cumming!
Was it alright?
It felt really good.
Not that.
Was it alright not to put on a rubber?
Yeah, I didn't want to be separated from you.
Not even by a thin rubber.
What's the matter, Kenji-kun?
No way, you're embarrassed, that's so cute.
Shut up!
I know! Instead of calling you Kenji-kun, I'll call you Ken-chan.
Don't call me that.
Hey, Ken-chan.
What now?
From now on we'll always be together, right?
Always.
Nami...
H-hey! Nami, you...
Let's do it one more time, Ken-chan.
Graduation. Congratulations!
Hey Matsubuda! Tanou!
Hey, stand up straighter.
Look, Ken-chan, your necktie is...
Hey, cut that out.
Cut it out, Nami.
Everyone's looking you know.
You should button up properly.
Look, your hair is too...
Hey, I'm taking it!
H-hey, Ken-chan!
You won't be in the picture!
We'll always be together!
Wait, Kenji!
Ken-chan, take responsibility properly.
Kibun Kibun
The End