It looks like you drank a
lot of water, Ms. Shiraki.
I'll let you drink a lot
from down here as well.
No! Stop it!
Don't hesitate to
drink a lot, Teacher...
Hurts...
It hurts!
No, stop it!
My stomach will burst!
You have to let us enjoy more.
You're not trying hard
enough, Ms. Shiraki.
No...
Now tell me Ms. Shiraki...
What were you snooping around for?
No!
Bible Black: New Testament
Chapter 4 Recollection
General Hospital
Aki Ichikawa
Spear of Longinus.
General Hospital
What a nightmare...
Since I couldn't take away your virginity,
I think I'll settle with this.
It hurts!
It's hot!
It's coming inside!
The Spear of Longinus...
Phew, it feels so cool.
It's no use resisting.
Give me the Spear of Longinus...
Are you okay?
I need a doctor!
What the hell?
It's embarrassing.
I want yours too.
Sure. Go ahead.
Yuki...
From now on, you will be my eyes and
ears. You're now my loyal servant.
Yes, Jody.
I want you to give it to me, Jody.
Promise me, Yuki.
Yes, I promise.
I will be your loyal servant...
And l promise to help you carry out the
prophecy of the great Aleister Crowley.
Good.
Amazing...
Jody...
Yes, yes, Yuki...
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Resignation
You're dismissing my report as sheer
nonsense and taking me off this case.
Then I have no other choice but to quit.
Thank you very much for
everything, good bye.
What are you planning to do after this?
I'll just keep on investigating
this case on my own.
I see...
But it's gonna be tough if you don't
have the organization backing you up.
Especially with a case like this one.
I really want to solve this case.
The address for the special
investigation agency, Tokken.
You see, the head of
Tokken is named Toru Yuge.
We've known each other since our
days at the police academy.
He said the same thing you
said and left this place.
You can stay in this room for the
time being until Imari comes back.
Yes, thank you very much.
I left the files on your desk.
Let me know what you think later.
Yes sir!
Oh, and stop saluting me like that.
We're not police officers.
Huh?
She's from my school?
She was enrolled as a
student during the year...
When Ms. Kitami transferred
to another school...
What? You're transferring
to another school?
Yes.
I won't be able to see you anymore.
No!
I don't want you to leave!
Yamanishi...
I want you to give me good
memories from this school.
What?
You really like me too?
Don't ask any questions.
It's my first time so...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Do me.
Be gentle with me.
No...
It feels good...
I'm so happy.
Keep on going.
Be gentle with me.
It's embarrassing...
...but I'm happy.
Let me do you now.
No, don't tease me like that.
Feels good.
Does it hurt?
Are you comfortable?
Yes, I'm fine.
But are you feeling comfortable?
Yes, I'm feeling great...Ms. Kitami.
Call me Reika.
O-Okay...
Reika, can I start moving?
Yes.
I'm back.