Truly a very fine specimen.
All we have to do is wait
for the right moment to arrive.
Minase left this book...
Could this be...
So, Miss Imari?
Help me!
Why don't you just be honest.
The more you deny it,
the more worked up you will get.
Help me, Minase!
Imari!
Minase...
...look how big you are.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I can't bear it anymore.
Miss Imari, I'll ask you one more time...
You really don't masturbate?
I do.
I masturbate.
Oh?
How many times a week?
A-About three times a week.
Three times a week!
And you still insisted that you didn't?
No, don't say that!
Not in front of everyone!
I will reward you for being honest.
I'll make you come
many times in front of Minase.
No!
Minase!
Please stop!
This is not normal!
Imari!
Minase, help me, please!
Help me!
Minase!
Imari!
Who do you think gave you your balls?
You are just a coward.
What are you going to do?
Get away from me!
Imari!
No, stop!
No!
Looking good, Miss Imari!
I won't forgive you for this!
Let go of me!
Saeki!
You're even harder than before.
What are you...
Let me go!
Please let me go!
Miss Imari...
...you have too much energy...
...so I'm going to give you a
shot that will calm you down.
This is going to work so well!
Enough with your jokes!
Do you think this is a joke?
So, Minase, why don't you
give Miss Imari a big fat shot?
I can't do that...
Oh, stop lying.
You want to be inside Miss
Imari so bad, you can hardly stand it.
Unfortunately I
can't give you the front...
...but I will give you
the virginity of her ass.
What!
Enough already!
What are you doing?
No!
That's not going to fit in my butt!
Please!
Stop it!
Stop, Saeki!
Stay still, Minase.
I can't hit the mark.
Here goes!
W-Wait!
See, it fits!
M-Minase!
Imari!
I'm sorry.
Oh, come on!
Stop just sitting there and move!
It hurts!
Minase, it hurts!
I can't control my body!
Stop it.
Go on, enjoy it!
Give yourself over to your desire.
It's human nature.
No one can resist pleasure.
See, Minase, Miss Imari
is starting to feel good too.
Go harder and make her feel good.
No Minase, no!
I'm sorry Imari.
I can't stop my body.
Minase...
It's okay...
If it's you...
Since it's you it's okay...
Imari...
Good for you Minase.
Give her everything you have...
Fill up Miss Imari's little ass!
He's coming inside me!
So much of hot come inside me!
Miss Imari...
How did it feel?
To give up your ass
even though you are a virgin?
You are the worst sort of human.
A compliment, thank you!
The devil!
That is the highest compliment!
Relax, Miss Imari.
I will take your virginity eventually.
It's good!
My butt...
Imari!
Minase, you're still here?
You can go home now.
Minase, Miss Imari has
done it with five people already.
She loves to take it up her butt.
Look at Miss Imari,
how happy she looks!
You'd hardly know she's a virgin!
You did that with those pills!
Is that the only reason?
I'm coming.
I can feel it in my stomach!
It's inside me!
Imari!
Minase, you're all excited again.
Why are you like this?
Imari...
Miss Imari, your hole is twitching.
Do you want more?
I want more.
More in my butt!
Fine, I will give you more!
It's squeaky!
Your ass is wonderful!
My butt feels so good!
It feels fantastic!
Why?
Why is it so good?
Imari!
Minase, thank you
for bringing Miss Imari.
She is a vision of health.
Such a wonderful body.
Don't stop!
Do it more!
If you stop now, I'll go crazy!
Oh, this child!
I'm coming!
Go ahead, Miss Imari!
Come in front of Minase, still a virgin!
Come on, let Minase see you
come for the first time in your life!
Minase...
Minase is watching.
Imari!
Minase!
I'm coming!
Imari!
Minase, why don't you come with her?
It's coming, Miss Imari!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Imari...
I will save you.
Look how you soiled her...
...how can you say that to her?
I can't just waste
my power on you now.
I need to save my
strength for the ritual...
...but if you're going to
get in my way, I'll kill you.
Go home and tell Takashiro...
...to just shut up and watch me.
If you do anything stupid
tomorrow, I will show no mercy.
What a pitiful man.
He's the worst.
Ma'am, you're awake...
Minase, you look pale.
I'm okay.
Minase, thank you for
helping me this afternoon.
It's my fault that happened to you.
You've cut your ties with Kitami.
Yes.
It's all because of this book of spells.
I had no idea you had this.
I have no idea how
you got your hands on it...
...but this is a power that
we shouldn't interfere with.
Once you do, it's over...
...you won't be able to go back.
I realized right away...
...right away...
But I couldn't go back.
What have I done?
Minase...
Ma'am.
You came to your senses just in time.
Twelve years ago, I became
terrified by what we were doing...
...and I left the circle.
It was right after that.
Reika Kitami was...
...the girl who...
...was supposed to
serve as our sacrifice.
Just before her death,
she made a deal with the devil.
That contract, the life
she was given by the devil...
...is about to come to an end.
Kitami plans to take over
Miss Imari's body and defy the devil.
Impossible!
How?
She knows how.
I need Miss Imari's pure body.
If you do anything stupid
tomorrow, I won't show any mercy.
Tomorrow...
That's what she said.
If I get in her way
tomorrow, she'll kill me.
I see.
Kitami is going to perform the
ritual on the night of the Walpurgis...
...just like twelve years ago.
Miss Takashiro.
Minase, we might
still be able to stop this.
What?
But we need time...
Ma'am.
What's the matter, Miss Takashiro?
It won't stop.
They gave me huge
amounts of those pills.
I thought I was used to pills but...
Then why don't you take a hot shower.
Minase...
Yes?
Take me.
Ma'am?
I can't stand it!
My body is out of control.
I think I'm going to go crazy!
But...
I know I shouldn't
ask you to do this but...
Miss Takashiro...
Please...
Just think of it as helping me out!
I don't want you to see me masturbate.
Minase, it's good!
Ma'am, I didn't realize it before,
but you smell like a grown up.
Smell me more, do me more!
It's so good!
Minase, give it to me!
I can't stand it anymore.
Ma'am, I'm going to put it in.
Hurry, put it in!
I want you inside me!
It's coming in!
You're inside me!
All the way!
It's all the way in!
I can feel it.
Ma'am.
No, if you do that I'll...
...come!
Minase!
It feels so good!
I'm going to come again!
So strong!
I'm going to come again, Minase!
I'm coming again!
I'm coming too!
Let's come together!
Let it come wherever you want!
I'm coming!
Minase, thank you.
Let me sleep for just a little while.
The ritual will take place tonight.
The power of darkness grows...