If only I could hear your voice...
If only I could see your face...
... I think I could turn back...
Imari!
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Here you go, Minase.
Pumping her full of water?
It's like the Medieval witch hunts.
Minase.
Good evening, Miss Takashiro.
Stop!
Wow, Miss Takashiro, it's all going in.
Please, Minase, please stop.
My stomach...
My stomach is going to explode.
Minase, go on, put some more in.
The human body isn't that fragile.
Isn't your body human?
Why are you doing this?
Because it's fun, why else?
Seeing a human being fall from grace...
... I never tire of it.
A face twisted with suffering...
...a face drowning in pleasure..
It speaks to my heart
more than any work of art.
No more.
It's going to come out!
Minase, plug her up.
Yes ma'am.
Minase, stop it!
Please stop it!
I'm putting it in, Miss Takashiro.
No!
S-Stop!
Don't!
Ma'am.
It's tight!
It feels so good!
My my, you've got your student
up your ass and you're howling!
You're the worst kind of teacher!
You're crazy!
That's right, I'm crazy!
This entire world is crazy.
There are evil monsters roaming
the earth in the guise of humans.
People just choose not to accept it.
God has abandoned us.
We've continued to break the Ten
Commandments and commit sins.
People like me are
best suited for this world.
What this world really
needs is a true demon.
You...
Who are you?
I joined forces with
the devil twelve years ago.
T-That's nonsense.
How can you say that?
After all, you must be a
survivor of that magic circle...
Minase, harder!
Yes!
Please stop, Minase!
It's true, isn't it?
Tell the truth!
That's right, I was
a member of that circle...
But I don't know you.
Of course not.
I didn't have
anything to do with that circle.
And, I didn't have any interest in magic.
Then why?
It can't be.
I'm coming, teacher, I'm coming!
Minase, don't come!
Don't put anything else in my body!
I can't hold off!
Please, let me go to the bathroom.
Go ahead.
In the hall, first door on the right.
How hideous.
You look like a half dead frog.
I just want to squash you.
Please stop.
It's going to come out!
What a great hole.
You're the best!
No!
There's no plug in
your ass, so keep it closed!
I can't!
Please stop!
I'm going come!
It's going to be huge load!
You don't want me to come inside?
Then, I'll be sure to!
Heikas heikas...
...estei biberoi.
Female sacrificial lamb...
May you be the pillar of strength...
Slain sacrificial lamb...
...give us the strength
of the gods of darkness.
Female sacrificial lamb...
...give us the strength
to crush the evil that rebels.
Oh sacrifice, open the gates of hatred...
...open your gates...
...your princes...
...open the gates of eternity.
The King of Glory shall enter.
The King of Eternity
is the Almighty King.
He is the King of Glory.
Let there be glory for father and child...
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
No!
Something's wrong.
The Gate of Orkus is
not opening all the way.
Did you make a mistake?
No way.
We did it just like the book said.
Then why?
We made a mistake.
What are we going to do?
We've sacrificed a human being!
Not enough.
It's not enough.
There's not enough blood.
What are you saying?
It's too late.
That's not true.
You're not...
Nami, have you lost your mind?
What are you saying?
We are all crazy.
Ever since we read the book!
Saki!
No!
Here it is!
What are you doing, Rie?
Look, the gate is about to open.
I can hear the bells of hell.
Ide!
Berzelt the devil!
Answer my call!
No!
It hurts...
It hurts!
Girl, do you want to live?
Do you wish a contract with me?
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
Minase, your lover is here.
Shiraki, were you following me?
Welcome, Miss Shiraki.
Shiraki!
Good morning, Minase.
What are you doing here?
You told me to wake you up last night.
I did...
I'll do this for you every morning.
Minase, what's this
book you're reading?
That book has
made you lose your mind.
What is this?
What's wrong?
This is...
Imari, If only I could hear your voice...
If only I could hear your voice...
I think I could turn back.
Minase...
Good morning, Miss Imari.
Imari...
Let's go, Minase.
Y-Yeah...
Minase!
Imari.
Um, well...
What do you mean by turn back?
What is happening to you?
You're behaving strangely lately.
You've totally changed.
What happened?
Never mind.
Never mind, leave me alone.
Huh, Minase...
Imari!
What?
You shouldn't come
to the art club today.
Why?
Ma'am!
Miss Takashiro!
Hurry!
I can't hold it anymore!
Hurry up and do it!
I'm going to come!
Go ahead and come inside her.
Is it okay?
Don't!
No!
Of course!
If you don't come inside
her, it won't be practical sex ed.
Then, then...
I'm going to come!
Stop!
It's coming!
It's coming inside of me!
Out of the way!
Ma'am!
It's been my dream to do it with you.
No!
Miss Takashiro, your lips say no...
...but it looks like
your body is enjoying this.
That's because you...
Wow, Ma'am!
It's so hot and soft inside of you!
For those of you who can't hold it...
Let it out on her wherever you want.
Squeeze it all out.
Ma'am!
Here I go!
Now it's a real ejaculation party!
Here's your beloved
student body president.
We get to do it with Miss Shiraki too?
This time I get to go first!
No I do!
No, stop!
Minase!
Minase, help me!
These are Miss Shiraki's tits!
Check out her you know what.
Hey, what is this?
Miss Imari...
Miss Kitami, please make them stop.
Minase, Miss Saeki,
what's the matter with you two?
Stop it you guys!
Stop it!
Miss Takashiro!
Miss Shiraki!
I can't believe it!
What is this?
Minase, why aren't you stopping them?
Miss Shiraki is your...
Miss Imari, why don't you join in?
It's fun.
Miss Saeki.
Minase, say something!
Wake up!
Minase...
Minase, let's take her.
Y-Yeah...
No, Minase!
Don't take Miss Imari.
Come, Minase, hurry.
Truly, a very fine specimen.
All we have to do is wait
for the right moment to arrive.
Minase, this is your first time
seeing Miss Imari naked, isn't it?
Yeah...
Unfortunately I can't let
you take her virginity but...
...if the ritual goes well...
... I will let you have a good time.
Ritual?
Have you woken up?
Miss Kitami, what was...
It wasn't a dream.
My clothes!
What is this?
Ma'am, why are you doing this?
Please take these off!
I can't do that.
Miss Kitami...
Minase!
What do you mean by ritual?
What are you going to do to Imari?
I'm sorry, but we don't have time.
We need Miss Imari's untainted body.
You already did, Miss Shiraki,
the other girl I had my eye on.
Minase, why?
Why are you doing this?
Minase...
You dragged us into this...
...but you're not really one of us yet.
We've gotten all these
girls together for our sister.
Saeki.
Speaking of which...
You took awfully long to get here.
Where did you go after
you put Miss Imari in my car?
Well, Minase?
Minase left this book...
Is this...
What is this?
This is a chastity belt.
What is it for?
It's for you to put on.
Until I take your purity.
What are you saying?
It might be strange at first...
...but you'll get used to it.
N-No!
I don't want to wear it!
But if you put this on, you
won't be able to masturbate so...
I will give you plenty of pleasure!
I-I don't want any!
I wonder how long you'll keep that up.
Miss Saeki, give
me the you know what.
Yes, Sister.
What are those?
I'm going to give you
something that will make you honest.
They'll begin to work right away.
Humans are weak against desire.
Especially young girls like you.
Pretty soon, you will begin to drool...
...and then you will begin to beg...
I won't do that.
Your strength won't hold up.
You masturbate all the
time at home, don't you?
I-I don't do that!
Stop lying!
I don't do that!
It's started to work.
Soon, the effect will
become much stronger.
No!
Something's not right.
No...
What...
Imari...
So, do you want it?
Do you want it so
bad you can't stand it?
That's not true.
What a stubborn child!
Well, Miss Imari?
Help me!
Why don't you just be honest?
The more you deny it...
...the more worked up you will get.
Help me!
Help me, Minase!
Imari!
Minase...
...look how big you are.
Aren't you embarrassed?
I can't bear it anymore.
Miss Imari, I'll ask you one more time...
You really don't masturbate?
I do.
I masturbate.
Oh?
How many times a week?
A-About three times a week.
Three times a week!
And you still insisted that you didn't?
No, don't say that!
Not in front of everyone!
I will reward you for being honest.
I'll make you come again
and again in front of Minase.
No!
Minase!