El Elohim, Elohi Elohim Sabaoth Elion...
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas...
Bible Black: New Testament
Chapter 3 Rule
Extreme acts of black
magic, Thelema doctrine...
...descendant of Aleister Crowley...
...Jody Crowley...
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas...
I'll make you feel more comfortable.
Yes, yes...
My stomach feels hot!
No, more...
More!
So it is Reika Kitami...
A Woman in red?
Drive out the evil spirits,
destroy my bitter enemy...
Provide me with the powers of the
seven forces of nature.
Rin, Byo, Tou, Sha, Kai,
Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Another interference!
Is it Jody?
Barrier!
Takashiro is here as well?
Ms. Takashiro.
Ms. Takashiro...
Please wake up.
Shiraki...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
What are you doing here, Shiraki?
Today's my first day
as a substitute professor.
Good thing you're here.
What?
Can you come with me
to the school's cellar?
You want me to call the ambulance?
No...
So she's the woman in red...
Ms. Takashiro, what's the woman in
red?
She's the devil's partner that
Aleister Crowley is looking for.
Devil's partner?
This pretty girl is...
Crazy devil worshippers
admire her as their leader...
...and as a descendant
of Aleister Crowley...
She has inherited his powerful
abilities, her name's Jody Crowley...
In order to fulfill the prophecy, Jody
went on to look for the woman in red...
...who is mentioned in chapter 17
or the Book of Revelations by John...
...and is predicted to give birth to a child
stronger than any king in the world.
But as of now, Jody is missing.
In order to seal Reika Kitami inside
Imari before, l was preparing...
...some related documents.
That's when l saw her photo.
Then Jody appeared before me today...
I was only able to use a
barrier to protect this girl...
...so l couldn't figure out how
Jody and Reika Kitami are related.
Shiraki, please don't
tell anyone about this.
Yes.
Reika Kitami, I'll get you this time...
While your teacher is out, Ms. Shiraki
will be your substitute teacher.
Hello, nice to meet you all.
I'll leave you in charge.
Good luck, Ms. Shiraki.
Thank you Ms. Saeki.
General Hospital
Excuse me.
She's sleeping comfortably right
now, but she'll be up by tomorrow.
So you can go home without any
worries.
I see...
She thinks I'm her father...
Is something wrong?
No.
Well, who stayed with her all this time?
I believe it was a nun.
If you check the records
in the emergency office...
...you can find out her whereabouts.
Oh, you're awake.
Mr. Oshima, you were hit by a car.
Do you remember anything?
No.
Eri Harada...
You should take it easy.
Why did you do that?
Don't ask any questions.
Despite your appearance,
it's a bold color.
But it looks good on you.
Yes, it's beautiful.
No, don't be so rough...
No.
That hurts.
Stop it!
Please stop.
Don't do this.
This is a hospital...
We can't do this...
No.
You're telling me to stop?
You know you want it bad.
You shaved it clean
because you want it, right?
Your nipples are hard and
your crotch is really wet.
You're just craving my cock.
Long time no see, Imari.
No, maybe l should
call you Reika Kitami.
How did you know l was here?
I saw an evil aura surrounding
this area from afar.
You came at the right moment.
You saved me the trouble
of looking for you.
I don't know what
you're planning to do...
..but l suggest you keep
quiet inside Imari's body.
You caught me by surprise last time...
But it won't be so easy this time.
Faculty Lounge
Huh?
Can l help you?
Kiriya...
What are you doing here so late?
We were all waiting for you, Ms. Shiraki.
M-Ms. Saeki...
When the goddess of mercy tried
to seek out profound wisdom...
...she determined that the 5 elements
that make up the human mind...
...and body weren't essential. And she
took away all pain and suffering.
Heikas Heikas Estei Biberoi...
El Elohim, Elohi Elohim Sabaoth Elion...
Stop it Imari.
Imari...
You're feeling good after
I played with your ass?
You haven't changed at all.
Your ass is warm.
Yes, with this ass...
With this ass, my Minase...
You took away my Minase...
My Minase...
...with this ass.
It's certainly a very tasty ass.
It feels so good.
I just love your ripe ass.
Ms. Takashiro, your
ass is craving more.
Imari, please...
Not in the ass...
Please...
In the front...
Do it in the front...
What are you saying?
Your ass is feeling it.
You're a dirty little slut like always.
Don't be embarrassed.
Your ass feels good, right?
It feels so good.
The more you try to resist...
The better l feel.
No...
Not in the ass...
Now, since your ass made my cock
dirty, l want you to clean it up for me.
It's not...
...over yet.