Big sister...
You're cute.
Look at you, you're already wet.
N-No...
If you do that, I...
What's going to happen if I do this?
N-No...
Get down on all fours.
Yes.
You have a big ass.
Are you embarrassed?
I-I am...
B-But you told me to...
Are you talking back to me?
You're a bad girl.
B-Big sister...
You're beautiful, Junko...
Nami!
Lick deep inside me!
That's right...
You're great, Junko...
That's good!
You are so hot and soft...
Delicious!
Nami, harder...
Squeeze my nipples harder!
That feels so good...
Big sister...
Big sister!
Yes, yes!
Oh, I'm coming!
Wheel of Fortune...
Hey, I got the same card before!
Yeah.
"A great change is upon you..."
"Something will
change your life completely."
Maybe I'm going to find a boyfriend!
I'm going to ask Takemura out!
Well, it may not be about boyfriends.
Hmm, I see...
How about Utsuno from history class?
Weren't you listening to Hiroko?
Nami Kozono...
From the Student Council...
What are you all doing here?
You shouldn't be here if
you don't belong to any club.
Kozono, what were
you doing staying so late?
I don't need to answer that, Takashiro.
Having a hobby is nice, but why
can't you do something healthier?
Don't take witchcraft lightly.
What's that?
Magic, spells, and ritual...
Witchcraft has been part of
people's life since ancient times.
The power of
darkness can perform a miracle.
Isn't it fascinating?
We're trying to learn the truth
of history through witchcraft.
I'm not lying.
Read this book.
Here, take it.
Ridiculous!
Bitch!
Bible Black, Black Brand
I can't...
I can't run anymore...
I'm too hungry.
That will be 240 yen.
240 yen...
240...
Um, I don't want the bread.
Take it.
But, I...
It's on the house.
But why?
This business is
built on you hungry kids.
Thank you very much!
I've never seen you around here before,
did you just move to this neighborhood?
Yes, my name is Reika Kitami.
What's this?
I found this at an
antique shop yesterday.
It must be an original, it's hand written.
It looks old, was it expensive?
Not at all.
I found it in a pile of sale books.
Hand written magic book...
It was probably written
by a priest in the Middle Ages.
What a find, huh?
Excuse me.
I came to inform you that your
request to form a club has been denied.
Denied?
But why?
Did you really think the school
would let you have such a silly club?
Hold on, don't you
think that's a little too much?
I just came to deliver the
message from the Student Council.
Good day.
Wait, you!
Saki!
Rie, Saki.
Let's translate this book.
A new student is
joining this class, Reika Kitami.
Hello, I'm Reika Kitami.
Nice to meet you!
Hello Kitami.
My name is Nami Kozono.
I'm on the student council here.
Nice to meet you, Kozono.
Ask me if you have any questions.
Yes, thank you very much.
You can ask me anything, okay?
Um, yes...
Um...
Uh, this...
I'm sorry, but I'm not interested in men.
And even if I were,
you would be out of the question.
Waiting for a girl in front
of the women's bathroom...
What the hell were you thinking?
In those words of great magic...
...you shall find the spell to
summon the evil of darkness...
It's too difficult!
It looks like these words
are based on Latin and French.
We should be able to figure it out.
But Hiroko, we spent three
hours to translate a couple of pages...
We're doing good.
Let's try one.
I found a simple spell.
"To make a woman dance naked?"
Well, it sounds like
easier than raising dead, but...
What kind of spell is that?
It just says that the woman
who's under this spell will dance naked.
Hey Hiroko, let's put this spell that girl!
Who?
What does this last line mean?
Which one?
"People shall not envy but pity her."
Don't worry about it, just do it!
Requests for amendments will
be discussed at the next meeting.
That was all for school regulations.
And next, the report on the club budget.
Mochida, please give us the report.
Y-Yes.
Hello, I'm Mochida.
F-First I'd like to read the
budget report for this year.
Sports clubs and
literature clubs are, they are...
I can't bear it anymore!
Hi everybody...
Look.
Come on, look closer...
Am I beautiful?
It feels so good...
Look, Junko's pussy is melting.
Please look at me...
Please look at my pussy...
Isn't it pretty?
Look deep inside my pussy.
Good...
I'm coming.
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
What's going on?
What happened to her?
Somebody, put some clothes on her!
Hurry!
Everyone is talking about her.
Saki, do you think it was...
Nami Kozono...
How is Mochida?
She's sleeping.
Maybe we'll make
you dance naked next time.
What?
Saki!
Let's go, Rie.
Could they have...
Nonsense, what am I thinking?
But what happened to Junko?
The police are here.
How many people did
you tell about the spell?
S-Sorry...
Don't talk about it with
anybody anymore, okay?
Okay.
We don't know if
it was really magic, though...
But Rie, if it wasn't
magic, then what was it?
What do you think, Hiroko?
I can't say anything yet...
U-Um...
I want to ask you a favor.
Kitami.
Kozono?
Where are you going?
This class is more
advanced than I though...
...so I was going to ask
the professor to tutor me.
Maybe I can help you out.
Oh, now I understand!
You will make a great professor!
Kozono?
Kitami...
Come on, don't you like me?
K-Kozono!
No...
K-Kozono, stop it!
No, stop!
No!
Well, I think your body
has a different opinion.
Please stop.
Please stop it...
You sure?
Doesn't this feel good?
No!
Nobody has ever rejected me before.
Good morning!
Good morning, Kitami.
G-Good morning.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm so embarrassed...
I'm really sorr-
Hiratani...
Hiratani!
Good morning, Hiratani.
Kozono!
I can't believe she's talking to him.
I can't wait until after school...
...so please come see me
in the council room at lunch.
I have something important to tell you.
I'll see you later!
Do not disturb
Hiratani...
Good...
I've never felt like this...
Yes, Hiratani...
Yes!
Kozono!
No, call me Nami.
Nami!
This is my first time.
I'm so happy to be your first, Hiratani.
Nami, I'm going to...
Come inside me, come!
I'm coming!
Oh Hiratani...
You're a naughty girl.
It's deep inside me...
Nami, can I do your ass?
Of course, wherever you want.
Nami, Nami...
It's deep up in my butt.
Hiratani...
I'm coming inside.
Give me...
Give me your come.
Maybe this is it...
What?
Hiroko's tarot.
"A great change is upon you..."
"Something will
change your life completely."
I don't know...
But I can tell you this...
That book...
...of magic is real.
I'm coming!