He's late...
Kaori...
I understand, Onee-sama.
Are you all right?
What?
Yes.
I want this to be the last fight.
No, it has to be the last fight!
Has to be...the last fight?
Yes...
The fight for the sole possession of the dark bible known as Bible Black.
I...
I'm responsible for everything.
Anyway, I'm worried about Yamanishi over at Tokken.
We should head over there first.
No!
Please take me to the school.
We must get to the school in order to stop Imari-san!
It won't take long.
It's possible that Aki-kun has regained consciousness.
If something did happen, then it's already too late!
Either way, we'll have to get to the school.
Please, Yuge-san!
I'm an investigator.
If we were to head over to the school, I'll need some useful data.
And some weapons...
Hurry up and bring those two.
Yes!
S-Stop it!
J-Jody Crowley!
T-Takashiro-sensei!
Yuge-san...
I-I'm sorry.
I'm not much of a help...
Yuge-san!
T-Takashiro-sensei!
Looks like we got ourselves a sacrificial lamb...
...that is very appropriate for this place, Kaori.
Yes, Onee-sama...
Takashiro-sensei...
This is...
Either way, we'll have to get to the school.
To the school...
Ichikawa Aki, the woman in red...
Rise...
Come...
C-Chief Investigator Imari?
Woman in red!
Use your blood and show us...
Show me where it is!
No!
Show me where the Bible Black is!
Why?
You...
I can't believe you interfered with my ritual...
Your ritual?
You're a foolish woman.
You should be happy that you're still alive.
You had to rely on the power of evil...
...and now you want the power to control evil?
You must be dreaming!
Kitami Reika!
You're nothing but a sacrificial lamb as well!
For my ritual that is!
This spell is like child's play!
What?
Onee-sama...
K-Kaori...
You were careless...
Don't worry. I'll take everything you have to offer.
Stop...
Oh, but doesn't it feel good to be on the receiving end for once?
It's pretty impressive.
Hey, Reika...
See?
You got excited since you wanted this, right?
No...
Enjoy as much as you can.
Enjoy having me, that is!
Stop...
Looks like your pussy is working fine.
Yes, I feel it...
Your humiliation...
Show me all of it.
I'll taste every single one.
I want you to taste me too.
This is going to be the last flesh you'll ever feel in this life.
No!
You're starting to feel good now, Reika.
Now...
Now, take it all in...
Take in all your desires...
No...
No!
Now, I want you to pleasure me.
Come on...
It's still not enough, Reika.
More...
I want you to give me more!
You like it in here too, right?
It's great, Reika... It's amazing...
It's tight...
You're wonderful, Reika.
My ass feels good!
This woman...
She's not Reika!
No...
My ass...
My ass feels good!
Did you hide back inside this woman?
That's it...
That's it, Reika.
We'll climax together...
T-This is the ''Ritual of Coronzon''!
I can't believe it!
Woman in red...
Allow me to impregnate you...
By using the power of Coronzon vested in me...
...you shall give birth to the one that will rule the world.
N-No...
No!
What?
The Spear of Longinus...
Aki-kun! Yamanishi!
Takashiro-sensei...
Yuge-san...
It's too late...
There's no way for you to stop the ritual!
Y-Yuge-san...
Are you okay, Takashiro-sensei?
Yes...
This is the weapon, right?
Thank you, Yuge-san.
I'll go help Aki-kun.
Yuge-san!
Y-Yamanishi! You...
Vam! Hum! Trah!
Hrih!
Ah!
Vam! Hum! Trah! Hrih! Ah!
What?
What is this?
Bible Black...
The original!
Sensei, what should we do?
That chain...
If we can break the seal with that chain...
Now is the best time to do it!
If we break the seal now, that Bible Black will just be an ordinary book.
Get a hold of yourself!
I never thought that a deadly poison like this...
...would come in handy at an unusual time like this.
Poison for poison, huh?
Not so fast!
Yuge-san...
Hurry...
Shit!
Defend against evil spirits, drive away my bitter enemy...
End the Seven Misfortunes and bring forth good fortune...
Such nonsense!
This is...
Ones involved with the ritual...
You wish to bind a contract with me?
I-Imari-san!
I will take your souls in return!
Do you wish to bind a contract?
The contract...
Yamanishi-kun...
Kitami-sensei...
Yamanishi-kun!
Help me, Yamanishi-kun!
I wish...
...to bind a contract...
As you wish.
No! Yamanishi-kun!
Kitami-sensei!
Defend against evil spirits, drive away my bitter enemy...
End the Seven Misfortunes and bring forth good fortune...
Rin, Byo, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
This isn't it...
It's not me!
No!
Stop!
Seal!
Easy now!
Is it finally over?
It might be difficult for me to file a report on this...
Are you finished filing the report?
Um...
There's no need to panic.
Just make sure to file the report by today.