Agios Otesk Esherhus Atanaton.
N-No!
Agra Eimehn.
No!
Please stop it!
I can't believe this
body is going to be mine...
Minase!
It's so big and hot!
Minase, I'm coming!
Please come with me!
I can feel it!
I can feel you coming inside me!
Please give it all to me.
You are so beautiful, Imari.
Minase, I need you to help me.
There is one spell in this book
that might be able stop Kitami.
Minase!
Those who rebel against the will of God.
I command you to leave this world,
and go back to where you belong.
Who the hell...
Minase!
Fool, it's too late.
All you can do is watch me.
I'll kill you when I'm done.
I won't let it happen.
The protector of the
Gate to the Heavens...
I possess the great power of the
gods, I hold the secrets of magic.
I ask you to close the Gate of Orkus.
Don't you get it?
Your spell won't work on me!
Minase...
I possess the great power of the
gods, I hold the secrets of magic...
What a fool!
What's that?
I ordered my followers to kill
them after they enjoy them.
Aren't you going to save them?
You're just showing me an illusion!
Believe what you want, I don't have
time to play with you right now.
No!
Please stop it!
No, it hurts!
No!
It hurts!
See, my life's depending on it...
I suggest you leave.
I won't let anyone get in my way.
M-Minase!
Minase!
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
Hein ron hirai sabeios.
Herim radisha redieah adonai.
Minase...
Imari!
Minase, what are you doing?
Miss Takashiro...
Hurry, cast the Forbidden Spell...
If you defeat Kitami, Miss Yukiko
and Miss Shirai will be saved...
Defeat Kitami, please...
Minase, hurry and stop Kitami!
Miss Takashiro!
I can't move...
You can still save them
if you defeat Kitami...
Hurry, before it's too late...
Please, stop Kitami!
Miss Takashiro!
No!
Hein ron hirai sabeios.
Herim radisha redieah adonai.
Gate keeper of the Heavens...
I possess the great power of the
gods, I hold the secrets of magic.
I ask you to close the Gate of Orkus.
Jehoyah yar tetoragramaton saday!
Mesias agios ishuros
emanuel agra alpha omega!
In the name of Jesus Christ who knows
the beginning and the end of this world...
...and in the name of other holy gods...
I forbid you to remain in this world.
Saint Michael, lend me your power to send
this devil back to the inferno of Hell.
I command you to stay there
until the end of eternity.
Amen!
Let's get out of here!
It was in the magic book.
It's the spell to send the one that
possesses the evil power back to Hell.
Kitami, your plan has failed.
Kitami...
I heard that the police
closed the case yesterday.
Looks like everyone thinks
Miss Kitami committed suicide.
Yeah.
What happened there was
beyond human understanding.
Imari...
I'm so sorry.
I dragged you into
this, it's all my fault.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
But...
I think everyone has
evil deep inside them.
But you won the battle
with evil, Minase.
Minase, where were you looking?
And you saved me from evil, too.
Imari...
Are you sure?
Yes, if it's you...
Minase...
Are you scared?
No, I'm okay.
You're so beautiful.
Don't stare at me.
No, Minase...
Are you ready?
It's inside you, Imari.
I can feel you inside me, Minase.
Is it okay if I move?
I-I think so.
Imari!
Minase!
It's so good!
I'm going to come...
I heard that the basement is
going to be closed.
Yeah, it will be sealed
with concrete next week...
...so that no one can ever enter the room.
What about the book?
I went to put it back
where I found it today.
In the basement?
No one will ever find the book again.
I'm not going to practice
magic anymore, either.
I don't think I will stop
casting my spell anytime soon.
What spell?
I've been casting it for a while now,
and it looks like it's working, so...
Hey, Minase...
What is it?
Nothing.
What's the matter?
It's embarrassing, forget it.
You can tell me anything.
Um, well...
I want it in my butt.
I said I want you to put it in my butt.
Lick me more.
Minase, lick my butt.
Good!
Imari...
Imari!
Minase!
Minase, it feels good!
It feels so good!
Imari!
It's deep inside my butt!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
Minase, I saw Miss Kitami's past.
What?
Twelve years ago, Miss Kitami
transferred to our school.
She was just an ordinary girl.
She had a crush on this
boy in her old school...
But she couldn't even
tell him how she felt.
I guess she was also a
victim in this whole thing.
Who is it?
Imari?
What are you doing here?
That book...
We must get rid of the book.
I-Imari?
Can I try out my new body with you?
N-No!
No!
What are you talking about?
Your body seems to like it.
Where are you going?
It feels so good!
It feels fantastic!
This is how the body
of Kurumi Imari feels!
And this is my new body!
Good!
I'm coming!
Minase...
We will be back!