Autopsy Room
Tight, tight!
Once in my lifetime,
I've always wanted to violate
I- I'm coming!
Time to enjoy the main dish.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
The Lance of Longinus...
Hey, Aki-kun!
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas...
Nasatanada Zazas.
I thought you were just visiting me,
It's my first time seeing a corpse like that.
The man was burnt to a crisp,
She's still her pretty self.
But, Boss, aren't we supposed to abandon
At least the autopsy should be our
responsibility,
because those people are just a
Uh yes... Yes, that's true.
Autopsy Room
It can't be!
What's the matter?
Special Criminal Investigation and Research.
What? The corpse came back to life?
Y- Yes.
Just now, the detective in charge called me.
Here's some evidence.
The abrasions in her vulva and her
...as was mentioned in her statement.
There is a possibility she was raped by
So she was allowed to go back home
I will go on campus to see how things are.
Sure.
Go take a rest in the break room first.
As you wish, sir.
Head Investigator Imari seems
LB NOTE: TL CHECK
By the way, Aki-kun,
what about the evidence from the bank?
Oh yeah! Right away!
That's the only thing missing from the bank safe.
The bank robbers all died.
Head Investigator Imari and I were
Yoshitani Souji, left in the bank safe.
So there's a connection with
That Yoshitani Souji has been missing for half a
year.
Supposedly he said he was looking
Domestic or international,
research all of the religious Satanic
...and go search the school with Imari-kun.
Yes, sir!
Professor Saeki, what's the matter?
Vice Chancellor.
Thank you for coming here so early in the
morning.
No, no. Of course I'd visit the enthusiastic
And besides, today is the start of the new
quarter.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Every time I drink it,
It's a bit more bitter than usual.
Yes. I put in more than usual.
Oh?
Anyway, Vice Chancellor,
Please, this way.
Uh, sure.
I didn't know this campus had an
It's from back when this place was a monastery.
Back when we were students,
Oh yeah, Professor Saeki,
By the way, Professor Shiraki who's here
...she was a graduate of this school also.
She was in the same grade as me.
Anyway, it looks like there was an incident
P- Professor Saeki!
From the student council president Kiria
Saki-san
I don't know what you heard from Kiria-kun,
but according to the police
and the rejected professor tried to act upon
he realized the impact of his sin and
My, how scary.
About the incident...
Her father, Chancellor Toudou,
But what I'm worried about is the
That emotional wound is...
You're so nice, Assistant Professor.
Toudou-kun...
Vice Chancellor,
today we celebrate the Vice Chancellor for
So there's a request for you
Request?
Toudou-kun!
You girls... What are you doing?
Metallic elements?
Yes, Iron, carbon, nickel, chromium,
molybdenum...
...and in small amounts, manganese,
Aren't those the basic elements of meteorites?
That's right.
The object in the bank safe is this.
I had them study the powder
but according to the X-rays, it
What's that?
After He was crucified...
Jesus was stabbed in the side with it.
Basement?
What's here?
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Professor Saeki, for a while...
I liked you, Professor...
Is this too stimulating for a little girl like you?
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Not there...
I want to put it in.
Put it in, Vice Chancellor.
Harder... Do it harder please.
What kind of ceremony is that?
Preparations to revive the black bible.
That is...
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
The ceremony is starting.
I have to hurry.
Jodie Crawley?
Head... Investigator... Imari...
What... are you doing... to me?
Good work, Saeki-san. I kept you waiting.
No, I'm thankful for the reunion, Professor
Kitami.
Ki... Professor Kitami, Head Investigator Imari
is...
Ero Erohim, Sabbath Leon.
Ero Erohim, Erohi Erohim, Sabbath Leon.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.