START THE ADVENTURE NOW
Could someone be so foolish as to venture into the lair of Viken, the Monster Mage?
So, what does this lowly cat-slave seek from me?
If you please, I come seeking the Sword of the Triton.
What? The Sword of the Triton?
And just what do you propose to offer...
in exchange for the Sword?
All I have is yours for the taking.
I see, I see!
Give my Sword to a simple cat-slave? I think not.
Master Monster Mage...
...before you have your way with me, may I see the Triton's Sword?
Well, I guess a quick peek would be all right.
So, that's where you've been hiding it!
Who said that?
Now, Monster Magician Viken...
...the Sword of the Triton shall belong to me!
So, that was your game!
That wasn't very nice!
Here it comes!
Heh, nowhere near as tough as I thought he'd be.
How about you Pink?
Are you all right?
Did you really think I could be defeated so easily?
Santa!
A transformation spell?
Now you shall learn the face fate of all those who dare to fuck with me!
BOMBER!
So, you brought a witch too!
I'm here as well!
Bobo!
Now!
I told you two to keep out of this!
Don't be so inflexible!
Wow, this is gorgeous!
If it wasn't for the fact that it's cursed, I'd be tempted to keep it!
The important thing is that it's worth a bundle!
With the profits from this quest we can afford to take some time off!
Then maybe you'll finally buy me some new clothes?
Nah, that's a waste of money.
You're a pig, Santa.
Santa, go ahead and buy her something.
Yeah, it's only clothing.
All right, all right, I'll buy them.
Yes! You're the best!
I like this one.
No, this one's better.
Which one should I get?
I'll take this one!
Let me take a look.
I want to try it on!
It costs a fortune!
Greetings!
I'd like to try this on!
Forget it!
We don't serve your kind here, cat-slut!
Now get out!
There's no call to be like that!
She's with me!
And I said we don't have anything for her!
If you want suitable clothes for her...
...go kill a monster and wrap her in the hides!
Pink!
Please Pink, don't take it so hard.
I'm sure there'll be a much better store in the next village.
Santa...
If you want suitable clothes for her...
...go kill a monster and wrap her in the hides!
If I had some tiger skin, maybe I could handle this myself.
It won't be long, Pink.
Damn! Just my luck to find a Hell-Tiger!
It did that with one swipe?
I can't believe how lucky I am!
Bobo?
You shouldn't be such a stranger, Santa.
Sorry, you saved my ass.
Ooo, what pretty clothes!
Thank you, Santa!
Pink, you look so cute!
"Even a tomboy looks great when properly adorned."
Who the hell are you?
Show some proper manners, you foreign scum!
Wait a second!
What have we done?
We're here to escort you to Tajif Castle!
That's a laugh! Go ahead and try it if you've got the balls!
Maybe we'd better do what they want for the moment.
Damn...
Wow! What a babe!
Your Majesty, we have brought before you the villains...
...who steal the souls from your forest!
Soul stealing? What the hell are you talking about?
Don't feign innocence!
We know you are the ones who have been kidnapping young women...
...from the village in the North Forest!
We don't know what you're talking about!
Last night, another young girl failed to return...
...from a trip through the North Forest.
We have irrefutable evidence that you also...
...were in the forest last night.
Your Royal Highness, it's true that we were in the North Forest...
...but to accuse us of kidnapping young woman is unthinkable!
Show some respect!
Hold it!
We of Tajif have already lost six women to these soul-thieves.
How can anyone be sure you are not the culprits?
But we only came to this village yesterday!
I see.
Guards, untie them.
You are Questing Warriors, are you not?
Is there some chance we might persuade you...
...to search for the girl who have been spirited away?
We will reward you in a suitable fashion.
A suitable fashion...
Santa, darling...
I can't hold it!
Reward me in a suitable fashion!
Why do you have to be such a sleaze ball?
Finally, it is ready.
My work will be finished once this last seed is planted inside you.
Wait!
What is it, Pierce?
I'm sensing an evil presence!
This way!
How far are we going, Pierce?
We're almost there.
The evil is radiating from that old shack.
It's spooky all right.
I'll take a closer look.
Santa, please be careful.
Looks like we hit the jackpot.
Who's out there?
For what you've seen, you shall never leave!
Santa!
Are you all right?
That witch is the one the source of the evil!
So, it seems we've found our soul thief!
You're already too late!
Such a waste of effort!
That rotting body of flesh and blood has already been abandoned!
Pierce, what is that thing?
We're in serious trouble!
That's a Slave-Witch!
A really vicious looking one too!
Sown in flesh, my spawn of Hell...
Be joined as limbs to serve my will!
Behold!
What the hell is it?
Damn, if we attack we could kill those innocent girls!
That's not playing fair!
Witness the power of my slave dolls!
Maneuvering magic:
BEAST KNUCKLE!
That's going too far!
I'll fry your ass!
ENER-PSI-BURST!
Not too bad!
Don't fuck with me, damn it!
Let me give you a taste of your own fire!
BREASTS OF FLAME!
Now do you understand my power?
Look! There's something wrong with her!
Using magic power must weaken her ability to hold her composite form!
Damn! My rebellious little toys must sense my power dropping.
Elemental demons who lurk in the sky...
Bind yourself to this doll, floating on high!
Go! To the doll!
What's she up to?
It can't be!
MOON CHARGE!
Somehow she's recharged her magic power!
What kind of monster is she?
Santa, what'll we do?
Be quiet! I'd like to know the answer myself!
Pierce, hit her with everything you've got!
What? She'll just charge herself up again!
Go ahead and do it anyway!
OH, whatever!
ENER-PSI-BURST!
You can't hurt me!
Oh, no!
Time to take you out of the game, elf!
Take this:
RAY PASS!
Pierce!
My body...
Suffer the exquisite pain...
...of drowning in an ocean of pure pleasure!
Control yourself, Pierce!
I can't...
I'm so horny I could even die!
There's nothing I can do to stop it!
There's one chance!
Bobo...
I want you to throw Pink at her!
What???
Pink, I want you to catch that doll!
I get it! If she can't recharge her magic...
I caught it!
Now that's not fair!
Give it back, cat-girl!
Not on your life!
Stop, you rotten cat-bitch!
You can't catch me!
Look at the witch!
She's already staring to fall apart!
My lovely body!
I'm so hot. I'm melting!
Now, Bobo!
Let's rip her out of there!
Now you've gone and done it!
You can't kill me so easily! I'm immortal!
Sure of that, are you?
What?
I'm going to make sure you rest in pieces!
Now it's over.
Thank you, Questing Warriors!
Because of your deeds, peace has been restored to the land of Tajif.
We would like to give you a suitable reward for such noble deeds!
Who needs a reward?
Serving a lovely ruler such as yourself...
...is the greatest honor a warrior could ever ask for.
Santa, you're a real jerk!