The Lance of Longinus?
How do you...
...know about that?
It impaled Jesus through
The Lance of Longinus...
...is an artifact that even Hitler tried to obtain.
Some guy found it.
This is the 3rd floor!
C- Chief Yuge!
There shouldn't be any reason to be
Are you making progress on the
Y- Yes.
Oh, you can send that to the Iab.
Anyway, where is Imari?
Investigator Imari is... over there.
All of a sudden, she told me to wait here.
Those magazines and that trash... Clean it up.
Uh, yes!
Uh, yes?
Quit saluting me.
We're not the police.
What's the matter?
Did you see something?
No. I thought l heard something.
Will there be an interruption again?
... Is to get the original burnt black bible.
This time we will discover the location
Ero Erohim, Sabbath Leon.
Ero Erohim, Erohi Erohim, Sabbath Leon.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Yoshitani-sensei!
Tell me where the Lance of Longinus is.
Yuki-kun, I will!
The Lance of Longinus... My dad... My dad...
Damn it! Again!
Such an interesting corpse...
The man was burnt to a crisp,
She's her pretty self.
Boss, her private parts are still wet.
Maybe this case is something we shouldn't be
handling.
Don't run away, Yamanishi.
The Special Investigators are busy with that
serial killer.
Special Investigator...
Yes, from the Department of Investigation
Why do we have to use the stairs
A dimensional field?
This is...
Professor Reika Kitami.
Yamanishi Naoto-kun...
K- Kitami Reika-sensei...
517 Yamanishi Naoto-sama.
Takashiro-sensei, it's been a while.
Shiraki-san...
Hospital...
Hey, you're awake?
You were lucky since you only had first
Did the Special Investigator guys...?
You shouldn't overexert yourself.
Really? So you're a professor at the school?
Yes. I'm a third-rank substitute teacher now,
Is it here?
It certainly smells like candle wax,
What?
Imari-san's memories were... sealed?
Yes, those bad memories from that incident.
But there's a side effect.
Side effect?
Yes. Inside of Imari-san,
Kitami Reika's existence was sealed.
The father of Yoshitani who was burnt
...was using his safe deposit box?
That's correct. His father,
is using his son's name to borrow from it.
This Yoshitani Souji has been missing for the
past six months.
To his family and the media,
To investigate further,
This place is...
It's about to close.
Sure, but don't call me Head Investigator
Ah, okay!
There are five in all.
It seems like there are no others.
You two are quite beautiful.
That's true. Seems like we're gonna have some
fun.
Do you not know when to stop talking?
She's the type I like.
That's not fair!
Shut up!
You lackeys hurry up and start the ceremony.
Ceremony?
Shit. What kind of people are they?
Now their top priority should be securing an
escape route.
What's going on here?
Now stand up.
You're a lively little girl.
Why do you bother trying to fight me in this
situation?
When you stare at me with that cold gaze, I get
hot.
Now observe my foreplay.
No! No! Help!
No!
Oh! Oh, I see!
You were robbed of your virginity by this thing?
Oh, this is tight, tight!
Does your hole want a taste of this too?
Tight, tight, tight!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Now...
Time to enjoy the main dish.
Prepare... Prepare for the ceremony.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
Zazas Zazas azas.
Zazas Zazas Nasatanada Zazas.
N- No!
No!
The seal... ken.
The seal... has been broken.