Starting the Adventure
Enter Name and Character Class
Name
Class
SANTA
HERO
Hey, dude!
Name
Class
BOBO
BARBARIAN
Name
Class
PIERCE
MAGE
Name
Class
So, what should I make her?
Oh, yes, first of all, let's change her clothes. Let's see...
Let's see now, not this.
Oh, yes, that's it! I like it!
Evil Music Begins To Play
This is awesome!
CAT-SLAVE
No way!
Your name is "Pink"!
PINK
This is so cruel!
I'm so tired!
Carry me, Santa!
Are you forgetting that you're a cat-slave?
Oh?
What?
Santa, I know we've passed through here before.
Damn it, we must be lost!
I told you that we should have headed east...
Yeah!
So, what do you want me to do now?
I'm hungry!
Shut up! Go catch a mouse or something!
Huh?
I don't think we should camp out here!
If we just knew where the sun was...
Huh? What's that?
Why am I getting this nasty feeling?
Pierce! Bobo! This way!
Oh, well.
The Monster appears!
Santa...
We'd better get out of here!
Pink!
No!
Gross! It's going to eat me! Stop it!
It's going to eat Pink!
But we can't do a thing with what we have now.
It's going to molest me!
What are we going to do, Santa?
Hey, you monster!
Get your tongue off my sex-toy!
Don't you know I get really pissed when other people play with my things?
Give me back my Pink, skull-face!
He's doing pretty well.
Yep.
Or is it just a little too big for him?
Hey! Don't just stand there! Help me!
All right, I'll use my best spell.
Uh-oh, my power level's a little too low.
Hurry!
Give us a minute, Santa!
I'll need your cooperation!
What?
I don't care what you do!
Just hurry!
Wait...
You can do it, Bobo!
Oh yes, it's so hard, Bobo.
Bobo! Come now, please!
Pierce absorbs the liquid protein.
Pierce, hurry!
Boy, are you bossy.
Oh spirits of the Mother Earth,
help us in our time of need!
Send your will against our foe and make him really bleed!
Embrio!
Now that's a spell!
Hey Pink, are you still alive?
I was so scared, Santa!
Get off, you're too hot and sweaty!
Who are you?
We're just what we look like.
I'm real brave, she's a slave, and these two are a Mage and a Warrior.
My name is Sina.
Thank you for saving me.
Aw, don't mention it...
...but I wouldn't refuse an invitation to dinner, you know.
Santa!
It's not just me.
I'm not the only one.
What's wrong?
There are many more like me, held captive in a nearby dungeon.
A dungeon? Around here?
I've never heard of it.
I beg you, please rescue them!
Not a bloody chance, lady!
My body's hit-point level can only take one fight against a monster of that level per episode. Sorry.
But you said you were a hero and a warrior.
Yeah, well, business has been bad lately, so we'll take any job that pays at least one gort.
I can pay you...
What?
Nothing.
But there is the treasure.
Say what?
I've heard that there is a great treasure, deep inside the dungeon.
The dungeon's this way, right?
Right! Let's go Bobo, Pierce!
Right now?
Thank you! Please save them!
Don't worry! We're a hero and a warrior, after all.
C'mon guys!
Hey, wait up, Santa!
Yeah! Wait!
Hey Pink, come here.
What is it, Santa?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm so unlucky.
We don't know where we'll find traps, you know.
It's mind-boggling.
Yep.
What's that?
Wow!
No way! This is awesome!
Is this some kind of extra service?
Santa, this isn't right.
Shut up. I'm going in for a closer look.
I can't open it!
Hey!
That woman's gone too.
Talk about the perfect trap for Santa!
Sounds like we've got company as well.
Yep.
Slave Knights appear.
None shall pass beyond this point!
Help me!
She'll still conscious.
You can't touch us, can you?
Here!
Die!
Here, here, here!
Santa!
Pink, you're finally awake?
Why are you upside down?
I don't know, but get me down anyway!
Okay!
Is this it?
Why do I have a bad feeling about this?
Stop, little cat-girl!
Don't touch my prey!
What?
Nymphomania, the Slave Queen appears.
Don't you think it's rude,
touching my things?
Isn't that right, cat-girl?
Give Santa back to Pink,
you Snake Woman!
Looks like I'll have to get physical to teach you!
Look down! Do you see the poisonous snakes that fill my lair?
Fall, and you'll die instantly.
Santa!
Good work Pink! Don't let it go!
I didn't think you'd fall for my trick quite so easily!
And that! And that! And that!
It hurts!
How long can you endure?
Pink!
I won't let go, not even if I die!
This is the last one!
What?
He killed the hostage too?
I'm not about to die myself, you know.
That's right!
I won't let you suffer though.
Energy Psi-Burst!
I'm sorry...
Okay, let's find Pink and Santa.
Yeah.
You're tough, aren't you?
I'd like to cook a lovely girl like you.
Ouch!
Cat-girl, let me give you something special.
This is a Dildo Cobra.
It can literally kill you with pleasure.
No!
Stop!
No! Stop it!
All right, now let's put one in your lower opening as well!
Disgusting!
No!
Oh! A gusher?
Oh!
Your body is very honest.
It hurts!
Aren't you starting to feel really, really good?
I'm going to go mad.
I just love to watch a slave in convulsions.
Pink! Pink! Hang in there!
Oh, trying to stay conscious by biting your tongue?
Now, let me tell you something more.
Once that Dildo Cobra finishes giving out its poisons, it releases blood-spikes as well.
I guess I've really got you.
Torn between Heaven and Hell...
Santa!
Santa! Pink!
What?
Fire!
Thank you, Pierce!
You're finished, you reptile!
What is this intense emotion?
I'll give back what you gave,
one hundred times over!
A Sword Dancer?
What are you going to do?
Get ready for it, snake bitch!
Spirit... Sword... Cut... Blood Flower... Form!
Go to Hell, you bitch!
Pink?
Pink, are you all right?
How is Pink?
She's okay. She's conscious.
I'm glad you're all right, Santa.
We're both okay.
Okay, we kept our promise.
Now let's go get the treasure!
Awesome! Now this is what I call a good deal!
Beautiful!
Yeah!
Wonderful!
Yeehaw!
What's that?
An earthquake?
It's going to collapse!
No, no, it's mine! The treasure...
We'll never forget you.
Oh, don't mention it.
But we don't have anything to give you.
Don't worry about it.
It'd be too much trouble to dig all that up.
The treasure's nothing.
Isn't that right?
Oh, it is, is it?
Take it easy.
Thank you.
Hey Pierce, Santa was really great today, wasn't he?
Was he?
We don't need treasure!
We're Heroes and Warriors!
Hey Pierce, isn't this pretty?
Oh, Pink! What the...
Pink, give me that!
No! It's mine!
Shut up! We'll all be able to eat with that!
No! I got this by risking my own life! No!
You give me that! Give it to me!
There's such a difference between what he says and what he does, isn't there?
Yep.
Oops!
It's mine!