Bible Black Only
At the faculty room toilet...
I was raped by the devil...
I lost my virginity to the devil...
Once more...
I want to feel that sensation once more...
...from the devil!
Vice principal!
Please stop...
No...
No!
How about this?
Vice principal...
You're amazing...
It's not subsiding...
This feeling won't go away...
Vice principal.
Give me more...
This time, give it to me down there...
Ouch!
Vice principal?
I'll do as you wish.
That voice...
Yes, yes...
Please let me go.
Please don't stop.
My ass...
So strong...
Yes, this is the sensation...
This is it.
This is what I wanted...
Vice principal...
I'm the devil's slave...
The End
Bible Black Only
Secret lesson
You're late.
They're hard...
No, someone might see us.
Delicious...
Mikimoto.
Yes, manager.
Look, your nipples are getting hard.
What about down there?
It's responding well too.
Then let's strip her.
It looks fun.
Let's go.
Hey, you can have more fun
if there's a guy involved.
Pretty cunt.
It's wasteful to leave it like this.
Right?
No!
Stop it!
Stop it, please.
Amazing.
Manager...
Please, suck on it...
Yes!
Hey, this one's ready too.
No, wait!
Mine...
This is mine...
No, it's mine.
Let's do this again.
The End
Bible Black Only
Events in the locker room
Stop masturbating by yourself.
Here you go!
The End