Yes?
Are you making any progress?
Ah...yes!
Well, not really...
Maybe you should take a break.
Thank you.
Are you checking up on me?
N-No...
Where's Yuge-san?
He had an emergency.
I heard Investigator Ichikawa was under your care.
What?
Chief Yuge told me about it.
Thank you so much.
Ah, well...it was...
Oh, I see. She was an investigator from this place?
Yes...
Before your report was destroyed...
...Chief Yuge secured this file.
That's how we learned about this case.
Secured before it was destroyed?
About this wound on Investigator Ichikawa that disappeared with a strange light...
Can you tell me about it in detail?
Soon, the ritual will take place.
Now, I want you to bring me your bride.
My bride?
What the hell is that?
Oh, my.
Even though you seem pretty weak, you're quite persistent.
You're no different than the Yamanishi-kun I knew back then.
Kitami-sensei?
That's right, Yamanishi-kun.
l wanted to see you.
No!
Yamanishi-kun.
I want you to provide me with wonderful memories of this school.
Sensei!
No, Sensei!
Sensei...
Kitami-sensei...
Come.
Yamanishi-kun...
D-Do it...
Don't tease me like that...
No...
No!
No, not this...
I don't want this!
No!
No...
You can't put that big thing in my ass!
It's too big!
No...
That woman...
Onee-sama! What is this?
Stay calm!
I'll just...
O-Onee-sama...
So it was you...
That woman's puppet...
I'm sorry for making you do so much...
It's all right.
After looking at the files you sent me, I came up with an educated guess.
Devil worshipers.
We're looking for a devil's partner mentioned...
...in Chapter 17 from the ''Revelation of John.''
And this crazy cult was led by Aleister Crowley.
Even now, they're looking for the woman in red.
She is the one known to give birth...
...to a being that will be more powerful than any king in the world.
Up until recently, Crowley's granddaughter was that person.
J-Jody Crowley...
But I thought she died in a plane crash...
She is the one responsible for all these incidents...
Jody Crowley...
Takashiro-sensei, do you know her?
Yes...
So did she steal the Spear of Longinus that is said to have...
...pierced the flesh of Christ when he was tied to the cross?
It was probably her.
But, why?
In order to find the devil's partner or the woman in red.
That scrap of metal has that kind of power?
But, we haven't found any evidence that will link these crimes to her...
She may have a different objective...
...but by reviving Kitami Reika, who was after the original Bible Black...
...she thought she could find the woman in red much faster.
The woman in red will seek the original Bible Black.
In other words, it's like a compass.
Kitami Reika...
I heard she was sealed inside Imari-kun...
Yes.
I told you that when I handed Imari-san over to you.
Wait...
So, you're telling me that Imari-kun is now Kitami Reika?
Yes.
Impossible...
Before I came here, she showed up at the lab as Imari-kun!
I'll show you...
Ritual of the Vulgar!
Looks like you're finally awake.
You know what's going to happen, right, Todo-san?
Since you interrupted our ritual, we'll have to punish you severely.
How could you do...
Where's that woman?
Seems like you want to join her.
Shiraki-san!
Takashiro-sensei, what's going on?
Sensei!
Why you...
Jody-sama.
I want you two to help me.
Yes.
What just happened?
Yuge-san?
Yuge-san!
Jody!
Defend against evil spirits, drive away my bitter enemy...
End the Seven Misfortunes and bring forth good fortune...
Rin, Byo, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Destroy!
Takashiro-sensei?
Let's go, Yuge-san.
We're going to rescue Shiraki-san!
Attempted murder at Hou Hospital Report, Naoto Yamanishi
That wasn't Chief Investigator Imari...
The person who actually saved me was...
Hey, not so fast, Shiraki-san.
It's time for your meal. Cheer up.
Now, you can consume as much lust as you like.
Come on, others are waiting.
Better make it quick...
Come on, come on.
Are you not used to getting tormented?
You can't get full satisfaction with a thing like this, right?
Even though it's not your first time, it's rather tight.
Come on, get in there.
Come on.
O-Onee-sama, what are you doing?
Did you get treated well as a slave for that woman, Yuki?
Are you ready to confess, Yuki?
What is that woman's objective?
Where is she, Yuki?
Where is that woman?
Jody-sama...
Hey, you're not done with your meal yet, Shiraki-san.
You haven't had your main dish yet.
You're doing great, Shiraki-san. Come now.
You need to be punished severely for being a traitor.
Hey, you need to make a formal greeting.
Looks like Shiraki-sensei is going to give you something better, Todo-san.
Go on, Shiraki-san...
A teacher's job is to treat their students with utmost care!
I guess it's time for dessert.
Now that you're done doing it up the front, you want to do it in the back too, right?