Staring the Adventure
Enter Name and Character Class
Name
Class
SANTA
HERO
Hey dude!
Name
Class
BOBO
BARBARIAN
Name
Class
PIERCE
MAGE
Name
Class
So, what should I make her?
Oh yes, first of all, let's change her clothes. Let's see...
Let's see now, not this.
Oh yes, that's it! I like it!
Evil Music Begins To Play
This is awesome!
CAT-SLAVE
No way!
Your name is "Pink"!
PINK
This is so cruel!
I can't... I can't take it anymore!
Come on, Pink!
Please, no more.
Almost there...
It hurts!
Hey Santa, aren't you being a little rough on her?
If that's how you feel, don't ride.
Why do I have to suffer like this?
C'mon! Giddy-up!
You're a jerk, Santa! I've got big bruises all over my bottom!
Oh, be real! That's just loving discipline!
Monster!
What a jerk!
No shit.
If you don't like it, walk!
All right, this is good.
Pink!
It's too early!
Oh, shut up!
I don't like this.
A proper slave does what she's told without any backtalk!
He's lower than a snake's balls.
You got that right.
I'm not happy here!
Just hang around for a bit, okay, Pink?
Let me down! Idiot! Meanie!
A proper trap needs bait, y'know!
All right everyone, let's hide.
Santa, think of some other way!
All the blood is rushing to my head!
I hate your stupid guts, Santa!
Well, that was quick!
MONSTER
The Kusarimame appears!
No! Please! Help me!
No! Don't do it!
This is so icky!
There's got to be a better way, Santa!
Nope!
This is the only sure way!
Y'know, I always get off watching a monster make out with a girl.
I'm gonna die! No!
Hold on just a little longer, Pink!
No! Stop!
All right, Pierce!
Use your fire spell!
Boy, you're really getting bossy!
Oh Guardians of Flame, recall your rules of blood true!
For three gorts worth of magic power, the control of fire is due!
Fire!
Hot! Hot!
All right!
Ouch!
A medium level magic pearl!
Not bad.
Right, Bobo?
What the hell is this? Get off!
With this kind of loot, we can afford to stay at the Princess Hotel!
You are so cruel!
Pink receives 35 points of damage.
Get off... damn it...
Pink, it's okay now!
Come on Pink, pull the cart!
What?!
Hang in there, Pink!
Huh?
That's it, Pink!
That's Gatashi Castle's wall.
We're here!
All right!
Man, that smarts!
Pink, what the hell were you doing?
Santa, we're here!
Oh, we're here?
Lets eat, eat, eat! I'm starving!
So, you see...
Now, this is where we are now.
Wow, we sure have come a long way!
According to this map, a lake to the east may provide us with a clue.
Here's your vittles!
Wow!
This is excellent.
Let's eat!
It looks wonderful!
Here, this is for your cat slave.
No way!
This is awful discrimination.
Man, that was incredible!
I wanted to eat like they did.
Your total bill comes to 200 gorts.
Sure thing!
I think I lost my wallet.
WHAT?!
Sir?
Oh, Manager?
Trying to eat and run?
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no way!
Then pay up!
Santa...
What?
Santa, you asshole!
If you're not back with the money by tomorrow, I'll sell her off!
Wait right here, Pink!
Oh, and Mr. Manager, as long as you've got her, make her wash dishes to pay for our meal!
Man, how low can you get?
Pretty low.
Santa, you jerk! Meanie!
It's going to be hard finding something worth that much money. Maybe we should just hoof it.
How can you think such a thing?
It was a joke! A joke!
Honey Moon Fairy
All right! A Honey Moon! Her honey's worth a bundle!
I'll just take this and...
Bullseye!
Bee! Bee!
Now, to harvest the honey...
Pierce, give me a strand of your hair to hold it with.
Well, okay.
I guess it's okay.
Santa, look what I found.
I found a Lubri mushroom.
It's an aphrodisiac. For Honey Moon harvesting, it's a must!
I feel sorry for the poor thing.
Here it comes. There now...
We've got more than enough honey now.
Sorry for all of this.
Be careful.
Let's hurry back.
Right.
Pink must be worried.
What? You sold her?
Sorry! I didn't think you were going to come back, so I sold her to a dealer in the next village.
He paid a pretty good price too!
You asshole!
Damn!
Pierce, Bobo, let's go!
Right!
Let me out! Let me out!
Why waste your energy? We're going to be sacrificed.
What?
Once a month, the sacred shrine holds a special ceremony where girls are given to the monster.
That's awful! No!
Let me out! I don't want to die!
Even being with Santa's better!
Oh, will you shut up!
Maybe I should educate you some.
You won't need those clothes!
Oh, no! It's just begun!
Ouch! It hurts! It hurts!
How do you like the taste of my chains?
Forgive me!
One more time!
She creamed all over the place!
Hey, it's time!
Yes, Sir! I'll take her right away!
Oh Goddess of the Water, Yuarisla! We have brought prey for you.
Please do with them as you with.
Bring them out!
No! Let me go! No!
Be silent you!
Here! Be anointed by our goddess!
Open! Open it!
Pierce! Bobo! Santa!
What?
The Evil Yuarisla Appears!
You're so cute!
I could just eat you up!
It's so cold! Stop it! Stop it!
You monster! Stop it!
Just wait your turn!
You'll be next!
Ouch!
Now, let me absorb the life-force from inside you!
No... It's inside!
Deeper... deeper...
Help... Help me!
Young girls always taste so fresh!
Now, I shall try something different for my second course!
I'll make you feel wonderful for a few moments!
I enjoyed that.
Pink, are you okay?
Santa!
It's heavy.
Sorry about that!
Sorry to interrupt, but I'm going to take Pink back home now.
How dare you interrupt?!
I cannot forgive such impudence!
Go, destroy them!
Damn! More enemies!
Come on, Bobo!
Oh!
What power!
If we're to match strength against strength, I cannot lose!
For I, Bobo...
...am the most powerful of all!
Now, Pierce!
Right!
To all those single moving parts, answer the calling of my heart!
Ruins!
All right!
Your defeat of my Gargoyles was impressive, but don't think escaping will be as simple!
You're nothing but a big crabby bitch!
Santa!
Bobo!
That was easy!
Damn it!
Pierce! Please!
Pierce!
Santa! Pierce! You bitch!
You bitch! You bitch! You bitch!
Stop it! Cut it out!
Ouch!
Desist!
Pink!
Do you want me to finish you now?
Stop it!
Here, I'll return it to you!
So, who shall be first?
It hurts!
There!
You!
Yes, it's loosening!
Bobo!
Santa!
Pink, are you okay?
Yes, how about you, Santa?
These little baubles saved me.
I earned this money to get you back.
Santa!
And best of all, I got a free meal out of it!
What a dork. Because of you we faced near disaster!
Hey, what's with you, Pink?
I was thinking that Santa really was worried about me, after all.
Well of course. Without you I'd have to pay whenever I want to do the nasty!
Santa, you asshole!