Hand written magic book...
It was probably written
by a priest in the Middle Ages.
What a find, huh?
Look at you, you're already wet.
Big sister!
Squeeze my nipples harder!
My name is
Reika Kitami, nice to meet you!
Hey, she's cute!
"To make a woman dance naked?"
Hey Hiroko, let's
put this spell on that girl!
Who?
What does this last line mean?
Which one?
"People shall not envy but pity her."
I can't bear it anymore!
My pussy is melting.
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
How many people did
you tell about the spell?
S-Sorry...
Don't talk about it with
anybody anymore, okay?
Okay.
We don't know if it
was really magic, though...
But Rie, if it wasn't
magic, then what was it?
What do you think, Hiroko?
I can't say anything yet.
Um...
I want to ask you a favor.
K-Kozono, stop it!
Well, I think your body
has a different opinion.
Please stop.
Please stop it...
Please...
You sure, doesn't this feel good?
Yes, Hiratani...
Nami!
Come inside me!
Come!
Maybe this is it...
What?
Hiroko's tarot.
"A great change is upon you."
"Something will
change your life completely."
I don't know...
But I can tell you this...
That book...
...of magic is real.
Bible Black, Black Altar
Idiot, you wanna die?
She's crazy.
Weirdo.
Maybe she wanted to die.
Are you okay?
Yes...
Oh, yeah...
There's nothing we cannot do.
With the magic book, we are...
Takashiro.
Kozono...
Long time no see.
I heard that ever since you found a
new boyfriend you've been neglecting...
...your duties on the student council.
I know you practice magic.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Please...
Please, I need your help.
Hiratani's been cold to me recently.
I want him to want me.
I think about him all day...
It makes me feel so hot...
I'm going crazy thinking
about making love to him!
Please, make him love only me!
I want you to use
your magic to help me!
Please!
Okay.
Really?
Yes, but with one condition...
Ew, this room smells moldy!
I'm sorry, but this
is the only room available.
It's not that bad.
This is great for our witchcraft club.
From today on, this is our sanctuary.
We appreciate it, Kozono.
So, can you tell me
how to make Hiratani mine?
Of course.
Hainrou ira sabesu erimidaresi.
Deriea adore.
Yehoba iteyora madou dousi.
Have you come to your senses?
Why...
...did I fall in love with that filthy man?
It's the power of magic.
Hiroko, what was that?
A release spell.
I undid the spell.
Nami, I can make you feel really good.
I know what you want.
I've been saving up so
I can fill you up with my come.
Where are we?
What are you doing?
Come on!
Just don't kill him.
Yes, Miss Kozono.
What?
Kozono is joining our club?
She's interested in magic.
We don't need any more new members.
Besides...
...she might be still holding a grudge?
So what?
I think it's funny that she used to look
down on us, and now she's begging to join.
I like it.
Don't worry.
We have this book.
Please Kitami...
Please purify me.
K-Kozono, stop it.
I want to take that man's
disgusting smell out of me.
I want you to purify me!
But you said you were
embarrassed the other day...
I like you.
I wanted you the moment I saw you.
Doesn't it feel great?
I know you want me, too.
No!
Kozono, you're crazy.
Wow, this looks pretty serious.
We're preparing for a ritual.
Ritual?
Yes, to summon the Devil himself.
But before that, we're going to
summon something smaller for practice.
What are you going to do
when you summon the Devil?
We'll get him on our side...
...and make him use his power for us.
Sounds interesting.
If the practice goes well,
we'll summon something bigger...
...on the next night of Walpurgis.
Walpurgis...
From Goethe's Faust?
That's right.
It's the feast of witches and evil souls.
It's the night the power
of darkness is at its strongest...
What if something goes wrong?
This book is perfect.
Nothing can go wrong.
What confidence.
But we need one more thing...
This ritual needs something to work...
A sacrifice.
I'll prepare it.
Kozono...
You've changed.
So have you.
By the way, what's
the name of this club?
Rose Cross.
After the alchemists
from the Middle Ages...
The Rosicrucian.
Good name.
El erohim erohi erohim.
Savant erohim.
Eiehay Eiheyaja eiehay ado night.
Ya shadie tetora gramaton shadie!
Agura amen!
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
Hiroko...
Hiroko!
Takashiro!
I haven't seen him lately...
I wonder if he's been
picked up by somebody...
Hi, I need your help.
I found a wounded puppy nearby.
Is that true?
We will perform the
ritual tonight as we planned.
But Nami...
Even if we succeed to
summon the Devil, what if...
We will acquire a power as great
as God's, it's a risk we have to take.
Takashiro wasn't ready for it.
But we still need a...
I know.
I have read the book too.
I will prepare a virgin.
W-Who are you?
You lied to me about
the puppy, didn't you?
No, he didn't lie, Kitami.
K-Kozono...
No!
Why?
Why did you do such a thing...
I need you to be our sacrifice.
You're going to be our precious
sacrifice, and we'll receive great power.
W-What are you talking about?
But I'll let you have fun first.
Finally...
No!
Too bad, I liked her a lot...
Put her to sleep and take
her to the room before the ritual.
You can do
whatever you want until then.
Yes, ma'am.
Just one thing,
you can only do her ass, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Wait!
Please, help me!
Kozono!
Walpurgis night...
Oh no!
It hurts.
No, it hurts!
You're going to tear my butt!
What can I do?
I only can do your ass.
You've got some great tits.
Come on, suck it!
I can't bear it anymore!
Hey, she told us
not to take her virginity.
She's not gonna find out.
I'm going to enjoy both her holes.
No...
No!
What do you mean "No"?
I know you love it.
Look how hard your nipples are!
How are you feeling?
Kozono, you must stop this ritual.
We should stop using magic.
Amateurs like us should stay
away from it before it's too late.
What are you talking about?
This was all your idea, remember?
We all saw what the
power of darkness could do!
It's going to be a lot stronger this time.
Please stop it.
Our sacrifice should be here soon.
Kozono!
Heikas heikas estei biberoi.
Take her out.
Rie, Saki, please think about this.
When I get the power,
I'll take revenge on three of them...
I'll make them pay for turning
me into Hiratani's sex slave!
Sorry, Hiroko.
Just until we finish our ritual...
Sacrificial lamb...
May you be the pillar of strength...
Why?
Slain sacrificial lamb, give us
the strength of the lord of darkness.
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
No...
No!
Something's wrong!
The Gate of Orkus is
not opening all the way.
Maybe we did something wrong.
No, we did exactly what the book said.
We didn't make a mistake.
Then why?
We failed?
We killed her, what are we going to do?
Not enough...
There's not enough...
There's not enough blood.
What are you saying?
It's too late now.
It's not too late.
What do you...
Nami, have you lost your mind?
What are you talking about?
We lost our senses a long time ago.
Saki!
No!
Here it is, I found it!
What are you doing, Rie?
Look, the gate is about to open...
I can hear the bells of hell.
Come, Berzelt,
and grant me your powers!
It hurts.
It hurts...
Girl, do you want to live?
Do you wish a contract with me?
I don't want to die...
I don't want to die!
Saki, Rie!