Heikas heikas estei biberoi.
El erohim erohi erohim.
Savant erohim.
Eiehay Eiheyaja.
Eiehay ado night.
Ya shadie tetora.
Gramaton shadie!
Agiosu oh heikas.
Iktron ah thanatos.
Agura amen!
You are the sacrifice.
You will feed the power of the demon.
Why?
As the sacrifice dies, please bestow
upon us the power of the dark gods...
Oh, sacrifice...
Give us the power to control the demon's mischief.
May you open the door of heaven...
Open your door...
May your prince...
...open your eternal door.
The king of glory will enter.
The eternal king is a king of kings...
God is a king of glory.
Father, son, and holy ghost.
Why me?
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
No!
Minase!
Oh hey, lmari.
What's up?
Minase, let's eat lunch together.
What?
Did you already eat?
Well, you were in the bathroom so long...
Is that so?
You ate it during class, didn't you?
The school bell just went off, you couldn't have...
...finished such a big lunch already.
What is that?
Nothing.
Did you bring two lunches?
Kind of...
I have to go.
Where are you going?
That's none of your business.
You have some rice on your face!
Come in.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Teacher, what did you
want to talk with me about?
Ms. Ito, have you eaten yet?
N-No, not yet.
Really?
Then...
I'll treat you.
Ero erohim ero erohim zabatoerio.
Teacher, Teacher Kitami...
I feel kind of strange...
It's very hot down here.
Teacher, stop!
It's so bad...
That's true.
I'm being bad.
Then, I'll stop this!
No.
D-Don't stop it.
You want it or not?
You decide.
Don't stop it...
Say, "Please don't stop it."
P-Please don't stop it.
Don't stop, please.
Say, "I want you."
l-l-l-I want you.
Good girl...
It's so good!
Your hole feels so good!
Teacher!
Teacher Kitami, you're so good!
Do you like the taste of my member?
It's yummy...
Very delicious...
Then, I'll let you eat more...
I'll give you every last drop.
Teacher...
Teacher, Kitami...
This one isn't a virgin, either...
I have to find an unspoiled body...
...before the night of Walpulgiss...
All this mischief...
I thought so...
It shouldn't be this way...
Minase!
Rika Shiraki...
I'm sorry, I'm late.
I had a student council meeting.
N-No problem.
Did you write this?
Since yesterday...
...I haven't been able to stop thinking about you.
S-Shiraki...
I think only about you...
I can't breathe...
Minase.
Minase...
Make love to me...
Please, right now.
I can't stand it any more.
S-Shiraki...
Minase, you don't like me?
That's not it...
Actually, I've longed for you.
I'm so happy...
Touch me...
Don't make me wait...
Please...
Minase...
It feels so good.
Minase.
Please rape me, right now.
Please...
Minase.
Hurry...
That's a good look...
I didn't know you were so horny.
It's because of you.
You made me like this.
I can see your special place.
No.
I'm embarrassed.
You're a girl with a cute
face, but you smell so strong.
No, don't smell down there.
Minase, stop it.
But, it smells very good.
Really?
Yeah, I could smell it forever.
I'm so happy...
Shiraki, lift your hip up.
Okay.
It's done.
Will it work?
I don't know...
You don't know?
No way!
I pricked my finger on a needle for this!
If Saeki can't do it, then I probably won't be able to.
True.
It would be too weird if Saeki tried doing this for her.
Not Minase, though...
Imari, you shut up.
I'll enchant the charm now.
Charm?
Murai.
Afterword, put it secretly in Asada's bag.
Y-Yeah.
All right.
Eroi erohim eroe zabato.
Elion eshelsadoni ya.
Yatetoragramaton sadi.
Minase!
Emergency!
Asada!
They suddenly started...
Asada was walking with his girlfriend...
...but when he met Murai, he confessed his love for her.
But they just started doing it as soon as he confessed?
That's strange, really strange!
Really!
What are you guys doing?
Stop it!
Shiraki...
Where do you think you are?
Let go!
What are you doing?
Get your hands off me!
Murai!
No, let me go!
Asada!
Everybody, don't just watch, help us!
Shiraki.
Minase.
Minase, please come inside me.
Shiraki...
I can feel you inside of me.
It feels so good, even though it's my first time...
I feel good, too...
You're so good...
Harder, harder...
Minase.
You're too tight, I'm coming.
Wait.
I'll...
I'll come soon...
I'm coming.
I'm about to...
l-I have to take it out.
No!
Come inside!
But...
It's okay!
Give me everything!
Fill me with your come!
Good...
It's so good, Minase.
Hey, Minase, let me look at it.
No...
Oh, is your drawing bad or something?
That's not true.
I just haven't finished yet!
Come on, it's fine.
I told you not to...
The drawing is good, but...
What's this?
I draw what I see.
You could have told me first!
Minase, lmari!
Teacher Takashiro...
You guys really are the perfect couple.
Hey, Minase...
What?
What's up?
No...
Never mind.
Teacher Kitami...
What are you doing here?
Well, I was looking for something...
Do you need any help?
No thank you.
Any signs of power are well hidden...
Could it be?
Yesterday...
What?
What happened to Murai yesterday...
That was a weird coincidence, right?
Of course.
Saeki actually believes in magic,
but she even said it was a coincidence...
What's wrong, lmari?
Saeki...
Minase...
I have to talk with you.
Well...
Then, I'm leaving.
You don't need to.
Thanks, Ms. Imari.
S-See you...
Minase...
You always deny the existence of magic, right?
Yes.
But you used it yesterday...
...on Murai...
And...
...on Shiraki, today...
Sorry, but President Shiraki would never really fall in love with you.
This is my house.
Come on in.
What are you, a black magic fangirl?
Is this really the room of a young woman?
Don't talk like my parents.
You can relax.
There is no one except us.
So, what's the story?
I want...
...your secret.
I don't have any secret.
Liar.
You're using love curses to...
...manipulate the hearts of others and give orgasms.
Without some kind of secret, you couldn't do it.
Minase...
Have you heard about the magic
club there was twelve years ago?
It's only a rumor, right?
Their magic was just simple at first...
But...
However...
They got deeper and deeper into it...
They tore up animals to give their blood and souls to the demons...
I don't believe it.
They performed ancient arcane ceremonies...
And finally...
On the night of Walpulgiss, twelve years ago.
I'm leaving.
Wait, Minase.
I don't know what a Walpulgiss is.
I'm not interested...
I can't deal with it.
Wait!
Don't cheat on me.
I'm sure you're using magic...
I told you that was a...
Coincidence?
Minase...
Tell me your secret...
Please...
I'll pay for it...
I wonder what Ms. Saeki wanted to talk to him about.
Minase has been acting strangely...
Tell me...
...your secret.
Hey...
Don't ask now...
You promised you'd tell me if I did it...
You said you'd make me come.
I could open the window and shout!
Please, continue.
I have a magic book...
What kind of book?
It's not like the books in this room.
More...
More like an original, hand-written book.
How did you get it?
Can I see it?
Hey, where is the magic book, now?
In...
In the bag.
Thank you, Minase.
How do you like it, Minase?
Is it good?
Your breasts are so soft...
It feels so good...
Come, come...
...all over me!