It's squeaky!
Your ass is wonderful!
My butt feels so good!
It feels fantastic!
Why?
Why is it so good?
Imari!
Minase, thank you for
bringing Miss Imari.
She is the vision of health.
Such a wonderful body.
Don't stop!
Do it more!
If you stop now, I'll go crazy!
Oh, this child!
I'm coming!
Go ahead, Miss Imari!
Come in front of Minase, still a virgin!
Come on, let Minase see you come
for the first time in your life!
Minase...
Minase is watching.
Imari!
Minase!
I'm coming!
Imari!
Minase, why don't you come with her?
I'm coming, Miss Imari!
I'm coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Kitami is...
Kitami is planning to take over
Miss Imari's body and defy the devil.
Impossible!
How?
She knows how.
Ma'am.
What's the matter, Miss Takashiro?
It won't stop.
They gave me huge
amounts of those pills.
I thought I was used to pills but...
Then why don't you take a hot shower?
Minase...
Yes?
Take me.
Ma'am?
No, if you do that I'II...
...come!
I'll come...
Minase!
It feels so good!
I'm going to come again!
So strong!
I'm going to come again, Minase!
I'm coming too!
Let's come together!
Let it come wherever you want!
I'm coming!
Reika Kitami is going to...
...perform the ritual on the night of
Walpurgis just like twelve years ago.
Having trouble sleeping?
Miss Takashiro...
Minase...
It's so big and hard...
Miss Takashiro!
Please...
Please Minase...
The drug is still in your system...
Do it harder!
I'm coming!
Imari...
Minase...
S-Shiraki...
Shiraki...
Minase, how could you?
I like only you, Minase.
I love you.
Minase, you don't even care if
I'm having sex with someone else...
You didn't even try
to save me yesterday.
And I stopped by at
your place earlier...
M-Miss Takashiro!
It's your fault.
Please Minase...
Please make love to
me one last time.
Minase!
It's so big and hot!
Minase...
Minase, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Please come with me!
I can feel it!
I can feel you coming inside me!
Please give it all to me!
Thank you, Minase.
I love you.
Hold it, Miss Shiraki!
Eroi erohim tzaba otrieohn
Tetoragramaton saday
Minase!
M-Miss Takashiro...
Don't move.
Heiotto heiwauai sebrune hanael
Miss Takashiro?
I was caught off guard the other day,
but I wouldn't let that happen again.
We will purify the altar and sacrifice.
Now fill up the holy cup.
Lord of the underworld...
We call upon the Lord of Darkness...
And he shall become our God.
Damn it!
Minase, calm down.
It's all my fault!
If I didn't find this stupid book...
...none of this would
have happened to Shiraki.
And Imari...
Because of me, Imari is...
Where are you, Imari?
She's probably in the
basement of the school.
Wait, you're just going to
end up like you did yesterday.
Miss Takashiro, you've got to help me.
With your magic power,
we can bring Kitami down.
My magic is no match for the
real evil power she possesses.
They will perform the
ritual at midnight tonight.
At least, Miss Imari will
be kept alive until then.
Minase, I need you to
help me with something.
There is one spell in this book
that might be able to stop Kitami.
It's scripted right here on this page...
It's called the "Forbidden Spell."
Forbidden Spell?
There was no blood on the page
when I saw this book the last time...
It must be from the
ritual twelve years ago.
It's very hard to read, but I think
I can make out the names of the gods.
And I recognize some of
the letters written here...
But still...
I'm going to try to piece
it together with my memories.
With your memories?
It's a long shot, but that's the only way
we have now to stop that devil, Reika Kitami.
We don't need to kill Kitami.
All we need to do is stop the ritual, then
Kitami will run out of time, and perish.
But what if...
What if we can't stop them?
Then Kitami would obtain
the body of Miss Imari.
And Miss Imari would be sent to Hell
for the sins Kitami has committed.
Tonight, on the night of Walpurgis...
...I will leave this
cursed body and be reborn.
And when this ritual succeeds...
...I will punish those who are
wretched and sinful in place of God.
I will become the ruler of the millennium and
leave my name in the Book of Revelations.
You are the chosen ones.
And I must have a new body
to accomplish our plan.
Let us begin the ritual.
We're running out of time...
Don't give up, Minase.
Eiehay eiheyaja eiehay ado night.
Agios otesk esherhus atanaton.
N-No!
Agra eimehn.
No!
Miss Takashiro!
Wait, we're almost there...
No!
Miss Kitami, please stop it!
I can't believe this
body is going to be mine...
You are so beautiful, Imari.
No!
Imari!
You've been saving
yourself for a long time...
I will take your precious virginity!
No!
Don't worry, it only
hurts for a second...
No, please don't kill me!
It's time for me to say
good bye to this body...
Please stop it!
It's too quiet...
It's pitch dark...
She must've created a barrier...
Cheap trick...
Eekeh zodoheecal Seguehn daroh!
Let's go!
I can't believe she would
ditch me for her boyfriend.
I want a boyfriend too!
Who's there?
I knew you would come.
Saeki!
Miss Shiraki tried to warn you, but
I guess you are just that stupid, huh?
Miss Saeki, we are in bit of a
hurry, will you let us go?
And you think we would
just listen to you?
Juisrhufshe Jepolkdonom!
Minase, stay back!
Zodor arohendor phurzondeh.
The Princes of darkness,
Astaros and Asmodeus...
Our Lord Lucifer...
Please, stop it!
Help me!
You are all crazy!
We offer you this sacrificial lamb...
Slay this sacrificial lamb, and give
us the strength of the lord of darkness.
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
Minase!
Open the gates of eternity.
The King of Glory shall enter.
Lord of Sabbath, Lord of
Baphomet, accept our sacrifice!
Grant my wish, and save
me from this eternal agony!
Minase!
Those who rebel against the will of God.
I command you to leave this world.
Who the hell...
Minase!
Fools, it's too late.
All you can do is watch me.
I'll kill you when I'm done.
I won't let it happen.
Gate keeper of the Heavens...
I possess the great power of the
gods, I hold the secrets of magic.
I ask you to close the Gate of Orkus.
Don't you get it?
Your spell won't work on me!
Minase...
I possess the great power of the
gods, I hold the secrets of magic.
What a fool!
What's that?
I ordered my followers to kill
those girls after they enjoy them.
Aren't you going to save them?
You're just showing me an illusion!
Believe what you want, I don't have
time to play with you right now.
No...
Please stop it!
See, my life's depending on it...
I suggest you leave.
I won't let anyone get in my way.
M-Minase...
Minase!
Jesus Jesus, Nester Jesus.
Hein ron hirai sabeios.
Herim radisha redieah adonai.