Bible Black Only
Virgin Hunting
Obscene dance of the devils
Hey, have you ever done it with a girl?
No, l haven't...
l see...
Oh no, it's getting hard already...
Saeki-san...
Wow.
l didn't know your cock was so huge...
S-Saeki-san, l think l'm about to...
No, don't climax yet.
But l can't hold it...
Amazing...
You released that much but you're still rock hard...
"Locker Room"
lt's better to do it with a real girl than be a Peeping Tom, right?
Calm down...
That's not fair.
l'm coming!
Don't release it inside!
That's impossible!
Hey teacher, do you have a girlfriend?
No, well...
Well, you see...
ls she giving you pleasure?
Well, l...
Then...
What are these?
Wait a minute, are you still a virgin?
W-Well...
Tell me the truth.
Yes.
Dissection!
Let's dissect this guy!
We'll take good care of you.
Liquids taken from the fresh victims...
After the liquids are consumed...
...show me the pleasures of your magic.
The End
Secret torture
Bible Black Only
And so...
...people's actions are sometimes controlled by their hormones.
Now let's find out the statistics and see...
...how these hormones affect the body and its actions...
l'm sorry...
No...
What's happening to me?
Minase-kun!
Excuse me...
Professor...
Stop it...
These clothes aren't meant for a student...
l can't give credits to a slutty girl like you...
What...
Here you go.
lt looks good on you.
Now...
Professor, it's embarrassing...
lt's cold!
No, it's too much! l can't hold it...
No, please!
Professor, l can't hold it...
Please don't...
There...
Don't put that inside!
l can't hold it anymore...
lt's coming out...
ls it painful?
You don't have to hold it in.
No...
That looks nice.
l'll make you feel better now.
Feel free to release it.
No...
No!
l'm coming!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
lf you put that inside...
No...
l'm going to break it...
l'm putting too much pressure on it...
l'm scared...
No!
lt's amazing!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Do it once more...
This time in the ass...
The End
That's a teacher...
Bible Black Only
lt's not easy dealing with seniors.
Let's see, after Habuo-kun is...
Oh my, is this me?
ls this how the boys see me?
Don't stare at me like that, everyone...
lt's embarrassing.
No...
l told you to go according to the attendance list.
lf you do that...
l'll come...
Get in line everyone...
l'll do you all with my mouth...
You released it three times already, but you're still rock hard.
You can't concentrate on our studies like this.
Yes, yes!
Hurry, hurry!
l want you to do me!
Yes, yes, yes!
Here's another one!
No...
Don't do it so rough...
No, don't...
You can't...
Let me get some action.
Come on, you can do it.
Yes, yes!
l can't hold it any longer...
l'll come!
How many more are there?
lf it keeps going like this...
The End