No...
It feels good!
M-My ass...
My ass! My ass!
My ass feels good! I feel like I’m going crazy!
This penis tastes good! Penis... tastes good...
I'm cumming...
There’s so much cum.
I’m going to be such a fantastic slave
by the time you return, Master!
It feels good!
More... More...
Streets of Olympus
If you're asking about this girl, I gave her a ride.
Really?
I remember because elf maids are rare.
Do you know her?
She’s my missing older sister.
Can you please take me to where she went?
Please!
Recently, there has been disappearances
happening one after another.
It sounds like there’s been more policing of the area,
but you should still be careful.
Especially a young girl like you.
Coming!
May I ask who is here?
Meru?
Meru.
I was so worried Syl-neesan!
Nobody had any idea where you went.
Really? I thought I sent a telegram saying that I had arrived,
but I guess I forgot.
So that’s what happened.
You're just the same as always, Nee-san.
We were so worried!
I'm getting an uncomfortable feeling from this place...
Don’t say that, just relax.
What's this?
This is...
It's cum! No need to hold back, have as much as you want!
N-Nee-san!
Nee-san! Syl-neesan!
This is the room in the mansion where
you will polish your genitals.
I welcome you.
Welcome to the Residence of Obscene Art!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net v
Translation: Ainomiko | Timing: Mr.Mew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
No! That's...
Stop! Don’t touch me!
Nee-san! Snap out of it!
I’ll use my magic to save you...
Too bad, it would be easier if you could use
magic without having to recite a spell.
Meru, let's train together.
No! Not there...
No... Don't!
Ow!
No...
It hurts!
What's the matter, Meru?
If you don't do it soon, the dirty liquid will come squirting out.
S-Spirits of the wind,
appear to me now!
No good! Once again, from the beginning.
Don’t go any deeper into my bum!
No more! If you enter me more than this, my bum will rip...
Amazing! Meru can take both of those thick cocks!
Looks delicious.
What’s wrong, Meru?
Do you enjoy feeling cocks in the place
where poop usually comes out?
Feels electric, doesn't it?
Hey Meru, how about my master and I make use of you?
I...
Okay, Meru?
As long as I’m with Nee-san.
Look, Meru!
My penis is hard and itching to be inside of you!
Nee-san, it can’t be that you had your body changed!?
Nee-san, stop...
What's going on?
It hurts, but it feels good...
The semen in this cock has the ability to turn pain into pleasure!
Your body will never feel as good as it does inside this mansion!
Cum...
Wow, there's so much...
Your pussy feels so good!
Nee-san, I like it! I like cock!
Your pussy is pulsing!
I like it! I like it!
Nee-san! I like cock!
Meru, Meru!
Nee-san, Nee-san!
I’m cumming!
I'm... I’m cumming!
You’re...
You've just been thrown away by your master.
Huh?
Your master, Agnes, has decided to refuse
the cost of training you and taking you in.
As per the rules, the two of you put up for auction.
Well then, first of all it's the Hors-d'oeuvre.
Let's go see the prey Lilit found us.
A missing person’s investigation, eh?
There’s been a lot of girls going missing.
And now I get to savour a girl like this? Fantastic!
So warm! This pussy is the best!
Look at these awesome’s cow tits!
Oh god, I’m going to cum!
I’m going to cum inside!
I tried to hold off, but I blew my load pretty quick.
Hey, what’s wrong?
N-No way!
Please run away! I can’t control myself!
I said to run away!
Even though I said that...
No, my nipples!
It feels amazing having two cocks inside of me.
I’m going to cum... I’m going to cum...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
This is charming magic!
The missing persons incident, it can’t be that...
What is your job?
To be the sex bait that lures in your prey.
Let's go, Lilit. It should be time the main dishes arrive.
There’s a lot of people here.
That’s because the merchandise on
sale today is of the finest quality!
Finest quality?
Just see for yourself.
Beautiful slave sisters have been placed
in the middle of the meeting hall.
A troll's dick is rubbing inside my bitch pussy and asshole!
What an awesome orgasm face!
And look at the younger sister!
She’s taking it in the ass and looks like she’s loving it!
Awesome!
Keep thrusting into me more!
Nee-san, Nee-san!
Meru...
And that’s it, the viewing has finished.
We’ll now commence the auction.
We’re two sisters who've been abandoned by our master,
Nee-san, Nee-san!
so make sure to bid a lot and take us home!
1500!
1800!
I love the smell of cock... such a turn on...
3000!
Cocks... Cocks...
3200!
4000!
6000!
Please...
Please bid more!
Cum... Give me lots of cum!
10,000!
Cocks are amazing!
13,000!
20,000!
Amazing!
We have 20,000, going once, twice...
50,000!
It’s been a while, Sylphy.
Master!
Agnes-sama!
Show me the bodies of both you and your sister.
Yes!
Everyone, please watch our bodies one more time!
Nee-san, Nee-san, Nee-san!
Master! Please looks at us!
Two sisters are cumming right before your eyes!
Nee-san... Nee-san...
I’m cumming! I’m cumming...
Master, we're covered with cum!
Are you satisfied?
I owe you one.
That was an awful lot of money to pay in this case.
And yet, now that it’s over I’m smiling.
It was lucky that I ever got the younger sister, too.
It seems that my life isn't going to be boring anymore.
While we must be careful while looking
for prey and barely make a living.
Humans are certainly interesting beings.
And now...
I wonder how a person drowned in his own desires would taste?