Master's penis is very hot.
You're doing great.
I feel great, Kasumi.
I'm back.
Sis...
Welcome back, Kaho.
Master's cum is delicious.
Kasumi allowed Kaho to find out about the slave contract.
If she continues being my slave, their lives as sisters can't continue.
But it seems Kasumi has a different intention in mind.
Whatever the case, I seem to have sold the stocks at their peak.
Now that I think about it, compared to what Kasumi was like before...
Kasumi has been completed engulfed by the pleasure.
No, saying "engulfed" is a bit wrong.
Kasumi is now completely in love with me.
Well, leaving Kasumi aside.
Geez, there's no point in remaining a slave.
I'm going to dissolve...
...this kind of contract.
Eh? Would that be fine with Kasumi-chan?
Sis is...
Don't talk about my sister!
So... dissolve that contract!
I don't have any connection with you anymore!
Kaho insisted on dissolving the contract of slavery.
I also agreed to it.
And my relationship with Kaho should have ended there.
But why is she still staying at my house as a housekeeper?
Kasumi didn't approve or disapprove of Kaho's decision.
And she teases me even more now in front of Kaho.
She might be doing it to make her little sister give up on her.
It seems like she feels really good...
Amazing.
Those... those kinds of things...
Sis!
Amazing! Amazing!
That's really amazing!
That sort of thing.
Sis!
Master!
It's painful.
Why is it only my sister?
Why did I say I don't want to be a slave anymore?
If I hadn't quit being a slave, I could have been loved like Sis...
It's... it's so painful like this...
Please, Master!
Let me be your slave.
I love you, Master!
I've always loved you, ever since back then...
So make love to me...
Make love to me like that, too.
It feels good. It feels good!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
The hidden camera filmed Kaho masturbating two days ago.
Kaho regrets not being a slave.
She wants to return to her former position.
And she's thinking of me...
Kaho is in pain right now.
I'm the only one who can relieve her of that pain.
At any rate, Kaho keeps repeating that unsightly masturbation.
I have to hurry up and think of something.
You're already soaking wet.
This place is wide open, too.
It's embarrassing.
Since you're already this wet, we don't need any foreplay, right?
That's...
Alright, I'm putting it in.
Amazing.
It's going in.
The vibrator is going in.
It's in so deep...
I'm turning on the switch.
Yes. Please, Master.
It's inside.
It's going deep inside me.
It feels good, twist it more!
The vibrator feels good.
It feels so good.
I'm going to come.
Kasumi's going to come.
I'm coming!
Please put it inside me, Master.
I want Master's hard dick.
Sure.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
It feels good!
Just as I thought, the real thing feels so much better!
Kasumi, shake your hips more.
Yes, I'll serve you even better, Master.
Please taste my lewd spot.
I'm feeling it deep inside.
Master's dick is great.
Like this, it'll feel even better.
I'm happy. It feels good.
Master, Kasumi is happy.
I'm so happy, and it feels so good.
Ah, I'm going to come!
I'm about to come!
Let's come together, Kasumi!
Yes, Master.
I'm going to come!
I'm coming!
Kasumi!
Master's sperm is inside me.
I'm so happy you came inside...
Kasumi, in just a few more days, our contract will come to a end.
That can't...
So I'm going to be thrown away after this is over?
You're throwing me away, Master?
It's not about throwing you away or not.
It's a part of the contract.
I remember it.
I thought the contract expired a long time ago.
You know...the word of masters and slaves has set rules that both sides should follow accordingly.
You're a bad slave if you can't understand this.
I'm terribly sorry.
I didn't understand this.
I've made master unhappy.
I'm truly sorry.
It seems like you haven't been disciplined properly yet.
60 days is not enough.
No, not enough at all.
How about it?
After the contract is up, do you want to continue being my slave?
Yes, I'd be glad to.
I have a bad memory, so 60 days isn't enough.
One day, I'll become a perfect slave for sure.
So until that day comes, please continue to discipline me strictly.
Please.
We're going to need a new contract, then.
Yes, please.
I will do anything Master wishes for.
Anything?
Then before we form the new contract, I have something to ask of you.
Yes, I'll show you I can do it for sure.
So please let me form the contract.
I want Kaho.
Kasumi, you have to help me.
Like I was saying, I want Kaho to be my slave.
I want her to be a slave, just like you.
Aren't I enough?
Why? Am I not good enough for you?
You see, Kasumi...
It isn't about you being enough or not; it's about whether I want it or not.
I want Kaho.
But if Kaho became a slave, what's going to happen to me?
Nothing is going to happen to you.
If you obey this order,
we'll form a new contract, and you'll be able to continue being my slave.
But when Kaho is with Master,
what should I do?
Ah... that's right...
We can't always limit it to two person play.
No, I don't want this!
It'll be too painful to be left alone.
I get it. I understand your pain.
But Kaho is going through more pain than you.
Eh? What do you mean by that?
Master, it's painful.
Why is it only my sister?
What is Kaho doing?
If I hadn't quit being a slave, I could have been loved like Sis...
It's... it's so painful like this.
Please, master. Let me be your slave.
I love you... I love you, Master!
I've always loved you, ever since back then.
How can this...
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Don't you think you should save her, as her sister?
Kasumi!
I was wrong.
Master.
Please allow Kaho to become Master's slave.
Please!
The promise I made not to lay my hands on her...
I couldn't keep it. I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault that she's in so much pain.
So please liberate her from this pain.
Don't cry.
It'll mess up the face I love so much.
Master! Master!
While Kasumi was on duty this morning, she told Kaho to come here.
Well, she isn't a slave, so there's no helping it if she doesn't come...
But Kaho will come for sure.
So you've come, Kaho.
What do you want with me?
What do I want? Shouldn't you know that already, since you're here?
What are you saying?
I'm not your slave anymore.
That's...
If you do it with me just once today, I'll dispose of all the photos and data.
And the underhanded threats will stop from now on.
B-But...
You know...
Since we've already done it, would it matter if I did it with you one more time?
But that couldn't be helped.
That's right. And the number of inevitabilities will only increase by one.
Now, be my partner because it can't be helped.
You don't want that kind of picture exposed, right?
That's right. This is something that can't be helped.
No!
Kaho looks great in any pose.
You have a good body for S&M.
No!
Don't look at me!
Sorry for the wait.
Master.
Sis!
Why?
You came just in time, Kasumi.
It suits you.
You're really cute.
It's embarrassing.
But if it pleases Master, that makes me very happy.
There, there.
I'll take good care of you in a bit.
Yes. I'm looking forward to it, Master.
Kaho, today I want the three of us to have fun together. How about it?
I can't do something like that.
Don't hold back.
You want to feel good, right?
No way. There's no way I could do something like that with Sis...
Is that so?
It can't be helped, then. You can watch from there.
Kaho said she doesn't want to join us.
It can't be helped, so we'll do it by ourselves.
I'm so happy! I can have Master all to myself.
Kasumi, take off your skirt and come over here.
Yes, Master.
Alright. I'm putting it in, Kasumi.
It went in, Master!
It went inside, Master.
Master's penis is deep inside...
Just a bit more and it'll be all the way in.
Master's dick is filling up my insides...
Well, how's this? You like it like this, right?
Yes, I like it.
I love being penetrated hard like this...
Master, it's in deep... my insides are pulsing!
How is it? Does it make you happy?
Yes, it feels good... I'm happy, it feels so good!
Very good, Kasumi.
It makes me happy to have a slave like you.
I'm happy. I'm happy, Master.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy I became Master's slave.
You're gonna come? You're about to come, right?
Good, I'll give you a reward.
Let's climax together.
Yes, Master. Together... together!
I'm coming!
It's coming... it's coming in...
So much of Master's reward is coming in...
I'm happy.
It felt good, right, Kasumi?
I felt really good.
Kasumi, are you glad you became my slave?
Yes, Kasumi is really happy about becoming Master's slave.
But you know, only the older sister is having all the fun.
Doesn't it make you feel sorry for the younger sister?
But, that's Kaho's own decision.
Sis.
I heard everything from Master.
Kaho became Master's slave and then gave it up right away.
That's right. So you heard all about it.
After hearing that, I was really sad at first.
Kaho sacrificed herself for me.
Yet I indulged in the happiness of becoming a slave.
I felt like I owed you a lot.
I... I'm already at the point where I can't live without Master.
I love you. I love you so much.
As a slave, being loved and rewarded by Master is my everything now.
You're jealous of me receiving rewards from Master, right?
I'm not...
Poor Kaho... you've been holding back all the love juice flowing out from that wet place, haven't you?
Sis...
I'm already...
I regret that I quit being a slave.
I'll be more honest from now on.
So... so...
Make me a slave... let me become a slave again!
Please, Master... please listen to Kaho's wish.
Please.
Then I'll renew the contract with both of you.
Swallow it.
Yes.
I'm coming!
Kaho, I'm cumming on your tits.
You did well.
It felt really good, Kaho.
Thank you, Master.
Master, I have a request.
What is it?
I... I can't hold it in anymore.
Okay, I understand.
It's coming in... Master's penis is coming in!
It's great. You'll become a good slave.
Master!
Here, Kaho... drink Master's sperm, together with my love juice.
Let's all have fun doing this together.
You're both great... you both make great slaves.
Kaho, it's good.
Lick it more... lick your sister's pussy more!
It's great, just a bit more.
I'll fill you up with a reward that won't lose to Kasumi's.
It feels good, I'm gonna come. I'm about to come!
Kaho! Kaho!
It's coming, I'm coming, Kaho!
I'm coming!
I'm coming.
Master's dick is making me cum!
Master...
After that, for the next few days,
in order to make Kaho into a perfect slave,
I brought her to a high class love hotel.
I'm going to completely transform your mind and body into that of a slave.
We're going to have sex like crazy here; you're gonna have fun, right?
I'm scared.
What's going to happen to me?
Didn't I tell you already?
You're going to be transformed into a real slave.
Your boobs are shaking.
Can you feel it?
I'll finger you here...
Stop, I'm too sensitive.
It feels so good.
My clit feels so good!
I can't... I can't!
You're coming, right?
If you're going to come, say it properly!
I'm coming!
Kaho is coming!
That's...
From here on out, I'm going to develop that place with this.
I just came, and I'm already...
It went in...
Alright, I'm going to move it now.
You look like you're feeling good.
It's stretched out even more because of the vibrator.
No way...
This feels completely different than usual...
This is your G spot. It feels amazing, right?
Take your time enjoying this feeling for me.
Amazing, Master. It feels so good!
Very good, Kaho.
I'm coming, I'm gonna come...
Kaho is coming!
Master.
Kaho.
And like this, Kaho became my slave, too.
And then...
TL Note: The tattoo on their body says "For Master Okura's use only".
Oh! Your new tattoos really are pretty.
Now, let me see you two touching each other again for today.
Master.
It's not limited only to sex.
Right now, half of my feelings are that of a lover.
It would be great if things could continue like this.
Kasumi and Kaho probably feel the same way.