Master.
What do you want? Say it. Beg me for it.
Please do it with me... please do perverted things with me, Master.
Master.
Master, I can't take it anymore.
Please let me feel more of you, Master.
Why not? As you wish, I'll do perverted things with you.
Master.
It's good, as always!
That's great.
Her name is Miyamori Kaho.
She's the little sister of my homeroom teacher, Miyamori Kasumi.
That's why she's making lunches for me.
Ah, I'm so hungry.
Welcome-
Ah!
Eh? Miyamori, aren't part time jobs prohibited?
As to why Miyamori is here, she is repaying her family's debt.
Knowing that, I pretend not to know the truth...
...and buy lunches from her every day for 750 yen.
Um, Okura-kun.
I won't be bringing any more lunches starting tomorrow.
Eh? Why?
My sister found out about me bringing you lunches.
I'm Sorry!
Kasumi-chan did?
Yeah, she said she'd feel troubled if she borrowed money from you.
That's why...
Is that so?
Here's the money you've been lending me, Okura-kun. I'm returning it to you.
You've really done a lot for me.
I'm really sorry.
Preparation Room
Kasumi-chan!
Hey! It is not Kasumi-chan, it's Miyamori-sensei.
Why don't you get it?
Leaving that aside, aren't you being a bit cruel to Kaho?
If it's only lunches, you don't have to step in, right?
I won't allow that shameless way of repaying our debt.
You think Miyamori's been making lunches every day because of the debt?
That's not it-
Ah, there you are.
So you were over here, huh, Miyamori-sensei?
Kasumi-chan?
Miyamori-sensei, I'll be troubled if you don't pay this month's interest.
This guy is a debt collector?
Um... Can you wait a bit longer? We shouldn't talk about this at school.
That would be a problem!
Ah, wait.
What's mine is mine. Now pay it back as soon as possible.
Um... but I don't have the money right now.
Huh? Are you fucking with me?
If you don't pay it back, I'll use this  for payment.
Uniform maniacs will like this kind of getup.
N-No!
Mister, enough already!
How much?
Okura-kun!
A brat like you doesn't have that much money.
Whatever, just tell me.
At the moment, 50,000 yen.
I understand.
You have it now! Now get out of Kasumi-chan's sight!
Sensei, you sure do have a good student.
I'll be back next month.
Exactly how much do you owe?
It doesn't concern you, Okura-kun.
I'll return the money I just borrowed right away.
I don't need it.
But-
Hey, how much do you owe?
Hurry up and return to the classroom, Okura-kun.
What is it? I don't get it at all.
Ah, it's here.
Miyamori Kasumi's Investigation Report
Um, the debt amount is...
20 million?!
Because of the debt her father owed, and the interest that's been building up...
If things continue like this, she'll be sold to repay the debt.
This can't be for real! This is impossible!
I have 10 million. If I can double it... But on such short notice...
I just have to give it a shot. If I don't try, then Kasumi-chan will...
Long time no see, Kasumi-chan.
What do you mean, "long time no see"? We just saw each other at school.
Well, what did you want to talk about?
About that... this is for you, Kasumi-chan.
What is it?
That's 20 million yen. I'll lend it to you for now to pay back your debt.
This is...
Don't worry about where I got the money from, it's my own money.
But, this much money...
You don't have to force yourself.
Why do you know about my family's debt?
I found out by chance.
I was always concerned about that debt. I just couldn't let it go.
If the debt isn't paid, you'll be forced to sell yourself.
I don't want something like that to happen.
Something like Sensei selling herself... I don't want it to happen.
Thank you, Okura-kun.
Then...
Just as I thought, I can't accept this.
You can't accept it? Why?!
If things go on like this, you'll be used to repay the debt.
Are you really fine with that?
This is my family's problem, so...
It's alright, so...
You don't need to worry.
But why do you have to do this?
Your good intentions made me very happy, but...
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Both you and Kaho will be sold!
I will protect that child for sure.
But Sensei, you'll...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Okura-kun.
Kasumi-chan is going to be...
I won't be able to endure something like that. How can I endure it?
But what should I do? What should I do?
I see.
That's it!
Isn't it simple?
In order for others not to get to her, I just have to use this money to buy her myself.
It's that simple. It really is simple!
Belong to me... become my possession.
No! Don't look at me like this!
You can't resist me; you've finally become my possession.
N-No way...
Kasumi, you're still a virgin, right?
Isn't that why you're so wet?
See.
Don't!
What is it? It feels good, right?
That's not it! Don't! Okura-kun, please stop!
Okura-kun? You still don't understand what kind of situation you're in?
What am I to you? Say it.
You're my master.
I can't hear you.
Please stop! Please stop, Master!
Listen carefully, Kasumi. You're my slave.
That was written on the contract.
Yes.
Do you still remember the contents of the contract?
Now, let me hear it.
Well, what's wrong?
According to the contract of slavery.
I, Miyamori Kasumi-
Don't! Not there!
Miyamori Kasumi-
Because you helped me pay back my 30 million yen debt...
And then?
I offer every part of my body to Master!
That's right, I'm Kasumi's master.
I'm going to make you understand my status right now.
Kasumi belongs to me.
Forgive me! No! No! No!!
Faster.
Yes, Master. Like this?
That's right.
This is good.
Just like this.
Yes! Yes! Just like this...
How is it? It feels good, right?
Yes, it feels good.
Master!
What about you, Master? How is it?
Do you feel good inside of me?
Good, just like this. I'm going to come inside soon.
I'm going to come, too.
You're going to come? Let's come together.
Ah, I can't stand it anymore.
Master, together!
Please come together with me!
Alright, let's come together.
I'm coming.
I can't- I'm coming! I can't hold on! I can't hold on any longer! I can't- Master!
Master.
The Kasumi-sensei I know has improved a lot within a short amount of time.
That's because..
Because of the debt?
If you had left that debt alone, that man would done much worse things to you, right?
Have you been getting along with Kaho?
Ah, yes.
Didn't you promise me, Master? You promised me that you won't lay your hands on Kaho.
Please!
No matter what Master does to me, I'll gladly accept it.
That's why, please-
Don't worry, Kasumi.
I love you very much, Master.
It's okay, it'll be fine.
Yes.
It'll be fine, since I've already made the preparations.
So you've come.
You know my motive, right?
Yeah.
Good, that'll do.
With that, the contract has been sealed.
Now you can forgive my sister, right?
You siblings really have an amazing bond.
You're willing to sacrifice your own body for your sister's sake.
You're the worst.
Well then, become my slave right here.
I said, read the contents of the contract I brought here.
What's wrong? You can't read it?
Well, that's fine, it doesn't concern me.
It concerns the sister you love so much...
Contract of slavery-
Wait.
What is it?
This is a bit boring.
Well, how should we do this?
Even if you say that...
Ah, that's right.
How about a striptease?
I can't do something like that.
What are you getting confused about?
This is not a request, it's an order.
But-
Don't joke around!
I'm not going to let you do whatever you want.
It doesn't matter if I don't have you as my slave. I still have your sister.
Hurry up.
You've got a nice body.
Don't look at me.
What are you doing?
Don't try to cover it. Read it properly.
Contract of slavery: I, Miyamori Kaho, along with Miyamori Kasumi...
Together, we will swear to become Master Okura's slaves.
And with that, you're now my slave, right?
Yes, Master.
It suits you, Kaho.
Welcome back, Master.
Well, for being like that all this time, you've done well.
Thank you very much.
Well then, it's time for the maid service.
Open your eyes.
This is Master's, you know.
Look at it closely!
Hurry up!
Now, how is it?
It's really big, and it's throbbing...
It's scary.
It's not scary at all. This is something that'll make you feel really good.
Well, you should know what to do next, right?
Right?!
Continue! Can't you understand me?
Yes!
How long are you going to keep doing that?
Suck on it!
This is pretty good...
I'm going to come.
It's coming, it's coming!
You did very well.
Now, what do you think we should do next?
Please take my virginity, Master.
Please... I... beg you.
Fine, you did well.
I'm going in.
Yes.
I-It hurts! It hurts!
Don't yell.
Don't focus on the pain.
Otherwise, it'll hurt even more.
Well, it really hurts...
Your debt has already been paid, right?
I'll protect Kasumi-chan, okay?
So do your best.
It's so hot inside of you, Kaho. It feels so good.
Just a bit more.
Forgive me.
And now you're no longer a virgin. How do you feel?
I don't feel good at all.
It hurts! I don't want this!
Don't worry, your sister likes doing it like this.
You'll get used to it soon.
Look, I'm going to move.
This... This... Save me! Save me! Sister!
It's great, it feels great, Kaho.
I'm going to come again.
I'm going to break!
I'm coming. I'm coming, Kaho!
Kaho!
From here on out, things are going to get interesting...