Ayame?
What's wrong, Ayame?
Can't you sleep?
Don't worry. You can sleep with me.
Are you there, Kaede?
Yes, sir.
Come in.
A ninja must have a heart of stone.
In order to survive,
you can't get too emotional.
You're not supposed to see, hear, or talk.
You must complete your mission even if it costs your life.
That's how ninjas are.
Yes, sir.
Now, girls, show me your butts.
What?
Get down on your hands and knees and thrust out your hips.
Okay.
Kaede, lick Kikyou's pussy.
You aren't supposed to feel anything.
With any kinds of enemy, you have to keep your heart closed.
Use your tongue more, Kaede, and lick her asshole as well.
That's the wrong hole, Kaede.
You're not supposed to lick there.
Do it harder.
Okay.
Try your best to stay calm.
You two have to be patient.
Bear with this, Kaede.
Put your fingers in Kikyou's pussy, Kaede.
Okay.
No, Kaede, I'm going to cum.
Try to feel nothing.
Note: the Heart Sutra.
Kanzijai bosatsu gyo jin hanya haramita ji
Sho ken go un kai ku do issai ku yaku sharashi shiki fu i ku...
If you want to live,
you have to eliminate your self.
Got it?
No, I'm going to cum.
What are you doing, Kaede?
I feel sorry for Ayame.
Huh?
She could have been happy.
She's going to kill someone she had sex with.
She's always been with someone she loves.
I guess we have to lose our feelings in order to live honestly as ninjas.
Kikyou.
Woman
0kizari Fansubs
presents
Kunoichi
Bakumatsu
Kitan
Episode 2
Treasure every encounter,
for it will never recur
Nagai-san. Yamanouchi Youdo-san from the Tosa clan told this man,
Goto Shoujirou-san, to lead the impending restoration of Imperial rule.
I hear you have been a good friend to Kondo-san since the Kinmon Incident.
Yes, he takes good care of me.
And I hear you and Kondo-sensei have known each other since the Choushu Expedition.
No, I was just his bodyguard when he went to Choushu as a government interrogator.
Choushu was thought to be experiencing problems after the conquest.
Kondo-san is good at both studying and sports.
Treasure every encounter,
for it will never recur
He respects old-fashioned manners,
so different from the careless people of today.
Treasure every encounter,
for it will never recur
I trust him and share all kinds of things with him.
Treasure every encounter,
for it will never recur
I know that very well.
I-It's very nice of you to say that.
Oh, yes.
The man you were with when you were guarding me...
You mean Ito Kashitaro?
Yes, him.
I hear he left the Shinsengumi and took an assignment in Koudaiji.
Ito Kashitaro was appointed to guard the tomb of Emperor Koumei.
He heads the contingent of guards.
I knew back then that I couldn't trust him.
He told me that it'd be dangerous for us to enter Choushu territory.
So he did that for me and afterwards said things that would favor Choushu.
Based on his movements after that,
I assume he was meeting the group that is causing the trouble there.
Toshi-san had been suspicious of him for some time.
Hijikata-kun has shrewd instincts.
I heard something strange.
Oh?
One of my group members, Sakamoto Ryouma,
came up with the idea of restoring Imperial rule.
I helped make it happen.
We did it to restore peace and defend this country against threats from foreign powers.
Kondo-san told me that Sakamoto Ryouma is a person of foresight
and is well-versed in foreign affairs.
However, some people on his side who don't like him have threatened his life,
so I hear that he's now in hiding.
These days, we have to be cautious.
We never visit him without an appointment.
Ito Kashitaro managed to find Ryouma and told him to be careful,
because the Shinsengumi are planning to kill him.
What?!
Excuse me.
Hokushin itto-ryu, huh?
Note: a fencing technique from the late Edo period.
I'm not fighting.
If you really wanted to kill me,
I'd be dead already.
You pretended to attack me to test my ability. That was unpleasant.
I was curious about the heavy-looking thing you have in your pocket.
Oh, you mean this?
Oh, it seems you have someone with you, right?
Please tell him that I don't have any intention of killing you.
You remind me of Souji.
Huh?
As long as we have you, I guess we'll be safe, even if enemies invade here.
I'll leave Shoujiro to you guys.
Neither of us will live very long, but at least...
at least...
It's getting cold.
I'll have hot pot tonight.
Do you want me to find out his identity?
He's Sakamoto Ryouma.
You mean the man who left the Tosa clan?
I'm basing my guess on his use of hokushin itto-ryu, his gun, and his appearance.
That's exactly how Kondo-san described him.
Such a careless guy...
I thought we knew all the masterless samurai in Kyoto, though.
Ayame's gone far, far away, where we can't reach her.
Please give us the next order, Master.
There is a masterless samurai whose name is Sakamoto Ryouma.
Sakamoto Ryouma...
It's not an emergency, but when the right time comes...
He can be useful to us,
so we'll let him live for a while.
Die!
Hold up! Wait! You've all misunderstood.
Calm down!
Looks like I'd better run!
It's easy to understand what he's trying to do.
He simply doesn't want anyone to die.
He wants Tokugawa deposed so that the state can become a republic.
However, there are many people who don't want that to happen in this country,
especially the government, of course, and highly-placed officials motivated by greed.
That's why he's been hiding.
Yeah, even from the Tosa clan.
So when are you going to stop following me?
When I get my next order.
That means you might disappear suddenly.
So why don't you show me your face for once?
I can't do that.
Why not?
It's the rule.
The rule, huh?
It seems like no one can do anything without rules.
Are there rules for the Shinsengumi as well?
Yeah, there are five rules I made called Kyokuchu-hatto, including:
"You can't leave the group."
"You can't make money on your own."
"You can't get involved in a lawsuit without consulting the group."
I guess they sufficed, instead of trying to specify lots of details.
The rules say not to oppose
the leader, don't they?
Yeah, human beings are weak.
It's hard for us to think and act properly by ourselves.
I can't think of anyone who can do that.
No, actually, there is one person.
Who is that?
Sakamoto Ryouma, the man you just saw.
His way of living seems similar to mine,
but his objectives and patterns of thought are quite different.
He's trying to act based on his beliefs.
He's loyal to his values.
Loyal, huh.
He's honest and faithful...
...to himself.
You've decided to break the rule?
I'm tired of hiding.
Hijikata-san!
She's gone again.
What happened, Souji?
Hijikata-san, the commander and
vice-commander of the Shinsengumi
shouldn't walk around without guards.
It's not safe.
As leader of the first team,
you shouldn't be here either.
When we're together,
we stand out even more.
You have a point there.
She's too beautiful to be a female ninja.
Stop!
Die!
I guess we're even now.
Kikyou-dono... It's you, isn't it?
How do you know my name?
Don't you remember the time when we shared our names?
The time...
Please don't stop.
Is the drug still active?
I'm scared.
Do it harder.
Please don't leave me.
Don't worry. I won't.
Say my name: Kikyou.
It feels good.
Would you tell me your name?
I'm Sakamoto Ryouma.
Feels... good.
Ryouma-sama...
The rescript to overthrow the government has been given to Satsuma and Choushu.
Their daimyo are outsiders and have never held important positions in the government.
Their nobles have stayed out of politics for the past 700 years.
Even after forming a new government,
they won't be able to manage the state.
Through the power of these daimyo,
Tokugawa will soon be back in power.
That's what our lord said, and he was correct.
Only a dozen daimyo out of 260 followed the government's orders to gather in Kyoto.
Yet they still established a new government.
I guess we have no choice but to kill them.
Yes, sir.
Would you cross the ocean with me, Kikyou?
This ocean leads to other countries, like America, France, and Britain.
I want you to put this on your finger.
What are you doing?
It fits perfectly, doesn't it?
I never forgot the feel of your hand that last time, when you were holding my fingers tight.
Why did you do this?
It's a ritual.
A ritual?
That's right.
It's a Western ritual.
To keep you all to myself, Kikyou-dono.
You're beautiful, Kikyou-dono.
Ryouma-sama...
Now I understand how Ayame felt...
How she felt...
Has the ache subsided?
It's getting worse.
Same here.
It feels good.
Please, Ryouma-sama, hurry up.
It feels good... so good!
This country will change.
Everyone will be able to live freely. Not just men, but women too.
Women can live freely?
Yes, eventually one's background won't matter.
It's true.
I'm going to make this world like that.
So I want you to change, Kikyou-dono.
Ryouma-sama, Ryouma-sama...
Kikyou-dono...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Let me pass, let me pass.
What is this narrow pathway?
Kikyou, you know the face of Sakamoto Ryouma, correct?
Y-Yes.
He's at the Myoho shrine,
near the Tosa clan's safe house.
What is your order?
Kill him.
Wh-Why him?
I'm not talking about just Sakamoto Ryouma,
but about everyone trying to overthrow the government.
Hurry up and go, Kikyou.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Shin-san.
Because it's so cold, Minekichi went out to get some chicken.
Chicken hot pot, huh?
That sounds good.
Is it still snowing?
In fact, it's snowing even harder now.
You know what, Shin-san?
Today is my birthday.
Shinsengumi HQ
What do you mean, the Ito group is acting oddly?
I heard from a spy, Saito-sensei, that they are organizing a hit team.
What should we do, Toshi-san?
Say, Yamazaki-kun, do you remember that the leader of team ten, Harada Sanosuke,
lost his scabbard when he asked someone to sharpen his sword?
Yes.
What about it, Toshi-san?
I assume that was a plot by Ito Kashitaro.
I mean, what if they kill a key leader from Satsuma, Tosa, or Choushu...
and leave Sanosuke's scabbard there?
I see. Then it would seem like the Shinsengumi were responsible.
People would direct all their anger against the Shinsengumi.
And the Ito group intends to mediate between the government, Satsuma, and Choushu.
That way, they could position themselves as being important.
Oh, so that's why they warned Sakamoto Ryouma.
Can you tell us where Ryouma is hiding, Yamazaki-kun?
What are your orders for me?
Follow Kikyou.
Yes, sir.
If Kikyou doesn't kill him,
then you are to kill both of them.
Both of them?
If she can't follow orders, she won't be able to survive in any case.
Hey, be quiet, Minekichi!
Oh good, here's some chicken.
Great. I'm hungry.
Who did this?
I wanted to do this myself, at least.
Good job, Kikyou.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't me!
Kikyou!
Kikyou...
Kaede...
To be able to live, I had to eliminate my self.
Kikyou.
He said I'd be able to live freely.
Kikyou, stay with me!
Thank you, Kaede.
I guess we're too late.
Are you okay?
Hijikata-san, people are coming to see what happened.
Let's go, Yamazaki-kun.
Yes, sir.
Let me pass, let me pass.
What is this narrow pathway?
It's the narrow pathway of the Tenjin Shrine.
Please allow me to pass through.
Going there is fine, but returning is scary.
I am scared, but let me pass.
To be
continued
kaze na kaoru yoru omoidasu wa
The sweet night breeze reminds me
anata no koe wo watashi dake tsutsumu
0f your voice that enveloped me and only me
sono kotoba ni omoi tsunoraseta
Those words made my feelings for you grow
kanau hazu nai to wakatteite mo
I knew it would never come true
mukuwarenai to wakatteite mo
I knew it would never be reciprocated
osaekirenai kono kimochi
But I just couldn't contain my feelings
aishiteru anata wo ashita wa nakutemo
I love you even if there's no tomorrow
namida wa zutto mukashi sutetekita wa
I stopped shedding tears long ago
sore ga watashi no ikiteku michi dakara
That's been my way of life
dakedo kitto watashi umarekawaru
Still, I'm sure I'll start over
anata no soba de egao miseru
And get to be next to you smiling
itsu no hi ka
Someday