So will you talk?
I'm just a dealer in used fans.
I am Masuya Kiemon.
As a result of previous investigations,
in addition to weapons and ammunition,
a secret order from the lord of Choushu was intercepted.
And you know nothing of this?
Very well then.
Toshimaro-sama, Toshimaro-sama!
Ayame, that's good.
Right. That's right.
We can't be complacent.
According to my friends from the Tosa clan,
members of the Miburo clan have been snooping around us.
We have to be careful.
Precisely.
A ninja.
Your life is mine.
Woman
Khmer-Hentai &
0kizari Fansubs
present
Kunoichi
Bakumatsu
Kitan
Episode 1
The lord of Aizu province
doesn't have it easy.
He's become the Guardian of Kyoto City in these dangerous times.
There was talk of sharing tasks with the Satsuma clan.
But it seems he has to shoulder it alone.
He's a model samurai.
Isn't he the same age as you, Hijikata-san?
What are you trying to say?
You both live awkward lives.
What are you talking about?
Souji, difficult times are ahead,
for us in the Shinsengumi as well.
It's the duty of the Guardian of Kyoto...
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
Aizu Domain
Office of the
Kyoto Protector
A bodyguard for me?
Yes. There has been unrest among the outlaws.
We can't be too careful in these situations, sir.
I regret disregarding your thoughtfulness,
but those you just met are active in the field
and face greater dangers.
Yes, sir, but it's been arranged.
Oh?
They're here.
Yes, they're here.
Souji, as summer approaches, there are more flies in the air.
Yes, seven in the bamboo thicket
and four at the fence up ahead.
You deal with the four by the fence.
I'll deal with the four in the thicket.
What? Hijikata-san, the math doesn't add up.
Never mind. They're here!
Insolent dolts, do you realize that we're Shinsengumi working under Aizu?
You are Hijikata Toshizo
and Okita Souji, right?!
On guard!
Your skills have really improved.
Who's there?
That's the end of it.
Did the math add up?
Those are...
As you see, I brought down four.
What are you doing?
These weapons are too good to throw away.
Is your objective our security, or is it to observe us?
I'm grateful.
I-It's a woman?
That's incredible. What skills!
Those were shuriken.
I've heard of them, but this is the first time I've seen one.
Huh?
Why are you talking to yourself?
She's already gone.
What? You mean...
that was a ninja?
They still exist?
How did you know?
I didn't notice anything.
Come on. Tell me!
The smell, I suppose.
The smell?
The Shinsengumi are impressive.
Feigning ignorance.
Yes. I'd hate to be their enemy.
And?
Kaede, Master is asking for you.
Understood.
What about Ayame?
She's finally going to get the information
from a lordless samurai who's been visiting her.
That's what she said.
Kikyou, Ayame is new at this. Stay on top of it.
Yeah, I know. Leave it to me.
I'm happy.
You came to visit me again.
I'll come every day for you.
Toshimaro-sama, will you come again tomorrow?
Tomorrow? There's a big meeting tomorrow.
Meeting?
Where?
N-Near the Sanjou Bridge, at Ikedaya.
Hurry. I can't take it anymore!
This is what I love about you, Ayame!
Me too, Toshimaro-sama!
This is great!
Toshimaro-sama, I'm going to cum.
Toshimaro-sama...
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum, Ayame!
Jeez! Listen to them call each other.
Ayame is really turned on.
So will you talk?
I'm just a dealer in used fans.
I am Masuya Kiemon.
Masuya Kiemon from Hakata Village in Koushu province.
A vassal of Runnouji Temple, Kotaka Shuntaro.
We've already looked into it.
Enough. It looks like he wants to die.
Drive nails into him slowly until he's dead.
N-No. I'll talk. Please don't.
Then talk!
On a hot day, Kyoto will be set on fire.
The bureaucrats, members of the court, and the Prince of Nakagawa will be struck down.
They'll kidnap the Emperor and bring the men of Choushu into power in Kyoto.
What? And where do these conspirators meet?
Shikokuya on Nawate Street...
or Ikedaya near Sanjou Bridge.
Shikokuya... or Ikedaya.
To tie and tie again,
I lose myself in tousled black hair,
endlessly.
I composed it upon seeing your hair.
I'm happy, Toshimaro-sama.
Let's do it again.
Shit! Ayame is forgetting her job. I'm gone.
What?
KAWAUCHlYA
Kawauchiya
Damn. Got away.
Izou, the assassin.
Shit! A ninja.
I can cut and toss you,
but it will dirty my sword.
You hired dog of the Shogunate.
Kawauchiya
Okada Izou, lordless samurai from the Tosa lands.
A source of mayhem.
For the murder of Inoue Saiichiro and Honma Seiichiro, I...
A female ninja?
Your intelligence is bad.
Policeman Watanabe Kinzaburo,
Ookawara Shigezou, Mori Magoroku,
Ueda Sukenojou, and...
Neo-Confucianist Professor Ikeuchi Daigaku. I killed them all.
Shimada Sakon's underling,
Bunkichi the Monkey was a snoop like you,
Kawauchiya
so I killed him with my hands to keep the dirt off my sword.
Damn you!
Good thing you wore chain mail.
You almost became dirt on my sword.
Stop it.
This ointment is...
paralyzing me.
How is it? Mortifying?
But it'll get good soon.
Why do you feel like this?
I'm rubbing in plenty of truth serum!
I gagged your mouth with my underwear.
It won't stay quiet and busted out!
You're feeling it.
Shit. My body is tingling.
It's working better than I expected.
It's because I rubbed a lot in!
Take this.
Sorry, I haven't had time to bathe.
Or is it too big?
Yeah, good. Keep that going.
You keep me going.
Really impressive.
I've been trained to deal with this serum.
Damn you. How dare you! How dare you!
Terrible, terrible, terrible!
In the darkness!
Izou! Are you all right?
Let's see.
Not good.
He's bleeding too much.
Take him to our headquarters.
What do we do with the woman?
Ryouma, I'll leave her to you.
You have to quench her fire to get her back to normal. Take care of it.
"Quench her fire"?
Due to your arousal, you forgot what the samurai said?
There is no excuse for my lack of discipline.
I will accept any punishment.
Ayame.
The Silent School.
The trick of the puppet.
This was going to happen.
Ayame needed to be indoctrinated.
"I'm happy."
"You came to visit me again."
"I'll come every day for you."
"Toshimaro-sama, will you come again tomorrow?"
"Tomorrow? There's a big meeting tomorrow."
"Meeting?"
"Where?"
"Near the Sanjou Bridge at Ikedaya."
You heard that, Kaede?
Yes, sir.
Among them will be Miyabe Teizou from the Higo clan,
Mochizuki Kameyata from the Tosa clan,
Yoshida Toshimaro from the Choushu clan.
Make sure you kill those three.
Without fail. Understood?
Go!
Yes, sir!
I'm cumming. I'm going to cum!
Don't stop.
Not quenched yet?
Oh, well.
A lot of people will listen to my opinion at the meeting tonight.
I should ease up.
I'm scared. Hold me tighter.
Don't leave me alone.
Don't worry. I'm by your side.
It's good. It's really good.
I'm here on business!
Oh, yes. I'm coming.
Hey!
It's empty!
Nobody.
Nobody's here! You!
Check over there!
Yes, sir!
Look back there!
Sir, there wasn't anyone suspicious.
Not in the closets or the storage room.
No traces on the roof or in the garden.
It's Ikedaya.
Toshimaro-sama.
IKEDAYA
K-Kondo-san...
Souji, hang in there until Toshizou-san arrives!
Shit.
This is unmistakably Mochizuki Kameyata, of Tosa.
Miyabe's face.
You are Miyabe Teizou, of Higo?
All that remains is Yoshida Toshimaro.
Yoshida Toshimaro?
Choushu Domain
Open up!
I'm Yoshida Toshimaro!
We were attacked by the Shinsengumi.
We need reinforcements.
Open up!
Shit.
Withdraw. Please let me go.
You were cruelly betrayed,
and despite that wound,
you still want to go back to your group?
It's regrettable.
But it's fate that I met a friend of Ayame.
You knew Ayame's identity?
I had my suspicions.
But it was worth it.
In these confusing violent times,
do moral ends justify the means?
The things we've done.
The things we're trying to do.
Are they right?
Then I met Ayame.
Even though a lie, it was a good dream.
I will assist.
I'm grateful.
To tie and tie again,
I lose myself in tousled black hair...
Ready.
...endlessly.
Ayame...
Let me pass, let me pass.
What is this narrow pathway?
Ayame has gone to a place we cannot reach.
Master, what are your next orders?
The lordless samurai of Tosa,
Sakamoto Ryouma.
Sakamoto Ryouma...
To be
continued
kaze na kaoru yoru omoidasu wa
The sweet night breeze reminds me
anata no koe wo watashi dake tsutsumu
Of your voice that enveloped me and only me
sono kotoba ni omoi tsunoraseta
Those words made my feelings for you grow
kanau hazu nai to wakatteite mo
I knew it would never come true
mukuwarenai to wakatteite mo
I knew it would never be reciprocated
osaekirenai kono kimochi
But I just couldn't contain my feelings
aishiteru anata wo ashita wa nakutemo
I love you even if there's no tomorrow
namida wa zutto mukashi sutetekita wa
I stopped shedding tears long ago
sore ga watashi no ikiteku michi dakara
That's been my way of life
dakedo kitto watashi umarekawaru
Still, I'm sure I'll start over
anata no soba de egao miseru
And get to be next to you smiling
itsu no hi ka
Someday
mabuta tojireba sou itsumo soko ni
When I close my eyes, I always see
anata no kao watashi dake miteta
Your face watching me
sono hitomi wo keshite wasurenai
I'll never forget those eyes