I told you! You were wrong!
That's weird...
In any case, the problem has been solved!
I have to punish you.
It's the opposite from the other day. Today, please become smaller.
Okay!
Please give us back the egg!
You want me to say something?
No, not particularly...
Okay, I'm going to sit down.
Yeah.
Like this?
That tickles!
Master, please let go of me!
Yeah, there's no way Suzuna could be Nazuna in the first place.
T-That's right, but could you please bring your voice down a little?
Oh yeah, that's right!
What?
Is the stalker situation okay now?
Yeah, it seems okay.
T-Thanks...
No, but I'm glad. Now the world is at peace.
Suzuna and Nazuna are different people!
Oh, geez!
Oh yeah, supervisor, how is your child doing?
What? Yeah, she's good.
She keeps on drinking so much breast milk.
B-Breasts...
It's so obvious what you're thinking...
Oh, Takuya, you want to drink it too?
Supervisor, that isn't funny...
N-No, Takuya...
What are you saying? You were the one that invited me.
That was just...
No, my husband's going to yell at me...
Just your breasts...your breasts...
Okay, but just the breasts...
If it's just the breasts...
You're having your baby suck on these breasts, huh?
But the baby isn't the only one that sucks on it, right?
Don't say such a thing...
I can suck on them too, right?
I'm so embarrassed...
No, don't suck on them that hard!
On top of that, it isn't just your breasts that are overflowing...
You're totally wet over here too.
So this is your stork, huh?
No, if I'm turned on, my breasts...
Takuya, no...no, not that...
Even if you say that, you're totally soaked!
T-That's...
It feels so good inside you, supervisor!
It's gotten dirty...
Please clean it with your tongue.
W-What's that crowd of people!
There's a lot of people like Takuya here!
What?
What is this?
Apparently Suzuna is an idol or something like that.
Nazuna discovered working at a convenience store.
When a male employee asked her, she denied it, but...
...she does kind of look like her.
Parentheses, thank you, employee.
I had Suzuna go home for the time being.
It's my fault.
I knew this was going to happen some day, but...
I'm guess I'm going to have to quit this job.
Ah, Suzuna?
Takuya...
What did you say? You want me to come to Akihabara tomorrow?
What are you saying? Didn't you hear what's going on with me right now?
If I went somewhere like that...
I'll...
I'll do something about it...
Suzuna!
What are you trying to accomplish calling me somewhere this crowded?
It's easy. If Nazuna showed up here while you are here... Right?
What are you saying? There's no way she would come!
T-Then Suzuna, you really are...
I'm sorry!
W-What?
This happened because I screamed about it.
I-Idiot, stop.
I was going to be found out sooner or later.
It's not really your fault...
And I'm sorry for one more thing.
W-What is it?
Hey, idiot, what are you doing!
Hey, isn't that Nazuna that had a thread up on 3chan?
Are you serious?
Is that really Nazuna?
H-Hey, Nazuna!
Hold on!
Who are you saying is me?
How can you think this chick and me are the same person?
Is there something wrong with your eyes?
It's the real Nazuna!
I feel her personality is a little off, but it's Nazuna!
There's no...
It's a lie!
This should be the real Nazuna!
What?
He's the stalker!
Speaking of which, I've seen him at the convenience store too.
Ah! That blog was most likely written by him too!
Hmph! You're the one who sent off that information, huh?
Maybe I should post it on my blog too!
''Stalker who causes a mess with faIse information!''
What, stop!
I-It's something you did.
What are you saying now?
Then me too!
Me too!
S-Stop!
Stop it!
Justice always prevaiIs.
U-Um, you are...
Um, Nazuna, can I shake your hand?
Nazuna!
Me too!
Wow, if I stay here, something crazy is going to happen.
Then I'll be off!
Wait up, Nazuna!
Wait!
Huh, Nazuna is gone.
Hey, that's a dead end.
Hopefully now you won't be suspected anymore.
What is going on?
Still, it's amazing you brought someone that similar.
Is she your girlfriend by any chance?
Well, if I talk about this, it's going to be a long story.
Come on, tell me.
I'll think of something as a thank you.
What? Like going on a date with you?
Idiot.
I'm home.
Oh, she's home.
Welcome home.
Nice to meet you, Suzuna!
N-Nice to meet you.
Good job. You did well. It was wonderfully done.
Yeah.
Um...
Ah, she's...
I'm Seri the sexanoid.
Sexa...
I'm glad I was able to help you.
Help?
She's the Nazuna that showed up instead of you.
What!
You have to be lying! No matter what you say, her face is different!
Do I have this carefree face?
That's kind of cold...
T-That's...
Lies! There's no way that's possible!
I thought that too.
But...Seri, please transform for her.
Okay!
I can't...believe it...
But I have no choice but to believe it.
Hey Seri, I would like to return the favor for saving me.
No, don't worry.
I wasn't talking to you.
What, me?
Yeah, ask me to do anything. As long as it's something I can do.
Um...
Well...
What! You want to do it with a girl?
I've wanted to do it once.
That's right. Her purpose is like that.
Hey, why are you agreeing too? You're her master, stop her!
There, there, don't say that.
There, there.
Mom!
It's so soft!
No!
Sister!
Suzuna, please lick mine too.
It feels good...
Ah, no!
Nazuna...
These are Nazuna's lips...
And these are Nazuna's...
Ah, Master, not fair!
Um, it feels good, but there's something missing...
What are you saying?
W-What?
What!
H-Hey, no, you can't...
Oh...please?
N-No!
It won't stop... It feels so good! This feels so good!
Ah, I'm going to come... I'm going to come!
There... My penis is coming from inside...
Suzuna, your butt is totally exposed.
No!
You're both totally soaked.
I-Idiot!
This is Nazuna's...
Suzuna is...
Nazuna is doing it for me...
This became a good last memory.
What, last?
Gosh, you didn't read the instructions?
My cells...
It takes about five minutes to grow and in one week...
One week?
Day one...
Day two...
Day three...
Day four...
Day five...
Day six...
And...
T-That can't...
Suzuna, thank you so much for listening to my last self-indulgence.
It was fun being at your place, Master.
From normal sex and playing as your old next-door neighbor...
...to playing with your supervisor's breast milk and Suzuna stripping...
They were all fun.
Goodbye, Master...
Hey, whatever you say, this is way too sudden!
There's still role-playing I want to do!
Seri...
Goodbye...
Goodbye, Seri...
Hmm, this will be good for this.