W-What is this?
It must be from that time...
Takuya!
Yes?
Come on, that item has to be on this shelf.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Supervisor! He won't get it through his head if you say it like that.
His mind's always floating around.
So you need to at least say, ''Damn it, do it right!''
S-Suzuna...
A girl shouldn't be talking like that!
P-Please stop.
Well, I'll be going to the back, so watch the store for me.
It's amazing how this place doesn't close down with that supervisor in charge.
Gosh, you can't even put things out on the shelf right.
H-Hey, I just misunderstood a little!
Yeah, that's right.
You misunderstand 90% of your life and live on.
''No regrets in a life of misunderstanding!''
You're going to go that far?
Wait, calm down. Calm down.
Today is that special day I've been waiting so long for.
It's star cosplay idol Nazuna Suzushiro's DVD release signing.
Um, you're kind of creeping me out...
Thank you very much!
H-Hooray!
On top of that, with clothes that widely open...
Wow, she has a mole in a place like that...
Hey, hurry up!
Today I learned the meaning of the word happiness.
Thank you, God!
The live Nazuna was so cute.
Please keep on cheering for me!
Of course! Of course! I will cheer you on!
It's about time...
Now to go home and watch this DVD.
I-I'm sorry.
Oh gosh, there, there.
Ouch...
Ah, Suzuna!
Geez, where the heck are you looking and walking!
What do you mean where...
What are you looking at, you pervert!
N-No, it's...
Just apologize!
Why? You apologized first, so you know you were at fault!
Shut up, you crazy theory nerd!
I just apologized because of a conditioned response.
Now that I found out it was you, I want my share back!
W-What a theory...
Shut up! You're a perv!
Here, young man.
I'm so sorry. By the way, are you okay?
Yes, I am okay.
Gosh, you should watch out more.
Y-You!
What, you panty peeper!
Then I will be going...
I-I saw...
Look! I'm going to tell everybody!
Not that!
More importantly...
What?
What! A stalker?
Really?
Seems like I was being followed.
Great timing. Just keep on walking with me.
I'll keep you peeping up my skirt a secret.
I didn't peep!
If she was Nazuna...
That guy...maybe...
It most likely switched at that point!
This sexanoid Seri will change her cell arrangement...
...and service you in any form.
Please be aware it will start growing in about five minutes after opening.
After a week...
In about five minutes?
What?
Nice to meet you, Master!
Do you like it, Master?
F-First off, your breasts... I mean your clothes...
Yes!
Wow!
Does this mean you can transform into anything?
That's exactly right.
Your type of face, body... Anything is okay!
So if you are a sexa-something...means...
Meaning, you can do anything you like as you wish.
A-Anything...
Master, you're so dirty!
You know what I'm thinking too?
No, I just thought I should say it.
Why you!
No!
You don't have to hold back.
I-It's soft...
Master, this one...
Please suck on it...
D-Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels so good, Master!
Here, let me look at it more here...
Yes...
I'd be happy to...
ls this okay?
Y-Yeah...
This is girls'...
I saw this a lot over the Internet, but...
Master, does it taste good?
Is mine tasty?
Master, please put it in...
Please put it into my warm...
O-Okay...
Master, yours is overflowing...
It's pouring all inside me!
Thank you for your hard work!
So how is it?
How is what?
The stalker. Did he go away?
As of right now, there's nothing.
But why does it have to be you of all people, Suzuna?
Did you do something to make them target you?
T-There isn't anything like that...
But it's weird for you to be targeted for no reason.
Yeah...
Wait a second. What does that mean!
Nothing...
You say that, but the most you could do is go to a cosplay idol's signing.
Uh, w-what are you talking about?
To be honest, I saw you that day.
Someone was thinking perverted thoughts standing in line...
Man, I feel like telling someone about it!
S-Suzuna...
Please, keep this a secret from everybody!
Then call me Lady Suzuna from now on!
So, you can become any kind of shape, right?
Yes, of course!
If you wish, I could become an amoeba or martian too!
No, not like those...
Let's see, if we're talking the person I dream of...
No, the impact is too strong!
I can't! I can't defile Nazuna!
First of all, Nazuna wouldn't do such a loose thing...
...and she doesn't go to the bathroom either!
Yes she does. Look.
Hey! Don't defile Nazuna!
I don't like boys that have fantasies about girls.
Stop slacking as Nazuna!
Geez...
By the way, would you be able to become like this?
T-This...
Wow...
I won't let you get away with cheating-cha!
But you're thin as paper...
Oh, I forgot to fix myself.
Then next...
Wow, a gymnastics idol!
Please take me to Kourakuen!
This time I corrected it to be three-dimensional!
Hmm... Even though you tried that...
Maybe this face isn't fit to be three-dimensional.
That's horrible!
Then what about this!
That's kind of creepy though...
I'm fully dimensional!
Your facial expression not changing when you're angry is a problem...
I guess it has to be someone that actually exists.
Ah, speaking of dreaming of...
There was an older girl who lived next door when I was young...
Kotomi is going to become my bride!
Aw, I'm happy.
Hold on one second.
Here, that's a picture of her.
Okay!
It's been a while, Takuya.
Huh? What's the matter, Master?
Is there something wrong?
She was bigger...
You mean the breasts?
No, I was always looking up to sis...
T-That's because you were still young, Master.
No, no, sis was a lot taller!
He's already in child regression mode...
Sis!
Geez, I got it!
I am a proud sexanoid!
If it's the master's wish, then I'll make it come true...
...to the best of my abilities.
Wow!
To lose the awkwardness, get rid of the lights.
So let's...
W-What are you going to do?
Ah, Kotomi...
Come on Takuya, come over here...
Sis, you are so warm...
On top of that, you smell so good.
Really?
But back then you used to run away embarrassed when I did this.
Of course, I was still a kid.
Hey, Takuya...
Yeah?
Do you want to do some perverted things with me?
Um, but...
See, I know you're trying to hide it, but you're already so hard.
You were always thinking you wanted to see my breasts, right?
Come on, feel them. Aren't they soft?
You're allowed to massage them.
You want to touch them directly?
Unbutton my shirt.
Look, you can see my bra now.
Put your hands in there.
It feels so good, Takuya...
Look, this is mine.
Is it different than what you imagined?
This is...Kotomi's...
No! No, Takuya...
Not...not there...
No!
This time I'm going to make you feel good, Takuya.
Let's take your clothes off.
What a cute penis.
No, it's going to come out...
It's fine, please pour it into my mouth.
I wonder what the real Kotomi is doing...
Maybe she's married already and living a happy life...
Kotomi, how long are you going to be single?
Be quiet! Leave me alone, already!
It's unusual for you to be out of it.
ls it that stalker you were talking about the other day...
Yeah...actually...
Just kidding, there's nothing.
Go to hell...
Geez...
Sorry, sorry.
Damn it! That girl...
Oh, did something happen?
I just got a devilish idea.
Hey! What are you going to do to me like this?
First off, I'll get you to pose in positions you can't show anyone!
Are you crazy?
Shut up! I'm telling you to do it!
O-Okay...
That's good!
Hey, you slacked on the transformation!
There's a mole in the same spot as Nazuna!
I can't help it. It's her.
What did you just say?
Like I said, Suzuna and that idol Nazuna are the same person.
W-What!
T-There's no way...
There's no way that's possible!
My analysis says that their DNA is fully identical.
T-There's no mistake here, right?
Well, have I ever fooled you before this?
N-No, but I can't really trust it...
No, even if you aren't lying, maybe it's just a mistake?
The other day too...
Hey, could you tie your hair in pigtails?
Piece of cake!
Are you mocking me?
What?
Remember that happened once?
Then you should ask her yourself.
You should see with your own eyes so you don't regret it later.
Good morning!
Suzuna!
What?
Ah, umm, well...
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to ask...
I'm going to ask!
You were so loud just now, Takuya...
Sorry...
Hey...
So what was it?
It's really a stupid question, but...
Suzuna, are you Nazuna?
W-What kind of stupidity is that?
There's no way!
Y-You're right.
I-It's amazing your imagination can run that far...