It's pay-back time!
Magic Missile!
Who..?
Yuusuke!
It is written clearly upon your face that women will be prove to be your undoing!
Shut up!
Welcome, my brave Yuusuke.
How I have waited for your coming.
I shall never let you go!
I will not allow you to escape, Yuusuke.
You are all mine....
HELP!!!
Bouncing Bosoms Everywhere
I must have over-done it on the Famicom.
I think I'll go back to sleep.
Oh, Yuusuke! You're such a naughty boy!
That wasn't a dream...
It was a nightmare!
Towel?
Not again!
Yuusuke....
Won't you come play with me?
Um, excuse us....
Is this the Yamamoto residence?
AARGH! HELP!!!
Pa
These two girls, who are first year students like yourself...
...expressed their deepest wishes to become nurses...
...and asked whether they could study under me.
I am Nakamura Yuka. How do you do.
And I'm her little sister, Rika Nakamura. Pleased to meet you, Yuusuke.
And while they were student nurses I thought I'd let them stay here, but...
...eh, since I'm too busy to look after them....
You don't fool me, Dad. You're just trying to cure my fear of women.
Forgive me, my son.... But if you're to become a gynaecologist like me...
...you must get used to women.
Being afraid of women, living with twins is gonna be hell.
Especially because of THAT really bad experience....
Some twins used to live next-door when I was little.
I don't remember their names or faces, but...
Wait up!
Gotcha!
When I grow up I want to marry you.
No, I'm gonna marry Yuusuke!
He's gonna marry me!
No way! Marry me!
Hey, Yuusuke - let's play "Doctors and Nurses"!
Yeah. I get to be the doctor?
Uh-uh!
You be the patient!
Yes, please remove your clothing.
What a place to have a boil!
It's not a boil!
But we don't have one of those. Look!
If we don't do something, you'll get them all over your body!
That'd be terrible!
Let's operate while there's still time!
Yes!
Eeh...
Thinking about it, that's probably what caused all my fears.
But there's a problem....
We've only got one spare room, and that's not very big.
True; it's definitely too small for two.
I guess we'll just have to call the whole thing off....
Oh, no....
Now just hold on there.
If there's only room for one, how about if only one stays?
W.. w.. wh...
When you say "only one", which do you mean...?
Whoever you like best should stay, Yuusuke.
But... choosing who I like the best....
What'll I do if Yuusuke doesn't choose me?
Yuusuke, choose me!
Well, we can't choose by drawing straws.
There's no need to hurry; you've got a day to think it over.
Well, I have to get back to the hospital.
Da..Dad!
Wa..wait! Don't go Dad!
You've got until the Christmas Eve party tomorrow night to decide.
Oh, and tonight... I'll be staying at the hospital.
But...
ra
Name:
Yuusuke
How I can choose between you....
I can't even tell which one's who.
One of you'd better explain how I'm to tell you apart!
Well then, I'll wear my hair in a ponytail.
Oh, it won't come out right!
Let me try.
All done.
There you are, Yuusuke. Rika has a pony tail...
...and Yuka has hers straight.
Okay, at least now I can tell you apart, but I still don't know who to choose.
Well, I'm going to clean this house up.
Me, too.
An Amazoness appears.
Yuusuke's Command:
Attack.
V
You cannot win
against the
Amazoness.
Yuusuke dies.
Here we go!
Hey, look! I'm cute from behind too!
Oh, Rika! Don't you have any shame?
A girl can't help showing off her assets when she's doing the housework!
I can feel Yuusuke's eyes following me. I've got him hook, line and sinker!
I've got to start cleaning.
I can see hers, too.
I'm beginning to feel strange.
Eh? Yuusuke...!
Hey, Yuka... that's cheating!
You sure got friendly with him fast, sis!
I'm so jealous!
Oh, Yuusuke, you musn't do that!
It's not that, sis! He can't breathe!
What? Oh, I'm sorry!
I almost asphyxiated!
If that happened, I'd be giving you the kiss of life!
But what good would that do him if he was dead?
Oh, that's right, isn't it?
These girls are just like those twins grown up!
Ooops.
da
We've nothing left to do.
I know.... I'll go cook something for Yuusuke!
I can help, too.
Wow, you're such a good cook.
Well, there's no-one here 'cept me and Dad,
so I have to do almost everything myself....
Let's eat!
Deeelicious!
Isn't it?
Yuusuke, can I have some more?
If I married Yuusuke I'd be so happy....
He can do everything!
I wonder how Yuusuke and the girls are getting on?
If he can withstand such a potent dose of female sexuality...
...then he shouldn't have problems with any other women.
"A hair of the dog that bit you," after all....
What? It's okay for you to stay over?
Well, we planned to start living here from tonight.
But there's only one guest room, and it's too small for both of you.
Don't worry yourself about that.
I hope it'll be fine tonight, though.
Let's see them get through that!
I don't wanna be woken up like in last night's dream.
It's cold. Oh, the window's open.
Wow, am I tired.
Now, where are my pyjamas?
Hmm, let see....
My pyjamas...!
I warmed them up for you! If you wear cold pyjamas, you'll catch cold.
Ah, they're warm! Skin temperature....
Goody, he looks pleased.
Yuusuke, don't look -- I'm taking the rest off.
Okay....
Pants!
I need my pants first!
Boo!
Rika...! N..n..not you, too....
I warmed your pants up for you, Yuusuke!
Here are your pants, Yuusuke.
But those are knickers....
Your pants are inside.
Why don't you go ahead and take them?
Yuusuke!?
i
A dream.... I must of had another bad dream....
Morning, Yuusuke.
This isn't any dream.
I'm stuck with two twins I have nothing in common with.
Those twins in my childhood, and with these twins now!
Who do you mean by "those twins"?
Do you know any other twins apart from us?
They used to live next door.
No... that's impossible....
Do you remember playing "Doctors and Nurses" with us?
I was right.
Yuusuke, do you remember that promise you made?
What promise?
What, you mean to say you forgot that you promised to marry one of us?
But I made that promise when I was a kid!
But the thought of marrying you is the only thing that's kept us going!
Yeah, that's right! We've pulled out all the stops...
...so we could be sexy enough to turn you on!
But there are plenty of nicer guys than me!
Uh-uh. Ever since that time, only you've been the guy for us, Yuusuke!
What do you mean, "that time"?
You saved us from that stray dog....
Wha..? A stray dog?
After that happened, we didn't want to marry anyone else.
Help! We're scared!
Hey!!!
L-leave those girls alone!
Now scat!
It's okay now.
That was the first time we met you, Yuusuke.
You were so brave confronting that mad dog...
...and not once thinking of your own safety.
You stole our hearts.
I don't remember....
After that, we want to become accomplished nurses, marry you, and live happily ever after.
To marry someone who saved us, is like something out of a romantic manga.
Besides, marrying someone who'll become a rich doctor is a good marriage.
Someone must've put a curse on me....
Ah.. I thought that you'd be unable to decide and would come to see me.
Since this is the last working day before the New Year, and the hospital is short of staff...
...I thought the two young ladies could assist us by cleaning the bathroom...
...so Yuusuke can decide who's the more suitable person.
Okay!
We'll give our all to snare Yuusuke's heart!
Well, that's that.
Try to make a decision this time, Yuusuke.
Oh, no....
So after that long speech, all he really wanted was to make them clean the bathroom.
And since neither of them can clean anything properly...
Yuusuke....
Hi!
Can you spare a moment?
I'd like you to do something for me....
What?
My bottom is itchy with all this soap.
Scratch it for me, Yuusuke!
Scratch it yourself....
I said scratch it!
Okay! Okay!
Stop playing around.
I'm all wet.
Oh, Rika...! You're no use here, go wash the towels.
You're just trying to get Yuusuke on his own so you can seduce him!
I'm not that kind of girl!
Oh, *really*?
Yuusuke... even if you do make a mistake with Yuka, I'll still forgive you!
W..wh..what do you mean "mistake"?
I guess I was too much for him....
Oh, no! Yuusuke, are you okay?
Rika... go wash those towels!
Okay! I'm on my way!
Thanks to you I was got soaked too.
I better dry these wet things.
Oh, I can't reach!
What happened?
I can't move....
Yuka, can you..?
I'll try....
Oh, no! Water!
We've gotta pull the plug!
It's no good! I can't move!
At this rate we're both going to drown!
It's all my fault. Forgive me.
Yu- Yuka....
Alright!
Yuusuke...!
Oops-a-daisy! I wonder how can I turn on Yuusuke this time?
I've gotta somehow get up and turn off that water!
There's no other way apart from between those!
Here goes!
Oh, no!
At this rate Yusuke will drown!
What'll I do if he dies?
HELP!!!
That's it! Yuusuke, go down further!
Why?
If you do what I say... we'll be able to get out of this!
Quick! Hurry!
Now, push your face between my legs.
I know it's embarrassing, but it's the only way!
If I do that I drown for sure.
But...
Ah, what the heck!
Yuusuke....
Yuusuke...!
I did it!
Yu- Yuka!
Yuusuke.... I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused you.
I so wanted to marry you, Yuusuke....
Yuka!
Okay! I'm gonna give it everything I got!
Yuka...!
Are you awake, Yuusuke?
You're okay....
Yes.
But how?
Rika saved us.
Rika? Where is she?
She went off somewhere.
I wonder where....
Keeping sexy is much more important than cleaning!
This time I'll get Yuusuke for sure!
su
Merry Christmas!
So who did you choose?
I can't really decide between the two, but...
...Yuka going as far as to try to sacrifice herself in order to save me...
...and Rika... though she's brazen, did save Yuka and me from drowning....
Well? Haven't you decided yet?
Actually Dad...
I was wondering... whether they both couldn't stay!
What?!
BOTH of them?!
I thought you'd say that! They can have my room.
But what about you, Dad?
I'll move into the spare room.
This means we can both be together with you, Yuusuke!
Count it as my Christmas present to you.
Tha..thanks a lot....
Yay!
Thank you, Yuusuke!
Yuusuke?
1+2 = Paradise...
The fun's only just begun!