Keita, I'm going
to please you this way now.
If you want to come,
just go ahead, okay?
Spray my face whenever you want.
How is it, Keita?
No fair, Chiyo. I want to do it too.
Gosh, Haruka, it's just a little longer.
No, you shouldn't hog Keita's sperm.
That's right. Let me get some too.
That's true. Keita is all of ours.
How did it turn out like this?
It started because of
what Dad said that day.
Like a Mom
Episode 1
Dad, what is this? It's out of the blue.
Keita, I've been thinking
about something for a while.
W-What is it?
It's...
...the fact that
you still need a mother!.
It's sudden, but I've brought
a couple of candidates.
Come in, ladies.
She's the daughter at
a bento shop I often go to.
I'm not their daughter.
Just a part-time worker, Jinta.
Hello, I'm Kazuho Tateshina.
I don't know if I can become
your mother, but please look after me.
And this young lady is
a secretary at my company.
I'm Chiyo Sawagiri.
She is an excellent young lady.
Not at all. I don't know if I'll be of
any help, but please look after me.
O-Okay...
What was that? Greet her properly!.
I'm Keita. Nice to meet you.
Hey, what do you mean by "mother
candidates"? And why are there two?
Idiot, it's not two.
There's another one coming later.
A young detective,
Noriko Kasukabe.
I'm asking why there are that many!.
Plus, aren't they candidates to be your
wife, not my mother? You choose one!
You're so hardheaded.
It's the person who'll become
your mother, so you have to choose.
So these three will be
living with us starting today.
Listen. You'll be choosing one
by the end of summer vacation.
As I said, she'll be your wife...
Oh, it's time for me
to return to work, Keita.
It's up to you. Good luck.
Hey, listen to all I have to say!
Also, I won't be back for a while.
I'm going on a business trip!
So apparently...
Saying that...
Please look after us.
R-Right.
Heave-ho.
That's the last of your stuff.
Thank you. I feel bad that you
had to carry most of it for me.
I'm okay now, so could
you check up on Miss Sawagiri?
Okay.
Oh no!
That's was a pretty loud sound...
Miss Sawagiri, are
you okay? I'm coming in.
Miss Sawagiri,
you're not hurt, are you?
Ouch...
Sorry, that was embarrassing.
I-I'm fine. I just fell.
Okay, it's because
I heard a loud thump...
More than that though,
that's a lot of stuffed animals.
U-Um, this is... Well...
I can't resist these things.
It's just different
from my image of you.
I can't go to bed at night without
them, so that's why I brought them.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
But I'm glad you're not hurt.
Is she okay?
Seems so.
Then I'm going to start
getting dinner ready.
Please don't force yourself to, Kazuho.
Well, Miss Sawagiri...
Um, Keita...
Would you call me
by my first name too?
It just seems a little too formal.
Well, It just feels kind of rude if I do...
Is that so.
Keita, could you go pick up
something from the store?
Sure, no problem.
What is going on?
What the hell is Dad up to?
I can't wrap my head around
the idea of a mom at this point.
On top of that, they're so young.
Man, I can't think of them as a mom.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing
here dressed like that?
Coming back from practice.
Why are you riding
a bike dressed like that?
The school shower is broken,
and I'm covered in sweat.
I want to hurry home and shower.
Why are you standing
in this heat with a blank look?
Running an errand.
An errand for your dad?
Nope, for a mom.
I was just wondering if
I still look that much like a kid.
What's that?
Maybe you're
going crazy from this heat.
Maybe.
The break just started.
Don't go losing it now.
I'm off. Gonna take a shower ASAP.
Yeah, see ya.
Telling me to decide by the end of
the break... It's not going to happen.
Speaking of which,
who's the last person?
Keita...
I was just wondering if
I still look that much like a kid.
Keita... Keita...
That's right. We're not kids anymore.
I-I'm coming!
All done!
Was it good?
Yes, it was.
How long was it
since I had homemade food?
If Kazuho becomes the mom,
I can eat that kind of food.
Plus, getting to see her in that apron
every day isn't a bad thing either.
Yup, it's not a bad thing.
Alley-oop...
What is it?
What?
"What," my foot. Why are
you coming into my house?
Oh, good evening,
I'm Noriko Kasukabe.
You can call me "Mom."
You're the other candidate, huh?
And why are you
coming in from the window?
Well, I'm a detective.
It's burglars who
come in from windows, right?
Come on, it's your mom.
You can fawn on me all you want.
"Mom"? Man, you reek of booze!
What are you, totally drunk?
Hey, come on, let's try to get along.
You're young. So sensitive!
Come out here!
Noriko, what are you doing?
Hey!
Oh my.
Thanks for the food!
Wow, what a family
resemblance. Just like your dad's.
That doesn't matter! Just hold on!
No way. Let's get along more.
Alley-oop.
Here you go. Keita, you lick mine.
Come on, Keita.
Hurry up.
Oh, come on, do it with your mouth.
You came a lot.
Want to see my boobs?
You're saying this now?
Don't sweat it.
Ta-da!
Look, boobs. Is it your
first time seeing some?
I can't breast-feed though.
Here you go!
Isn't it nice and soft?
Come on, come on, come on.
What? Noriko?
Hey, Noriko! Noriko?
Noriko!
Keita, it's time for breakfast.
Keita!
Don't keep sleeping
just because it's summer...
Keita, who is that?
Hey, Keita!
Oh, good morning,
Miss Sawagiri. What is it?
As I said, who's that?
Who?
Is it morning already?
Where is this place?
It's you, Noriko.
It can't be... Why?
Keita, what is the meaning of this?
No, this is a misunderstanding!
I didn't... I didn't do it with her!
Ow... Man, I did it again.
I was following someone last night,
and I drank too much at the bar.
I was out of it on my way here.
Sorry, Keita.
We almost went all the way.
It's a bit late,
but please look after me.
With becoming your mom and all,
but it seems we're closer already.
Anyway, best regards.
Chiyo, best regards too.
Noriko, what are you saying?
Doing such a thing with Jinta's son...
What's going on? Oh my! What?
She's the third candidate,
Noriko Kasukabe.
Why is she naked?
And Keita too...
When did I...
It was kind of like "skinship."
U-Um, er...
W-With that said, let's all get along.
A Few Days Later
Then I'll be going. I'll be home late, so
please don't wait up and just go to bed.
Have a good day!
Have a good day.
Well, I'm going to do laundry, so
please give me whatever you have.
No, it's okay. I can do it myself.
I've been doing it myself up till now.
Really? It's been a few
days since I came here...
...but I've never seen you do laundry.
You have a huge pile, don't you?
Can't avoid it, huh?
Please don't talk like a mom would.
What are you saying?
I may really become your mom.
Please bring it out.
Hey, Keita!
I said to bring it out!
What are you opening the door for?
Jeez, I was about to bring it down.
Sorry.
What happened?
Noriko, what are you wearing?
Sorry, I hate wearing clothes...
...so I'm always like this at my
own place. Anyway, what's up?
You're spacing out in front of
Keita's room. Getting bad ideas?
No, I came to take his laundry, but Keita
was in the middle of changing, so...
What? You saw him naked?
W-Well, yes...
I see.
You know Keita's looks like that, but
it's just like Jinta's when it gets big.
When I was drunk before and almost
did him, I mixed them up. It was bad.
As I thought,
he had this much piled up.
Are all guys like this?
Kazuho, I'm going to work now.
I don't know when I'll be
back, so I won't need dinner.
Thanks.
Have a good day!
Heave-ho.
There's still so much.
Whoops.
I never thought I'd be washing
a guy's underwear at my age.
Keita's looks like that, but
it's just like Jinta's when it gets big.
When I was drunk before and almost
did him, I mixed them up. It was bad.
H... W-What?
Kazuho... Kazuho... Kazuho...
Keita, what's the matter?
L-Let go...
What are you saying? What do you
expect me to do after seeing that?
"Expect"? Let go of me, and...
Living with a cute girl like you,
it'd be weird not to feel like doing it!
But I'm supposed to be your...
I don't need a mom!
That's just my dad saying that!
I... I want to be with
you every day, Kazuho!
This has nothing to do with my dad.
Keita...
Keita.
Kazuho, I...
If I do this, I fail as a mother already.
Gosh, Keita. This...
You really are just like your father.
I'll make you feel even better.
Keita, I can't hold it in anymore.
Can we do it?
Kazuho, I can't hold
back anymore either.
Keita...
I'm putting it in.
K-Keita, your thing
is completely inside me.
I can feel it pulsing inside me.
Oh, Keita, this feels so good...
It feels so good...
So, Keita, how does it feel?
Y-Yes, it feels so good.
I-I feel like I'm going to come already.
No, not yet!
Just a little more...
Just a little more and I'll also...
No, I can't hold on anymore!
So you came, did you?
But it's amazing
that you're not done yet.
You're still hard inside me.
How amazing.
Don't take it out.
Let's continue on like this, okay?
Gosh, Keita...
My boobs are my weak spot.
Don't bite so hard...
What is this?
You're harder than before.
I feel bad that it felt better for me.
So how is this, Kazuho?
I-It's so good. Your come
is getting mixed up inside me...
My insides...
My insides feel amazing!
It's hitting all the way in the back,
and it's not supposed to go so far in...
KaZuho, it feels
totally different from before.
I feel like I'm going to get
sucked farther and farther in.
Keita, come here. I want
you to come deeper inside me.
I'll pull all of you in.
Hurry.
Kazuho...
Keita...
It's amazing.
You're filling me up completely, Keita.
It's all the way inside me...
I don't know where I start.
I'll... I'll turn completely into you!
I'm going to become you, Keita!
I'm... I'm going to come...
You're going to make me come...
It feels so good!
No, no, no, no...
I'm coming!
Forget about all the love games.
It's just me looking away from you.
I walk away without saying a word.
Although my footsteps
create a rhythm for a second.
The image of me
jumping deep in your eyes.
A halation reminiscent
of our promised place.
Someday the distance
between us will narrow.
I believe it, in that promised place.
In that scenery
that doesn't change...
...I looked up, and I can
hear your voice. I love you.