Production
Hakozaki
Yasushi
(Japan
Home Video)
Nomura
Kazufumi
(A.P.P.P)
Sebata
Fumio
(Adness)
Hirata
Mikihiko
(Panorama
Communications)
Takahashi
Mitsunori
(Churoku
Service)
Executive Director
Kikuchi Yasuhito
Character Design
Takahashi Shinya
Screenplay
Yamada Mitsuhiro
Art Director
Kuwabara Satoru
Okazaki Hideo
Sound Director
Honda Yasunori
Director
Abe Masashi
Chapter Two
An Animal Trail
Oh, more to the right!
No, to the left.
What is that?
Like I said, it's called a "camera."
Camera?
Whatever I see shows up in here!
Why, I bought this when I went to a foreigner's mansion just the other day.
Ever since the ship docked, lots of things have come into the city of Edo.
Well, I'll take a picture. Stand still, okay?
Oh, you shouldn't move!
It's Magoroku.
Is he dead?
No. Not yet.
Yet, someone's getting in our way to this extent.
Who could it be?
That person's eye seemed wretched...
like someone full of bitterness.
"Bitterness," you say?
That's unfortunate, isn't it?
That's our duty as assassins.
Karyuu.
Yes?
If that creature appears again...
I won't mind.
Get rid of her.
Yes.
Aoi-sama, it's Magoroku-sama.
Let him in.
Well then, I'll take my leave.
The men of Daikokuya Rihei,
the ones dealing in dry goods.
I won't question the means you employ, as long as they're brought down.
But, Magoroku...
speaking of the Rihei, weren't they your intimate friends long ago?
That's why they mustn't be allowed to live.
You see, betrayal cannot be forgiven.
Betrayal?
Those bastards, stealing my business...
Oops! Please, don't ask any more.
First things first: here.
Will you accept it?
My, my, if it isn't Karyuu.
You displayed excellent skills back then.
It's nice, isn't it?
The friendship you and I share, Karyuu.
Magoroku.
You mustn't touch Karyuu.
No one who's slept with Karyuu has come out alive.
Thank you.
So, I'm depending on you, Daikokuya-san.
Bring them down as soon as you can, if possible.
Sure.
Rest assured, and leave it all to me.
There won't be any mistakes.
Really, people like you would do anything for money.
What a fearsome man.
Such jokes...
Thank you very much.
Well then...
Yes.
K-Kourin?!
There's an intruder down there.
What?!
Wh-What did you say?!
Well?
You let him get away?!
He's light on his feet.
Don't act so calm!
Go after him already, and be sure to kill him!
Damn it.
Who could it be?
Bastard! Don't let him get away!
Go around!
I see.
Magoroku is Rihei's business competitor.
Well then, Miss. We've arrived.
Is it possible?!
Just as I thought, she's alive?
Why is she with Rihei?
What exactly is that girl planning?
It's just like Daikokuya, to be so thoughtful.
Fewer merchants nowadays display such courtesy, and it troubles me.
Well, this looks delicious.
Still a virgin?
Don't...
Delicious...
You have fine skin.
Good! This is good!
I've been spotted?!
Kill him! Kill him!
Kourin!
Give it up already!
Th-This is...
Y-You!
Even though you've realized it now, it's too late.
The poison should take effect quite soon.
Stop resisting.
Just as I thought, you're a woman.
So unfortunate...
You're so young.
I can't bear this.
I'll make you feel good before you die.
This is good!
So good!
It's enchanting.
Just wait. I'll give you pleasure.
This is the best!
Well then, time to have you.
So tight!
That... dream again.
You're awake?
Who are you?
I'm Gisuke.
Drinking this will give you a little relief.
I've drawn out the poison, but not the pain.
And that man?
Dead.
He was a foolish man.
If he'd finished you off right then,
everything would've been over.
You can take off the bandages now.
Umm, what's this place?
It's my home. You don't need to worry.
Gisuke-dono, was it? You've taken care of me.
You have my thanks.
It's better for you not to move yet.
No. In time, my pursuers will come to your home.
If I remain here, I'll only cause you trouble.
You don't need to worry.
This is a temporary home.
I intend to leave immediately.
I'll probably meet you again.
Treasure your life.
Beautiful...
Almost like a nymph.
Such skin... I've never seen its like before!
Where did you come from, exactly?
From heaven... or from hell?
It doesn't matter which.
I need you to work more and more...
for my sake.
Well, then.
How about it? Would you like a sip?
Western wine is hard to get a hold of, you know?
Please don't mind me.
Something like that shouldn't be wasted on me.
You don't mean that.
So, how are Rihei's defenses?
For the time being, I believe it's all right.
Are you sure?
Y-Yes!
There's no mistake!
Good.
Y-Yes!
Soon, Tokugawa's night will end.
But...
Magoroku, beware the shogunate's dog.
Y-Yes!
It's done.
Sorry.
Does it hurt?
No, it's all right.
Kinoto.
Aren't you lonely?
Uzume, where did you go?
I told you that I won't allow you to move about on your own.
Gisuke?
Please wash me, Gisuke.
(Note: This chant is an exorcism against spirits consumed by demons.)
Rin, pyou, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai... zen.
I'll place my stone here. How about that?
You're placing too many stones with no strategy!
Why'd you say that?
If there are enough stones...
Roll!
I lost.
Who are you?!
Rihei's not here.
Well done.
It seems your wounds have totally healed.
Just as I thought.
You're an assassin, too!
I don't want to fight you.
If you're going to get in my way...
I'll have to kill you!
I told you before,
"Treasure your life."
Karyuu, listen carefully.
Don't get involved in this business.
You mustn't kill Rihei yet...
even though Magoroku paid you to do just that.
I know everything.
You must not trust Magoroku!
The world will change,
and you won't even realize it.
When that happens, an assassin like you will be needed again.
The blood of a true assassin flows in you,
and so, I thought...
I...
I will only follow my orders!
Karyuu!
Kinoto! Stay there!
That's all, Karyuu!
Your real enemy is somewhere else!
Don't forget that!
Wh-What?!
What exactly does he mean?
Rihei...