Hey, check him out.
Luck's not on your side tonight, kid.
Want another try?
When my husband left me,
he took all my luck with him.
This is my last coin.
I'm too scared to use it myself.
I don't want to be the one
who brings it all to an end.
Thank you.
Kiroemon-sama...
Good luck, ma'am.
There is a family whose leader is said
to inherit the Ear of the Golden Dragon,
the Natsume clan.
This power lets him bring about any fate he desires.
It allows him to make any woman submit to his will.
He is Natsume Kiroemon the 45th!
Translation
Moho Kareshi
Translation Check, Songs
Iri
Timing
ninjacloud
yami ni oritatsu ougon no me yo
His golden eyes descend into the darkness
yobisamasu kokoro saranaru toki
His heart awakens, time quickens
miyo tanabiki kaze ni mau kami
See his hair sway and dance in the wind
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
ten wo kakenuke kiseki wo yobe
Soar through the heavens, calling forth miracles
mabayuku kagayake
Shine brilliantly
QC
Calyrica, konnakude
shukumei no mono wa
The fated ones
shijou no chikara ni seinaru shukuhai
Drink from the supreme power in a holy toast
Encoding
Piyo Piyo Productions
omae ga yuku no ka
Will you go?
Oh, like a dragon!
yatsu he mukau no ka
Will you go to him?
King of kings
shifuku wo eru no ka
Will you find happiness?
Oh, like a dragon!
mirai hiraku no ka
Will the future open to you?
King of kings
Take away my gold ring
Set me free
I'm gonna win the game
Orphan Fansubs presents
Ear of the
Golden Dragon
Mina's Story
(Part 1)
Father... Mother...
Natsume Kiroemon was
the 44th head of the clan.
He adored this church.
He loved the children here like his own.
He preferred tranquility to power
“He preferred tranquility to power.”
Father...
What should I do with the power you bestowed upon me?
What should I do?
That was wonderful!
It's better than the music I heard in the Sistine Chapel.
Thank you.
I'm glad someone as nice as you heard my final performance.
I appreciate it.
Your final performance?
But you played so terrifically.
Indeed, but I won't be playing anymore.
Kanako!
What are you doing up there?!
Ichiro-sama.
You came sooner than I expected.
Foolish wench.
Did you really think you could escape me?
Damn you.
How dare you humiliate me in front of the Prime Minister and all those politicians?
I won't go with you!
You still won't give in?!
Don't you dare touch her!
What do you want?
You're in a church.
I won't allow any further violence.
She doesn't even love you.
Did you put her up to this?
I knew she was too weak to do this alone.
You were trying to steal her from me.
You're wrong!
He has nothing to do with this!
Out of my way!
Fuck you!
Eat this!
How dare you defy me!
Don't you know who I am?!
How dare you!
Are you trying to be her knight in shining armor?
Apologize to me this instant!
Please stop, Ichiro-sama!
I'll go with you!
Please let him go!
Don't!
What?!
He just wants to take advantage of you.
I know his type!
You mustn't go with him, Kanako-san!
Silence!
Wh-Who's there?!
I've got another earring.
Would it look fashionable embedded in your forehead?
How dare you mock me, bitch!
You're a pathetic excuse for a son!
Did you really think you could get away with this?
H-How dare you?
You rotten old geezer.
What do you...
Ichiro!
Get in.
B-But...
Now!
Okochi-sensei.
I apologize on his behalf.
Your son raised his hand against someone he shouldn't have.
If you value your life, get lost!
Who was he?
He's a candidate to be the next Prime Minister,
Soma Jinzaburo.
He can't even raise his son properly.
I've been waiting for you, Kiroemon-sama!
Um... Who are...
My, how you've grown, Kiroemon-sama!
Yes, indeed, it's the son of the Natsume clan, Natsume Kiroemon-sama!
Miss Gordon!
Kiro-sama, he knows a lot about your clan.
Thank you for saving me.
No big deal.
I-I should have known.
That woman...
What's the matter, sir?
That woman, Shijo Kanako.
She's from the Mina clan.
The Mina clan?
Here we go!
Hop on!
I... I can hardly believe
he's Natsume Kiroemon.
Understand?
Natsume Kiroemon is our clan's most hated enemy.
His evil power rests in his left ear.
We were born to give pleasure to men,
but to bring death to that man.
You must never forget that.
He preferred tranquility to power
From the moment we first met, you have never left my mind.
Kiro-sama, is this because of your evil power?
Kanako-san.
Were you crying?
You don't have to worry
about him anymore.
Okochi-san said the same thing.
I'm aware of that.
You looked sad, so we made these for you.
I hope you'll feel better tomorrow.
The kids and I made them.
They're adorable.
I-I feel strange, Kanako-san.
Ever since we first met, I've...
I've wanted to embrace you.
I want to embrace you and never let go.
Kiro-sama.
I have something to ask you.
What kind of power sleeps in your left ear?
Kanako-san.
How do you know about that?
Please tell me!
Will it doom me to a life of misery?
O-Of course not.
Why would it do that?
Kanako-san.
Damn you! How dare you humiliate me!
My old man's clearly lost his edge!
That decrepit old geezer doesn't scare me!
You're dead meat.
Kiroemon-sama.
Die!
Kiroemon-sama!
Serves you right!
Get up!
I'll hit your heart next time!
Put your gun down.
The next shot will strike you.
You pathetic worm!
What a fool.
I know that you're from the Mina clan.
Why did you approach the 45th heir?
Okochi-san!
I am indeed a member of the Mina clan.
Nonetheless, I only met
him by coincidence.
I approached the Soma clan on orders from the Mina clan.
However... I couldn't be with him... with Ichiro-sama.
You're from the Mina clan!
You can't fool me that easily.
Please, stop!
What does the Mina clan have to do with this?
The Mina clan is very ancient.
Like the Natsume clan, their lineage extends back more than a thousand years.
The women of the Mina clan are all exceptionally beautiful.
They can make men dance in the palm of their hand.
It's no exaggeration to say that those vixens control Japan's government.
Any man who sleeps with her will serve the Mina clan until the day he dies.
They are as alluring as succubi. Men cannot resist them.
That's what it means to be a woman of the Mina clan.
I don't care about that!
I don't care what her clan is like.
She's cut all ties with them.
They're trying to kidnap her.
I can't just abandon her.
I... I love her!
Kiro-sama.
Okochi-sama has her
best interests at heart.
Even if the Mina clan is after her...
we have taken steps to ensure her safety.
The Mina clan has enough power to destroy the Natsume clan.
Kiro-sama, no matter what happens,
we cannot allow the Natsume bloodline to die out.
B-But...
He's right, Kiroemon-sama.
I will leave in that car.
Kanako-san!
Thank you.
I... I...
I'm so glad I met you.
Goodbye.
Kanako-san!
I beg of you.
As the 45th head of the
Natsume clan, let her go!
Kanako-san!
I can't let you go, Kanako-san!
H-How is that possible?
How could the seal come undone on its own?
Kanako-san!
Kiro-sama!
You can't go!
I won't let you!
Kanako-san.
Perhaps... Perhaps he has already surpassed
the power of the 44th head of his clan.
Kiro-sama.
You're safe now.
I'll never let you go.
We... We can be together forever.
Kiro-sama.
Please make love to me.
I will return to the Mina clan.
Kiro-sama.
My love and respect for you will never fade.
Kanako-san!
yoru ga owaru mae ni
At least hold me tightly
semete tsuyoku dakishimete
Before the night ends
ima wa nukumori wo zutto kanjiteitai no
Right now, I want to feel your warmth forever
hoho ni kisu shite
Plant a kiss on my cheek
soshite wakare wa
And let our parting come
sou madoromi no naka de
While I'm still dozing
Flying every night yume no naka de
Flying every night in my dreams
watashi wa tori no you ni
I am like a bird
anata no moto e yuku wa
I will go to your side
tsubasa hirogete aa
Spreading my wings
Flying every night tonde yuku wa
Flying every night I will fly
kono sora wo doko made mo
All over this sky
ikutsuka no toki ga sugi
And much time will pass
futatabi anata to meguriaeru
Until I can meet you once more
sono toki made
Until that time
I dream of you