Production
Hakozaki Yasushi
(Japan Home Video)
Nomura Kazushi
(A.P.P.P)
Sebata Fumio
(Adness)
Takahashi Mitsunori
(Churoku Service)
Executive Director
Kikuchi Yasuhito
Character Design
Takahashi Shinya
Screenplay
Yamada Mitsuhiro
Art Director
Kuwabara Satoru
Okazaki Hideo
Sound Director
Honda Yasunori
Director
Abe Masashi
Chapter Four
Vicissitudes
Uzume.
The smell of blood is dyed into your skin.
You certainly are a demon.
I will use your power as much as I can.
You must kill all those who disturb me.
Uzume...
what are you doing here?
Go back to the mansion.
Uzume, can't you hear what I'm saying?
I'll do as I please.
You see... I won't take orders from you anymore, Gisuke.
Uzume...
Please take care of Uzume.
Umm, why did you summon me?
I can't talk to you if you're out there.
Get in here.
Y-Yes.
I have something to ask you.
To ask me, sir?
Chen was killed.
S-So, what is it?
I didn't order it.
T-Take a look at this.
I ordered Aoi to do just what is written here, as usual.
Where did you get this?
The usual hiding place, sir.
I didn't write it.
Don't you understand?
With Chen's death,
the colossal wealth from the opium trade will disappear.
How are you going to make up for this?
Stop!
Karyuu-san.
Magoroku?
Oh, stay right there.
I want you to listen to something.
A trap?
Yes.
That order was a fake.
And because of that, I'm in real trouble.
The truth is, the jobs that I asked Aoi to do were mostly-
No, it could be that all of them were orders from that man.
That man?
The man who was with the foreigner you killed.
Who is he?
A terrifying man called "Black Jyuuzou."
He believes that the ends justify the means.
If anyone obstructs him,
even if it's one of his own men, he will kill him.
In other words, he is the boss of all assassins,
feared by both the Bakufu and the Imperial Court.
[Note: The Bakufu were the bureaucracy of the Tokugawa Shogunate.]
There isn't a murder he hasn't been involved in.
By the way, Karyuu-san...
don't you know him better than you know me?
A long time ago, when you were still a child,
your house was burned down,
and your entire family was murdered.
That man was responsible, wasn't he?
Magoroku!
Oh, my!
I'm just telling you what I've heard.
But, it's a cruel story.
You were getting orders to kill from your enemy.
Where is he now?
First, I'll tell you something else that's interesting.
What is it?
There is another secret about this.
Another secret?
Then again, it might be better if you didn't know.
Magoroku!
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
He's hiding in that foreigner's ship.
No one can reach him while he's there.
It was just for a short time,
but it was nice to see you again.
This will be our last meeting, so take care.
Wait! Magoroku!
Karyuu, that bitch!
Never let her escape, do you understand?
Chase her to the ends of the earth and kill her!
Yes!
You have great skill.
Truly, you've grown to be an adept shinobi.
I really should have killed you.
Is this supposed to be revenge?
I haven't become that weak yet!
Surely, this is a blood feud.
Your strength reminds me of your father.
What?
Karyuu. Don't you want to know why your house was attacked?
Hmm... Your father was the chief of the Bakufu's secret service.
He was our biggest enemy.
Is that why you killed him?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You know that in a world of peace,
we shinobi will be treated like scum.
That's why I started this business.
It was to survive.
Shut up!
I'll tell you something interesting, though.
I wasn't the only one your father was after.
He was also pursuing Aoi.
You may not know this.
Aoi abducted children from the families she killed.
Then she raised them as shinobi,
and let them work under her after they grew up.
What are you saying?!
She chose them with great care.
In all likelihood, a child like you.
You are...
Were you...
with that man?!
I went easy on you before...
but that will never happen again!
There's no escape.
Why?
Why do you hate me so much?!
Karyuu.
Don't you remember that girl?
What?
She's the girl you took pity on and spared that day.
It can't be...
It's your fault that I am what I am now.
Die!
Blood. Blood!
Why are you with that man?!
It's because he told me everything.
What?!
That you were the shinobi from that day.
So, I lured you out here.
You entrapped Magoroku!
Yes, to make this place your grave.
Blood.
Blood? Blood?
That much of my blood from...
Karyuu!
Hurry up, Karyuu!
Uzume!
Gisuke...
Because of this... everything is...
Everything is over.
Both Uzume's father and I...
were originally from the same group of shinobi.
Uzume's father realized that there was a peaceful world out there,
so he gave up the way of the shinobi,
and chose to live as a merchant with the rest of his clan.
But that man, Black Jyuuzou, wouldn't let us leave.
Before anyone noticed that Uzume's father was happy,
Jyuuzou ordered the surviving shinobi...
to assassinate him.
I was told not to let Uzume follow the way of the shinobi.
But...
I ended up being the instrument of Uzume's death.
From the time she was a child, if Uzume ever saw blood,
there was nothing to be done with her.
So in any case, the consequences would have been the same.
No...
If...
If I hadn't killed Uzume's father...
After all, Uzume was the same as me.
I made her take up the same destiny as I did.
Please, forgive me...
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
Karyuu, the world is going to change tremendously.
It will not be a world for samurai anymore.
Hey, wait!
Kikka.
You two were very unkind to leave me behind!
What happened?
I think that
it's boring without Karyuu-sama around,
so I've decided to go with you!
It's fine, though.
I told my family that I'll be traveling for a while.
So don't worry.
We're together again.
Yes. We're inseparable!
Hey. What are you doing?!
You idiot!
Stop that!
Hey, wait!
Don't leave me!
The End