A Mushi Production
It's Baghdad!
I'm finally here!
A Thousand
and One Nights
Presented by Orphan Fansubs
Executive Producer
Tezuka Osamu
Production
Tomioka Kouji
Series Composition
& Screenplay
Tezuka Osamu
Fukazawa Kazuo
Kumai Hiroyuki
Key Animation
Miyamoto Sadao
Nakamura Kazuko
Background Art
Itou Shinji
Cinematography
Tsuchiya Asahi
Cinema Supervisor
Yamaura Eiji
Sound
Tashiro Atsumi
Art Direction
Yanase Takashi
Music
Tomita Isao
With the voices of
Aoshima Yukio
(Aladdin)
Akutagawa Hiroshi
(Badli)
Kishida Kyouko
(Miriam/Jalis)
Director
Yamamoto Eiichi
Water!
Drinking water refreshes your body!
Water here!
The cure to any form of disease!
I've got water scooped from the Nile!
Water! Water!
Come and get some refreshing water!
How about some water?
Water! Water!
Get some refreshing water!
From the Nile, the cure to any form of disease!
Here I'm showing you one of the most attractive girls in creation!
This girl's as beautiful as a dahlia flower, only 18 years old, and good in bed!
Any buyers?!
A beauty like this occurs once in a century!
Great! Really nice!
Show us her face!
Ugly! Too ugly!
You lied!
Get out!
The best part of a girl is not her face, you know, so take a look at her—
It's obvious no one's gonna buy her. Show the next one! The next one!
All right, gentlemen, how about this woman?
Come and have a look!
You'll all love her plump legs and nice, round breasts!
Enough talk. Remove her clothing!
Sell her! Sell her to me!
You can take all my money!
One and a half gold pennies!
The candy shop's that way, boy.
A hundred gold pennies!
Yo, ladykiller, good choice!
Four fifty!
F-Five hundred gold pennies!
Six hundred!
Six fifty!
S-Seven hundred gold pennies!
Eight hundred!
Thirteen hundred and one!
Two thousand!
How about five thousand?
In that case, ten thousand!
Sold! The girl's yours, sir!
Sold for ten thousand gold pennies!
What? Ten thousand gold pennies?!
My woman! My woman! Move aside!
My woman! Where's my woman?!
That's my woman, you thief!
Thief! He's stealing my girl!
Someone catch him!
Take that!
There's no way I'd let those
Baghdad losers catch me.
What's the matter?
Did I look too pathetic?
I'm sorry about that.
I just wanted you that badly.
It's awfully quiet.
This is a pretty luxurious house. Let's go have a look.
No one lives here, huh?
There's not even one little cat.
I guess there really is one cat.
My legs feel numb! I can't move anymore.
You must be tired too.
Not at all.
What's your name?
Miriam.
I'm Aladdin.
I'm a poor water seller.
I can't believe I can make love to a beauty like you on this fancy bed.
I'm really glad I came to Baghdad!
However, one thing is bothering me.
When we were doing it, you were even more aroused than me.
I've dreamed about something like this, so it's not surprising I was turned on.
But how come you were so passionate with a poor man who stole you?
Maybe because I was glad.
You were glad?
That I'm not here because you bought me.
I followed you because I fell in love with you.
I see.
Not as master and slave,
but as man and woman, on an equal footing.
So you were more passionate because we were on equal footing?
That bothers me even more.
Miriam.
I'm not just fooling around here.
I'm ready to give you all the love you need.
It was open earlier! Why can't I open it?
Aladdin, the window is...
The two of you were moaning rather nicely.
Were you spying on us?
The whole time.
Who are you?
The owner of this house.
The owner? In that case, forgive us for breaking into your house.
But you didn't have to trap us!
Now, now. It's all right, isn't it?
I'll provide everything you need to live.
Stay here and try to entertain me as much as you can.
This is my sole source of amusement.
Are you kidding me?!
We're not your toys!
If you try to resist,
then I'll have no compunction about reporting you to the police.
Miriam.
We're like birds trapped in a cage.
You seem to understand your place now.
But really, your moans and cries were better than any other birds I've had,
so let me listen to more of those.
Mommy, I want her very badly!
I want to suck on her rose-like boobies!
I want to bite on her shell-like pinks nails!
Hey, Mommy, can't you do something about it?
Your father will get her for you soon.
Darling.
You did something about it, right?
As I told you last night,
the insults that our son has received
are like insults aimed at you, the Police Chief of Baghdad!
Our son is suffering right now,
and yet you're indulging in drugs as if nothing's wrong.
Your father must have been a mouse in his former life, right, son?
Are you listening?
Darling.
Darling!
Inspector Badli has arrived!
Badli, did you figure out where that woman is?
Yes, the water seller wandered into Lord Suleiman's house after kidnapping her.
And?
They still haven't come out,
so Lord Suleiman may have entrapped them.
I'm sure you know of Lord Suleiman's eccentricities.
Not to mention he's a favorite of the King of Baghdad.
It will be tough to negotiate with him.
Why don't we use force to solve the matter? I could arrange that.
This is a good chance to bring down Lord Suleiman.
Oh, that.
I leave everything to you, Badli.
I'm expecting good results from you, as always.
There's a promotion meeting coming up soon. Don't forget.
Madam.
You shouldn't play around too much with the bandits.
My husband said he wanted to promote a certain man...
I can't really stop you, can I?
Open sesame!
I've waited a long time for you, Madam.
Hey, Kamhakim.
Huh?
Forgive my rudeness.
Enough. Get lost, you fools!
Mahdya...
you should go too.
Aren't you going to listen to your father, Mahdya?!
Keep your filthy hands off my arrows!
I just saved you.
That was a carnivorous fish, right?
It's none of your business!
You don't really know me, do you?
Sure I do.
You're a woman, Mahdya.
Badli!
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you!
There are two tasks!
First, kill Suleiman and take his treasures.
Second, capture the water seller and the female slave,
who are flirting in Suleiman's mansion, and hand them over to Badli.
Yes, sir!
Huh? Where did my daughter go?
Do you want to be thrashed, Mahdya?!
Hurry up and get on your horse!
Let's go!
What's happening?
I'm not sure myself.
It must be war!
Let us out! We wanna leave!
Seriously, open this door now!
You haven't found Suleiman yet?!
Spare me!
Girls don't kill other people, right?
Free us! Open this door!
Are you trying to make grilled chicken out of us? Damn you!
Miriam. Miriam!
Did you open the door?
You're the water seller, aren't you?
Miriam!
Bring everything out!
You bastard!
What's your name?
I'm Aladdin.
This is my wife—
Aladdin!
Yes?
You killed Suleiman, didn't you?
Are you joking?
Now, take him away.
This is absurd!
This is a conspiracy! Help me, Miriam!
Aladdin!
Miriam!
So you're Miriam.
Badli.
Send her to my son.
My woman. My woman.
My very own woman.
You hated it, didn't you?
You were lonely, weren't you?
It's all right now.
Talk about pearls before swine.
Help me.
Stop it!
Please don't hit me!
Not a fan of getting whipped?
Of course not!
Then you'd better confess!
Will you let me go if I confess?
You'll be sent to trial for it.
And then?
Sentenced to death.
Did you kill Suleiman?
Admit it.
Did you kill Suleiman?!
You still refused to confess today.
Do you want to live that badly?
Isn't that obvious?
If I die, there will be nothing.
The doctor who examines corpses is my friend.
I'll make arrangements with him.
If you pretend you're dead, you'll be thrown into the commoners' grave.
If you want to live so badly,
escape from there on your own.
I'm so grateful. I really am!
Thank you.
But why are you helping me?
As the saying goes, a man with a good appetite can't be a bad man.
Water...
Water!
This won't do.
You need to sleep with me.
Listen, Miriam.
You've been here for almost a month.
I'm dying to show you how great I am in bed!
Miriam...
You fool.
Why are you talking to yourself?
"Open your legs!"
That's how you deal with a woman.
And you call yourself a man?!
That's what Mommy always says too.
Like they know better!
Let's see.
Found it!
A stimulant.
Having a drug maniac as a dad really helps at times like this!
My cutey pie!
Miriam, my woman.
I'm not my usual self tonight.
I'm tellin' you to open your legs!
Now do it, Maria—
Miriam!
Wh-What's h-happening?
I-I'm seeing f-four of y-you!
Things aren't looking good for you, Miriam!
Come down here!
I'm telling you that I'll help you.
Come down quickly!
You had nothing to do with this fool falling to his death.
I'll be your witness.
In exchange...
you'll belong to me.
Do you know about a girl named Miriam?
Her name is Miriam.
She's a slave girl.
She's about 16 or 17 years old.
If you're referring to Miriam the slave, then I'm sure I saw her at the Police Chief's house.
Is there a woman named Miriam living here?
There was.
But she disappeared suddenly.
When?
Just recently.
Do you know where she went?
I don't.
A woman called Miriam...
Miriam...
Get ahold of yourself, Miriam.
The baby will be born soon.
Women become mothers only after they go through the pain of labor.
Now, Miriam, use your strength.
Think of your beloved, the one who impregnated you with this child.
Think of him, and use it as your source of energy.
More!
Once more!
A-Aladdin...
Did you mention Miriam?
Yes, Miriam. Do you know her?
She's in the house down the road.
Down the road?
In the house of an officer named Badli.
Thanks a lot!
Miriam...
Miriam!
Jalis.
Jalis?
Is that the name of this child?
Yes.
It's a wonderful name, don't you think?
It's a good name, indeed.
What's the matter, Miriam?
Miriam! Miriam!
What do you want?
Please! Let me in.
My wife, Miriam, is inside.
I could pretend I hadn't seen you if you...
But I don't have any money.
Then it's out of the question.
At the very least, please tell me whether or not she's all right.
You're one helpless guy. Wait here.
Jalis...
My heart can't rest easy because I must leave you alone here.
I...
I have to return to God's side now.
Be a good child, Jalis.
Also...
I have just one request.
Please grant me this one request.
I want you to tell your father, Aladdin,
that I still loved him when I died, smiling.
Please tell him that...
She's dead?
Impossible!
How would you know?
When did she die?
I don't know.
That's what the chief maid said.
Give up.
Miriam is dead.
Miriam!
Miriam...
Guard Captain Badli, correct?
Who are you?
You've become quite a successful man.
I asked, who are you?
Miriam died because of you!
You bastard...
You're alive?!
W-Wait, Aladdin.
It wasn't my fault!
You're taking revenge on the wrong person.
I heard that Miriam got pregnant by—
Hey! Stop it, Aladdin!
Save me! Somebody save me!
Get up, Badli.
A captain of the Guard shouldn't be flustered!
I won't kill you.
It's not like Miriam's gonna come back.
It's petty stuff.
All petty stuff!
I'm a big man.
Open sesame!
Um...
An automatic door, huh?
Open a little more sesame!
Be more careful, you idiot, sesame!
Close sesame.
Close quietly sesame!
You bastard, I'll slice you!
Open... barley!
Did I say it wrong?
Open rice!
Open millet!
Open bean!
Open corn!
Open peanuts!
That's not it.
Um... Open red bean paste!
Open wasabi!
Open garlic!
Open pepper!
Open...
...sesame!
That's right! Sesame!
Open... what?
You have guts.
A thief has come to a thieves' hideout.
However, you're not getting out of here alive!
Hey, you can't do that! I don't have a knife.
In that case, take this.
Hurry up and take it!
Don't shout!
Otherwise, you'll wake everyone up!
Just take it!
If I do, you'll follow me, won't you?
Yup.
If I don't, then you won't, right?
In that case, don't follow me.
Open...
Stop fooling around!
Hey, stop that!
What the hell is this?
You're the water seller I met at Suleiman's palace!
That's right! You opened the door and freed us before we burned up!
I heard that you'd been imprisoned. Did you escape?
Yes, thanks to you.
So you're here to take revenge, huh?
Nothing that serious.
I just thought I could take some of these.
What are you going to do with them?
That's obvious.
I'll invest them in many different things and make lots of money!
Basically, I'll take a chance on these treasures.
It's a big world out there, after all!
Why don't you ditch your boring life in the mountains
and hit it big with me?
What'd'ya say?
That sounds interesting.
I wonder if I should go.
And while you talk big, you don't seem very reliable.
So I'll go with you!
What's that?
You should ride it.
It's from my father's loot.
What am I going to do with this toy?
Stop asking questions and get on!
Hang on tight.
Open sesame!
Whoa! It's a flying horse!
Aladdin!
Are you all right?
What the hell is this?!
Aren't there any men on this island?
That's right. There's just us.
So this is the fabled island of women.
Here comes another one.
I am the queen of this island.
Are you a normal woman?
Perhaps you're a goddess?
From now on, you can live a life carousing in an endless supply of our love.
Great! Great! I don't mind hangovers!
Everything sounds so good!
Then let me take you deep into the island.
Stop! What are you going to do with my Aladdin?
My Aladdin?
You strange girls!
How did I become such a popular guy?
Take everyone away and disappear!
Can't you see this?
If you don't keep quiet, you'll die.
You dare to talk back?!
Stop! Please stop. I can't bear to see this.
She's just a child, so stop that!
I'll let her live because she's with you.
However, she can't stay on this island.
Leave this instant!
I will!
I wouldn't stay on this island even if you asked me to!
Let's go, Aladdin.
No, I'm going to stay.
I can't leave all this treasure behind without doing anything!
What?
This is what you meant when you said you'd hit it big?
I'm disappointed in you!
I'm really sorry to disappoint you, Mahdya.
If there's a chance, perhaps we'll meet again.
I'll never forget you.
Be careful on your way back!
Aladdin, you stupid bastard!
It's almost dawn.
Go to sleep.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
If you want these days to continue forever,
then I have a request.
Promise me that you'll never open the forbidden door in the middle of the forest.
I swear.
You're a good boy, aren't you?
Queen!
Where are you, Queen?
Queen, say something!
Who cares if it's night or day? Let's just keep having fun!
Aladdin...
What? Aladdin?
Lord Aladdin. Aladdin...
Lord Aladdin. Lord Aladdin...
Aladdin...
Lord Aladdin...
Aladdin. Aladdin!
Aladdin!
Aladdin. Aladdin...
Lord Aladdin...
Remove all the water inside him.
Hey! Why are you all slacking off?!
Don't leave your stations.
Hey, everyone, stop staring at the drowned man and continue with your work!
Huh? Who are you?
Me?
Oh, you see, actually, I was just rescued.
C-Capture that freeloader!
Riding without paying is impermissible!
You have to work!
Yes, I understand, Master.
Use all of your energy!
Hey, new guy.
Are you thinking about something?
About the island full of women.
You fell asleep and had a dream, didn't you?
Hey now, there's no such place!
There is.
As a matter of fact, I just escaped from it.
All you see day and night is women.
In particular, their queen is pretty glamorous.
She pushed her breasts at me, bent down, and whispered in my ear...
What did she say?
"Yearning for love, my body is dying to have a man."
The flame of lust went wild, burning out of control! She started touching me!
That's all.
No more?!
It's hard to speak when I'm rowing.
If you switch places with me, then I'll tell you more.
All right, all right!
So the two of us were embracing each other really tightly.
She wrapped her legs around my waist.
Then I put my hand between her legs, which felt absolutely—
Can't you row properly?!
The ship's going around in circles!
It's as if the ship's chasing girls—
Even the chief mate's gone crazy!
That must be an egg of the legendary bird Loplop.
The biggest bird in the world.
Hey, guys, doesn't that sound great?
I'm sure we'll get stronger if we eat that!
Yeah!
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
A little bit to the right.
It's the mother!
Its mother is coming!
What an eerie island!
At least we're not dead.
What are you saying? Our goods are gone!
I'll go and see if someone lives on this island.
Hey! Is anyone here?
Oh, hey! I guess someone was here,
but that doesn't help.
Is there anyone here?
Anyone?
Dammit. I'm so unlucky.
I'd love to have some wine right now.
It's wine!
This is fantastic!
It'd be wonderful if there was something good to eat.
For example, fresh-grilled meat.
What's happening?
Am I drunk and seeing an illusion?
This is real meat!
I guess I'll turn in for the night. Actually...
Could you get me a bed to sleep on?
I like this ghost ship!
Or should I call it a magic ship?
Whatever.
Move. Move the ship!
It started moving.
I'd like to have a window.
I can really see it moving!
Where do you wish to go?
As you ordered, we have left the island.
You have not yet told me where to go.
You're... the ship, right?
Yes.
Any wish of yours will be obeyed, Master.
He's really something.
All right, I've decided on our destination.
Basra, the port!
As you wish, Master.
In this outfit, I don't look like the captain of a ship.
Give me clothes. The highest quality clothes.
I also want six useful sailors.
Get to work this instant.
But why are you listening to my orders?
I was a ship owned by a demon king,
but I was abandoned there 5000 years ago.
I swore to work faithfully for the first man who found me.
And you are that first man.
Is that so?
I see.
Then why don't I make another request?
A woman would be nice! I'd like to travel with a beautiful woman!
What's the matter?! Is something wrong?
Asking for women is not allowed.
Women are forbidden aboard the ship.
I guess that can't be helped, then.
Women, huh?
I'll get all the women I want.
I have this ship, after all.
I'll sail across the seven seas
and make every treasure in the world mine!
Just you watch!
15 years later...
Eggs again, dear?
It's so we can have more fun at night.
All you do is eat, sleep, and have sex with me.
Don't say that.
Abandoned by both God and demons,
we can be neither humans nor beasts.
So this is the only fun we can have.
You never have any hopes or dreams.
I'm tired of it.
We've been married for more than 500 years now,
so that's no surprise.
That aside, let's try a wager.
A wager again?
Heads or tails?
Heads.
Here goes!
It's tails.
Tonight, we're going to do it in the form of my choice.
It's up to you.
I'm sure we already tried kangaroos a month ago,
and we've done dolphins about fifty times.
I'm sick of that one.
Aren't there any other forms?
None.
I know! There's still one left.
The cockroach.
I'm sure this will be wonderful in its own way!
Don't turn into something like a cockroach!
I won the wager, didn't I?
So you've got to obey me!
I hate living like this.
I wanna go somewhere else.
Let's turn in for the night.
I'm longing for a love worth risking my life for.
Don't say something a human would.
Humans are humans, and we are who we are.
Hey! Stop for a moment!
What is it?
There's a man there.
There she goes again.
He's so handsome.
Hey, let me give you a word of advice.
We're different from human beings.
I know that!
That's why I'm thinking about ways to lure him.
It's hopeless.
I'll do it.
Hope-less!
I-don't-care!
One time, when I was in Baghdad,
I saw someone who was way better looking than him.
I don't believe you. It'd be hard to find someone better looking than him.
In that case, I'll bring that person here.
All right. Just a little more.
Stop.
Don't hide him. Show me already.
You'll see when they wake up.
Go wake up the man you brought.
Isn't that a woman?!
You were just jealous!
You really are out to get in my way!
I only said it was s-someone better looking than him!
It's your fault for thinking
I was talking about a man.
I'm sure she'll give up on him now.
Here goes!
Huh? It says she's still in love with him.
I'm Jalis from Baghdad.
I'm Aslan from Basra.
Aslan...
Jalis...
This is a wonderful meeting.
You're a wonderful man.
They said it at the same time. It's a draw, then.
This isn't looking good!
Jalis...
Aslan...
Aslan?
It wasn't a dream.
Jalis! Oh, you're awake.
I will be talking to the King about you today. Understand?
Father...
as I said last time, I'm turning it down.
I won't let you.
Listen, Jalis. It is the highest honor for a girl to be part of the King's harem.
I took you, a lowly slave's illegitimate child,
and raised you as my daughter for fifteen years,
all to bring you happiness.
Why won't you understand?
Now, I'm a busy man.
Think about it and make up your mind.
Milady, you should change your clothes.
I have a request.
Bring me men's clothing.
Men's?
I've always wanted to try it once.
Aslan...
No matter how much you love him,
it's impossible because he's a human.
Forget him, I'll give you a good time tonight with my best techniques—
Shut up!
You disgust me!
Really now?
As if flirting with another man isn't disgusting! Suit yourself!
I'm leaving!
If you want to follow, then now's the time.
Hey, I'm saying that you can come along.
You've made me mad now!
This is goodbye!
If it's heads, she'll come back.
If it's tails, she'll come back.
Here goes.
You're going to defy me too?
Oh, well.
I guess I'll enjoy the single life for a while.
I know!
I'll go to Baghdad.
I won't be able to meet Jalis if I stay here.
Where did that come from?
No saddle...
Did I see it wrong?
Whatever. Just when I needed one!
Hey, can you go any faster?
The sun is setting.
I should stop around here for the night.
A tent?
How did this end up here?
Two pillows.
Who are these for?
I saw a tent here.
Do you think I could stay here for the night?
Actually, I stumbled on this tent just now, too.
I came from Baghdad.
From Baghdad?
I'm on my way there!
Do you know someone named Jalis?
Jalis...
I've fallen for her.
I'm going there to look for her.
I know this Jalis!
What? Really? Where is she?
What do you know?
Anything will do! Please tell me.
Let's get in the bed first.
Put your hands on my breasts.
Your breasts?
You have... strange interests.
Mine are far better than a woman's!
Stop teasing me.
Are you scared?
If you won't do as I say,
then I won't tell you about Jalis.
Hey, now.
Come, put your hand on my breast.
You're... You're a woman?
Aslan!
Jalis!
Lady Jalis...
Your father is worried about you.
Please come back with us.
Vizier.
I have important news.
A great merchant called Sinbad will be visiting Baghdad soon.
According to my investigation, this man's wealth exceeds all other merchants.
If you can get Sinbad to be your ally,
you should be able to wield even greater influence.
I see what you mean.
So how do I make him my ally?
I have a brilliant, albeit violent, plan in mind.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, sir.
You're going?
Yeah.
When will you come again?
I don't know.
Do you love me?
Of course I do.
Don't ever come again!
Badli, be considerate to Mahdya.
You always tease that poor girl.
The worries of a father, huh?
That aside, how are the preparations for the raid?
Everything is ready.
We'll kill Sinbad dead on the spot.
Let's discuss Mahdya's future when this is all over.
Great.
Boys!
Stay quiet.
Now go, Mahdya.
I'm counting on you to deceive Sinbad.
Lord Sinbad.
We are a father and daughter who sell oil, on our way to Baghdad.
Would you be so kind as to let us spend the night next to you in this oasis?
Of course. Feel free.
When did you change your business, Mahdya?
It's me.
Aladdin?
Now, now, don't overreact.
I can imagine what you've got in your oil barrels.
Still, you've become quite a woman.
Aladdin...
you're so cruel!
I thought about killing myself so many times.
But the sliver of hope that maybe, just maybe, we'd meet again
got me through the painful days.
Let's go, boys!
What's wrong? What is it?
Badli...
You bastard...
You bastard. You tricked me!
Tricked you?
This is the first time we've met.
You traitor!
Mahdya...
Father!
Badli!
Leave her.
It's just one woman. We can capture her anytime.
Mr. Sinbad, I presume.
Yes.
Bandits were about to assail you.
I am Badli, the Police Chief of Baghdad.
I am in your debt.
You saved my life.
We'll be escorting and guarding you.
Thank you, sir.
How do you feel here?
Nice, very nice. I can really relax.
There's no place safer than the Police Chief's home, after all.
Did you come to Baghdad to trade?
Not at all. I'm here for other reasons.
Oh? What might they be?
If you can, please tell me.
It's important for me to know so that I can ensure your safety.
Chief, my collection of treasures is so massive...
that I can't add any more to it.
So I want to buy this country.
In other words, I want to be the King.
Th-The King of Baghdad?
Yes.
The King of Baghdad is a well known collector of treasures.
So I propose a contest between my collection of rare treasures and his,
with the winner taking the throne.
That's what I have in mind. Will you help me?
Aslan.
Was this what your first taste of love was like?
Take him to the army. Tell the Captain to send him to the slave troops.
Aslan!
Jalis.
Jalis!
Aslan...
Aslan!
Jalis is the daughter of that water seller.
She's my trump card.
Is that man serious?
Yes.
Sinbad clearly said he wanted a contest of treasures to determine who would be king.
He should know his place!
What should I tell him? He wants a response.
What do you think I should do?
Why don't you relay the message to the King?
We'll be fine, no matter who the winner is.
Actually,
Sinbad's just a parvenu, so he might be easier to manipulate.
I see. Sounds great!
Everyone in town is coming to see the treasure contest.
But really, you have an amazing collection.
I'll have it all taken to the royal coliseum under tight security.
Thank you.
Miriam?
Is something the matter?
Who is that girl?
She's my daughter.
Her name is Jalis.
Jalis...
She's like Miriam.
Dear people of Baghdad, the children of God,
I am the King who rules over Baghdad and you, its people.
I, Mahomet Bin Subaig IV,
hereby swear in God's name
that I will compare all of my treasures against Sinbad's,
and the winner will be decided objectively and fairly.
The winner of this competition will be the King of Baghdad.
Are you the fool by the name of Sinbad?
Yes.
Be prepared to lose your head.
I will now state the rules.
There will be thirteen rounds in all.
The thirteen best treasures of each contestant will be compared.
The results will be recorded on these boards.
White will award the point to the King,
while black will give it to Sinbad.
Well then, let us begin.
First round.
Second round.
Third round.
Is she trying to seduce me, the King?
Quickly!
Bring in the water!
She was a mermaid?
That treasure won't be useful anymore.
She's the only one in the whole world, so it's truly a pity.
Sinbad, let me warn you.
This figure approaches a person whose mind is agitated
and throws its sharp sword, piercing the person's heart.
No one can escape.
Unfortunately, my King,
I'm not agitated in the slightest.
So it's true.
The Vizier commanded me to do this in order to put Sinbad in his debt.
The plot involved making Kamhakim attack them.
Then we appeared and saved Sinbad.
I felt very sorry for Kamhakim.
I had to betray a good friend, after all.
That swine! I'll make him pay.
I understand your feelings, but...
You stay out of this.
Wh-What?!
Argh, that evil traitor!
M-Medicine... M-M...
Vizier!
It's revenge for killing Kamhakim, darling.
That frightened me.
Hurry up and declare the result!
I knew it.
Sixth round!
Will this require an extra round?
It's really hard to predict the result.
Yeah, I bet it'll take an extra round! This is so entertaining!
There's really no way to tell who will win.
They're tied at six points each!
Now on to the thirteenth round.
The decisive round has come!
Summon the executioner here.
The thirteenth round.
Quiet, please!
This final round will be a contest between horses.
The first horse to bring back the King's pennant from a hill 50 km away will be the winner!
That's the fastest horse in the world.
Don't be frightened!
The flying wooden horse!
That wooden horse is mine!
I received it a long time ago!
What are you talking about?
That horse is my treasure.
I don't think so. A girl named Mahdya gave it to me 15 years ago.
Shut up, fool!
This horse was confiscated from the cave of Kamhakim the bandit!
Or are you trying to say that you used to have a close relationship with bandits?
But this isn't a real horse.
Not to mention it can fly.
Even if it can fly, a horse is still a horse.
Worry about your own horse!
I understand.
I will ride my horse.
What?
I'm too anxious to just sit and watch.
At the very least, I want to try my best for the final match.
Mr. Sinbad,
for this round, I will be your rival.
Betting tickets! It's a chance to make big money! Get yours!
Proceed to the starting line.
Ready!
I used to torture prisoners like this when I was just an officer.
Stop hampering me, please!
I was just fooling around.
They're now on their way back!
Move aside!
You're in my way!
Come to the think of it, this is the first time I've ridden a horse.
Let's check your pennants.
The winner of this round is the King!
That's impossible!
The horses crossed the line at the same time!
It was a draw!
There's a tear in your pennant,
but none on the King's.
You lose.
A tear on the pennant doesn't matter!
Shut up.
The pennant has the sacred symbol of royalty on it.
Damaging it constitutes lese-majesty!
You lose.
As promised, prepare yourself for execution.
Please hold on a moment, O King.
I gained my fame on the seas.
I want to meet my death on a ship.
My ship is anchored at the mouth of the river.
All my treasures are stored there.
Please take a look at them before you cut off my head.
I will give all of them to you.
Please wait, Vizier.
I'm talking to you, Chief.
Vizier?
Whatever happens, you'll be the next Vizier.
I want to keep you around because you have political experience.
Okay.
So, where are the treasures?
There's nothing here!
Magic ship,
go to the end of the earth at top speed!
Yes, Master.
It seems I win.
My King of Baghdad.
Good day to you, my King.
Yes, Vizier Badli.
How does it feel to become the King?
Good. It's very nice.
Now that you are the King, I wish to hear your new policies for the country.
I will now declare my new policies.
Write them down.
Yes, sir.
First, everyone should greet each other by licking each other's noses.
Pardon?
People in Baghdad are to lick each other's noses as a greeting.
Nonsense. We are not dogs.
That is my command. Write it down.
What is your answer?
Yes, sir.
Your voice is too soft.
"Yes, sir!" Just like that.
Yes, sir.
It's still too soft!
Yes, sir!
Very good.
Next, standing on one's head will be the respectful greeting.
Pardon my rudeness, my King, but that is not policy.
Then what is policy?
Housing, commodity prices, education...
In that case, make rice and salt ten times more expensive,
and make chili pepper and mugwort ten times cheaper!
That's just unreasonable.
Are you saying people should eat chili pepper and mugwort every day?
Order the police to arrest all dissidents.
Suppress them mercilessly!
That's it. Please announce it to the Senate.
Yes, sir!
Stand on your head!
The third policy.
The King commands that a tower be built.
A tower? What kind of tower?
A tall tower.
One tall enough to reach the Sun.
What are we building it for?
To spend tax money.
That's ridiculous.
This is why we don't want novices in politics.
How are we going to explain this tax to the public?
With that much money, the pension for us and veterans could be doubled.
Those who disagree will be executed.
Anyone disagree?
Construction is to begin tomorrow. That's all.
Stand on your head!
The seventh policy.
We will start a war!
Good day, my King.
Don't be so formal.
Come here and pour me some wine.
You see, Jalis,
I asked the King about you a few days ago.
He wants you to be the first member of his harem!
Yes, that's right.
What's wrong, Jalis?
This is an undeserved honor! Thank him!
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Jalis!
Well, I'm not in a hurry.
You're just frightening her.
The King has arrived!
Has the tower reached the Sun?
Your Highness, we have tried our best.
Baghdad has used up all of its technology, labor, and resources.
We've even pulled resources from other nations we've conquered,
but this is as far as we can go.
And that's why you want to end the project, correct?
Yes.
If it continues, the tower will eventually collapse, and Baghdad will be ruined.
When will that be?
Well, it's difficult to say exactly when.
Then continue building the tower until that day comes.
Are trying to ruin Baghdad, Your Highness?
You'll never know unless you try!
If you can't reach the Sun,
then at least reach the Moon!
Wait.
This is to save Baghdad.
Please let me kill him, Vizier.
Revolting in haste will only end in failure.
What's important is public opinion.
Well, just believe in me.
So this is as high as it can go?
What are you roaring about?
Do you have a grudge against me?
Do you want me to be a good king?
Hah! Don't even dream of it.
What is a king?
It's power!
When a king sneezes once,
ten doctors lose their heads.
And when a king yawns once,
a thousand beauties start dancing for him.
That's what a king is!
I've become a king, but what does it mean to be one?
Just how much power does a king have?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
Come on, answer me!
Can the tower really only be this tall?
Is this really the limit?!
Jalis?
Are you Jalis?
What are you doing?
Looking at the front lines of war far away.
Do you see anything?
Many men who are fighting for you.
Jalis.
Yes?
Badli said you have refused
to be part of my harem.
Why is that?
I don't want to.
No?
Why not?!
Your Highness, I have Aslan.
Aslan?
Yes.
He is in the slave troops.
Are you saying he's your lover?
I love him.
I want to love of my own free will.
I am the King.
"I want to love of my own free will."
It doesn't work that way!
This is my command.
Come to my bedroom tonight.
No!
All right, I'll call Aslan back.
Huh?
And I'll make him give up on you.
Don't work too hard, brother.
Private Aslan has been sentenced to death for attempting to escape.
A-Aslan...
Forgive me, Jalis.
It's my fault for sending him to the slave troops.
You don't have to join the King's harem if you're not willing.
As atonement for what I've done to Aslan,
I will reject the King's demand, even at the cost of my life.
Father!
I... will be part of the King's harem.
I refuse to testify about it.
Then what are you going to do? Huh?
That fool.
It's just like a dream!
How wonderful that you remember me.
I am the Vizier, you know?
How could I forget about the Vizier's wife?
The Vizier and the Vizier's wife...
I see where you're going.
Didn't your late husband have a potion that could make the dead speak?
You're the best, Badli.
Bite my breast.
Where is the potion?
The third bottle on the second shelf.
Tease me more.
All right!
What I couldn't forget was not you but the potion.
If you're going to kill me, then make it fast.
It won't be long. This is the
infamous Valley of the Lions!
The hungry lions will be here soon.
Stay away!
He's gonna wake up!
Why did you hide?
I owe you a debt.
Aslan.
If a human saw my real form as a magical being, I'd die.
Fine.
I'll go out and make you mine, even if it means my death.
That fool!
This is weird.
Ouri!
Jalis is in trouble!
You messed up my plan again, didn't you?
We can fight later.
We need to take Aslan to her!
No! You kidnapper!
Jalis.
Yes, sir!
"Yes" is sufficient.
You'll spoil the mood.
Yes.
I love you, Jalis.
It's up to this man now.
Let's go.
I'm satisfied now that I've done my best.
Goodbye, Aslan.
Who's there?!
Aslan!
Aslan?
Jalis!
You're still alive, Aslan!
Aslan!
I see. Perfect timing. Let's settle this.
This is the King's command.
Aslan, abandon Jalis!
You won't? I'll behead you!
Aslan!
I see what you're up to.
You're a shrewd fellow, aren't you?
Here, take it with you. You won't have to work for the rest of your life!
So get away from Jalis, okay?
This isn't enough?
How about now?
All right, here's an astonishing deal.
I'll give you my entire fortune and my crown!
I'm saying you'll be the King! Hey, listen!
Aslan, I'll give you one more chance.
Get away from Jalis.
Jalis, come over here if you don't want to be beheaded.
You defiant...
I'll make mincemeat out of you!
Jalis.
You understand how much I love you, don't you?
I'm just another man in the agonies of love.
Can't you sympathize with me at all?
I can't.
Why?!
You are, and will always be, the King.
That makes me so different from other men?
Why? Why?!
Is this what it means to be a king?
I want to love and be loved, too, just like other people!
I'm alone.
Why does no one try to understand me, leaving me frustrated?
Is there no God in this world, dammit?!
Vizier, what is this ruckus?
I gathered them.
I thought I'd show you something interesting, Your Highness.
People of Baghdad!
Now, in the name of God...
the trial of Sinbad, King of Baghdad, shall begin!
Huh?
Bring forth the witnesses!
Auntie!
Chief maid, you are the old woman who brought Jalis up.
Answer me from the world of death.
What are the names of Jalis's parents?
Her father is Aladdin, the water seller, and her mother is Miriam.
Bring foward the former warden!
Yes, sir.
You know the relationship between the water seller Aladdin and King Sinbad, don't you?
Is there a cross-shaped hook mark on his neck?
Indeed, there's a cross-shaped hook mark.
And where did this mark come from? Witness, explain.
That's the mark I left on the water seller Aladdin when I tortured him ten years ago.
Kill him!
Thus Sinbad is the water seller Aladdin,
and Jalis here is his daughter.
These two facts should now be clear!
Silence! Silence!
Now, this is what happened last night.
The water seller Aladdin,
who is now known as Sinbad,
spent the night with Jalis, his own daughter.
Father and daughter made love to each other!
He may be the King, but he committed incest!
His actions are intolerable to God!
Take away his crown!
Wise people of Baghdad!
There is one more matter to discuss!
After we confiscate the crown from this savage, Sinbad,
who will take the throne and be the next King of Baghdad?
Badli!
So that's how it is.
That's how it's going to be.
Step down, Aladdin.
That's perfect.
I was waiting for the right time to throw this crown away.
Take it.
Jalis!
Wait! Where do you think you're going?!
It's a lie that Sinbad spent the night with Jalis!
Who is this man?
I took Jalis back last night.
I'm the man who's married to her!
That's how you've always been, Badli.
Obsessed with moving up the ranks,
you lived your life deceiving everyone around you.
You're a man who should be the King of Hell!
What are you doing? Seize her!
Don't move!
If you move, you'll die too.
Come, Aladdin.
It'll be just you and me, two people the public hates.
Let's depart on a journey once again, Aladdin.
Mahdya!
Mahdya.
It seems I can never stay with you.
Aladdin...
The people have decided.
The heinous King Sinbad,
also known by the name Aladdin,
is hereby sentenced to death.
He will be beheaded immediately.
Do you have any last words, Aladdin?
Father.
Your father is quite a strange man, Jalis.
However, even if we are father and daughter,
it doesn't matter.
All human life boils down to one thing.
Pursue and achieve your own dreams with your own power.
Keep building on them.
That's the first step towards anything.
Father!
All right. Farewell, everyone.
The role of king was too small for me.
What comes after being a king, I wonder?
Translation
convexity, ElyasRay
Editing, Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Corbyn, Saji
Encoding
tophf