Production
Hakozaki
Yasushi
(Japan
Home Video)
Nomura
Kazufumi
(A.P.P.P)
Sebata
Fumio
(Adness)
Hirata
Mikihiko
(Panorama
Communications)
Takahashi
Mitsunori
(Churoku
Service)
Executive Director
Kikuchi Yasuhito
Character Design
Takahashi Shinya
Screenplay
Yamada Mitsuhiro
Art Director
Kuwabara Satoru
Okazaki Hideo
Sound Director
Honda Yasunori
Director
Abe Masashi
So tight!
Well done.
Chapter Three
Fugitive Ninja
Makoto Riso's daughter.
Was Rihei murdered?
There can be no mistake.
Very well, then.
Yes.
Did something else happen?
No, that's all.
Isn't that dangerous?
This isn't a toy.
Karyuu-sama always tells you
not to touch weapons on your own.
But it seems like fun.
You're sly.
It's okay for me because I'm an adult.
Damn! So close...
One more time.
It was almost there.
So frustrating!
Kinoto.
Give them all to me.
Take this!
How is it?
You!
One more time!
Go!
How is it?!
Here.
Thank you, but I need to rest a little.
Ninjas sure have it hard.
What is it?
It's rude to look at a person's butt.
P-Poisonous snake!
No! No! No! No!
H-Help me!
No!
The devil?
Yes.
But that thing isn't wearing the devil's skin,
but the same skin as ours.
He is officially a merchant.
However, he is cautious and keeps the opium trade secret.
Opium?
He seems to make an enormous profit.
Come in.
Shura and Hyakki.
This time, they will help you with your mission.
Aoi-sama, I can do it alone-
You can't!
Got it?
Kill him for sure.
Use any means necessary.
However...
I won't allow anything to be done behind my back.
If they find out about us,
how you feel about it won't matter.
Without hesitation...
kill him.
Hate him with all your heart.
Hold a grudge against him.
Don't let him escape, no matter what.
Yes.
Please allow me to join you.
Wonderful.
This is the first time I've felt like this.
There is something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
Do you know about Chen-sama?
Chen? I don't know him.
Come on...
You must know about him.
I love oriental women!
Your smooth skin makes me unable to answer.
I beg you.
What about him?
What do you want to know about that man?
It's your fault.
M-My...?
Actually, tonight he has to be at a meeting.
That is...
Does he worry you that much?
Yes.
Chen-sama is a dreadful person.
He kills without apology.
He is a silky-smooth poison.
But he's a common man,
and he doesn't know the location of the special meeting.
I really don't know anything.
H-Hey, stop it.
I got it, I got it.
Tonight, he will indeed stop by the company offices.
Thank you very much.
Is it certain?
There's no mistake.
Tonight.
There was no need to kill him.
What?
If he's dead, it's certain he'll be found.
You should've let him sleep, or hidden him.
What are you implying?
Karyuu has recently been on Aoi-sama's bad side.
Don't forget that you're not the only shinobi.
Oh well.
Let's go, Shu.
Chen-sama.
Two of them?
Are you all right?
Was your opponent skillful?
Yes.
That was close.
What are you trying to say?
I'm not trying to pry into your business.
Karyuu... I want to ask you something.
Did you see a man with a wound on his right arm?
I'm pursuing that man.
Who is that man?
Then you have seen him?
He's a dreadful man.
I can't say any more than that now.
Be careful. Chen is dangerous.
Karyuu... as I thought.
Hyakki, we should let Aoi-sama know about this immediately.
Who is it?
I've brought your dinner.
Come in.
Excuse the interruption.
Honored guest?
Umm...
Don't mind this.
Serve it.
Okay...
H-Honored guest?
Please stop it.
No!
An assassin?
Who sent you?
Don't move!
How did you sneak in?
You must be the one who attacked me recently.
However, this is the end.
Shinobi...
I heard that this country has such things.
I've taken care of Chen.
You're a traitor.
You're spying for Gisuke.
What?
You and Gisuke...
Wait a minute.
I did indeed meet with Gisuke.
However...
Be silent!
Aoi-sama has been watching Gisuke's actions all this time.
Karyuu, I'll tell you why Aoi-sama sent us to accompany you.
It was to watch you.
This is absurd!
Like the rule says, you must die.
What are you trying to accomplish by killing your comrade?
Comrade?
You're in the way!
What?
You're an eyesore!
Because you're too strong.
Die!