Production
Hakozaki Yasushi
(Japan Home Video)
Nomura Kazufumi
(A.P.P.P)
Sebata Fumio
(Adness)
Takahashi Mitsunori
(Churoku Service)
Executive Director
Kikuchi Yasuhito
Character Design
Takahashi Shinya
Art Director
Kuwabara Satoru
Okazaki Hideo
Sound Director
Honda Yasunori
Soon. There, that's the end of it.
Now then...
What have we here?
No!
Oh, they're beautiful.
Producers
Seya Makoto
(Japan Home Video)
Nomura Kazufumi
(A.P.P.P.)
Tsukamoto Yoshirou
(Panorama Communications)
Ah, no!
Director
Abe Masashi
And here...
Wh-What is this?!
Wh-What's happening?
I fear someone is after your life.
What are you saying?
Someone help me! There's an assassin here!
Someone...
Chapter One
Law of Darkness
Don't tell me...
Too bad.
M-Master!
Oh, no! The Master's dead!
Welcome back.
Karyuu-sama?
Aoi-sama has been waiting for you.
Very well.
Karyuu is here.
How did it go?
I see.
You had some trouble.
Aoi-sama.
What is it?
I wasn't the one...
who killed him.
What?
I don't know her...
but I fear she could be an assassin.
Do you know anything else?
No.
That man Magoroku...
might have hired another assassin besides us to do the job.
Well, no matter.
You must be tired. Rest for a while.
Aoi-sama.
What is it?
How long must I do these kind of jobs?
Are you dissatisfied?
Yes.
That again.
We, the shinobi, must do this to stay alive during this long period of peace.
It can't be helped.
However,
soon the world will change.
I'm sure it will.
Blood, the smell of blood.
So much of it...
on my body.
Excuse me, I've brought the vegetables.
So...
Is this enough for my request?
I'm counting on you.
You're up against a great man this time.
It won't be easy.
No need to worry.
Aside from that, do you know anything about another female shinobi?
A female shinobi? Not really...
Nowadays, you'd expect them to be working as bodyguards or as hitmen for hire.
Oops!
Thank you.
She will complete the task.
Rest assured, her skills are quite adequate.
Thank you.
My name is Karyuu.
Ah! It's that little one again.
There it is!
D-Damn you, you thief of a raccoon!
You're eating it.
It was supposed to be for the guest.
I won't let you off today!
Wait! You little... You...
Wait!!
Kinoto, hand me that raccoon!
Kikka-kun.
Wh-What?
Fuu is a giant flying squirrel.
See?
Whatever it is, that doesn't change anything!
Anyway, you...
Kikka-san.
Oh, excuse me, Saki-san.
I'll handle the rest.
Thank you.
Who's the guest?
It's Magoroku.
It'll get busy again.
Work?
K-Kind of.
But you're still a child, so you don't need to hear about it.
Excuse me.
Magoroku-sama?
It really has been a while.
Are you done talking with Aoi-sama?
Yes, that's the reason I'm here with you.
You mustn't! Please!
Nice skin.
Don't...
I'll fondle these more, soon enough.
That aside, has something weird happened?
Something weird?
Aoi spoke in a strange tone today.
Nothing special, really.
Nothing special...
Nothing special, huh?
Karyuu-sama, won't you join us for tea?
Nothing for you.
All you do is eat.
By the way, Karyuu-sama,
is it true that someone tried to interfere with you last night?
Umm, th-that's just what Saki-san told me.
Kinoto...
I'll come back here. Wait for me.
Excellent!
Taking a bath, huh.
Who is it?
My name is Ryuu.
[The Bakufu was the military bureaucracy of the Tokugawa shogunate.]
Seems as if the Bakufu has really lowered its standards.
Sending a different woman each day to an outsider like me.
I will wash your back.
Wait.
Maybe you're trying to get me to face that way.
If someone killed me, the ranks of the Bakufu's enemies would decrease dramatically.
What a fearsome man.
I merely came here to be of service, master.
That's really cunning.
Nice skin.
And so pure...
M-Maybe you should stop.
Oh, hey!
Really...
Don't say something so lonely.
You can rely on me.
Because of you, I can't stop myself from making a little mistake.
Lord!
What's all the ruckus?
Lord, there's an assassin!
Wh-Wh-What is this?!
It's a killer!
Could it be...
I'll be damned.
Who are you?
And now what?
At last, the final moment.
Blood? Blood!
Blood! Blood!
It's all your fault!
Oh, it's you.
How were my foolish men?
What happened to the assassin?
She was killed.
Is that so? And you did that? You're brilliant.
Was that shinobi who flew in here...
so unskillful?
You have great skills, and on top of that, your body is glorious.
How's this. Will you work for me instead?
I'll top the other's offer.
You're the kind of shinobi that will become increasingly useful.
Thank you for the offer.