Orphan
Fansubs
presents
St. Michaela
School
Drifting
Story
Part 1
Daisuke-san!
Is everything okay, my lady?
Yes, I'm fine, Gonza.
I just had a bad dream. That's all.
That's not good.
Well, it's still too early to get up,
so please go back to sleep for now.
Amakusa Shirou believed in some kind of evil religion, but it wasn't Christianity.
The flag of Amakusa's rebellion flies in Harbin even now,
but it's a Protestant revolt rather than a Catholic one.
The government used the Shimabara Rebellion as an excuse to clamp down on Christianity.
I mean...
They called the peasants' revolt a Christian plot.
Sister must be really angry right now,
because she's very strict about time.
The new transfer student is supposed to be brilliant,
but she's late on her first day, huh?
Stop talking in class, Yamato-san and Aochi-san!
Yes, ma'am.
Stand up and come to the front!
How many times do I have to tell you girls that even small things...
will affect your school recommendation?
Get ready for punishment.
Here goes!
Stand out in the hall.
So that's Michaela School, huh?
Shit, I'm late.
What the hell?! Am I still that far from the school?
Oh well, I'll take a shortcut.
Ikeda Rika, you got 99 points.
That's just what I'd expect from you as leader of team Hana.
Everyone should emulate her.
Oshima Mayumi, you got 75 points.
Not too bad.
Miuchi Youko, you got 32 points.
You know you have to develop a cultured mind to get into Takarazuka.
Ow!
You're not trying hard enough!
Takemiya Kozue, you got 22 points, the lowest score in the class.
Sorry I'm late!
I'm Mimura Aiko.
I'm the new transfer student.
Huh? Did I come to the wrong classroom?
How dare you to be late for class on your first day, Mimura Aiko?
I came right to the class without stopping by the dorm, though.
What's with your hair color?
Where is your cross?
Your socks and shoes do not conform to school rules either.
Wearing pierced earrings is an outrage!
Your belongings are supposed to have subdued colors,
including your underwear, handkerchief, rubber band, and hairpin.
They can't have patterns either.
Putting on makeup is not allowed, not even lip balm.
All the rules can be found in the Student Handbook.
Are you even listening to me, Mimura-san?!
That's stupid.
Why do we have to give up our personalities?
Why can't I dye my hair?
That's...
Don't even ask.
That's just the way it works here.
Rules are rules.
I guess that's because you're afraid
that if everyone chooses their own hair color, they might start thinking for themselves.
Am I right?
Don't talk back to me!
I didn't talk back.
I just asked you a question.
Get ready for a punishment!
Oh, aren't you the sadist?
Hit me hard, harder, harder, please!
Mimura Aiko, you have violated school rules on your first day and rebelled against the sister.
I didn't rebel against her.
Therefore, in the name of the Girls' Crusade, we are going to punish you.
In the name of the Girls' Crusade, we are going to punish you.
What?! You guys are kidding, right?
Get her!
Let go of me!
Come on!
What the hell are you doing?
Stop it!
What was that?
She's far from an excellent student.
Her best subject is P.E., especially swordplay and martial arts.
Report
"The Establishment
of Roman Catholicism and Its History"
Hold on. Is this some sort of joke?
This isn't a joke.
The school permits students to be harshly punished as part of religious training.
No way! Help!
Stay there for the rest of the day.
W-Wait, what about my lunch?
I'll have to pee too!
Just hold it in if you don't want to wet your panties.
Geez! You're evil!
Moron! Nitwit!
You're a cold-blooded demon!
Give me back my tuition!
Your playing is wonderful, as usual, Daisuke-sama.
Sister Yumiko, this phase of the war is getting more intense.
How is the Michaela Project progressing?
It's going well.
Everyone is working hard
to get to Takarazuka.
And we received a transfer student today.
A transfer student?
Yes.
She transferred from Hibiya High School.
She looks like a good student in terms of grades,
but she's rebellious.
Of course, we're keeping her in the punishment room,
to give her time for self-reflection.
Well, we don't have much time until the Mass.
I'm counting on you.
Yes. Please leave everything to me.
Rolled eggs again?
I mean they taste good, but...
Don't say that.
In the dorm, we're supposed to cook for ourselves.
But Youko always cooks for you, right?
That's okay.
I'm happy to do it.
I'm not good at anything else.
If I can't make it to Takarazuka, I'd like to sell boxed lunches.
I'd sing and dance while I pushed the serving trolley.
I'd feel like I was on my own little stage.
How romantic! I like the idea, Youko.
Hey, let me play on that stage once in a while too, okay?
Whatever.
Hey, you want to go check on the girl in the punishment room?
What?
You should stay away from her.
Don't be an idiot.
I'm just going there to smoke.
Watch out for people coming, Youko.
Okay.
Boy, you know how to unlock all kinds of locks, Atsuko.
I wish you could unlock the one down here.
I don't think I can.
It has a special lock.
Too bad.
You're so saucy. Don't you think so, Kumi?
Yeah. It was funny when she called the sister "a sadist."
Leave me alone.
Well, it serves you right.
By the way, have you been to the discos in Roppongi?
Of course.
That was why I got transferred here.
I'm jealous.
I want to go to a disco and dance too.
Then why don't you quit this school?
What?
Are you crazy?
Both our parents and the world in general have abandoned us.
If we leave here, the only place we can go is a juvenile facility.
And here is better, right?
That's right.
Plus, here we can hope to get into Takarazuka.
I want to be a star and surprise the world.
We do want to go to discos, though.
That's what you came here for as well, right?
You even lied to them and said that you were a good student to get in here.
You have to act smart here to get what you want, though.
Like that bitch, Rika.
Oh, you mean the girl who was saying something like "in the name of the Girls' Crusade"?
You should stay away from her.
Rumor has it that she controls team Hana and perhaps all the students as well.
Rika, huh?
Someone should take her down a peg.
Why don't you do that, Atsuko?
The next class is P.E. That's a perfect place for it.
Me?
You're the only one strong enough to fight her.
Geez, everybody's such a coward here.
Uh oh, we're gonna be late!
Hey, can you let me down?
Unfortunately, we can't.
Because we don't want the sisters to punish us.
Later.
This world is in a state of confusion,
because of Darwin's theory of evolution and the Copernican system.
We should never forget Moses' Ten Commandments.
Magazine: Pop Teen
Fornication is forbidden.
I found this magazine in someone's desk.
He said, "Let's feel good together."
"By that, I-I mean I want you to suck my dick."
"In return, I'll lick your pussy."
"That's called a b-blowjob...”
These kinds of magazines are everywhere today,
but you girls must not look at them.
You must all remain innocent and beautiful.
Now, as members of the Girls' Crusade,
strengthen your bodies to get into Takarazuka.
Team Hoshi, to the right.
Team Tsuki, to the left.
Team Yuki and Hana, on standby.
So this is the transfer student, School President?
Yes. Her name is Mimura Aiko.
Y-You're the school president?
Will you let me down now, please?
I have to pee.
Hey, that was dangerous!
Couldn't you have done it more gently?
I want to see how she does in training.
All right, come this way, Mimura-san.
Oh, are you going to let me go? Cool.
You're missing certain documents required for entering this school.
What?
You have to submit a parental proxy.
A parental proxy?
Yes, you have to get it from your parents.
The letter should say that they entrust us with all discipline.
Waza-ari!
You win.
It's not over yet!
She got me.
Not yet.
Come on, you're still a part of the Girls' Crusade.
The transfer student.
Go ahead.
Move your lazy butt!
Or are you only diligent in reading those magazines?
Now, get up!
Youko...
Shame on you, Miuchi Youko.
Fight with her, Ikeda-san.
Without mercy, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
More!
Please stop.
I won't read those magazines anymore!
Please!
Sister, how about a fight between leaders now?
Very well.
Take her to the confessional.
Yes, ma'am.
The leader of team Tsuki, Takemiya Kozue, versus the leader of team Hana, Ikeda Rika.
Youko...
Fight!
Hey, why are they doing this?
To get into Takarazuka, of course.
On stage, you may have to act like Oscar in the French Revolution or Carmen the gypsy.
So martial arts are a necessity.
Only to get on stage, huh?
How cruel of you to attack her like that!
That was a punishment for her reading that magazine.
You bitch!
Waza-ari!
Wow, you're so strong, Rika-san!
Come here.
You're going to fight Ikeda-san now.
Me? How scary.
What's taking you so long?!
Yes, ma'am.
Waza-ari.
Ikeda-san is the winner!
She might be useful in the future.
Mimura-san, you did well against Ikeda-san,
so I'll let you go for today.
Lucky! Thank you.
She's pretty good, huh, Kozue?
Come to the punishment room after dark.
Atsuko, I'm going to make something simple today,
because we don't have the chef tonight, right?
Newcomer, do you know how to cook?
Me? No.
Geez. You're only good at P.E., I guess.
But it felt good
when you turned aside all of her attacks so easily.
I don't think Youko is coming back today.
Probably not. She's in the confessional.
Well, she screwed up.
She should never have brought those kinds of magazines to school.
Hey, what does she do in the confessional?
Look out through the window.
It's the building behind the school.
The sisters lock you away in there.
You might even have to stay the night.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine...
How's that?
Youko always sings that song, doesn't she?
Forget all grudges, hatreds, and sorrows.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine, sing for tomorrow.
Youko!
We are returning Miuchi Youko to you.
And, Aiko Mimura...
come to the school president's room tomorrow before class, okay?
Hey, are you all right?
Youko, can you hear me?
My goodness.
Her nose is smashed.
They're so evil!
Th-They're gone.
What is this?
St. Michaela
School
My lady, Kanou-sama is here.
How are you feeling, Yuki-san?
Are you scared?
I am scared, Daisuke-sama.
I've had the exact same dream for the past two days.
In it, your plane crashes on a southern island.
That's absurd.
It's probably because of the fever.
Don't worry. The students will turn this bad situation around.
Daisuke-sama, I'm worried.
You shouldn't go to the school anymore.
Yuki-san, let's get married.
Right after the Mass.
Daisuke-sama.
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
..St.
.Michaela
School
My students went to sleep peacefully today, as usual.
Thank you very much for your mercy.
Please help us with the Michaela Project.
Um, excuse me.
We're traveling entertainers.
We're looking for a place to stay for the night.
H-How did you people get in here?
Well, the gate was open.
That's impossible.
Men are not permitted in this school,
so I can't allow you to stay here.
Don't you have any pity?
I-I can't let strangers stay in any case.
How come men are not allowed here?
Well... it's an old tradition.
How come Michaela School is located in the middle of nowhere?
That's also an old tradition.
No, those aren't traditions.
The school has been this way since you came here and took charge of it.
You've collected many female students using the name Takarazuka as bait.
Now tell me why you've done that.
Now, it's time for you to confess the darkness in your heart.
All right.
I...
The man I fell in love with...
First Love
Mom...
Who the hell are you people?
Tell us what the Michaela Project is.
What are you trying to do?
School President!
What?! Men?!
F-Filthy pigs.
Drive them away!
Our Father, who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come.
Look at this, School President!
That mark is...
Thy will be done,
in earth as it is in heaven.
You shouldn't let yourself get into this stuff too much.
I wonder if these paintings show that
people believed in God till the last gasp,
or if they show that we'd be better off if we believed in other religions.
Probably the latter.
But I personally take is as "you should die with your dignity,"
because God is always
watching over everyone.
You would say that.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
Amen.
I have something I'd like to tell you.
I don't care!
Do you really think
you can defeat me?
Didn't you learn anything
from our fight today?
You devil!
You're a devil come here
to ruin everything.
I wonder if devils have these.
Look here.
I don't think devils would have these.
The scars of wings?
Yeah, the wings of an angel.
Unfortunately... no, fortunately, they fell off.
You said you prayed for the martyrs
who sacrificed themselves to God, right?
When I was little, I was very religious, just like those people who believed in God.
You know about the Children's Crusade, right?
Y-Yeah.
It was a Christian crusade
organized by the Pope.
Its aim was to take back the holy city of Jerusalem from the Seljuk Turks.
Although Jerusalem was captured in the first Crusade,
it later fell into the hands of the Seljuk Turks.
What about it, though?
The Children's Crusade was organized because all the crusades before it had failed.
Adults thought innocent children might succeed where they had failed.
Soon after the Papal proclamations were issued, devout boys and girls left their homes.
They were accepting a challenge where adults had failed,
or they wanted to see the holy city of Jerusalem once in their lives.
They made no allowances for their own puny abilities.
They acted based on their religious devotion alone.
Some children actually received divine prophecies,
and other believed that they were led by angels.
Anyway, they were all filled
with crusading zeal.
However, it was just a pack of lies,
created by adults.
Lies?
That's right!
We headed to Marseille first, to get to Jerusalem.
We believed that the Mediterranean would part when we got there.
But Marseille was really far.
We were mere children.
Many died after just a little while.
There was a girl named Francois.
She suffered from tuberculosis but still wanted to go to Jerusalem.
She coughed up blood and died.
And there was a boy named Marco.
He was ill with fever.
When he couldn't walk any further, he told the others to leave him.
Hey, there's the ocean!
Lord in heaven above, Marco is at the end of his physical life.
Please lead him to the gates of heaven,
and please show us the way to the Mediterranean.
Sure enough, the ocean remained calm.
It didn't part as it did for Moses.
How come nothing is happening, Hans?
Well, be patient. It will happen.
Now, let's pray hard.
Then the ocean will split in two.
Children, the ship will leave soon!
You mean, you're going to take us to Jerusalem?
See? God didn't abandon us.
Don't be silly!
Look, you guys are going to Africa.
I have a signed deed too.
All of you have been sold.
That's impossible.
Oh Lord, did you abandon us? Why?
We came all this way for you,
and this is how you treat us?
We were summoned here to become slaves in Africa?
God, I won't forget what you did to us this time,
nor my peers who threw themselves into the sea.
Not even after a thousand, or ten thousand years.
That can't be true!
God? There is no God in this world.
If there is, I will kill him.
You would kill him?
You still haven't understood?
Hermaphrodite...
I'm Hans, the leader of the Children's Crusade.
Unbelievable.
I'm Aiko, Hans, and an angel come to kill God.
No.
Oh Lord...
The word is meaningless.
I'm sorry. That's cruel.
Sister Yumiko must be up to something.
I'm going to discover her plot.
Can you help me with that, Rika?
St. Michaela
School
Drifting
Story
Part 2
O Lord, I can't forget my first love.
Please let me go back into the past, when I was seventeen,
and be together with him.
Offer the girls to me before they lose their virginity.
Y-You are...
Aiko Mimura. I'm here.
Come in.
Mimura-san!
You still don't get it, do you?
You're not allowed to dye your hair here.
Where is your cross?
Put this on.
That's our school rule.
Here's another sadist, huh?
I don't want to wear that shit.
Put this on her!
Catch her! Catch her and punish her!
Yes, ma'am.
Also, check her background right away.
Uh, okay.
Daisuke-sama... I smell someone's perfume.
Who in the world is this girl?
I couldn't find her over there.
Let's try her dorm.
Right.
You shouldn't move yet.
Why don't you request an excused absence?
I'll give it to the teacher for you.
Yeah, I also think you should do that.
If she said you needed a doctor's statement, we could ask her to come see you.
Huh? What perfect timing.
Where is Aiko Mimura?
Didn't she go to your room?
She left here a while ago.
You know what will happen if you hide her.
Excuse me, Sister.
What?
Um, Youko doesn't seem able to go to school today.
How weak of you to be like that from just a bit of punishment.
You must come to school today.
Don't dare be late, okay?
If you don't show up,
everyone in this room will suffer.
That's harsh. She hasn't even
seen a doctor yet.
Please give her a little bit
of time to recover.
I'll go.
Youko!
We have dance class today too.
I don't think you can dance in your condition.
Karino-sama.
Karino-sama, things have been crazy.
Strangers broke in last night,
and Mimura Aiko ran away today.
Well, she won't be able to escape the school campus, though.
Take a look at this.
This is...
Did you look into her background?
Yeah, I asked someone to do it.
There's no record of her enrollment at the school she supposedly transferred from.
Also, we couldn't find anything on her parents or birthplace.
We have no information about her at all.
Sister Yumiko, please prepare for the Mass.
We will hold the Mass tomorrow.
Okay.
All right, well done, team Hoshi.
If you can do this much already, chances are high that you'll get into Takarazuka.
It's all thanks to you, Sensei.
No, it's a result of your own efforts.
You followed the school rules,
stayed pure, and worked hard.
Next, team Tsuki, up on stage.
Sister, Miuchi-san isn't feeling well.
Youko...
Miuchi-san, you fail to improve because you're mentally weak.
All right, you can go back to your dorm.
With your results, you won't be able to get into Takarazuka.
Youko, are you all right?
Let's go.
Hold on.
You two must stay.
You can take care of yourself, right, Miuchi Youko?
Y-Yes.
Youko!
Now, the other members of team Tsuki, up on stage.
There will be an important announcement. Everyone, go to the gymnasium.
Everyone, go to the gymnasium.
Let me repeat.
There will be an important announcement.
Everyone, go to the gymnasium.
I would like to introduce you to someone important.
Karino Daisuke-san, a producer from Takarazuka.
Salute!
I am Karino Daisuke.
You've all done well.
I've been watching you working hard.
You can all be proud of yourselves and go to Takarazuka.
I know this is short notice,
but Mass will be held tomorrow.
That's right.
You will all enter Takarazuka after the Mass.
Your stage is ready.
You are going to dance the Imperial Waltz on stage and get to know what first love is like.
Just as you said, Hans.
But before that, a servant of evil has invaded this school.
Mimura Aiko lied about her identity and transferred to second year class 3 yesterday.
She ignores Jesus Christ and will foster the potential for evil in this school.
Sister Yumiko has joined hands with this guy and...
You will all follow Ikeda-san's instructions and catch Mimura Aiko,
then sacrifice her to God at tomorrow's Mass!
Yes, ma'am!
Ikeda-san, give them their orders.
She's made a horrible scheme with him.
Ikeda-san?!
Y-Yes!
In the name of the Girls' Crusade, we will sacrifice the betrayer.
Sacrifice the betrayer!
Mother, you used to sing in difficult times.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine, sing with hope and dreams.
That bitch did it again.
Well, all the students are looking for her, so it won't take long to catch her.
More importantly, we don't have much time before the Mass tomorrow.
Let's spend some precious time together.
Yes.
Where did she go?
Where is she? Not here.
Did you find her? No.
Over here?
Not here.
Not here, either.
Go check the school grounds.
Got it.
Go check the gymnasium.
Roger.
This is stupid.
She's going to be sacrificed to God at tomorrow's Mass.
That's not our business.
Still, I wonder who she really is.
The teacher said she was a demon...
She was an oddball,
but kind of lovable in her own way.
I'd like to let her go if I could.
Let me tell you who she really is.
Rika! Did you hear us?
Let's beat her up!
Wait. I don't intend to fight with you.
I'm hiding her.
It's true.
Now, let me introduce her.
She is Hans Heilner.
I wish I could dance with you like this forever.
Are you serious?
It's hard to believe.
So what scheme have those two come up with?
To take all of you to the other world and make you work as soldiers.
The training you received here was all directed at that.
And one more thing.
What is it?
To become women of the battlefield.
Women...
...of the battlefield?
The “stage” he was talking about is actually a battle line somewhere.
He's not a producer at Takarazuka but a real soldier.
That's the truth.
Finally, the time has come.
Your army team and my students are going to meet soon.
Yes, the soldiers will gain energy from sleeping with the girls...
and will then make significant
contributions to liberating Asia.
I really appreciate your cooperation.
It's my pleasure.
I just wanted to go back to the day I met my first—
Someone's on the roof!
Look!
Who are you? Come down!
Wait!
Sounds like they found her.
That was really quick, but I...
Say nothing.
We were just born in different times.
I... I...
I'm not going to forget about you.
Those two are just like the Pope who sold us into slavery.
But is it really possible for us to go back to the past?
Yes, it's possible.
What?
The entrance to the time tunnel is in the chapel.
Wait!
Are you okay?
This medicine is made of medical herbs from Shimabara.
It's really effective, especially for sword wound.
Wh-Who are you guys?
We're just travelers.
Why did you let yourself get cut?
Karino-sama is a bad guy.
He's cheating on my lady Yumiko
and planning to send the students here to a battlefield as comfort women.
Just as I thought.
School President, we've got trouble! School President!
What happened?
Four sisters have been killed.
What?
Huh?
Th-This is...
Sister Yumiko, we must hurry.
Please prepare for Mass right now.
Okay.
H-Hey, look...
That horrible dream again.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
I can't smell anything now.
person who sells box lunches
I don't think I can be a
anymore.
Good luck at
Takarazuka!
I can't guarantee the taste, but
I made one last dinner for you.
Well done.
That's why I chose you to be the leader of the Girls' Crusade.
You're a pain in the ass.
Who the hell are you?
A spy from the police?
Give me back the key you stole!
What are you talking about?
You won't be able to act like that for long.
At tomorrow's Mass, you're going to be sacrificed to God.
Spawn of a demon!
Daisuke-sama?
Daisuke-sama!
Can't you see me?
My eyesight gets worse every time I have that bad dream.
I saw it again today.
I'm scared!
I don't know what you're planning to do, but...
but I sense that it will kill you in the end.
I smell perfume.
I want to become one with you right now!
Yuki-san...
I sent Gonza away, so it's just two of us tonight.
Y-Yuki...
Daisuke-sama...
Which one is Karino-sama's?
Is this it?
Sister said that was Youko's fault.
She's cruel.
They beat her so bad.
There's no time to cry.
We have a lot to do before the Mass.
For Miuchi-san's sake too.
Yeah.
It's going to happen tomorrow, huh?
Good work.
No. I just did what I was supposed to do.
You came up with the Michaela Project.
If it works, this phase of the war will go better for us.
This is still a secret among us,
but it serves the national purpose.
Yes, sir!
The lily, pink in the yard, and various flowers grew on the fence.
Today is the last day I will see them.
With tears running down my face, I say so long to my hometown.
So long, my hometown, so long, my hometown...
Is everyone here?
Yes, Sensei.
Then we are going to begin the Mass of St. Michaela School.
Please be safe, Daisuke-sama.
St. Michaela School's 70-year history will end after this Mass.
However, it doesn't mean that
this school is going to disappear.
You should always remember the spirit of martyrdom and benevolence.
In the name of love and spirit, bless this Mass.
Amen.
Bring the sacrifice here.
Yes.
Bring the sacrifice.
Lord in heaven above, we are going to return the love and spirit now.
I offer you the blood of a sacrifice and all these virgins.
Now, execute this sacrifice!
Wait!
Wh-What are you doing?
You...
Ikeda-san?!
Y-You devil...
A devil, you say?
I'm Hans Heilner.
God betrayed me and sent me out as a slave on a ship.
But I threw myself into the ocean before we got to the shore.
I am an angel come from heaven after transcending time.
I-Impossible.
You...
Girls, now it's time for rebellion! Let's fight!
Yes!
Why... Why?!
You said that we don't know what first love is like.
But our first love was taken by your complex!
I-I just thought I would offer your virginity to God.
Shut up!
We're going to get the freedom to enjoy love, discos,
hamburgers, and everything else from now on!
Fight for freedom!
I-I'm sorry, Daisuke-sama, but the Michaela Project has failed.
Girls, we've put her to death!
Now we're going to have a Black Mass,
a rebellion against God!
Fight!
Watch out!
An earthquake?
An ill omen.
I hope Daisuke-sama is okay.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine, sing with hope and dreams.
Forget your grudges, hatreds, and sorrows.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine, sing for tomorrow.
Joy, beautiful spark the divinity, sing with hope and dreams.
Forget your grudges, hatreds, and sorrows.
Joy, beautiful spark of the divine, sing for tomorrow.
Aiko!
I won't let you go!
Shit!
Wait!
He won't be able to survive.
Now, let's go to the real fight.
We need all of you.
The fighting will be intense.
Now we are transcending time.
It looks like the project failed.
I'm sorry.
We're going to make a sortie by ourselves.
We just passed the era of the Great East Asia War and the Russo-Japanese War.
We're almost there.
Where are you taking us?
To Shirou-sama's world.
Shirou-sama?
We're Shirou-sama's servants.
We came here to fetch you girls.
Where are we?
We are in the Shimabara peninsula in 1637, the middle period of the Kanei era.
That's Castle Hara over there.
You mean...
the Shimabara Rebellion...
My goodness.
Shirou-sama!
We just came back
with the Girls' Crusade.
Good job.
Welcome to my world.
I'm Amakusa Shirou Tokisada.
The government is planning to kill all Christians.
Several thousand have already been imprisoned and crucified.
My troops are injured and have used up all of their energy.
So I would like you to join us in the name of God.
In the name of God?
We just killed him.
Are you guys okay with that?
I guess you did kill the God that you believed in.
But here in this world, I am God.
What?
Why don't we fight together and defeat the government?
Heaven is almost here.
No way! We came together to kill God.
What are you talking about?
I am God.
I'm going to make this world a paradise after defeating the government.
If you live and die in this paradise,
you'll be able to ascend to heaven.
Now, girls, please lend me your hands.
No!
What?
If you say you're God, then you're our enemy!
You...
Zeus-sama, please show these girls your power.
It's magic! It's magic!
It's not magic.
It's the power of God.
In this world, there are miracles you can't even imagine.
Don't be fooled!
He's just a hypocrite!
She's right.
Don't forget what the adults did to us at school.
Rika!
Hans, I love you.
Thanks to you, I got to know what first love is like before I die.
Rika...
Thank you, Hans.
All right, bring it on.
Fight!
No one is going to control us anymore!
Th-This is...
What's going on?!
Daisuke-san!
Daisuke-san... Daisuke-san just died in the war!
What are you talking about?
Who's this Daisuke-san?
There's no war anywhere.
Yumiko, I'll give you some milk.
There have been no wars since the government was defeated at the battle of Shimabara.
You're right.
I don't know what I was thinking.
The Girls' Crusade destroyed the Roman Catholic Church and the Holy Roman Empire.
The things people used to fight over, like religion or nationality, are long gone.
It's all thanks to Amakusa Shirou and Hans Aiko.
Translation
Translation Check
Timing
Editing
QC
anonymous
convexity
Eternal_Blizzard
Collectr
Calyrica, CP