Orphan & M74
present
Blue
Flames
Hey, on the way home, let's go to the arcade by the train station.
Okay, sounds good.
One, two, three!
One!
One, two!
Yoshiwa.High.School
Here it comes!
What's wrong?!
At this rate, we won't be able to protect our strong reputation!
Are you guys going to make us seniors graduate in shame?!
Kirioka, huh?
He's lucky, getting a rugby scholarship to Jounan University.
Yeah. Hey, look.
Kaizu, huh? What's he thinking?
Running around every day,
even though he's not in a club.
Plus he's creepy.
He never says anything.
He's like a block of ice.
Please accept this.
Kaizu, you sure are popular!
Not really.
Wait.
We're pretty bummed out about getting rejected from our first-choice schools.
We're borrowing you for a sec.
When you're pissed off, it's a great relief to beat the shit out of someone!
Here we go!
Wait!
Why not solve this with money?
What?
How about 50,000 yen each?
50,000?
I'll bring it tomorrow, so let me go. Please.
Yes!
Ryuu-chan, it's so good.
You're the best!
Oh, yes, yes!
Money?
Sure, if it's for you, Ryuu-chan.
But you must be the only high school student in the country
who plays around with hostesses.
I need 100,000.
You'd better not've found a girl.
It's for men.
Liar. Really? If you're lying, I'll make you pay it back.
No. Ryuu-chan, no. Oh God...
Again!
Here you go.
Thanks. If you have any problems, talk to us.
Yeah.
Later.
Hey, look. That's the second year student Naito Emi, right?
Her family is incredibly wealthy.
Yeah, her family owns a huge hospital.
They even have two Mercedes!
Hello.
Thank you for yesterday.
I'd like to show my appreciation. Are you free this Sunday?
Yes, I am.
How about we go to the ocean, then?
Sure!
Then I'll see you on Sunday.
What a nice person.
You look pretty with long hair.
But they make us tie it for school, so...
You look pretty with tied hair too.
Should we go?
Um, why do you run every day?
Exams are coming up soon.
To keep my body in shape.
Come on. I'll walk you home.
Sure.
This is fine. It's right there.
What a house.
Thank you for today.
You even walked me home.
Will you see me again?
Huh? But I'm so boring.
I've always liked you.
I've always looked only at you.
Oh...
So will you see me?
I will.
I'm so happy.
I'm home.
You're late.
I was with a friend.
Choose your friends wisely,
because your future is to marry a man who will take over the hospital.
This again?
It's not fair that brother got to become a lawyer.
Hey, hey, don't bring me into this.
What? Something wrong?
That red mark on your neck...
Oh this? It's nothing.
I bumped it, so don't worry.
I'm going to my room.
Hold on, Emi.
Ryuuichi-san...
Yoshiwa.High.School
Misao, hurry, hurry, big news!
What big news?
Look at that. Isn't that your brother?
Brother...
But it's surprising for your brother to have a girlfriend.
I thought he had no interest in girls.
What's going on, Brother?
Since when did you...
Too bad, Kirioka. Looks like Kaizu took your madonna.
Good morning, Brother.
Yeah, good morning.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What?
Brother, about your girlfriend...
Ryuuichi, what are you going to do?
We're going to Grandpa's house. Are you?
I can't go. I have to study for exams.
We thought you'd say that.
Have you decided on a college?
A top university in Tokyo.
That will cost money.
Don't worry. Plus, I'll be going to a state school in two years.
Give your mother an estimate
of the costs later.
Sure.
We're going. Misao, get ready.
Uh, okay.
Seriously, I never understand what he's thinking!
Dear.
You mean Brother?
Yeah. I don't know if it's because he's not cute or something.
He's my child, yet I don't feel like
doing anything for him.
Stop it, Father.
He's having a rough time,
studying for college entrance exams.
We should watch over him lovingly.
I know that, but...
Excuse me.
Nobody's here. It's all right.
Let's go to my room.
Um, uh, okay!
Oh, it's quite tidy!
I love you.
No, stop! We can't...
Don't! Stop it. We can't!
Wait!
Stop. We can't...
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Hold on a moment.
What's that on your neck?
I-It's nothing. Don't worry about it!
Wait, show me!
Stop, please. Let go of me!
What is this?!
What's wrong, Father?
Look at her neck!
Emi!
So you won't reveal his name?
We love each other.
Please believe me!
Don't be foolish!
I won't let some nobody we don't even know take you from us!
You're important to this family
for finding an heir to the hospital!
But it's too late.
I'm not your puppet anymore.
We've already slept together!
What?!
That's why I have kiss marks.
We love each other.
I've become a woman.
You fool!
Father, stop it.
Shut up! Let go of me!
Who is this man, and where is he?
Father, calm down. Let me handle it.
I want to discuss this with Emi alone.
Okay, I'll let you handle this.
Everything's fine now. Are you hurt?
I don't think I've done anything wrong.
I understand your feelings,
but I would like to meet this man.
I don't want to fight him.
I just want to get to know
the person you fell in love with.
Okay, I'll ask him.
Kaizu Ryuuichi-kun, right?
You're Emi-kun's brother?
Nice to meet you.
Are you the thief?
Father, calm down!
I'm sorry about my father.
He insisted on coming along
when he heard I was meeting you.
Please.
Welcome. What would you like?
Coffee.
The same.
I'll get to the point. I don't want you to go near Emi from now on.
I thought it would be something like this,
but I can't promise that.
What?!
Father!
You probably know this,
but my Father has planned for Emi's husband to take over the hospital.
You're a humanities student, right?
You have no interest in medicine?
No, I don't.
But I'm serious about Emi-kun.
Please believe that.
I understand that, but... this is difficult...
No, it isn't. We just have to keep him away from Emi.
But Father, Emi is saying
she'll leave the house if she has to.
We won't let her!
So you won't forgive us,
no matter what?
Of course not!
Okay. I understand. We'll break up.
What? Really?
But I have one condition.
What is it? Go ahead.
Give me ten million yen.
What?!
Ten million?! Are you... serious?
I love her,
but after hearing the realities of your family,
I'm forcing myself to break up with her.
I think I deserve compensation.
What kind of foolishness are you talking about?!
You weren't even married. What do you mean, "compensation"? How dare you?!
Are you sure you want to say that?
I think if I tell her to leave your family, she will.
You... What kind of a man are you?
Well, think about it.
I'm expecting a favorable reply.
Hey...
What a bastard! That's a high school student?
Emi sure fell in love with a horrible man.
What are you talking about, Father?
How stupid. You think
I'd believe a story like that?
Give it a rest.
Ryuuichi-san isn't that kind of a person!
I'm not lying. Toushirou heard it too.
It's true, Emi. Kaizu Ryuuichi really asked for ten million.
I've lost my respect for you both.
Even you, brother. You said you were going alone,
but you must've planned this story with Father from the beginning!
That's not true. Please believe us.
Stop! I don't want to hear it anymore!
I can't believe you two!
Emi!
Damn it, this is just as he planned.
Stop it, Father. Solving this with money will only hurt Emi more.
I know. Don't worry.
Here's five million. Now break up with her.
Are you confused? I said ten million.
The rest will be paid after you break up.
All right. I'll trust you.
But you understand what will happen if you betray me.
Just hurry up and break up with her.
That's all you need to do!
I understand. Bye.
I can't take it.
My father then says you asked for
ten million yen to break up with me.
Can you believe that?
Sorry for telling you this,
but I believe in you, so don't worry.
It must be tough...
for your family to worry about you this much.
But...
We're just from different worlds.
You should marry a doctor, for your own sake, as well as your family's.
No! Don't say things like that!
Let's break up.
If it's inevitable, then let's do it now, before the pain gets deeper.
No! I don't want that!
I love you, Ryuuichi-san.
I love you so much!
And...
Frankly, I've grown tired of you
and your body too.
No.
So let's end it.
No!
No...
I'm home.
Father!
Come quickly. Emi's condition is strange!
What?!
Emi. Emi!
Dear!
Honey, I found this under her bed!
Sleeping pills! Toushirou, call an ambulance right away!
Father, you didn't pay him?!
Shut up. Hurry!
Emi, don't die!
Emi!
What? Naito Emi tried
to commit suicide?
Yeah, but she survived. It was because Kaizu dumped her, apparently.
How horrible.
Yeah, I can't believe it.
Look, there's Kaizu!
I can't believe he came to school.
Does he have no feelings?
Yeah.
Really.
Kaizu, come with me for a minute.
Emi tried to kill herself?
I see. So that's why everyone
was looking at me strangely.
Is that it? Don't you feel
the least bit sorry?!
Not really. What do I care about people I'm no longer with?
You bastard!
Why the hell are you getting mad?
Oh, I see. You liked Naito Emi.
Get up. I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Then maybe I should tell you
about her body in return?
Shut up, you bastard!
Her skin is pearly white,
and her breasts are huge.
Stop it! I don't want to hear about that!
Those are the punches of
the best athlete in the district?
What a mouth you have!
Say just one more thing
and I'll rip you apart!
Watch your back!
What's going on, Ryuuichi?
You're incredible today!
Hey, put some medicine on it.
It's fine.
No, it'll get infected.
I said it's fine.
What's going on?
It's fine. It's fine like this.
Principal's.Office
Excuse me.
Kaizu!
Kaizu-kun here says you assaulted him.
Effort
Is it true?
Well, Kirioka? You aren't the type to do something like this, right?
Effort
I'm sorry. It's true.
Kirioka!
I see. That's most unfortunate.
Unless there's a good reason, I have no choice. Kirioka-kun,
your scholarship to Jounan University will be revoked.
Huh? N-No way!
Of course, we can't have violent students receiving scholarships.
Kirioka, tell him!
There must've been a reason to cause you to...
Effort
That is...
Yes?
Forgive me. I can't reveal it.
You may leave, Kaizu-kun.
Excuse me.
Hey, did you see Kaizu?!
Where'd he go?!
Hey, Kirioka's gonna kill Kaizu.
Should we save him
and get more money?
Idiot, we can't beat Kirioka.
Then let's go watch.
Yeah, let's go.
Kaizu!
You lost your love,
and now you've lost your scholarship.
How pathetic can you get, Kirioka?
I'm not afraid of anything now.
I'm gonna beat the shit out of you, you bastard!
It's useless. I've been able to see your punches from the start.
Then you... yesterday...
This time I'll attack.
Now, get up. I'll teach you a lesson.
You bastard!
What're you lookin' at?!
Uh... um...
You're strong. If you're so strong why did you, against us...
I only solve things
with money the first time.
And I don't like wasting my time.
Brother!
Ryuuichi!
Mother, I wrote it in the letter,
but I got into my college,
and I'm skipping the graduation ceremony to go to Tokyo with her.
What are you talking about?!
We haven't paid your school expenses yet!
How rude. Will you please shut up?
What?!
I'm cutting off my relationship with you.
Ryuuichi...
Brother...
Of course, I'll pay for everything myself.
I don't need anything from you.
You'd better not come back crying!
Why would I cry? I'm happy to cut myself off from you.
Do as you wish!
Brother! Brother.
Forget about me. Tell Mom that too.
Brother...
Ryuuichi...
You're free, Ryuuichi.
Parents don't matter.
I'm taking on Tokyo. I don't intend
to return to this small town, ever.
I'm going to become a first-rate hostess in Ginza.
Let's do our best, Ryuuichi.
Yeah.
Keio University
Hey, you join anything?
I was thinking about
joining the tennis circle.
Tennis Circle
I heard they have connections to all-girl colleges
and that the daughter of the head of Sumibishi Bank joined there.
Ryuuichi!
Sayuko.
I'm sorry. I know I'm not supposed to come,
but just for today, forgive me.
I want to show everyone that
my boyfriend goes to school here
and that he's this wonderfully gorgeous!
All right.
Really? That's why I love you!
What about Ginza?
I'm off today. Hey, let's go somewhere.
Roppongi, Asobu, or Daikaiyama?
Hey, that's the Sumibishi daughter.
She's cute, but it's no good.
She's outta our league.
Really?
But the older students are all over her.
And look, the older students have their eyes
on all the other girls too.
Yeah, and do you know what guys call girls from each year?
First years are snacks,
second years are prime meat,
third years are old ladies,
and fourth years are just rotten.
So I'm an old lady, Kuroeda Kieko, third year. Nice to meet you.
No, we would never call you an old lady, not at all.
Oh, it's the captain!
He's impressive.
I heard he was good and works fast,
but it looks like the captain's picked the Sumibishi daughter.
Come on.
Do you always sleep around with men like this?
This is the first time,
because you were so sexy.
Could it be to make someone jealous?
Don't be stupid!
You ruined my mood. I'm leaving.
Wow!
You're pretty when you're angry.
It doesn't feel this good with the captain!
Incredible. So this is real sex.
Kuroeda was?
Yeah, she was with a first-year named Kaizu.
Isn't she your girlfriend? We can't let
an underclassman do as he pleases.
Hey, speak of the devil.
Kuroeda-kun?
Oh, Captain, let me introduce you.
This is first year student, Kaizu-kun.
I know.
Come over here.
Keiko, what are you doing?
With a first year?
You were doing the same thing with the Sumibishi girl.
I see. You're jealous.
Not really. Don't be so arrogant.
What?
Well, Kuroeda-san, I'll be over there.
Hold on. I hear you're really good at tennis.
No, I've never played before.
Don't lie.
It's true.
Then let me test you.
Don't bully him like that!
There's no way he could compete with you in tennis!
You stay back. Come on.
Look, the captain is gonna play a newcomer!
Really! Why? Must be a really good new student!
The captain is the best player in this circle, right?
Sounds like fun.
Um, where should I stand on the court?
Don't act stupid. Here I go!
Good luck, Kaizu-kun.
All right, I'll crush and embarrass him.
What's this? He really can't play.
In that case...
Oh, this isn't a good match at all. How boring.
That's enough, Captain. Stop!
The poor guy.
Not what I was expecting.
Let's go, Keiko.
Poor guy, huh?
Sayuko, can I have 30,000 yen?
What for?
To hire a tennis pro for some intensive training.
Um, I'm Kaizu. I called you.
I'm a tough teacher.
That's fine. Thank you.
You've improved greatly.
Why don't we rest?
Thank you very much!
Locker
Room
So how's practice going?
I'm Sayuki, a second year from Keizai University. Nice to meet you.
I see, so you don't like shaking hands? No matter.
I have the perfect part-time job for you.
Would you like to try it?
A job?
Yeah, as a Black Suit in Roppongi.
A Black Suit...
They call the guys who work in the disco clubs Black Suits.
They're a big part of the scene.
The crazy girls want to sleep
with all of them,
and most places succeed or fail
based on the skills of their Black Suits.
But I can't do a job like that.
It's fun, and a good study of society.
And you'll never run out of girls.
Don't you feel that something is lacking in your school life?
You too?
The same type of people recognize it,
with intuition or whatever.
Sounds like fun. Let me give it a try.
You're new, huh? Very cool.
How about hanging out after work?
As I expected, Tokyo's great!
Everything's so exciting.
This is the city for me.
I'll get to the top here.
Ryuu-chan, what's been going on lately?!
You rarely come home anymore.
What are you doing?!
Things are tough for first-years.
I have tennis practice,
and a friend got me a part-time job.
Liar! You have a girl, don't you? Say it!
Stop it. Let go!
I can't take it.
I'll kill you!
I said stop it!
Ryuu-chan...
That's enough. Stop complaining about my life.
Otherwise, I'm leaving this house!
What did you say? Just try it.
If you do, I'll seriously kill you!
We're finished.
Wait!
I'm not your slave!
Yeah? You are my slave.
What?
Bye.
Fine. I'll really kill you!
Don't be stupid!
I'm serious! I'll kill you, then myself!
Stop!
No, stop! No! Stop it!
Don't stop, Ryuuichi!
I'll do whatever you want!
So don't throw me away, please!
What? He came on the trip?
I thought he'd quit the circle after losing to the captain.
Oh, it's awesome!
What kind of car is this?
Mercedes-Benz 190SL.
From about 30 years ago.
Oh, it's you. How boring.
You don't want to ride in a loser's car?
Bingo!
I wouldn't want to ride around
with such a boring, spoiled girl either.
How dare he...
Don't worry about what he says.
He's totally lame!
Hey, hey, looks like Kaizu's gonna play the captain again!
He requested a game!
Huh? What an idiot.
He'll just get crushed again!
Sounds like fun. I'm going to go watch.
You got a little better, huh?
I got a coach and practiced.
I don't see how you could improve much in a month or so.
Oh well, I'll test you. Here it comes!
Kaizu-kun.
That was just luck. Here I go!
Whoa, Kaizu's incredible!
The captain is pathetic.
He couldn't return anything.
Seems like the match is over.
Thank you very much.
Kaizu-kun.
You remember calling me a loser?
Yes, I do. Of course.
I know I'm just a boring, spoiled girl,
but can I ride in your car?
My pleasure.
Wait, Ryuuichi.
Aren't you forgetting about me?
Not really.
He's just not interested in old ladies.
What?!
I'm just joking. I can't believe you took it seriously!
What is it, Ryuuichi?
I want to hear your feelings.
You're embarrassing yourself, senpai.
Please don't look at me like that.
But it's true. I've lost interest in you.
Let's go, Ryuuichi-kun.
Yeah.
What should we do, Captain?
How can we allow this?
Snap out of it, Captain!
Yeah, I know.
Wait, Kaizu!
Apologize for what you said to Kuroeda!
Why? Isn't it a private matter?
I see. But I'm going to be frank.
You've disrupted this circle, and we want you to quit.
We all discussed it.
What's so funny?!
You guys sure are pleasant.
If you hate me so much, why don't you try to kick me out physically?
You discussed it? You make me laugh.
We aren't animals. We deplore violence!
I guess that's the limit of people who entertain themselves in a tennis circle.
What?!
I'm sick of guys like you,
satisfied just to get into an elite school
and then to get a good job at a major company.
I've had enough of you losers.
I'll quit this stupid circle on my own!
How dare you?!
What's wrong? Come at me.
You're older, right?
You're gonna let a first year get away with that, huh?
There's not a single guy with any guts among you?
Dammit.
I feel bad for the girls
who come here looking for boyfriends.
What are you going to do, Sumibishi Hisayo-kun?
I'm coming. I'm sick of this trip too. Let's go, okay?
Hisayo-kun, not you too.
Later. This is goodbye,
future first-rate salarymen!
You're gonna let him
get away with that?
You're a man, aren't you?
Do something.
That bastard.
I feel much better now!
You sure are amazing, Kaizu-kun.
Not as much as you.
Yeah, I'm a pain!
But now I'm away from my parents for a few days, so I can do anything I want.
Take me somewhere!
Okay!
I bought you the car you want, so don't throw me away.
Don't let anyone else sit in this seat.
I'll be your slave or do whatever it takes!
Okay, I promise.
Look, isn't that the captain?
Hey, what are you going to do?
I won't lose to a guy like that.
Yay! What an idiot!
D-Dammit!
I'm a bother, but...
You're a bother, but?
But please don't think that
I'd do this with just anyone.
I know. You're the only one for me too.
Within my heart, blue flames burn.
I'm not satisfied yet.
As long as these flames burn, I...
Original Subtitles
Transcription & Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Raw Provider
Random Masters
M74
Collectr
bananadoyouwanna, M74
M74
gamnark