No! Absolutely not!
She has returned to her home town.
I will not let you follow her.
If you go, it will be without my blessing.
Kanako-san probably went back to her clan in Kyoto.
To protect me from her clan,
she's sacrificing her happiness.
I can't allow Kanako-san to sacrifice her love so that I might live.
Such a man would be unfit to lead the Natsume clan!
Kanako-san.
I swear I'll save you.
By the power of the Natsume clan!
There is a family whose leader is said
to inherit the Ear of the Golden Dragon,
the Natsume clan.
This power lets him bring about any fate he desires.
It allows him to make any woman submit to his will.
He is Natsume Kiroemon the 45th!
Translation
Moho Kareshi
Translation Check, Songs
Iri
Timing
ninjacloud
yami ni oritatsu ougon no me yo
His golden eyes descend into the darkness
yobisamasu kokoro saranaru toki
His heart awakens, time quickens
miyo tanabiki kaze ni mau kami
See his hair sway and dance in the wind
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
ten wo kakenuke kiseki wo yobe
Soar through the heavens, calling forth miracles
mabayuku kagayake
Shine brilliantly
QC
Calyrica, konnakude
shukumei no mono wa
The fated ones
shijou no chikara ni seinaru shukuhai
Drink from the supreme power in a holy toast
Encoding
Piyo Piyo Productions
omae ga yuku no ka
Will you go?
Oh, like a dragon!
yatsu he mukau no ka
Will you go to him?
King of kings
shifuku wo eru no ka
Will you find happiness?
Oh, like a dragon!
mirai hiraku no ka
Will the future open to you?
King of kings
Take away my gold ring
Set me free
I'm gonna win the game
Orphan Fansubs presents
Ear of the
Golden Dragon
Mina's Story
(Part 2)
Kiroemon-sama.
Pardon? Natsume Kiroemon?
Yes, ma'am. He recently left Tokyo.
He is most likely headed here, to Kyoto.
What a fool.
To think he would actually come to us.
Have no fear.
We will see just how powerful the new head of the Natsume clan truly is.
Kotoko.
Begin preparations at once.
How strange.
Okochi-sama told me the manager of Kanoya would meet us here.
I'll give her a call.
You are Natsume Kiroemon-sama, the 45th head of the Natsume clan, correct?
Who might you be?
My apologies for arriving late.
I run a place called Kanoya in Gion.
You're the one meeting us?
Shall we be on our way?
Yes, but Miss Gordon is-
I just met her.
Okochi-sama explained everything to me.
When we informed her of what we've discovered so far,
she immediately-
Miss Gordon!
She said you should have some tea and relax at my tea house.
She will be driving around for
a while to learn the streets here.
Kiro-sama!
Taxi!
So this is what the tea houses of Gion are like.
Do you know where Kanako-san is?
Did you find anything out?
Kiroemon-sama.
Yes?
I'm a woman.
Why don't you drink some tea instead
of rambling on about another woman?
I-I'm terribly sorry.
I-I was just wondering
where Miss Gordon went.
Something's not right.
We're going in circles.
It's a tea house called Kanoya.
Of course. That's where we're headed.
The staff are very busy.
What?!
How do you like the taste of the Mina women?
Do you feel loved?
Do you feel isolated?
You will become our slave, Natsume Kiroemon.
This is the Ear of the Golden Dragon, said to bring calamity upon our clan.
Playtime is over.
Who are you?
Why are you wasting your life on pointless hatred?
How amusing.
I will show you all of my techniques.
The head of the Natsume
clan is still a whelp.
You don't know how to use your power's full potential.
Even so, I can do this.
That's nothing more than a goodnight kiss.
Wh-What is he...
You must never underestimate the power of head of the Natsume clan.
Kiro-sama.
Sky
Ocean
Mountain
Wh-Who are you?!
It's no wonder the head
of our clan fears you.
Most impressive,
Natsume Kiroemon the 45th!
Miss Gordon!
Brother!
Useless fools!
I'll send you all to hell!
Miss Gordon!
If you want Kanako back,
come to Kiyomizu Temple.
Wh-What?
Miyabi! I didn't need your help!
I'm not like other women.
Miss Gordon!
Kiro-sama.
I swear I'll save you.
I'll... I'll use my luck for you.
Kiro-sama!
I'm so happy to see you again!
You can't fool me that easily.
Well done,
Natsume Kiroemon.
I won't let you use Kanako.
If she knew she was being used as bait for me,
she would take her own life!
That's who she is!
You made her fall that deeply in love with you.
Is that what you trying to say, brat?
What's the matter?
Why don't you use your power?
I'd love to see the power
of the head of the Natsume clan.
You don't know how terrifying this power can be.
I can feel Kanako's pain,
and it infuriates me.
Anger courses through my every vein.
If I remove the seal now, anything could happen.
Even I can't be sure.
Your naivete and overconfidence will be your undoing!
Do you really think you can defeat me
without using your power?!
Kanako-san.
I'm impressed. You can still stand after taking all that poison.
Had you finished me off immediately, you might've had a chance.
No one can defeat me if I release the seal.
The one I want to defeat
is the man with a power that terrifies even the Mina clan.
Bring it on!
Wh-What?
The wind...
If you continue to attack me,
you could die.
Silence!
You have yet to see my true strength!
I am Miyabi, the one destined to live in darkness!
Behold, the true form of Miyabi of the Mina clan!
Do I disgust you?
My own parents abandoned me because of this.
But it grants me strength without peer.
A Mina assassination
squad adopted me.
With this body, I could
not live in the light.
But that ends today.
Once I kill you, I will be a high-ranking officer in the Mina clan,
and I will be able to live in the light.
She's no ordinary fighter.
There's a great sorrow in her eyes.
You're a worthy opponent.
Please, stop.
You shouldn't die here!
I can tell!
Begging for your life?!
Stop!
Oh, no!
Why did you save me?
I didn't come here to hurt anyone.
I'm here to rescue the woman I love.
You've wasted your time,
Natsume Kiroemon.
Kanako-san!
If you value her life,
reseal your power.
Fine.
I'll do as you ask.
Wait.
Do you really think you've won?
We're not done yet!
Silence!
Miyabi. You forget your place.
He was meant to be my prey.
I have no further need for you!
Begone!
B-But, Noriko-sama...
Are you defying me?
You ugly beast of darkness!
Learn your place!
Do anything you want to me.
Just let her go.
Th-This is insane.
He could control Japan with his power,
but he sealed it for one woman.
Fine. You can have her!
Kanako-san!
Damn you, monster!
Stop!
Why?
I'm just repaying a debt.
You're truly a strong man, willing
to die to protect the one you love.
It will be most amusing
to see how you live.
Miyabi!
Get out of my way!
Move it!
Natsume Kiroemon!
Remove the seal!
Show her your true power!
I've never wanted to kill anyone before.
You won't get another chance.
This will be your grave!
You hurt and kill others
to satisfy your own greed.
Even a god couldn't change your wicked heart.
Silence!
There's only one path left for you.
Death.
I can read your movements.
Behold, a defenseless woman!
You cannot kill me!
The power of the Mina clan will not work on me.
A Mina woman can do more with her body than just bewitch men.
My body... is my weapon!
If I can destroy your ear,
you'll never use your power again.
D-Did Miyabi's moths poison his blood?
How unsightly.
What?
You called your subordinate "ugly."
But in reality, you are far uglier than her.
What was so ugly about her?
D-Damn you!
How dare you call me,
a woman of the Mina clan, ugly?!
Why aren't you running?
You know what I'm going
to do, don't you?
You said you could read my movements!
I can see your future.
What?
Kanako-san!
Kiro-sama.
You... You don't have to go back to them.
I know.
yoru ga owaru mae ni
At least hold me tightly
semete tsuyoku dakishimete
Before the night ends
ima wa nukumori wo zutto kanjiteitai no
Right now, I want to feel your warmth forever
hoho ni kisu shite
Plant a kiss on my cheek
soshite wakare wa
And let our parting come
sou madoromi no naka de
While I'm still dozing
Flying every night yume no naka de
Flying every night in my dreams
watashi wa tori no you ni
I am like a bird
anata no moto e yuku wa
I will go to your side
tsubasa hirogete aa
Spreading my wings
Flying every night tonde yuku wa
Flying every night I will fly
kono sora wo doko made mo
All over this sky
ikutsuka no toki ga sugi
And much time will pass
futatabi anata to meguriaeru
Until I can meet you once more
sono toki made
Until that time
I dream of you