Wataru?
Wataru.
Wake up, Wataru.
Gee, I suppose there's no other way.
It seems that I won't get slapped this morning.
Idiot.
No, Wataru. We'll be late.
Liar. You woke me up quite early.
No, that tickles.
What? Is Wataru half asleep?
I was thinking of telling him about my date with Shimamoto-san.
But I wonder what I should do after this.
Wataru.
Tell me!
Wataru!
Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Climax
File
Thanks!
Wataru, here.
My room key?
When I stayed here last time...
You took it, right?
So that's how...
Are you mad?
I'm not mad, but...
Keep it.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
But tell me one thing.
What are you four plotting?
We made a promise.
On the last day of summer vacation,
the other three came to see me when I was ill.
They told me about you.
They told you about what we'd done?
Yeah.
I felt like I was falling behind. It was a shock.
No... That's...
But after talking with them, I understood.
Everyone really loves you.
So we decided to stay as we are,
until we graduate.
As we are?
Good morning!
Yo.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
I'm embarrassed that everyone seems to know about yesterday.
Is that how girls feel?
Honestly. You're so insensitive.
That's why I'm alive to this day.
You're right!
Of course.
Sign: Sakimake Academy Cultural Festival
Hey, here they come.
Apparently it went well.
I'm glad.
Yeah.
But I envy her.
Waking up together.
Kurumi, you're plain out of it!
Haunted  House
Café
Chea p Sweets
Fortunes   Told
Y        o             y         o
Hey!
Haunted  House
Fortunes   Told
Misa, look at that.
Haunted  House
Chea p Sweets
Good morning!
Candied plums
Yummy!
He has no delicacy.
I'm going on ahead.
Candied Plums
A-All right.
Oden
Wataru.
Udon
Oden
Kazuya!
Why do you look so miserable?
Was your date yesterday with Shimamoto a failure?
It's not like that.
The date went well.
But what happens now?
Candied Plums
Shimamoto went on a date with you.
That means she's not totally mad at you.
I think you have hope.
A-Are you sure?
Shimamoto is a serious girl.
You'd better not go at this indirectly.
I think you should attack without hesitation.
"Attack without hesitation."
What do you mean by that?
I mean like kissing her directly.
Taiyaki
Kiss her?!
Soba
Taiyaki
What if she's reluctant?
Candied Plums
That's...
What if she hates me?
Candied Plums
I'm saying you shouldn't be intimidated when she says, "No, stop it."
If you stop there, most girls would be disappointed.
I get it!
I feel confident now.
All right. I'm going to do this!
Wataru. Without hesitation, right?
Yakisoba
PC Games
I may have pushed him too far.
Brown banner: Sweets, Märchen Box
Thank you! I didn't get enough sleep.
That's why I made it stronger.
Did you make this?
Cashier
Yes. Why?
Well, it tastes good.
Thank you. I'm happy even if you're just trying to please me.
Satomi-san, do you think a surprise visit like yesterday's is all right?
That was special.
Misa has been distressed for a long time,
because you stopped seeing her.
And I took up with other girls?
That's right.
We said that Wataru is just an easygoing pervert.
Hey, what's that?
Do you deny it?
I can't.
Well, we have to prepare for the opening.
All right.
To start, you keep talking about profitability.
What's that?
I don't know.
Snacks
All you talk about is money.
Tell me, is it really that important? Well?
Of course. This café is run by every member of our class.
We have to make a profit.
But if we serve coffee this weak, what will our customers think?
That doesn't mean it has to be strong.
To start, caffeine is a stimulant and has a diuretic effect.
It's also said to reduce calcium levels.
Snacks
If we're concerned about our customers' health,
we should make the coffee weaker!
Can't you do something about this, Wataru?
Me? Why?
All right, all right. I will.
What's wrong with you two so early in the morning?
Wataru, listen, Kenji is...
What are you saying?
I'm concerned about the management of this café. That's why...
Juice
Got it. So the problem is the strength of the coffee?
Shimamoto. Could you bring that here?
Sure.
This tastes good!
That was ridiculous.
Now let's do our best today.
Kazuya...
Hey, will you guys do me a favor?
It's about Kazuya.
He's interested in Shimamoto.
Kazuya-san is?
So I'd like you guys to find out how Shimamoto feels.
It's none of our business...
but I think I'll give it a try.
Yeah.
Okonomiyaki
Fortune
Telling
Fortune Telling
Shimamoto-san, I'm going to ask you directly.
Do you like Kazuya-san?
I-I'm...
Haunted House
Sakimake
Festival
Come on, say it out loud.
It's...
no use falling in love with anyone.
I'm not cute like all of you.
What are you talking about?
You just don't understand your appeal.
rtune Telling
That's right.
That's...
All right! Let's all help Shimamoto-san to change.
Change?
Change, change.
Sign: Band Heaven 2nd Floor
Change, change, change...
If my intuition is right, Kazuya-kun thinks you have hopes too.
Now, now. Stop wandering around here.
If you have time to spare, go help others.
Horoscopes
Accessories
Junk, Scr   aps
Okonomiyaki
Takoyaki
I suppose I also have hopes,
Yakitori
Sign: Tin Toys
but she's dating Kazuya.
Maybe I shouldn't have pushed him so hard.
Accessories
Okonomiyaki
Horoscopes
Banner: Yakisoba
Idol
Shop
Chocolate       Scoops
Hey, are you from Yasohachi Academy?
Yes, and?
I thought so! I recognized your uniform.
Are you waiting for your boyfriend?
Red banner: Yummy Taiyaki
H-He's not my boyfriend.
I'm Morooka Wataru. I'm a senior here.
I-I'm Narusawa Yui.
Yui-chan? That's a nice name.
It's Wataru-san.
Huh? I see.
Are you a freshman?
Y-Yes.
Should I show you around?
Onii-chan.
He's here, so...
See you.
Taiyaki
Orange sign: Fancy Goods
Wataru-san, that was a shame.
Yeah. She's cute.
No. She's no match for you guys.
See you later.
Well, really...
Seriously. That's his problem.
That was close.
I won't be able to do anything inside school from now on.
What?
That's Kazuya and Shimamoto.
Sh-Shimamoto-san.
Do I look strange?
No. You look beautiful.
You say that to all the girls, don't you?
N-No!
B-But...
So I do look strange.
I-I didn't mean it like that.
You look beautiful,
b-but I like it when you wear you hair down.
Th-That way you look like the perfect high school girl.
Are you always funny like that?
Don't say that.
It makes me feel insecure.
Why?
Crepes
Girls say I'm funny or fun to be around, but that's it.
Maybe I lack something.
That's not true.
I think you're a nice person.
"A nice person."
That means "a person I don't care much about," right?
I didn't mean it like that.
I-I'm sorry. It's not about you. It's just...
It's just?
I was hoping I could be like Wataru.
Like Morooka-kun?
Yeah.
He seems irresponsible, fickle, and perverted,
but he's different than that.
I think I know what you mean.
But I'm...
scared of him.
Of Wataru?
Yeah.
I feel like I might be attracted to him.
I found that out yesterday.
But... you're different.
You're okay with being normal.
No. I want you to be normal.
Sh-Shimamoto-san.
I...
I have to go back.
Huh?
I'm concerned about how our café is doing.
Y-You're right.
Main
Bldg
Brown banner: Sweets, Märchen Box
Thank you for coming!
Green banner: Cookies! Cakes!
Finally we can close.
A café isn't easy to run.
Snacks
Juice
Satomi, you're going to take over the master's café, right?
I think you'll have a tough time.
I know the routine, so I'll be fine.
I'll go report today's sales to headquarters.
Thank you.
Snacks
Juice
I'm exhausted.
You're such a mess, Morooka Wataru.
My job isn't like yours.
Kazuya, let's go have dinner.
Juice
I-I'm sorry. I have stuff to do.
See you later.
Snacks
Juice
What's wrong with Kazuya-kun?
I don't know. He seems to be busy.
No way.
Yeah, you're right.
Really?
That's what I heard.
Great, Kazuya-san!
Do you know what's "great"?
No, I don't.
Please explain to Kurumi somewhere else.
Hey, please tell me.
Please tell me over there.
Soft Ice Cream
Baked Yams
Sh-Shimamoto-san.
Wh-What's wrong?
I hate cultural festivals.
Ever since junior high, I've always been alone during cultural festivals.
Or else I'd spend time with my girlfriends.
So it will be a good memory if a boy...
takes me around the booths in this...
my last high school cultural festival.
U-Um, Shimamoto-san.
S-So, um, if you don't mind...
Candied Plums
Shimamoto is a serious girl.
You'd better not go at this indirectly.
I think you should attack without hesitation.
No!
Kyouko-san, I love you!
I love you!
That was so sudden.
So you changed it back.
I like it better this way.
I want to ask you something.
I hope we can stay friends from now on.
Shimamoto-san...
Can't we?
No!
Friends...
I don't want to be just friends.
Sakagami
It's really a mess!
C-Could you wait while I clean up?
I'm fine.
Even if it is a mess.
I-I...
Shimamoto-san.
No.
Don't call me Shimamoto-san.
K-Kyouko-san...
Kyouko.
Kazuya-san.
Could you please turn off the lights?
You're beautiful.
Liar!
It's true.
I'm not lying.
Kazuya-san.
Kyouko.
Kazuya-san!
No, stop.
I'm embarrassed.
Kyouko...
I love you.
Here I go...
Kyouko.
K-Kyouko...
I-I'm scared!
It hurts.
That's not it.
I-I'm sorry.
Please be more gentle.
This is my first time.
I'm scared.
Yeah, I understand.
There...
Kazuya-san.
I'm coming in!
Kazuya-san, I love you.
I love you, Kyouko.
K-Kyouko-san, I-I love you!
Kazuya-san, I love you!
I feel like I wasted my opportunity...
because I gave advice to Kazuya.
What did you advise him?
Satomi, what's up?
You slipped out during the bonfire.
I was a bit worried.
Wataru, were you interested in Kyouko?
Wh-What's this all of a sudden?
Wataru, you were concerned about someone Kyouko was interested in.
I-I have nothing to do with them.
Really?
Does that feel good?
I wonder who that is.
Leave it.
Wataru, listen.
I... I... did it!
After persevering for 18 years,
I've finally met a wonderful girl.
Do you understand?
I'm totally happy. And she's so cute.
Oh, yes. You know who it is, don't you?
If you don't know, I don't mind telling you who it is.
Don't be surprised.
No, I won't tell you.
You'll learn eventually. See you.
That Kazuya.
Good for him.
Yeah.
Too bad for you.
Wataru.
Good evening.
Sorry to intrude.
Satomi?
I'm sorry.
I forgot everyone was coming.
Satomi!
You stole a march on us.
That's unfair!
Y-You guys!
Translation
anonymous
Wake up to your love
sotto kaze ga fuite kitayo
A gentle wind is blowing
Timing
archdeco
kimi ha boku no ude no naka de
You are in my arms
Editing
Collectr
QC
CP, Saji
yuutsu na kumo wo nuke
As we go through gloomy clouds,
haruka na sora ni
it feels warm
tsutsumareta nukumori oboete ite
to be surrounded by the distant sky
muneutsu shizukesa ga futari no ai wo
The touching silence will color
toki wo wasureru gurai somete yuku
the couples in love who defy time
sunao ni nareba tayasui kedo
It'd be easy if I could be honest,
kotoba dake jya tarinai
but words are not enough
Wake up to your love
itsumo katari kirenai hodo
I feel full of love from your
ai ga kimi ni afure dashite
overflowing words
Wake up to your wave
kitto hito ha dare mo tabibito
Everyone must be a traveler
kimi mo ashita wo sagasu hazu
You too can search for your future
Wake up to your love
itsumo katari kirenai hodo
I feel full of love from your
ai ga kimi ni afure dashite
overflowing words
Wake up to your wave
kitto hito ha dare mo tabibito
Everyone must be a traveler
kimi mo ashita wo sagasu hazu
You too can search for your future
You too may search for your future