Wataru-san, are you still asleep?
Wataru-san?
Kurumi?
Why are you here?
I see. This is a dream.
You should wake up.
This is a nice dream.
Wataru-san!
No!
Ouch!
Hey, didn't I tell you?
Is that all you think about?
S-Satomi!
So you really are like that.
Bad boy.
Wh-Why are all of you in my room?!
You promised us yesterday.
Huh?
The cultural festival.
You said we'd go ask the master
about borrowing things we need for the class café.
Sakagami-kun is also waiting for you downstairs.
I see. I forgot!
Orphan Fansubs
Presents
Classmates
Climax
File
I wonder if we'll be able to make good coffee.
It'll be all right. I'll visit you guys afterwards and coach you.
Never mind, Master.
First of all, you have to take care of your own café.
I-It doesn't matter. I'll take a day off.
Or... do the two of you hate me?
We understand! Please help us!
You can count on me.
I wonder if we'll have a lot of customers.
I hope so.
At times like this, school seems very far away.
Sign: Steaming hot Chinese buns
Sure does.
Wataru-san.
Here. Say "Ah."
Ah...
This is lemon flavor.
Here, you too, Kazuya-san.
Thank you.
How long are you going to take?
We'll be late.
I know!
See you later.
This is peppermint flavor.
Don't be disappointed, Kazuya.
I'm sure you'll eventually find a new girl.
I'll support you when that happens.
Stop kidding around!
If you get involved,
it'll turn out badly!
Don't do anything stupid next time!
Got it!
Hey, what are you guys in front doing?
We're not moving.
It's heavy!
Takoyaki
Accessories Shop
Sign: Sakimake Academy Cultural Festival
Whoever took the electric foot-warmer from the principal's office,
bring it to the Faculty Room immediately.
And whoever put ice lollipops in the chemistry lab freezer,
remove them right now.
Hi, everyone.
Good morning.
Good morning, Miho.
Done.
Morning.
Good morning.
You're late, Morooka Wataru.
Kenji!
Stop calling me by my full name, as though you're the boss!
Do you have a problem with that?
I do.
Again?
Their hobby seems to be fighting.
You two.
Chairperson!
The real four-eyes!
I'm not "four-eyes."
I have a proper name, Shimamoto Kyouko.
First of all, what's wrong with the two of you?
We're busy right now.
And what's up with this furniture?
It doesn't match our café.
Gee!
Um, well, Kenji brought it.
I got it from a company affiliated with my parents' group.
This is nothing for the Aihara group's power.
By the way, Morooka Wataru.
Because you said we should do a café run by cute girls, I asked my father.
Cute girls?
Café?!
What do you think girls are?
C-Calm down, Chairperson.
If you say that,
there's a guy who's even worse than us.
This is bad.
Kazuya!
Yes?!
Hey, Kazuya.
You went further and said the girls should wear bunny costumes.
I want to wear a bunny costume.
Or maybe not.
You guys!
Yes?!
I didn't hear anything about it.
And... And...
A cute girl café...
I... I...
Everyone is making fun of me.
Hey!
Hey, you guys!
Huh?
Hurry up and go apologize to Kyouko.
Morooka Wataru.
I will give this honorable duty to you.
St-Stop joking!
I have difficulties with that kind of girl!
Kazuya, why don't you go?
What?
M-Me?
Of course.
Yeah.
You got carried away, and your idea made matters worse.
Why?
All three of you should go!
Why are guys like that?
Banner: 2-4 Bazaar
Spend
some
elegant
time
Aomori Apples
Spend
some
elegant
time
Aomori Apples
Spend
some
elegant
time
Aomori Apples
Spend
some
elegant
time
Aomori Apples
Poster: Flea Market
I can't do this. This is stupid.
I couldn't find her.
Really?
I wonder where she went.
Maybe she's back in the classroom.
The only place we didn't search is...
...the roof.
I wonder where Ms. Four-Eyes went.
Sp      ace Ima ges
Crepes
Pancakes
Stop it!
O-Ouch.
Shimamoto-san!
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Are you Sakagami-kun?
Well... um...
I...
I'm sorry.
The cute girl café was Wataru's idea,
but I also went a bit overboard.
I didn't think you'd try to kill yourself.
I'm sorry.
Kill myself?
I was just cooling off.
Huh?
Really.
Um, hey, my glasses?
Oh, yeah.
They don't seem to be broken.
Thank you.
Y-Yeah.
I should go back.
If the chairperson is seen slacking off,
it sets a bad example.
R-Right.
My, my.
An announcement from the Festival Committee.
Running in the corridors is forbidden.
White banner: II-B Haunted House
Cosplay before the actual day of the festival is forbidden.
Red banner: Manga Society
Shimamoto is...
quite cute.
Wataru!
I... I...
What is it? You're acting strangely.
My springtime might have come again.
This is... This is my springtime!
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Yakisoba
Udon
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Curry
House
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Yakisoba
Udon
Goldfish
Science
Room
Huh?
He's...
Come on. Leave it to me.
But...
You don't have to hold back.
Wataru-san.
Tell me
when you are
ready to order
Tell me
when you are
ready to order
Here's your lunch.
It looks delicious!
Did you make this?
No, unfortunately.
Misa, thank you!
Idiot. Why does he have to say it out loud?
At least he's thanking you.
Good for you, Misa.
That was great.
Misa is quite good at cooking.
Excuse me.
Oh my, Master!
Brown banner: Märchen Box
Green banner: Cookies! Cakes!
Oh, Sensei.
Thank you for taking care of Satomi-chan.
Not at all. So you're here to coach today?
Thank you.
No problem. I'm glad I can help everyone.
Master, enjoy yourself.
Wataru-kun!
He's mean.
Photo Gallery 2-A
Gee, I didn't really think he'd come.
Ah, Morooka-kun.
Infirmary
Mako-sensei, how are you?
Are you slacking off again?
Whatever. Morooka-kun, would you like to have a cup of coffee?
Infirmary
Of course!
I'd go anywhere with you, Mako-sensei.
This is good!
Because you made it, it tastes really good!
Now, now, don't make fun of a grownup.
Hey, Morooka-kun.
How many girls are you interested in?
I'm screwed.
Mako-sensei knows about it all.
I heard a lot about what you did this summer.
What?
From who?
That doesn't matter.
The problem is the number of girls you slept with.
Huh?
So, Morooka-kun, what are you going to do?
What do you mean, what am I going to do?
Do you have someone waiting in the wings?
Huh?! Well...
Waiting in the wings? I don't know what you mean.
Then are you sleeping with any girl who's willing?
How can you say it like that?
But all of them are good.
Am I irresponsible?
You're mysterious.
You definitely don't look like a playboy.
What do you mean by that?
Don't take it as criticism.
None of the four said anything bad about you.
And this way, it's as easy as pie.
None of them are jealous.
Does that mean none of them are serious about me?
Whatever.
Morooka-kun.
Shimamoto?
Can I have a word with you?
What?
Sure!
When that's done, pour in a glass full of ice while it's still hot.
That's the key point to remember.
What is it?
Shimamoto.
Morooka-kun.
Forget about a cute girl café.
Huh?
Miss
\
SGH
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Because I'm not cute.
I feel miserable.
Oden
It was just a joke.
A joke?
Did you think I was serious?
My bad.
Were you really joking?
That's right.
You're not bad-looking.
When you take off your glasses, you're cute.
Liar!
Oden
I'm not lying.
It's true.
Oden
Then what about what you said?
Keep your word.
Hey, Shimamoto!
Oden
M-Misa.
So in fact you're...
fine with anyone!
Hey, wait, Misa!
Misa.
Don't touch me!
Wataru-kun.
Misa is worried about something.
Does her knee hurt?
Archway: Sakimake Academy Cultural Festival
Reception
Used Books
Flea Market
All right! We're done here!
Sakimuri Matsuna 95
3-1 Disco Room
Festival
Sakimuri Matsuna 95
3-1 Disco Room
Festival
Tomorrow we have an early start, so let's call it a day.
Thanks for your hard work.
No, thank you.
Hey, Kazuya, let's go to the penny arcade.
Hey, Kazuya.
I'm sorry. I'm in a hurry today.
See you tomorrow.
What's wrong with him?
Wait!
See you tomorrow!
Aren't you all going home?
Um...
We have an early start tomorrow, so they're going to stay at my house tonight.
Then can I stay with you too?
No!
If you come, my father will shoot you with his hunting rifle.
Yes. That's right.
Hey, hey. You're joking, aren't you?
No. It could happen.
I was just kidding.
All right. I'll go home alone.
Don't be late tomorrow.
Then why don't you wake me up?
Not with a slap, like someone did this morning,
but with a kiss or something.
Wataru-san, I hate you.
See you tomorrow, Misa.
Booths: Polaris, Chariots of Fire
Reception
Sign: Idol Shop
Lucky!
Reception
Kazuya.
Sign: Brass Band Concert
That bastard.
Whatever.
Slacking off makes me tired.
I wonder if Kazuya is making progress.
Maybe he took her to a hotel.
No way.
Wataru.
Wataru, what do you think of me?
I love you so much.
Misa, you...
I'm sorry.
I woke you up when you're tired.
Wataru. I love you.
How did you get in?
This morning too.
Don't ask me anything right now.
All right.
Thank you.
Wataru!
You kept your promise.
Promise?
You said it before.
You'd come have fun at my house.
So you remembered.
Yeah. I've always remembered.
Misa.
I love you, Misa.
Wataru.
Yes. That's good.
Wataru...
Wataru!
Ouch.
Wataru.
I love you.
Wataru?
Wataru.
Wake up, Wataru.
Gee, I suppose there's no other way.
It seems that I won't get slapped this morning.
Idiot.
No, Wataru. We'll be late.
Liar. You woke me up quite early.
No, that tickles.
What? Is Wataru still asleep?
I was thinking of telling him about my date with Shimamoto-san.
But I wonder what I should do after this.
Wataru.
Tell me!
Wataru!
Classmates
Wake up to your love
Translation
anonymous
sotto kaze ga fuite kitayo
A gentle wind is blowing
Timing
archdeco
kimi ha boku no ude no naka de
You are in my arms
Editing
Collectr
QC
CP, Saji
yuutsu na kumo wo nuke
As we go through gloomy clouds,
haruka na sora ni
it feels warm
tsutsumareta nukumori oboete ite
to be surrounded by the distant sky
muneutsu shizukesa ga futari no ai wo
The touching silence will color
toki wo wasureru gurai somete yuku
the couples in love who defy time
sunao ni nareba tayasui kedo
It'd be easy if I could be honest,
kotoba dake jya tarinai
but words are not enough
Wake up to your love
itsumo katari kirenai hodo
I feel full of love from your
ai ga kimi ni afure dashite
overflowing words
Wake up to your wave
kitto hito ha dare mo tabibito
Everyone must be a traveler
kimi mo ashita wo sagasu hazu
You too can search for your future
Wake up to your love
itsumo katari kirenai hodo
I feel full of love from your
ai ga kimi ni afure dashite
overflowing words
Wake up to your wave
kitto hito ha dare mo tabibito
Everyone must be a traveler
kimi mo ashita wo sagasu hazu
You too can search for your future
You too may search for your future
Preview
Hey, everyone, listen up!
Finally, finally, spring has come for me too.
I, Sakagami Kazuya, have a wonderful girlfriend,
after persevering for 18 years!
The next episode of Classmates Climax, File Two, will be:
Kyouko-san!