Doctor, how's her condition?
Rei.
I've got to go.
What am I... doing... what happened... to me...
Hey, been waiting for you. I've been waiting for you
for 40 hours.
You know what to do, right?
Ye... Yes.
REI
Special Woman Agent Falls into Bitch Slavery!
There, get inside.
Thirteen. Do you know what that means?
Is that so? Do as you like then.
Thirteen people. It's the same as the number of times you hit me.
In less than 30 minutes you'll make them all cum.
Who's going to let you do that?
Hm... Even after looking at that, you can talk like that?
Re... Rei.
Sh-Shouko!
If you don't hurry up and start satisfying these people,
that woman will die.
You-!
It's not really my concern at all, but are you okay with that?
There's no more pitiful death... than that.
Hey, start already!
I understand.
"Please let me serve you."
Please... let me serve you.
I can see from what you're doing that you really like
sucking at that dirty penis after all.
It's... bitter.
Hey, hey, if it's that delicious, why don't you taste
it all the way in your mouth!
Haha! This woman is really eating me on her own!
There, eat it all the way in!
The way you're sucking that penis, it seems
it's not enough if it's just one penis, doesn't it?
You bitch!
Hey, why don't you please mine as well?
Hey, hey, do it more seriously!
If you don't, you're going to put your friend in danger.
Shouko...
Hey, hey, why're you stopping?
If you do that, this woman will be...
It's... feeling... good...
Hehe, this bitch is beginning to lick our cocks on her own.
Hehe, is it really that delicious?
You whore bitch!
All right, for a bitch whore like you, I've got plenty of semen to give you.
I'm letting it out!
I'll let you taste it deep in your throat.
Hey, drink it up!
There's no time for you to take a break.
Don't struggle, okay?
Now, it's my turn.
Tha... that place.
Relax yourself, so it won't tear apart.
It feels so good to enter this deep place inside you.
How is it? Does it feel good?
There's...
no way...
it would feel good...
If you do that...
It will tear... my ass will be torn apart...
I'm moving.
Stop it! If you move that hard... you'll make my ass tear.
It'll tear apart!
I'll die!
I'll die! Don't kill me!
You'll make me die if you do my ass like that.
What's this, what's this? You're drenched so much
from getting fucked in your asshole?
Do you want it in here, too?
No! Please let me go-
I'll die from it... you'll make me die from it...
Don't lie, you bitch! I can feel that you're getting tight
when our dicks are inside of you.
I'm full of them... the inside of my pussy and my asshole is full of them.
All right, I'll let it out inside of you! I'm going to fill it all up.
That's okay, right? That's your duty to have us
fill you up like this, right?
No, don't let it out! Don't let your sperm inside of me.
It's out... inside of my pussy... there's a lot of sperm inside of me...
Hey, hey, why're you taking a break like that?
There's ten people left. I'm sure you can make it
if you work a little harder.
Okay... It's 29 minutes, a little bit close isn't?
Actually... after the thirteenth hit, do you remember the kick?
That's fourteen, and the fourteenth person is... me!
That can't be!
It's almost time that the drug's effects should make her body fall apart.
It's time over.
Rei, don't mind it...
Tha... Thank you for doing that... for me-
Shouko!
I'll kill you! I'll make sure to kill you!
It's there... there it is.
Wow, is this really that famous special agent?!
I heard that she'd been caught by the drug dealer syndicate,
and after that she's getting trained to fuck those guerrillas every day.
I think that it would be the perfect job for her.
Right... right... that's what she gets if she's arrogant like that.
Hehe, she deserves it.
Heh... she's sucking that man on her own!
There's "double pie" as well, what kind of training is that?
Besides... her chief is searching for her whereabouts all these months.
Collecting them all is difficult but
collecting them would make a fortune.
It's already three months, huh?
Do I lose again?
Shall we start for today?
There.
What a noisy mouth, there!
I'll make you know your place, bitch!
The next one would be this hole, here!
Please... stop it...
There.
Clean it up.
Your pussy is still tight after getting fucked every day for these last three months.
Stop it... I'll break... apart...
No... No! I'm cumming!
There, I'm letting it out! It's your favorite semen!
I'm going to release a lot of it inside of you!
Sto... Stop it...
I'm cumming!
I told you... to... stop...
Move away!
It's full of it-
Heh heh heh, do you not wish to get pregnant that badly?!
There!
There you go!
If you don't let it out quickly, you'll get pregnant, right?
Okay, it's meal time.
Don't start eating yet.
The general told us to fill it up with semen first.
Fine, you can start eating it.
It's okay for you to not eat that like before.
I know that your older brother has a daughter, Yukari-chan isn't it?
It's easy for us to bring her in here anytime.
There, I'll add more of it!
That's right, I forgot to tell you, that when you got caught in here
your junior Saki-chan is just about now
already on sale into a foreign pervert club,
Even she's already forgotten her own name.
I'm sure that relieves your mind.
Hehe, this bitch is really eating that.
Is it really tasty to eat our semen like that, you bitch whore?
It... It's delicious...
Then why you don't taste more of it?!
There... there you go!
It's shift time.
This woman?
She's the special agent who's was caught
by the the North Cartell crime syndicate
This is Joachim Night, or we know him as the Red General.
He makes me sick.
Cumming... cumming... No...
Cumming... I'm going to break apart...
No... No... It's cumming... I'm cumming!
Open your mouth.
We need to piss.
It's out, going out... there-
Taste a lot of it, you bitch.
Stick out your tongue, bitch!
That's a good face.
Smile and make a peace sign!
Right, that's good.
There's no one going to save me... there's no way
I could return to who I was before...
Hey, where's your smile, bitch?
Yes.
Night, you bastard! I'll make sure to save you, Rei!
I'm going to take revenge on Shouko's death as well.
Chief, there's something that's come up in our investigation!
What?
Thank you very much, Master.
Your reward.
That's a good face, now you know your place as a bitch slave.
Protect the General! Don't let them in!
What is that, so much noise out there.
Shit!
Move inside!
The information from the other crime syndicate
was correct!
Rei, I'm coming to you right now!
It's Joachim Night, the Red General, right?
Where are you, Rei?
Wait, Xien!
Yes, Kouryuu-sama.
Who... are... you...
Kouryuu-sama, it's time to leave.
Pursue them!
Rei!
Rei, are you okay?
Backup is on its way.
Chief...
You don't have to tell us anything. Everyone is waiting for you.
Let's go home.
Chief!
This way!
Give her treatment, quickly!
Nagasarereba Itsudatte Kurikaeshi
If I drifted away, I can always go back
ni Mieru Hibi
to the days where I belong
Daijina mono wa Ushinatte
Even if I lose something important
Harumete Kizukurashii kedo
There's a way to remember it
Haritsuketayou ga Mainichi ni
If i just attach to those lost days
Natte Nakushite Kizuitatte
I might be able to remember something
Koukai nante shinai to Omotteta
But I never feel any regret in my mind
Sono Hitomi wo Mou Ichido
With those eyes once again
Douka Watashi wo Utsushite
I want you to look at me
Kono Omoi wo Mou Ichido
With this feeling once again
Douka Anata ni Todoite
I want to reach for you
Mou Ichido
Once again
It's already been a year, has it?
You're ready to start all over again, right?
You're late!
Wait for me, Rei-senpai!
I'm leaving you behind, Fuuko!
Senpai, wait!