What is it? You know that this parade is to celebrate our engagement.
Why don't you show your love a bit?
What's with that look? Don't you think for a princess of Filhem, a human like me doesn't have a chance to have your love?
That's...
Princess!! Princess!!
What's with your laziness!? Why are you not doing your job properly?!
That really hurts, Mom.
Hey, why don't you do your job instead drinking beer in the afternoon like that?
But, it's because of that Elf Princess...
You know I never met such a beautiful being like that.
You know I never met another being who's as much of a drunk as you.
Ho... Honey... that's really hurts, you know?!
Even someone like me wants to try to do it with such a beautiful woman like her.
That's enough, you should do some work right now you lazy bones!
That's... I told you that hurts, Honey!
Elf
Hime
Nina
Prostitute Princess
in Tentacles Suit
Elf
Hime
Nina
Prostitute Princess
in Tentacles Suit
What's the matter with you? Don't just watch, join us.
You two... what're you doing?
What are we doing? Why don't you find out for yourself, right?
For a woman, making a man feel so much pleasure doesn't always have to be with her pussy.
Like this for example, but I guess that's impossible for you.
You... you know, I don't want to be as indecent as a Dark Elf.
But with Cail... No, If you do it with body parts from the King's race
It'll surely become a habit like with me.
Don't you agree?
That's... not... for me...
For an Elf's race, the semen from the King's race is important for you to make a healthy baby.
Doing something like this is a necessity, right?
Hey Milia, you have some space here.
Why don't you release it to demonstrate to our princess here?
The power of the king's race is limitless after all.
It's really hard... and the hot feeling when it rubs me...
My breasts are going to meltdown.
You're gonna cum, right? I know it.
I can feel it when your semen slowly climbs into the top of it.
Look, the fluid is already coming out of the tip.
I'll give you a taste of tit-fuck in front of your Elf princess.
Hey... It's okay to let it out.
My breasts really feel like a pussy with your penis in here...
Let your semen spread between my breasts.
You came a lot... But that's not really all of it, right?
Then my princess, now it's your turn.
Don't put that filthy thing any closer to me...
Don't say that... That penis is the one that could make you pregnant.
First off... why don't you clean it up?
With your mouth of course.
With my mouth? I have to clean this filthy thing with my mouth?
Such an indecent thing...
What's the matter? It won't get clean by looking at it.
I... I understand, but...
Right... that's right, lick the sensitive part of the penis, that would make the pleasure come out from the tip.
Licking at the sperm like this...
Does it really feel that good?
Hey, what's the matter with you?!
I don't feel good enough, you know?!
You're such a fool.
If you're still doing something like an amateur, you won't make the man feel good.
Hey, don't just look. Why don't you take a place here?
I want you to lick all over the penis, you can even lick the balls as well.
T... the balls...
That's right, that place is where the semen comes out to make a child.
If you keep licking it,
It'll produce more semen for you.
Even... if you say something like that...
That's right... I'm sure by now you understand how to do it with pleasure.
That's not...
Even though you're an high elf, you're still a woman after all.
It's in your instincts to make pleasure with men.
No way, It feels really bad.
Looks like you're ready for this!
Here I come.
Wait...
Open your mouth wide.
It's going inside my mouth...
It looks so good when you two are having fun like that.
Then, I'm gonna take a place back here.
Mi...li...a...
Even though men like to thrust into us, that doesn't mean they don't want us to thrust into them.
Hey, you stopped moving!
It's hitting...
It's hitting my throat...
That face is surely priceless, now I'll release a lot of it in your mouth!
That's a beautiful cosmetic, right?
This is really disgraceful...
Then, now for the real deal.
In return for what you did earlier, I'll release a lot into you until this day is over.
Today...? You can't do it that inside, please let me go.
Hey... hey... I'm ashamed of you, tonight let me do it with you in other ways.
But tonight, I'll take your virginity from this hole.
That... that place...
It's a rare chance for you, I'll let you taste
the other seventh heaven.
Wait! That's just wrong!
It's nice how tight you are.
It hurts... that's just wrong...
I'll just do whatever I want, in the mean time you can just rest.
What're you doing?
Stop it... it hurts... it's...
What's the matter? Do you prefer it from the front?
It's not like that... don't say something like that to me.
That's good, even though it's your first time you're doing just fine.
For an elf woman, both your pussy and asshole are really good after all.
It hurts... and it's hot...
It's ripping apart... my asshole is gonna rip apart...
You're really a spoiled one...
At the same time, let me help you with this.
In there...
Stop it... in there... if you're teasing it as well... I'm gonna...
You're already drenched here from getting fucked in your asshole.
Stop... it...
Or maybe you're feeling ashamed for getting spread with semen like that?
Stop it... being teased in the back and front at the same time,
It's hot... hot like I'm gonna meltdown.
Stop it...
Stop... doing something so intense...
What is it, do you feel good from being fucked in your asshole?
That's not... being fucked in my asshole... doesn't make... doesn't make me feel good at all...
Release it! I'm going to release a lot of it into your virgin asshole.
Stop it... If you release it right now... I'm gonna go crazy...
I'm gonna go crazy from it being released in my asshole like this!
No way! It's out... It's coming out inside of my asshole!
It's out... It came out inside of me... I can feel the hot stuff slowly flowing inside of me.
When are you going to get used to things like this?
That's... I'm not... I'm won't accept any indecent things like this.
But, If you keep saying things like that, I'm sure you won't be able to live like this.
Be happy, I've got some training for someone who's never known the night life like you.
A place like this would be good, right?
You... made me dress like this...
Quickly take off that cloth and do what I say.
What's the matter? It will be over soon enough, but I can't guarantee you won't like it.
Who's going to like it?!
Do as you please.
Hey, do it with that guy.
What kind of an old lady gives me trouble and gives me too much work to do?!
Doesn't she know that I'm the great one?!
For god sake!
Hey, you over there!
Miss, do you have something to do with me?
Do you want... to buy me?
Miss, I'm sure I saw you somewhere before.
That's fine... Would you like to buy me?
Hey, Miss-
No!
Hey... Miss, what a gorgeous suit you have.
Hey... hey... If I look closely, you're an elf aren't you?
I didn't know that there were prostitute elves here.
What the matter? Why do you look so indecent?
I want you...
No way... I have to say something like this to a human, even though I don't want to...
But... If I don't do that, this thing...
Please... please just buy me!
If I just say something like that... then this human...
would surely buy me...
I want you... I want you to buy me as your elf prostitute!
It's gonna break... in there...
If those tentacles keep rubbing me...
He... hey, Miss Elf?
Please buy me...
As your prostitute elf... I want you to have me, as your elf prostitute...
Hug me..love me... with it...
That's fine with me, If you're saying it like that
I'd be happy to buy you.
There's some cheap inn back there, come on!
Wait a minute... I just had to say something like that to you...
Ca... Cail, where are you?
Miss, If I look closely at you... you have the same face as the Elf Princess who was with the King this afternoon.
Is it possible that all women from the Elf Kingdom are this beautiful?
Let me go, you filthy human!
Now way... no way... It's in... It's inside of my mouth...
Miss, you're already like this after being kiss like that?
But, I'm sure you're gonna feel good after this guy is inside of you.
Then, now it's show time.
Sto... stop it... no more of this, I don't want to be a prostitute for a human like you...
Humans... I don't want to get pregnant with a human child!
Hey Miss, you can't say something like that when we're gonna do this.
If you're still like this, then I'm gonna make you feel so much more horrible.
I want to look at an elf with her body breaking apart like that.
That's...
If you don't wanna feel it, then shut your mouth.
It will be done sooner than you think.
No way... please let me go... I don't want... to do it with a human...
Why don't you behave yourself, or do you want me to force you to?
I... I understand... but please... do not use the front one...
With this one, please do it with this instead of using the front one...
An Elf princess asshole?
An Elf's hole is a little bit smaller than a human's,
It's gonna be much tighter in here.
That's fine, It's my pleasure to have sex with an elf's asshole like this.
It's great! It's so much tighter than my wife's asshole,
It feels so good!
Not... that intense...
Even though you're an elf, women are still women after all.
Look how you've been eating my penis like this.
No... It's rubbing... rubbing inside of me...
Please let me go...
Inside of me... my asshole is gonna be... shaped like your penis from being fucked like this...
I never knew that an elf could be this indecent.
Here you, I'll give you a whip!
No, If you're whipping me like that-
The more I hit you, the tighter it gets in here.
No... It hurts... this is. ..this feeling hurts... but, why does it feel so good-
No way, It feels good...?
Penis in my asshole... being fucked in my asshole... feels so good...
Hey, that's a good reaction from you.
Is it okay with you? Is it fine to just be fucked in your asshole like this?!
No... don't say such a thing... my asshole... my ass-
No... I'm... I'm going to...
Cum! You're gonna cum?! You're gonna cum from being fucked in your asshole by a human?!
No... I'm going to cum... gonna cum from being fucked in my asshole like this... I'm gonna cum!!
It's out... it's inside of me... there's human sperm, inside of me...
I'm going to smell like a human female...
Hey Miss, there's no time for you to rest!
Let's do the next one!
That's not possible...
Then, this time for sure-
My customer, If you would excuse us a minute.
What are you doing in here?!
I said you just have to get the attention of a costumer, but look at you now.
Mi... Milia?
Is it possible that you want to giving birth to a human child?
Who would want something like that?!
Rest assured, for an indecent one like you
I've brought the perfect partner for you.
What?
These creatures?!
They're cute, aren't they? They're gonna give their love to you.
Wait-
Stop... It's inside... Let me go... I don't want to do it with these creatures...
Is it probably that uncle... doesn't want you to use your front hole?
Stop it... in there... just in there...
No... no... no... NO~!!!
No... I just told you no...
You're going back to your kingdom like this, so it would be fine just to do it like this.
No... no way... I don't... want to go back like this...
With these filthy creatures like this-
You're not gonna put that-
This is... this... filthiness...
I don't...
I don't... want to feel like this from goblins...
Hey... hey... An elf princess is being fucked by goblins like this.
That's... gonna make me...
Hm... It's because you're in good condition, so all of your indecency has come out.
Look, in there too.
No, don't let it out... you can't let it out!
If you let it out... I'm going to get pregnant... with a goblin...
I'm going to get pregnant with a goblin's child!
NO~!!!
No... It's out...it really came out... I'm going to get pregnant from a goblin's sperm...
No... it's going inside of me... a monster's sperm...
I'm going to get pregnant for sure...
I'm going to get pregnant from these filthy creatures...
No... don't let it out... this filthy stuff... is spread on me...
I can't go back... I'm not going to be able to go back to Filhem.
Such foolishness! I can't believe you even gave your body to those goblin like that!
I just give up trying to warn a Filhem princess like you.
I didn't do it! I'm sure that you two planned this already.
Hmph, It can't be.
It doesn't really happen without a purpose.
But, what do you think? Did you feel the results of your night life training?
What's with that "night life"?! You made me suffer like this!
Hey... hey... who do you think you're speaking with?
I'm your... No, I'm just doing a favor to help your elf race.
Don't fuck with me! What you did to me is going to destroy all of my elf race!
Is that so? But, If you don't make a union with me then that's going to happen to your elf race anyways.
If Seil's still alive, I don't wan to do that thing with you-
What?! Who the hell are you?!
You... Is it possible that... you're... Seil...
Wha... what's with him?! And why is his body so powerful?
He's not human, he's one of the king's race like me...
Guard! Is there guard in here?!
I want you to guard this whole area!
Let no one come in or out!