You're getting horny, aren't you?
It's not... like that.
Besides that... Doing it in this place...
What are you saying? Did it feel different when we're doing it at noon?
Who do you think you're speaking to?
I'm an elf, that's something...
Is that so? Then I'll enjoy it by myself.
It's too intense.
That's good, your womanly thing is getting tight around my penis.
Did you really like my thing as well?
That's not true, doing something indecent like this...
I won't make a pledge with you, I won't do it...
Even you say that, you want it to come out right?
Even though we're doing it in here, It's still so much fun.
My lovely elf princess.
Who are you calling lovely? If you're weren't here... I would...
Elf
Hime
Nina
The Princess who imprisoned
in the Lust Castle
Once upon a time, there was king who had overwhelming power within his hand.
Aside from the king who rules over all humanity, there's a demon king who rules over all demons in this world.
One  time that King's race would stand against the demon king to prevent him from destroying the world.
They would be the lights of hope, who would stand beside the king of humanity with the seven powers in their hands.
They're the unforgotten heroes of humanity, Earth union, D'Arc the count, Forest union, the Elf Princess,
Grass union, the hobbits, the sage who controls this world wisely, and also the union of all magicians.
In front of those heroes, the demon king stood and fought with them.
Even though the opponent is the king who rule over all demon kings,
by reuniting all of the heroes' powers, they finally can defeat him.
It's called the "battle of heroes".
What awaits them after that would be the new age, the world which fill with all the light.
Inside of the brightness, there are new lights of hope for their world, that would be the hope which given to them by those seven heroes.
The world is continuing change into the new world, as the world regains its peace once again, the seven heroes pray it would last forever.
Nina-sama.
Princess-sama?
Ah, what is it?
Do you still feel worried about this journey?
We also understand your feelings, princess.
That's nothing, you don't have to worry.
This journey is something important for our Elf race,
and it would be my responsibility to do it as Saint Seirhelm's princess.
Princess-sama.
Seil...
Saint Seirhelm's princess, Nina Asrath has arrived!
Thank you for coming in here, Elf princess.
Yes, I've come in here to make a pledge for the union of my Elf race.
There's nothing I can say but thanks for taking this pledge with us.
I've come in here to represent my father, the king of Filhem.
It's nothing...  After all, everything is because those rebels...
No, we're also the King's race, living in this land beside your race for a long time.
It's like we don't have any option besides living through this problem with your race.
If we're dealing with this problem together, we'll need to unite our races with this pledge.
That's why we're helping each other.
Thank you very much.
In exchange for making this pledge, I want you to stay in this castle for a month.
You're here as a delegate from the kingdom of Saint Seirhelm, I hope that you can do that favor for me.
Yes.
Then our pledge will be official now.
Why don't you raise your head upon me, princess?
Seil...
Welcome, Princess Nina.
Cail...?
The hero who fight the demon king Zeromus, Seil Van Ganossa.
Then the other hero who's standing beside him, Princess Nina from the Elf union.
You're using their relationship in a previous life, to get what you wanted in here.
Are you the kind of bad person who would try to take your brother's position?
And the one who killed that brother of mine, wasn't that you, Dark Elf?
But is it okay? I don't think that princess would agree with you being her partner in this deal.
There won't be any problem, I'm planning this matter very thoroughly.
What's he doing in there? he's supposed to be in Seil's place as the king of this kingdom.
The one who will be my partner in this pledge should be Seil.
If it's Seil, then I'll give everything I have for him.
Seil...
Princess-sama... princess-sama... princess-sama...
You're came at a good time, come inside.
I've decide to revoke this pledge right now.
My father is still healthy, so we don't have to be hasty.
Princess-sama...
What is it?
The truth is... A messenger informed us that your father has...
The king of Filhem has fallen ill in his castle.
What?!
So you're a bad king, lying to the princess like this?
Huh, whatever you say.
You're setting up a situation where she can't revoke the pledge.
Right... Then before the pledge would happen in the next month...
There's a contract that the Elf princess has to fulfill as an old pact with the king.
Ah, King of Seirhelm...
I'm sorry that you've had to lie to your princess like that.
No, we're glad we can be such a big help to the benefit of our kingdom.
Please take care of our princess.
Of course, I'll make a promise to take care of the princess.
And then, I'm planning to give you some reward for your help.
Eh?
That's not necessary...
We don't deserve a reward...
Don't hold back, I'm sure you're gonna enjoy it after this.
King of Seirhelm, is this?
A reward for you, then this will be your place for a while.
King of Seirhelm, what is this?
Besides your princess, the virginity of your Elf race shouldn't be underestimated after all.
The first one is starting.
No... No~!! Help me... princess-sama... help me!!
It's okay, you don't have to worry, you're gonna be even more beautiful after this.
Da... Dark Elf...
What a beautiful ass, I would love to taste it.
What are you saying... You filthy Dark Elf...
In there... my asshole... I won't...
let that filthy Dark Elf lick it...
Hm... I'm just doing a favor for you...
Then, I'll let you have filthy thing, instead of more of me.
What...
I feel something coming inside... a slimy thing...
No, no more of that... Please don't push it in!
I said... no... I just said... no more of that...
It's okay, the fun has just started.
What... something is coming... it's spreading...
It's spreading inside of me...
Wh... What is this? It's slippery...
This is what you'd call an artificial penis...
It's just like a real one.
No... Don't touch that.
It's strange... painful... it's painful!
If you don't want it to be painful, there's one thing you need to do.
No... stop it...
Penis... the penis is getting hard... let me do it... just let me do it...
If the penis is rubbed in the hole...
If I get it rubbed inside of it...
I've been told it's gonna feel much better.
Your front hole is already drenched.
Then in here... in this hole...
This hole is more filthy than the front one, let me put the penis inside of your asshole...
No way... don't do that...
Please don't do... that!!
Pussy is good... the pussy is really good...
Inside of the asshole is also feels good!
Stop it... please don't rub it... If you do this to me...
I can't... go back... I can't go back to the elf country!
It's good...
Whatever you say, an elf is also a woman after all.
No... please no more...
No... let me go... back... let me go back to my country...
What is it, you're still saying things like that?
It's intense... the big penis... is too intense...
Gonna rip... it's gonna rip apart!!
As I thought an elf body is really different than the others.
There... it's the sperm of King's race, you know?!
I'll let you taste before your princess!
No... the penis is bursting out...
It's filling... a lot of it is filling me up... the King's race's sperm is inside of me...
Let it out... I'm gonna let it out... I'll let it out from the penis...
Even you're an elf... I'm gonna make you pregnant...
I'm gonna make you really pregnant...
No... no more~!!
NO~!!!
I can still feel it... I can still feel from the penis...
It's gonna burst out...
It want to cum... I'm gonna cum!
I guess the sensation of that thing is too much for an elf like you.
Did you do this to the princess as well?!
Rest assured, she's a special one to me...
She's different than you.
Those things...
Well then..when the the time comes,
I'll let you see your princess.
A lot of penis...
Cail, did Seil really die?
He died when we were at war with the rebels, how many times did I tell you that?
That is...
You don't have to worry, If you get pregnant with me then the Elf race is going to be saved.
Though it's not my brother's child, but my child.
Then why don't you just simply live with me?
Don't get the wrong idea, even though I let you have my body, I won't let you have my heart as well.
If there's not a pledge, who wants to be with you...
The one who I left for and trust my whole body with is Seil.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going outside for some fresh air, I don't want to breath the same air as you.
There might be some rebels lurking outside, please be careful.
It's true that you have to be careful.
Seil...
What?
That armor... Are you the rebels?
Let me go!
I never thought that the elf who came out when we battled with the imperial at noon is actually this beautiful.
With this you can't cast any spell, can you?
I never thought that I'd get to do it with an elf.
What are you doing?
I'm sure it's different than with the usual woman.
I'm asking you, what are you going to do?!
Don't yell at me like that!
Don't you know your place?
That is...
What is it Elf-sama? Is it your first time seeing a human's thing?
Is this woman a virgin? Lucky for you, isn't it?
Let me go! Don't you know who I am?!
Of course we know, you're a foolish elf who came out in the middle of the night to get raped by us.
Here I come.
Wait...
It's inside of me... That filthy human's thing is inside of me.
What?! This woman isn't a virgin.
What are you saying? Is it possibly you're enjoying it too, Elf-sama?
That is...
Then I don't have to hold back, right?
Stop... You're moving it... It's rubbing it...
That's not a problem, right? Here you go, let me make it more intense for your pussy.
No way, that thing... that human's thing is inside of my body...
If this is continues...
It hurts... you're putting it deep inside of me!
That's a good moan you have.
Please take care of it in here too.
It stinks.
You're going to eat this stinky thing right now, Elf-sama!
I'll let you eat all of it!
This woman's mouth is really good! It's like a real pussy and it's getting tight as well!
This tightness down here is amazing too!
I never thought that an elf could have this kind of tightness and be so perverted.
Stop it... please stop it...
We can't hear what you're talking about!
I'll let it out... I'll let it out in your mouth...
I'll let you taste human sperm!
Stop it... If this is continues...
What are you talking about? There's no coming back!
Look.
What... what are you going to do?
Of course we're gonna take turns, to make you our side dishes.
Side dishes...?
Don't look...
You can't look while masturbating to me!
Masturbating while looking at me...
Don't let me be your side dishes!!
There's no one who would give up at a time like this.
Here you go, why don't you look at it clearly?
Too... in...tense...
Side dishes... I don't want to be a side dish like this!
No, sto...stop it... pull it out... crazy... I'm going crazy...
Even though I'm being raped like this...
While being a side dish for filthy humans...
Being raped like this...
Cum... I'm going to cum!
That's right, I'm gonna let it out!
I'll let this filthy human sperm go inside your lovely womb.
No... A child from a human...? I don't want to give birth to a child from a human!
No way... It's coming inside my womb...
Pregnant...? I'm going to get pregnant from this filthy human...
Stop it, I'm going to smell so stinky...
If I smell the stink of human sperm again...
I'm gonna cum again~!!
Doesn't it feel good after doing this?
We're doing it as an order from his majesty.
Over here! Our enemy is attacking!
Your majesty, what are you talking...
They've escaped, follow them!
That's why I told you earlier, you just can't trust me.
Cail, they let it out... They let out a lot inside of me...
Child from human... I... I'm...
Right, I'm definitely going to let you get pregnant from it.
To give birth to a human child.
No way, I don't want to give birth to a human child.
No... No...
That's why this thing exists.
That's... a purification stone?
That's right, with this we can purify the inside of your womb.
Is it over?
Yeah, but is it okay with you?
Eh?
The purification stone... also purified the release I gave you before.
We'll have fun once more, Nina.
Until the day you give birth to my child.