R2, I've arrive in destination.
All clear from up here.
Can you hear the helicopter sounds?
No.
Is that the newest machine?
I just can hear these cricket sounds from here.
Are you really in there?
Then, would you like to play a game with me?
Scissors.
As usual, you're not afraid of anything isn't?
You should try it once, Munei-san.
You'll get used of it.
I'll have to refuse that.
R1, preparation is OK.
Understood.
Rei, follow my instructions carefully.
Don't do any stunt play for today.
I'll do my best.
R1, proceed!
Understood.
REI
Let's capture the special agents!
The power going to back on soon, proceed right now.
Understood.
This is R1, I've confirm the power has turn back on again.
R2, infiltration is success.
OK. R3, you can move in right now.
I'm sorry, It seems we've trigger something
within the building electricity.
Hey, that makes trouble in here...
As we've planned before, there isn't any security in 35th floor right now.
If we're just move in right now, then it'll be our success.
If there's more than 3 people guarding that place,
step away from there.
Alright, I'll step away if there's more than 5 people.
I'll cut off the communications for now.
Rei? Rei?!
It's in here.
This is?
The power has down back there.
That's right, but we've run back-up power supply in here
so there won't be any problem.
5 people, huh?
Like I care.
Hey, where do you think you're go-
Damn it!
It seems you don't have much time to finish your conversations.
NORTH KARTELL's boss, Joachim Night?
Who are you?
I'm the who's asking you.
Joachim Night, right?
That's right.
You dare make me bleed like this-
I don't allow you to threaten me.
It seems this place isn't really narcotics storage place.
What's that thing?
It's the money resources.
You're one of narcotics special agent, huh?
Just answer what I'm asking you!
What's your name?
I'll make sure to kill you!
I'll rape you..rape you..all over again,
so you'll regret being born in this world.
That's right I'll make your family, your friends, and everyone,
I'll make them suffer to death~!
Is that so?
Let's talk again slowly after this.
This is R2, I've capture the target.
You can pick me up.
Sure you won't be lost consciousness down there, right?
Joachim Night.
International crime syndicate's Boss, NORTH KARTELL.
Nick name: General.
Birthplace unknown.
Japanese descent people.
He's also one of the most wanted guerrilla terrorist in 20th century,
known as the Red General.
He's also have several secret quarter in South America,
which create the new generation of narcotics.
His syndicate always using violence within their actions,
after these years he's able to create the most powerful crime syndicate.
Since last year, he's planning to make another quarter in Japan.
Within half year, he's already conquer all syndicate
in Kanto's area.
We've tracked and captured him in one of the hotel within those area,
we also find out there's a lot of unknown things in the other rooms of the hotel.
One of his subordinate who's working as goverment staffs already notice,
and now he's planning to look after his missing boss.
We just have maximum 48 hours to lock him in here,
before the time is over, I want you to find out what's his plan
with all those materials back there.
You're talking like that's possible to do, Chief.
Though it's not impossible to do.
Rei!
Don't you think it's better for us to act like a soldier,
since he's part of soldier in the past?
Former one of the biggest guerrilla terrorist, who'c working as narcotics boss.
Don't you think you've lost your authority in there,
Mister Red General?
12 times.
You've hit me 12 times.
It's 12 times, since you hit me back there in the hotel.
Now it's the 13 times.
It's good for us, If you have good memory in your head.
Then I'm sure that you're able to answer my questions easily.
What's that thing?
I've seen that creepy things within those tubes.
Though I couldn't take all of your material data back there,
but I'm able to take some of your data last night.
Our specialist already working on that data right now.
It won't be long for us to find out what is that.
It's better for you to talk to us without hiding anything.
I'm not sure about that.
It's 30 hours...
No, maybe you just have 40 hours left to lock me up like this.
I'm sure there's friend of mine who's already prepare
to release me from here.
Then your data which you stole from me earlier,
It'll be useless within the next few days.
Do you understand right now?
It's 13th times, Miss Special Agent.
Stop your interogation.
What?
There's informant wants to talk with us about
the thing that happen yesterday.
Informant?
I'm sure you've already know Uematsu the informant, right?
Yeah, that mouse who's having bad taste
with his golden watch in his hands.
Of course I couldn't forget that man.
Also he's always took a lot of money for his informations.
It's the first time I've seen such informant like him.
I suppose that's the proof about his trusted informations.
But, don't you think it's strange for Uematsu
to contact us like this?
I assume it's gonna be dangerous informations after all.
He wants to give it directly to us.
He also demand that we pay him in cash.
Don't you think that the timing is too coincidentally?
Though it's gonna be a trap, but it'll be usefull
if we can find something to pressure Night.
We'll decide it after thinking about the dangerous part first.
Yes, of course.
He's also thinking the safety within this crowded trains.
Be quiet.
It's coming.
Understood.
Oh..No-
What is this...
You're able to hold against one shot.
Usually, there's only need one shot to make you like a doll.
St..op..it-
It's gonna be a problem if you called someone.
Re..Rei...
Don't say that...
All of this passenger is...
What a clever woman aren't you?
You've got it right.
And then, this is the thing you've been searching.
It's called Brain Control Nano Machine.
It's serum to control someone brains with one word.
Even for vulgarism using.
It's not going to be fun, If there's no reactions coming from you.
I'll let you have your own sexual pleasure after this.
Re..Rei.
Then, shall we enjoy ourself in here.
Stop..it...
No~! Stop..pinch..on my nipples...
No...
If you pinch on my nipples like that...
No..you can't do that!
My tongue is moving by itself...
My breasts and my pussy is drenched a lot of it...
I've made a contact, proceed with the transaction.
I'm sure you've already know Uematsu the informant, right?
Yeah, that mouse who's having bad taste
with his golden watch in his hands.
Of course I couldn't forget that man.
Rei, what's the matter?
Rei, answer me!
Say there's nothing happen in here.
Why..should..I...
Say it, that there's nothing happen in here.
There's..nothing..happen..in..here...
Is that so? Then proceed with the transaction.
Wait, It's not me who's saying those words.
Don't..say that...
Today, we're gonna let you know how to deal
with arrogance women like you.
I'll let you scream with your voice.
You can let out your voice of pleasure.
Hm..so this is how it looks inside of your violence body.
It makes us feel excited with it.
You, let me go-
Hey..hey..that wasn't enough for you?
I'll let you release a lot of your women liquid with this serum,
then you're going to take care of them.
What's the matter?
It's alright for you tolet out your moaning voice.
Let me hear your womanly moaning voice.
Though I can't guarantee that your friends going to hear it.
Who's..going to-
Who's going..to moan-
No-
You...
Stop..doing that...
Stop..that-
Though your mouth saying like that, but your pussy is being honest.
I can't endure something like this.
But,
I'll make sure this won't-
Hm..even though we're doing like this, you're able
to keep your voice in there.
It's good..good.
As a reward of what you're doing, I'll let you see your precious
friends from special agents.
No..stop it...
Let me rest a bit...
I'm going to cum...
Going to cum...
Cum..cumming..cumming-
Rei...
No..stop it...
Don't look at me..don't look at me with your face like that-
There..there, why don't you tell her how you're being rape.
Explain to her!
Though I don't want my pussy being raped, my pussy is filled with it...
there's a lot of penis coming inside my pussy...
Though I don't want it, but I couldn't do anything!
That's good, you can explain it properly.
Look at me..I'm going to cum while Rei is looking at me-
Going to cum..going to cum again...
I'm going to cum with my pussy while everyone is look at me...
Cum..cumming~
Munei-san is being shot with that serum,
my fault...It's my fault!
It's..it's feels good..being seen like this...
I'm going to cum while you look at me...
Next one, we'll do it with your asshole.
You've already screaming with one thrust?
But, It's only the beginning you know?
There you go! I'll make you pregnant with this, Grandma!
There's a lot of sperm coming out...
There's a lot of sticky thing come out from your penis,
It's coming inside my pussy...
It's coming..It's still coming inside of me...
Make me cum with it...
Make me cumming again!
It's coming through..in my womb.
Don't pust it in..don't push it in my womb-
Cumming..cumming right now..I'll make you cumming too!
Who's going to-
Who's going..to cum-
It's out..It's really come out..inside of me...
His sticky sperm is coming inside of my womb...
Damn..damn it!
Let me go~!
In..inside of my womb is being stir up...
I couldn't think of anything else-
No..not that hard.
If..if you're doing it that hard, I'm going to-
Admit it..say it..that you're feeling all of it.
Who do you think..would feeling..feeling something..like this-
There you go, bitch!
Cumming..cumming..cumming! I'm gonna cumming~!!
There's a lot of sperm coming inside my pussy,
those semen gonna make me pregnant...
Don't think to bite on it, okay?
Gently...
That's right, suck it gently with your mouth.
Please let me go...
Don't spread your sperm to me..stop it!
You've let it out inside of me again...
I'll..kill..you..I'm going to..kill you...
Then, shall we drop you at the next station?
I'll take care of your friends.
If you want to save her, you'll know what to do.
Hey, It's time for you to go.
Hey..hey..what the matter with her? Is it the making of AV in there?
What's wrong with her?
It's digusting~
There..is-
The last serum is?
It's the release serum.
It's pity that we're not able to watch what happen after this.
I can't..hold it-
My body...
is being...
freed.
Toilet.
Right now...
I can't...
If you're not...
let me come..inside the toilet-
Hey, you!
It's out!
It's..going out-
My urine...
is come out...
I'm cumming..while I'm..peeing...
I'm cumming..while peeing...
I'll..kill..you.