It all started...
when I opened that box.
When I opened Pandra's box.
It's like I've gotten a baby!
The demon that has possessed me, Parasite,
used my magic powers,
Cumming... cumming! I'm cumming!
to capture the talented girls of our Academy,
A loli's bust feels the best!
and tormented them one after the other.
Onii-chan's dick is... hitting deep inside... over and over...
Take it out... No...
And finally it came to...
my best friend, Rayleigh.
They even took Kuro-chan.
Parasite's true objective was to find a worthy body to be its vessel.
Amazing, what a spectacular body!
And, after finding a worthy host,
Parasite took over Kuro-chan's body,
and took my virginity.
This must be karma.
My punishment for bringing such chaos to the peaceful academy.
Parasite continued unleashing its hidden powers.
It posessed all the male students,
and continued to disgrace the remaining female students.
Robbing them of their magical powers,
Onii-chan's dick is amazing...
to increase it's own strength even further.
I'm sorry...
It's all...
It's all my fault...
Our last hope is what remains
U-Unico... hold on... we can't...!
C-Concentrate!
No, not there! That place is...
It shouldn't be this...
A-Am I... about to lose again?
Your attitude is quite stern,
but your body is being brutally honest.
Looks like these guys are reaching their limit.
Won't you be their partner?
Your dick... feels good!
Let it out!
Let out lots of your thick semen inside Unico's tight pussy!
Amazing...
There's so much of this thick, syrupy stuff...
Parasite is able to help one realise their real desires.
There isn't anything more direct than the desires of a man.
Stop...
This...
Wait... that's...
How is it?
Are you ready to accept your fate as a whore?
Don't be foolish...
I will fight... till the end...
No... I'll break...
Such a huge cock is thrusting in and out of my pussy and my ass...
No... no... I'm going... crazy...
Make sure you use every part of their lustful body,
and squeeze out every drop of semen from their balls!
Cum inside...
Cum inside of me!
Cover Unico's small dlutty body with your dirty semen!
Fuck... Fuck... Fuck the shit out of me!
Cumming... I'm cumming!
Once penetrated by a person possessed by parasite,
regardless of how powerful you are magically, you can't help but lust for pleasure.
The half century we were sealed inside of this box...
It was long...
You! Damned witch!
No!
Look, she wet herself!
Don't look...
Well, have a look at this!
This witch marked herself in a spot like this!
P-please...
Please spare my son, at the very least!
Huh?
I-I'll do anything for him!
Please...
If you suck all our cocks, we'll consider it.
No way...
Is that so?
Guess we'll kill him too.
I-I understand...
It reeks...
It's because I haven't showered in while.
I haven't cleaned that area either.
Hey, you need to look after me as well.
I have to bear with it.
If it's for my child, this is nothing...
Mom...
I can't stand waiting in line for so long.
I'm have my way over here!
No, that side is...!
By the way, you're a widow right?
Aren't you frustrated that you haven't done it in such a long time?
N-No... that's not true...
Then how do you explain why,
your soaking wet pussy is wrapping around my cock so hard?
That's not... No... That's too rough!
Hey, bitch, don't forget about the cocks over here!
Wow, just what you'd expect from a widow!
She really knows how to handle a cock!
I'm... about to cum!
No... not inside!
That was so satisfying.
I haven't felt this good in a while so I went all out.
Is this part of your magical powers as a witch?
Magic? What else could it be!
We're not even close to finished!
Yo, bring the others!
We'll let everyone enjoy her!
S-Stop it...
You bastards...
Shut up!
I can't wait any longer.
Shall I enjoy her up here?
Let me rest! Even if it's for a bit!
All right, here I come!
No, that place is—
What are you talking about?
You think we'd let you get away with only your pussy torn up?
No...
A dick... is going so deep...
It's rubbing hard...
A dick she says!
I never thought I'd see a witch drooling like this with such an erotic face!
My asshole... feels amazing!
It's good!
She's started to move on her own.
She's really turned on now.
Cock... cock! Gimme some more of that cock!
Witch or not, she's just public pussy now!
Does it feel good? You perverted witch!
Yes... being penetrated in my pussy and my ass at the same time..
It's amazing!
This is the best!
I'm cumming!
Let it all out!
Spooge it all into me!
Cumming!
Amazing! So much of it is...
M-Mother...!
The hate of a young man, descended from a witch became a vortex,
and us parasites were born!
But humans ceased hunting witches and joined forces with them instead,
and thus, we were sealed inside this cursed box!
Now there is nothing left to stop us!
Your body has pretty good compatibility with demons.
For being so special, we'll use you as the host to give birth to new members of us!
We'll take over your consciousness then increase the reproductive ability of your body.
It's.. inside.
A tentacle cock is thrusting inside me...
It's reaching my womb...
A tentacle cock is having sex with me...
Amazing!
More! Give your body and mind to us and drown in the pleasure!
No!
Shut up!
Back down, bitch!
Such a dirty smell...
It's violating my nose...
Delicious...
The tentacle cocks...
They're so good...
It's coming out!
My dirty pussy is having so much semen cum inside from this tentacle cock!
No! Amazing... so hot!
Defile me!
Defile my body with your hot, thick semen!
You look amazing, even when broken.
Now, continue until you're pregnant!
Yes... fuck me up more and more!
Impregnate me!
My ass is being pulled apart...
Yes... stuff that tentacle cock in my ass...
My ass.. I love getting it fucked...
Amazing...
My pussy and my ass... getting fucked at the same time is amazing!
More...
Give me more of your thick semen in my mouth and on my tits...
The tentacles are going in... and out...
There's so much semen... it's making such lewd noises...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming while being surround by loads of tentacles and semen!
A-Again...
Sh-Shiro-chan...
Kuro-chan?!
Is that you Kuro-chan?!
Please, get back control over your body!
Shiro-chan...
Shiro-chan... I...
Kuro-chan's soul is still there...
She's still alive!
Kuro-chan was the first person to talk to me...
She's my one and only friend.
I must save her!
I have to save Rayleigh... I have to save Kuro-chan!
Huh? What is this?
This is...
Kuro-chan!
Sh-Shiro-chan...
This can't be! What just happened?!
I always thought this pendant was tied in with the curse from the box...
But in fact it's not!
What?!
This pendant was made in case this box ever opened...
The last, last hope!
Don't fuck with me!
I won't accept that! You hear me?!
Kuro-chan!
No... it's so slipper...
No... that place...
Too big...
I'll extinguish any hope you have,
and take your bodies away again!
My nipples... they're too sensitive...
If you rub.. or pull on them...
I'm...
Shiro-chan...
My body is covered in all this slimy stuff...
Deep... the tentacles are going so deep into my pussy and ass it's driving me crazy!
I can't hold on...
This time I'll have you together!
It's rubbing my pussy!
Shiro-chan...
Your nipples are... so hard...
Kuro-chan... no...
It feels so good!
Both of you look amazing as sluts!
Now, drown in my pleassure!
I'm.. going to cum soon...
I'm cumming!
So hot...
It's so hot...
The tentacle dick... is twitching...
It's cumming... I'll cum...
Sh-Shiro-chan...
Kuro-chan...
What?! What is this?!
This can't...
What just happened?
The demons... Parasite... just disappeared?
Everyone who was possessed seems to have fainted as well...
There's no presence of demons remaining at all!
What's going on?
I guess this is what you call a miracle, right?
After a month, our school finally returned to peace.
It's nice that it's peaceful again...
But why does it seem like the work at the Student Council just keeps piling up?!
Geez...
Just where did Shirley and Rayleigh go?!
They promised to help with the work!
Nurses' Office
I still think... this is wrong...
We're both girls...
Don't worry, it's fine...
I also...
Like Shiro-chan...
Shiro-chan...
Kuro-chan...
No... don't be so rough...
I'm jealous... Kuro-chan's boobs are so big...
But Shiro-chan's are so cute!
No... my nipples are... really sensitive...
Right there... it feels good...
Shiro-chans pussy is really wet with love juices...
Kuro-chan...
My clitoris... feels so hard...
When they rub together... it feels amazing!
No... Shiro-chan...
Shiro-chan... we've only known each other for such a short time...
I'm really glad I met you!
Me too... I'm glad I met Kuro-chan.
Shiro-chan... it feels good there..
More... rub me more there...
Amazing...
We're covered in our juices...
Our nipples are so hard...
It feels so good...
Kuro-chan...
I-I'm going to cum...
Me too...
Let's cum together... together...
Shiro-chan!
And so, I returned to being the librarian.
Unico!
Um.. did someone call out to me?
Did I just imagine it?
Unico... Unico!