I'm... I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Give it... Give it to me...
Give... Give it to me!
I'm... I'm cumming!
It's hot!
Stick it in deeper!
Yes! Amazing!
Asagi.
TAIMANIN ASAGI
VOL. 01 Ouboro's Counterattack
The Demon City Tokyo.
A place where humans and demons coexist.
There exists an unspoken rule, followed since ancient times,
that humans and demons will not interfere with one another.
However, with man's falling to the dark side...
There are now crime syndicates and corporations
forged by both humans and demons together.
No...
No!
Help me...
Someone, please...
Like I said...
Come on...
Yesterday the bodies of a young man and woman
believed to be in their twenties, were found.
It's suspected that these deaths are related to the string
of murders that have plagued Tokyo in recent months...
Nine of our people in a month?
They were all fairly experienced Anti-Demon Ninjas too.
Just like you.
Asagi... Can you come back?
I'd like for you to resolve this matter.
Asagi?
I'm sorry.
Did you possibly give up your devil fighting because of me...
I have no regrets.
That's good.
Meet me tomorrow at 7 at the restaurant.
I've already made reservations for 2.
Once I'm done with work I'll come over.
Okay.
I'll have something to give to you then.
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
Hey, hey! How did your date with Sawaki go?
What's wrong, did you get dumped?
No...
I didn't get to see him...
This is Sawaki, I'm unable to answer the phone right now.
If there's something you need to tell me,
please leave your name and message...
This is a criminal organization.
That man has probably been captured already;
it's possible that you're their next target.
Don't tell me...
because of me Kyousuke got involved.
White are you saying?
You must've messed up the location or time.
Hey, you have to get to school now.
Yeah, yeah. I'm going.
Have a nice trip.
Onee-chan...
Looks like he came to visit you.
The car's there, looks like he went to the dojo already.
Good luck.
Kyousuke!
What happened yesterday?
Sorry, I forgot my cell phone.
Idiot! You should have at least called me.
If something had happened to you, I-
I've finally gathered enough courage to tell you this.
We can have a real engagement, not just one in name...
Kyousuke...
I want you to marry me.
Asagi!
I'm sorry for always making you worry.
No, I'm very happy.
There's definitely a youma around. Could
it have been following Kyousuke?
Who's there?
Oboro?
Long time no see, Asagi.
Wh... So you're still alive?
Die, Asagi!
I was sure that that time you fell you were done for.
I wanted to see you again.
So I allowed a youma into my body in order to stay alive.
A youma, you say!?
I used its strength to crush your friends like insects.
This was all done to draw you out.
Then I just need to defeat you again!
What's wrong?
My body is...
Run, Kyousuke!
You still haven't noticed? Asagi.
What?
You are already under my spell.
Just like the other men here.
Come over here, Kyousuke.
This is my ninja magic
The minute you put on that ring you were finished.
Kyousuke! Kyousuke!
Your target and objective is me.
Kyousuke has nothing to do with this.
From now on, this is mine.
He doesn't seem to be complaining either.
No way!
This is quite healthy, isn't it?
Asagi, this isn't what I want.
What's wrong? Has Asagi done this to you yet?
Kyousuke!
It's not that hard yet?
Really, what a shameless dick.
After such stimulation,
I'm... getting turned on.
How is it? Are you reaching your limit?
Oboro, you...!
Please stop!
I can't hold back anymore, I'm going to cum.
It's inside, your dick is inside me.
How wonderful...
Your dick's amazing...
Your dick feels amazing!
Inside... Your dick...
It's inside me!
No!
Kyousu-
More, more!
It feels great... Your cock... So good...
No matter what, you have to cum inside.
Look at Asagi now.
She's a real slut.
Continue fucking her in the mouth.
It's okay to cum inside.
Give me... your cum!
Don't look over here...
No...
What's wrong, feeling really dirty now?
Shoot it all into that cock-sucking slutty ninja.
I'm cumming. Shoot it!
Shoot all deep inside my vagina!
It's okay to shoot it.
Shoot it all inside me!
Fill me up!
Do it! Cum inside me!
Stop... Stop it...
No!
Give it to me!
Shoot it... inside!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming, too!
How wonderful...
Wonderful... It's coming out.
Inside... It's coming out inside me.
Cum... It's shooting out.
Amazing.
Asagi, this man isn't bad.
He came twice in a row.
Asagi...
Asagi, wake up!
Kyousuke... Kyousuke...
Asagi is a very slutty woman.
Give it to me!
It feels amazing!
Fill me up... in my pussy...
Pitiful... What a shameful sight, Asagi.
No one has ever escaped without having
their body altered by this flesh prison.
I'll make you sluttiest woman, Asagi.
Will it work as planned?
The drugs are rewriting her cells at a genetic level.
Her sense of touch will be increased by about 3000 times.
If it were an ordinary woman.
The slightest touch will send her into a climax.
I can't wait to see it...
Asagi transforming into an object for men's pleasure.
Inside... I'm splitting up inside...
It's tearing me up inside...
It's so... It's so embarrassing!
I'm... I'm leaking!
I like this... I'm loving this...
It's no good... I can't take it anymore...
I'm... I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
It's so strong!
Please... Let's...
Let's... Together...
Together... Cum!
Cum together with me!
Inside... Cum inside...
Inside my womb... Cum...
Cum inside me!
No... Inside...
Cum inside me!.
So good...
I can feel it inside...
I'm... I'm...
Cumming!
These past few days have really been interesting, Asagi.
You can cum as many times as you want, Asagi...
How is it?
How does it feel to have your entire body turned into a pussy?
What's wrong Asagi-tan?
Don't tell me you just came?
You, perverted female ninja.
Does it feel good?
Doesn't it feel good when I hit you?
Cumming?
Are you cumming?
You should be feeling it.
Cum Asagi!
Come on! Come on!
Cum already! Come on!
You guys can do whatever you want now.
Are you really going to let us do anything we want?
Fill this slutty woman with your cum down to the very last drop.
So you guys better make sure you don't waste any.
Who... Who would want to fuck you guys...
Clean it with your mouth!
How wonderful.
It's just like a pussy.
I can't hold back anymore, come on!
OK, I'm next!
This is great! Come on, suck my cock!
It's so fucking tight!
l'm cumming!
Come on, show the ores your face.
Not bad, Asagi. You can bear the ore's children.
Suck them completely dry with your pussy.
Stop it, please...
Stop it!
No! I don't want it!
No... No!
It feels great, the suction!
I'm cumming, cumming!
No... Don't...
N-No... No!
No...
I'm breaking... I'm breaking!
I'm... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Pl... Please... Please...
I'm... I'm cimming...
Now the Arena events will surely be a huge success.
Black-sama will also be pleased.