Boss...
You made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
Fucking Shinichirou, Koutarou's son, has Fire Bee.
What do you think about the efficiency of Fire Bee?
Answer the question!
So far, she's not ready to go as our main weapon.
I can't believe she is Fire Bee.
Good morning!
Ramune in the morning is a very tasty dish.
Uh. Fucking Morizaki!
He made the machine a little too sensitive.
The National Army's secret weapon is now a waitress?
I'll give you one more chance.
Complete the rescue operation!
I'll do anything to get what I want now.
If Morizaki's son is against us, kill him.
Don't forget. Your sister's life is in my hands.
Yes.
Only Fire Bee....
If I could get Fire Bee, the Fire Dragon project would be completed.
If so, we won't have any more enemies.
Moke Moke Taishou Dendo Musume Arisa Vol.2
Hey, do you happen to have an omelette fried rice plate prepared?
Okay, a little bit more...
How about some curry rice?
One minute!
Master... additionally, a cutlet and a hamburger steak, A set each, please.
Okay.
But I need more helpers.
I know it, but...
Yuuri is busy in school, and Kotomi is sick.
So, I need to work harder.
Arisa... not yet?
Yes... right away...
Hey, Shinichirou.
I'm sorry, but I don't have time to play with you today.
I didn't come here to play with you.
What, Saya?
If you need a helper...
I thought I could be...
Saya, don't you have a fever?
I'm doing you a favor!
Wow! Saya, you're going to help us?
Thank you.
Uh, no. That's only if you and Shinichirou are okay with me...
Of course!
Okay? Master?
Well, we need the help, so...
Okay, please.
Saya, you're cute.
You think so?
It's true, ''fine feathers make fine birds.''
Okay, I want you to work hard, Saya.
If Morizaki's son is against us, kill him.
I want to avoid having to do that.
Please come in.
May I take your order?
Um... a cup of coffee, please.
Okay.
Why is Saya?..
Kotomi is sick now.
Really? Is she okay?
Kotomi, you don't need to pretend that you're ok.
I wonder if I made her work too hard.
I hope she gets better soon.
I miss Yuuri too.
I have to find a means to...
Thanks for your help.
We need to help each other.
You can help us tomorrow as well.
What? Are you sure? I can help you?
Of course you can.
Now that's very kind of you.
Okay, so... see you tomorrow.
Oh, thank you.
Good bye.
Bye.
Yuuri, why?
Let's cum together...
No.
Brother...
Kotomi. May I come in?
I brought dinner for you.
Thank you.
I enjoyed dinner very much.
It was very appetizing.
You're welcome.
It's an honor to be your sister.
What?
I lost both of my parents during the earthquake 7 years ago.
And I met my brother when I was alone...
Since then, I've been living with my brother and his family at the restaurant...
My father was always away with the army.
And, my mother has passed away...
Brother, don't abandon me.
Never. I will always be your brother, Kotomi.
Kotomi?
Promise me...
Kotomi...
Kotomi.
Ah, brother!
Brother...
It's my turn.
You have pre-cum already.
Ah...
Brother...
Oh god... I'm cumming...
Thanks a lot for your help. I'm cool now.
Wow! It was my pleasure!
Okay, so I don't need to help you anymore?
If Kotomi helps you....
No, Saya! Please help us!
Kotomi...
Brother?
Yuuri is not back yet, and...
Of course.
Okay. Let's take a vacation and go somewhere together tomorrow.
Wow! We're going out together.
I want to go to a park where things go 'round and 'round...
Ah, you're talking about an amusement park.
That's it! You call it an amusement park.
But I don't have the right clothes.
No problem. I'll lend you my clothes.
Kotomi...
So, let's finish today's work first.
Amusement park... what a treat.
Ah... Great!
There are horses going around.
Arisa, don't get lost in the park.
It's not easy to walk in these clothes. I'm not used to it.
Really? But, Saya, you're looking so good.
Seriously though?
Um... Yeah.
Really?
I didn't know Saya could look so feminine.
Oh, Master!
I want to ride on this horsey.
Brother, Saya, Let's go.
Now that was some good fun!
Arisa.
Yuuri! You came back!
Yes. I came from Asakusa.
Nice to see you again.
I'm going to bring master.
Ah, wait, Arisa.
What's wrong?
Well...
Uh, I'm thirsty. You don't want a Ramune?
Wow! Ramune? Let's go!
Well it's kind of scary.
Uh, this is nothing.
Where is Arisa?
She finished the ride first.
Fuck...
I'm going to look for her.
Oh, thank you.
Pooh... shua, shua...
Yeah, if you like it, you can drink more...
Yes! I'm going to drink it all down.
Arisa!
Saya.
Yuuri is back!
Arisa!
Oh, shit!
Hey, man, leave Saya alone!
Master! We've got a problem.
Yuuri, you...
Okay.
I'll proceed with the second contact.
No, Shinichirou. I...
You guys!
This is a direct order from our boss, Ryugasaki.
This is not what we had arranged.
Morizaki Shinichirou, bring Fire Bee here at midnight.
If you don't, she'll be killed.
Ryugasaki Daimon!
Do you know him, grandpa?
Yeah. He, Koutarou and I were studying the electric doll together.
He is a vengeful man...
Arisa.. I am a weapon, aren't I?
I'm going to see some soldiers.
No, I don't think this is really a place for me.
Don't be a fool!
What?
You're not a weapon!
You're a part of our family.
Master...
I won't let the army do whatever they want to Arisa, Saya or Yuuri.
Brother...
Koutarou and I didn't want to make an electric doll as a weapon.
Grandpa...
We were making the doll in order to stop the war, but Ryunosaki refused it.
Koutarou disappeared after he destroyed all the materials about the study.
I see.
Shinichinou...
Hold on, Saya and Yuuri.
I'm disappointed with you, Yuuri.
Boss, how should we treat them?
Okay...
Now...
What are you going to do?
No! Stop it!
Get off me!
Keep quiet!
No!
Saya!
No, don't touch me!
Wow, It's still hard...
Let me see your pussy... it must be cute...
Stop it!
No!
Wow, you must be a virgin.
I'm sorry, Saya and everyone...
Grandpa, are you sure it's okay?
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
Kotomi and I will take care of this!
Grandpa...
There is a secret army base underground.
Both Saya and Yuuri should be there.
Move quickly.
I'm going!
Kotomi, right here!
Okay!
Shit! It's a huge base!
Where are Saya and Yuuri?
There!
Here is Fire Bee!
Oh, shit! Fire Bee made a raid on!
Arisa...
Master... I seem to be a weapon...
Stop it!
Saya's voice!
This way!
What?
Oh, shit. We gave Fire Bee clearance to enter the base.
Hurry, bring Fire Dragon in!
Okay, let's go all the way....
Ah! No!
Be quiet!
It hurts! Stop it!
Saya...
Hold still...
Fuck you!
I was scared.
Saya...
I won't ever forgive them.
I'm sorry, that's my fault.
Tell me about it me later!
Let's get out first!
What?
What happened?
Brother!
Oh... good.
Okay, grandpa, let's get out now.
What? Where is Arisa?
What the heck....she got lost again?
It's Daimon!
Fire Bee!
And I will show them no mercy.
Arisa!
Master, I'm going to destroy all of our enemies.
No, you can't... even though you're...
Arisa...
Everyone, thank you very much.
I won't forget any of you.
This is what Koutarou was looking for...
Arisa, you must come back to us.
We're going to be waiting for you at your home.
Promise me!
There's Fire Bee ahead.
Fire Bee... how frustrating, but...
it's easy to clean up enemies on the ground if we have Fire Dragon, even though it's still incomplete.
Shoot it down!
Um, shoot it down!
I'm going to shoot, too.
It doesn't affect you at all?
You can't!
I won't give up!
Fire Bee is coming!
Her name is Arisa.
It's Shua, Shua.
I like that!
Thank you... master...
What? Oh, my God...
Arisa!
Shit!
What's the matter, brother?
Again!
Arisa!
Master!
Dream?
Master, I'm back!