And now, let the deathmatch begin!
TAIMANIN ASAGI
Vol. 04           Dansing Ninjas of the Dark
What do you think of their popularity?
For the past few days, the show has been a huge success...
Especially the gangbang part...
Now we're a step closer to your ambitions.
What about Asagf?
Just leave her to me.
Don't worry about it, the ores will take care of them.
The deathmatch between them is the best main event we've ever had.
You're an excellent dog.
I'm cumming-
Oboro.
Yes?
Don't you think that Anti-Demon Ninja is beautiful?
Black-sama...
It would be a waste to just kill her off.
I want Asagi to join our organization.
W-What are you talking about!?
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I object!
I can't agree to this!
Who knows if they'll betray us-
No, I didn't mean to disagree.
Oboro, you truly are amazing.
Thank you very much.
However...
It's no good to remain in the organization just for revenge.
T-That's not-
Remember the oath you swore to continue living as a demon.
Remember those days.
Oboro!
If you devote your body to me, I will
let you live as a demon once again.
I have always been faithful to the organization!
So please, don't ever send me back there again!
Oboro.
Asagi will be your comrade from now on.
Black-sama!
Please excuse me for the intrusion, Black-sama.
There might be trouble waiting for us if the arena events continue.
The organization's aim is world domination.
Those Anti-Demon Ninjas were taken as prisoners
simply due to my own curiosity.
I want to see the outcome of the battle with my very own eyes.
Do you fuckheads plan on betraying me?
Don't think you'll get away with this!
Don't touch me, you disgusting bastards!
No...
Stop it...
It hurts...
I was raped by monsters... I was once dead...
This is nothing compared to that!
Oboro, serves you right.
Now you can feel what I feel.
Asagi, It's all your fault that I'm being punished.
I never thought he would take you into our organization.
What did you say?
But it's already too late.
My revenge is already complete.
All that's left is the deathmatch between the both of you.
Hopefully Asagi dies here, or gets killed by her sister later on.
Oboro, you bitch!
W-What!?
Asagi.
Black?
I'll make your wish come true.
Wish?
To fight with Oboro.
Is Black-sama really serious about letting Asagi join us?
If that happens, my status in the organization...
Onee-chan, fight seriously.
I want you to get out of here, even without me.
I still haven't given up hope of getting us both out.
However...
The audience might go on a rampage if
they have to wait until the fight's over.
My body...
Time's up! This is a draw!
Oboro, what are you scheming?
Please look forward to the special match tonight.
If both of you win against him, both of you can leave.
What!?
My dear audience, I now present to you.
the deathmatch of the survivors.
Let the battle commence.
Kyousuke, this is your final match. Good luck.
Oboro, are you fucking with me?
No!
Fuck her until she's dead.
I'm cumming...
Right now. Kill her right now!
Come on, you monster.
Kill her. It's in your blood.
Asagi...
Asagi!
Kyousuke! You're still in there?
There's not much time left.
Listen up.
Everything is part of the Elder's...
Elder's?
Asagi! Kill me while I'm still in control!
Kyousuke...
If you don't...
Please, Asagi! Do it!
Kyousuke, I love you.
Now there's nothing left to stop me.
You're up next, Oboro!
Black-sama!
Stop right there.
I'm sorry but I don't think I can satisfy you with just this.
It's unfortunate, Asagi.
Are you just going to stand there after stirring all this up?
Take a look at the arena.
Black-sama...
Don't you want to kill Asagi, Oboro?
So it's fine to just kill her, right?
I'll leave the Japan HQ to you if you win against Asagi.
Black, I want to use the Anti-Demon Sword.
Fine.
I will avenge Kyousuke.
You're merely just a human, do you really think you can defeat me?
Both of you, fight your hearts out.
One of you must fall tonight in this arena...
In this arena where reality and illusion intersect
I never thought I'd get the chance to defeat you again.
I'll have to thank Black for giving me this opportunity.
Don't get so cocky.
Die, Asagi!
The winner is decided.
The Anti-Demon Sword is made specifically
for fighting against demons.
The immortality a demon receives after
selling their soul is only temporary.
The slowness in your movements proves my point.
N-No way...
Black-sama...
Beautiful!
I've lived for centuries and it's my first time seeing someone like you.
Asagi, will you join my side?
What do you think!?
Getting cocky after defeating a demon who has died once already?
Your Anti-Demon Sword is useless against me.
And I don't have the time to play with you.
So you're not going to fight?
I'm leaving Japan soon.
Even though it's been a very short time, you've entertained me a lot.
May I ask you a question?
What is your objective?
What is the true goal of the Vampires?
I don't answer questions of humans who have short lifespans.
You'll understand if you receive immortality.
Immortality?
I'm a bit sad.
I look forward to the next time we meet.
Onee-chan, you defeated Oboro, right?
Kyousuke is dead.
Onee-chan...
Come in.
We're back, Elder.
Asagi?
Why did you come?
In order to defeat Oboro, clearing my past and birth as
an Anti-Demon Ninja and deploying Sawaki Kyousuke.
You're behind all that, am I correct?
What makes you think that?
Kyousuke told me right before he died.
Under the codes of the Anti-Demon
Ninjas, I will pass judgment on you.
You'll make yourself an enemy of the state if you kill me.
That won't happen.
I won't be the one who kills you.
Anti-Demon Ninja Sakura is delivering your
punishment under the government's name.
I don't fight for anyone.
I'm not doing this for the sake of anyone.
I'm simply just striding forward on this thorny path of carnage.