Oh no, what time is it?!
All right...
I'm Mayuko Arisugawa.
l recently decided to stop being exploited by everyone like a machine.
l feel bad for the real machines if that's what it's like!
Sorry, l was running a little late!
Good morning, Mayu.
You're late! We started cleaning up without you.
And these are my lovely sisters-in-arms.
The always stylish and academically successful lzumi Moriyama,
and the always upbeat girl who loves to eat, Usagi Hanao.
The three of us, using the power of mysterious pendants,
formed a corps that repairs broken machines that have been thrown away.
It's a great job, isn't it?
Oh, and then there's Tsutomu.
We accidentally let that jerk know our secret.
No!
But we got over that and now the three of us are doing the best we can!
So, what will we be repairing today?
Welcome!
WE'LL FIX THAT FOR YOU!
No...
ls that good?
Do you like it?
Do you like it...
So, for whatever reason, today our corps finds itself on the Silk Road.
But no matter what situation we find ourselves in, we'll do the repairs!
It's frigging hot! Let's take a break.
Shut up, you're the one who's riding on a horse!
Riding on a horse doesn't lessen the pain at all.
My butt hurts, my back hurts...
I'm thirsty and hungry!
What a pain!
It's Mayu's fault for being late!
I'm hungry, too.
Now that you mention it, it is taking her a lot of time to go shopping.
But we've almost made it to town, so let's just grin and bear it till then.
No! l can't make it another step.
Me neither!
I'm starving, lzumi!
Because she's the only one who can fly,
l bet she's just taking her sweet time somewhere!
l know it's a little heavy, but you can do it.
He's a horse, he's fine.
Ah, I'm in Heaven! Heaven!
Now, on we go!
Come on! Move!
We'll cut you into horse sushi and eat you!
What do you think you're doing?!
Oh, that was quick, we can see the town already.
We should have been doing this from the start.
Come one, come all!
We've got some great vegetables!
Oh boy! That looks delicious!
Come back again now, okay?
I'll throw in something extra next time.
I'll be back tomorrow, then. Until then.
Thank you very much.
Where's Master going?
The bathroom, maybe?
Welcome.
I'm glad you've come to Nyan-nyan Spa.
Spa?
That is correct.
Why don't you rest from your journey alongside our lovely girls?
Yeah, pampering yourself once in a while isn't bad at all.
What? You two are here, too?
Anyway, I'll buy what you're selling!
Right this way, then.
Have you made your decision?
Yes, yes! This girl's the one!
Ah, most certainly. Thank you.
Please wait in the spa room, then.
Darn it! I'm running so late.
l just couldn't make it until l got home, okay?
I'm only gonna have one.
Huh? That's odd.
They should be wandering around here still.
And l bought all these pork buns too, sheesh!
I'm eating them all now!
That... That feels great!
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
l...
No, it's fine!
Just use the tip of your tongue, okay?
Like this?
ls that okay?
Yes, yes, that's the ticket.
Does that feel good?
I've never been to a spa like this before.
Now, now... Let's take those off.
Ah, so smooth!
ls this how you want it?
Raise your butt up a little.
I'm so nervous...
Yes, just like that!
Now, open your pussy up with your fingers.
Yes, sir.
Oh, sweet Lily...
Do you feel that, too?
ls that good? ls it great?
ls it the best?
What am l saying?
That's no good, Lily!
You need to express your pleasure more openly.
Like, ''Ahhhhh!''
But sir, l have to service you.
Just let me pleasure your body.
How does that feel, sir?
Like I've died and gone to Heaven!
ls that where they are?
Now then, l have to search for those three.
Lily... l... l need a break...
l was about to blow my load.
Now, it's time for the other hole.
But that's not...
It will be fine!
I'll be gentle.
Not in my butt...
No!
No, stop!
It's fine! Fine, l tell you! Fine!
You'll break me!
What happened all of a sudden?
How does that feel, miss?
Miss, how does that feel?
It feels great!
Bingo!
No, I'm gonna pee!
I'm gonna...
Miss, this is part of today's service package.
No...
No!
A..Amazing!
Geez, at least give the horse some water.
l feel bad for him.
They're gonna work him to death.
So, let's see, they said it was Room 202...
Ah, here it is! Found it.
Master, I'm back.
Not here, l guess.
Help me!
Master!
You whore!
Hope you're ready!
Welcome.
You are here for the C Course, correct?
Miss, please just allow me to pleasure your body.
St..Stop!
Does that feel good, miss?
Now!
Sh..She's an android?!
lzumi?!
l..l can't take any more!
Off of her!
Ow...
Mayu!
Did l interrupt something?
Go, go nyoi-nyoi-nyan staff!
Miss, please just allow me to pleasure your body.
ls their service program on the fritz?
l need to stop her without breaking her!
l hope Mayu's okay.
Wait!
Pardon me...
l said wait!
Please stop.
No!
Miss, you must stay perfectly still.
Mayu, these girls are most likely...
Yup, androids.
And they weren't being taken care of by the humans very well, l bet.
Also...
They seem to be in pain.
So, is it our turn now?
But before that...
I'm in Heaven...
Usagi! Usagi! Wake up!
It's time to get to work.
She won't wake up at all.
Guess it can't be helped, geez.
Here.
Ow, ow, ow!
It's time for work, Usagi.
Th..This is...
l know it's been rough for you guys until now,
but it's fine now.
This time...
...we will...
...repair...
...you!
I'll make you feel even better.
It's so big...
l thought l had met my match.
Now then, ready to finish them off?
They're beautiful.
Now they're back to their old selves again.
Ah, my most sincere apologies. I'm so sorry.
l will make sure something like that never happens again.
It's okay, we believe you. You can stop bowing now.
My goodness! Androids have hearts too, you know!
You'd better remember that or you'll have trouble again.
Right, I'll do as you say.
Be sure to take really good care of yourselves, maids.
Just like us, work really hard to become professional repair artists!
We will!
Bye-bye! We'll come back sometime.
Let's go, Usagi.
Huh? Hey, wait for me!
What the hell happened here?
Hey, lzumi! lzumi!
You aren't here?
Usagi!
Geez, where the hell did they run off to?
By the way, where's Master?
Oh dear, we forgot about him.
Do you really mind?
He's too loud, anyway.
That's true.
Hey, by the way,
why are we leaving town when the sun's about to set?
l hate sleeping outdoors.
Oh, that is true.
Well, whatever, l can just sleep on the nimbus cloud when l need to.
That's not fair!
It's fine.
We'll be at the next town in no time.
Really?
Really.
Yay!
I'm in Heaven!
No... I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's pulsating!
I've died and gone to Heaven.