Right now, we're above Asakusa Park
Estimated passing time is 8:26 p.m.
Repeat. This is Daizero, the ship, Torikago.
Right now, we're above Asakusa Park. Estimate passing time is 8:26 p.m.
But, I don't know why we're using this ship just for one load.
What's the cargo?
According to a rumor, old Morizaki factory developed a new weapon.
Hey, hope it's not something scary.
There is air turbulence ahead.
Bow up 4 degrees!
Okay!
Moke Moke Taishou Dendo Musume Arisa Vol.1
Thank you very much.
Brother, I'm done.
Okay, I'm almost finished, too.
Brother, hurry!
Don't rush me! The food won't disappear.
Because...
You're still a kid...
But, she'll be quiet if she gets food.
See, you always treat me like a kid.
Like before, when I was cleaning a glass window on a chair, you called me a little girl.
Let's dig in...
What's that noise?
What's this?
Earthquake?
Don't worry. Let's finish.
Let's dig in....
Ummm, Kotomi....are you okay?
Are you okay, brother?
Ah...I'm okay. Are you okay?
Brother, look...
Yeah, it's a girl.
She is a little different from you, Kotomi.
You're a leech!
What? What happened?
Grandpa.
Are you okay, Kotomi?
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
Hey, Shinichirou!
What are you doing in front of your little sister?
Grandpa, it's not that.
Did you hear the huge noise?
Then, the girl may have come from the sky.
The girl from the sky?
I wonder if....
Yeah, that's right.
What?
It's an electric doll.
Electric doll?
Which my father was studying...
That's right.
The shape is a little different, but Koutaro and I were studying this.
Fuck father...
He left us besides and he was studying this stuff....
I told you many times. You shouldn't curse your own father.
I know it. But, grandpa, does she move?
I think so.
There must be a switch somewhere.
It must be somewhere...
Look for it.
The switch must be the tip of something. It must be easy to find, but....
There is no such thing.
Oh, she moved!
Ah, no...
Shit...did I break it?
Starting....
Oh, it's moving!
Starting... checking.... okay ... registration starts.
Please register your user name by a voice input.
Register user name?
Well, say your name.
Okay, Morizaki... Morizaki Shinichirou.
Checking... visual and sound... registration complete.
Be quiet!
Ah, master.
Just call my name and I'll be there.
Cooking, cleaning, washing anything you want! I'm a super girl!
I'm a precocious, cute and lovely girl.
My heart is beating strongly with eager anticipation.
I'm Arisa, the last angel on the earth!
Because of you, I'm here!
Too long...
Grandpa, why don't you dismantle her and use the parts for a clock.
I'm going home now.
Ah! No! Master!
My lord! Please, mercy! Mercy!
Parts? Wow, he has such expensive stuff...
Ah....what should I do?
My mother left me the store...
Hi, master.
Hi, brother. Brother, her name is Arisa.
Why are you here? And now you get along with Kotomi.
You're bad. You registered your name.
My role is to serve you, master.
That's right, brother.
I heard it from Arisa.
Brother, you need to be serious.
I registered, but...
And Arisa is the electric doll which your father was studying for.
She doesn't have anywhere to go. There is no problem to stay with us.
That's a different story.
No, ah...Kotomi...
I was lonely.
But since I live with my brother, I have been happy.
Arisa is also the same.
Kotomi...
I got it.
I let her work, living with us.
Brother, thank you.
Wow, my master, thank you very much.
You're lucky, Arisa.
Yes, thank you for having me.
Okay, Arisa, can you help me to clean up the store?
Yes.
Girl is...
Formidable...
Now, three of us have started living together, but...
How many times do you need to do it better?
I'm sorry.
You drop water and break a plate.
You can't cook. You can't clean up well.
You can't go shopping.
Are you useless?
I'm going to trash you.
I don't have anywhere to go if you trash me, master.
Hey, don't cry, you're a machine.
Brother, you're too harsh with her.
Arisa is trying her best at least.
I'm going shopping now.
Yeah.
Bathtub is ready. Take a bath.
Okay, see you.
Arisa!
I'm sorry.
Whew, wow, I'm so glad to take a bath so early.
The machine also feels sad....
I was a little harsh with her.
Master!
What are you doing?
I was always making troubles, so I would like to wash your back.
Don't look.
Master, how do you like it?
Do you feel good?
Ah...
Don't you feel good?
Good, I feel good.
Arisa... she has such big breasts...
Master, I want to serve for you.
What?
Hey Arisa!
Master, did you feel good?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Be sure to collect ''Fire Bee'' back.
Otherwise, your sister going to be a doll instead of ''Fire Bee.''
I understand it.
I'm counting on you. Don't make a mistake.
I'm sure going to collect ''Fire Bee.''
There's so many things I haven't seen before.
Arisa, looks like she's having fun.
When you think about her, she is also misfortune.
She doesn't know why she was made.
When she woke up, we were in front of her.
But, we're not strangers anymore.
I know that.
Master!
Can you buy this for me?
It's very pretty.
Oh, my...
Are you dumb?
Master, what do you call this?
We call it Ramune.
I wonder if your fuel is that....
Ramune...
Shua, shua... it's very delicious.
Starting today this is my only food.
So far, so good, with three of us, but...
Arisa has done nothing as usual.
I can't stand anymore!
I don't see her progressing at all.
I have been so busy lately, but she still makes trouble.
But, are you sure you need helpers?
I don't have a choice.
Arisa is useless.
She also makes you trouble...
But...
Ah... We're going to close today.
Ah... I saw the ad in front of...
The ad? Helper wanted?
Yes. My name is Ayase Yuuri.
I don't have any experience, but I'll try my best.
Okay. you got it.
That was fast!
Thank you very much.
And I need to ask you a favor....
I don't mind.
There are extra rooms upstairs, so you can use any one you like.
Is it okay, Kotomi?
Yeah...
Really? Thank you very much.
Well, I also thank you!
A lady who goes to Seiryu Girl School can work for us.
Lady... me?
She is Fire Bee...
Kotomi, please teach me everything.
Yes. Ask me anything!
She is different...
Our store has been getting better since Yuuri came.
Arisa is still a trouble, but she's getting used to it.
Ah... I feel good now.
I took a bath.
I need to ask Kotomi to shop for me, and I'll go to bed.
Yes. I found the girls we're looking for.
Yes. I understand.
Yuuri... who is she speaking with?
There is no telephone in this room...
Yes...
At this time, it's not possible to make sure if she really is Fire Bee...
Yes, but...
That's the communication device which my father had for the army.
Um? Is she...a soldier? Not school girl? Is she lying?
I copy that.
I'm going to see them tonight.
Okay, I'm going to begin with.
Kotomi, I have something to discuss with you.
May I come in?
Yes, please.
Did you wake up? Kotomi?
What are you going to do?
What is she going to do?
She said something about a second contact.
Kotomi, I have something to make sure.
Please cooperate with me.
Don't be afraid too much.
You're very cute, Kotomi.
Let me see your private parts.
I'm going to make you feel better with this.
Did you feel good?
Yes...
Can you make me feel good next time, Kotomi?
Here... lick my pussy...
Yes...
Kotomi, you don't need to hold anything.
This is the finish.
Okay, wake up... Fire Bee.
Let's go together.
No... this reaction is about humans.
She is not Fire Bee.
Oh! Is it possibly...
that girl...
Oh shit!
Who is Yuuri?
I can't sleep like this...
I'm going to drink...
35, 36, 37, 38...
Good morning, Yuuri.
Good morning.
Morning Ramune is very delicious.
Arisa, you shouldn't drink only Ramune even though you're a machine.
A machine?
According to Gen grandpa, I am an android for the army.
Right, Gen grandpa?
Yeah, that's right.
What? I didn't tell you so, Yuuri?
No, you didn't.
Yuuri, what's the matter?
Why didn't you tell me before!
I couldn't sleep anyway