And now an update:
For the past several days the dismembered bodies of young
men and women have been found outside the city;
The families of the deceased are asking the citizens
of the city for help and are offering a reward...
The demon city: Tokyo.
Humans and all manner of demons live together here,
and as an Anti-Demon Ninja,
I have fought criminal organizations and companies created
by an unholy alliance between men and demons.
Onee-chan... I'm coming for you.
TAIMANIN ASAGI
VOL. 02        Prison Rape Arena
The demon city of Tokyo seemed to be once again at peace;
but one of these organizations plotted to captured me.
My body has been sexually modified and I have
been forced to fight here in the Chaos Arena.
Onee-chan?
Unfortunately, Sakura, we lost contact with her two days ago.
No...
Most likely she has fallen into an enemy trap.
Elder!
I am giving you two missions: first, to infiltrate the enemy
base and gather all the information you can;
Second: to rescue the captured Asagi.
That is all.
Onee-chan wouldn't lose to somebody like that!
This... This is...
Die, Asagi!
Sawaki!
What are you doing here?
I came to save you and my sister!
Sawaki, no...
You...
Stop it!
No, stop! It'll never fit!
Stop it! Stop!
No...
No!!
S... Stop...
My pussy... It's going to break!
Hey, she's cumming!
No way, really? What a maso-bitch!
Hey, look at that!
She's really a masochist!
She must've lost the fight on purpose!
She'll love it no matter what you put in her!
No...
That's... That's not true.
Damn, that's hilarious!
It doesn't, feel good!
Man, I want a piece of that!
Stop it!
Put it in her! Put it in Asagi-chan!
Wow, look at how wide it is!
That's amazing!
Amazing! Amazing!
Pervert! Asagi-chan is a pervert!
It's coming out!
You don't have time to just lie there!
Oboro, I'm going to kill you.
So there's enough left in you to talk, eh?
That's good to hear.
Let me introduce you: this is Ou-chan, he's a big fan of yours.
He has infinite stamina and thinks of nothing
but continuing to rape a woman.
Everyone he fucks end up breaking.
He says he can't hold back after watching that fight.
Come on, it looks like she'd love to make you cum.
Make her scream!
A monster...
Stop it, please!
No! Stop it!
No!!
Too late.
Nobody can stop him now!
How is he?
Feels pretty good, huh?
Expanding inside of you...
You're already feeling it.
That's my ero-ninja!
She's loving it!
Stick it in her!
No...
This is...
No!!
It hurts...
I'm... cummmg...
No! No!
No! No! No!
Oh look, he's going to cum.
Go for it.
Fill her up!
My, my... He's cumming!
Wow...
Good news, Asagi.
He says he'll look after you for the rest of your life.
Look he really likes you!
Hey! Do it harder!
My, how filthy you look.
I never knew you were such a filthy slut...
Even I'm impressed.
How awful...
You're even worse than he is.
Cumming! Cumming!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!!
What is this?
You're finally awake?
You're...
I never thought Asagi's sister would come here.
Yes.
My name is Oboro; your sister cut off my head once.
But I lowered myself to the demon world, and survived,
You're sister Asagi... No, I've come back to take
my revenge against all Anti-Demon Ninjas...
With the help of this man, Sawaki Kyousuke! Asagi's former fiance!
You bitch!
What did you do to him?
You demon, give me back my sister.
Turn him back to normal!
You're great.
love you.
Then I'll have to give you a reward.
Stop it, what are you doing?
What?
I'm going to give you a nice body that'll
make the men happy, just like Asagi.
You'll never get rid of all the men around you.
You'll be everyone's idol.
That's right... You'll be an angel!
I'll let you meet Asagi soon.
You'll both appear as the warriors of love.
How is it?
The response is good; adjusting output to +20.
I'm detecting damage to her chest area.
Continue!
Yes.
Adjusting output to +24.
More!
Yes.
Amazing!
They're like butter!
All changes complete. It will last for two to three days.
That's more than enough time.
I've got a special event for you, Asagi.
Hey, what's that?
A punishment game?
What's going to happen?
Now then everyone, I've prepared a special punishment
game for today's pathetic loser, Asagi.
The girl you see on the monitor is her little sister,
Sakura, who came here to rescue Asagi.
Wow, she's got huge tits!
I'd love to fuck her!
Onee-chan...
How about a rape show where her virginity is
cruelly stolen from her in front of her sister?
Please, Oboro.
Don't hurt my sister!
In her place, I'll...
All right then.
I'll give you a special chance.
No way; with everybody here?
Promise me you won't touch Sakura!
I'm first!
No, I'm first!
I'm!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan!
Yes.
It's great.
More, more!
Hot!
This is awesome.
This girl's amazing; she's soaking wet just from sucking me.
Seriously?
What a dirty bitch!
Ero-kunoichi!
I'm cummmg!
Swallow it!
She's loving it!
She came while swallowing it!
Oboro's personal slut!
Get her!
Fuck her brains out!
Onee-chan... Onee-chan!
Thanks to this girl, everybody chose Asagi, Kyousuke.
You comfort him instead.
Stop it, Sawaki!
Don't do this! My sister will be sad!
Stop it!
It hurts!
No... No...
He isn't the Sawaki you know anymore.
He's just a demon.
It hurts! Stop!
Stop it...
Onee-chan... Onee-chan...
Amazing!
I'm going to cum any second!
Me too!
I'm cummmg!
Catch it on your face, you pervert!
I came inside her.
That's not fair!
Let me do it too!
No...
Stop it! It hurts!
Stop it! Sawaki! Stop!
I'm going to break... my insides are going to break...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry Onee-chan!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum inside her again!
Is Sakura alive?
Of course she is, idiot.
You're trying hard, Asagi.
Onee-chan, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
S-Sakura...
Sawaki... Sawaki is.
Now, Kyousuke!
Leave that cheating Asagi alone and fill up her sister!
No! No!
No!No!
No! No! No!
I'm cumming inside Asagi-chan!
I'm cummmg! I'm cummmg!
Asagi-chan!
Wow... this is amazing...
Amazing! I can't...
More!
I want more!
This is great!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum on her face!
Take this!
It's not over yet!
I'm cummmg!
Not yet!
I'm next!
Great... You two are wonderful!
This is great! This is the best!
Do me, do me!
More, do me more!
Great! This is great!
I'm cummmg!