I'm cumming!
No!
No, stop!
N-No!
No, don't!
The Demon City Tokyo.
Humans and all manner of demons live together here.
While fulfilling the duties of an Anti-Demon Ninja,
I fell into a trap set by our arch-nemesis Oboro,
who was revived with the powers of Hell.
My sister Sakura and I were forced to become
playthings of the Chaos Arena's residents.
TAIMANIN ASAGI
Vol. 03                       Sisters, Fight!
She came five times.
I can still continue!
We honestly appreciate all of you for coming
to have fun in the arena today.
We will strive to deliver better quality service for you all.
Please remember to come again.
No... No...
Everyone, please enjoy the final round.
Sakura...
I'm sorry...
I wanted to save you, but..
Sakura, we will endure this because we're Anti-Demon Ninjas.
Hang in there, Sakura.
I can endure this?
I'm not as strong-willed as you are...
And my body was modified...
Sakura, don't give up!
I'll definitely get us-
It's no big deal to you, right?
You gave your virginity to Kyousuke-san, after all.
You gave it to the person you cherish... the person you love...
Me...
But me?
Sakura!
Those monsters took mine!
S-Sakura...
The customers were amazing today... They were fucking like rabbits.
Please reward me, Black-sama!
I'm on fire! It feels so good!
Sucking your cock is an amazing experience...
I can't take it anymore! You're such a bad boy...
Black-sama, you're such a bad boy.
I'm already...
I really want it now...
Look at me...
Black-sama, I...
You're always teasing me...
I want you inside me right now.
I'm cumming!
If you don't put it in, then I'll do it myself.
It's in.
Black-sama's cock...
It's inside me!
How is my pussy, Black-sama?
Fuck me with all you've got!
Oh, wow! I'm cumming...
Please cum inside of me.
Oh, no... I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! Oh, no!
Black-sama's...
Stop teasing me... Please...
Oh, no! I'm going to cum!
Black-sama... Black-sama... Black-sama!!
Forgive me...
Please release it in my mouth.
Black-sama... Black-sama...
You fucking bitch! How dare you-
Thanks to you two, the arena today was a great success.
I wonder when I should hold the next one?
You should thank me for making your bodies feel pleasure
no matter how many times you've been fucked.
G-Get your hands off my sister.
Keep your mouth shut, Asagi.
I'm the boss here.
Oh, that's right.
Shall I gave you both a special chance?
The boss who manages the transportation and administration
of the arena slaves is coming here soon.
He said hell grant a wish to whoever can satisfy him the most.
Wish?
In other words, this is your chance to get free.
What makes you think I'll believe you?!
It's up to you.
I tried my best asking him for this favor.
So what do you want to do?
That's impossible from an old bitch like you.
What?!
An old bitch like you won't be able to promise me that.
What the fuck are you saying, you fucking cow?!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
Don't be so cocky!
You're just an Anti-Demon Ninja, what can you do?!
Don't look down on us Anti-Demon Ninjas!
Just watch, I'll free myself from this place!
You old bitch!
You never learn! You... You,
For crying out loud.
You brats never learn to shut your mouth.
I'll fight my sister if you let me go.
Sakura, you're kidding, right?
Hey Asagi, your sister just said she'll fight you.
Sakura...
Sakura!
Now I'm interested to see who's more skilled between the two of you.
The person you're about to meet also holds
absolute authority in the normal world.
Even if you do break free from the handcuffs, you won't be able to...
I get it.
I apologize for making you wait.
These are the two Anti-Demon Ninjas I was telling you about.
They both look so charming.
I've prepared them both to your liking.
I'm pleased to hear that.
Now I know I didn't come here for nothing.
I'm glad you're happy.
So who's first?
I don't mind a threesome.
Let me see...
Sakura!
You're a rather assertive one.
What's your name?
I'm Sakura.
I'll do anything you want, Mister.
That's great.
Now prove it to my penis.
I haven't showered in a week for the sake of this.
The smell's amazing, right?
What's wrong? Why have you stopped?
My penis is the physical form of love.
II ensure that you'll regret it if you stop.
You sure know how to talk.
Let me help you, okay?
How is my love?
Your mouth is now filled with my love...
You want more of my love, right?
Sakura...
What's wrong, you're going to stop?
Great... That's right...
This is amazing.
She's Asagi's sister,
it's only natural for her to love dicks.
You can tell she's a virgin.
No way...
Sakura, you're just being shy, right Sakura?
I see.
I'm bored of this.
I'm gonna let it all out.
Here I go...
Hey, you should swallow it all!
That's no good.
I'm sorry that the slave is so rude.
Don't sweat it, she's still young.
Slowly chew it.
Don't swallow yet.
Harder with your hands.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, look at that expression.
Wow, you really do have talent.
Do your best!
Only swallow when I tell you to do so, okay?
All right, now.
How was it?
Delicious.
All right, let's do this once more.
Okay.
I'm a faithful man.
I'll play with you until the end.
Oh, that's wonderful.
If you show enough effort, I'll make you my personal cum dumpster.
That's so nice of you.
Thank you very much...
Lick my balls clean too.
Serve me until I have nothing left.
Under my training, you will become a world class cum dumpster.
And be able to take every man's semen.
You truly are Asagi's sister.
You overflow with talent.
She's perfect for a blowjob cum dumpster.
Do you really want my semen that badly?
Suck it harder and throat it.
Show me how good you truly are.
I'm letting it all out in your throat.
Here I go...
I came again.
And you must swallow it all.
That is the first step towards becoming a good cum dumpster.
How does it feel to have so much in your mouth?
I'm cumming.
Here's more...
Aren't I great?
Oh well, it seems like this cum dumpster
isn't interested in my special semen.
Hurry up and swallow it all.
If you can't even do that,
you're useless as a blowjob cum dumpster.
That's crucial for a blowjob cum dumpster.
Sakura... Sakura!
Are you okay?
You useless bitch!
Do you plan on embarrassing me?
Try again.
This is irresistible.
They're both so passionate; that must mean they really want it.
Really?
You're right.
Please take good care of these two.
Not bad.
Wow! You're so wet!
You're great.
It seems like the younger one is doing better.
Don't worry.
I'm like a fountain, so there won't be a shortage.
How is it?
That's not all.
Come on, try harder.
You both look so slutty.
All right, which one of you wants to get showered by my cum?
Here I go.
Please... hurry up and cum!
No, don't....
No, don't...
No!
No, don't!
No, not inside!
If you don't satisfy him soon, it'll get worse.
It's going to rip... It's going to rip!
No... I'm cumming!
No, don't!
No! No! No!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum...
No... No... No...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
No, I can't take it anymore!
Stop it...
No, it's disgusting!
N-No more!
No, I'm going to break!
I don't want to cum anymore!
I'm cumming!
So she broke down too.
Let me enjoy this, Asagi.
But real hell awaits you after this.
I never thought we'd make it here.
There's no way to escape.
This is the place that I've prepared for you.
Both of you can enjoy a true match here.
Now, get in.
K-Kyousuke...
Aren't you happy, Asagi?
He's been turned into a goblin for so long.
There's no trace of a humanity left inside him.
But there might be a way to turn him back to normal...
But only Oboro, the one who originally
transformed him, would be able to do that.
Onee-chan...
Now you're like a man.
I will return these two to you.
Enjoy yourself.
Sakura...
Kyou,
I don't think you remember taking away my virginity...
Come on, now's not the time to daydream.
K-Kyousuke...
Kyousuke...
Kyou...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
So Kyousuke picked you in the end.
Out of respect for the power of love, I declare you the winner.
You're free now.
Of course, your sister still has to stay.
Do you want to just kill her?
It's only a matter of time before she completely breaks down.
Why don't you kill her before she becomes
a burden to your organization...
Isn't that also part of your duty as an Anti-Demon Ninja?
So this was your plan from the very start?
Sisters killing each other...
Very well.
I agreed with Sakura, after all.