That shiny shoreline of the island.
A love island flows through within summer.
It finally drifts across using the southward winds.
Love affair; bewitched by the love magic.
Hey, I want to catch you while the air current rises.
I love you!
Facing the vast blue ocean.
Set off, charge in.
No need to be shy, laugh out loud.
Today is also very hot.
It's really hot, under the sun's rays.
That's the expression of our sweet and happy love.
Drenching the entire body under this glaring sunlight.
Letting it flow on its own. Looking forward to the vast flowing ocean.
Gently embraced by the wind like that.
Looking forward to the colorful future.
Near yet far.
I feel it, it's starting now, let's try to change.
I'm always gazing at you.
The sparkling ray of love, striking towards your heart.
Makes you unaware of other girls.
Using my charm, I mesmorised you dizzy, dominating your sight.
Chronicles of 15 Beautiful Girls Adrift: ~Heart Thumping Harem~ Chapter
is about to start!
A foxy and unfriendly classmate
An island spirit with animal ears
and furry tail
Thump~ Steam-covered hot springs filled with naked girls!
Who would've guessed there were new products?
Luckily my new multi-functional digital camera made it here.
Girls here seem to live a better life than in Japan.
There's only one thing to do when a guy gets ahold of a camera.
Sorry that you have to do this every time, monkey.
Finally!
Nanashi, want me to scrub your back?
You're always keen on helping the gods.
That's a very commendable thing!
My bad, I did it without thinking...
You'll be facing divine punishment if you don't do it properly!
Fine, fine. I'll clean you up properly.
You better shtop that at onche!
Watch out!
Ch-Chiba...
You're so cute.
The burning passion in my heart for animal care has been ignited.
S-Stop it, Chiba.
Disrespecting a god is a serious crime!
I've done nothing wrong.
I just can't resist because you're too cute.
What's up with all these excuses?
If this bullying by humans continues, my pride as a god will...
Just wait up, Nanashi!
No!
Even though you're so smooth in front, your tail is so rough.
It feels so good.
Don't touch my tail. It's very sensitive...
Nanashi, why are you so lovely?
Nooo~
You said your tail was sensitive, right, Nanashi?
Doing such lewd things even though we're both women...
As a god, I cannot allow this to happen.
It's not like I'm really a lesbian.
I just like cute animals. That's all.
Treating a god as an animal... How could you?
Don't do that! I'm very sensitive there!
Nanashi...
Chiba's slippery place... is rubbing against mine...
Nanashi.
Stop it, Chiba. If you keep going I'll...
Don't grab onto my tail!
But I didn't grab it.
Oh shit!
I was so into it that I accidentally grabbed her tail.
Kazuma, you asshole!
You dirty monkey!
Oh, no!
A chance appears!
Now's the time for revenge. Help me, God!
What are you trying to do?
I'm not the kind that would stay silent when pushed around.
Helping him is just a way of thanking him.
Let me go, Nanashi.
Don't let go, Nanashi.
S-Stop... you monkey...
I'm actually starting to feel good while being rubbed by this monkey...
Dammit.
Your nipples are all erect.
P-Please, anything but that...
I'm not doing anything wrong.
It's just that you're too hot.
No!
Why you-!
Did you get a taste of how I felt just now?
Cut it out... Nanashi...
I'm cumming, Chiba!
I never thought I'd see Chiba in this state...
Fuck you, monkey!
Younger of the twins
who is dark and likes to curse
Older of the twins
a cute and cheerful classmate
Tokimeki Sisters' Photography club.
Oh! It's Kazu.
Is he dead?
Who says I'm dead?!
What a pity. I have no choice but to curse you.
Don't do that!
Your curses are extremely dangerous!
Kazu, what's that?
Allow me to explain...
It's a Hatsujima NTR15B Digital Camera.
'Sup with that...
I'm not happy.
Thinking is my work.
Whereas flashing is mine!
Don't get in the way, Dark Queen!
If you breach my sister's portrait rights, a curse awaits you.
It's okay, Kage.
My beauty is an asset of the entire human race.
Your naive and romantic personality is dazzling.
Make sure you take beautiful shots of me.
Leave it to me!
How's that, Kazu?
Am I sexy?
Yeah... You sure are.
I know, right?
I'm pretty confident about my body!
Hey, Kazu! Where are you taking those pictures from?
This is not what I mean when I say my body!
Sorry, sorry.
Those excited heartbeats of yours... I can feel it.
Don't tell me you're feeling something when being photographed by Kazu...
Seriously, Kazu... You're really into this.
Am I so attractive?
Y-Yeah...
Since you're so honest, let me give you some extra service.
No!
Don't get in the way, Dark Queen!
I'll curse you if you harbour desires for my sister.
You're so irritating!
Oh, c'mon. Any healthy male would get excited after seeing me that way.
Sis...
It's a rare opportunity, so we should have you take a few shots, too.
A-Are you serious about this?
Your figure and genes are the same as mine.
You're definitely attractive.
Am I right, Kazu?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
It sure does look that way on the surface.
See? Even Kazu said that, and he loves cute girls.
Come and join me, Kage.
Okay.
Since you asked me to... I'll do it.
This pose... is embarrassing.
It's really cute, Kage!
I-Is this all right, Sis?
Good job!
I prefer dark places, and yet I'm under the spotlight.
All of my sensitive parts are being exposed.
Here you go. Say "aah."
Did you grow bigger, Kage?
My weight is the same as yours.
Does that mean you've grown fat?
I-I didn't say that...
Hey Kage, you're feeling exciting now, aren't you?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I can tell even if you try to hide it...
We're twins, after all.
You should also very well know that I'm wet already.
Sis...
Kazu, take more shots of my lovely expression.
Look. Look at my naughty expression.
Look at me more. C'mon.
Look at me! Please!
Sis...
You're rubbing yourself too...
I'm feeling twice as excited!
Sis.
I'm feeling good, too.
It's like being touched by you.
I'm starting to feel you as well.
It's your fault we're like this, Kazu.
You have to take responsibility, got it?
That's right...
First up will be Kage.
Sis?
You sure about this?
You know, it's lame to ask girls for permission when they are ready to go.
Sis, I'm not ready for this at all!
Look, you're already so wet.
Let's dig in!
What should I do?!
It feels so good!
I feel so damn good down there!
You're really cute this way.
I feel it too.
Kazu, make me feel good too.
It's coming inside!
Sis, even though it's inside of you,
it feels as if it were inside of me as well!
This is bad! I'm getting addicted to this!
Both of you are incredibly tight.
The feeling inside of you is similar.
You're not twins for nothing.
Kazu, take turns fucking us... Please!
All right! I'm on it!
It's really deep inside me this time!
Put it inside me as well.
I can no longer tell if it's inside of me or Kage!
Since it's the both of you, I'll try to do my best!
Sis!
Kage!
Here it comes!
Cumming!
I finally shot something awesome.
Timid cry baby, clumsy
and gorgeous big-breasted teacher
The childhood friend that
always sticks to the main character
Forbidden lesson under the blue sky.
This is what you call "shamelessness."
Got it, everyone?
Yes!
Make sure you remember this!
I will!
Oh, Shiraishi.
It's Kazu!
Yotsuya, we're in the middle of a lesson right now.
Miss, what are you two doing here alone?
Can't you tell by looking?
I cannot.
You have to stand up if you don't know the answer.
I've been standing here for a while now.
The correct answer is: we're having a lesson.
Ha-ving a les-son.
You see, I'm a teacher.
But ever since we got stranded on this island, I haven't had the opportunity to show off my skills.
I'll lose all of my teaching abilities if I go on like this.
So, as a teacher, I'm going to present my qualities.
I see.
However, it won't mean much if it's only Kotoshi alone.
That's right!
No one wants to join us!
It's all ruined!
Why are you the only one here?
I joined so I could learn to write a search log for Neta.
Shiraishi, a person like you who's not upset by the inability to study properly,
how can you understand my feelings?
How can this person say such hurtful things to a student?
Cheer up, Miss.
Everybody knows that you're an amazing person.
Shiraishi...
Glasses... Huge tits... And a female teacher...
Your virtues are just fabulous!
This shouldn't be related to glasses or huge tits...
That's right!
If there's a subject that students are interested in,
they will surely attend your lessons properly,
and they will come to respect you, the teacher.
An interesting subject like...?
That would be none other than Health and Physical Education!
In short, Health Ed or Physical Ed!
But I don't specialize in Health and Physical Education.
I don't know a single thing about it.
In that case, study it together with me!
For the sake of Health Education.
Let us investigate the differences in male and female reproductive systems!
Kazu, that's totally weird! It's completely unethical!
If you really want to investigate... please investigate with me.
Right now, on this island, the declining birth rates are becoming a severe problem.
Let's learn about the counter-measures.
What? You're doing it?
Going to such an extent for me...
I'm touched! I'll do my best!
I'll do my best too, Kazu.
You sit there!
My penis... is not for you right now.
What?!
This is something I have to do for our teacher.
You wait here quietly. I'll give you your reward later.
Really?
Really.
Really really?
Absolutely.
Don't you dare go back on your word.
Well then, allow me to begin.
The most important element of sexual intercourse is to bring the male genitals to an erect state.
Judging by the books I read, fellatio would be the most effective method to achieve this.
But your penis is already erect.
This isn't nearly enough.
Apparently, you still need more in-depth study about the male body.
Come, give it a lick please!
I-I got it.
Teacher is actually blowing a student's shaft.
This view is so moé.
It really does grow bigger.
It's always been changing gradually.
I've got to work harder.
Miss, use your breasts this time.
Shiraishi, you want to touch my breasts?
You're such a kid.
No! What I want is this, Miss!
Use both of your hands and your rack to rub my penis!
This is the definition of Health Education, a tit fuck!
So breasts can be used like this as well... It's so profound.
M-Miss...
It's so sticky... And it smells...
Shiraishi, you won't be getting any babies if you don't shoot it inside.
It's all right.
For I am Shiraishi Kazuma,
Japan's number one sperm producer!
If only you were this passionate about other subjects...
Behold, it has recovered already!
Now, let's continue.
It's my first time, so... please be gentle.
Miss!
I'm having sex while working...
I'm about to cum, Miss.
Are you prepared to take my seed?
Today is not my safe day, so go ahead and cum loads inside.
I want to bear many children.
Miss...
It's so hot and flowing inside of me.
Hey, how long am I supposed to wait?
Oh, Koto. I was so focused on the Health Education that I totally forgot about you.
It's my turn next!
I get it, okay.
Finally... Finally it's coming.
My wet and slippery pussy finally found Kazu.
It's coming in!
Kazu's semen is delicious.
Yotsuya's tongue is so dirty... Where did you learn this from?
She frequently practices on her own.
Kazu, more... I want more...
Got it.
Kazu!
Come on, lick more of the teacher's.
Understanding the bodies of others is also a part of Health Education, right?
It feels so good...
I'm about to cum again...
My students are doing this to me... All of my pride as a teacher is...
Nooo~
I'm cumming, Koto!
It's coming in... Kazu's semen is flowing inside of me.
Now our relationship is a reality.
I looked around the hot springs and found you lying here.
Really? So all that was...
Yup, it was all a dream.