I never thought of it as anything special.
It should only be lust, nothing more or less.
So why? Why do I feel bad about it?
A Forbidden Time
Kodomo
no
Jikan
English Translation by:
SakuraCircle Fansubs
sakuracircle.animeholics.org
Original Subtitles from:
Kuroyama Fapsubs (Russian)
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's go Ta-kun
Bye-bye!
Wait a minute.
Yes?
What shall we have for dinner?
I want...
Kouji, Osamu...
Which between us and that kid do you think is a grown-up?
Of course we're the grown-up ones.
What's up with you suddenly?
The right answer is...
Everyone's a child.
What the hell was that?
Ryouichi you tricky bastard!
You really hate losing, Kou-chan.
I wonder when...
we will grow up as adults...
Amazing!
Lewd!
It's dripping like crazy!
I really is amazing.
Both holes are twitching.
Okay, next would be...
Look, onee-chan, isn't this
the one you're longing for?
No... No!
Osamu, take a look at this.
Onee-chan is...
Once the vibe is inside
more juices are gonna flow!
She's loving this so much.
...not someone special for me.
Hey onee-chan, aren't you gonna come when I turn the gauge up?
It's gonna be good.
You bet!
Don't do that!
She's just a bitch.
Stop!
I'm putting it in!
Please don't!
Ryou-chan?
Onee-chan said no, didn't she?
Kouji, go get the mirror.
Okay...
Here onee-chan, take a good look.
This is your true self. Getting wet while bound and abused.
You're nothing more than a bitch!
P-please stop!
You're not someone special for me!
Look at yourself.
Can you still say no when
you're lewd like this?!
Say it.
Who... Where... And how you do want it.
My...
In my special place...
I want the vibrator plunged in.
Aren't you asking for a favor?
Then beg for it.
Please put the vibrator...
inside my special place.
You say no when you really wanted it.
You deserve a punishment.
You won't have it in your pussy.
Eh, but...
But since I feel bad for you,
You'll get it in your ass.
However...
My finger or my cock,
Which one of them would it be?
T-That's unfair...
Ryou-chan, that...
You shut up, Osamu!
Well, name your choice.
Please use... your finger on me.
Here...
The truth is a single finger
isn't enough, right?
Take out your finger, Kouji.
Okay!
No! That's... Please, make me cum!
Please!
How do you want us to make you cum?
Something bigger...
Like how you always do it, please.
Kouji, onee-chan wants
to cum from a cock.
N-No! I wanted a vibe!
This... feels good!
No, no, I'll cum, I'll cum, I'll cum!
I'm cumming!
She's not something special.
There's no way I feel special for her.
Even for this woman, I'm not someone special either.
She only sees me as a child.
So you're here all this time, Osamu. What are you doing in this place?
You're not going home yet?
What's the matter?
Kou-chan...
Isn't Ryou-chan acting strange lately?
Well yeah...
It started when we went
to the hot spring, right?
Somehow, it turned out weird.
And even last time...
I feel that Ryouichi is
always holding back on us.
We've been together
since he transferred here,
but it still feels like that for me.
Kou-chan...
He's not opening up on us,
like he doesn't want to bother us.
That's why I've decided,
that until he opens up on us
I'll go along on what he does.
Kou-chan...
See ya!
See you next time.
No, I should hold it up...
I can do it. Just a little more and I'll be home
Hey onee-chan who has
something plugged in her ass,
For being a horny slut, put this in your ass for a day at school.
You shouldn't remove it yourself, onee-chan
Onee-chan.
We've been waiting for you
so we can go home together.
The train is arriving at the second platform.
Please step away from the white line of the platform.
It's already a rush hour now.
Did you know, onee-chan
In this train, the last car is the most crowded.
In this experiment, we'll count how many molesters will you lure.
The train arrived. Please step away from the white line of the platform.
T-that's...
It's okay.
We'll be next to you and see how you will be molested.
Shall we go, onee-chan?
I don't want to be touched...
by strangers other than those kids.
But I'm being stimulated since this morning,
I can't take any more...
Oh no...
This can't be, I'm being groped for real...
He's doing it.
I'm gonna moan...
Stop!
If he touches inside my skirt...
He figured out that I'm not wearing anything.
We're arriving at the station soon.
Onee-chan, aren't we gonna get off on this station?
I never thought we'll find one really quick.
That's one person from when we get on and off a station.
If you're making a lewd face like that,
the train molesters will notice it quickly.
Let's do an experiment on our next ride.
No... I can't control my own body's reaction.
More...
My body... wants more...
My voice... Oh my...
If you're making a lewd face like that, the train molesters will notice it quickly.
Hey...
Are you for real... You're a lewd girl.
You even have this thing inside you.
You won't be satisfied with only this, right?
Hey, your voice is too loud.
People will notice us.
I'm gonna make you feel good,
but try not to moan.
Here, grab onto this.
Oh, it's stirring your insides.
Are you cumming?
Even though you're in a train?
Hey, how about coming with me...
Onee-chan, we're already here.
Kouji, what time is it?
Yes, we're on schedule.
Onee-chan, I wrote about you online that you're riding on this train,
and asking "Please grope me."
It's okay, we told them "no penetration allowed".
Oh, the train is coming.
We don't know how many will go. Isn't it exciting, onee-chan?
Onee-chan, I wrote about you online that you're riding on this train,
■
High school girl here.
Please Grope me.
■
and asking "Please grope me."
Nobody would believe on such a ridiculous post like that.
A post on the internet like that is suspicious. Nobody would take it seriously.
It could also be just the kids lying on me.
It's okay...
No one will come...
It's just a bad lie.
Is it...
Yeah...
That girl? For real?
But this uniform...
Maybe it's just a coincidence.
Or, could it be her?
She's kind of cute.
Why...
It cant be...
Should we try it?
This can't be...
...happening!
Hey...
She moaned!
Try looking under her skirt. She has a rotor inside, it's really her.
Yes!
She's the real deal...
Cool...
This is great!
It's really true. A slut high school girl.
Did we keep you waiting?
I can't believe this...
Don't you want your tits massaged?
She's been waiting for men to molest her.
You're lewd. Did you buy this toy yourself?
I'm being touched by strangers.
Oh yeah!
No... Please stop...
Stop? Isn't this your whole idea?
And look, you got wet having this inside and you want to stop?
You're very horny for a virgin.
Why?
I don't want this...
Though I don't want to be touched by anyone other than those kids...
My body still feels it.
Hey, look at this!
That's amazing.
You even have something like this, miss?
Here, take this.
Did she just cum?
You never had a dick, but you've been using these toys.
She even has this one.
What a very lewd high school girl.
Here, here.
Look, it's dripping wet here.
You wanted us to use these, right?
We're gonna molest your pussy and asshole just as you wish.
If you scream everyone will know,
that you're feeling good with vibes inside both holes.
Although there have been a lot of people who read your post online and came.
Even when I don't want to be touched by strangers...
Being molested...
Then... why?
Why do I feel good?
Why is it so?
What a crowd!
Am I such a person?
Onee-chan is more turned on than usual.
You're right.
You're nothing more than a bitch!
You're not someone special for me!
That's it...
This hair... This long black hair makes me remember about that girl.
What did you say, onee-chan?
Ryouichi-kun.
I...
I am your...
How was it, onee-chan?
How did it feel to be groped by strangers?
Slut.
You're fine with anybody, right?
You're a horny bitch who will
get on it with anyone!
I've heard those words many times,
but hearing the same words today broke my heart.
And it's like I heard something  inside me shattered.
To be continued.
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization