All right. Today we finished all of the activities scheduled for training.
I'm tired!
I'm all sweaty.
Thank God it's over!
Tomo, this isn't the time to relax!
O-Okay!
You have classes for the recording next week in Tokyo.
But until then...
...You're free!
Yay!!
Where are we going?
What will we do?
Huh? You're not happy, Saya?
What are you talking about?
You know that the recording time will be next week, don't you?
But at least tomorrow...
I'll train by myself.
I thought you would say that, Saya.
What? What are you talking about?
Yuki, if you don't rest a bit, you'll collapse.
You're kidding, right?
I don't want to rest!
But it won't be like you want.
Huh?
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me ...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
Blue Station
Fukusumi Station
Goodbye! Fukusumi Station!
That's a good one, isn't it?
It is!
Thank you! Fukumsumi Station \ Goodbye Ceremony \ There'll Also Be A Special Presentation With A Famous Idol!!
What is this?
Looks like a stage, doesn't it?
I know that!
Why do I have to introduce myself in an isolated place like this?
For Kogure-san's Father.
For his father?
Exactly.
Lately, Saya is trying hard, so...
...she needs to do something more relaxing and rest a bit.
That's what he said.
Gure... doing unnecessary things!
Everything will be fine.
If we don't relax once in a while...
Huh, Saya-chan...
There sems to be an onsen nearby!
Note: "Onsen" is a hot water spring
Onsen, huh?
How wonderful!
What kind of delicious foods will be there?
Perhaps seafood?
Of course wild greens are also delicious.
Could it be that she came because she wanted to?
Saya-chan, did you say something?
No.
Nothing.
You're Saya-chan?
Yes.
Nah... you're not Saya-chan...
My name is Saya.
No, no it's not...
I think Saya-chan was prettier...
What do you mean by that?!
Now, now... I'm sorry!
Ah... Onsen, onsen.
You're pretty.
Seems that this onsen is beneficial for your skin!
What?
But it was a mistake, a mistake...
Will I get ten years younger if I get in?
Hey, wait...
Wow, I'll be exactly like Saya-chan!
What was that?
Could I be a Lemon Angel?
Just kidding...
That's enough!
What's wrong?
I'm going.
Don't go!
There's an irresistible reason!
Reason?
It's Saya-chan?
What is it this time?
Nishioka-san?!
Long time no see.
Yes, it's been a long time.
What happened for you to look at me like that?
Ah... nothing!
But why're you here?
Huh? Keiko-san hasn't told you?
What?
The person who's organizing this event is the one that helped you when you were still Yayoi, Nishioka-san.
What? Really?!
Long time no see.
See, you can't refuse, can you?
You've grown a lot, haven't you?
Y-You think?
You're a beautiful woman already.
Th-Thank you.
But I thank you for coming here today.
It's nothing...
If it's for you, I'll go anywhere!
Ah! You learned to speak politely!
Not really...
Nishioka-san, Start preparing yourself please.
Okay!
This is today's schedule.
The talent is on standby, okay?
What? Wait!
And that also! It's the same as ever.
So today's the deactivation ceremony of Fukusumi Station.
But thinking about it, it's a natural fact that this station stopped to exist, didn't it?
Because only old mamas and papas live here...
No, no, no, no, no.
Everyone here is a visitor, right?
She really won't find out?
It's perfect!
I think it's too weird.
Weird.
Everything's definitely okay!
Where did that confidence come from?
Why are we doing this on our day off?
Oh Yumi, aren't you worried about Saya?
Of course I am.
Then let's root for Saya's work!
But I never imagined that Miki-senpai would come too.
Is there a problem?
Of course not!
Take beautiful photos, please!
E-Erika!
Photos?
It's nothing !
No need to hide it.
Miki is fascinated with trains..
Whaaat?!
Is that true?
I-Is that a problem?
Miki said that she wanted a picture of Fukusumi Station, since it'll be deactivated.
I never imagined!
Shut up!
That's why I didn't want to come along with you guys.
Are you Saya-chan?
You're waiting for her?
I think... in a while she'll introduce herself.
In a while?
I'll wait a bit then.
And one more guest that has decided to come.
Saya-chan has a lot of fans!
Sure does!
Hey, oba-chan, Saya's about to introduce herself.
Note: "Oba-chan" is a title given to older women.
I'm going to introduce you to a special guest that came specially to this end of the world.
About time, right?
The old Yayoi, Yuki Saya!
Good afternoon to you all that are here at Fukusumi Station!
Incredible, isn't it?
Why do I have to go through with this?
I thought some crazy guy came in.
But you're the guest?
Yes! It's a pleasure!
How humiliating!
Is it true that you like Fukutsumi eggs, the food that stands out here?
Yes, I eat them everyday!
I wanna leave!
It's okay that you like eggs, but it's weird being dressed as a chicken, isn't it?
This is the outfit I dress in everyday!
Of course I don't!
That's the clothes you wear everyday?
So you go shopping like that?
Of course!
No person dresses like this!!
If you really like it so much, cluck like a chicken!
Yes, with pleasure!
I'm going to smack him after this!
One, two, three!
I really will!
Very good, one more time!
I'll definiely, definitely smack him!
Let's try to accept... one more time!
Then I'll smack Gure too!
Saya-chan's work is very complicated.
Looks good.
Bravo, Saya, Excellent!!
What are they doing here?!
Saya, you imitate very well!
You can't say that, because next...
Three...! Two...! One...!
I'll smack all of them later!
You surprised me!
You really look like a chicken like that!
One more time, imitate laying an egg.
Everyone got excited!
Really?
And also, all Lemon Angel members...
I'm happy!
I didn't bring them.
They came by themselves.
Saya, it was an amazing presentation.
That outfit was great also.
I want to dress up too!
Since little Saya-chan would combine with this costume,
What?
Wait, Nishioka-san!
She already dressed up in costumes?
Yes, she dressed up for other events.
Such as...
Let me see...
Whe we went to Hokkaido, she was dressed up as a sea urchin.
Yes, she was very cute.
And when we went to Koute, she went as a fish.
That's right!
How pretty!
Looks tasty.
And when we went to Kyoto, she went as Kinkakuji.
Note: Kinkakuji is known as a golden pavilion, who's walls are gold and was built in 1397 in Kyoto.
It's glowing!
Kinkakuji is also very good.
Hey, don't have random imaginations!!
How nice.
How I missed those times!
Nishioka-san, have you known Saya for a long time?
Yes, when Saya-chan was... on some music event for her last job.
Yes!
But when I knew she got into Lemon Angel, I became scared.
You got scared?
Yes, that Saya always cried...
What?
Note: "Nakimushi" has 2 meanings: 1 - insect that sings; 2 - person who cries a lot.
Saya's
a Naki-
It's not that!
Could you stop with those old stories?
I always had to comfort her behind stage before presentations.
Looks good.
Stop imagining weird things!
Eh~?
What's with those faces?
So, keep up that rhythm in the afternoon.
What?
It's not over yet?
What are you talking about?
You still have the Station Chief job for the day!
Hold on, I didn't know about that!
What? I didn't tell you?
Ah, I know!
What do you guys think about participating too?
Huh?
Us too??
Yes, I want to participate!
Me too!
I wanna try!
Can we, Keiko-san?
Even though you have the day off, I'll go ahead and tell the company.
All right!
You can't!
Miki-senpai!
It's already close to the recording date.
And we don't have time to waste at a place like this.
You truthfully want to do it with us, don't you?
What crazy things are you talking about?
That time you were taking photos of the Station Chief.
Th-That was for the resource that is still to come...
If you want, I can give you the "front play" for the train deactivation.
That's in three hours, you know.
So it's decided, right?
Hey, Don't decide things for me!
I wanna leave!
The train will arrive shortly.
Please stay behind the line.
Erika-chan looks so natural.
Me too. Me too!
Eh, today is a pretty day...
Tomo-chan, what kind of greeting is that?
U-Um...
Miru-chan, you can't sing!
Why?
Don't ask why.
I trully understand now.
It's my turn now! Hey, Tomo, now let me...
We'll be recording next week.
And no one is nervous?
You could've at least gave me the right size.
Um, excuse me!
The... The old lady from before.
When does the next train arrive?
Um, Ma'am, you should ask that to the real station chief.
What did you say?
Let me see...
One hour and twenty minutes.
Ah, yes, thank you very much.
That lady...
You know her?
No!
She only said that she was waiting for Saya.
Me?
No.
I guess it's a different one.
I'll ask her!
Hey, Saya!
So you're waiting for your granddaughter who's called Saya
that visits you during this season, right?
You can say that.
She is exactly the same age as you.
She's a person that's as happy as a sunflower.
Ah, really?
Maybe she forgot about this old granny.
Of course not.
You think so?
I'm sure she's anxious to see you.
I would be happy if it were like that.
Um, can I wait for your granddaughter with you?
But aren't you working now?
There isn't much to do, being a station chief for a day.
It's okay.
Is that so? Thank you very much.
Do you see her?
I see.
Then, she must arrive with the next train.
Oba-chan, the train arrived!
Find her?
I see.
Saya-chan. It's almost closing time.
So today these six girls worked for us as station chiefs.
Wasn't it fun working as a station chief at a station like this?
It wasn't all that much...
It was a lot of fun!
Really?
Really! Because I met a lot of different people!
There are many rare people that exist in this world.
Even so, thank you for today.
Thank you very much.
You did a good job today.
Um... can I stay a little longer?
What?
What is it?
It's that...
Let's see...
You can stay a little longer.
Thank you very much!
You haven't left yet?
I want to stay a bit more here.
Really?
Of course!
Can we stay too?
You guys...
We heard a bit of your conversation earlier.
Can we wait with you?
My camera's memory is also full.
I'm going to stay a little more.
Wow, it suddenly got busy here.
Thank you very much.
A plane passed through here, you know?
On line two, the last train will leave.
Thank you very much for your time.
All right. That's all, Minaguchi.
Okay.
Here's a letter for everyone.
The old lady?
Dears,
I spent a lovely time talking with you yesterday.
I have to apologize for one thing.
To tell the truth, Saya got sick while in Tokyo and had died.
But I couldn't believe it, so I started going to that station.
Because I felt that she really would arrive at anytime.
But when I spoke with you,
I felt good because it seemed like I was talking with Saya.
Thank you very much everyone.
Oba-chan...
Look, Saya's a real cry-baby.
I-I'm not!...
This is sweat!
Ah, Is that so?
All right, break's over.
Yuki's up next.
Yes!
Please!
It's ready.
Wow!
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
With the debut near, the Lemon Angels are finally back?
We've made it, finally...
W-Why?
The program that Yui-senpai destroyed.
Yes, but...
Miki-senpai, you know something about it?
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 11, "Immoral Scenario."
Yui, the time has finally come.
What do you mean by that?
Immoral Scenario