Aozora ni tobitatsu shunkan ni wa
When i fly to the azure sky
READY FOR YOUR FLIGHT
kimi wa dare no kao wo omoidasu no?
Who's face do you remember?
samishia ni umorenagara sakebi tsuzuketa
I kept shouting as i was buried in sorrow.
kinou niwa mou modoritakunai yo
I don't want to go back to yesterday.
You've got...
EVOLUTION!!
ima wa mada chiisana koe da toshitemo
Even if your voice is small right now
mou sugu deau yo dareka kimi wo matteru
You will soon meet someone who is waiting for you.
EVOLUTION!!
The Group, Lemon Angel, that all of Japan was excited about,
suddenly disappeared last summer, while i was still in my third year of middle school.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu Anata no kokoro suki wa aru no kana?
In the middle of the night, I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login.
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Out of my control.
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
I can't stop it. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokani no dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me...So hold me tight.
A year has passed since then.
Angel awoken from a dream
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Welcome to the night of dreams.
Lemon Angel Act 2, the last audition!
Dear Yui-senpai, I've finally made it this far.
1, 2, 3, 4...
I'll do my best, Senpai.
Though there are too many people out there.
What's wrong Tomo? You aren't scared, are you?
Yeah, it's not like you, Tomo.
Shut up. Unlike Saya, this is my first time.
You have to enjoy yourself at a time like this.
So, so. Let's enjoy! Right, Yumi?
Oh Yumi, are you okay?
Come on, hold yourself together.
What should i do? What should i do?
Yumi, it'll be fine. Now relax...just relax.
Áh, I wonder if this means there'll be fewer rivals.
Senpai, I may be you junior right now, but i'm not backing down.
Because i swore i'd be able to sing the songs you wrote.
Tomo! Wake up already! You're gonna be late!
Ouch. What? Uh-oh! Mom, couldn't you have waken me earlier?
Dear Yui-senpai, my high school life has just started, so i'm not used to it yet.
Huh? I have to brush my teeth again!
Alright!
My studies have also become much harder.
Ah! Oh no, Isn't there a test today?
I'm off.
But i've already made friends. Making friends is one of my skills.
Tomo!
Morning Yuki-chan.
Seriously, what are we going to do about today's test?
Hmmm? I didn't do anything.
Eh? And do you think that's fine?
I guess. You know?
Hey, hey, hey...
Ta dah!
Hu-huh? Isn't that Himuro Shinya?
I scored some tickets!
Seriously?
Yay! Thank you Yuki-chan!
Huh? Why do you think i'm taking you with me?
Huh? So you're going alone then?
It's a secret.
What do you mean?
Of course, i'm going with my boyfriend.
Oh. Then you shouldn't be showing off your tickets like that!
Oh yeah, have you decided on what clubs to join?
Nope. Our school's clubs are just lacking...
How about music, since you're good at singing?
If there were a karaoke club... Miki-chan, what about you?
Me? I thought i'd go take a look at the archery club today.
Archery?
She's there. Torowa-sama that is.
Incredible!
Wow! Amazing!
How can Suwa-senpai be so incredible?
Even though the Lemon Angels broke up, she should've continued to sing solo.
Yeah.
They say that she's the only daughter of a diplomat, and has lived in many countries.
Which is why she's fluent in German and English.
Her hobbies are tea ceremonies, horse back riding, flower arranging, ballroom dancing and piano.
Like a true celebrity princess.
She's won a lot of awards at piano competitions.
Oh? That's incredible!
Shhh! She's about to shoot.
W-W-Woah...
Ouch.
Sorry.
Tomo, are you okay?
What? Did you do something again?
What do you mean by "again"?
But you were scolded yesterday too, weren't you?
Yesterday was just an accident.
I was doing ballet and used a little too much strength, and the classroom window just popped.
Oh?
Today i just slipped on some stairs and there was a painter there re-painting the walls.
Just picturing that is scary.
Wow, you high school students are a cut above.
Huh? Oh this? You're wrong, this is just a hobby of mine.
Hobby?
Yup. Oh, hey, i finished a new song. Want to hear it?
Yes, yes.
It's just a short little melody of mine.
Wow, cool.
The song's called "Evolution."
TRUST ME, aozora ni tobitatsu shunkan ni wa
TRUST ME, When i fly to the azure sky
READY FOR YOUR FLIGHT
kimi wa dare no kao wo omoidasu no?
Who's face do you remember?
This has a nice rhythm to it.
samishia ni umorenagara sakebi tsuzuketa
I kept shouting as i was buried in sorrow.
Thank you.
Actually, though it's not official, this'll be a debut song.
kinou ni wa mou modoretakunai yo
I don't want to go back to yesterday.
Huh? When did this get decided?
Ah, sorry, sorry. Not me. The one to debut is her -
You've got...
Evolution!!
ima wa mada chiisana koe da toshitemo
Even if your voice is small right now
Suwa Miki. We became friends in an online programmer community.
Oh?
mou sugu deau yo dareka kimi wo matteru
You will soon meet someone who is waiting for you.
This is a co-operative effort between us.
Right now she's living overseas, but will be returning next year.
When she gets here, i'll have to introduce you two,
EVOLUTION!!
Evolution!!
kiseki wa hitori ja tsukurenai yo
Miracles can't be made with just one person.
though she may be a little hard to get along with initially.
Okay!
She'll be back and will attend Hakuo H.S. next year, so why don't all three of us go there?
Amh uh,i don't think i could...
What are you saying? You shouldn't give up without trying.
Tomo, you should be able to do it.
Ah, uh, umm.
I'll be waiting for you.
Uh, okay!
"Wait for me", huh?
Sound off!
Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
Hey, you freshman, you're not keeping up!
Again!
Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
Okay...
Again!
Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
Dear Yui-senpai,
Again!
I thought i had gotten over it already,
but i guess i'm hopeless, my memories keep coming back.
I thought you'd be there.
You must really like it up here.
You could say that.
Do you want to walk home together?
If so, then i have to turn this in first.
Oh? A new club membership notice? That was quick.
Wait for me at the gates, okay?
Okay.
Huh?
Who could that be?
Suwa-senpai?
Kya!
Ah!
Eh, ah, Su,Su-Su, hello. It's nice to meet you.
I...I'm Minaguchi Tomo...
Uh, well i was on the roof and i heard the song you were playing.
Uh, not that being on the roof was worth mentioning. Anyway...
Um, i just wanted to say that the song you were playing was "Evolution".
I liked the song since way back.
Uh, not just the song, but i like all of Yui-senpai's songs.
I'm not sure how to put this, but i get a nice, good feeling.
Ah, and why is it i'm talking about Yui-senpai? Well, i'll start explaining all of that now.
That is, i'm Yui-senpai's junior. Ah, i guess that's obvious since she's my Senpai.
Umm, and i've heard all about you from her, so i thought i'd like to meet you sometime.
I was so worried about what sort of person you would be, personally.
Umm, back at the archery field, you were really cool. Really impressive.
Um, that is to say i have the utmost respect for you.
You're good at studying, singing, playing the piano...
Umm, uh err...
Uh, what am i going on about...i don't know...
You're awfully noisy.
Huh?
I hate people like you.
Please, never speak to me again.
Dear Yui-senpai, could it be i've gotten on her bad side?
Ah, it's all over...
There's no way i can fix this.
Cheer up. I'll become friends with Suwa-senpai, and make an appeal on your behalf.
I'll tell her Tomo isn't all that bad of a person.
Mmmm...
Besides, it was probably because she was in a bad mood.
But she didn't have to say she hated me.
We have only just met. It wasn't very nice.
"Please never speak to me again."
Now, there, there.
Ah!
How could the old leader of the Lemon Angels act like that?
Maybe the reason the Lemon Angels broke up was because of her bad personality...
Eh? Ah, yeah, probably.
Ah, now i'm pissed! What id i do to her?
I may have been a little noisy, but it didn't warrant that speech.
I'm pissed!
Hey, calm down a lttle. I'll treat you to some Shiffon Cake.
Really?
Really, really.
Alright.
You got over that quick.
Yuki-chan?
It's nothing. Let's go.
Wait...
Yuki-chan, what's gotten into you?
We're being followed.
Eh?
It's probably a stalker.
Seriously?
Let's split up.
I can't go on...
E-Excuse me...
What is it?
Save me. There's a strange man stalking...
At last...
Kyaa, pervert! Why you?!
Kogure-san.
Eh?
Ah, isn't this...
I'm fine. He really is a record maker.
It looks like this'll take some time, Yuki-chan,so go on home without me.
Yeah, yeah. Well, i'll see you tomorrow. Bye bye.
Ouch... Minaguchi-san, you're pretty strong.
I'm so sorry!
Now, now. Let's start over. I'm Kogure Ryota. Pleased to meet you.
Woah, you're an important person.
You surely don't look like it.
Sorry to disappoint you.
By the way, you know about the Lemon Angels, right?
Yes, of course.
So, do you know the reason for their sudden break-up?
No.
I see...
Actually right now there's a project to create a new Lemon Angels.
Eh? Really?
Yeah, the Second Lemon Angels.
We'll be keeping the same leader as before, but the rest will be completely new.
By leader, you mean Suwa-senpai?
That's right. And for the new members, we're planning on holding an audition...
So, would you like to give it a shot?
Huh?
Would you mind giving the Lemon Angel auditions a try?
Now hold on a moment. My chances of becoming a Lemon Angel are hopeless. Absolutely hopeless.
To be honest, i thought so too, that you wouldn't easily succeed.
So why is it you asked me?
Yui-senpai? You knew Yui-senpai?
Yeah, it was back when i was still an assistant, and i got involved in the creation of the first Lemon Angels.
That was when i got to talk with Yui about all sorts of things.
She really wanted you to sing.
To sing the songs she made.
But...
What's with the uncertainty? You're now the only one that can make Yui and my dreams a reality!
Huh? Dreams?
That's right! Dreams!
It's what both Yui and i always thought about. The desire to make real music.
Just by listening to it, it would lend people strength.
I want to make such stupendous songs with the new Lemon Angels!
Right now there's no such thing as real music in this world!
Current music is just trendy. One second they're popular, the next they're gone.
Aren't they just like mass produced "shake and bake" songs for the masses?
I want to create something far different!
Something that will last decades, centuries as a great song! That's what i want to make!
Lemon Angels will become, as the name implies, Angels!
Yeah! Angels will deliver music to the whole world!
Don't you think it would be great to be selected as a member of this elite band?
There will certainly be difficult times, trials and hardships.
But if you overcome them, you'll be able to see the light ahead.
That's where the music we create exists!
So won't you give it a try...
Huh?
Looks like i did it again.
Kogure-san, I think i may have made a mistake. It shouldn't have been like this...
Yui-chan...
I wonder why my Lemon Angels have come to this.
Then just quit. You should quit.
That's already impossible.
Dammit. It's because of him.
Stop it. Please don't speak bad things about him.
Sorry.
Yui...
Me at the Lemon Angel audition? Impossible...
How much longer will it take him?
It has been over a year already.
Himuro Shinya?
How about if you fire him and hire another programmer?
It would be the same story. It's not something that can be easily fixed.
Dammit, if Kohno Yui-san were still here.
Huh? Yui-senpai?
Excuse me...
Himuro-san? Hmmm?
Hey, your security is too weak.
As long as i'm here, why would i need to lock the door?
Aw, they closed the door. I'd better get out of here before i'm spotted... Uh-oh!
What should i do?
I'm telling you Kohno Yui was a genius!
Anyhow, i'd like you to hurry up. You've been paid by both the company, and Himuro Shinya.
Even if i tell you, you'll probably wouldn't understand, but...
The program's core code was destroyed by Arucan. Fine. here, take a look.
Lemon Angel?
What's going on?
Dammit, it's because i don't have a plugin for this portion that this happens.
What? What is that?
Kya!
Yui-senpai...
Who's there?
I'm in a pinch! A big pinch!
Hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
Nazeka kokoro wa nemure nakunat
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
Dewa suru yuuki mo nakawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
Tomawaru guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
Onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
Ko wo suru tabi ni
Are in love...
Sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
Itsudatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arenai
because whe in love, this feeling says no-one else but you will do
Girls in love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world i can only dream about.
Ah! It's already time for the audition. What should i do, Yuki-san?
Although Kogure-san said i shouldn't take it too seriously.
What are you talking about, that attitude won't get you into the Lemon Angels!
But i'm taking it seriously, it's just...
People like you really piss me off. You're probably here just because you have connections with the producer.
Huh? What do you mean be connections?
Next time on Lemon Angel Project, Episode Two, Evolution.
I'm not going to lose to the likes of you!
Why won't you listen to me!