Okay, Mizuna.
Don't get me wrong.
He's not my fiance, and l don't want a close relationship with him.
l just mean l can put up with it for now.
Anyway, he'll leave here after the Expecting Moon Ceremony.
That is all there is to it.
You look like you don't believe me, but it's true.
All right?
l mean it.
Hayama doesn't mean anything to me, okay?
Don't hold back your feelings.
No.
lt is all right.
You don't need to think about anything now.
l don't want to see your suffering face.
l like your smile.
Your happiness is my happiness.
More, l want to be satisfied.
l want more.
l can't.
l can't hold back.
l will be able to sleep tonight.
Only you and l are together forever.
lt's too good, it's driving me crazy...
Oh, my.
l've been waiting for you, Mr. Hayama.
l've waited for a long time...
...since then.
l've been between life and death.
Then, l came across a flower that bloomed with filthy desires.
However...
l need your power to resurrect completely in this world.
Your true...
...your sealed power.
l'll awaken your soul.
lf so, you will...
You will become complete...
...as the God of the Kuraki.
Take as much of me as you wish!
Mr. Hayama?
No, you are not the one l want.
l see.
That's why l suddenly felt Hayama's strong power.
The seal's too powerful!
l know she was a former shrine maiden, but now she's just a ghost.
For some reason, she has great powers.
No wonder that they can't give up Mt. Kuraki.
l told you not to disappoint me, Hayama.
Maybe l should've done this in the first place!
lt's impossible...
You also have incredible power.
For the sake of the Expecting Moon Ceremony, give your power to Mr. Hayama.
Mizuna?
You said that you have only me.
But it was a lie.
Wait!
Oh, well.
Half of my lost power has been recovered already.
Also, Suzuna is getting attached to him.
The Expecting Moon Ceremony is coming soon.
ls this my room, isn't this, Tomomi?
Don't look at me.
l just woke up.
l don't want you to look at my terrible face.
How embarrassing!
l will bring something for you to wear.
Which panties would you like?
The pink ones?
The pink doesn't look good on me.
Well, l will bring your usual white underwear, then.
We did it last night already.
Yes, we did many times.
How about the lavender ones?
They are for a special day.
l wonder if he likes lavender.
Only you and l are here.
Who am l thinking about?
Perhaps, he is someone who is important to me.
Miss Suzuna, please think about only me.
You look like a real student if you put on an uniform.
So do you.
What happened?
Your size doesn't fit to me.
lt's a little big.
So, why don't you wear yours?
You went to the same school, too.
l've already thrown it away.
Did you hate school?
l liked it because people paid attention to me.
Did you change my clothes to do this?
Miss Suzuna in School Days, little Suzuna, newborn Suzuna...
l want to know absolutely everything about my Suzuna.
Your body is tender.
These could drive a man crazy.
Miss Suzuna?
Hayama...
Miss Suzuna...
Suzuna..
Where am l?
What?
Mi-zu-na.
Mizuna?
ls it your name Mizuna?
Hey, are you okay?
Are you tied here?
l wish she would act a little more like this.
Then, she'd be much prettier.
l didn't know there was a cave back here.
Mr. Hayama.
Tomomi, what are you doing here?
l am here to bring Miss Suzuna back to you.
Hayama.
Do you want a morning kiss?
Hayama...
Hayama!
Hayama, Hayama, Hayama!
Hey.
You can't go anywhere.
No, you can't!
What's the matter with you, Suzuna?
Are you going somewhere, Hayama?
Are you going to go somewhere without me?
Suzuna.
l don't know myself.
lt was like a dream.
l'm kind of confused...
But, but...
As l said, l'm not going to go anywhere.
l see.
We were looking for you, Tomomi.
Mr. Hayama and Miss Suzuna...
Miss Suzuna's heart belongs to Mr. Hayama.
lt's full of you.
That's why she doesn't need me anymore.
What are you saying?
Who else can take care of this spoiled princess besides you?
She is stubborn, selfish and spoiled.
l can't relax if you don't watch her.
Can l be by Miss Suzuna, then?
Of course, you've been my friend since we met.
And you always will be.
A friend...
Even just a friend, you still need me, don't you?
Yeah, she can't even choose her underwear without your advice.
That's not true.
l just couldn't decide what l should wear...
Because l am the one who wears them, but the person who takes them off is...
What did you say?
l couldn't hear the last part.
Shut up, l didn't say anything!
lsn't it too handsome?
He's late tonight.
You don't need to knock on the door all the time.
That's why l gave my room key to you.
You're supposed to just sneak into my room and surprise me!
Excuse me...
Sorry to disappoint you.
Forget what l said, would you?
ls Mr. Hayama not here?
You're talking strange, why would he have to be here?
lf he isn't here, l guess he's in Tomomi's room.
Mr. Hayama is still young.
He came to my room last night.
Don't gossip about me.
Where have you been?
Just to enjoy the cool air.
Alone?
Cut down on cigarettes.
l've got to go now.
Are you going to sneak away?
Don't take seriously what l said, l was just kidding.
Wait.
Hold it!
Don't, Sayaka is watching us.
l'll erase your worries.
Now's my chance.
Good morning.
Did you stay up all night?
l was worried you'd disappear while l slept.
Don't talk like a child.
You aren't going anywhere?
But l can go the bathroom at least, right?
You look just like her.
No, it's nothing.
What is that?
Who is she?
Are you all right?
l've never seen Hayama smile like that.
Who is that girl?
She looks like me.
Hayama's smile...
l wonder if he likes that girl.
Why are you here?
Sayaka said nobody was here.
Aren't you angry with me?
l guess you can stay a bit.
l will wash your back.
How do you know how to do that?
Don't you feel good?
Yeah.
Suzuna?
Who is the girl you met at the cave?
l don't know.
Are you nice to me because l look like her?
What are you talking about?
So, you like her.
Suzuna...
Don't smile like that at anyone besides me, please.
l don't like to be watched all the time.
Of course...
l know you prefer her to pesky little me.
Come here.
Suzuna!
No!
Suzuna..
l don't like you.
You show up, confuse me and kiss me...
...without concerning yourself with my feelings.
Why are you chasing me?
Why don't you go to her?
Suzuna!
Hayama...
l...
...love you.
Since you came here, actually before you came, l've been waiting for you.
So, l want to be with you even if you like her.
l wore this against my will the first time, but l really want to wear it now.
l...
l told you, l have only you.
l don't care if it's not true.
l want to believe you.
H-Hayama.
Call me Koichi.
Koichi.
No...
Stop!
Oh, no.
lt's deep inside of me.
Koichi, Koichi!
What will Mr. Hayama and Miss Suzuna do after the Expecting Moon Ceremony?
Perhaps, they'll go down Mt. Kuraki.
lf so, what will you do, Tomomi?
l will go with them no matter what.
Because that's what l want to do.
That's my Tomomi!
To be continued...