No way...
There's no way...
I'm...
I'm going to...
...be the comfort station?
That can't be true!
This month's public comfort station
Oh, look. This time, it's...
now way!
It really is...
It's the student council president.
The president?
comfort station
What is this nonsense?!
I'm the council president, you know!
Here comes the cock!
I was raped by 411 men
comfort station
It is a title given by the students to a randomly chosen
female for the purpose of mass sexual satisfaction
much similar to the concept of a public urinal.
The school adapted this system with the objective of
healthily nurturing the mentality of the students,
in order to tone down sex related crimes by allowing these
so called pre- planned "safe" yet stimulating scenarios.
This so called academy that claims
to practice a new outlook on life,
sounds crazy, right?
Even I thought so... till now.
I was raped by 411 men
Oh, now this is something.
Hi there, Reika-san.
You're all set it seems.
You're going to satisfy us completely today
as well, right Council President?
Reika-san, it seems that there are
about a hundred people in line.
For real?
President sure is popular.
I don't want this!
Please!
Stop this!
One week...
Just one week earlier...
I was this school's council president.
I'm...
I'm going to...
...be the comfort station?
You're lying, right?
I'm not lying.
It's a fair and square result of a completely random draw.
Ball = Council President
From this moment forth, you're the comfort station.
Thank you for your work as the council
president, Kujou Reika-san.
What are you saying?
I am the council president,
one who earned this title by winning the hearts
and minds of the students of this academy.
For me to be treated by those same
students as something of a toilet...
That...
That mere thought should be considered outrageous!
You would wish that, wouldn't you.
I believe in the students of this school.
The council president has really become
our personal comfort station.
Look, look. Reika-san's pussy sure looks miserable.
Crap, I really want to do it already.
No way...
This is all a lie...
Everyone... Why...?
What?
What are you going to do?!
A contraption of sorts used specifically for "public exhibition".
On their first day as comfort stations, these women undergo a
kind of a cleaning process called the "excretion treatment".
If you don't stay still, you'll get hurt.
Inserting the tube now...
No!
No...
No...!
Pull it out!
You've only consumed one pack.
We're just getting started, Council President.
No way... It's impossible...
Stop this.
Stop pouring it in me!
No, I don't want this!
President...
No...!
Please...
Let me go...
Let me go to the restroom.
It hurts.
It's going to burst out.
What are you saying?
You're virtually the toilet itself, you know.
Somebody save me!
I'm the council president!
Please!
Somebody release me from here!
Shut up.
I'm only here to see you become the sex tool.
Council president? How arrogant.
I kept fantasizing about how the President
would look as the new comfort station!
Hurry up and do it already!
To be honest, all that we are really
interested in is only your body.
No way...
Let it out!
I can't endure anymore.
It's going to come out It's going to burst!
Please. Don't look!
Don't look!
I beg of you all, please don't look!
No... No..!
Public Exhibition Day: Over.
Council president's self image,
Please... don't look at me...
and her dignity as a human being
now lies in shambles.
Yet, the ritual continues
into the "regional penetration ceremony".
It's about to begin.
You're crazy...
You're all crazy!
No way something like this would be forgiven...
But of-course it will, Council President!
That big thing won't fit in!
No way...
Stop, stop!
Farewell, President.
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!! It hurts!!!
Up until now, I have never been this glad
to be the com fort station facilitator
Pull it out.
Pull it out!!
This is the best.
It is the birth of the best comfort hole in
the form of Reika-san's alluring pussy!
I'm never going to...
I'm never going to forgive you all!
What kind of "comfort" are they talking about.
Waiting in line to violate me. Planning
to put me though nothing but pain.
This is definitely wrong!
You're all crazy!
Well, you might be right about that.
But even though you have been the
council president for a while now,
you did nothing but turn a blind eye to this system as well.
That's...
Moreover, as soon as you were initiated
as the new comfort station,
you went from a lady to a complete
nympho on your very first day.
It really is crazy, isn't it?
That's...
You have probably realized it by now, right?
That this feeling of pleasure is amplifying
with each passing second.
Why?
Why am I getting horny
while being raped in front of everyone?
Explanations are beyond logic now.
Your body is now simply accepting
itself in it's new role as a sex tool!
Stop this already.
Stop rubbing me with your cock.
If you keep on doing that,
I'm going to lose myself!
Reika-san, I'm going to make you cum.
I don't want to!
I don't want to cum!
I don't want to cum, but...
I can't...
I can't hold it in anymore!
I'm going to pour it into you next!
No, no!
Don't... Don't cum inside!
Please... Don't!!
Regional Penetration Ceremony: Over.
However, this was just the schedule for the first day.
She is actually going to start her life as
the proper comfort station tomorrow.
Council President will definitely be used by everyone.
Save me...
Calling the first three days of being the com fort station,
hellish would be a severe understatement.
Being treated as some sort of disposable item,
getting gang raped every single day.
I'm now only something that exists solely to be used.
That's right.
I endured it all and then finally gave up.
Otherwise, I don't think I would have lasted long.
What's this? How interesting..
That's why...
I tried to be strongly conscious about it.
She finally understands what her real worth is.
I tried to be stron I conscious about it
That my worth is nothing more than a public toilet itself.
Go ahead, please use my pussy however you want, master.
Oh, acting submissively now, eh?
Well, I don't hate it though.
I am a sex tool.
Something that's only there to be used
"By letting my inner self go, lean overcome
this ordeal as a mindless husk."
Or so I thought at least, but..
Could it be that you are actually getting a feel for this?
That's right. Shake your hips more!
Rub my cock!
Yes, I understand.
Yes, that's right.
This is an order.
This is not me.
This is not me!
Look, she's getting excited all over again.
This is an order.
I'm falling...
...down...
President!
On behalf of the student council, I am here to rescue you!
There,are no guards at this hour, so let's escape!
Come, hurry up President!
Vice-president?
President?
I'm sorry.
I can no longer fight this overwhelming
urge of wanting to stay in this place.
My body is...
My body is asking to be raped and abused!
N-Noway...
It would be best if you stay away from me.
I'll just cause nothing but trouble for you.
President!
You're the only one who treated me as the
council president until the very end.
Thank you very much.
One week after that,
I was raped by 411 men.
Including the teaching staff of this school,
there are a total 472 males.
Out of those, 411 of those violated my body.
Comfort Station
You're the worst!
Woah! Why the sudden anger explosion?
What's the big deal? I just went to pay a visit
to our school's new comfort station.
You love the concept of comfort station, don't you?
Okay then.
You just love the whole "sex tool" thing as well.
What am I trying to do?
Hey wai-Chika! You...!
That's...
I'm going to...
I'm going to become your personal comfort station.
Wai-! Calm down.
Why are you doing something like this?
What are you trying to say?
I am not good enough to get your horny?
That's not what I...
Sorry...
Th-Then what do you mean?
Even your thing is as stiff as a rock now.
This... This...
I took it in...
Sorry, Chika...
It feels good...
Are you okay?
You don't need to drink it if you don't want to.
This bitter liquid...
I really wanted to spit it out, you know.
Would you rather prefer some random sex tool over me?
Chika...
What?
You don't even know how I feel.
I love you.
I love you, Chika.
U-Unfair!
Saying that at this moment...
Me too, you know?
This is embarrassing...
I want to...
I want to fondle them some more.
I want to play with them!
Me, too.
I want to lick it.
I want to smell it.
I want to hear your horny voice.
More and more
No, inserting your fingers in my ass...
You pervert!
Hey, moan loudly for me.
I don't want to.
I would probably die of embarrassment.
For you to get this horny with just
my fingers in your butthole...
You're a world class pervert, aren't you Chika?
How cute.
Sh-Shut up!
Compared to you, I'm...!
Yeap, I'm a pervert too.
I want to put it in.
No way...
You really are the more perverted one here!
But you have no objections, right?
That's because...
I think it's gonna be an amazing experience.
I told you, right?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good in your butt...
But of course it does!
Crap, it feels so good that my hips just won't stop.
Chika's really a pervert!
In my butt...
Drill it deeper into my butt...
I'm going to cum!
It's coming. I'm cumming!
Me too.
Oh, no. I'm gonna cum.
Chika, I'm cumming!
Me, too. I'm going to cum.
Chika, I want to fuck you again.
Lower your hips.
This is so indecent
Making me insert that thing...
How is it Chika?
It's a completely different feeling compared
to when that thing was in my butt.
This is...
I'm going to increase my strokes.
This is bad.
I'm...
going over the edge...
Y-Your cock is twitching inside me.
I don't want to moan.
I don't want to let slip my voice overflowing with arousal.
It's beyond embarrassment to say the least...
It feels good.
Chika...
Please don't look at me. I'm sure that I have a very
embarrassing look on my face right now.
Look at my face.
Terrible, isn't it?
Nope. It looks cute.
Look at me. Look at me till your heart's content.
I'm going to look at it all...
I love you.
Ryou...
Look as much as want!
Violate me more!
Enjoy thoroughly!
More, more...!
Enjoy as much as you can!
Ryou, that's some expression you have there.
You too, Chika.
That's because...
I'm going to cum!
Me, too. I'm going to cum!
I'm happy.
Together.
Yeah, Let's cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...
I-It was extremely embarrassing, you know.
No going after other girls anymore, okay?
I'll... become your...
Then let's get started already!
You're such a pervert!
But you said you were going to be...
Shut up!
Then for this problem...
Takamine.
Yes.
Geez, you were waiting for the opportune
moment, weren't you?
My name is Takamine Chika.
I'm Sakurai Ryou's...
...personal pet now.
Well done.
That is correct.
His... sex tool only.
Let's go.
To a place,
beyond the extreme.