l had been there the whole time...
Miss Suzuna, what are you doing?
Oh, she is...
Miss Suzuna, stay away from her, please.
lt seems that something is coming to her.
Please, satisfy me, satisfy me!
Have you ever had doubts...
...about the daily ceremony?
Why it's a tradition, and what the ceremony's real purpose is...
What it does is awaken an evil spirit within women of the Kuraki family.
An evil spirit?
Yes, for the Expecting Moon--
How dare you, Saya!
Gohei.
Well, ah, let me explain...
l did it for Mr. Hayama's sake.
l try to discipline her as a lady because she's now ready to be...
Have l ever asked you to do that?
Don't forget your role at the Kuraki, Gohei.
Go to grandmother's room, lppei.
l'm sure she needs somebody to talk with.
Yes, Ma'am.
Suzuna.
Only person who comforts your sorrow, your pain and your desire...
...is Koichi.
The smell of cigarettes...
His smell...
Oh, no...
Stop!
No!
Ask me if you want to do more.
Mr. Hayama.
l know what you want, Tomomi.
N-No!
Stop!
No.
Don't do that.
Hayama.
Uh, hi.
Hayama...
H-Hey!
Hayama!
What's going on?
Hey.
No!
S-Stop it...
Stop!
This is not the real me.
No, l don't want to be like this.
No!
Hey, calm down.
Do you feel better now?
l am scared, too.
l feel like l've become a different person since l came here.
Use my bed and get some sleep.
lt will help you feel better.
Aren't you going to...
l don't want to sleep with a girl who's out of it.
Maybe when you're back to normal.
What's this feeling?
The smell of cigarettes makes me feel so calm.
l didn't like it before, though.
lt seems that this camellia feeds the lust of the Kuraki family.
This place is a regular haunted house.
Don't take it personally, but...
You'd better not get involved with Hayama.
He is not an ordinary man.
D-Did you see what we were doing?
What is wrong with this girl?
What?
Where is she?
l must be with her!
l don't want to be alone.
This is wrong!
But in romance manga, girls always become attached to their first man.
lt can't be...
lt can't be love!
lt is not love...
What happened?
Do you have something l can wear?
What?
You're bigger than l thought.
And it smells of cigarettes.
You've got to bring it back to me later.
l'm a little low on shirts.
Of course!
Then, you'd better go now.
You have to go to work or something, right?
You like to rest your head on a girl's lap, don't you?
This is to show my thanks for last night.
Huh?
From now on, ask me if you want to do it.
What?
l'm saying, you shouldn't go to Tomomi anymore.
Are you jealous?
Don't flatter yourself.
l mean, l should be enough for an evil man like you.
Evil...
What?
Since l'm evil...
Whose are bigger?
Compared to Tomomi's, whose are bigger?
Tomomi's.
But l like yours.
Liar.
You said hers would drive any man crazy.
Oh, man.
l'll have to punish a Peeping Tom like you!
l have only you.
Don't get me wrong.
l don't think l want to be your...
...special someone or anything.
Stop it.
Did l hit you that hard?
Tomomi...
Good morning.
Do you think Miss Suzuna will be angry?
About last night?
Why don't you forget about it?
What?
l'm on already?
Good afternoon, l am Ruri Yamato.
l've been given a special role for the 50th anniversary of this TV program.
l'd like to give my thanks to the screenwriter and casting director!
About my role?
l am so excited.
My heart beats faster every time l read the script.
l've been longing for a positive and cheerful role like her because l am shy.
l wish l could be like her.
l want to be like Sayaka Kurihara.
That hurt!
Well, Mr. Kuraki has good taste, indeed.
No, Stop it.
Mr. Kuraki fell in love with you at first sight.
You will be a maid for the Kurakis from now on.
Why did this happen?
l just want to disappear.
You want to forget...
...like l did.
lt's very easy.
Just close your eyes, and bury yourself deep inside of your mind.
l am...
l am Sayaka Kurihara.
Now, you forgot your painful memory, didn't you?
What are you doing here?
You're not allowed!
This is a great spirit pond.
l feel sharp.
And it's restored my power.
Go away.
You're interrupting a purification.
l think your maid's name is Tomomi.
You'd better be careful of her.
Don't get me wrong.
l don't care about Hayama at all.
lt doesn't bother me, even if he is being close with her.
Besides, he is not mine or anything...
Tell Hayama, then.
Why don't you tell him yourself.
l don't like to be pried by a jealous woman like you.
Jealous?
She is a retainer...
...for that witch, l guess.
No, it's not necessary for you to know.
Huh?
She disappears from the Kuraki house by night...
A few days have passed and nothing else has happened...
You are very good, Miss Suzuna.
You are good at it.
Do you really think so?
lsn't it fantastic?
Miss Suzuna made all the dishes for you.
Stop it, Sayaka.
What a lucky person you are!
Sayaka and Tomomi have been the same as always.
That day seems unreal now, like it never happened.
lt's better if l don't think about it.
l'll never understand, even if did.
But one thing has changed since then.
Hayama and l talk together all the time.
And now it feels natural when he calls my first name.
Let's see...
lsn't that typical.
What?
Sexual stimulation is very important for you and your husband, right?
You have to knock on the door before you come in.
l've got an idea.
You have these pink panties you've never worn before.
The pink ones don't look good on me.
Why do you know that?
Because l am your maid!
l hate to tell you this, because you're expecting him tonight...
Mr. Hayama won't be coming by.
He was called by your grandmother.
My grandmother?
No...
Miss Harukawa...
Why?
l've seen how you look at me.
Miss Harukawa, l can't...
l can't!
l want it deeper, deeper.
Don't stop, lio, don't stop!
l want more, l need more!
Since then...
He hasn't tried to do anything to me.
But he does kiss me, though.
Hayama?
Tomomi?
What's the matter with you?
l want to be with you tonight.
l...
l will be happy only if l am with you.
Wait, Tomomi.
Mrs. Yuriko also feels pleasure when l do this to her.
You have been waiting for your husband, haven't you?
No, l haven't.
You're lying.
Let's do it.
All right?
Relax.
No!
l know every sensitive spot of yours.
How about here?
Not there.
Stop!
To be continued...