Hey!
Lets go, Wataru.
Darling, lets go too.
Yeah, lets.
Wataru, step back more.
Oh, OK!
How about here?
l want to see too.
Here l go!
Nice shot Wataru.
lt's a luck shot.
Wataru-chan...did he really loose his memories?
That's what his father told me.
But it doesn't feel like he did.
He doesn't seem any different.
l'm getting warmed up.
Here!
lt does seem like he's more active than before.
What's wrong?
She has no chest!
Huh, what do you mean?
See?
l won't go easy anymore.
A-cup!?
What, l thought Wataru liked em' big!?
That means...
Amnesia!
Wataru?
Fine, we'll use these breasts!
To bring back Wataru-kun's memories!
Well, we can figure out what to do tomorrow.
Since we're at a California beach...
Yea!
And off!
Rena, have Wataru milk the cows.
OK, Dad.
Wataru.
Milking time.
R, roger!
Well, lets start with her.
Alright.
Sorry about earlier.
l didn't mean to startle you.
lt's alright, don't worry.
O, OK...
l will...l will take the responsibility.
Besides, his memory might return if he stays here!
Please, l want to help!
Not like that Wataru.
l think you're squeezing too hard.
O, OK.
More gentle and and softly squeeze...OK?
OK...
Yes, just like that, good job.
Good job, Wataru.
l bet you do the same to different girls.
Eh?
lt's a joke, l was kidding.
Well, l'll let you finish.
l'm going to go feed Ed.
Rena is surely one of a kind.
l can't, l need to concentrate.
Huh, the nipples...?
Come on, milk me.
Strongly...
Yeah...
You better do as she says.
So...
OK?
Come on Wataru-kun, milk us.
Yeah Wataru-chan, hurry.
Come on Wataru-kun.
Wataru-chan.
Wataru-kun.
Huh, what....?
Yes, good job Wataru-chan.
Very...good job Wataru-kun.
Wataru-chan.
What are you two doing!?
Get away from Wataru!
Who are you two?
How are you girls related...to Wataru?
Those chests...and Japanese!?
Wataru's dearest friends...?
These two are...
lf l didn't push Wataru then this wouldn't have happened..
l see, l never knew that happened.
But can you let us take care of Wataru-kun?
So yeah, can you please leave the room?
lt's time for grownups now.
lt might be too graphical for a child like you.
See you.
Hey, wait!
Don't bother us.
Rena...
Well Wataru-kun...
Time to start the treatment.
Treatment?
Yes, treatment.
ln other words, healing.
And we'll be using our specialty.
Sexual therapy.
Hey, remember this picture?
Yeah, l remember we....
Yes, that was sure...
We want to experience it again and we want to help you experience it.
So Wataru-kun....
B, but...
You know what to do Wataru-chan.
Continue where we left off.
But...
You're already really hard.
Here l go.
Here l go too.
Well, do you remember you liked these?
You're so hard.
Well Wataru-kun, is this helping?
Maybe he needs more stimulation.
Well, shall we try ''that''?
Yeah.
F, feels good....
Does this help?
Well, l'm getting wet...
That means we need to take the treatment to the final phase.
Yeah.
Well Tomoka, you first.
Understood, Dr. Love.
Don't kid around, concentrate.
OK.
So hard...
Wonderful, ''this'' hasn't changed a bit.
Wataru-kun...
Suck it, suck on them.
Wataru-chan, you're amazing!
More, give me more!
Wataru-kun, right there, there, there!
l feel it deep, very deep!
Wataru, feels good...
lt's amazing Wataru-chan!
l, l'm going to!!
Wataru-kun, me too, me too!
Well, you're the best Wataru-chan.
You remember something?
N, no...
Let me try it now.
Then, you'll probably...
No!
Rena!
E, Ed?
That tickles.
Alright, l won't.
There, there.
Thank you Ed.
Thank you for cheering me up.
Rena.
Wa, Wataru!?
W, what?
l'm sorry...
That l got you involved in this.
lt's nothing.
So you really like busty girls...
Maybe...
However...
lt looks like l made you depressed...
That's not it...
lt's my fault...
My chest...is at fault.
Chest?
l've said that your amnesia was a result of you bumping into me and falling onto the ground.
That's a lie...
l'm sorry...for not telling the truth...
The truth is, it's the result of my chest hitting you.
R, Rena?
T, that's...
When l knocked you out, l was afraid that you were going to hate me.
Because of the incident, l was holding down my chest to make them smaller.
But if these can help you out, l want to...
Wataru...
Please...
Rena!
Wataru!
l see how much you love chests.
That's not everything.
Rena, l love you.
l love you too, Wataru.
Hey, Wataru...
Down there too, please...
Yes, of course...
Wataru, it's amazing...it's driving me wild!
Rena, your tits are so soft and delicious.
You can be more rough with them...
OK.
Wataru, it's amazing...
Rena.
Can you make me feel good too?
OK.
Does this feel good?
Yes, it is...very....
Rena, use your mouth too.
lt's amazing, Rena.
Try using your breast, too.
S, so soft.
Does it feel good, Wataru?
Yeah, it does...
Faster, please.
Like this?
Yeah Rena.
l'm...
Sorry, l got you dirty.
lt OK, because it's your cum.
Wataru, come...
Rena...
Wataru, hurry, put it in!
K, here l go.
D, did it hurt?
No, l'm fine...come!
A, alright.
Wataru, it's deep inside!
Rena, you're really tight!
Amazing, you're amazing Wataru!
Wataru!
T, this is driving me wild!
lt's in very deep!
Rena, Rena...
Oh Wataru, Wataru.
R, Rena, you're so tight you're going to...
B, but it feels so good!
Wataru, l'm going to cum!
M, me too!
Cuming, cuming, cuming! Wataru!
So much...
You came a lot...
lt's twitching inside me...
Yeah, it is...
Wataru...
Rena...
You don't need to be worried, Rena.
Wataru.
Wataru...
Rena, it's soft.
Wataru, touch me more...
OK...
Wataru, you sure love breasts.
T, those tits...
W, why!?
U, um...
Rena?
Don't look!
Wataru-kun!?
Y, you alright!?
l think...?
Wataru!
Yeah, but...
l feel dizzy...
Wataru-chan, you alright?
Here.
Wataru-kun, you'll be fine.
This is Fumie-san's smell...
Wataru!