Toyotaro the protagonist... went to Germany to study...
He is crying in the old church in Carosdel.
How did it become like this?
The Body Hidden In the Mist
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Episode 01: The Chalk Which Falls Into the Nebula
Good morning!
Onee-chan!
Yui!
You have to call me Sensei while we're at school, remember?
Oh right, Takagi-sensei.
That was a strong gust of wind!
If you're not careful, the male students will see something!
I doubt that.
There isn't a male student here who wouldn't want to see your panties!
I was having a hard time getting a job as a tutor.
But thanks to a recommendation by one of my dad's friends,
I was offered a place as a teacher at this Nansui Academy.
Dad is an employee and with Yui as a student, we go to this school.
I'll go ahead to class, then!
G-Good morning!
She's an S, huh?
An S? I wonder what he means...
Good morning to you, headmaster.
It seems you're doing well, Takagi-sensei.
Yes.
The students have entrance exams coming up,
so please make sure that they can concentrate.
Yes.
Do your best so that we don't have any students losing focus.
Understood.
What is this?
Who did this? Who pulled this prank?
See you!
Onee-chan!
Yui, you're on your way home?
Yep!
Anyway, weren't there some lewd photos on the board today?
Yes, the staff room was in an uproar over who did it.
Isn't it obvious?
The culprit must be Murayama Kenji.
That can't be true!
Onee-chan, why are you defending him?
Is it because he's the headmaster's son?
T-That's...
Yes, because Kenji-kun is the headmaster's son,
we can't say anything bad about him.
Is it because you believe in him?
I... want to believe in him.
If that's what you say, Onee-chan, then I won't keep bugging you.
Thank you for understanding, Yui.
I heard an interesting rumor about those photos...
It seems that Kenji is under suspicion.
Kenji says that it's hurt his feelings,
and he says that he doesn't have the will to study.
No way...
All of this is your fault, Takagi-sensei.
U-Umm...
If you don't raise his spirits,
I'll dismiss you and your whole family.
I-I understand. I'll fix it, so please don't dismiss us.
Remember that everything is up to you.
I must do something.
I can't be a burden to Dad and Yui.
Kenji-kun!
So this is where you were.
Is there something you want?
Can I sit next to you?
Huh?
You didn't come to class. Is my lesson...
...that boring?
You suspect me of taking those photos, right?
No way! Sensei's always on your side.
I believe that you didn't take those photos.
Then show me some proof.
Proof?
Proof that shows that you're on my side.
W-What? How do I prove it?
It's easy!
W-What are you doing?!
If you make me cum with your hands, I'll believe you.
You're on my side, right?
Or was that a lie?
I-It wasn't a lie! I am on your side.
Then you'll do it, right?
It stinks...
For me to touch such a thing...
Sensei, hurry up!
F-Fine, then.
It's.. getting hotter and bigger...
Rub my balls too, Sensei.
N-No... What an indecent shape...
Hurry, please... Hurry up and cum!
W-What are you doing?
I'm going to splash your face with my semen, Sensei!
No! Anything but that!
It stinks...
This is semen?
Onee-chan? Why are you stopping?
Yui...
Did something happen?
Is someone bullying you?
No, it's nothing. I was just lost in my thoughts.
If so, then it's fine...
However, if there is someone bullying you, tell me okay?
I'll teach them a lesson.
Thanks, Yui.
I'm going ahead, then!
I can't worry Yui or Dad.
We can live as a family if I bear with this.
I'm not supposed to be sighing, but I feel down.
1 new message
No way!
There was someone watching?!
Who? Who would take...
No! W-Why?
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
If you don't follow
the instructions,
that photo will be
leaked across the
school campus.
Is Kenji-kun the sender?
No way. A teacher can't blame their students...
But... Who did...
Atsuko.
D-Dad?
Something wrong?
You look pale.
I-It's nothing.
Oh really? Well, don't overexert yourself.
Yeah, sure.
No, I can't talk to Dad...
I don't want him to worry about me any further...
Why do I have to put on these clothes?
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Wear the costume that's
inside the second drawer
of the desk. Don't wear
a bra.
Y-You may start your test.
Is obeying the texts all I can do?
For me to lure Kenji-kun...
Sensei... You want me to touch them?
I-It hurts If you grab me like that!
Even though I don't want this...
If I fight back, everyone will see those photos...
No!
I-I'm sorry, I...!
You said that you were on my side...
Wait! Kenji-kun!
From that day on, Kenji-kun stopped coming to school.
I heard that you flung Kenji off of his chair during class.
T-That's because... Um...
I don't want to hear excuses!
Kenji says that he's shocked. Now he refuses to come out of his room.
No way!
Normally, I would have already fired you.
Please! Don't do that!
I'll give you one last chance.
Get Kenji out of his room.
If you can do that, I might reconsider.
I understand...
Kenji-kun, Sensei was wrong. Please forgive me.
What should I do for you to forgive me?
Isn't that obvious?
This...
If you suck this, then I'll forgive you.
That's...
If you won't do it, then leave. I won't go to school.
We can't be pushed out of this town for my sake!
What are you doing to do, then?
F-Fine, then. I'll do what you say...
No... It stinks...
Amazing... This feels great...
This feels disgusting. I feel queasy... I don't want this!
I'm going to cum in your mouth, Sensei...
N-No! Really, no!
No, no! Don't look!
You want me to forgive you... don't you?
I don't want to feel good, but my legs feel numb!
What's happening to me?
I can't hold back...
What?!
N-No!
Stop! Stop it! Don't!
Damnit.
No way! Kenji-kun's cock is entering me!
I-It hurts! Please! Pull it out!
It hurts... Not only that, something inside me is!
I'm cumming!
No! Don't! Don't release it inside!
Please, not inside!
I... have been defiled...
I want to go home!
Stay with Kenji until morning.
Oh? You're not leaving?
Then we can do it again, can't we?
Wait!
No!
How long... is this going to go on?
All night... I was played with by Kenji-kun...
No!
No, your penis is filling me!
No, Kenji-kun! No more! If you keep going, I'll!
Onee-chan, where were you?
S-Sorry. I had extra work so I stayed at school.
Oh... Is that so?
Yui? Are you feeling alright?
Huh? Oh. I'm fine, thanks.
If you're well...
Then that's good.
The blackmail kept coming.
Ones that said I had to let Kenji-kun molest me on the bus...
No! It's entering me!
It's going deep inside me!
No!
Stop!
Everyone is watching!
W-Wait!
N-Not here!
No... Letting out so much...
Other ones said that I had to invite him for private tutoring at my house.
Hello there, Takagi-sensei.
Kenji-kun, you're here early...
Yeah, you did sent me a text after all...
Y-Yeah, I guess so.
L-Let's go to my room.
Atsuko?
D-Dad!
U-Umm... This is...
Oh? If it isn't Kenji-kun, the headmaster's son!
Sensei said she'd tutor me privately...
Oh really?
How diligent.
N-Now then, let's study.
By studying... You mean this, right?
That's...
Hey Sensei... I have a request...
I want to do you in this...
N-No! I can't!
You're the one who invited me here.
F-Fine, then.
In a place like this...
If Dad sees us...
So this is what a titfuck is like...
Lick the end!
My head is going blank!
Open your mouth, Sensei...
His hot cock is entering my mouth!
This feels great!
Atsuko! I brought some tea...
Dad! No! Don't come in!
He can't see me like this!
Sensei... He's calling you...
Thanks, Dad, but we're fine without tea for the time being...
What are you doing, Kenji-kun?
What am I doing? I'm putting it in since you're overflowing, of course.
No! Don't put it in!
What's wrong, Atsuko?
Atsuko? Is something wrong? Talk to me!
We'll have tea when we finish studying...
So just leave it outside the door, please!
O-Okay, I got it.
It's coming in!
It's rubbing against my insides! So hot...
No! Don't! Don't mess up my insides!
Your insides feel great when they squeeze me!
I'm gonna cum soon, okay?
No! If you cum inside me, I'll lose it!
No, don't cum! I-If you pour it inside me, I'll!
What... is going to happen to me?
This can't go on... But who is sending me the texts?
What?
If you don't follow the
instructions, I will leak
the photos across the
school campus.
I wonder what it's about... Maybe the sender will be there?
I-Is anyone there?
I-I came alone like the text said.
W-Who is it?
Dad?
W-Why are you here?
Atsuko?
What does this mean?
Why is Dad here?
What's wrong?
Um, well...
It's odd for someone to be at school at this hour.
Did you forget something?
Y-Yes! That's right, I suddenly remembered something important...
This is Dad... right?
Something important... like these photos?
No way!
Why does Dad have them?
Did you come here because you wanted to feel good?
You look more and more like your mother, Atsuko.
Dad?
The voice I heard from your room... was just like your mother's.
No way! That's a lie!
Can you let Dad hear your voice again?
No way... No way!
N-No!
What are you doing, Dad? Stop it!
You don't need to be worried, Atsuko.
Just leave it to Dad.
N-No!
No! Please, Dad!
No!
Dad! No, don't!
Atsuko, does this feel good? Atsuko...
N-No!
Dad's cock is getting hard... It's hitting me...
No! Dad! Please stop this!
Atsuko, you're overflowing already!
No, no! That's not true!
Dad, stop this...
I shouldn't be doing this with my Dad...
But I can't apply any strength to fight back!
Dad!
Why? Why do I feel good when Dad licks me?
Not there!
I came... Dad made me feel too good...
No!
Atsuko, will you make Dad feel good too?
No... No, Dad!
I'm your daughter! I-I'm not Mom!
We shouldn't be doing this!
It's entering me!
Dad's penis is entering Atsuko's deepest reaches...
Your cock feels good...
Doing it with Dad inside the classroom...
I'll fail as a teacher! We'll fail as a family!
My pussy is quivering from your thrusting, Dad!
No, Dad! If you thrust inside me any further, I'll lose it!
Oh no, Dad! Someone's coming!
Huh? Yui?
Onee-chan... Dad?
No, Yui... Dad, don't!
Atsuko, Atsuko!
Yu-Yui, this isn't what you think! Yui!
No! Even though Yui is looking, my pussy won't stop!
No, Yui! Don't look!
You can't look! I'm about to cum! I'm going to cum!
My mind is going blank!
Yui, you mustn't look!
Yui, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!