Well, this is the only thing left!
Big Tits Grand-prix!?
Yes, the winner gets $10,000.
So that's about...1 ,000,000 yen.
But that's not all.
Lets make is so that the one that wins will also get Wataru-chan, well?
Sounds like a plan, l accept.
Challenge accepted.
Wataru will be mine.
Sounds like both of you are pumped.
Well, may the winner have Wataru-chan's heart.
lt's here again this year folks!
The show we've been waiting for, ''Big Tits Grand-prix!''
After a rigorous selection process...
13 Big Tit finalists have made it to the finals, enjoy!
Well, we're not sisters here.
You are my rival.
l accept.
l don't intend to loose!
Alright, we will be moving to a segment called ''Appeal Time''.
Please enjoy these girls showing their performances.
Well, what do you think of Ms. Chan's ball technique?
Wow, that's amazing!
Our next competitor is...
Sweden's gorgeous beauty...
Fumie is up soon.
...please.
Ms. Shane Annison!
She will be performing an imitation of the infamous Beyon Bolrge.
Wow, how wonderful, look at...
Fumie-san.
Wataru-kun?
l came to cheer you.
T, thank you...
You nervous?
Yes, a little.
l know.
l want you to help me get relaxed.
You know what l mean.
F, Fumie-san, but...
Don't worry, come.
Hey...
Fumie-san, we can't!
Don't worry.
Hey you, you're up soon!
Where are you going!?
lt'll be quick.
What was that about...
Next we have Spain's Ms. Zoe Sabastian....
lt's been a while...alone together.
...you're right.
it might be tight because of the bikini.
Fumie-san, your tits are...soft.
Treat them as you will, they are yours Wataru-kun.
Yes, that's it.
l....l can't!
What's gotten into you Wataru-kun?
You're so wild.
Maybe America's weather?
Come on, don't tempt me, hurry!
Y, yeah...
lt's so..big!
Fumie-san, you have to keep it down, or else..
But....Wataru-kun, my boobs too!
Of course.
Wataru-kun.
Wataru-kun, it's g...great!
My body feels so warm, warm!
Feels like l'm...going to burn!
F, Fumie-san, l can't hold...!
Alright, cum, cum!
Wataru-kun...l want...your warm...cum...inside me!!!
Hey, water water water water!
What to do, anyway take her.
Someone take care of her!
And bring in the next!
lt's my turn...
l have to go.
Fumie-san...
Oh my, we have to look for a substitute.
....will save the show, are you ready?
Ms. Fumie Fusano!
Fumie-san is so great.
l knew it.
lt was so obvious.
lt's not fair either.
Am l right?
....will show us some Japanese calligraphy.
Hey you cherry boys, don't get funny ideas.
Great, it's great Tomoka-san...
l'll make you feel better.
Tomoka-san, it's, it's, it's...great!
ls it that great?
Definitely, it is great!
l guess we can say this is one of Japanese's secret techniques.
But yeah, this pose is very seductive.
Come on Wataru-chan.
lf you don't please me, l'll scream so that everyone can hear.
A, alright, here l go...
Wataru-chan, you're wild, really wild!
T, Tomoka-san, your inside feels great!
Wataru-chan, my tits, my tits too!
OK!
Wataru-chan, you're amazing!
l, l'm!!
Tomoka-san, me, me too!
lt's alright...cum, cum inside me!
Drink my milk!
Tomoka-san, your milk tastes good.
Yours too...
lt's delicious...
Next up, we have another Japanese girl!
Ms. Tomoka Fusano!
lt appears that she'll use her chest for a card guessing game.
She says that her chest will twitch if you guess the right card, wow!
l'll win this.
Our next girl will be the last one for this round.
An Arizona cowgirl, Ms. Lena Ashford!
lt's Lena's turn.
Hey Wataru!
Stay still.
Alright, here l go!
Marvelous, marvelous.
That was beautiful, Ms. Ashford.
Alright, give me the rope.
Oh, OK.
You're done, return to the backstage.
Uh, OK.
Alright, Appeal Time segment is over.
Thank you girls.
Meet me at the pool 15 minutes later, Lena.
...until then, take a break.
Wataru.
Do l...look funny?
O, of course not!
You're...
...really beautiful.
Wataru...
Lets sit.
Yes...
l'm...so happy that l met you.
My dad raised me like a boy, so this is my first time wearing a dress.
You're the first one to look at me as a girl.
lt's thanks to you.
Wataru.
Please...turn me into a woman.
Lena...
Wataru...do with me as you wish.
OK.
Wataru, you're so good!
l, l'll make you feel good too.
L, Lena...
Wataru...
Wataru, you're so hard.
lt's because of your soft chest, Lena.
Wataru...
Does it feel good?
Yes, very...
lt's getting bigger in my mouth, wow.
Lena, l'm going to cum!
Wataru, it's so delicious.
l want to feel good too.
Amazing, you're still very hard.
Wataru, l'm letting it in.
lt's...
ln!
Wataru, please fuck me hard.
Alright, OK!
Wataru...so wild!
Lena...
Lena, you're tightening around my thing.
lt's because you're so big!
Lena!
N, no...l'm going to cum.
Yes..together!
Cuming, cuming, cuming, cuming, cuming!
Wataru, it's warm...
Lena...
Everyone, sorry to keep you waiting.
We will finally announce our winner of the grand-prix!
There's been few accidents, but we've made it this far.
Before the announcement we'll have them dance for us!
Music start!
Such a beautiful view!
Everyone, take a good look!
l can't...
l'm so tired, l can't keep my eyes open.
By the way, who was the replacement of that girl who burned her hair?
l missed the announcement.
l don't know.
l was almost late for the stage as well.
l see.
But l think l've seen her before.
l'm thinking the same.
Come to think of it, l think so too.
Alright, no more teasing!
lt's time to announce the winner!
Big Tit Ladies from all over the world...
Who will stand a winner!?
W, who is it!?
Unbelievable, the winner is the one that replaced entry #5...
Mrs. Sakurai!
Come Mrs. Sakurai.
Come to the center.
M, Mrs. Sakurai, isn't she...
M, Mother!?
See, your mother is the best.
F, Father!?
Here's your $10,000 prize and the tiara.
Hey guys, hold this.
So, she is....
Everyone, please give Mrs. Sakurai another big round of applause!
Who would've thought Wataru-chan's mom would win.
We couldn't conclude our battle.
lt doesn't matter, we all had sex with him so you can say it was rigged.
You're right.
That's why we've decided to play with a new rule.
So l'm naked in the bedroom, does that mean....
Yes, we're going to have a foursome.
We have to be fair.
Who ever pleases you the best wins you.
But it's getting late and l'm pretty drained.
That's why!
A perfect reason to please you!
We're going to totally drain you out!
So yeah, that's the reason Wataru-kun.
Enjoy us to the fullest.
We'll be mad if you can't get it hard.
Well, that won't be the case with me around.
You mean me.
Are you two kidding?
Are you saying you are all that?
Let it be, she's more ''experienced''.
Are you saying l'm old?
W, we shouldn't be doing this.
You're right, the one who'll be choosing...
Will be Wataru-chan.
Wataru-kun, l can feel your hardness with my tits.
Of course Sis, my boobs are making him hard.
Lena, don't tell me you're....
B, but...
But l can't help it.
lt's because of your position.
Switch with me!
Shessh, you...
Wataru-chan, taste mine too.
Wataru-chan, i, it's wonderful!
Tomoka, don't cheat.
Wataru-kun won't be able to make a fair judgement.
Who cares about that.
l can't resist my temptation in front of Wataru-chan.
Stick out your tongue more!
She's right!
Wataru, it's delicious...
Wataru-chan, it's great..more, more!
This isn't fair, both of you.
Not fair at all...
Me too!
W, Wataru-kun!
More, more...touch it and make it more wet!
Wataru-chan, l'm...cum...cuming!
l'm sorry, Wataru-chan.
Wataru-kun's love juice...
Fumie!
Delicious...
l, it tickles.
Wataru!
Did we turn you on that much?
Y, yeah.
Lets have some fun then.
Yes, both of us together.
Alright.
H, here l go!
W, what's going on?
lt's rubbing me!
Wonderful!
Shesh, l was planning to do that with my Sis.
Don't complain, you're the one who suggested not to hold it in.
That's right, we're only doing what you've said...
l know, don't rub it in.
Wataru-chan...
What?
Hurry and finish up, then give it to me next, OK?
Wataru-kun, you don't need to rush this.
Take your time.
But, l'm going t, too!!
L, Lena, if you hug me tightly, you're going to....
Wataru-chan, you're amazing!
You just came but you're already extremely...hard!
Because it feels good!
B, but l think this is the last round.
lt can't be!
Wataru, hurry up and finish then give me some attention.
The night still young, you gotta keep us satisfied.
Stop bugging us!
lt's my turn right now.
Yes, keep it up!
Hurry up and cum.
No, not yet, not yet!
Not yet, yet, yet...yet!
Come, Wataru!
Come over here.
Wait.
Wataru-kun, get hard again.
lt's soft.
Are you really finished, Wataru-kun?
Can't be, you're not done yet.
Wataru-kun, come on...you can do it.
You can do it, Wataru.
Wataru-kun, doesn't it feel good?
Wataru...
Looks like only l can get him hard.
Fumie, Tomoka, go feed the cows and the horse.
Why do we need to do such things?
Who cares why.
We're too tired to get up anyway.
Last night was wild.
Yeah, so wild that he hit his own head against the wall.
You two are unwelcome guests.
l think you can at least do that.
lt's your fault for keeping Wataru-kun here.
After all, his memories are back.
Hey, forget about that.
Lets wake Wataru-chan up.
Through our ways...
l agree.
Wataru, wake up.
How long are you planning to sleep, sleepy head.
lf you don't wake up, no reward for you.
Who are you...girls?
Why are you all naked?
Where is...this place?
Huh, l'm naked too!?
Wataru, not again!?