I can't take it anymore! My body is going to melt!
It's hot, it's so hot!
Put it in, please, I beg you!
Please ram it into my dripping wet pussy!
I want it, I want it so badly!
Your cock, please give me your cock!
Put it in, hurry up and ram it in!
Karen wants a big cock inside her dripping wet pussy!
Mom...!
It feels so good, I'm gonna cum...
No, you mustn't do that!
Please stop, Mom!
S-So good—!
Stop it, Mom! You can't—!
Mom—!
I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Mom...
She's been taken over by the Zoid, and can't restrain her lust.
She'll probably break down, and...
Stop it!
Erena...
Mom said that she doesn't have any memories after being attacked by the Zoid.
Emille... Where are you?
Presented
by Shikkaku
Erena, she will do it!
W-What is this place?
W-What are those things?
What—?
No! Stay away!
This is disgusting!
Onee-chan, help me!
L-Let me go!
Onee-chan, I'm scared!
D-Disgusting!
Onee-chan, where are you? Onee-chan!
S-Stop...!
What are you going to do?
No, stop! Please!
Onee-chan, please save me!
T-That's—!
Stop it!
That's Emille's precious place!
Please don't touch me there!
No!
I-It hurts!
Onee-chan! Onee-chan, please save me!
It hurts! No, no!
Stop it! You'll break me!
It's... it's going in so deep!
N-No! That's—!
That's my butt, you can't put it in there!
S-Stop it!
You mustn't put it in there!
I-It hurts...!
M-My butthole, it's—!
Please don't spread my butthole!
N-No! You can't—!
It won't fit, it won't!
My butthole is going to break!
S-Stop it—!
I-It hurts—!
It's... it's—!
My butthole is going to tear!
It's going in, it's going into my stomach!
Onee-chan, onee-chan!
Help me! Onee-chan!
Onee-chan...
Where are you?
Where am I? Where could I be?
Where is Emille?
Abandoned. You were abandoned.
Abandoned...?
This is bad!
I sense that the Zoid is attacking Emille!
What should we do?
No!
I can't leave Mom like this!
Onee-chan chose Mom over Emille...
No way...
That's right, she chose to abandon you instead of your mother.
She chose Mom rather than Emille...?
No! No, I won't believe it!
I'll never believe it!
Onee-chan... Onee-chan is Emille's only—
Onee-chan is only for Emille.
She's mine.
She belongs to Emille.
Do you want Erena?
Do you want her back?
I want her... I want her back.
Because Onee-chan belongs to Emille.
She's only for Emille.
I will not let anyone else have her.
No matter what.
Then, accept me.
Accept...
That's right, you want her back, don't you?
If I accept you, will I get Onee-chan back?
Will she come back to Emille?
That's right, I shall grant you powers. The power to do it.
The power to get her back.
Do you want it?
Give it to me.
Grant me the power!
M-My pussy—! It's going to tear!
More! Violate Emille more!
Give Emille the powers!
You are the one who must do it, Emille!
Taisetsuna mono mamoru tameni
I will never give up
watashi wa mou keshite akiramenai
to protect the precious things
ikuta no kanashimi wo koete kagayaku
I will overcome the many sorrows
watashi wa knight of serene!
as I am the Knight of Serene!
Shown the way from the stars above, magical girl Erena, reporting for duty!
Ovi, do you sense anything?
I don't sense anything.
I normally only sense the presence of the
Zoid, so I'm not sure if I can sense Emille...
Hey, Ovi!
Emille!
Onee-chan.
Emille! Thank goodness you're safe!
Erena, be careful! I sense the Zoid!
W-Watch out, Emille!
Ano hikari de korosu tabi
Every time you kill with the light
Emille, run! It's dangerous here!
Watashi no yoru, with you
the night, it is with you
It's got me!
Damn you—!
kudakete
Break away
Emille, run away! Get out of here, hurry!
Run away? Why would I do that?
sagashitemo yumewo
Even if I look, my dreams
Emille?
Erena! You're mistaken, Emille is—
kokoro kara nigeru
they escape from my heart
Ovi!
chikkatte oboowoete
I swear, and remember
te watashi no itami yo
that this is my pain
E-Emille?
sekai ga yugamu
The world is being twisted
subete kiyeru, kawaruno makkurani
Everything is disappearing, changing to darkness
Emille...
That appearance...
W-Why, how...?!
I'll make sure you have fun, onee-chan.
W-What are you going to do?
You'll soon find out.
Ouch!
M-My breasts! It's getting hot!
What is this?!
My breasts, my breasts!
My breasts are like cow udders!
No, stop it!
If you suck on them so much, they'll come off!
This is...! My tits will break!
Ouch—!
Whoa, onee-chan, does it feel that good?
Your nipples are standing up. How lewd!
You're wrong! It's because my breasts are being played with like this—!
No! It's stretching me!
It's already stretching too much!
Stop it! It won't stretch further! I'm serious!
It can't stretch anymore!
If you do that, then—!
No! It's going to come off!
By nipples and breasts are going to break!
Your enormous breasts are fantastic, onee-chan.
My breasts...!
So hot!
What's this? My breasts feel like they're burning!
It's going to light up in flames!
Let it come out!
No, something's coming!
Something is going to come out!
My breast milk is going everywhere!
It's still coming out!
This is too much milk!
Even though I'm not pregnant, so much is coming out!
It's like I really am going to be pregnant!
We're not done yet. We won't be finishing things off yet, onee-chan.
I'll violate your breasts, onee-chan.
Stop it! This is wrong! It's really wrong!
This totally isn't normal!
No! Don't push them into my breasts!
They're... inside my breasts...!
Stop...! Please stop right there!
They're inside my breasts!
M-My tits, they're mixing them up!
It feels too good!
I-I'll become a perverted magical girl!
It feels way too good!
So good, my breasts feel too good...
I don't care if my breasts get pregnant, so do it more!
It's coming out, semen is coming inside my breasts!
Onee-chan, you're beautiful.
Emille wants to stay with you forever.
So let's join the Zoid together, onee-chan.
I love you, onee-chan.
Does onee-chan like Emille? Does she love her?
I like you too, Emille.
I do love you.
Onee-chan!
But...
But, I can't join the thing that killed Dad, and made Mom like she is...
Emille...
So Onee-chan thinks Mom and Dad are more precious than Emille.
That's not it! Get a hold of yourself, Emille!
Let's go home together, to where Mom is.
E-Emille, is that...?
I'll make you feel better with this.
Don't! No, Emille please, anything but that!
Onee-chan belongs to Emille!
Emille loves Onee-chan the most!
Stop, stop it, Emille—!
Does it feel good, onee-chan?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can make you feel good whenever you wish!
See? Why don't you come join the Zoid?
No, Emille—!
Emille!
I'm coming, I-I'm gonna cum—!
Emille came too...
Did it feel good, onee-chan?
I can't... I can't, Emille...
I can't come with you to join the Zoid.
It's that bitch's fault, isn't it?
That's why you refuse to come with me!
You're the true only family to Emille!
That bitch... That bitch is...!
You-You're... Emille?
Is it you, Emille?
I'm glad you're okay!
You... If you didn't come around...
Huh?
Onee-chan would have been Emille's forever.
E-Emille...?
You... I'll break you apart!
No!
Mom?!
Emille, what are you doing?!
Stop it, Emille!
You-You can't, Emille!
We're family!
Family members aren't allowed to do this—
What? You should be happy!
Isn't this the long awaited family reunion?
P-Please don't!
Get a hold of yourself!
Shut up!
Your pussy is great!
It must be good because you've been violated by the Zoid all long!
No, s-stop it!
E-Emille! This is—!
You're so dripping wet,
you've definitely become a perverted cum dumpster!
Don't say such things! P-Please!
P-Please, no more!
What are you talking about?
She likes it because it feels good.
Say it honestly, say that it feels good!
Say that you're dripping wet from your daughter violating your pussy!
I-It doesn't feel good...!
We're connected like a family!
My thick cock is in the place where I was born!
This pussy feels so good!
This is it, isn't it? This is where I was conceived, wasn't I?
Stop—!
Emille will destroy the uterus where she was born!
T-To think that I'm going to cum from my daughter violating my pussy!
I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming—!
I'm cumming!
Stop it!
Stop it now!
I'm going to break her pussy!
I'm going to crush it!
So good—! My daughter's super big cock is amazing!
My uterus feels too good! I'm going to cum!
Go on and feel more of it!
Feel it with your rotten dripping wet pussy!
Go on and cum like crazy!
Your daughter will be sure to shoot her semen as well!
I'm going to get pregnant from Emille's big cock...
M-Mom!
Get pregnant, go on and get pregnant!
Get pregnant with Emille's Zoid baby!
I'm cumming!
M-Mom!
Onee-chan, be sure to closely watch what happens next.
Because, it's your entirely your fault, onee-chan.
Soon, you'll only have me left.
Emille?!
My stomach, it's—!
Mom!
Mom, hang in there!
Something's going to be born, I'm going to give birth—!
Something is being born?!
N-No—!
It's... it's coming out!
No!
Erena...
Mom!
Hang in there! Mom!
Erena... i-it seems like it's the end for me.
No, Mom! Don't say that!
T-The moon...
"The moon?"
I remember when I gave birth to that Zoid.
I was captured by the Zoid and was trapped on the moon...
The Zoid are on the moon?
Please save Emille...
She's probably on the moon, too.
Mom!
Sorry Erena... be nice to each other.
Mom?!
Mom...
Mom...!
No!
Mom... Mom...!
Erena!
Ovi!
That was close!
That's a Zoidling, a full-fledged Zoid monster!
It quickly joins with other creatures to make more of itself!
Hurry! Kill it now!
Mom...
Erena!
Knight of Serene!
Erena...
The Zoid are on the moon, and Emille is probably there too.
Ovi, we're going to the moon.