Long ago,
there were four dragon gods that guarded
the four gates of the city.
Byakko of the West,
Suzaku of the South,
Genbu of the North,
and Seiryuu of the East.
These gods, with dragon blood in their veins,
fought to protect their city.
Their battles happening in the shadows of history.
Even after their city fell, their bloodlines remained.
However,
with the passage of time, their blood thinned,
until Genbu lost his powers completely.
Sensing a crisis, the remaining gods
desperately sought human heirs,
vessels to carry on the blood of the
four gods to future generations.
Until that was done, the descendants of the four gods
stopped fighting and focused on creating offspring.
Those possessing the strongest genes are
Seiryuu, Byakko, Suzaku, and Genbu.
These four have the DNA that will sustain the existence
of the gods. Their battle is about to begin!
Haramasete Seiryuu-kun!
Episode 1: Make A Baby With Me
I know this is sudden, but...
will you... with me... um...
Four Gods Family: Suzaku Natsuhime
Will you do...
Wh-What, Suzaku-senpai?
And why are you so angry?
Don't make me be more explicit.
If you refuse me, then to save face, I'll have to kill you.
But then I too will no longer be able to live!
This can't be.
This isn't like you, Suzaku-senpai.
And... what do you want me to do?
What?
Must I say something so embarrassing?
But I couldn't hear you.
I want you to do me.
Huh?
Do... That's what I'm saying.
Pardon?
I want you to have sex with me!
I want you to impregnate me!
S-Sex with Suzaku-senpai?
The Student Council President that everyone worships?
The school's heroine?
Many times, many times, I've spied on her at swimming practice!
My beloved Suzaku-senpai!
Sex?
Hey, hey, Seiryuu?
Didn't you hear me?
I need to protect the bloodline of the four gods.
Sex with Suzaku-senpai...
So that means you don't love me.
You're only after my dick.
That's not true!
I've done some research on the bloodline
for the sake of preserving the four gods.
And you and I, Tougo...
Senpai is only interested in my dick and balls.
And here I was, devoted to the
sexiness of Senpai in her swimsuit.
He's not responding to verbal seduction. Then let's get physical!
Well? What'll it be?
Tell me you'll make a baby with me,
Seiryuu Tougo!
S-Senpai, um, y-your boobs are pressing against my back.
I'm well aware of that.
S-Suzaku-senpai's boobs!
Awesome!
Well? Do you feel like making love to me now?
C-Can I.... Can I trust that you're not joking, Senpai?
He's not even using his powers.
Seiryuu really is the strongest of the four gods.
Suzaku-senpai, what are you...
If you don't let your power flow forth, I'll entice it from you.
Your lower body wants me.
This is Seiryuu's? It's so big, and it's going to be inside of me.
S-Senpai, we don't need to rush.
I have feelings for you, too.
What?
In that case, why wait?
Senpai, I'd like to date you first.
Don't you want my virginity?
Whoa, are you really a virgin?
You fool! I wouldn't surrender my body to just anyone!
I seek only the one with the strongest genes of the four gods!
Ah, that's right. Senpai is only interested in my Seiryuu genes.
She doesn't care about me.
Sorry about that. I didn't mean to mislead you.
This is for the sake of Suzaku's bloodline. I admit it.
But even if it weren't for that, I'd still offer you my body.
Senpai, do you really like me?
You might not remember, but we met when we were children.
Ever since then, I've...
And even if my only goal were to preserve Suzaku,
I still wouldn't give my body to someone I didn't like.
Won't you help my dreams come true?
I can't hold back anymore!
Suzaku-senpai!
So you're finally in the mood. I'm happy.
Do you like my breasts so much?
Your tits feel fucking great.
Really? Then do with them as you wish.
I never dreamed I'd end up like this with Suzaku-senpai.
Wait a minute. What about that letter from Dad this morning?
- What the hell is this!?
The Four Gods     Seiryuu Estate
Dear son. I am doing well.
Please listen to me.
Ah yes, I have selected two possible wives for you.
Please choose one of them before I return.
Stupid Dad! Just when I thought he was finally coming home!
Two possible wives?
So who is the other one?
Shit! Stupid Dad.
Maybe the heat made his brain melt or something.
Tougo.
Four Gods Family: Byakko Akiha
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
Ah, th-that's right. Here.
What's this?
I-I made myself a box lunch.
And while I was at it, I made one for you too.
So...
Akiha cooking box lunches? That's a first.
Are pigs flying?
Can I eat with you today?
Sure.
To-u-go-kun!
Good morning!
Oh, good morning, Kitami.
Don't get so close. I can't breathe.
Aw, Tougo-kun, you're blushing!
I'm not blushing!
And besides, I'm not into boys!
Four Gods Family: Genbu Kitami
Just a bit more.
Kitami-chan, aren't you the facilitator
of the Heian Martial Arts club?
Shouldn't you get to school early?
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Well, then, Tougo-kun,
see ya later!
Boy
He may not look it, but he's Genbu's descendant.
And he's a guy, too.
What's going on?
I-I'm not sure.
I've been waiting for you, Seiryuu Tougo.
Suzaku-sama was waiting for Seiryuu?
S-Suzaku-senpai?
I knew she'd show up.
They're both from the four gods.
I guess that means they share a bond.
G-Good morning, Suzaku-senpai.
Good morning, Seiryuu.
Good morning, Suzaku Natsuhime-senpai.
Good morning, Byakko Akiha.
So you came to school with him.
I see.
You've made the first move.
You misunderstand!
This is a normal occurrence.
Akiha, would you please back away from Seiryuu peacefully?
I'd never do that.
I won't let you have Tougo.
Then until he's mine, I suppose I'll
have to settle the score with you.
I gladly accept...
Senpai!
Akiha! We're gonna be late!
Seiryuu Tougo!
Come to the pool after school.
So, not knowing what she was talking
about, I went to the pool after school.
And she said, "So you chose me after all".
Perhaps the two potential wives Dad mentioned
in his letter are Suzaku-senpai and Akiha?
Senpai.
Do you know how to make a baby?
E-Everyone knows that!
I researched the topic last night in my father's magazines.
First, the man and woman press lips. They kiss.
My first kiss with Senpai!
Tougo's tongue.
Senpai!
Senpai's tongue is so sweet.
When he sucks on my tongue, my pussy clenches tight.
What do we do next, Senpai?
Next, we... Next, we...
get naked, and you caress and suck on my breasts.
So delicious.
Senpai's boobs.
Do you really think they're delicious?
You're almost like a baby.
Don't suck so hard.
Your nipples are stiff.
If you suck that hard, it makes my nipples and pussy throb.
What's next?
After that, both man and woman, well,
press their crotches together.
Eh? What do you mean?
They press their... I can't say that!
Tougo's is so big, and it smells erotic, but I love it.
S-Senpai!
She's sucking my dick.
Tougo's dick! So lewd, but I love the flavor.
This feels great, Senpai!
According to Father's pictures, you line up your bodies like this.
Senpai's crotch is before my eyes.
On the other side of this thin fabric is Senpai's pussy.
Tougo, you're getting bigger.
This is the first time I've been touched there.
You're getting wet. Can I see it?
If you want to.
This is Senpai's pussy.
This is the first time anyone's seen it. I'm kind of shy.
Senpai!
S-Sorry, Senpai!
Amazing! So much came out.
Tougo's semen...
Seiryuu's dick isn't shrinking.
I can't get pregnant unless he ejaculates in me.
Suzaku-senpai, are you sure?
Seiryuu Tougo, do you love me?
When Suzaku-senpai shows that
expression, no one can resist her.
Ouch!
This is my first time. Seiryuu is taking my virginity.
Suzaku-senpai...
Tougo...
Suzaku-senpai is fucking me.
Seiryuu Tougo is fucking me.
It hurts.
But I'm finally bonding with Tougo. I must endure it.
My pussy is throbbing. This feels strange, very strange.
My insides... My womb is hot.
Something is whirling inside me.
Yes, I kind of like this.
Yes!
So hot!
My pussy is so hot!
Put it in!
Put it in deeper!
Deeper, deeper!
T-Tougo, thrust harder!
Use your cock to plow me. Plow deeper.
- Impregnate me!
Senpai, even if you ask me, I...
- My insides... need you more.
Senpai's pussy is surrounding my dick...
Your dick!
My pussy!
Now I see. That's how... I can feel it.
Tougo's dick...
...is filling my pussy!
Suzaku-senpai is using the words "dick" and "pussy".
Whoa! Senpai, I'm almost there!
Your semen! Keep it coming, inside of me!
- Make me... Make me... Make me pregnant!
Ngh!
I'm cumming!!
He's ejaculating... into me. Tougo's semen... is inside of me.
I'm so hot.
My insides are so warm.
So I became one with Tougo.
Ever since that time,
I had always wanted to be with Senyuu Tougo.
You fool. You'll never make it with that attitude!
You must carry on the Suzaku name!
No! I don't wanna! I hate you, Father!
Darling, Natsuhime is only five years old.
Shut up!
Unable to tolerate my father's strict rules any longer,
I bundled my belongings into a backpack and ran away.
What are you doing out here?
I got lost. Who are you?
I'm doing some road work as training!
Hey, do you know the road that leads to town?
Yep! I'll take you there.
That boy helped me.
I didn't find out he was Seiryuu until later.
Akiha-chan, three coffees. They're all ready.
Coming!
Akiha-chan is my favorite!
She's beautiful and one of the four gods.
I can't believe it!
Tougo, aren't you coming here today?
I really had sex with Suzaku-senpai.
Seiryuu's semen is inside my pussy.
I can get pregnant right away.
No, no! I hate spiders!
Hey, Moemi, do you know where Tougo is?
Seiryuu-kun? Someone saw him headed for the pool.
The pool?
Huh? But the Swimming Club isn't practicing today.
It couldn't be...
That was mean, Senpai. Ow.
Senpai, are we supposed to have two children
in order to sustain both family lines?
That's right.
And you must marry me.
Yes, but it's my choice whether I marry you or Byakko.
What?
We just bonded, and you say you won't choose me?
No, it's just that this is the first I've heard of it.
And it's an important life decision. I'd
like more time to think about it.
Now I see.
I suppose I was too forward.
I'll do anything to show you that I'm superior.
Senpai is getting desperate!
The snobbish and proud Suzaku-senpai...
G-Gosh, I wonder what I should do?
I'll do anything!
Then take off your swimsuit.
R-Right here?
Yes, right here.
At the pool that you and the others always practice in.
Very well.
S-Suzaku-senpai's... naked!
Is this okay, Tougo?
Yes! V-Very pretty, Senpai.
Now, sit on that diving board and spread your legs.
Then expose your pussy and beg for it.
Beg for it?
You want to get pregnant, don't you?
Is "sex" synonymous with "pussy"?
What about a woman's vagina?
They're both called "pussy".
Do it.
Seiryuu Tougo...
Use my pussy, and let's make a baby.
This is so embarrassing, Tougo.
Something's different.
The semen you just put in...
Suzaku-senpai, if you want more, you'll need to beg harder.
Tougo, please put your dick inside of my
pussy again and fill it with your semen.
Make me pregnant!
Th-That's perfect! I think I'm getting a hard-on.
Now let's practice our start.
On the diving board! Suzaku Natsuhime-san!
Ready.
Start!
Suzaku-senpai!! Oh! It's tighter than last time!
Tougo, not in a place like this.
We're having sex where you usually practice...
I feel strange again.
So rough.
- It's hitting so deep.
We're having sex at the pool where you practice every day.
Yes!
This is really hot!
This is amazing! I'm really getting off from being forced into this.
I'm getting roughly handled in a deserted pool. Ah, I feel strange.
I feel so good!
Why? Why does it feel so good?
- Oh, no!
Here! Suzaku-senpai!
- Not so roughly!
You're so cute!
- Not there!
I'm cute?
Don't say strange things, Tougo.
That's the first time anyone's said that to me.
I'm embarrassed yet very happy.
Tougo, amazing!
Your dick feels so great!
So deep. So deep...
Senpai!! Senpai's pussy...
It's squeezing me hard! It's so tight.
Yes. Yes!
Tougo, yes!
It still stings a little, but...
Senpai! This is practice! Let's take a lap around the pool.
Huh? What?
Let's do a wheelbarrow.
And go to the window over there.
Oh, no.
No! They can see.
Senpai, look. Right before your eyes.
There are some underclassmen.
No! This is embarrassing.
No, stop. They'll see!
Senpai! It's okay! They can't see.
You know this is a magic mirror.
But they're so close. They'll hear me!
It's embarrassing.
Oh, no. Stop it.
I don't want them to find out.
Come on, let's show them.
The school's heroine, Suzaku-senpai,
is getting fucked.
No! Don't!
Is it really that embarrassing, Senpai...
Tougo, this is amazing. Your dick...
It feels so great!
- Even better than before!
Senpai, I want you more.
Me too. I want... more of... Tougo.
- More. I want to feel you more!
Um! Senpai, I'm almost there.
Then cum! Fill my womb full of Seiryuu semen!
Ngh! It's coming. I'm cumming!
Hot stuff is shooting deep inside me!
Wh-What's that?
Tougo...
Akiha?
And here I was worried about you.
What are you doing?
Tougo!
This was just...
You're too late, Akiha.
Seiryuu and I have already bonded.
So give up on him.
Tougo is going to marry me!
You can become a single mother!
Hey...
Oh? The single mother is going to be you, Akiha.
Go ahead. Get angry, and get pregnant.
Kitami?
Kitami.
Did you come to interfere with our battle?
No, I've come to join the battle!
What the hell? This doesn't concern you, Kitami-chan.
So butt out!
But I also love Tougo-kun!
I'll allow you to have an affair with him,
but I'm going to be his wife.
What did you say?
How foolish.
Can a guy become a wife?
I'll find a way to turn into a woman by then.
Naturally, a woman able to bear children, Tougo-kun.
And Suzaku-senpai, the martial arts match is a week from now.
During that time, the battle is off.
If you break this rule, you won't be able to compete.
A rule is a rule. It can't be broken.
Akiha, we'll put our dispute on hold until then.
Very well, Senpai.
But I won't go easy on you in the competition.
Hmph.
Meow! Don't leave me out of this!
I-I get the feeling I'm listening in on
a very disturbing conversation.
I... What's gonna happen to me now?
Well, Natsu-chan got there first.
I'm not gonna let her win!
I'm gonna get plenty of revenge in the next episode.
I'll do this and that.
Oh! I'm too ashamed to say the rest out loud.
Damn you!
Tougo already bonded with me!
Are you going to make a cheater out of him, you big-titted bitch!?
You aren't married yet, so it wouldn't be cheating!
Hey! Don't forget about me!
Tougo-kun's dick belongs only to me.
But you each can take one of his balls.
What the hell are we supposed to do with those things?
Aki-chan, by the way, why aren't ya moving?
I'll move plenty next time. Look forward to it.
I'm not out of this competition.
So make sure to see us then.
Ta-dah!