It's all because I don't set things straight...
Saeki-san,
Mio,
Reiko-senpai,
Rika-sensei...
I ended up sleeping with all of them.
What should I do... ?
Hello everyone, pleased to mee t ou.
I just transferred to this school.
I'm Kamiwazumi Maya.
I hope that we'll get along well.
Fault!! S
- The new rival
Sugiyama-san.
Can I bother you for a bit?
See you tomorrow then.
Shuuichi-
Maya?
Why is she here... in this school?
Are you in the tennis club, Sugiyama-san?
Well, yeah.
Why'd you ask?
Oh, nothing.
I just wanted to know.
I don't have any ulterior motives.
So please don't try to fantasize that I'm interested in you.
I'm getting a different vibe from her than from before.
Sorry for stopping you.
Well then, Sugiyama-san, see you later.
What was that?
Maya...
Tennis club
Hey, look.
I thought of using this costume
as the one I'll wear at our
cosplay cafe booth for the upcoming annual school festival.
Well Shuuichi?
My, my.
I wonder what you're getting dazed for?
Perhaps it's already stiff down there?
Wai- senpai.
Wanna do me in this costume, Shuiichi?
We already did it before here, didn't we?
Besides, I'm curious about cosplay sex.
I like you, Shuuichi.
Won't you do it with me?
I will show my embarrassing side only to you.
Shuuichi...
You like butts too?
But you can't touch that.
Shuuichi, I said you can't, didn't I?
No... my butt...
It's dirty, so you can't...
Don't open up my butthole like that!
Shuuichi, I won't let you do that....
My mouth is getting completely filled with Shuuichi's cock.
It's really hot and it's twitching a lot.
Just imagining taking in this stiff thing already
makes me really wet down there.
Please, Shuuichi,
hurry up and make me feel good with this cock.
Shuuichi...
suddenly entering me like that...
No...
If you do it that intensely,
I'll...
It's hitting deep in me.
It's completely different from my first time.
Shuuichi...
If you do it like that, I'll break...
I'm sorry...
If you...
If you do it like that to me...
I'll really break...!
Tennis club
Shuuichi, your cock is reaching to the very end.
No...
Don't push it that deep.
My insides are getting all messed up.
My mind is going blank...
Something is...
Shuuichi, I can't hold on, I'm going to lose it already.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
Sorry,
I went out of control.
It's okay.
As long as it's you,
I don't care even if I'm treated like a toy.
I already told you that I love you, right?
Besides,
I kind of like being roughly played with like this.
Hey,
if you want it,
I'm up for another round.
Don't tease me like that.
Put it in already.
Shuuichi, I feel hollowed out...
This is really good... Being done by you...
Shuuichi, let's do this more often, okay?
I don't care if we're not in an official relationship.
This is good!
I love it!
Senpai, you're really a masochist, aren't you?
No, that's not it.
I just wanted to feel good.
Because when I'm done like this, I lose it...
Seems that I'm badly needed for someone
as perverted as you, senpai,
so I'm going to discipline you thoroughly.
No, please don't!
If you "discipline" me like this,
I'm really going to become a pervert.
Now senpai, say it.
No...
I'm not a pervert.
Say it, Reiko!
I give my gratitude to you,
so please discipline me with your amazing cock!
Please, discipline it more,
my lewd pussy!
My slutty pussy and your cock...
Shuuichi, I'm cumming again.
I'm cumming!
It was a lot different from when we first did it, right?
Yeah.
Listen, Shuuichi.
We'll keep this a secret from everyone, okay?
But let's do it again, Shuuichi.
The rain's pretty heavy...
It doesn't seem that it'll stop soon.
Sorry for making you accompany
me to buy groceries, Shuuichi.
Hey, Shuuichi.
Can you listen to my request?
What is it?
From now on, when we are alone,
I want you to drop the "senpai", and call me Reiko.
Please, Shuuichi.
O-Okay, Re-Reiko.
Thanks, Shuuichi.
I love you.
Hey, Shuuchi, I've got an idea to warm our bodies up,
what do you think?
Look, Shuuichi, look carefully.
It's Shuuichi's fault that down here
it's starting to feel really hot.
I don't really feel this aroused normally.
But weren't you the one who asked me to watch?
You're really mean.
Is it that fun to tease girls older than you?
I won't allow you to make a fool of me...
That's why I'm telling that you were the
one who wanted to have it seen,
and making that, your pussy, really wet like this.
No, my thing here isn't like that!
Don't call it "thing ", you call it "pussy", Reiko.
I'm going to cum!
I'm climaxing while being teased by Shuuichi.
I'm cumming while making my pussy wet.
I'm cumming while being seen by Shuuichi.
In gratitude for teasing me, I'm going to make you feel so good
that you'll feel like you're reaching heaven.
You don't have to restrain yourself if you're about to cum.
Make your cock twitch as much as you want Shuuichi!
Shuuichi, not there...!
You can't touch there!
Reiko's butthole,
I'm going to pierce it with my dick.
If you thrust your cock there, I'll break!
No, please don't do it...
No!
I'm starting to feel horny with my butt.
Shuuichi, hurry up and spray your semen all over me!
I’m cumming!
And you've put it inside just now!
Shuuichi, I've just cummed...
Let me rest for a bit
or I'll cum again!
Shuuichi, you're getting intense from the start...
You're really a bully.
You also teased those girls intensely, didn't you?
You can't hide it from me.
Because I'm also a tennis club member.
You've already done it to Ai, Mio and Rika-sensei, haven't you?
But that's okay.
I love you, Shuuichi.
That's why you also need to do it to me a lot.
Besides,
I'm going to do something even
more amazing than those girls.
I'm going to give everything to you,
so you can do whatever you want with me.
My insides feel so full...
Does it really feel that good in the butt, Reiko?
That's...
It feels too good to have it stirred in there.
Thrust your cock deeper!
Oh no, my voice is...
Shuuichi, someone might hear us.
It's entering my pussy...!
Your cock is rubbing inside me.
Reiko, I'm going to cum inside.
Fill my pussy with your semen.
Spray it inside my womb!
Do you want to be pregnant before you graduate, you pervert?
I'm fine with it.
I want to have a child with you Shuuichi.
I'm going to do my best to raise the child after I graduate.
Give it to me.
Your semen!
Pour it in my womb!
Shuuichi, I really love you.
I love you.
Kamiwazumi-san.
I thought somebody else came in,
but it's just you.
I saw someone's shadow at the rooftop.
But why are you here?
I just wanted to be alone.
I see.
I said I wanted to be alone.
You're really are a thoughtless person, it seems.
What's so funny?
You seem to keep saying harsh things, but...
I really can't hate someone like you after all.
You can't hate me?
What in the world are you saying?
I'm saying that I feel you flaunt an
aura similar to my senpai, Date.
Your personality is totally different,
but you're somewhat similar in mood.
Maybe that's the reason.
I don't understand a thing you're saying.
Won't you go away already?
Well then, see you again.
Seems that I'm starting to understand why she likes him.
Sugiyama-san, Sugiyama-san.
What is it?
We're in the middle of class so don't talk to me.
Sugiyama-san, I'm interested in you.
Please go out with me.
Huh? What did you just say?
I said that I like you now.
Or maybe this kind of approach is more preferable?
Hey...!
Just stay still there.
People around us will notice.
I said wait...
What in the world are you thinking?
Just be quiet.
Just make your penis stiff.
I said stop.
We're in the middle of class.
Then can we do this if we're not in class?
Okay, so please...
So for you it doesn't matter who it is, after all.
I just wanted to see you ejaculate.
Just make your penis stiff.
The tip is starting to get wet...
Are you about to cum already?
Quite quick there.
It'd be bad if you cum here, Sugiyama-san.
Stop that act already.
That was close.
I was already about to burst it out.
What is she thinking?
It feels good...
I don't know what she really wants to do...
It's my first time feeling this good.
For me to feel horny with this...
My clitoris is getting this stiff.
So lewd...
It's like that person's penis.
There's still some of it left...
The stinking scent of a male.
I get aroused as I try to remember it.
This isn't enough.
I need it more intensely...
If someone sees me masturbating in this place...
I-I'm about to lose it.
I wonder what the look on his face would be if he were here.
Since when were you there?
Well...
Forget about it already.
It can't be helped if you saw me.
What is this thing?
It doesn't seem to be the same penis I saw earlier in class.
Does the texture of this stocking really feel good?
Please look at this.
My feet are dripping wet with your secretions.
Why are you doing this?
Because I like you.
Don't you have any other reason, Kamiwazumi-san...?
Sugiyama-san.
No, from now on I'll start calling you Shuuichi-san,
so I allow you to call me Maya from now on.
Wait, that's not what I'm asking.
Shuuichi-san, address me as Maya.
Now call my name.
I want you to show me your embarrassing self.
I'll accept it all.
Maya...!
I never thought that semen could be this hot.
It won't get small after just one shot, eh?
Why don't we continue?
Now, preparations are complete.
You can go on anytime you want to.
I'm giving you permission to do it.
Are you okay?
It's not really that painful.
So it's this painful...
Your rough penis is filling up my pussy.
I'm glad that it was you.
It's all thanks to the size of your penis
so it's not that painful.
You don't have to force yourself to endure it.
Don't mind me.
Just thrust your hips like an animal.
Does it feel good?
I wouldn't know if it feels good or not!
Just cum already.
Cum by yourself.
So this is it...
It's rubbing a different part in me
and it's starting to feel good.
I'm really getting wet
and starting to make lewd sounds.
I'm about to cum.
Even though it's my first time...
I can't hold it in...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm waiting at the rooftop
Kamiwazumi
Are you serious about that, Maya?
You're really a blockhead, aren't you?
Acting like a big sister, while being completely oblivious
that your boyfriend had already been stolen from you.
What are you saying?
Why are you doing this?
Maya, you weren't like this before.
Maya, we were like real siblings back then, right?
I guess there was a time like that.
Maya...
I'm going to trample down
the one person important to you, Shuuichi-san.
Just like how you trampled on my heart before.
If you don't want the one important to you to get hurt,
then disappear somewhere at once.
This eyesore of a hair...
Should go somewhere where I won't ever see it.
Shuuichi-san.
You heard it, right?
Yeah.
I hate that woman named Date Reiko.
She denied everything about me and desecrated me.
The Senior Student and Transfer Student