Yu-Yui...
Dad!
Stop this, p-please!
No... Really!
Dad, you can take a bath now.
Huh? Okay.
Photos? What's up?
These... These... D-Dad, a-aren't these-?!
Hmm? Oh, those are of Atsuko, aren't they...
Why is Onee-chan...?
Huh? What? Why? Huh? These are...
Those photos were secretly taken and put up on the school bulletin board. These are the originals.
What? No way!
Don't tell me... Onee-chan...
She was called out by the headmaster.
Apparently she tried to seduce a student.
Lies! No way! Onee-chan wouldn't...
She wouldn't try to seduce a student!
She must have been b-blackmailed! Otherwise she wouldn't have!
That Atsuko...
I thought that she was still a kid, but she turned out to be such a lewd woman!
Huh? Dad?
Isn't she about to happily suck that student's cock?
She has such a lascivious look.
Dad! What are you saying?! Onee-chan has a lascivious look? Hey!
Those once tiny breasts sure have gotten larger!
It's going to happen to you too, isn't it Yui?
You'll seduce men just like Atsuko, won't you?
That isn't good, Yui!
I think I'll have to punish you.
Dad? Wait! Hey! Listen to what you're saying! Hey! Dad!
N-No! Dad! Let me go!
Oh? You've grown nicely!
D-Dad is groping my breasts!
N-No, Dad...
Hey, stop it. Stop it!
The Body Hidden In the Mist
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Episode 02: Yui's Butt Is...
N-No! Stop it, Dad! Not there!
D-Dad!
Huh?
Hey, this isn't right.
We're family, right?
Yes, we are. I am your dad.
So you'll listen to me, right?
No!
No, Dad's touching me down there...
What's this, Yui? You're wet?
No!
No no no! No, Dad!
Please stop this! Onee-chan will be home soon!
Getting wet from something like this, Yui...
No, don't look at me like that!
Dad, why are you doing such horrible things?
It's because you're cute!
Dad...
No! He can see everything!
Dad... Please, what's happened to you? Hey, Dad!
No, Dad! No, not there!
Don't lick Yui there!
Dad is opening up my pussy and licking it!
Yui, having Dad lick you arouses you, right?
That's not true...
Dad! You're kidding, right?
We're not really going to... Are we? No, no!
No no no! Dad, you can't! We're family!
You can't put that inside me!
No...
No way, Dad's cock is hot... It feels strange...
Wha, D-Dad... Dad...!
You can't! You can't! You can't!
It will only hurt for a moment. Okay, Yui?
No... It's entering me... Dad's cock is entering me!
Ow... Dad, it hurts!
Oh no... I was made a woman by Dad's cock...
It's warm inside you, Yui.
O-Ouch! Dad! Ow... Ow...
Dad looks happy...
He's more than happy to put his cock inside his daughter...
Dad's cock is going in and out!
It feels unpleasant...
This is wrong!
Wha? No, Dad! That hurts!
Dad... Hey, don't! Don't! You can't cum inside me!
No, Dad! Not today! Today's a dangerous day! Dad!
No!
Noo!
No way...!
Dad made me a woman...
Is he going to make me a mother too?
I can't get it off... I can't get the smell off!
I... I can't talk to Onee-chan about this!
Yui, what's wrong?
Onee-chan, where were you?
Sorry. I had extra work so I stayed at school.
Onee-chan! Onee-chan...!
Oh... Is that so?
Yui? Are you feeling alright?
Huh? Oh. I'm fine, thanks.
N-No... I can't tell her...
Yui... Dad can't hold back any longer!
D-Dad, we can't keep doing this... Okay?
Oh? Oh, sure. This is the last time, Yui... This is the last...
I didn't know that the pain would go away this quickly...
My pussy is making lewd sounds... I'm feeling flushed...
It's okay, let it out!
Ever since that day, Onee-chan hasn't come home.
Whenever I ask Dad, he just says that she's busy with important work.
Dad! What happened to Onee-chan?!
Last time I saw her, you were doing the same lewd things to her that you did to me!
Yui, Atsuko came to me of her own accord to beg for my cock.
Of her own accord?
Nonsense! Onee-chan wouldn't...
I guess she wasn't satisfied with that student's cock...
That Atsuko...
Anyway, Yui... Dad wants to...
No!
So this is?
D-Dad!
Please stop doing this!
Yui! You're soaked!
Have you become a lascivious girl like Atsuko?
Don't tell me that you attract guys for the want of their cocks?
D-Don't be stupid!
Neither I nor Onee-chan would!
Then why are you so wet?
I-I don't know...
No... Everyone will see me!
How can Dad let that out here?
No, his pulsing cock is rubbing against my thighs!
It's hot... He's about to let it out!
So much is coming out... It'll stain my clothes!
What happened to Dad?
He's doing such lewd things! Even to Onee-chan...
Is it because we don't have Mom anymore?
But we're his daughters! Dad!
What do you want?
If you want something, hurry up.
Wait, aren't you that guy from Onee-chan's class?
W-What? What do you want?
Why are you getting scared? Disgusting.
H-Hmph! I don't want to hear that from some pervert who's aroused by their father.
W-What are you talking about?
No way! He was watching?
Y-You're the same as your sister, Takagi-sensei!
S-Shut up! I don't want to be told that by a pig like you!
W-What? I-If you say things like that, then I'll spread this around!
T-That's... Why do you...?
Isn't that spying?
I knew it!
N-No! I wouldn't do that!
I obtained this through legitimate means!
Like I can believe that.
Anyway, since you're the headmaster's son, you can get away with almost anything, right?
I-I wouldn't do...
Oh, t-that's not all.
I-I'll spread this on the Internet!
I thought that fathers molesting their daughters happened only in porn games.
What do you want me to do?
H-Hurry and get on with it! You're wasting my time...
You're aroused by this?
T-That's not true!
It's!
You don't need to be embarrassed!
W-What are you?
No! If he keeps rubbing me there, I'll!
My technique's making you feel good, isn't it?
D-Don't be ridiculous! There's no way!
H-Hey, w-wait for just a second! I'll be right back!
As if! I bet you're going to run away.
No... I-I'll leak! S-So!
L-Like hell you are! As if you're going to pee...
What are you saying?
S-Stop kidding around! H-Hey! Please, let me!
No! If you keep rubbing me... H-Hey, stop!
Hey! Please, please! Hey!
N-No... No, stop! No!
I-I can't hold it in!
I-It's coming out!
N-No!
No...
You wet yourself? How old are you?
It's pouring out! Looks like I'll have to put it in and reset you!
N-No...
Please, stop! P-Please!
So you're alright with these being spread round?
Along with Sensei's photos?
F-Fine, I get it.
H-Hurry up and put it in!
Hmph!
A-Amazing!
What's with this guy? Doing me like this...
No! Don't! W-Wait! You can't!
N-No! No way!
He came inside me! Today isn't safe...
For not wanting it, you sure were aroused by my technique.
I'll make you feel good some other time.
You fat freak!
Don't be mistaken, you quickshot!
Hmph!
Atsuko, Atsuko!
No! Yui, this isn't what you think!
No! Even though Yui is watching, I can't stop!
No, Yui! Dad, don't!
What's happening? Has everyone lost their minds? Even I'm...
Attention, Takagi Yui-san from year two, group A.
Please make your way to the headmaster's office immediately.
This is... Onee-chan!
Onee-chan?
She's here.
So you're Takagi Yui-kun.
I heard from Kenji...
Um!
I hear that you kicked my dear son.
You and your family are dismissed!
What?
Get out of this academy immediately!
U-Um...
Save your excuses. We don't have a place for your family here.
That is all.
N-No way...
I can't believe it! We're dismissed? I... Onee-chan... Dad...
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me. S-So, um...
However, it seems that Kenji has taken quite a liking to you,
so it's not like it's not negotiable...
Huh?
If you please Kenji, we may reconsider...
Right, Kenji?
Yeah.
So when a guy wants you to please them, it ends up like this.
Takagi-sensei could titfuck me, but you don't look like you can.
This bastard! I knew he did something to Onee-chan!
You sure are bad at this.
Sensei was much better.
I'm going to make the likes of you finish quickly!
For me to be sucking this guy's cock...
No, it stinks! It's disgusting...
But if I make him feel good, then...
W-What?
Quit stalling!
W-Where does he think he's touching?!
Does this tickle?
N-No! No way!
No! He's playing with my butt!
Unfortunately, I'm only interested in this...
Did you know that you can feel good here, too?
His finger is entering me!
N-No more!
If I loosen you up gradually, you'd be surprised how big it can get.
I-It's going in again! Why is he going for my butt?
N-No! I-It's dirty!
Your butt sure is beautiful.
W-What?
Did he just call my butt beautiful? My butt is nice?
It's untouched? It's not like it's ever been violated...
No!
It's getting quite loose now.
I can't hold back... I'm taking this end!
N-No! Not there! No!
C-C'mon, you mustn't talk!
N-No... Why is he putting it in my butt?
It won't fit!
No way! No!
It's hitting my butt. It feels unpleasant!
You're quivering over here. Do you feel good?
What is he saying? Of course it doesn't feel good!
This can't be happening! I can't take it in both ends!
Why...?
I can't think straight!
No! It's bitter... N-No more...
Why! Why?!
Dad! Why?
You said you wouldn't do Yui, that's why I...
O-Onee-chan...
N-No! Don't look...
Onee-chan saw me doing this...
Doing something so embarrassing!
Oh! You're tightening around me!
Yui! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
This... This shouldn't be...
P-Please, I'll... I'll take her place! You said it would only be me! Why is Yui...
Ask that guy over there.
You two were sold to this town.
By doing so, your father can take as many photographs as he wants!
No way... Lies... No way...
Onee-chan is... crying...
I... must protect her!
O-Onee-chan, I'll be fine... okay?
Please, don't do anything more to Yui...
Please, I'll take her place! So just don't...
What are you saying, Onee-chan?
I'm the one who's going to protect you, Onee-chan!
Give me more... Give it to me in the butt!
Yui! Yui!
Onee-chan is crying...
It's okay. As long as you're with me, I can...
Since you're with me... My body is getting flushed...
You're getting even more turned on by your sister watching you?
You're such a pervert!
No, that's not true! I'm just embarrassed that she's seeing me like this!
My body is just getting hot from embarrassment!
You think this feels good? How can I feel good with something so thick inside my butt?
Huh?
Dad?
Atsuko...
D-Dad! What are you doing?
No, no! Dad! We can't!
O-Onee-chan!
No, Dad! We can't!
Onee-chan!
Yui... Yui!
Yui, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Onee-chan! Don't cry! I'm fine!
When you're with me, my butt starts to feel good!
Even if it's my butt, it's starting to feel good!
No! Yui! Don't say that, Yui!
Onee-chan, are you feeling good too?
You look happy when Dad is mixing up your insides with his cock!
T-That's not true!
I don't! My pussy isn't starting to feel good!
Onee-chan, my butt is... I'm going to cum!
No! My butt feels too good!
N-No!