Saki-san.
Yes?
Did you really go and changed your clothes?
Yes, in the station's toilet.
Look.
T-That's...
That time...
Yes...
This is the very erotic underwear I wore last time in the hotel.
Sorry for showing you this side of me...
I haven't worn this till now because I was shy.
After one year, me and Takumi-kun, are back to our memorable place.
Let's go.
SubDESU-H Presents
Aneki...
Saki-senpai, again...
Saki-senpai
again
Even now, when I remember that time,
My body gets hot...
I’ve done many dirty things in front of Takumi-kun.
I masturbated putting just a vibrator in my ass.
Takumi-kun, look, look...
S-Senpai...
It's like my stomach is being stirred...
This one too...
S-Senpai, you don't need to push yourself.
I’m all wet just by smelling your dick, Takumi-kun.
I...
Senpai...
Takumi-kun... there...
Please come in...
I-I can't...
Senpai... I-I also...
T-Takumi-kun... My ass...
It's touching...
T-Takumi-kun, please don't make me wait... put it in...
Not yet...
I want yours... I want yours, Takumi-kun.
No... that part is starting to get wet...
Senpai...
Takumi-kun...
What should I do?
What if someone notices that I'm wearing this kind of attire?
Maybe I'll be raped.
That time it was so intense...
No.. I’m over thinking it...
Should we go to the park, Saki-san?
Yes.
I've removed my clothes...
The video... have you started recording the video?
Y-Yes...
It’s embarrassing...
It’s so hard...
Yeah, my nipples are so hard...
The pussy is all wet and dirty, ain't it?
Yes.. it's all wet...
No... Even though I’m embarrassed,
I’m feeling good because of the camera.
Takumi-kun, what are you going to do with the video?
I-I want to masturbate while watching this video.
You are doing it, huh?
Record it... my different parts...
S-Saki-san...
Takumi-kun, you are masturbating while watching me do dirty things.
You are doing it as you rub your dick so many times.
It feels so good.
It's like...
I'm being raped by Takumi-kun through the camera.
Saki-san, are you going to cum?
P-please, record the part when I cum...
Hey, lets go to the toilet.
Eh?
Takumi-kun, do you remember?
The first time we did it in here?
Yes...
This is my memorable place, which I can't forget.
That time, I was caught by you while I was masturbating.
And I was pushed down suddenly, right?
N-No...
I was surprised at first, but...
I was nervous and so horny.
I-I'm sorry.
I couldn't help it because I was embarrassed, but...
I couldn't stop because it felt so good.
Saki-san...
D-Don't tease me...
No, don't look!
Stop it Takumi-kun, it's dirty there...
Don't!
Takumi-kun, don't!
Don't...
Takumi-kun, please be more gentle...
Senpai... Senpai!
Takumi-kun!
I'll break if you do it so intense!
Senpai... Senpai... Senpai!
No!
I'm...
Senpai... senpai... senpai... senpai...
I’m done.
Eh?
This is the one I wore today for my club activity.
I sweat a lot today so it's really smelly.
Sa-Saki-san...
Saki-san!
W-We did it only once that time,
B-but I wanted to do it a many times.
Me too...
I smell a lot of Saki-san's smell...
P-Please rape me a lot today, Takumi-kun!
Yes. That's it, lick it... lick it some more.
Saki-san, this part of yours is so dirty.
Saki-san, I’m...
Takumi-kun, me too...
Sa-Saki-san...
Good... good...
It feels so good!
S-Saki-san...
My nipples... My nipples feel good...
It's so intense...
It's reached my inner most part...
My pussy is being destroyed...
I'm... I'm being raped...
No!
N-No I can't... I can't...
Good... good...
I-I’m cumming...
I'm cumming!
After that, we couldn't stop.
And we had sex so many times.
It seems we did it too many times.
It's our anniversary.
Sa-Saki-san...
T-This...
Eh?
I'm giving it to you.
It's a one year anniversary gift.
I’ve ripped it though, eh?
S-Saki-san’s different kinds of smells...
Take care of me from now on.
Saki-san...
I...
Again...
Ok, let’s do it.
Aneki...
Masakazu.
Hey...
The body soap is gone.
You not done?
What's it? Don't just...
Hey, give it to me quickly.
What are you doing?
Eh? N-No...
Thank you.
P-Please prepare it yourself before entering the bath.
Beautiful elder sister...
I'm sure many people will get jealous of living with such a sister-in-law,
But everyone doesn't understand.
Dirty
Elder Sister...
Umm... the finger food will be...
Oh! Found a chikuwa!
TL Note: chikuwa is a fish paste cooked in a bamboo like shape.
Please do something about your outfit!
Sheesh...
Hm?
Don't mind whatever it is I wear inside the house.
Look, change your clothes immediately.
I-I'm a man after all.
Hmm, a man, huh?
Even though you're a virgin?
I’m not a virgin!
Ok, ok.
Hey...
It's so good.
W-What's it?
It's not bad to take away the man's first time, right?
And it’s a brother-in-law’s.
It's like a dirty situation.
Do your best cherry boy.
Your sister will cheer for you.
I’m not a virgin!
Ok, ok.
Can’t I do something about this kind of lifestyle?
Sis' presence is too dangerous for me.
Where's Masakazu?
Where are you?
W-Wait...
Here I go!
Stupid! What are you doing!
Your room is over there.
Sis?
Oh, I’m sorry...
W-W-Wait!
Let me stay here, it's too troublesome, I’ll sleep here.
Wait! Stupid! Stop it!
Hey, you're quite drunk.
Yes I am.
Because it's a weekend.
I must release my stress.
Stop it.
Get away you stupid sis.
I wont.
I wont stop.
No~
Hey if you don't stop, I will really do it.
Sure, if you think you can then do it...
Virgin-kun.
Hey wait, are you serious?
Hey...
What are you doing? Stop it...
D-Don't!
Masakazu!
Really, you're 10 years too early to push me down.
If you want to have sex that bad,
I’ll teach you everything from the beginning.
Prepare yourself.
I was surprised with my sis' scary face which I hadn't seen yet.
The skin is still covering it, even though it released so much.
So dirty...
Just as I expected from being so young.
You’re already this big.
Sis...
Sis, I can't...
Wow, you release a lot.
Sorry, I'm already...
What are you saying? This is just the beginning, we're not done.
You wanted to do it with me, right?
Sis...
H-Hurry...
With what?
Hurry up and put it in.
Huh?
I won't understand what you want if you say it that way.
Say it clearly what you want to put in.
I-I want to put my dick into sis’ vagina.
Where is the "please"?
Please.
Sure, I’ll let you put it in.
Sis don’t make me wait, please put it in quickly.
It's already so hard.
Do you want to put it in so badly?
Yes, I want to put it in.
I want to put it in.
Ma-Masakazu.
Then, watch it properly.
The part when your dick enters into my vagina.
Please bear with it a little bit more.
I’ll let you put it all.
Look, it's all inside.
How is your first look at a pussy?
Don't be quiet and say something.
It's hot and all wet.
You can feel it with your dick, right?
Yes, I can feel it.
Then I’ll put it in deeper.
Hey, your hands are free, are you going to just leave my boobs?
S-Sis...
You’re cumming, right?
Your dick is already sticky.
Sis, I can't...
Hey, if you're truly a man, why don’t try to make me cum.
Sis!
It's okay to pound me hard.
Do it rough, do it really rough.
That's it Masakazu, do it rough, do it rough.
It's hot... My pussy and your dick...
Sis...
I-It's alright, you can cum.
S-Sis. Sis!
W-Wait! I can't do it anymore!
What are you saying?
There's no time for you to rest.
W-Wait...
Si-Sis!
After that, I was squeezed so much that I can't even remember.
Sis, is really amazing.
Right there...
And after that, I...
Hey...
Please bring me a can of beer from refrigerator.
Eh?
O-Ok.
I can't be obedient...
Aneki... My sweet elder sister.
Senior 4 will be on sale on summer 2011.