Hey!
What a bold uniform! Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm used to it now.
Anyway Sayaka, aren't you self-conscious lately?
I bet you're wearing something like an honorary student would; do you really have to hide it?
No!
I wonder what an honorary student wears underneath?
How lewd! I can't help but imagine...
W-What do you want?
You like that girl, don't you? You've been gazing at her.
That means we're buddies.
Isn't it fine? Let's have some tea.
Or rather, how about some fellatio with your uniform on?
What...?
Let's just start with being sex buddies.
How about an adult relationship?
I won't disappoint you... I'm quite good at these things.
Cut it out!
Huh?
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Ryoujoku Famiresu Choukyou Menu
Thanks for your work!
Thanks for before...
I really can't stand people like him.
He was such a pervert, it gives me goosebumps!
Sayaka, I thought you didn't like accessories?
It was a present-
O-Oh right! The present!
The apron you gave me on my birthday!
Thanks for that, I'll hold it dear.
It's fine here.
Good night then!
Um, can I walk you home when you have work?
I want to spend time with you. How about it?
S-Sure!
Showing off so early in the day!
Did you two perhaps stay at a hotel? On your way to school from there?
N-No, we didn't!
Make sure you don't overdo it.
Sayaka asked me last time: "What's a dangerous day?"
Checking out so quickly, you should have enjoyed it for a bit longer!
Don't be mistaken! I just didn't want you to come into my room, I...
You even paid for the rooms! How persuasive!
You masochist!
I just don't want to owe you!
You're always talking about work!
You came home late last night too,
or rather, are you hiding something from me, Nee-san?
I-I'm working right now! We can talk back at home, okay?
Jeez.
I heard that your sister came after you.
Can you introduce her to me? After all, she's going to be my future little sister...
Y-Your little sister?
My little brother's coming to the shop too...
Taking me to such places...
You pervert.
I was jealous when I saw my brother.
You guys get along too well!
That's because-!
Isn't that normal for a lovers' relationship?
I-I even give him fellatio...
Really?
I-I just did what you told me, Masashi!
No honorific? Getting all friendly are we?
No...
You've really become my woman.
Don't be so conceited!
I've soiled it...
Even though you bought it for me...
Silly, I'll buy you another one.
I'll...!
I'll throw all of my underwear away!
Hey now, you want me to replace them all?
I don't know...
I really don't know, but... But-!
I want you to choose them!
I want to become your perfect girl!
What? Then you've totally become mine.
Because, because if you keep thrusting, I'll lose it!
Keep doing me with your big, hot, hard... No-!
Even if I cry and dislike it, I can't win against it!
Big... What?
Your cock! I mean your cock, Masashi!
No, it's mine... It's a cock only for me!
I can't get it out of my mind! Even during class it's all I could think about!
I was about to go crazy!
Masashi-!
Masashi!
I-I'm about to...!
I'm gonna cum, so let's cum together, let's do it together!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum, so-!
Please let it out like this!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming-!
I guess it's a cute uniform, but...
Everyone will see my panties if I move!
Rather, don't tell me Nee-san works here because of the uniform...
Huh?
Hey, Sayaka.
H-He gave it to me as a present.
Do you prefer this one over the one you begged me for?
I don't know.
I wonder if I need to pee because I'm relieved.
Rather, who has these old-style toilets anyway?
Staff Only
Customers, please
refrain from using
this facility.
You would think Nee-san would complain straight away if she saw this place.
Because...
This kind of revealing uniform...
It's too much for me.
Ne-Nee-san...
Moemi, what's with the uniform? Also, what were...
S-Sorry, when I saw this uniform, I wanted to wear it for a bit, uh...
I'm really sorry.
Good night then.
That was quick... I wish I could spend more time with her.
Oh well, we've come a long way, so I guess I'll have to bear with it for today.
What?!
That's not possible, is it...
I was made fun of at school...
Let them say whatever they want.
Jeez, it would be a pain if the teachers found out and confiscated it, right?
So that's why you can only put it on when we're together, okay?
I guess it can't be helped...
Hello young man, it's been a while.
That uniform makes Sayaka-chan look quite slender, doesn't it?
I hear that you're her classmate.
No? Am I'm wrong? That's what she was saying...
I saw you two getting along, so I asked her if you were her boyfriend.
She said you were just her classmate.
Actually, I'm going out with-!
I ended up cheating, sorry about that.
Huh?
She sure looks like an honorary student...
Despite her looks, she's quite the lewd type, apparently...
You bastard-!
I'm very sorry, even though I said that we were buddies...
I'll leave you with that, today.
Huh? You're in charge of closing up?
I think it'll take a while, you should go home without me.
No, I'll wait. I have something important to ask you...
Uh, no, I mean I can't let my girlfriend walk home alone.
You're allowed to go home already, Sayaka.
I don't want my paycheck to be deducted...
My brother might get worried and barge in, you know...
But Masashi, I can't leave you like this... Can I?
Your sister is waiting too, isn't she?
She's even younger than me,
so I think she should at least have someone she can rely on...
No need to get hard, Moemi-chan...
No...
Don't!
I said you don't need to get hard... You're a naughty girl...
No-!
Also, those old style toilets aren't common, are they?
You were so cute, getting flustered like that...
Don't tell me that was your first time using such a thing?
No! Don't touch-! No!
However, you should take another step forward next time.
Otherwise, you end up splashing a bit if you're a girl...
No-!
I-Isn't this enough? It's embarrassing...
No need to hold back, we've got lots of time!
I ended up getting fired, you see...
Do you get it? I'll need you and Sayaka-chan...
It means you two need to comfort me.
No! What are you doing?
No way-! Y-You can't...
You can't keep relying on your sister forever.
Let's become more independent.
I'm loving this!
I was a teacher once, so I love to teach kids!
It hurts-! N-No, s-stop it!
I'll make sure that you'll happily make money like Sayaka-chan does.
Never mind that-! Please, pull it out!
A freshly squeezed gold shower?
It looks like you can make a lot of money just from peeing!
Just pull it out, please!
First, I'll make you into the academy's plaything.
No-!
No!
No, this isn't what you promised me!
Y-You said that if I did what you said...
You'd delete that video!
I said just the photos! Anyway, you were in such revealing clothes.
The men will gladly pay for it!
No way-!
Secretly filming staff going to the toilet? What a restaurant!
Stop it!
No!
Stop it already!
No more-!
I said stop it!
You dislike me, don't you?
Whoa! Your little pussy is trying to push me out-!
It's squeezing me-!
Your squeezing feels so good!
No, I'm not! I don't know anything!
There was a student who disliked me at school.
Every time I looked at someone, she would call out "sexual harassment"!
In the end, I was fired.
I'm getting into this! Letting out such a mischievous scent...
This scent, I can smell it! I bet you've been masturbating on your bed!
No, I wouldn't... I wouldn't!
Young ones sure smell good! The bedrooms of teen girls smell great!
C'mon, if you want me to stop, grab ahold of me!
Huh? Something hot is...!
Staff rules, paragraph four line one...
Be sure to wear panties that the customer will like.
Girdles, slips and s-sport shorts are not to be worn.
Showing yourself naturally to the customers is the first step towards good service.
What a great view!
I'll eat you up, Moemi-chan!
What do you think happened to the girl who got me fired?
H-Huh? You don't need to lock it?
I got someone to take care of the rest.
I said: Sorry, my boyfriend is waiting for me.
What's up?
I think I'll give my little sister a call, I bet she's worried that I'm late.
Right...
Hello? This is Sayaka.
Yes, I'll be back soon.
Yes, I said: "After you cum once, that's it for today."
He looked so surprised!
Huh? Is that all, you say? Forget about Masashi- I mean, my ex-boyfriend.
Moreover, sorry about not recognizing you immediately when I met you at work...
I was still a kid back then...
Oh yeah, is Moemi behaving?
She's asleep already.
Since that was her first.
Although it wasn't bad! She was a tense virgin!
When you come back, we're all gonna do it till dawn!
So meanwhile, I'll let her rest.
Sorry for the holdup.
Let's go.
Yeah.
That man... Even though he's persuasive and lewd, he's much better at it than Masashi.
It can't be helped, can it?
Matsura-san was my teacher before I switched over.
After finding out about what Masashi and I were doing, he blackmailed me to a hotel and...
Such a pleased look on your face, you're so lewd!
There's no one as lewd as you among your classmates!
That time, I told them... Do you remember?
Even though you look like a strict honorary student, you've got some loose areas, don't you?
Your panties were always hanging out of your sport shorts during class!
Anyway, would such a high class student like you do it in the toilets with your legs wide open?
You guys are too defenseless!
You think you got away with it? Apologize!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
Showing me such lewd things...
Although I won't forgive you just for apologizing...
Well, I'll hear your pleas all night long, so reflect on your actions...