There are many unexpected things that happen in life.
Even for a normal person like me, Arahama Yuu,
It's something that constantly happens.
"Let's get married,"
she said to me.
Getting envious now?
Outrageous.
Something wrong with her, you say?
Nope.
If I try gauge her looks, I'd give a high score.
How about her personality?
Very good, I'd say.
We've continued to stay in contact with each other for a long time.
There's also nothing wrong with our compatibility.
However...
Even with that, I still...
... don't want it.
That is, I don't want to get married!
For example, if my wife gets pregnant,
I'd have another mouth to feed besides her.
To carry a huge responsibility like that for the rest of my life,
the word "Torture" would be an understatement.
Bachelorhood, freedom, free to play around all I want...
I've never felt like letting go of any of these.
S-Sex friend?
I never said that we'd date each other.
No way...
Then, it was my misunderstanding...
All this time, I was the only one who...
When did this all start anyway?
If I remember correctly, I was taking care of her after she had entered the company.
Then, when I invited her to dinner, she agreed to go with me.
Somehow, after the date, we ended up having sex.
I thought that it was the start of our relationship as "Sex Friends", but...
You really intended for us to date each other then?
I thought that you needed me.
But in the end, I was just a sex friend.
Sorry...
Then, in that case...
Will you go out with me properly from now on?
Can we officially settle our relationship and plan for our future?
You have no intention of cutting our relationship?
You'll be troubled without me, right?
I'm okay with starting it officially from now,
so please properly consider me.
That's...
Are you hesitating?
W-Well, I can't really...
... go out with you if I am dealing with another woman.
You're doing these things with another woman?!
Please answer me!
Th-There is another one...
Wh-Who is it?
No...
I don't want to think about it, but...
H-Ho many of them are there?
How many of them are there?!
Four more.
Four more?!
What should I do?
Should I apologize?
Or do I say that it's not my fault?
I don't know...
Please call them here.
What?
Please let me speak with those people!
Oh, this is about to become a messy disaster!
I've been living in peace without any serious incidents until now.
I must do something to stop this.
Um, you know, Misako...
I told you to call them here!
Oh, but it's already this late.
Call them... here... right NOW!
O-Okay...
It's over for me now...
Sex Friends Convenience?
Original Animation
~SF War Outbreak!! My weapon is my body ♥ Chapter~
So that's why you called us there at this hour?
I thought that it was a weird time to call, but...
I have work tomorrow.
And I have school...
Sorry, I'm really sorry...
I am a co-worker of Arahama.
I also have the same intimate relationship with him like you girls have.
Same... intimate relationship?
Then all the people in here are...
I thought that might be it, but...
We're all at the same relationship?
Level...?
"Sex Friend"
I was in close contact with him because I thought I was his girlfriend.
I realized today that was not the case.
How terrible...
Isn't that a really bad thing?
You've been deceiving your girlfriend?
Even now, I still love Arahama.
So that's why, if any of you is Arahama's partner only for sex,
I would like you to end your relationship with him.
I understand now.
So, what do you plan to do?
Do you want to be married to her?
You're going to get married, Arahama-san?
If you're going to be married, of course we won't be able to continue our relationship.
Are you going to get married?
Getting married is something that is impossible for me right now.
I'm already having trouble just living by myself.
I won't be able to look after another person.
I don't even have guts to carry that kind of responsibility.
It's definitely not possible.
My, oh, my...
This guy just won't make it clear.
I suppose he just thinks that marriage is impossible for him.
He'll have to deal with us first then.
In my case thought, I'm still quite fond of him.
Same goes for me.
There are things that I can see only in him.
Me, too. I don't want to part with Arahama-san
Th-Then, I would also like to be with Arahama-san
No good.
Nothing is getting settled here.
What do you plan to do, Misa-
What do you plan to do, Arahama-san?
Y-You're asking me?
My real desire is to have things stay as they are.
I don't want to say goodbye to anyone.
I just want to spend my days having sex.
I bet you just wanna continue the current status quo and keep having sex with all of us, don't you?
You're seriously thinking of getting married to him, right?
Yes.
I'm still a little bit shocked, but... I want to properly start over.
I see, then...
I would also like to volunteer myself as a wife candidate.
I really like my current relationship with him.
That's why, if you're saying that you want to get married to him,
then I also want to be united with him through matrimony.
Is that so?
Hey...!
Be quiet.
You can't even give a proper answer, can you?
Well then, I would also like to announce my candidacy.
My thoughts are the same.
I don't want to break my connections with him.
Besides,
I'm the only one who can actually support him financially.
Representative Director
I also don't want to be separated from Arahama-san.
I won't be able to go on... without him...
Why?
Why did things turn out like this?
Okay, Okay!
I will also like to marry you!
I also love Arahama-san!
If you want a wife, someone young like me would be perfect, right?
This is a very scary situation...
I never thought that there would be women who would really want to marry me.
Marriage
What should I do?
Where is this place?
Arahama-san!
Misako, what's with that getup?
Arahama-kun!
Ryouko?
Arahama-san!
Arahama-san, please marry me.
Marry me, Arahama-kun.
That's...
Arahama-kun, you're better off marrying me. ***
Wait...!
Let's get married, Arahama-san!
That's why...
I want to be married to Arahama-san
Marriage!
If you refuse to marry me...
W-Wait, all of you!
K-Keep those dangerous things away!
If you won't marry me...
Stop...!!
I...
WILL...
KILL...
YOU...
...OFF!!
In any event, I have to dissuade them from this foolish idea of marriage.
Marriage is all about timing, right?
I already said that I don't have any such plans.
How long are you gonna keep ignoring my wishes?
I am not even interested in getting marriage to you in the first place.
I don't know about that.
Aren't you naive enough to be manipulated by other girls?
Hey, now...
I don't really trust you that much.
If the other girls give up on trying to marry me,
will you stop as well?
Oh, but I don't think there's a reason to give up.
Given this opportunity, there's nothing wrong in making you mine completely, right?
Really, now...
You look like you're not very convinced.
Don't try to read me.
How much we really need each other...
It seems best for you to remember it through our bodies.
Hey, I don't plan on doing it today...
You're not going to say no, are you?
It's already getting stiff, you know.
If you don't wanna, then I'd prefer you leave since you are just gonna interfere with my work.
Are we?
Are we not?
We'll do it.
Then I'll
do
it
for
YOU.
I am going to thoroughly remind you how insanely compatible we are.
Oh, it's quite excited today.
What do you want me to do?
You don't need me to tell you that, right?
I'm trying to make you say it, you know.
Then, do it using your hands today.
A Handjob, eh?
I'm fine with that.
It's hot and hard as always.
It's aroused and stiff.
The top part is bright red.
Oh my, it's also getting wet and sticky.
I plan on knowing your body more intimately than anyone else.
It must feel good, right?
Your cock's already feeling it, right?
As always, you're good at this.
That's right.
If you get married to another woman,
you'll never be able to feel this level of pleasure, ever.
You must be craving to do it more intensely now.
Y-Yeah...
Your erotic juices are oozing out in bulk.
Drenching my hand this much...
You have no self restraint, do you?
Do you want to cum?
Do you want to ejaculate while I stroke you with my hand?
Maybe I should stop...?
P-Please let me cum!
Oh, so you want to cum, eh?
I wonder what I should do...
P-Please!
Okay, cum then.
It's alright to cum while your cock is being stroked by my hand.
Wow...
So much, so hot and so sticky...
And white...
Delicious.
This thing is really amazing.
You came a lot.
Well , that's...
We're not finished yet, are we?
How rough of you.
What a nice view.
Your nipples are already stiff.
This feeling...
And your pussy's already very wet.
Geez, you keep looking there.
Want to put it in?
It's okay if you want to.
You actually are desperate for me to put it in, aren't you?
Who knows? Maybe it's true, maybe not.
Then how do you explain this wet pussy?
H-How do you explain that still-hard cock of yours?
You can put it in.
That stiff cock of yours...
... into my pussy.
You put too much force into it...
This is amazing. Your insides are even wetter.
It's thick and hot...
You can go ahead and cum if you want.
What's wrong?
Can't you do it more intensely?
You're always pushy no matter what, eh?
Here, I'll wrap it tightly inside my pussy.
Feels good, right?
Have you thought it over again?
Wh-What are you talking about?
If you marry me, you'll always get to do this.
That's true, but...
But I'm not in favor of all the other responsibilities I'll need to keep.
I thought you'd say that.
My breasts, hold them strongly...
These tender breasts, right?
That's... That's good...
You can use my body more, as long as you want it.
Ry-Ryouko!
What is it?
I'm putting it in...!
How's that? Are you feeling it?
Somewhat I guess...
Y-You're also feeling it right?
Well, that's...
Hit me deep inside.
Your pussy is the best!
I'm feeling good, too...
I'm going to cum!
Cum with me.
Release it inside me!
Release it!
Release it!... Release it!... Release it!
RELEASE IT!!
There's so much inside me...
It's inside me...
I can never get enough of this moment.
Ryoku's usually collected,
but it's at these times, that she reveals her slutty face.
She shows how fully she submits to her pleasure.
Hey, clean there as well.
It'd be bad for my reputation if there's a single spot of it left.
I know already!
So, how was it?
I'm asking about our compatibility.
You have lots of other Sex Friends, but...
Don't you find me the best after all?
Always able to see things through, huh?
Well, it's a battle between women anyway.
So I don't have any plans on losing.
But in the end, you're still the one who will make the decision.
Sex Friends Convenience?
I wasn't able to properly convince Ryouko,
but anyway, I guess there's no need to hurry yet.
Arahama-san!
Hi there! Going somewhere?
Off to somewhere for a bit.
This is perfect. I want to talk to you about something.
Talk about something?
Oh, perhaps it's a proposal?
Nope...
What is it that I lack?
Is she really serious about it?
Then I'll have to make her awake up as soon possible.
Want to walk around for while?
Oh, okay!
So what are we going to talk about?
It's about the marriage thing from before.
You're going to marry me?
Hey now.
There's nothing good about a marriage with a guy like me who has an unclear future.
That doesn't matter since you're a nice guy.
You can't just ride on that...
You don't want to get married?
I don't want to carry around unnecessary responsibilities.
Responsibilities, huh?
You're not seriously considering marrying me, right?
You know, I want to be with you for a very, very long time.
Kotori...
You're just so cute, Kotori!
Arahama-san...!
People will see us.
People don't usually come by this area.
B-But...
We can't just...
Really?
It's been a while so I though that maybe could...
W-We're really going to do it outside?
The weather's quite nice today, don't you think?
Alright the, here we go.
N-No!
Somebody might come!
It's okay as long as you don't make any noise.
No, my voice will be heard.
Hold it in, hold it in.
I-I can't...
I'm weak when it comes to my breasts...
You say you can't, but your nipples are already getting hard.
In reality, you feel aroused at the thought that someone might see us.
I-It's nothing like that!
What a lewd voice.
It's not my fault if someone really sees us.
No way...
They'll know what school you're from by your uniform.
N-No...
I don't...
It feels...
... really good.
Would you like me touch it directly?
But...
But?
We're outside.
Wow, you're getting really wet.
That's...
Oh, what is this?
... my clitoris!
It feels good.
It's good...
Someone will really hear us.
B-But...
I can't endure it anymore...
What is it that you can't endure?
Shove it in my pussy...
I am at my limit...
I want your cock now!
We're going to have sex here?
If we get seen...
Even...
Even so,
I want your cock...
Please, put your cock into my pussy!
You really want my cock?
You want it deep in here?
You're such a pervert, Kotori.
It'd be really embarrassing if someone were to see us.
No, I can't hold it in anymore...
Please...
Give me your cock, please!
Your pussy's really tight after all.
It's inside.
Arahama's cock is inside me!
It's good...
What's wrong?
There, at that spot...
You feel it more at that spot, right?
I know, I know.
It's moving...
Your cock is... moving inside me...
Your pussy's also tightening around it quite well.
Arahama-san's cock...
... is thrusting completely into me.
It feels good...
I'm also feeling good.
You're feeling good with my pussy, too?
Yeah.
It's really tight.
It's something that I can only taste with you, Kotori.
It's big.
Your cock is big...
My body's hot...
I feel like I'm burning...
Nice facial expression.
You look cute.
Am I really cute?
Yeah, very cute.
Oh no, I'm about to cum!
It feels too good!
My pussy is gushing.
Oh, you're about to cum?
It feels like cumming, my pussy...
My pussy feels like cumming!
Do you want to cum with my cock?
My pussy wants to cum... with your cock, Arahama-san!
In that case, I'll make it more intense.
Here I go!
Wow...
It's going deep inside.
Your cock's twitching...
It feels good.
My insides...
My pussy feels so good...
Are you about to cum?
I'm...
I'm about to cum...
My pussy is at the peak of climax...
... I might cum anytime.
I feel like cumming...
Arahama-san!
You can cum... whenever you feel like cumming.
Cum as many times as you like with my cock.
I-I'm cumming...
... with your cock!
I'm cumming with your cock!
My pussy's cumming...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I'll continue with this.
Please continue.
I'm cumming, too!
You're going to cum?
Yeah.
I'm going to release all my semen inside your pussy!
Cum in me!
Release all your semen inside me!
I'm cumming.
I'll release everything in you!
Release it!
Release all that's in your cock!
Release it all!!
It's being released...
Lots of it...
It's hot...
How was it?
Isn't outdoor sex the best after all?
It felt really good...
But...
But?
It's still embarrassing after all...
No one's here, right?
I already said it's alright.
Geez, it was really embarrassing to do it outside.
I was really uneasy...
But you liked it, didn't you?
Also...
I don't think I can do that.
It's okay, It's definitely going to feel good for you.
B-But?
Besides, you already understand, right?
Getting married is foolish.
Simply living our lives like this,
and having sex once in a while... isn't that truly good enough?
That may be true, but...
Right now isn't much of an issue, but what will you do when you get old?
Well... I suppose I'll just die normally then.
I wouldn't want that.
For Arahama-san to die alone like that...
That would be sad...
I'm grateful that you think of me that way though.
But this is something that I have-...
In that case,
you'll just have to feel like getting married to me, right?
I'll work hard from now on, and then I'll make you choose me!
No, wait...
Okay, I'll do my best!
See you later!
Hey, listen to me!
Until you marry me, you're not allowed to marry other women, okay?
It seems that making Kotori give up the idea of marriage will still take quite some time.
Arahama-san, You idiot!!
Zero