Dear Yui-senpai,
Starting today, we begin taking lessons for Lemon Angel.
Where were we supposed to meet again?
The lecture room. Kogure-san said it was an important meeting.
It's all because Saya took her time...
Saya? Why are you calling me that?
Isn't that right? I'm copying Erica.
No. If that's the case, you should call me "Saya-sama."
What? How about I just call you fatty?
What did you say?! You flat chest!
You two get along well.
No, we don't!
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyine else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
... cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me, (Only me...)
Hokani no dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... So hold me tight.
For you, who have passed the first exam, I will admit that you are bright.
But whether that brightness is from a gemstone or just a pebble is hard to tell at this point.
That again, Erica?
And so, by doing lessons, we want you to learn the basics together...
It's times like this that I need to be a ninja.
Wouldn't you get noticed easier in that?
Especially... ninja and companions over there!
Y-Yes!
Never be late!
Oh, he saw us. He must be a saru.
Erica shortened "sarumono", which means a clever, strong person with no weaknesses, to "saru" which means monkey.
Not saru, it's sarumono.
Stand up, everyone. Do not daydream.
I am in charge of dance and body design, Yamashiro Lisa.
Just because you are candidates, does not mean I will go easy.
I will cut those who cannot keep up without mercy, so I expect you to behave accordingly.
Understod.
Don't worry. If you try your best, she'll surely look at you properly.
I wonder...
You two!
Y-Yes?
You have some guts to be talking during class.
N-No, it wasn't like-
Don't answer me.
Understood!
Now we will begin with some warm-ups.
You! Bad posture. Stretch out your back a little more.
No, don't push your chest out, stretch your back!
S-So strenuous...
Don't relax your knees.
Keep your face up.
And done.
I can't take anymore!
Five minute break!
Your arms and legs are long so you'll look better on stage. Keep focusing on that in your dancing.
Okay!
What's with that? She was born that way.
Foreigners are cheaters.
Good for them.
Nice to meet you.
I'm in charge of everyone's voice training and teaching music theory. My name is Jounouchi.
So, let us practice singing to match notes.
Okay!
A Little clearer, please.
Yes, that's good.
You, to the left.
Y-Yes?
It's not about being as loud as you can.
Your voice should come from your stomach.
O-kay...
Hi everyone, we meet again.
I am Danny Yamaguchi, in charge of makeup and cameras.
Let's begin by learning the basics of makeup.
I need a model...
Here! I'll do it.
Hmm, let's see. Your face is too clear-cut, so it'll change your face too drastically. No good in this case.
Someone who has more of a shoyu taste would be good.
What about Haruka-chan?
What? No way. That makes the difference between me and the foreigner too apparent.
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, you're the funny girl from before.
Hmmm... you have too much, and in a different way, so it might be a bit too difficult, even for me.
Hey, what should we do for lunch?
There was a good place somewhere near here.
I'm so hungry...
Whoa! Amazing. Did you make all that by yourself?
Of course.
Obento's are best made at home.
Do you want to eat some?
Yeah! Give me some! Is that okay?
Go ahead.
Yay! Thank you.
So good...
Don't you cook your own food?
A little. But not like this.
Oh, looks colorful.
It's so good.
Why don't you eat some too, Saya?
Ah, no thanks.
You don't like it?
Oh no. I'm trying to wring my body.
Oh right, I wouldn't be able to walk if I ate more.
What does that mean?
Oh Erica, can you teach me some cooking?
Eh, Cooking?
Yeah, and I thought I'd want to visit your place.
Okay, I'll be waiting. Please feel free to come.
Yay, score.
Are you sure you're supposed to eat that much?
The first lesson this afternoon looks a little rough for a full stomach.
Oh, that's right...
And so, we grew up day-by-day like this.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete.
Retrieve the password and login...
Log in suru wa kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
Out of my control
Tomerarenai no Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka jya iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me
Me wo tojite mogurikomu anata no yume de
I close my eyes and sneak in
Mata aeru ka na?
Can i meet you again in your dreams?
Adoresu wo machigaete
When i get lost...
Mayotta toki wa tasukete kureru kana
from going to the wrong race, will you help me?
zoushoku suru i
The magnifying will
Out of your control
Kimi dake no karada Angel Addict
This is a body only for you. Angel, hurry
I don't know wether we are growing up day-by-day, but i won't give up! Never.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine. I slept a lot yesterday because it was the Harbor Opening Anniversary, so I feel great.
The anniversary for opening harbors for international trade is July 1, 1859. However, the anniversary is celebrated on June 2nd,
which corresponds to July 1st on the lunar calendar the Japanese were following at the time. Most schools do not have classes on this day.
Don't screw up like last time.
What? I didn't screw up.
What? Are you serious?
Erica, you're Takumi's older sister?
Yes.
Wow.
Oh? Takumi's, eh?
Hey, who's Takumi?
What? From Third Sence.
Third Sence...? Third Sence...
Are you serious? Takumi's? I'm so envious.
Hey, Erica-san, mind if I visit your place?
We're both candidates, right? And of course Takumi is going to be there?
Oh sure. You're welcome.
Then, Fuyumi, make sure you do everything in the morning.
Eh? Ah, I have to do something on Sunday...
You're coming, right?
Eh, oh, yes.
Erica, I want to go too. You said you'd teach me how to cook.
Oh yeah. Then I'll be waiting with a feast, too.
Yay!
Then I'll come too.
What? You said you were dieting.
I never said I'd go eat... and why are you telling everyone that I'm dieting?!
Who cares.
Miki-san... is something the matter?
Nothing.
What was that about?
Who knows...
Oh? This is a song by Third Sence... Who's phone is it?
It's gone now.
Takumi-kun...
Hey, sis, do you think I can make friends where we're about to go to?
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
You think so?
Yeah. It's the country mama was born in, after all.
Whoa. Such a cool color, Erica.
Thanks!
Foreigners are so different.
Her sense is so peculiar.
Maybe it's because she's a foreigner.
Even if she didn't want to, she'll stand out.
Don't worry about it, sis.
But...
We're a little different. That's a fact.
And about that invitation, I think I'll accept.
Huh? Which invitation?
Working today too?
Yeah, and then we have a party at a member's house.
I might be a little late. They'll insist that I stay.
Later.
Takumi... I can finally...
Hello? Takumi?!
If that's the case, then don't worry about it.
I'll be fine.
Okay. Bye.
Coming!
Hey, Erica!
Excuse me.
Wow, pretty big.
After all, it is a foreigner's house.
Say, where's Takumi? Bathroom?
No, he said he had to stay at the set longer.
Oh, but I made a lot to eat, so please enjoy yourselves...
Huh? Takumi isn't here?!
What are you talking about?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Haruka-chan...
Could the outfield please shut up?
Erica!
If your brother Takumi isn't here, you're just an opponent.
What a waste of time to go to a house that's owned by someone like that.
B-But we got to know each other because we got chosen as candidates. Couldn't we at least enjoy a meal together?
What? If we eat something weird like this, it's obviously not good.
I wouldn't go as far as poison, but maybe you mixed in some laxatives.
You aren't Japanese in the first place.
Hey, stop right there!
Haruka-chan, that's going too far...
Fuyumi and I came here instead of going to a relative's funeral.
Haruka-chan, there was a funeral today?
You're evil, aren't you?
You're trying to get into Lemon Angel with your brother's help.
And even trying to make other candidates drop out by making them eat food mixed with laxatives.
I pity Takumi for having this parasite of an older sister.
Erica!
Oh? Was I on to something?
You took advantage, didn't you? Of Takumi not being around.
So what?
Heh, so naive.
What?!
If you think you can win by crushing others, you have a lot to learn... about those in charge.
Heh, you're just a second rate singer.
Erica?! Where are you? Erica!
Erica?! Erica?!
Did you find her?
No... Not a trace-
Man, I'm soaking wet.
I can't keep this up.
Let's get going. If we don't find her quickly, we'll catch a cold... both Erica and I.
Yeah. But why am I not in that list?
Do I even have to answer that?
Hey!
Erica!
Erica! Where are you, Erica?!
Erica!! Erica!!
Where did she go?
Ah! There she is!
miorosu machi wo somete yuku tanashisouna shuumatsu no koe
The happy voices of the weekend which dye the city I look down upon.
Erica.
Don't come!
dokoka tooku kanjiteitano
I feel like it is far away.
Please don't come near me....
It's just a cycle of the same thing.
donna ni hito ga afuretemo watashi ni hito wa dare mo shiranai
No matter how crowded it gets, I don't know anyone.
I thought I really found the place where I belong this time.
In Brazil and in Japan, I was a foreigner. And now Takumi found his own place...
So I thought I needed to find one, too.
I met Tomo and other friends,
that wanted to be Lemon Angels.
kizutsuku tabi ni namida ga ochita
Every time I was injured, I cried.
Occassionally, people looked at me like a foreigner, but I kept thinking these people were different.
dare ka wo omoi au kimochi dake wa never change
The feeling that I have for others never changes.
But everyone was after Takumi and not me...
That's wrong, Erica. I...
It's not wrong. Even you... what should I do...
sekai no donna basho de mo egao wa with love
Smiles anywhere in the world come with love.
Why don't you just quit then?
I can see why you weren't competitive now.
In other words, you just wanted a friendly club out of Lemon Angel.
miorosu machi wo namida gao de arukidasu yo mai
I walk through the city I look down upon everyday with a crying face.
Quit playing games! We didn't come to make friends.
Everyone's a rival, like myself, even Tomo.
Everyone's putting themselves on the line.
We're all trying to be the last one standing after giving everything we have.
It's because we have that resolve that we can be friends.
And aren't you forgetting something? We can only be together until the last audition.
nidoto onaji iro no nai sora ga ima ya
Before the sky without color...
After that, there are two paths.
The winners, who attain a place to shine with other comrades, and the losers, who lose everything and disappear.
What about you? Are you prepared to give everything you have to win?
hohemi sae mo kieru mae ni kanjite itai
.. and smiles disappear, I want to make sure.
I-I...
I want to sing!
I don't know if I'll pass the audition, but I want to try my best.
We can be comrades, right, Erica?
dareka to tooi hi ni au toki wa never change
When I meet someone in a distant day, we never change.
We can become friends who sing together, dance together, compete against each other, but encourage each other, right?
We have to! Let's be. Because I want to.
hanarazu yasashisa uketotteru with love
I always receive kindness with love.
Tomo...
Let's sing together.
You're right.
dareka wo omoi au kimochi dake wa never change
The feeling that I have for others never changes.
What I really want is still ahead of me.
Tomo, Saya, I will do my best, too.
I'll give more effort and make my way to Lemon Angel.
And I will be your true rival. Definitely.
sekai no donna basho de mo egao wa with love
Smiles anywhere in the world come with love.
Sure.
And why am I giving advice to a rival.
I'm so glad we found you, Erica.
tanizoko ni iru koto kizuita no dakara
Because I realized that I am in the bottom of the cleft.
Tomo...
E-Erica?
H-Hey!
E-Erica, you're strangling me.
Hey, there's people watching.
I'm so sorry for making you worry.
Thanks for the food.
So good...
Hey, why are you eating my share too?
Because it's so good.
Why, you!
Then I'll be taking this.
Wha?! Now you're being spiteful.
There's still a lot left.
Yay!
Takumi, I found a place... truly just for me.
I will surpass you. And then... defeat you.
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest.
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, If for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...they become lonely..
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
They say there's a lot of harassment going on between the candidates,
but do you know anything, Tomo-
Wh-What are you talking about?
Chew before you swallow...
No, what's going on...
There's nothing coming out of our shoes, nor any frogs in our lockers.
Next on Lemon Angel Project, Episode 5, "Just Friends is Fine".
So, do you have any idea who the culprit is?
B-B-But I just said there's nothing going on!
Just Friends is Fine