I-It'll rip me apart!
No-! Y-You'll burst my stomach!
M-My uterus! It's gonna be crushed!
No-!
Please, help me!
N-No!
Someone-!
Keep going, Karen!
Erena and Emille are waiting for us back on Earth!
Yes!
What the-
Darling!
Karen!
Noo!
Presented
by Shikkaku
Mahou Shoujo Erena
H
Erena, lift off!
Onee-chan?
It's been over 10 years, hasn't it?
Since Mom and Dad died in that shuttle accident.
Onee-chan, are you feeling lonely because they're not with us anymore?
Yes, I do. You do too, don't you?
Emille isn't lonely, she has Onee-chan!
Emille is fine as long as she has Onee-chan!
Emille...
You're right!
We're our only two family members in the whole world!
Onee-chan will be with you forever, okay?
Yep! That's a promise!
We'll be together forever!
Forever and ever...
It's going to be our special promise.
No!!
Emille?! What's wrong?
W-What is this...?
Onee-chan...!
Help me!
Help me, Onee-chan!
Emille!
W-What should I do?!
You're late!
Now a rice cake is talking!!
I'll explain the details later.
The only way for you to save your sister is for you to become a magical girl!
A magical girl?
A magic user, as in a magi!
Zorudo can only be defeated with magic!
Zorudo? Is that the monster's name?
N-No! Don't!
O-Onee-chan!
Emille...
I'll become a magical girl!
I'll do anything for Emille!
Then let's hurry with the contract!
No! What is this?!
The girl who wishes to connect to one's true entity,
accept thy vessel.
The power which shimmers among the heavens,
may your power dwell in her, and prove your almighty strength!
H-Hey-!
I'm unsealing your magical power!
Hey-!
Get ready!
Wait-!  Stop!
My virginity-!
It hurts, it hurts! Stop!
I'll get pregnant!
I learned during health classes that I'll get pregnant!
Shown the way by the stars above, magical girl Erena, reporting for duty!
What on earth am I saying?
Not to mention this costume!
Emille!
I'll rescue you soon!
Magical girl attack!
It didn't have any effect!
You haven't charged your magic!
To charge it, you have to-
W-What are you doing?!
No no no!
I'm ticklish there-!
It's groping my breasts!
No!
M-My breasts-! Not so hard!
No!!
You'll ruin my breasts if you squeeze them that hard!
I might not be able to put a bra on if you keep doing that!
N-Not there-!
Don't come any closer!
S-S-Stop this at once!
T-That's my precious place!
Please! Don't do it!
No way, you can't-!
It's going in-!
S-Stop!
Don't stretch me down there!
I won't be able to get married otherwise!
I-It's going in-!
I-It's twisting up my insides-!
N-No-!
No!
S-Stop! You'll paralyze me!
I-It's going so deep inside-!
This disgusting thing is so deep inside my precious places!
It's going to split-!
It's splitting me apart-! Stop it!
Erena!
U-Use your magic!
Magic!
Night of Serene!
It makes me want to cry!
Having my virginity stolen by this flying rice cake,
And then being raped by that disgusting monster!
How rude!
My name is Ovi!
My duty is to give magical powers to those being targeted by the Zorudo!
Zorudo are a tentacled life form from another dimension.
They conquer beings from other worlds!
Conquer? How?
The Zorudo create a dimension called the "Reverse World", where they dwell and then capture creatures to study.
Reverse World?
Emille's room was an example.
The Zorudo who understand humans will now escape out of the Reverse World and mutate them!
D-Does this mean that humans will turn into monsters too?!
It does.
So, to stop that, we have to destroy the Zorudo overlord.
It should be controlling the other Zorudo from somewhere on this planet.
Does that mean that I have to fight those things?!
When you became a magical girl, you took on the responsibility of protecting this world from them!
Why did something like this happen?
I've never flown in the sky before!
Also, how do I make magic?
You'll use the source I injected as a catalyst to make it in your uterus.
It'll start being made after you start fighting the Zorudo.
Does that mean that I have to have such things done to me again?!
I can't have that!
You can dodge its attacks and just be in the battling mind-set and it'll still be made!
You'll get faster at making it as you gain experience!
Erena! Look over there!
It's the Reverse World!
Okay!
Right! I'll finish this off before I get sexually harassed!
Be careful!
What is that?!
It's already mutating this planet's creatures!
This is too sudden!
Erena! I'll help you!
This semen smells so strong!
No! Don't put your tongue there!
No-!
N-No, stop!
N-No! Take it out!
W-What is that large thing!?
Don't tell me that it's its cock!
It's not going to put it inside me, is it?!
No!!
No, stop it!
There's no way that something like that'll fit!
I'm a human!
S-So big-!
It's going to split me apart!
S-Stop it, already!
Stop, stop stop!
It can't fit anymore!
It'll break my pussy if it keeps doing this!
A-Anything but that!!
D-Don't cum!
Don't cum inside me!
I'll get pregnant with a Zorudo baby!
No more!
If it goes on like this, I-I'll die!
E-Erena!
Pick up your staff!
O-Ovi!
I can feel it.
I can feel the magic power overflowing!
Take this! Night of Serene!
Disappear!
I-It's over!
That's right! Well done, Erena!
I did it!
Erena!
Huh?
Onee-chan?
Did she go out?
What's this?
No! Help me, Onee-chan!
No!!
Jeez! Why do these Zorudo keep appearing?
It's strange; this is the first time so many have spawned in such a short period.
Erena, be careful.
No worries!
I got the hang of it last battle, so I gotta head home quickly before Emille starts to worry!
That's the spirit!
Erena...
Is that you, Erena...?
What was that?
What's wrong?
Erena!
You mustn't, Erena. You mustn't come over here...
Who is it? This voice really bugs me!
No, you mustn't come closer...!
Please don't come closer!
Who is it? Who are you?
You can't come! Please, you mustn't come!
This voice! It couldn't be!?
Mom?!
Is that you, Mom?!
Where are you, Mom?!
It's you, isn't it, Mom?
Erena!
Mom...!?
No, please don't look, Erena!
Please don't look...!
No way, why is Mom?!
Erena...
But... you died in that accident, didn't you...?
The Zorudo were responsible for the accident.
From then on, I was captured and I've been played with ever since!
Erena!
This is bad!
I sense that Emille is being attacked by the Zorudo!
W-What should we do?
What am I supposed to do!?
No way!
No, I can't leave Mom like this!
Ovi, please go help Emille!
I'll catch up soon!
R-Roger!
Mom! I'll rescue you!
Erena...
You bastard, let me go!
Let me go this instant!
Mom, Mom!
N-No!
Not in front of my daughter!
M-My nipples-!
S-So good!
No, Erena! Don't look!
Stop it!
Let go of Mom!
It's teasing my nipples!
I-It feels too good!
No!!
I-It's sucking on me!
It's sucking on my breasts so much!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
No!
Stop it!
P-Please, please forgive Erena!
No! Not in front of Mom!
Please! I don't want Mom to see me like this!
Don't put it in!
Don't, don't-!
No!!
Don't-!
I-It's churning up my insides!
Stop it!
Why does this have to happen to Erena too...?
It's... It's going in-!
It's going inside my pussy and my butt again!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
Even though I shouldn't, I'm gonna cum-!
So deep-!
It won't go in any deeper!
It's hollowing me out!
I-It's hollowing out my pussy and my butt!
No!
N-No-!
Not in front of her!
But I can't help it!
My stomach-!!
If it goes inside me any more-!
This is too much...
It feels incredible, it's too good!
My pussy and my butt are going numb!
Thrust harder!
Thrust it further inside my pussy and my butt!
What is this?!
I-I can feel mom's pleasure throughout my body!
It's too good-!
We're connected through the Zorudo!
Our senses are merging!
I can feel your pleasure pouring into me!
I feel it! I can feel Mom!
More, more!
Give me more of Erena's pleasure inside my wet pussy!
No no no!
I don't want any more!
Mom's pleasure, it's too strong-!
Stop, Mom! Please stop it!
It won't stop, I can't stop it!
This feeling, it's as good as doing it with your father!
No! Don't say that!
It feels like I'm doing Dad's thing, too!
It's fine, Erena!
It's okay to think of it as your father's cock!
Indulge in the pleasure of this family reunion!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum, mom!
Are you gonna cum, Erena?
Let's cum! Let's cum together!
Mom! Mom, Mom!
N-No, I'm gonna cum!
I-I-I'm cumming-!
We were saved?
I see, I guess the magic inside me was unleashed.
Mom!
What is this...?
Ovi!
E-Erena...
I'm very sorry, I couldn't save Emille!
N-No way!
Emille? Emille?!
Emille!!