Hey, honey...
Please? l want it...
lt's still five in the morning... Let me sleep a bit more...
Jeez...
H-Hey...
But you always say you're tired at night and never make love to me.
You're hopeless...
Honey...
Honey... Honey...
Getting so wet this early in the morning...
You're such a slut.
Stop teasing me. Just give it to me right now.
Yes... More...
Do me harder...
Honey... Honey...
Yes...
More... More...
Are you about to come, Kyoka-san? Well?
No, not yet!
Not yet...
Don't come yet, honey...
Make me come...
Hey, take it easy...
Almost there...
Just a bit more...
l'm about to come...
N-No...
Well?
lt felt good, right?
l couldn't come again.
Sex with my husband is dull.
l've never come with my husband.
Have a nice day.
Good morning.
Oh, good morning.
See you.
lt's cold again today, Sagara-san.
Good morning, superintendent.
l told you not to call me Sagara, right?
This young man is a part-time superintendent for our condo...
...named Hayami-kun.
When l look at his youthful body, my hot body...
...gets much more wet.
That's right.
Kyoka-san.
Yes. That's better.
Slutty Situations of a Housewife We lnvestigate Scenes of Adultery!!
Adultery
He's actually working under my husband.
Madam, if we get this far...
Y-Yes...
We met at a company party.
l was having problems with my marriage...
...so l started seeing him behind my husband's back.
l've been seeing him for about six months.
l see. Six months...
Madam...
You're sure about this?
Yes...
Hayami-san...
Madam...
Hayami-san!
l'm already...
Hayami-san, it feels so good.
Amazing.
You're really wet down here.
No...
Hayami-san...
l'm about to...
l can't take it!
Hayami-san...
l'm about to...
Honey...
Takeya & Hinako Aoki
Honey! M-More!
Great!
You're really tight...
You can make more noise if you want to.
Come!
Open your mouth.
Hey...
You're still hard.
Hey, you had enough, right?
Nope.
l want more.
lt's getting hard already.
Yes...
So good!
l can feel it rubbing!
Here? You like this spot?
That's the spot!
Yes! M-More!
More!
You're getting too tight...
Go ahead, honey!
Give me everything you've got!
l'm coming...
l'm coming.
l'm coming!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
Welcome home.
Man, l'm tired. Dealing with so many people.
Here.
Honey.
l want to do it tonight too.
Hey...
Give me a break.
Have a nice day.
Yeah.
Come home early!
What could that be?
Hello? Superintendent?
My washing machine stopped all of a sudden.
That's right.
l don't know what's going on.
l'm really troubled.
Please come quickly.
Takeya & Hinako Aoki
Coming!
Hayami-san! l was waiting for you!
What's wrong?
Hurry up and get in.
l was in the middle of washing.
l don't know what to do.
Y-You're right...
This is bad.
What's wrong with it?
ls something tangled in there?
l guess not.
What are you doing, Hayami-kun?
You have to take a good look at it.
Yes, all right.
3.15926535897932...
lt's not working at all.
No.
Be gentle with it.
You might break it even more.
R-Right...
These machines are very delicate.
Hinako-san!
Hayami-kun...
Hayami-kun.
Amazing.
You got this big already...
Hey, doesn't it feel tight?
l'll make you feel comfortable.
Your cock seems to be full of energy.
Looks like you'll explode any minute.
H-Hinako-san...
lt's true, isn't it?
Hayami-kun, you can come if you want to.
Well?
You can see it very clearly, right?
Yes.
You can play with it.
Yes, that's it...
Do it harder!
Yes, that's it.
More.
Amazing!
More... More...
Your cunt is amazing.
lt's really drenched.
Don't say that!
Hinako-san, if you don't keep quiet, someone might hear us.
l don't care about that!
l can't bear this anymore! Please, stick it in! Stick it in!
No...
Stop rubbing it and stick it inside.
Y-Yes, right away.
So big! lt's unbelievable!
lt's amazing to be inside you.
lt's so tight...
l-lnside...
lt's really deep inside!
Hinako-san...
No, l'm about to come...
M-Me too...
Fine... Just release it!
But...
Please!
l want you to release it inside!
Yes, superintendent's office.
Hi, this is Sagara.
Oh, hi. What can l do for you?
Sagara-san?
Please come right away.
l understand.
l'm sorry for making you come.
l-lt's okay.
Come in.
Okay...
Oh, you don't have to...
Are you okay?
Kyoka-san, you can tell me anything.
l'll try to help you...
You see...
l don't know what to do anymore.
Hot!
l-l'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Sorry, it's all my fault...
Kyoka-san!
No, l have a husband...
Don't say that.
lt's all right.
H-Hayami-san, you really shouldn't...
lt's painful for you, isn't it?
You don't have to keep holding back.
See?
Take a look.
lt's so wet.
No...
Y-You really shouldn't...
l look embarrassing.
That's not true, Kyoka-san.
lt's very beautiful.
Yes...
No, i-it's amazing...
Hayami-san!
N-N-No...
A-Amazing!
l think...
...l'm going crazy.
Kyoka-san...
Now it's your turn to make me feel good.
Feel good?
Y-Yes.
l'm glad...
Then...
How about this?
Yes, it feels really good.
Then...
Does this feel good too?
l-lt's really good.
l'm happy, Hayami-san.
Very happy.
M-Me too, Kyoka-san.
K-Kyoka-san, it's amazing...
K-Kyoka-san...
l'm about to...
Kyoka-san?
l'm sorry. l'm no good.
lt's okay. Don't worry about it.
Hayami-san...