Were she to bear the abuse for the entire seven days,
the demon army would retreat and the king and queen would be saved.
Princess Catue, Dragundara's imperial princess, accepted this exchange which General Ginel offered.
With the sinister tentacles and sexual desires of the demon army,
their pleasure had begun to blossom.
Although having herself accepted this, Catue was fearful for her escape.
Meanwhile, Ginel had imprisoned her mother Nina in the dungeon.
He used strong magic to twist her mind through the depths of lust and pleasure.
Also, Nina, who had lost her sanity, couldn't hold back her sexual desires.
She made the mistake of having sex with Jin Drak, her daughter's fiancée.
What is Ginel's motive for abusing not only Catue, but Nina as well?
With her father Ampia also in captivity, what will be the fate of Catue and Jin?
Also, will Catue be able to bear the sexual abuse for the final three days and regain her kingdom?
Presented
by Shikkaku Fansubs
The Blood That Goes Mad Inside
Day Five
We have something special for you today, Princess Catue.
How foolish. No matter what the abuse, I'll-
Amazing!
W-What is that? What's that voice?
Don't tell me-
Is it Mother?
Mother!
S-So good!
More, churn my pussy more!
More!
I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Mother has...
I can't believe it...
Y-You bastard! What did you do to my mother?
I just drew out her innate inner desires, that's all.
You bastard! I won't forgive you!
That voice. Is that you, Catue?
Catue, you came here to bask in this bliss, didn't you?
Mother! You mustn't say that!
Please take those strange insects off of you!
But these creatures came to lick my lewd juices!
It's prickly and it feels really good!
Now then, Princess Catue,
please entertain Nina-sama today.
You scum! Doing perverted things with family members is-
Catue, I'm so happy!
Just the thought alone of being able to feel good with my daughter...!
It's too much!
M-My clitoris!
They're... They're gathering around my clitoris!
My clitoris is getting bigger!
What on earth is this...?
No... This can't be Mother!
Don't worry, I'll take care of you with this monster cock of mine...
No, Mother!
Stop it! Let me go!
Why are you trying to get away?
This is our long awaited family reunion...
Mother, please change back!
Catue, you've grown up to have such a lewd body!
I'm so happy!
No! Please stop, Mother!
Oh my! You're already this wet.
As expected of my child. The lecherousness must be in our blood.
Stop doing this! Please turn back into your old self!
You're tense, aren't you, Catue?
You can tell me the truth. Just say that you want to feel good!
I can't believe this! Mother, your hand movements are too perverted!
It's okay! Just leave it all to Mother, Catue!
No!
Mother, we mustn't do this!
Relatives can't do this!
As I thought, your nipples are sensitive!
You're just like me!
This doesn't feel good-
You're lying. What a naughty girl.
I must punish you!
You clitoris must be sensitive like mine!
No! Don't rub it! If you do that-
I knew it! You really are my daughter!
Then you must enjoy it here, too.
Mother! That's-!
No need to worry, Catue.
No, anything but that!
Mother!
To think there'd be a time when I'd thrust my cock into my daughter!
Mother's cock is going inside me!
Its lumps are rubbing against me!
It's stretching my pussy out!
It's going in! My monster cock is going inside my daughter!
No, Mother!
So good! The pussy that I nurtured feels so good!
My insides are getting churned up!
M-My insides are full of your cock! Please don't thrust!
No more! I don't want it!
Your pussy is sucking on me, Catue!
I didn't know that you were already so well trained!
So good! Your pussy feels so good!
My cock is being raped by my daughter's pussy!
No! You're putting it in too far!
No! Stop it, Mother! Otherwise it'll feel too good!
This monster cock inside me will make me feel good!
It's okay to feel good, Catue!
More! You can feel even better!
No! Mother, your thing is-!
Catue, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna let it all out!
I'm going to fill you up!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming, Mother!
I'm really gonna cum!
It's okay! Go ahead and cum!
Catue, go ahead and cum!
M-Mother! I-I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum-!
Catue! Get pregnant with my child!
I'm cumming!!
I'm gonna get pregnant with my mother's baby!
Splendid! I really felt the familial love.
W-What?
What the hell are you doing?!
I've started to feel a craving after watching you two.
Stop it!
Let me go, let me go!
W-What is that large lumpy meat stick?
It's a penis especially for you, Catue-sama. Please enjoy it.
No! What is this?! It's stretching out my pussy!
My insides are being pulled out by the bumps!
My pussy is sucking on it!
It's quivering from sucking on his lumpy cock!
This is insane! It's churning and messing up my pussy!
Stop! Stop it! Please!
Don't put it deeper inside me!
What is this? I'm getting hot... It's getting really hot inside me!
That's from the pre-cum that's coming out.
My body fluids have some properties akin to those of an aphrodisiac, you see.
The bumps are rubbing in the juices!
It feels good! My pussy is beginning to feel really good!
I-It's mixing up my insides!
No!! I'm leaking!
Why is so much coming out?!
It seems as though you're lost in the pleasure.
Now how about we give your behind the same attention?
Stop it! Anything but that!
I-It really is impossible!
No way! It's going in!
My butt is welcoming his lumpy cock!
No!! M-My butthole! It's making a burbling sound!
How is it? Doesn't it feel good?
My intestines are clinging to it! My rectum is wiggling around!
My butt feels too good!
My butt! My butthole is going to melt!
It'll melt like this!
Oh, it seems you're already taking care of both of her holes.
Mother, please help me!
Then Mother will take care of your mouth!
Please stop this, Mother!
You've got to be kidding!
That isn't good, Catue-sama.
You mustn't disobey your mother's orders.
W-What?
Catue!
Your mouth feels really good!
Then I shall take care of your holes in turn.
Catue, does it taste good?
Does my cock taste good?
She probably can't talk because of its amazing taste.
As proof, her butthole is sloppily melting.
Catue, take it further!
There's no need to hold back!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum, Ginel-dono!
Let us cum together then, Nina-sama.
I-I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum too!!
I'm cumming! I'm going to let it out again!
I'm gonna cum too!
I'm going to let it out too!
W-What is this?
I-I'm getting dizzy!
I-It'll splatter all over the place!
It'll splatter!
No!!
It won't stop!
Please make it stop!
I-It stopped...
It's raining!
Catue, it looks very pretty.
Catue-sama, do you give up?
Or perhaps you wish to continue-
Well, it looks as though I won't be hearing anything more from you today.
We'll continue as agreed tomorrow morning.
Day Six
I plan to change the agenda a little today as well.
Ji-Jin!
Ca-Catue!
We're going to have you do something with Jin-dono today.
You scum! What are you planning this time?!
I just wanted to see you two make love.
You! How much do you intend to humiliate us?
Jin, we don't have any other option.
Ca-Catue...
Will you do it with me?
Will you make love to me?
Catue...
But Jin, I'm already impure, and...
Don't say anything. My feelings towards you are still the same.
Jin! Your palms are hot!
That's right... Catue... Catue...
I'm so happy! Ji-Jin is touching me!
Catue, you look very beautiful.
Really?
But I've been heavily abused there...
How pitiful. I'll have to be gentle with it, then.
So good! Your tongue is healing my violated spot!
Jin, cleanse me! Lick me and cleanse me more!
More! Touch me more!
Lick every bad thing away!
I'm cumming!
Catue, can we really...
Jin, I want you inside me.
Ji-Jin is inside me!
Jin is inside me! I've become one with Jin!
Jin, Jin thrust inside me!
Jin is going wild inside me!
Please, do it harder! Wipe everything away!
Jin, I love you! I want to be like this forever!
Yeah... I'm about to cum!
Jin, cum with me! Please, cum with me!
My body is getting hot-!
Jin, what's wrong?
Ca-Catue, I'll love you forever...
Jin!
No!!
This is very unfortunate. I forgot to mention something.
I put a curse on Jin-dono which would awaken the ancestral blood within him when he was near climax.
M-My pussy! It'll tear, it'll tear!!
I'll die, I'll die!
Jin, please! Please return to your normal self!
Jin, please change-
My belly!
I-It'll burst!
No way!
Day Seven
That suits you very well, Catue-sama.
Do whatever you want. I have nothing left to loose.
Don't say that. You're already suitably dressed for this special, last day occasion.
That sound...
Jin!
Jin, don't you recognise me?
Now then, Catue-sama. How about we move on to our last act?
Please slay this dragon.
What did you-
There's no need to hesitate. It is just a mere monster.
It isn't a monster! This is Jin!
There's no way I could do it!
Then give up on regaining your kingdom.
Even though you already put up with six days of abuse, if you say it was all for nothing...
Which do you prefer?
I don't mind which you choose.
Jin, I-I'm sorry!
I can't do it.
Jin is the person I love.
I cannot kill him!
What a peculiar thing to say.
You've already killed people you love with those hands.
What was that?
When you came back to the castle, who do you think that dragon you slew was?
W-What? Don't tell me that dragon was...
Right on the mark. That was your father, King Laurence.
As expected of the royal family's dragon slayer.
It was an amazing spectacle!
No way... That's...
No, no!!
I was waiting for this moment, Princess Catue!
Your body is drowning in lust, your heart is drenched in despair!
Now is the time for you to become a demon!
As the knight with the best genetic traits in the Dragundara royal family,
as well as the slayer of the king you are the worthiest candidate,
You'll be welcomed into the demonic forces.
Sleep by the Ruruiya, the king of all kings!
Drench this one in sinister blood and bind the ancient powers!
How could this be?!
C-Could this be...
How did this happen?!
This is a recessive gene!
What a joke!
Who would have thought that the mighty gene of the dragons, passed down through the royal family,
was a worthless recessive one!
Oh well. My plan has failed, but you managed to entertain me a great deal these seven days.
In return, I'll give you a life worthy of a failed dragon knight such as yourself, Princess Catue.
No!!
P-Please stop!
There is nothing to be worried about!
Just leave everything to me!
Please Nina-sama! Nina-sama!
It's tight!
Anna, you're a virgin, aren't you?
P-Please forgive me!
Please don't do this!
Then allow me to carve it into body!
The pleasure of this large cock!
It hurts! It hurts, Nina-sama!
This tightness! As expected of a virgin! It's so good!
Y-You'll tear me!
Ca-Catue-sama! P-Please save me!
Huh? You're done already?
Where is it? Where's the next cock?
Cocks! Please give me your cocks!
Will someone please pour semen into my continuously abused pussy and violate me?
Cocks! I love cocks!
Please let me service you with failure Catue's pussy!
I-I'm cumming!
Catue-sama...
Oh my, this isn't good.
Even though you're going to have cocks rammed inside you...
He's here!
Please thrust up my violated butthole!
So good! Rip it apart!
Ram it through my rectum and violate my intestines!
M-Mother! L-Look at me!
I've got a huge cock up my butt and I'm cumming like crazy!
That's no good, Catue. You mustn't hog Jin-dono.
Jin-dono, please give me your huge thing too!
Jin-dono, please hurry and ram that cock inside my butt and pussy!
My butt feels amazing!
Tear up my insides and break me apart!
The once noble kingdom of Dragundara has stooped to something low as this. It is an interesting ending.
This place suits both of you nicely.
Please have fun with Jin and the others and enjoy your life forevermore.
No!
I-It's going wild inside my uterus!
It's going crazy inside me!
More, do it more!
Stretch it so that my poop will come out!
Milk is coming out!
I-It's squeezing out!
Mother!
Catue!
Let's cum together!
Let's do it together!
Amazing-!
I'm cumming!!