So, we're in dire straits at the moment.
Since our first product failed significantly, we haven't been paid.
And, if our next one fails too, then Flower Studios will be finished.
We must make our next product much better!
Everyone! We're going to have an emergency meeting!
Please make your way to the conference room!
Be quiet!
Be quiet.
Shikkaku presents
Eroge!
Gaming and sex are still in the making!
Last time we did a softcore one, but we cannot fail at this again.
So we're changing strategies and going to try a hardcore rape product.
So, who is this person?
Um, he is…
I'll be working for this company from today onwards.
Eh? Please repeat.
My name is Mochizuki Tomoya, and I'll be working for this company from today onwards.
Nice to meet you.
Is he a full time, or just a part timer?
Regardless, are you serious about this?!
We don't have time to be taking in…
Hiyori-san! Please say something!
Himeno Kisara
E-Cup
My name is Himeno Kisara. I'm in charge of drawing.
She's in charge of drawing the original pictures; this is her third project.
She's in a fairly well popular circle, having published
several fanzines.
Virgin
Is that enough?
What? Don't look at me like that!
I'm Fujiwara Momoka. I'm the scenario writer.
Fijiwara Momoka
H-Cup
In charge of the scenario writing;
she's quite a popular writer who has
written several BL novels for magazines.
Virgin
That is all!
Kousaka Iori
Kousaka Iori.
C-cup
Graphics.
In charge of graphics; Through a CG dojin circle, she makes a somewhat decent profit.
Virgin
So I was sleeping, huh?
Sonono Nene
My name is Sonono Nene.
AA-cup
The president, also in charge of marketing. She's
also the director and does the programming.
She sleeps in the company's conference room
to cut costs.
As I mentioned in our interview, I'm a super lady who takes the role of the director!
32 year old; Virgin
So then, your job is…
Nene!
Where's our new pretty boy employee?
Re-Reina-chan!
Why have you come today? Don't tell me that the company has…
Thanks, you can go home now.
I knew that you guys wouldn't have done a welcome party,
so here!
No way!
T-Thank you Reina-chan!
Now then everyone, we've finished our work for today!
It's time to party!
Yay!
Jeez! You're a guy, aren't you?
Can't you get up and dance or something?
I guess…
What?! It's a must!
Kisara-chan sure is a tough girl!
I like strong girls!
That's why we shouldn't employ men…
Jeez, when I drink, I get so hot!
Okay! Attention everyone!
I'm going to strip!
Reina-san! You can't strip, not today!
Oh, c'mon! We're all women, it'll be fine!
What about me?
I suspect that you have a very nice one, Tomoya-kun.
I wonder if you use it often?
Oh! How sexy!
Aren't you going to try and appeal to me?
A new employee's task includes selling themselves.
Eh? Oh sure, then…
I have played close to 1000 eroge.
And of course, I played the game that this company made too.
There are some evident reasons why it failed.
The art, scenario, and the graphics,
all of them were not erotic enough!
I'm bad at drawing and I can't write scenarios or do graphics either.
However, my passion towards eroge cannot be matched.
Saying things like that, you must have had some real experience before.
Uh, well, I'm a virgin.
I can't follow your story.
Then, what about you guys?
L-Lately, I… I've been busy, so…
I'm not really troubled by…
They're lying.
If you people insist that much, how about we step it up a bit?
Literally. Okay?
Looks like that thing you have there is more assertive!
W-What about it? I'm used to seeing things like this.
Interesting, a real one is shaped like this?
W-What is that? Please put it away Reina-san!
It gets so big!
So then Kisara-chan, why don't you teach a lesson to that rowdy thing of his?
Eh? S-Sure!
L-Leave it to me; this is nothing…
W-What is it? Don't much such weird noises!
T-This is nothi-
I-Is this…?
It looks like delicious salad dressing…
O-Ouch...
I escorted her home,
so forgive me.
- Reina
I escorted her home,
so forgive me.
- Reina
So it wasn't a dream, huh?
Why did I do such thing…?
What can I do to help, when I'm not good at anything?
Okay.
I-I am really sorry!
You bastard…!
W-Well, Mochizuki-kun is a victim too, so…
That is why I can't trust men.
There is something I want you all to see.
Eh? What is this?
It's a document with all the erotic things I got from playing eroge.
I thought that it could be used as an example.
Sex scene lines and fundamentals?
I see, so graphics like this are erotic.
How to sell an eroge…
Did you write this all by yourself?
You're amazing, Mochizuki-kun.
Because you're all female, your interest in erotic things may be inferior.
However, a person who doesn't know about erotic things cannot make it.
I really want to make the next product from Flower Studios a success!
You really are an eroge maniac, aren't you?
I understand. T-Thank you.
There is something else too.
Even if things are blurred with mosaics, if it's not done properly, it can be seen.
Oh, that's a new one, so you can go ahead and use it Kisara-san.
Like hell I would!
Your job is to go around and look over everyone's work.
Eh?!
But he's the newcomer!
Since none of you have really played any eroge,
Mochizuki-kun is the best suited, as he knows the most about it.
Hello! This is Flower Studios!
Oh! Thanks for helping us out all the time.
You really were a great help the other day!
Here you go.
Um, director?
Yes, what is it?
Isn't this room really hot?
T-There isn't any way that's possible!
That's right!
It's true that it's hot, but…
But, but…
This isn't broken, is it?
Momo!
Yes!
The breaker shuts off when it is used when everyone's computers are on at the same time.
I wish you would have told me earlier…
Anyway, how did you manage this heat last year?
T-That's…
Truth be told, we all…
Nene-chan!
We all took our clothes off, didn't we?
Since it was so hot, everyone stripped down to their underwear.
That's-!
Tomoya...
Please hurry up and check my drawings!
That's not fair! He's checking my scenarios first!
Tomoya, I'm thinking of coloring this scene with the same color as my nipples, but…
Tomoya-kun! Please pick me up!
What are you fantasizing about? Disgusting.
Jeez, please say something to this helpless-
Yay! It's much cooler like this!
It can't be helped. We can't just leave it to these two to bear all the embarrassment.
Agreed.
What a dream-like scene!
It's not fair, so you strip too!
Yes…
I think that we're quite good at our individual areas...
But rather, it's as if they're pretending to not be interested in erotic things…
And I know that this isn't right for an eroge creator, but…
I-I see.
Thanks for your hard work!
Cya.
I'm off to the public bath too.
Sure.
Thanks for your work!
Why can't I draw these properly?!
Hey you!
You were glancing at my work during the day, weren't you?
Y-Yes.
So, how was it?
I'm asking what you thought about it!
R-Right.
It's more erotic than before.
However, for example this tit-fuck scene...
It's almost like her breasts and his cock are touching by chance.
Oh jeez, I can't understand when you put it like that!
Well, if you had experience in it, then you might understand.
Then, take it out.
What?
If we're going to try it out, you're the only person who can help me.
So, take it out.
T-That's…
We're going to do a tit-fuck, aren't we?
It's fine, I'll do it!
But only for documentation!
I'll bear with it, even with a guy like you.
Eroge!
W-Why do I have to do something like this to a guy like you?
You better be actually filming.
If not, then…
I'll chop you up.
Just in case someone else might see it, you can't film my face or anything!
Y-Yes.
So, what am I supposed to do?
It's not like I've done something like this before.
U-Up and down-
W-What's up with this? I can feel it throbbing!
Men are sensitive there, so it does that from just a little stimulation.
I-It's getting bigger?!
Don't move so much, otherwise it's hard to do it!
W-We're just doing this for documentation…
This probably means that you're feeling good, doesn't it?
T-This is quite…
Like this… A tit-fuck is like this, isn't it?
Yes, but do it more aggressively.
Then, how is this?
Men are such perverts to actually feel good from something like this!
Also, it is important to give an arousing expression.
Huh? Are you saying that my face isn't good enough?
That's not it!
For example,
[Azunyan]
It feels good…
it's quite a common theme for the heroine to look with upturned eyes at the protagonist during the tit-fuck scene.
With upturned eyes… l-like this?
And maybe with a more softer expression…
There's no way I can give such an expression when I'm having to do such perverted things!
I don't care! I know how to tit-fuck without you telling me!
Hi-Himeno-san… please be a little more gentle…!
W-What?! Aren't I being gentle enough?
Kisara-san being angry and blushing like this… I-I can't get enough!
You're giving way to many orders, even though you're the newcomer!
What is this?! Something strange is coming out from the end!
Hey-! You'll drench my breasts!
This is how a man is.
Shut up! Then be more of a man and help me out with my documentation!
It feels so good-!
T-This is… I might cum!
Three!
This better actually wash off!
Two!
Hey! I'm talking to you!
One!
What is this… What is all this…?
It's hot…!
You…! You covered me in it again!
Eroge!
Jeez! I ended up drinking it!
Jeez, why doesn't this place have a bath?
I showed my breasts for the documentation only, okay?
I'm sorry.
I got aroused too, and…
What's with you?
If I take a shower, I can probably wash it off properly, so I'll forgive you.
If it doesn't, I'll hit your after.
You already have…
I want to go over some stuff,
but since I want to take a shower as soon as possible, I'm going home.
Sure, thanks for your work.
But who would have thought she would allow such a thing to be recorded…
Maybe, Kisara likes me…
So cold-!
Ah, I-I'm sorry!
Momoka-san-
This is why I hate men!!
I can't quite grasp how a real one is…
Yes, it rather strangely looks like a toy.
Shut up!
Um, if you make too much of a mess…
Shut it, I'm in just a bit of a slump at the moment!
You better stay late like last night.
Sure…
I see, so base looks like this…
Hey, don't move, otherwise I can't get draw it properly.
E-Even if you say that, this is…
I can feel how hot it is… This is what a foot-job is, right?
Does something like this really feel good?
O-Of course!
Is this end bit called something in particular?
The tip, head –something like that.
It's dirty and disgusting, but you're getting aroused from me doing this.
How strange. Though it's quite amusing, a cock is.
You want to ejaculate like this, don't you?
Y-Yeah…
It can't be helped.
S-Since I couldn't see it properly because it was so sudden, I'll watch you cum this time!
C'mon! If you want to, go on and let it out-!
C'mon!
Jeez, how much do you think you're letting out?
My socks will be ruined if you cum so much.
W-Well, it made a good documentation, so I'll forgive you.
This is great! It looks really realistic!
If I take it seriously, drawing something like a cock is…
That's the way!
That way of thinking is how you bring out eroticism in art, scenario and graphics!
Now, please memorize the words used in eroge!
What's this? Cock? S-Semen?
What kind of language is this?
Eh? P-Puss-
I can't say things like this!
It's for your job! C'mon!
P-Pussy…
Louder!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Is this a fellatio scene?
Fine, jeez! I know what you want to say.
You must think how you can draw it erotically.
I know already!
L-Like this?
Perhaps try using more of your tongue…
Okay.
For me to be sucking a man's cock…
I wonder if people do things this perverted?
But, I feel strange…
Am I getting used to cocks?
I… don't dislike it as much.
That feels good…!
As expected from a perv-
Look who's talking! You're the one who's flooding my mouth with-
I'm sorry! It's just that it felt too good and-
Who said that you can cum?!
It won't be much of a documentation if you're too quick!
We're starting again!
I-Is this really me?
I can't believe I'm making such face and sucking his…
You mustn't show this to anyone! Not even yourself!
But I already watched it while it was actually happening.
Forget it, right now!
This shot where you can clearly see her pussy, don't you think it'll look more erotic if it was gleaming a bit?
Yeah, then I guess it'll look more erotic if we increased the amount of semen.
Oh, Momo! That bit is quite nice and erotic!
Then how about adding “Why am I feeling aroused from a guy like him?” to the script?
Speaking from experience.
F-From experience? As expected of you, Kisara-san!
I-I guess.
I can't be slacking off because I'm the director!
Well, your contribution is a little off, so…
Kisara-san did her best in learning about erotic things.
She pulled everyone along, and the forthcoming product became increasingly erotic.
I thought, “this will sell.”
The production is going well, and finally the next scene is…
So, what do you think?
My art that I've been drawing so far.
R-Right, it has really improved.
The tit-fucks, foot-jobs and fellatios…
I think all of them are spot on.
I hate to admit it, but it means that what we're doing is actually working.
Then, next is…
S-Sex…
What? Say it properly!
We're the only two here you know.
Your expression is easy to read, so I have a good idea as to what you're wanting.
Next would be having sex, won't it?
Um, well, if we looked through porno's and such, we could probably easily find material-
It's fine, do me.
“Do me”?
It's not as simple as that!
What are you saying this far in?
You used my body in heaps of ways and came all those times!
So why don't you do it to me like you've always wanted to?
I want to make this game successful no matter what.
So for that, sex would be not much to ask for.
I'm probably going to do lots of it.
But, I can only experience it one time.
Fine then! If you really don't want to, I'll find another man.
That's… Are you really okay with it being me?
W-Well, it's your first time too, right?
Then, isn't it convenient…?
Okay then.
Sit here.
No-!
Hey, this is my documentation, so close your eyes!
But, if I do that, I can move properly-
It's our first time, so there's no good or bad is there?
A virgin like you shouldn't talk like they know it all.
You're a virgin too.
It's hot-!
You're too hot down there!
So something like that is going to enter me…
Kisari-san, are you scared?
Why would I be?! Adults have sex all the time, it's nothing special!
Anyway, just put it in already.
You want to, don't you?
Then I'm putting it in. Okay?
You don't need to ask for my permission every second!
Sorry, I'll do it then.
It's going in-!
It's really going into me!
I finally took Kisara-san's virginity…
Ouch...!
I-I really am bleeding!
I'm… From the likes of you, I…
A-And it's going in so deep…!
T-That cock of yours is actually inside me!
G-Good…
We... we're having sex, aren't we?
Kisara-san…
I-It hurts-!
Y-Your cock is inside me!
It's going in deep!
I-It's tight, b-but it's going in-!
It feels like it might slip out-!
I-Is this what a cock feels like? It feels fine, I wasted my time being scared-
O-Oh no…
I-I'm sorry; I'm a virgin!
N-No way, already...?
Something's filling me up…
H-Hey! If you're going to cum, say so!
I-I'm sorry.
It really surprised me!
That's why I hate virgins…
I'm not a virgin anymore, but…
Did my insides feel good or something?
Of course!
Then I'll forgive you.
But, it's not fair that you're the only one who's feeling good.
Then don't worry.
N-No-! Doing it in such places-!
People might see us!
The cold glass is rubbing against my nipples…!
I-It doesn't hurt as much, and it feels strange…
Did my body become strange because you came inside me?
It's because you're overflowing with your love juices.
T-That's a lie!
I'm not such a pervert!
Burn the image of yourself in your mind, and draw it!
I-I can tell-!
I can tell the shape of your cock, the hardness of the tip! It'll burn into my mind!
I'm going to cum like this!
Make sure you remember it!
Y-You're cumming? You're going to cum again?
A-Are you going to pour your semen deep inside me again?
So rough-! It's rubbing against me so much-!
No, no-!
It's coming out... So much is coming out…
Even though my insides are so full…
Kisari-san, let's do it again.
Let me go already!
Please let me rest-!
It's better to have lots of documentations.
I-It feels amazing when you hit against my deepest spots with your cock!
It really hurt in the beginning, but now I can't think of anything but sex after you came inside me!
I can't think about anything apart from you rubbing against my insides…
I can't think anything else...!
All I can think about is us having sex!
This is what you should draw!
A scene where the heroine gets aroused by a big cock!
Kisara-san, can I cover you in it?
Even though you came so much inside…
S-Sure, go ahead… If that is what you want to do, I'll allow it.
I'm cumming… I'm gonna cum Kisara-san!
If you thrust so much, I'll cum-! Something is coming-!
It's coming, it's coming!
No, no-!
H-Hey, there was a scene where the heroine got raped and covered in semen, wasn't there?
Would this work for it?
I-I guess it would.
My body feels so hot…
It's like there's semen left inside me…
Are you okay?
What? Isn't it normal to have sex?
This is nothing… Of course not.
Oh no… she's too cute!
She has a tense personality, she's dominant, and hates losing.
But, I must love her.
I wonder… Should I confess to her?
U-Um, I…
D-Don't be mistaken!
I-It's not like I have feelings for you or anything-!
I hate it when people get clingy afterwards!
The only thing between us is that I am the boss, and you are the newcomer!
G-Got it?!
Didn't I tell you?
I-I was just looking out for you two…
Nene was here before me.
You idiots!