www.SubDESU-H.net
Is this sufficient?
You need to... clearly narrate your actions.
I’m m-masturbating right now.
Can you see it?
My finger has slid inside.
Not enough.
Be more serious about it.
My nipples are also so hard.
I’m so naughty.
My clitoris is throbbing.
Are you about ready to cum?
Yes!
I can’t ...hold...
I want to cum!
Doctor...
My pussy wants to cum...
Do as you wish.
I’ll be watching.
I’m cumming...cumming...
W
Forbidden Ward
Special Psychiatrist Yuusa Sousuke’s Patient Sessions
All of         Desire
「Release           Your          」
The doctor has sent for me neither for sex nor for counseling.
Even though I know no one is here, I’m so nervous.
Walking the halls buck-naked...
Is that all?
It gives me the chills.
I feel shameful...and my heart is racing...
but for some reason, it turns me on.
Next we’ll have a checkup in the exam room.
Okay!
Yes.
This is his experiment.
Special Case Doctor
Examination Room One
Doctor
Yuusa Sousuke
Special Case Doctor
Examination Room One
Doctor
Yuusa Sousuke
Special Case Doctor
Examination Room One
Doctor
Yuusa Sousuke
Kamiizumi Misara-san?
Special Case Doctor
Examination Room One
Yuusa Sousuke
Go ahead.
I came to this clinic for counseling... so that I could get over my Androphobia.
Come in and have a seat.
Th-thanks.
Well then, Doctor, we’ll be on our way.
No way!
The nurses are not staying with me?
It’s too sudden...to be with a man alone like this.
I’m Dr. Yuusa and I will be your counselor.
Th-thanks for...the help...
Special Case Doctor
Examination Room One
Doctor
Yuusa Sousuke
I see.
I understand your situation.
Take off your clothes.
My c-clothes?
That’s right.
But I...can’t do something so lewd...
Are you saying that taking off your clothes for a doctor is lewd?
W-well, not...really...
There is no need to be embarrassed.
Take off your clothes.
O-Okay.
Why?
This is so embarrassing, yet...
I have a feeling that I can’t go against the doctor’s wishes.
Next, take off your undergarments.
I can’t examine you otherwise.
Very well.
A man is looking at my naked body!
I-Is this sufficient?
Yes.
Oh no... don’t look at me with such nasty eyes.
What are you doing to me?
I am administering treatment.
Really?
No...
D-don’t...not so...no!
Your breast's shape and size are great.
And you’re scared of men?
B-because of these breasts, men stare at me wherever I go and it makes me uncomfortable all the time!
Oh? Then what is this moisture?
Doctor, not there... don’t look there!
I’m embarrassed!
You’re so wet...
The Androphobic, Kamiizumi Misara.
How will you react to what's about to happen next?
No! That’s embarrassing!
My pussy is being teased by a man.
It’s all wet.
Even your clit is firmly erect.
No, it's not!
You’re a tough patient.
Then I have no choice but to try a different treatment.
Not that...!
I feel it coming..
My pussy is getting hot...
And I feel strange.
Kamiizumi-san...
Your virgin smell... is nice.
I feel... something coming...
Something is coming!
Before I realized it, I had already lost the will to resist the doctor’s exam.
D...Doctor?
I... am doing something this naughty.
I’m still scared.
This is a man’s most prized item.
If you are able to bring it to ejaculation, that means you can control men.
Control men?
What will you do?
Do you want to stop?
I’ll do it!
I...I will squeeze... all your semen... out.
Doctor’s dick... is so big.
And there’s some juice dripping from it.
Lick it and remember how it tastes.
Ah, Okay.
How is it?
Delicious, isn’t it?
Yes.
Why?
It’s so dirty and shameful... but I can’t stop.
Doctor’s penis... is throbbing... and hot.
Put it in your mouth.
Like this?
Move your tongue and swallow it deep into your throat.
While sucking on it, try moving along it.
His dick... is so hot and throbbing and something is about to flood out.
More is coming out.
What is this I smell?
I feel... very excited and my body is getting hot.
I think I like this smell.
It makes my heart throb.
Delicious! It’s so delicious!
Doctor’s dick is getting hotter and more juice is coming out.
Now swallow it all.
This is the medicine for you.
Um, excuse me.
Ah, yes?
I have an appointment at 18:00.
Let’s see...
Shiomi Azumi.
Give this to the doctor.
Oh, your video footage.
Fuyuno-chan, could you check this for me?
Yes, I will.
P-please, wait a minute!
You’re going to... watch that video?
Of course we are.
We need to make sure it’s all there, make a copy, and then send it to the doctor.
Please rest assured.
But I...
Umm... that video is...
Footage of you in a swimsuit, right?
We know what your prescribed treatment is.
Don’t worry about it.
Is that so?
The video is fine. Everything is showing just fine.
Shizomi Azumi, please come into exam room #1.
Ah, yes!
S-sensei, are you going to change in here?
Y-yes.
The instructor’s changing room is closed for repairs.
Everyone, don’t mind me, go ahead and change.
Is it really okay to expose myself here?
Oh my! Lots of differently shaped penises.
Even that kind...
It’s embarrassing, but it’s no different than normally changing into a swimsuit.
I can strip just fine.
No doubt sensei, you sure have a great body.
Makes me hard.
As I thought, this is so embarrassing.
He’s gotten hard from seeing my boobs.
And I think I’m a little wet too...
Sensei, please take off those tiny panties, as well.
Of course I will!
Don’t worry, it’s just the same as them seeing me in a swimsuit.
It’s so wet.
Oh no, don’t look.
I’m embarrassed.
Sensei.
Very nice.
You’re touching me...
Don’t touch me with your hard dicks.
Oh no... if they touch me like this...
I’ll really loose control.
How did you find this treatment?
I was very embarrassed.
But just as you taught me, I took my clothes off in front of other men.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
And it got me aroused.
After that, this video turns into an erotic video, right?
Well when I touched their dicks, I suddenly...
Am I a pervert?
I...
Doctor... um, your...
thing... is on my mind...
If you so desire.
Let’s check your naughty video together.
Azumi-sensei, lookin' good!
Let’s continue what we were doing earlier!
They’re totally checking me out.
My body feels hot...
I’m so nervous.
N-no way!
Umm, you boys...
What is it Azumi-sensei?
Um, well...
What are you doing?
Um... you can’t do that!
So hard and...Amazing... it’s turning me on.
Oh no.
Squeezing me directly... I’ll...
I’ll become like these perverts.
But they’re so hard and hot.
So manly.
And I...
Azumi-sensei, you’re amazing.
Don’t say that.
I haven’t done anything...
Ah, not there.
I’m embarrassed. It’s so wet.
No, don’t look!
Your nipples are so hard.
Milk is coming out, too.
Azumi-sensei you’re such a slut.
Azumi-sensei, I had no idea you were so dirty. You really are a  pervert.
No, I’m not...
Pool's water is getting dirty.
So we’ll suck it clean.
I am loosing control.
I’m melting.
Not down there.
They’ll notice I’m wet.
Sensei, you’re soaking wet down here.
We should close up that hole, don't you think?
His penis... is going inside... my pussy.
It’s been a while since I’ve felt this.
It’s there!
Something so hard is there.
Awesome!
It went right in.
No! Don’t put it in!
It’s coming out...
Everything is coming out.
So deep!
It’s hitting all the way inside.
Wow.
It feels so good.
I had no idea this would happen... I must be a real slut.
I had no idea that my place of work could be so naughty and filled with pleasurable moments.
If only I’d noticed sooner... it would have been better.
Have you discussed your problem with your husband?
No, I haven’t told him.
And recently he’s turned down having sex with me.
Umm... I’ve been gaining weight.
And I’m losing confidence.
And now I’m embarrassed because I’m not getting any...
More, more, stronger! Deeper!
Azumi-sensei, I’m almost...
We can’t dirty the pool’s water.
But...
Just cum... just cum in me.
Can I?
Yes, you can. You can.
Just cum inside. Deep inside.
Were you able to release yourself from your sexual depravation? Slutty Azumi-san?
Licking me... at that place...
It’s embarrassing.
Don’t worry.
It’s very clean.
Doctor, your dick has already gotten this big.
It’s amazing.
Make it bigger...and even harder...
Um, will this do the trick?
Have you done this for your husband?
I haven’t.
Nothing so perverted like this... I...
But it excites you. I see, slutty wife.
Please don’t call me that.
If you just accept who you are, it will feel much better.
No way...
I’m sorry.
Milk is coming out of my boobs.
It’s making your dick all dirty.
See? You are a slut.
I’m sorry. I’m a slut.
I want to drown myself more into this pleasure.
I’m all soaking wet.
Your dick is... amazing... amazingly big...
Doctor, your tip has been releasing some erotic smelling juices for a while now.
Slutty wife, suck it clean and relish it.
Yes, I understand.
Doctor’s dick is throbbing. It feels like it’s about to burst.
My boobs made it this hard and thick... it makes me so happy.
Doctor... I’m almost... I want it too.
Request properly for it.
Okay.
D-Doctor, please thrust your big, hard dick into my naughty pussy.
Lucky girl, Azumi-san.
Doctor Sousuke is about to fuck her.
If I do as the doctor tells me, then maybe...
Doctor's cock is touching my most intimate place.
I can’t hold back anymore.
Put it in.
Please.
Doctor... I’m losing focus...
You haven’t put it in, yet why do I feel like I’m about to cum?
I’m cumming!
I didn’t tell you before, but your naughty self is being saved on video right now.
So we’ll check that data in our next session.
The slutty wife, Shiomi Azumi-san,
Wh-why?
You’re taping this?
You never told me...
No... I’ll cum again.
I’m cumming!
He’s taking a video of me being slutty?
Might someone see it later?
Could it be that someone is watching it right now?
Just the thought of it is making me crazy.
If it makes you feel that excited, let’s give them a better view,
Azumi, the slut!
Y-yes!
This feels so good.
I love having my pussy rubbed by your cock, Doctor
We’re taping from many angles.
No!
My insides are about to explode!
My heart is pounding!
I’m so embarrassed.
So much milk is coming out.
Your dick is so hot it’s gonna burn me!
I’m about to cum.
Then cum!
In my pussy... inside, inside...
Cum inside me!
Shiomi Azumi. Condition presently being monitored.
Two days after the experiment.
Doctor?
At 23:00, meet me at the 25th floor entrance.
Data collection.
He doesn't even wait for an answer.
www.SubDESU-H.net