There are many things in life that hit you unexpectedly.
For a normal person like me,
it's something that happens constantly.
"Let's get married", she said to me.
Getting envious now?
Outrageous. I don't like it.
Something wrong with my partner you say?
No.
If I were to rate her looks, I'd definitely give her a high score.
How about her personality?
I'd say it's very good.
We've known each other for quite some time as well.
There's also nothing wrong about our compatibility.
However still...
I don't want it.
I don't want to get married!
Like for example, if I end up bringing a child into this world,
I'll have another mouth to feed besides my wife.
To carry a huge responsibility like that for the rest of my life...
The word "torture" would be an understatement.
Is it that time already?
I'm starving. I'll grab something to eat.
Makiko
Mobile
Welcome!
Go ahead, please sit down.
You must be hungry.
Of course.
Well?
It's delicious, totally different from what I normally eat.
That's good.
You must have something you wish to discuss with me, right?
Saw right through me, eh?
I am "what-you-see-is-what-you-get" kind of a guy.
I can't really do much for someone like you...
But... there is something important that only you can do.
You understand what I am hinting at, right?
Well, I guess that's true...
Sex.
That's probably the strongest bond that ties me and Makiko.
If there's one thing that I alone can give her,
that would be carnal pleasure.
And that too coated with a special type of erotic play.
There's no other man who can give pleasure like you do.
Original Animation
~Wild Snapshot! Stuck 24/7!?
Erotic Investigation Frontline ♥   Chapter~
Original Animation Disc
~Sex Friends Convenience?~
Tsugou no Yoi Sexfriend?
Wild Snapshot! Stuck 24/7!?
Erotic Investigation Frontline!
As always, it seems you had a great
time relishing the meal, didn't you?
I indulged myself without reservations.
That's fine.
Better exert yourself physically to help
digest that, wouldn't you say?
You really want it that bad?
Yes, I want it now please.
What do you want to do?
Well, that's... I want to be...
I want to be teased by you.
That's what she really desires.
I noticed it a few times...
whenever we had sex.
She would approach very gently initially,
but eventually her real thoughts would just burst open.
And now... we're at this point.
Mind if we use the other room?
No.
So, where do we begin?
Come closer.
Hold your head up.
What do you want me to do?
I want my body to be stirred up.
Then, take off your clothes.
This is what Makiko wants.
I am the only one who can satisfy her,
so I have to promptly take the role of the sadist.
Okay.
This will...
probably do.
I-It's tight.
Shall we loosen it up a bit then?
No.
Don't say those nice things.
Well then...
That?
You like these, don't you?
I-I like them.
Alright, let's do this then.
Does your nipples feel good?
Y-Yes... My nipples...
My nipples feel good!
More... Do it more...
Do more of what?
Make the rotor vibrate more intensely, please...
Then, you already know what words
to use when pleading, don't you?
I'm sorry...
Please, tease my lewd... nipples more.
Like this?
Th-That's good...
My pussy...
My pussy is...!
Getting pretty horny with this as well, right?
I am...
It feels good...
Increase the vibrator's intensity to the max please...
It's making lewd noises.
Th-That's embarrassing...
You really are a pervert, aren't you?
I'm... I'm...
Do you want to cum?
I want to cum.
I want to cum!
Make my nipples and pussy...
feel good some more...!
– Now then, what should I do...
– I'm about to cum!
Just a little more...!
Isn't it a bit unfair that you're the only one who's feeling good?
But, please...
Continue and make me cum...
Make you cum here and end it?
That's not what I mean.
You can use it...
No, please use it.
That lewd hole that's now dripping wet...
Please use it as you please.
Okay, well then.
I'll be doing whatever I want with it later.
M-My nipples are...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from my pussy.
It's coming out.
It's coming out!
It felt good...
Th-That was good...
You came intensely as always.
As promised, I'll be using your pussy as I please.
It's thick...
and hot.
You want my cock in here, right?
Yes! Do whatever you want with it.
I wanted you to stir up my pussy
using your cock... your thick cock.
No. Oh, wow!
Please do it!
Like this?
Like this?!
There, there, there!
What a lewd woman.
Are you aroused from being bound and getting penetrated?
Yes, I want you to stir me up more!
I'm about to cum!
I'm about to cum again...
Why don't you learn to hold it in?
But it feels too good...
I'm about to cum.
Please cum!
Please cum inside my pussy!
I'm also...
I can't stop this. I'm cumming!!
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
It feels good...
I can't live without you.
You're overeacting!
It's true.
At the end of each working day,
it's only during my time with you that I really feel at peace.
That's why I'll use whatever I can:
money, status, reputation.
Anything. Understood?
I can't get married while feeling like this.
But I need to make up my mind,
exactly because Makiko is serious about it.
Tsugoi no Yoi Sexfriend.
Well then, thanks a lot.
Oh, well. I might as well get back to my room and sleep.
Arahama-san.
What are you doing here at this time?
Well, there's something that I'd like to talk to you about.
Something to talk about?
Umm, whose...
So, what would you like to talk about?
Umm... Well...
Arahama-san, are you getting married?
I'm not.
But, so many beautiful women hope to tie the knot with you...
I've thought about a lot of things.
"What do I want to do with Arahama-san from now on?"
I thought about it and I thought about
it again. I thought about it some more.
But in the end, my true feelings dictate that
I don't want to be separated from you.
So is that why you want to be marry me?
I-Instead of marrying, I think, I like how things are right now.
Are you not thinking of ending things the way they are?
Aren't you a student council president
and an ace student in your school?
If someone finds you entering a man's
room in the middle of the night,
things could go awry.
That's...
But I want to be with Arahama-san.
I'm fine with the current situation.
I'll go for marriage if it comes to that,
but I don't stand a chance against those mature women.
So if you're okay with me,
please let me be by your side!
You really don't realize your own qualities, do you?
"I indulge myself in fine women only".
Go ahead and ponder over that principle of mine.
B-But compared to those women, I'm still...
Stop blabbering about that!
Araha...
I'll teach it to you directly...
how good you are as a woman.
Umm, I...
Just leave it to me.
My uniform will be ruined.
It's always like this, right?
Does it feel good?
Yes... It feels good.
Which parts of you are aroused?
That's...
I'll stop if you don't answer.
No, that's...
In my nipples and pussy...
Your panties are already drenched...
Please don't say weird things!
You're clitoris and nipples are getting stiff.
Your feel it better if I touch it directly, right?
Yes!
That's a really great way to get wet as always.
No, don't say that!
Why is it getting wet like this?
Perhaps you're longing for something?
I want...
you cock!
I can't hear you.
I want a cock to get inside me!
I want my perverted pussy
to be stirred up by Arahama-san's...
h-huge cock!
I guess it can't be helped then.
It's still a bit early,
but I'll make you cum with my cock!
It's inside me...
This is what you wanted, right?
This is...
This is what I wanted!
Man, I can't get enough of this!
Arahama-kun...
What is it?
It's not enough. Thrust in more!
Like this?
It feels good already, but do it more!
Well? Should I thrust in deeper?
It's still not enough. More, more, more!
Then how about this?
It's good.
It really feels good!
Arahama-san's cock
keeps getting thicker
and keeps getting bigger.
My pussy's being widened...
It's loosening up...
It's gonna become a loose pussy.
Oh, no!
It feels good!!
But this is not enough.
This is still not enough...
Of course,
because the main course is yet to come!
This feels good.
I also feel quite good.
Do you like it?
Do you like my cock?
I like cocks.
I like cocks!
Thrust your cock in more.
Your cock...
Thrust your cock in!
Say you want more!
You love my cock, right?
I like cocks.
I like cocks...
My pussy's insides are getting stirred up.
This is amazing, Aina.
I'm about to...
Release your cock's thing into my pussy.
Here I go!
Cum in me!
Release your cock's liquids in my pussy!
Cum in my erotic pussy!
Release it inside me!!
It's flowing,
and it's hot...
Are you still stressed with your school life?
Th-That's...
Long before, there was a time that when
I ended up relying on a dating website.
At that time, the one that I got paired
with by chance was Aina.
We contacted each other and decided to meet.
We had sex, and Aina lost her virginity in the process.
But she had a sad look.
I just couldn't ignore the fact that she seemed to be in need
of someone, and I decided to learn a bit about her.
I asked her why she did that.
"Why would you do something like this?"
"I want something to change.", wasn't
that what you replied at the time?
Yes.
So, did something change at school?
Let's put an end to this already.
I don't want that!
I know that I'm currently reliant on you.
But, even so, I don't want to say goodbye.
I see...
Well if she prefers me sexing her up like this,
then the least I can do is to keep giving it to her.
I also receive a good deal of pleasure from this.
Give and take relationship, to define it simply.
I'll be on my way.
Be careful on your way home.
Okay!
I can't hold up anymore, I'm tired.
I'll think about the marriage next week.
1 week later
Marriage for me?
2 weeks later
I have to decide next week...
3 weeks later
Arahama-san.
Yes!
Have you decided yet?
Decided?
Who's the most fun to be with from among us?
With whom did you have the best sex?
Best sex?
It's impossible for me to make a choice...
I have to say that everyone felt good.
And each of you have different good points.
I want to try lots of other stuff,
so I can't choose!
Or maybe you got cold feet regarding the whole issue, huh?
With you not choosing anyone, is that an
indirect way of politely dumping us all?
Choose... you say.
That's the difficult part actually...
If it were that easy, I would have my answer already.
In fact, I don't want to choose.
That's why I have been delaying my response.
But if I really have to choose...
I'm sorry everyone!
A-Arahama-san?
Wh-What's with that suddenly?
I'm really sorry.
I can't choose!
I like how things are right now.
To have sex and feel good with anyone as I please...
I don't have other plans besides that,
so I want to stay with this level of relationship.
What a blunt and direct answer.
That's Arahama-san for you though.
So can't we just forget about the marriage thing
and keep things the way they are?
What do we do?
Not sure what we can do...
No matter what, we can't change
the way this guy thinks, can we?
Well then, it seems the women present here will
have to come to an understanding instead.
That means...
So it would really be that way?
You're right. Bloomers should be used again.
Would that look good on me?
That means the wedding's canceled?
As expected of the president! I love and admire you!
Arahama-kun.
Y-Yes!
You'll have to properly bear the responsibility.
Responsibility?
If marriage isn't possible, then it can't be helped.
It won't be good if it's forced anyway.
That's why, if you want to continue
with the way things are with us...
to continue...?
You have to sexually satisfy all of us!
That's our condition.
I absolutely, absolutely promise that.
Okay, here I go!
I-It's good.
It's entering me more intensely!
My insides are hot!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to release it
Yes! Please do!
My insides...
Arahama-san's semen...
His cock's liquid... cock's liquid...
Next is Ryouko!
That's good.
It feels great...
Something really big is deep inside me.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming with this really... really big cock!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming with this big thing.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Hot semen is flowing inside me...
– The cock juices are...
– Next is Kotori!
It feels great.
Something thick is moving in and out of me.
Arahama-san's hot semen...
Release your hot cock's liquid!
Pour your cock's liquid in me!
It's hot, and it's going to burst!
It's coming! It's coming out!
Next is Makiko!
This is good...
Thrust it more!
It feels good!
My pussy feels like melting.
Oh, no!
I'm about to...
I'm cumming!
Last is Mishako!
Hot cock's liquid...
Release it in my wet pussy.
Release it inside!
I'm going to release it inside. Here I go!
Your big cock... in my dripping wet pussy.
Your cock in my pussy.
Your cock in my pussy...
Thrust your cock.
Thrust your cock!
Cock...
Your cock in my pussy...
Your cock, your cock, your cock!
Your cock...!
I'm cumming!
It feels good...
More, I want more.
You can still go on, right?
Arahama-san, do it more.
Master...
Here, do it quickly...
I think I'm going to die if this continues...
Жениться придётся, однако...
Well then, next time on Collaboration Works:
Squirting on face and cumming inside.
Here we go!
Oh? The screen is fading out...
Why is this happening? Geez!
Why?!