It's finally ready!
That's...
our debut song?
That's right!
This is the primary source of sound.
Then it'll become CD's and high quality data archives.
And will be released all over the country.
Hey, when will it be released?
August 20th.
And on the day before, you'll participate in this. Ta-da!
Nouvelle Festa?
Is that the one that Takumi went to last year?
That's right!
At Admiral Stadium, the event will be divided into daily and nightly performances.
The biggest event of the summer.
My...
We did it!
Amazing.
There's still a lot ahead of us!
Let's do our best!
Then, let's work hard!
Okay!
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Hokano dareka ga iya
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Please accept the real me.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
In the middle of the night
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Suki wa aru no kana?
Retrieve the password and login...
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
and get to the heart of things.
kakushin ni furetai
The virus of love
Koi wo shiteru Virus
out of my control
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry!
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me)
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Hokano dareka ga iya
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
Okay, okay.
Everyone, hurry up!
Immoral Scenario
Alright
Everyone, look here!
Look at the camera!
Here you go!
Smile!
Yes, now spin!
Perfect synchronization.
Finally!
Seems you've improved a bit.
You always say that!
You could accept me better!
It's rare for you to praise me.
Now everyone, get ready to leave.
What? To where?
To a very good place.
Good place?
I guess I ate too much!
Could you look at my posture after lunch?
Now our last guests!
Whaaat? Tomo? No way!!!
These are the six that make up the new Lemon Angel!
The first Angel never introduced themselves...
You were transferred to this?
Yes.
Onto the presentation then.
Yes!
Our...
Debut single...
...will be released on August 20th.
Please...
Buy and listen to it!
Please everyone!
We'll present it in the event.
So, We'll see you tomorrow too!
Tomo, incredible!
Hey, hey, they're showing the Lemon Angel!
Look!
Really?
What? It's the new Lemon Angel?
Good work!
Keiko-san, you could actually get that, couldn't you?
This is so awesome!
Isn't it?
Changing the subject, Kogure-kun sent good news.
He said that there's a lot of orders for the debut song.
Really?
Yes.
Maybe we can surpass the first Lemon Angel's record.
Hurray!
Wonderful!
Uh, that...
What?
Incredible!
It also has those cool signs!
But the date is wrong.
It won't be out 'til the 20th.
Really...
Did the company's campaign made a mistake?
There's things that even Keiko-san doesn't know.
Because Kogure-kun is in charge of supervision.
Music Chat! News from the artist world!
Someone said something like, "There's a surprise at the event." Could it be that?
Is that it?
Nouvelle Group report 1 - secret rapporteur for the season. \ After Nouvelle Festa next month. \ There's a chance for you to return even better!
Finally.
Hey, move away!
Hurry, hurry!
Okay!
I'm sorry!
Huh? Where's the others?
They're here!
Wow, what's with that crowd?
Good work!
That means the news spread a lot...
Shall we go then?
Yes!
Look, if this goes on like this, the debut song will be very popular, right?
Sure!
Who knows, maybe millions.
Millions?
You mean one million?
That's right!
More than imagined!
End of the year...
Maybe we could participate in Nenmatsu Utagassen...
Note: Nenmatsu Utagassen is a music event that is on television on December 31st to celebrate the end of the year.
Nenmatsu...
How?!
There's that chance!
Maybe they'll call us out last and leave the responsibility with you!
Amazing! We'll be the best of the white team.
Extra Note: On that event, the best singers of the year are called and then divided into two teams: Red and White.
Let's ask Katagiri-san to sing!
What?
If that face appears on TV, it will be a scandal!
Hey, Tomo, Look out there...
Ah, yes, on that day!
First Lemon Angel will be reborn during the Nouvelle Festa!
Whaaat?
Reborn?
Ann will come back.
Keiko-san, what does this mean?
I don't know either.
Everyone, it's been a long time.
After a year and a half, we're back!
This transmission is coming from abroad.
We want to participate in the Nouvelle Festa too!
I'm here to fill in for Miki. My name is Seizu. I'll bring good winds for the group, I think.
People, we'll meet at the stadium on August 19th!
Wow!
Hurray!
Finally!
What does this mean?
At least, at least give me an explanation!
We don't have the obligation to notify any producer here.
But...!
It wouldn't make a difference if you knew.
Excuse me.
Kudou... damn you!
Hey, the directors will hear.
What's your goal?
Of course there is the raise of advertisement through shows...
An advertisement strategy.
The result is...
... the side that loses might disappear.
Don't underestimate us. We will make you regret for starting this fight.
Hey, hey, what do you mean by starting...
I know, you won't make it!
I'm sorry.
This was my last day at the company.
This... This is too much for me!
What a horrible thing you did!
Tomo...
Why?
Why did the first Lemon Angel have to harm Yui-senpai?
Tomo!
I'll ask Kudou-san to stop.
Don't be ridiculous!
They're enemies.
But...!
Ann isn't an enemy.
Ann saved me.
If I don't speak with Ann... I...
That's right, Miru-chan also doesn't know that the first Lemon Angel was a program.
No, you just can't! Saying that would be unthinkable!
Why?
If I said that you can't, then it's because you can't!
I want to meet with Ann.
Miru-chan, let's stop here.
It's because I think that they also might be busy.
Right, Kogure-san?
Yes, and they're still abroad and we don't have any way to contact them.
But... wouldn't that be a good chance?
Let's defeat them!
But the enemy is...
We won't lose to those that wasted their time resting!
Right!
That's right!
Yes.
Then let's stop thinking about useless things...
...and let's focus on tomorrow's work!
Okay!
You're wrong again, Miru. One more time.
Yes!
What is it? Already tired with such little dancing?
Miru-chan!
We'll be back in thirty minutes.
Until then, review...
And Suwa!
Yes!
Come here.
What happened?
With Nagisa?
No... with you.
What kind of training was that?
You who have never mistaken a tone have mistook several today.
Your impression...
Don't think you'll cheat me.
I'll ask again.
What happened?
N-Nothing.
I understand.
You're like Minaguchi.
You don't have any strength when you feel insecure.
You want to destroy yourself?
I... I...
I'm going ahead, okay, Miru-chan?
Cheer up!
Like I said, Ann's role doesn't change.
Ann?
I'm waiting.
I get it. I'll resolve it by tonight.
Bye.
Third underground floor?
Got it. Any more?
I understand...
Um...
I understand your pain, but...
Don't release your weakness in music.
What a relief!
Hey, hey, it's a forbidden entrance here!
You're from Miki's team, aren't you?
You're the surprise visit?
You did come to see the first Lemon Angel, didn't you?
It's incomparable!
Compared to a year and a half ago, it's a lot more efficient!
a lot... more..
Really?
Hey, hey, about that shopping...
Huh, Miru-chan?
Hello?
It's a lie, isn't it?
What?
Is it a lie that Ann is a program?
H-How do you know about that?
What is it? Crying so suddenly...
That voice?
Miki-senpai, Miru-chan is on the third underground floor!
What?
What did she mean by "Miru is on the third underground floor"?
Miru-chan!
Man, what am I going to do?
Quick, take her away from here!
When I was going to show her, she suddenly got scared.
I didn't know what else to do!
What kind of place is this?
M-Miru-chan... this is...
No!
Ann... Ann...
Tomo!
Thank God!
I didn't know what was happening...
What?
These are...
Are...
What? This is the first Lemon Angel of course. The ones who'll dispute against you.
These are the first...
Hey, what do you mean by that?
Huh?
I'm sorry for borrowing your room.
Doesn't matter, doesn't look suspicious at all.
And Miru-chan?
She's in the room resting for now.
And what does that mean?
Well, that's...
To tell you the truth...
It's...
What?
I think you saw the graphics of a new game...
Huh?
Of course not, right?
It's... it's because...
The truth is...
Then that person called Yui-san...
Himuro is really a bad guy.
Poor Yui-san...
So Miki and I decided to create
the new Lemon Angel to heal Yui's feelings.
But that complex program mysteriously appeared...
That is the problem.
Probably someone from abroad.
You don't know anything, Miki?
You're very knowledgeable about programs. Do you know anything suspicious about this?
Me... it was me...
I fixed the archives... and delivered them to...
What?
Miki-senpai...
Huh?
Miki?
That means...
The life of the first Lemon Angel is in that man's hands...
And when it's completed, I'll destroy him.
That...
That?
is my...
...revenge!
Miki?
Re... venge?
Miki-senpai...
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
hajimete negatta hi kara
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
Please, if for only a chance
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
When girls
onna no ko tachi wa
are in love...
koi wo suru ta bi ni
...They become lonely.
sabishigari ni naru
As they do.
itsudaatte
Girls in Love
Girls in love
because when in love, this feeling says no one but you will do
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
Girls in Love
Girls in love
Hold me closer
Motto dakishimete yo
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Yume no naka made tsuretette
Next Time:
It's been a while, Himuro.
Say something!
What is it?
Your a person who's lost with words.
It's not just for not talking!
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 12, "New Moon."
And what is it?
There's not much time left.
New Moon