Karen.
Y-Yes? What is it, Nii-sama?
Even if what you did was for my sake, it's not something you should be applauded for.
But that was-!
I don't want excuses!
You gave me quite a headache. You know that, right?
Yes.
I have to punish you for your wrongdoing.
But I'm your little sister!
You betrayed my trust.
I'm not such a nice guy when it comes to trusting someone again.
Nii-sama...
But since you are my precious sister,
I want to give you a chance to redeem yourself.
Redeem?
Karen, do you swear that you won't betray me again?
Y-Yes! Of course!
Then can you prove it?
Prove that you can endure any hardship for me.
Ni-Nii-sama...?
Nii-sama, who are these people?
I just finished answering that.
Nii-sama! These people...?
They're something along the lines of... the testers of your loyalty.
H-Help me! Nii-sama!
We won't hurt this princess...
Is that what's supposed to happen?
Now then, shall we have your beloved brother watch as you become a woman?
I-It stinks...
N-No-!
Ni-Nii-sama...
So this is the test?
If I can endure this...
For me to be touched by someone other than Nii-sama...
Oh? You're crying?
Well, I guess since this is in front of your beloved brother...
Let's show him how you swallow my semen!
I'm going to cum! Drink it all...
T-This is painful.
W-What does he mean by "drink it"?
Don't tell me that by "it" he means semen?!
No! I don't want it! Not from someone that's not Nii-sama!
No! No!!
It's pouring into my mouth...
It's thick and bitter! It feels wrong...
Nii-sama, was that alright?
Ni-Nii-sama?
Episode 01
Presented
by
Shikkaku Fansubs
No!!
I can't hold back!
N-No!!
N-No, it's entering me!
A cock that isn't Nii-sama's is going in!
It hurts-! No! No!!
Oh right, this is your first time.
N-No! Pull it out! No-!
Pull it out!
karen was going to give her first time to Nii-sama...
This... this is the test, isn't it, Nii-sama?
Even if it's your first, you sure are getting used to it quickly!
N-No way! M-My body is...
My body is getting aroused!
Ouch! Don't be so rough, please!
No-! I-It's so deep!
N-No more! Not in front of Ni-Nii-sama!
C'mon, let's show your brother! Even if he abandons you, we'll take care of you!
No, stop-! I-I'm going to cum, I'll cum-!
I-I'm cumming!
No, not inside! Release it... release it outside!
Please, not inside-!
No!! It's coming out! It's actually coming out-!
Ni...Nii-sama...
N-No-! Don't!
N-No, please not again, I-I'm-!
N-Not there!
Not my butt-!
It's pounding me! It's pounding me deep inside! It's messing up my insides!
My ass is getting paralyzed! If this goes on, Karen will start feeling strange!
I-I'm going to cum, I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Noo-!!
It's filling Karen up... again...
Where are you taking me?
I thought that we'd train you outside today.
It's too dark inside and I can't see your body well.
You seem pretty composed about this.
What would you do if I just ran away?
I wouldn't mind if only you ran away.
However, you know what would happen to Ibuki if you did...
You wretched bastard...
Akagi-senpai!
Why would someone like you join this maniac?
I know that you caused problems to a club and were kicked out,
however...
Miyauchi, why did you learn karate?
Is it because your house is a dojo?
Or was it to train yourself?
Senpai?
I'm different.
I'm doing this because I want to use my power to control people.
I am the power, Yakushima is the control.
The aims are different, however, the effect is the same.
Even if I didn't cause problems, in the end this would have happened.
No way...
Quit with the small talk, Miyauchi, now it's time for you to be ruled.
This position is...!
It looks good,
My preference is here...
S-Stop-!
Firstly, I'll loosen you up...
No! Don't touch it-!
That place... it's dirty!
It looks like you've loosened up here...
Then I can...
No! Not in the ass-!
Don't pull back! Make sure you feel everything with your ass!
Oh, are you shaking your hips?
Even though I did this to your friend... You sure are lewd.
T-That was-!
P-Please stop moving!
If you keep moving...!
My body is acting on it's own!
How does it feel? Are you getting used to taking it up the ass?
It doesn't feel good! My ass is getting paralyzed from being too stretched-!
Are you going to cum?
No! I just want you to stop-!
I'm not going to cum...
Even though I don't want it, even though it's just tight-!
You're a pervert who gets aroused by anal!
No, I'm not! I-I'm not feeling aroused!
No! It's so tight! It's messing up my insides!
Go on! Cum!
No, no! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
It's filling me up again...
No more, I don't want to cum...
You climaxed and squirted?
You sure are lewd.
I wonder what Kurata would say if she saw you...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Ibuki...
I-I've become...
Whoa, you sure are beautiful!
You look like a model, Ibuki-chan!
Your skin is so smooth,
just as I thought it would be. You've got nice breasts, too!
P-Please don't talk about my breasts.
Oh? You're worried?
I like slender girls!
It doesn't matter to you what I think of myself.
So, let's get started, Ibuki-chan...
No! I don't want to lick it!
You're pink and very neat here.
I guess you don't play with yourself.
Of course I don't!
Why would I do such a thing-!
C'mon, suck me as well!
More, suck it more!
I-I can't breathe!
Oh! I'm cumming!
No-!!
So... We're done with foreplay, shall we begin the main course?
Haven't you had enough?
P-Please stop!
It feels great every time I thrust!
No, really, this is painful!
It feels like I'm burning down there!
I think I'm going to cum!
Even though this is the eighth time, I going to cum again!
No-! Please don't cum in me again!
I-I'll really get pregnant!
Please, no! Not inside! Not inside!
I-It's filling me up...
Nii-sama...
Nii-sama!
You did well back there, as expected of my beloved sister.
I'm glad you're not angry anymore.
Of course, however...
You know what we're doing to Kurata Ibuki and Miyauchi Akira, don't you?
Yes.
But you let them escape knowing so.
Was it because you thought that what we're doing is immoral?
Karen didn't mean for them to escape,
Karen just wanted to tell them how lucky they are.
However, Akira did slip past me while I was talking.
Karen, are you willing to accept what we're doing?
If you do, would you like to join us?
For two more days...
Huh?
I watched that video that Kurosaki-senpai gave me.
Do you think they'll change to how we want them by then?
Do you have a plan, Karen?
Yes! I think that Miyauchi-senpai is almost there.
However, Kurata-senpai is still...
Please continue.
I think we should wedge her into shape to make her come around.
For example...
I approve of Karen-san's proposal.
We've got two days left.
Maybe it's time to step it up to the final stage.
I'm fine with it.
S-Same here.
Now then, we can assume that Karen-san is one of us, right?
Thank you very much.
Let us commence Karen's plan.
We've got two days; let's wrap things up.
Akira, how are you doing?
You don't need to worry about me.
I can still bear with it.
Could you come watch some entertainment with me?
Entertainment?
Could you first put this on?
Why do I need to put on such a thing...?
What took you? We've been waiting for ages.
Eh? Akagi-kun?
Hey, hey. Don't be so afraid.
We aren't getting involved today.
Because you're the one that's doing it.
Even though you're blind, you can sense something? You're pretty good.
That voice is your partner.
Karen-san's?
But...
This is Karen-san's personal request.
Before you is Karen in bondage clothes.
Please clean her by licking her up.
We'll get Kurata-senpai onto Miyauchi-senpai, and we're going to re-enact her worst experiences.
And how are we going to do that?
How about saying "Karen has an interest in girls, so she wishes to try it"?
What a fun plan!
Karen, that's a good idea!
Nii-sama...
It feels good here, doesn't it?
Very good. Karen looks happy.
It seems like your clitoris is poking out...
It's so pointy, maybe I should lightly bite it...?
Very well, she looks very pleased.
S-So then, can I go?
The thing she's pleased with is the foreplay.
Is it ready?
Right here.
This here is a magnificent dildo.
Now then, Ibuki, dig into Karen with it.
I-I can't do such a thing...!
That's Karen's wish, please make it come true.
It's... digging into me, too!
S-So deep-!
My hips are moving on their own!
A-Are you feeling that aroused?
You're feeling more than I am!
Did you cum?
But if I continue to do this, you'll feel much better!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Y-You came again?
I-I'm sorry! I can't cum that q-quickly!
Just a bit more...
I'm nearly there-!
It's coming, something large is coming!
N-No, I can't stop! I'm g-going to cum!
Very nice! That was quite a show.
T-Then can I go back now?
Of course!
But before you do, you've got time to look at what you've done...
Huh?
Eh? Karen-san...?
Akira?
I-Ibuki...
What have I done to Akira...
Akira! No, no-! No!!
I brought you tea, Nii-sama. I also brought these two...
Umm...
It's nothing; it's just that it suits you too well.
You're too kind, Shuji-sama!
I'm very happy! I thought that you wouldn't like it.
The training for these two was completed last night.
Now, in complete form, these two gaze at me like I'm their lover.
Nii-sama, do you know why we changed into these clothes?
I can tell by the look in their eyes...
They've run away from their memories, and, ironically, to something that's...
We would like to service you, Shuji-sama. Is that okay?
So I guess the link between the body and the pleasure yielded...
Of course! Allow me to enjoy it!
I'll permit you to service me.
H-How sturdy!
No getting ahead of yourselves, okay?
I-I also want to lick master's penis...
Shuji-sama belongs to all of us, so let's do it together.
C'mon, Akira...
Okay, Ibuki...
What an intense smell, that alone turns me on...
It's amazing... Just from this smell, I...
From just smelling this, I...
My pussy is throbbing...
That's it! I'm about to...!
You gave us so much!
What an intense smell!
I can hear you guys behind those doors!
How about you come in already?
Now then, how about we start our last act?
Your cock is so good! It's so large! Please thrust inside me more!
My ass feels amazing!
Even though I'm this wet, I think I'm going to cum a-again!
I'm going to cum again!
I'm...!
I-I'm going to cum!
I've got the slaves that I wanted...
What else do I want?
Nii-sama! Karen wants to re-enact what you did at the academy.
There's a road right in front of me. Only a coward wouldn't take it.
Nii-sama?
It's nothing, Karen. Do you have any other objectives?
Yes! About three.
I'm looking forward to it.
Now then, Nii-sama, let's enjoy ourselves, forever and forever...
So, it's time to begin another game.
We will service you more and more!