Girls, we have a problem!
Dear Friends
When I woke up, her bags weren't there anymore.
She really went to Takumi-kun.
So that means that she's disqualified?
It can't be!
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Hounto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai no Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
Symphony Of Sorrow
Baby?
It's Takumi-kun.
From now on, you'll be an older sister.
Older sister?
This boy won't be alone anymore.
Alone?
That's right, so we'll give him all our love.
Because we're a family now.
Takumi-kun, it's your older sister.
Wait~ wait, wait~
Let's go.
Takumi-kun, when you're in a pinch, your sister will always help you.
Sorry, I didn't understand, so all this happened.
Don't worry.
I'll bring Erika back!
I'll go too!
Wait.
If you do that, you'll also be disqualified.
Now's not the time to talk about this, alright?
I can't just let that happen like this.
Erika is an important friend.
Senpai, don't you think so?
Senpai!
Let it rest. Let's go!
Tomo-chan, Saya-san!
Erika is an important friend.
Senpai, don't you think so?
Senpai!
Good morning!
G-Good morning!!
Huh?
Wasn't Erika-chan the one in charge today?
Eh...! U-Um... Erika-chan couldn't...
What do I do?
What about Tomo and Saya?
They're still sleeping?
They went out.
What?!
Mi-Miru-chan!
Went out?!
N-No, that's not true...!
,Right, Miru-chan?
They went to Tokyo.
Tokyo?!
What for?!
Not good!! Especially since Kogure-san is coming today...
Mi... Miru-chan...
That's right, it's excellent news.
Make several pages for her, please.
And don't go out quickly.
You're also receiving a good amount from Kudou-san, right?
Later.
Well now, Katagiri, you're going to suffer.
I'll have my sweet revenge now.
Hello? Takumi?
What are you doing today?
Yeah, at the station...
Got it.
Takumi, please...
Don't leave until I get there.
I'll tell you the reason when I see you.
Yes... okay,
So... bye.
Did she answer?
Wait a minute!
Ah... Erika?
Where are you now?
Why're you quiet?
Tomo?
That's right!
Saya and I'll arrive in Tokyo in a bit.
What?
You can't do that!
Go back immediately!
But I don't want to!
Because...
Give it here.
Erika, stop avoiding the subject and tell me where you are!
We're going with you. It won't make any sense if we're not all together.
Understand, Erika?
Saya...
Hey, Erika, we're friends, right?
Tomo!
Erika!
I understand. I'm going to the studio.
What?
What station?
Oh, I didn't ask Takumi which station he'd be at!
It's so typical of you, Erika!
Whaaat?!
So you mean those three went back to Tokyo?
What'll we do?
And Katagiri-san?
I couldn't find him earlier.
Maybe he followed those three?
Even so, right now's an important period before the debut.
If news like this leaks out...
I know!
We'll call the company immediately!
We'll do anything to stop the news!
Yes!
I'll show that I... can protect the new Lemon Angel!
Damn, we stopped most of the magazines!
But there's one that doesn't want to give up.
So that means...
If they publish it, it's all over.
That was Nouvelle-san.
Not satisfied with my report?
It's not that...
It's just that my newspaper got famous with Himuro-san's reports.
And I don't want to upset him.
You...
By the way, Kudou-san told me..
You and Erika Campbell...
I'll put the scandals in my newspaper.
Ooh, scary, very scary!
But there's another person with whom I'm more afraid of, Katagiri-san.
She actually came...
Erika!
Tomo, Saya!
Is this the studio?
Yes.
I asked Takumi's manager, so there's no mistake.
Actually, I'm a bit scared.
Of not being with Takumi like always...
But the truth is, I want to tell myself to be strong.
I love Takumi from the bottom of my heart.
Yes!
Go, older sister!
Sister!
Takumi!
Why'd you come here so suddenly?
Eh...
It... It's because...
What a shame, I was discovered!
What's so funny?
Everything is going exactly as I planned.
What?
Was on purpose!
I told that story on purpose.
To finish my report...
To protect her sweet boyfriend Takumi-kun,
the poor Erika-chan returns to Tokyo.
Hey, stop right now!
You can't!
Are you all right, sister?
Takumi, you can't...
Move away!
This is a good one!
They look like real lovers!
The ones who don't share the same blood end up feeling strong emotions for one another?
Takumi-kun!
You and your sister next to you, did you know that you aren't real siblings?
What about it?
I've known for a long time.
What?!
Before we left our country, our parents told me.
I was a bit shocked, but as for me, I don't care if we have the same blood or not.
I only have one sister that I love.
Takumi!
So, nothing you'll write will cause us any problems.
Takumi-kun, nice!
You're good!
Damn!
My camera!
You bastard!
K-Katagiri!
Katagiri-san?!
They told me you'd tell all of your past to the newspaper chief.
To prevent the destruction of Lemon Angel.
What?
A super producer that would destroy his whole career to save the girls!
You disappoint me.
What, you bastard?
What did you say?
Next time, I'll do the same to you.
Wait, I shall return one day!
Hurray!
Look what happened!
You!!
You stopped training, and left the area...
You're really brave!
It's not that!
It's my fault they left.
E-Erika!
And also...
Katagiri-san, while I still have a chance, I'll say this...
If we continue doing that absurd training, we'll lose our vocal cords.
I... don't understand what you're wanting us to do.
Lose your vocal cords?
Arisu? How about resting a bit?
I'm okay. So please, don't stop the music.
But...
I could be a bird locked in a cage.
But if I can continue singing, I don't mind not knowing the sky.
Arisu!
Hold tight! Arisu!
Vocal cord rupture?
Arisu... Arisu can't sing anymore?
It can't be...
Haneda Arisu
Arisu, how do you feel?
Arisu? Arisu... ARISU!!
W-Wow, this will be an excellent story!
When I lost Arisu, looking like I ran away, I went abroad.
So that was it...
Yuki, while you've been training, did you feel any pain in your throat?
What?
Ah, no...
Speaking of which, I guess my high-pitch got sharper.
Me neither, and it looks like my voice is coming out of my stomach now.
I'm not asking you all to train to destroy your throats.
But so that they won't be destroyed.
So that's it.
So that's why...
Idiot...
You could've told us that from the beginning, Onihige...
Onihige?
Oh, Oops...
It's nothing!
Ch-Changing the subject, where are we?
Can you hear it?
Piano!
Someone's playing a piano.
It's a sound that warms the soul.
It sounds like it's singing.
Listen well.
Among the ones I know, that's the best pianist.
Teacher, you play well!
Play more to us!
I love teacher's piano!
I really do!
I sent all the information here.
Now I can have my revenge!
What's wrong?
Damn!
All the data is gone!!
What did you say?!
Again...
Well, it's good that everything went well this time.
But the next time something happens, talk to me first!
Understand?
Yes.
We're sorry...
It's Tomo's fault who left without saying anything.
Ah?!
You're mean...
Saya, you followed right behind me!
It was difficult.
After you three disappeared...
Real difficult..
Oh... Miru, you defended us too?
Seems like you're all okay now, right?
What?
You realized?
Of course, because I'm your temporary manager now.
Ah, the fact that the people who left would be disqualified...
Miki-senpai.
Um, If Tomo-chan and the others are disqualified, then I'll leave too.
Me too.
If it doesn't continue with these members, I don't want to continue either.
Yumi.
Miru-chan.
You guys...
So, new Lemon Angel, go get changed immediately!
Let's start the training!
What?
Why're you all standing around?
You want that Onihige to get mad with you?
So that means...
Miki-san!
Wait a second!
This is the debut music of the new Lemon Angel!
What?
Cool! Very Cool!
I'm already cheering up!
All right! Give everything you've got!
To start, you'll do 200 sit-ups singing this song!
Whaaat?!
Okay, come on!
Hip-hip-hooray!
Hey, all together!
Louder!
Hip-hip-hooray!
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love.
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
We Haven't got any regional work for a long time, have we?
Y-Yes, for some time, but...
Saya-chan, You're not cheerful?
I don't have good memories from my old work...
To put it simply, I have a lot of horrible memories I don't want to remember...
Ah, it's always been good, hasn't it?!
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 10, "Blue Station."
You were very pretty with the costume last time, you know?
That's exactly what I didn't like!
Blue Station