Aneki...
senior. 1 [Saki-sempai]
My Sweet Elder Sister
I've been watching Senpai for a long time.
But it was hopeless. I hadn't even known her name.
I tried to forget her, but..
But...
After seeing her covered in sweat like
that, I couldn't get her out of my head.
Just act natural.
She's going to notice...
Hey!
Yes?
Good game, isn't it?
Oh, this?
I've been playing it a lot lately.
Awesome!
At first I didn't know what to say to her.
Go for it!
But then I found out that we shared
something in common.
Thanks for teaching me that combo.
I was finally able to beat the boss using it.
Nice.
We had started out as total strangers...
...but being together was so great, so much fun.
Yeah, go! Get'em!
You did it!
That was great.
I really like her.
It sure is hot today.
Yeah.
I can smell her deodorant.
After volleyball practice today, you
should have seen my shirt.
It was like a wet rag.
Wow.
So hot...
I'm just gonna run to the bathroom.
Okay.
I wonder if her gym suit is in there...
This is her...
...her smell!
Senpai...
Takumi-kun, I hadn't known you felt this way.
It must stink like sweat and pee.
Suck it more.
Yes, Takumi-kun! More, suck it more!
It's embarrassing, but I'll show you everything.
Now, let me do it for you.
How's that, Takumi-kun? Feel good?
Then let me rub my smell...
...all over your body.
Senpai!
More! Don't stop!
Takumi-kun... Takumi-kun!
Senpai, I'm gonna-
Go ahead. Shoot your cum all over my face!
Takumi-kun...
Senpai...
The next day Senpai hadn't said
anything about the shorts I took.
I was sorry for taking them though...
...but I couldn't get enough of their scent.
I dreamed about Senpai all day long.
I watched her at every chance...
...dreamed about her all day long...
I can't walk around like this.
I'll take care of it in there.
Why's she...?
S-Saki-senpai!
I shouldn't do this here... someone will see me.
That's Senpai's...
Senpai...
I can't take it anymore.
Oh God, I might get raped!
Oh yes... I'm so hot!
Here it comes... it's happening!
No more hiding.
T-Takumi-kun?
No!
Takumi-kun, don't Takumi-kun!
No...
Her skin was even smoother than I imagined.
I could smell her sweat mingled with her deodorant.
Leave me alone!
Her moist breasts made me lose control.
Don't look down there!
I needed to go deeper.
Takumi-kun, stop it! This is dirty!
Don't! Takumi-kun, no!
You can't!
Takumi-kun... please, at least do it gently!
Senpai... Senpai!
Not so rough! You'll hurt me!
Senpai... Senpai... Senpai!
No!
Oh, God!
Senpai! Senpai! Senpai! Senpai!
I shouldn't do that in public, but I can't help myself...
Senpai?
I've tried to quit. I think there's something wrong with me.
I've liked you for a long time now.
So I don't care what's wrong with you.
Are... Are you sure?
Yes.
Yean...
I like you too.
A... ne... ki.
Morning!
What's up?
The next day, I was nervous about meeting Takumi-kun.
Good morning!
Hey!
He was his usual self.
But our friendship had changed...
You sure...? You don't mind?
Watch me masturbate.
Senpai!
Look, watch me.
Every day we masturbated together. Kind of perverted.
But being watched by Takumi-kun made me so hot...
Takumi-kun... let's do it.
Takumi-kun... it's going so deep!
Senpai.
Takumi-kun really knew how to get me riled up.
He kept me constantly on the verge of orgasm.
Slow down!
I couldn't believe how good it felt.
I can't take it!
Go ahead, cum whenever you want.
I'm going to cum too!
Se... Senpai...
Yeah?
Why do you masturbate?
I'm ashamed to let you see me...
...but at the same time, it feels really good.
I'm sorry.
I thought maybe you hadn't liked me enough.
It's nothing like that.
Without you, it wouldn't be so good.
I feel the same.
You know, I have a volleyball match next week.
We'll be practicing a lot, I won't be able to see you.
Really?
Was it, something I said?
No.
Just... could I have your underwear?
I want to always feel close to you.
In that case, I'd like yours too.
I'll miss you next week as well.
Um... Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Come on, don't stare at them like that.
They really make you horny?
Yeah, I'm hot too.
But, we can't masturbate yet.
Not until after the match.
Then, next time we meet, we can go crazy.
Okay.
Easier said than done.
Being apart from Takumi-kun was hard.
Saki!
Yeah!
Nice, Saki!
Good practice.
Good job, Saki.
Where's Saki?
Guess she went home.
Hmm?
I was lonely my body was lonely.
I thought of his face, his voice, his smell, and his touch.
I couldn't help it.
I couldn't control my excitement.
A single touch would have made me climax.
But I resisted the temptation.
Then, finally the week was over.
I'm getting wet just waiting for Takumi-kun.
Did you wait long?
No.
Takumi-kun...
Senpai...
Let's go.
Takumi-kun, I'm about to cum just from kissing you.
Me too.
Let's catch up.
Umm... Senpai?
Sorry, about the outfit.
I've never worn this, it's embarrassing.
But, I wore it for you.
Thank you.
Senpai...
Today I'll use this.
Watch how dirty I can be.
Okay.
I'm putting it in.
Takumi-kun... look, look.
Senpai!
It's wiggling around inside me.
This one, too.
Senpai, that's... you don't have to...
Senpai...
Takumi-kun!
Takumi-kun, I missed you so much.
I could smell your underwear!
The smell of your dick made me so
wet, it looked like I peed myself.
Senpai!
Takumi-kun, right there!
Your tongue's inside me... oh, God!
Senpai, I want to...
Takumi-kun, your cock's on my ass...
Takumi-kun, please... don't tease me.
Give it to me!
No, not yet
I want it. Please, Takumi-kun.
Senpai, you can see us in the mirror.
Don't be a pervert.
I had never felt so wonderfully dirty.
Using two vibrators at once, while Takumi-kun
grabbed me from behind...
It was so embarrassing, but so hot.
I can't stand it! I'm gonna cum!
It's so good! So good!
My pussy's tingling! I'm gonna... cum!
Senpai.
Takumi-kun!
You're inside me...
Senpai, it's tight down there.
Don't wony, fuck me hard.
Your cock's pushing all the way to the back!
Takumi-kun, let's cum at the same time.
Okay.
Oh, God... a dick and a vibrator at the same time...!
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Senpai, I'm gonna-
Yes, give me your cum!
Shoot your cum... deep... deep inside me!
I don't want... anyone... but you.
Me, neither. I don't want to be away from you again.
I'm never... ever... gonna let you go.
Oh!
I've been looking for these!
Sorry!
You could have just asked for them.
We should do it while I wear these.
Takumi?
S-Senpai!
To Be Continued...