Be quiet!
Stop it!
Shut up!
You want me to hurt you?
She's got really big tits!
lt hurts!
No...
No!
Now let me stick it inside!
No, no!
Stay still!
Don't put that inside me!
Someone help me!
Man, she's really tight!
She pushed my thing back out!
Don't bite it.
l'm coming!
He did it inside me.
Hot...
lt's hot...
ENCODED BY SHINKIRO
Menage a Twins
Vol. 1 Duet of Lust
l have to go Minoru-san.
Are you working a night shift at the hospital?
Yeah.
Your dinner is in the fridge.
l know.
Anyway...
What's this?
Ah, l forgot.
Newly hired nurses asked me
to make them some boiled rice.
l almost forgot to bring it.
l was working on it hard since last night.
There's some for you in the fridge...
You're gonna be late mother.
You're right.
l can't believe she's the head nurse.
She's doing it again...
Her husband does go on lots
of business trips but...
Wrong email?
Meet
Don't Meet
Yes?
Who is it?
l'm Akane.
From Akane
lt's called a dating site right?
lt's my first time doing this.
lt's not like that.
l asked one of your friends and got your email.
Why me?
l wanted to see you...
No matter what.
Be gentle with me.
Yes...
Feels good...
l'm so happy...
More, more...
More...
Not there Minoru-kun...
Little lower...
Yes, little higher...
The door isn't locked...
Did l forget to lock the door?
Minoru-san, l forgot something.
Can you get my commuter
pass by the television?
Are you here?
ls he in the bathroom?
Minoru-san...
Stop.
Not now...
That's weird.
l wonder where l put it...
Oh, it's right here.
Ok, l'm leaving now Minoru-san.
Keep it down.
She's gone already.
The neighbors are gonna notice.
Let's stick this in my ass.
So tight!
Tight...
lt's tight!
Yes, so good...
l'm getting very excited...
Yes, yes...
My ass is hot...
Do me more...
Give me more!
No, l don't want it like it was back then.
Make me forget...
The time l was raped by many men...
Do me much harder!
Raped by many men?
More, more...
Many men huh?
Don't take it out!
l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
Hot...
lt's coming inside me!
Do you like email or cell phone?
l have to pick one?
l think it's best for us that way.
Don't you want to see me again?
Whatever.
lt's up to you.
l'm Akane.
l'll take your word then.
Your mother just went out?
You can come and join me
for dinner if you want.
Really?
Sure.
My husband is on a long business
trip, it's really sad eating by myself.
Let me know if you want something.
l'll do my best to make it for you.
Thank you for the meal.
lt was really delicious.
l guess it was worth putting the effort.
But l didn't know you were pregnant.
Right?
lt's my first time, so l can't really tell.
But l feel it's moving inside.
Can you tell?
No.
Put your ears on it and listen.
Ok.
Well?
Can you hear it?
Well, let's see...
Do you hear anything?
Yes.
l hear you moaning when
you masturbate every night.
l'm embarrassed.
lt's wet.
Don't you wear panties?
lt's much more comfortable this way.
You can keep going.
Minoru-kun...
No, l'll go crazy...
Give it to me now!
Feels so good...
So good...
Feels good...
Yes...
So good...
Amazing...
Yes...
ls it safe for her to have
sex with the baby inside?
Yes...
What made you want to go shopping with me?
Nothing.
l'm sure you're tired from
work, so l thought l might help.
l wonder what happened...
What's wrong?
lt's been a while.
What?
You look good.
Who was that?
A friend of yours?
Yes, sort of...
This is Akane. l want
to see you now. l'm at...
Sorry mother, l have to see a friend.
l didn't know they had rooms like this.
l didn't know you liked
this kind of thing.
You thought l couldn't get
it on in a normal situation?
For a game, it kind of hurts.
You didn't just meet my
mother accidentally right?
lf you can tell me how you two are
related, this will be over very quickly.
l told you before, l knew her long
time ago, and we met by accident.
Let's start shall we?
lf you feel like talking, just nod.
l really want to know, the
relationship between the two of you.
Hey, do you feel like talking now?
l see, so you still won't talk.
l wonder how much you can take.
You must be thirsty right?
Have you had enough?
Let me go to the bathroom.
You feel like talking now?
Maybe we need to apply a finishing touch.
Where do you want me to stick it?
You really want it in the ass don't you?
lt hurts!
l'll give you something better in the other hole.
l have to pee!
Take it out of my ass!
Take it out, take it out!
Then tell me your relationship with my mother.
lf you want to know that bad, l'll tell you.
l'm your mother's older sister!
lt can't be...
Welcome home.
l'll fix your dinner.
l met with Akane-san.
Then she told you everything?
Yeah.
l'm sorry.
l wasn't trying to hide it from you.
Someday, l was going to tell you someday.
l knew this day would come.
lt's true, you're the son
of my older sister Akane.
No, l don't want it like it was back then.
Make me forget...
The time l was raped by many men...
Akane became pregnant after
being raped and l'm her son?
So l did it with my mother Akane...
What are you doing?
Stop!
No!
No...
Stop...
Please, stop...
You feel humiliated, mother?
To be stripped naked by the man
you thought to be your son...
And having your tits exposed
and my cock in your mouth...
You're being played around!
Now...
What the hell?
You're not even a woman yet!
You're still a virgin!
lt hurts!
l'm excited now!
What are you doing?
l'm gonna play with this hole!
No, stop it!
Don't get me wrong mother...
This is what l call mending our family ties.
There's no need to stop.
You're enjoying this.
lf you don't like it, then l can stop.
Ok, here l come!
lt's hot!
Your juice is flowing inside me!
Good.
You were a virgin but it looks like you climaxed.
You probably masturbated
a lot when l wasn't around.
l'll do you in the ass as a reward!