Yeah, so you've changed a bit haven't you, Himari?
Huh?
It's because of a guy, isn't it Himari?
Huh?!
You've have a feminine aura lately.
So, who is it?
Did it hurt?
Am I spot on?
Um...
It's...
Well then, let's go to the usual place, and talk of your sweet experiences.
I-I have something I have to do!
See you later!
Himari!
What am I thinking?
Jeez...
That person...
H-Huh?
Sensei?
Did something happen?
Huh?
Weird...
I'm sure he was around here...
Eh? No way, Sensei!
O-Oh my...
Who is that?
Shikkaku fansubs Presents
Episode 01 "I mustn't, but I..."
Himari?
Himari, what's wrong?
I-Ibu-chan... Uh, what is it?
You've been like this since morning.
Even though you're always hyped up.
Jeez, Ibu-chan. You're mean.
But I'm a bit sleepy...
Ibu-chan...
She's like always...
And yet that happened yesterday...
Your face looks red. Do you have a cold?
T-That's not it!
B-But don't you have a fever?
T-Thanks anyway, Ibu-chan. I'm fine, okay?
I'm going to the restroom.
Himari...
What's with her?
Ibu-chan hasn't changed...
She looks the same as always.
Huh? Oh right...
I fell...
Eh?
O-Oh my...
This is...!
No way.. No way!
No!
You silly!
This is amazing!
Sensei-!
Sensei, you're being too rough!
It's so big!
We shouldn't be doing such things here, but-!
Sensei! You're more... than usual...
It's because you're so cute.
Sensei, I'm so happy!
I'm sorry that it has to be here.
Jeez, you promised you wouldn't say that!
Sensei, you-!
Sensei!
I... I'm about to...!
No, Sensei-! If you do that, I'll...!
No! I can't take it any longer!
Sensei's semen...
No...
No... I did it in school...
Himari?
Ibu-chan...
You're still red...
We have gymnastics next, so how about resting in the infirmary?
I-I should do that, then.
S-See you then.
School Infirmary
What should I do?
I can't look her straight in the face anymore...
I-Ibu-chan's face was the face of a woman, right?
It would be really bad if I were to happen to meet Shun-sensei...
Are you all right?
Se-Sensei!
W-What's wrong? Shouting like that...
W-What is it, Sensei?
What, you ask...?
I just came to check on how my student is doing...
But you look fine.
Well, have a good rest.
S-Suddenly popping out of nowhere like that... Jeez!
You don't know how I feel...
I'm fine now, Ibu-chan.
I feel much better now that I'm rested.
See you then!
Since it's her, I thought she wouldn't be so flustered, even with a cold. But...
Everyone's worried about her...
I'm jealous of Himari...
Everyone loves her.
The only ones who are there for me are you guys.
Although the only thing I can do for you is feed you.
You're always like that, Kirisaki.
I thought I would be okay today...
Splendid as usual, Ibu.
J-Jeez, you're such a meanie.
You might catch a cold...
Hurry, you should take a shower.
T-This is nothing. I'll be fine!
So he's doing it with Ibu-chan...
I should ask him about it.
He's always worried about me.
Even I...
Sensei...
I'll leave your change of clothes here.
Y-Yes!
D-Don't look!
Oh no...
I always mess up...
Sensei!
What are you doing?
Please leave.
I locked the door.
That's not the problem...
Sensei, we shouldn't do it here...
I'm worried about you, Ibu.
You're stubborn after all.
W-What are you saying?
That's not...
Rely on me a bit.
I want to help you, too.
Well, since we're lovers...
Y-You're too reliable, Sensei...
Isn't it okay at times like this?
W-We can't...
But I love everything about you...
Sensei...
No... Sensei...
Don't, Sensei. That's my butt...
Se-Sensei, um...
M-Me too...
I want you to feel good as well...
S-So this is your...
I-Ibu, don't force yourself.
Sensei, I want to make you feel good as well.
Amazing...
It's reacting to me...
Does it feel good?
I-It's really big...
It barely fits into my mouth.
Don't force yourself...
Please bear with me.
Amazing, my mouth is so full...
No... S-Sensei's hand, it's...
Ibu, move your hips this way.
Don't, Sensei! That's too embarrassing!
Right there-! It's amazing!
It tastes so good!
Any more and-!
S-Sensei-!
Sensei, don't-!
T-That's too much! Please-!
It's fine, don't hold it in.
T-That's not it!
P-Please!
I can't hold it in-!
No! No! I can't-!
No way, no way!
I-Ibu, I'm sorry...
I told you to stop.
Sensei, you brute.
Well, you're so cute. I couldn't restrain myself...
S-Sweet-talking me like that won't get you anywhere.
Jeez.
You've seen so many embarrassing parts of me.
It's too much!
I-Ibu...
I will never forgive you.
Ibu...
To think that she's together with Sensei...
Even though males aren't allowed here...
The first time was gentler...
Err, am I going to be bullied?
No, that's not it.
I was able to change thanks to you.
You were always looking after me...
So...
Are you really fine with this?
I-I'm fine with it.
Sensei, I want to do it with you like this...
We've become one, haven't we?
Sensei, please move.
Well, I heard that it doesn't feel good if you don't move...
No-!
Shun-sensei-! I love you!
I...!
I want to feel more of you!
To be honest, I've always wanted to be with you!
You don't have to be alone anymore.
I'm so happy!
I want you feel more of you!
I'm gonna...
N-No way...
Sensei's "finger" is in Ibu-chan's embarrassing place...
Ibu-chan, you're making such a dirty expression...
Sensei's thing... is deep inside me...!
You're so deep inside me, Shun-sen-!
Don't!
Shun-sensei!
Shun-!
Shun-! Shun-!
So good-!
I'm feeling it deep inside me!
You're reaching so deep inside me!
It's so good-! Shun!
Shun, I love you!
Shoot it inside! A whole lot! Just do it!
Shun-! Let's cum together-!
Together!
No!
D-Don't-!
Shun's semen is overflowing...
No...
To find them together like that...
Himari?
Are you still not feeling well?
I-I'm fine.
I feel fine, and then I feel worse...
I wonder where I am now?
Hi-Himari, have you finally-?!
Hey, Ibu-chan, I hope you're not having rude thoughts.
O-Of course not...
It wasn't much of a thought.
Ah, I knew it. Jeez.
Hi-Himari.
Sensei, it's not okay.
Having sex with a student in our dorm...
That's not fair, Sensei.