Once upon a time, in the middle of the Central City,
there are four gates which have been protected by four guardians.
West Gate by Byakko, South Gate by Suzaku,
North Gate by Genbu, East Gate by Seiryuu
Though they were called four guardians, they have so much monstrous power
that many people mistake them for monsters.
Their lives were carved within Central City's history.
They still live even after Central City vanished.
But, as the time goes by, their powers start to slowly weaken.
It began with Genbu, who lost his power as a guardian,
The others decided to unite their powers
to protect what's left within them.
They borrow the forbidden god's power to share
their powers within humans flesh.
They lived in human flesh for a long time and even have their own
four children from a human generation...
Now, there are four people who inherit the most powerful spirits of
Seiryuu, Byakko, Suzaku and Genbu.
Now they fight amongst themselves to determine who inherits the most powerful
DNA of the guardians spirits, with the struggle of making children.
Haramasete Seiryuu-kun!
1st
Make a child with me
Haramasete Seiryuu-kun!
1st
Make a child with me
That's what it's gonna be, even though it's so sudden for you,
I want you to... with me... what do you say about it...?
I want you to do it with me...
What... what's with you, Suzaku-senpai?
And what did you mean earlier?
You dare make a woman say something like this,
even though I'm holding so much shame within me.
There's no time in this world that I'm not thinking
about trying to kill you by myself.
That can't be entirely true, you're not acting like the usual Suzaku-senpai.
Then, what do you need me to do?
What I need?! Do you want me to say those embarrassing things all the time?
You're mumbling to yourself, so I don't quite understand
what you were saying earlier.
I want you to do it.
Eh?
I want you to do it with me.
Yes?
I want you to have sex with me and let me bear your children!!!
Having sex with Suzaku-senpai?!
The student council prez? The academy heroine?
Many times... I've watched her swimming club training,
and now I'm having sex with the adorable Suzaku-senpai?!
Hey... hey, Seiryuu... Did you hear what I just said earlier?
It's to protect the power of Central City guardians within me.
Having sex with Suzaku-senpai...
Then you don't really like me, you're only after my penis?!
That's wrong!!!
I sense that me and you are descendants of the four guardians spirits,
so I'm tracing the history of each of our generations.
Then, between you and me...
Senpai, you don't really have any interest in my penis?
Even though I always look at you in your swimsuit with my perverted eyes.
He's already out of his mind, I shall use my true power.
Then, how is it? Do you want to make a child with me, Seiryuu Tougo?
Senpai, your breasts... are touching my back...
Well, They're touching you.
Suzaku-senpai's breasts... They're amazing!!
How is it?  Do you want me that badly right now?
That's... Is it true that I can have those things, senpai?
Though I've already used my spirit power, his guard
isn't even lowered at all.
Suzaku-senpai, what're you doing?
Even though I can't force you to do it, I'm going to wait until
you're up to doing it.
You want to put your thing inside of me, right?
So this is Seiryuu's thing... I'm going to put
this big thing inside of me.
Senpai, you don't have to rush like this...
I want to do it with you.
What did you say?! Then hurry!
Senpai, can we... have a date first?
Do you want my virginity or not?!
Is it possible that you're virgin?
That's rude! I wouldn't let someone touch my body so casually!!
Besides the one who carries the strongest genes!
That's right, senpai is only after Seiryuu's genes after all.
She doesn't have any feelings for me...
Sorry, I think I said too much earlier...
although I'm doing it for Suzaku's benefit,
It's more than that, I really care about you, that's why
I want you to look at me.
Do you really care about me?
You might not remember, but we did meet once when we're still young.
Ever since then, I always thought of you...
Even if there's not something like that, it's for Suzaku's family's orders...
I wouldn't look at someone with this uneasy feeling.
Can't you accept these feelings?
I... I can't hold it anymore, Suzaku-senpai!!!
You're finally up to it... I'm so happy.
Do you really like my body that much?
Suzaku-senpai's breasts feel really good.
Is that so, then you can do whatever you want.
I can't believe that I can do something like this with Suzaku-senpai.
I remember there was a letter from my father this morning...
What the hell does this mean?!
4 Guardians Descendant Seiryuu's House
To my son, your father is doing alright for now.
Also I've sent two girls to be your wife.
I want you to choose one of them before the battle in the art museum starts.
I thought that you would come home this time, you stupid father!!
Is it possible that another candidate to be my wife is...
That damn father, did he lose his mind in this summer heat?
Tougo.
Morning.
Good morning.
Here you go, this is for you.
What is this?
It's a bento that I made yesterday, also I made some for you too...
This is the first time that Akiha made a bento for me,
did the rain fall this summer?
Hey, would you like to eat it with me this afternoon?
Of course.
To-u-go~ku~n!!!
Morning, Kitami. Please don't stick to me so hard,
It's makes it hard to breath.
Tougo-kun, you're always shy about this.
I'm not shy about it. Besides, I don't have any interest in man like you.
Just a little longer, please.
Kitami-chan, you're on the art museum committee aren't you?
Are you sure that you don't have to go right now?
That's... right, well I have to go right now.
See you again, Tougo-kun!
Even though she's like that, she inherited Genbu's family authority.
She's also a man underneath that.
What's going on in there?
Wha... what is it?
I've been waiting for you, Seiryuu Tougo.
Suzaku-sama, you've been waiting for Seiryuu all this time?!
Su... Suzaku-senpai.
You've finally appeared.
I didn't realize that he could get close enough to her.
Go... good morning, Suzaku-senpai.
Morning, Seiryuu.
Good morning, Suzaku Natsuhime-senpai.
Morning, Byakko Akiha. It looks like you're with Tougo already.
I see, so you're making the first move after all.
That's not right, we're doing what we used to before.
Akiha, do you plan to keep Seiryuu to yourself?
Even though I don't plan to do something like that,
I won't let you take Seiryuu that easily.
Then I just have to take him from you, since we need to
decide everything between us after all.
I'll accept your offer, senpai!
Akiha, we're gonna be late!
Seiryuu Tougo!
I'll wait for you at the pool after school.
Though I don't know what's going on,
I keep going to the pool after school.
Even my father said that I had to choose between them.
I still can't believe this whole wife candidate thing,
Should I pick Suzaku-senpai or Akiha.
Senpai, do you know how to make a child?
O... of course I know something simple like that.
Yesterday, I'm even watched the video my father gave me.
The first thing that we have to do is make lip contact with each other,
with this simple kiss.
My first kiss is with senpai.
Tougo's tongue is...
Senpai.
Senpai's tongue is sweet.
The time our tongues made contact, I felt something in my pussy.
What are we going to do next?
The next... the next one...
We have to lick each other's bodies while we're naked.
They're tasty, senpai's breasts are really tasty.
Did you really like licking all over my body?
You're like a baby, you know?
Please don't suck them too hard.
Your nipples are getting hard...
If you do it so hard, I'm won't just feel it in my nipples, but I'll also feel it down there.
After this... what should I do?
Then... we should have our... things... make contact with each other.
Eh, what is it?
Have our things together... do you really think I can say something like that?!
Tougo's big thing... It smells so indecent.
But, I love it.
Se... senpai!
Senpai is giving me a blowjob.
Tougo's penis tastes so indecent,
but it's really tasty for me.
Somehow I like it the way it is.
It feels good, senpai.
I remember I should do something like this,
like in the video from my father...
Senpai's hips are actually in front of me?
Suzaku-senpai's pussy is inside of this swimsuit.
Tougo's thing is getting big.
This is the first time someone touched me down there.
It's drenched a lot in there, can I look at it?
If you'd like.
This is senpai's pussy?
It's embarrassing if you keep looking at it.
Senpai!
I'm sorry, senpai.
Amazing, a lot of it came out.
Tougo's sperm.
Seiryuu's penis isn't getting smaller at all.
If it doesn't come out inside of me,
I won't get pregnant.
Suzaku-senpai, are you sure about this?
Seiryuu Tougo, would you like to do it with me?
If I'm looking at Suzaku-senpai's face like this,
there's no way I could resist it this time.
No, Seiryuu's penis is taking away my virginity.
Suzaku-senpai...
Tougo...
I'm being fucked by Suzaku-senpai.
I'm fucking Seiryuu Tougo.
It hurts.
But I must bear with it, while I'm making bodily contact with Tougo.
Even though I feel so much pain... it's strange... it feels so weird to me.
My stomach is... My womb feels hot...
Inside of me feels good...
It's good!
It feels good inside of me!
Good...
Good... It feels so hot inside of me...
Inside... Please keep moving inside of me!
More... more of it!
Tougo keep moving it!
Please keep stirring me up with your penis!
Please make me pregnant!
Senpai, even if you say something like that... I can't.
Keep moving it... deep in my stomach.
Senpai's pussy is around my penis...
Penis? Pussy? Now I understand all of this...
Tougo's penis... keep moving it inside of me!
Suzaku-senpai is saying "penis" and "down there" too much.
No! senpai, I'm gonna cum!
Sperm... let it out... let it out inside of me...
Make me pregnant!
Make me... make me pregnant!!
Ukh!
Coming out!
It's ejaculating...
Inside of me... Tougo's sperm is inside of me...
It's hot
My stomach feels warm...
I finally became one with Tougo. Since that time,
I've always thought of Seiryuu Tougo...
You fool, what do you mean you did something like that?!
You have to be the heiress of the Suzaku family as a descendant of the four guardians!
No! I don't want to!
I hate you, father!
Honey, she's still 5 years old.
Shut up!
I often ran away from home, when I was sick
of all my father's lectures about that kind of thing.
What are you doing in here alone?
I lost my way, what about you?
I'm training myself.
Hey, do you know the way to go to the city?
Sure, I'll take you there.
So I was saved by that young boy back there.
I just recently learned that he's the heir of Seiryuu's family.
Akiha-chan.
Three coffees are ready to be delivered.
Yes!
As I thought, Akiha-chan is number one!
I just can't stand her lovely appearance.
Tougo...
You're not coming here today?
I'm really having sex with Suzaku-senpai.
There's a lot of Seiryuu's genes in me right now.
I can get pregnant soon with this .
No!!!
No! I hate spiders!! I hate bugs!!!
Hey... hey... Moemi, do you know where Tougo is?
I just saw Seiryuu-kun going into in the pool area.
Pool?
Eh, but the swimming club isn't supposed to be training today, right?
Is it possible...
You're so cruel, senpai...
Senpai, to make the vow official... We should have two children,
and each of them should protect our family's heritage, right?
That's right, then I'll be your wife for eternity.
But, It's my decision to choose between
Suzaku-senpai and Byakko Akiha, right?
What?
Did you plan to throw me away after we made a vow back there?!
No, that's wasn't what I was asking you just now.
I just want to think this over after all that's happened today.
I understand, so it was my fault for forcing you like that.
Until you accept me, I'm going to do everything you said.
I can see all the way inside of senpai's swimsuit.
That Suzaku-senpai is so lovely...
What should I do then?
I'll do everything, okay!
Then, I want you to take off your swimsuit.
In... In here?
That's right, in this place.
In the place where you trained with everyone,
in this spacious pool.
I understand.
Oh, It's the naked body of Suzaku-senpai.
Is it okay with you, Tougo?
Yes... you're really beautiful, senpai.
I want you to sit at the starting line and spread your legs wide.
Then spread your pussy open and beg for it.
Beg?
You want to get pregnant, right?
Do you want me to say things about sex and my pussy, right?
Not talking about anything else, right?
Either way, you have to talk about pussy.
Well then.
Seiryuu Tougo, I want you to make a child with my pussy.
It's embarrassing, Tougo.
It's a bit different though...
The sperm is coming out again!
Suzaku-senpai, If you want me to release it inside of you again
Please say it clearly this time.
Tougo, I want you to put your penis inside of me
and release your sperm in me.
Please get me pregnant!
That's right, that's the way to ask about it!
Then, why don't we practice at the starting line this time.
In lane number 5, is Suzaku Natsuhime-san!
Set.
Start!
Suzaku Senpai! Ukh! It's getting tighter than before!
Tougo, in a place like this-
That's because in a place like this~~
I feel something strange again! It's intense!
I can feel you deep inside of me again!
We're having sex in the pool where you train in everyday.
Good, I can feel it already!
It's too much for me!
Why do I feel good from being fucked in this pool?
I'm being fucked in this spacious pool,
it feels strange, but I feel so good!
Why can I feel so good like this?!
That's-
Here! Suzaku-senpai.
Not that intense!
You're so cute!
In there-
Cute? Don't say something weird like that, Tougo!
That's the first time someone said something like that to me.
It's embarrassing for me, but I feel so happy.
Tougo, It's great!
Your penis feels good! Deep... deep inside me...
Senpai! Senpai's pussy,
It's getting tight! Tighter.
It's good... it's good!
Tougo, It's good! I can feel it!
Senpai! It's training! Let's circle around the pool.
Eh, what?
Come on, move your hands.
Let's move until we're at those windows.
That's-
No, I'm gonna be seen.
Senpai, look... in front of you.
There's one of your kouhai.
No, It's embarrassing!
No, stop it! They're going to see us!
It's fine! senpai! They won't see it.
You know how this magic mirror works, right?
But, with with us being this close-
They're absolutely going to hear my voice!
No, please stop it!
They're going to notice!
There, why don't you show them.
The way that the academy's heroine, Suzaku-senpai's
pussy is getting fucked from here.
No, stop it!
Do you feel embarrassed enough, senpai...
Tougo... It's amazing... your penis...
It feels good, much more intense than before!
Senpai, I want to fuck you more.
Me too... I want you to fuck me even more.
I want to feel more of it!
Ukh, Senpai... I'm gonna cum soon.
Let it out! I want you to fill my womb with Seiryuu's sperm!
Ukh, It's coming out~~
There's a lot of hot stuff coming inside!!
What... what is that?!
Tougo...
Akiha?!
I came here, because I'm worried about you.
What the hell are you doing in here, Tougo?!
This is... It isn't-
You're late coming here, Akiha!
It's already over in here.
I've already made a vow with Seiryuu back there.
It's time for you to give up.
T-Tougo is going get married to me!
Senpai can just be a mother and not get married!!
He... hey-
Not a chance, you're gonna be the one who's not getting married.
Why don't you try to get pregnant by drinking
what's left of Tougo's sperm?!
Wait!!!
Kitami?!
Kitami, don't you dare interfere with our battle in here!
Let me join the battle as well!!!
What do you mean?! It doesn't have anything to do with you!!
Stay away, get out of here!
No way, I like Tougo-kun too!!!
I can't let you trick Tougo with something like that you know!
But, I'm gonna be his wife for-su-re.
What did you say?!
Huh, such a foolish act! Do you think a man can be a wife?
I can be a girl when the time comes!
Besides, we can make an artificial child.
Isn't that right, Tougo-kun?
Then again, Suzaku-senpai. I'm sure you're aware that there's not
gonna be a battle before the day at the art museum.
If you break that rule, you can't enter the competition.
I can't do anything, since it's the rules.
Akiha, we should delay our battle until that day.
That's fine with me, senpai.
I won't hold back in that battle either.
No, the two of you are getting fired up!
I thought... I heard something scary earlier...
What's going to happen to me from now on?
Natsu-chan was making the first move in this competition, right?
I haven't been beaten yet! Next time will be my turn to get all of it.
By doing that... or even something like that.
No way, I'm saying a lot embarrassing things today!
You bitch, Tougo already made a vow with me!
Do you plan to steal him from me?! You big breasted woman!
You're not even married to him yet, so I'm not stealing him from you.
No, you can't forget me in all of that!
Tougo-kun's penis is mine af-ter-all.
Even I would take all of his penis, even the balls.
What do you mean you're going to take his balls?!
Aki-chan, you're acting strange right now.
The acting would be in the next episode.
I'm not going to pull any tricks in it.
For you there, see you again!
Bye-bye!