Oh, what a pity...
Although it is the fate of all flowers is to fall eventually...
...l'd rather take their lives with my own hands...
Gohei.
Excuse me, Madam...
lt's looking beautiful tonight as usual.
Somebody!
H-Help...
Where am l?
What?
ls that me?
Who is it?
Tomomi?
Why is he here?
He is the one who...
A face of a...
...woman...
No!
Get the hell out here!
Wow, okay...
Calm down.
Go away, right now!
This is beyond crazy.
How nice to be young...
You're the one from last night...
Mother!
He did...
Men are like that sometimes, it's natural.
He was infatuated by you.
Only a maiden of the Kuraki's has the privilege to choose a devoted husband.
Do you realize you are the one who chose him?
l am the one?
How can l choose a man that l just met yesterday?
Besides, l hate guys who talk bluntly...
l can't stand his sloppy clothes...
...and the way he thinks he deserves to touch me!
...and he's an older guy, it's out of the question!
His black eyes, big hands, broad shoulders, and his sleepy face...
l hate everything!
l am...
...not going to...
...forgive that bastard!
What took you so long, Tomom--
At last...
Someone could have come to pick me up...
Please wait, Miss Suzuna!
Miss Suzuna!
The Madam really didn't tell you anything about this?
lf l had known that Tomomi was taking care of that bastard...
...l would have done something!
lsn't the view of the camellias amazing from here?
Oh, Sir, your face...
Oh, no, well...
l don't think you have a fever.
Well, l'm a little inexperienced, so l got slapped.
Oh, you are the same as me, then.
Do you have to do anything l ask?
Hayama-san!
You are not supposed to touch a lady's body without permission!
l-l...
l don't recall being introduced...
Who are you?
Well, Azuma-kun is Ms. Suzuna's cousin...
Tomomi...
Y-Yes, sir?
Hayama-san!
Stop acting like the master of the house!
l'll get you kicked out soon enough!
For now, you're just a visitor!
Well, l...
W-Wait!
No, don't touch me!
l'm sorry about last night...
l-l mean it, l apologize.
Whatever!
Well, l mean...
...you were my first woman...
So l...
That hurt!
That was my first, too!
lt's you, Sawaguchi...
l guess its about time that you paid, for all those women's hearts you've broken.
lncluding mine...
The fragrance of camellia is way too strong here.
Be careful not to be seduced.
lf that was his pick up line, it's a horrible one!
Not again...
Oh no...
You were my first woman...
No!
Give me a break!
Why is he...
Are you talking about the master?
l am sorry, l knocked, but you didn't answer...
l don't remember calling for you.
Her name is Chikako Sawaguchi, age and background are unknown...
She has been lecturing at the University your husband attends for two years now.
Psychology is her field.
Psychology, is it?
She looks like one of those women...
The suspicious...
Sayaka!
Besides, she was wearing Japanese white apricot incense.
That's a little unexpected approach, don't you think?
Which means we'll need to counteract it with a fleshed out plan...
How about this one?
This adult fragrance might create an exciting contrast for you, Miss.
Or if we want to emphasize your baby face--
Enough with that, just tell me!
ls this going to be a long stay?
Oh, you are already jealous!
l am not talking about her, l'm talking about Koichi Hayama!
Oh, your husband?
Your husband is...
Koichi-san is going to attend the Expecting Moon Ceremony...
...as the new head of the Kuraki family.
This is grandmother's decision.
No objection is accepted.
That's what the madam said.
So you mean he's going be here for a month?
Well, well, she seems to hate you quite a bit.
Women are hard to deal with.
By the way, what are you here for?
l felt like someone is calling me...
You mean l did?
l see, you've started to see the woman's face.
Yes, right after l arrived here.
So l guess you can't go against your destiny, huh?
Owning to my fate, l only have one regret.
Because, l've realized that you are more beautiful than l imagined...
l just hadn't noticed your femininity underneath your cool attitude.
My...
Hayama, don't disappoint me...
What?
Huh?
This scent...
lt is been said that Japanese White apricot incense keeps away evil sprits.
lt keeps away evil spirits?
l wonder what's taking Miss Suzuna so long...
Huh?
l thought she was waiting...
What are you doing?
Sayaka!
l'm sorry, l wasn't peeping!
l was just passing by...
l am not lying!
l've been staying in a village near here on location...
Please trust me!
Sayaka!
Miss Suzuna...
l am flattered, but...
l'm not really interested in woman.
Oh...
Miss Suzuna!
Something is strange about her...
Damn, security is tight.
What are you doing?
Look.
Tomomi?
...and that bastard.
What are you doing?
Well they are beautiful, so l just...
S-Sir?
Sir, if you are not feeling well...
...l can arrange a room for you.
That'll be nice, if you come with me...
lf that is what you want, sir...
Hey!
How can you call yourself the wife of Hayama...
...if you get upset at every little thing like this.
l'm not upset!
Remember, Hayama's future is in your hands, Suzuna Kuraki.
What?
You should take a good look at him.
No, sir...
That's how Hayama has been...
This is a joke, but it's also reality...
Although he hasn't revealed his true nature yet...
Why are you doing this?
That's because you are begging me.
Why don't you say it out loud?
No...
No, l cant...
Please, be tender...
Well, well...
ls something wrong?
No, these could drive a man crazy.
How about you, sir?
l'm going crazy too, of course.
Now l know why he spent so much time on my breasts...
lf Miss Suzuna found out...
We should give her a show...
What strong negative energy she possesses...
That is the maiden of the Kuraki family...
Her name is listed in the book of the dead.
To hell with that bastard!
W-Why...
Why am l...
Oh, you are already jealous!
No, l am not!
Miss Suzuna!
Uncle Harukawa!
l was looking for my granddaughter, and l found her in the hall...
lt doesn't look like something is wrong with her, perhaps it's a mental problem...
l am Ruri Yamato, l play the role of Sayaka Kurihara...
Uncle Harukawa, what is going--
Miss Suzuna!
Sayaka, are you okay?
Yes, l am fine.
l will go look for Uncle Harukawa.
You don't need to worry about me...
H-Hey, no...
This isn't easy to resist, is it, Miss Suzuna?
No...
How about down here...
Do you know?
Tomomi has an incredible body.
Her waist is so tiny and has no excess of fat at all...
But her breasts are huge, and very, very soft.
But l personally think that you are way more attractive than her, Miss Suzuna.
See how cute you are?
Does it feel good, Miss Suzuna?
No...
Do you want me to stop?
ls it okay or not?
Don't stop...
As a Maiden of the Kuraki, you should be ashamed of your behavior.
You may not believe me, but l am very strict when it comes to discipline.
Sayaka...
No!
Stop it!
No, no!
l will teach you the basics of how to be a lady, Miss Suzuna.
Deeper and deeper l dive...
Deeper and deeper l wonder...
Was l always this deep?
And now, l am here...
Because you call me.
The Third Night, Peony.
On sale in the fall of 2003.