It hasn't been decided that they've disappeared yet,
but this is the first time that my father and the others left the house at the same time.
I'm worried...
Kannazuki Sayaka
So we beat the boats against the current,
borne back, senselessly, into the past.
That's why we keep going forward.
Like a boat going out to the rough sea, and as being pushed back towards the past...?
Jeez, you're spacing out again!
Making me translate everything isn't fair!
Selected as a committee
chairman with fantastic grades
Huh?
She is.... my beloved girlfriend
Did something happen, Sayaka?
Perhaps it's something to do with your boyfriend?
Jeez, it's about work!
Haven't I texted you about it?
Lies! I know something is up!
You've gotten so mature!
Flattering me won't make me show you my homework.
You noticed...
I'm sorry, today...
It wasn't like telling you about it would have solved the problem...
I can't keep being so pessimistic, can I?
Good night, I'll see you tomorrow.
It was a few days later that I heard that she got a part time job.
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Ryoujoku Famiresu Choukyou Menu
Stand! Bow!
I'll come pick you up, so
let's go home together.
No way!
You've at least kissed, right?
Yeah, we have...
Did you French kiss?
Uh, um...
No way! Seriously?
Isn't that enough? We're finished for today.
What?!
I was asked if I was leading him on.
Guys are so simple minded.
It's disgusting.
Ah, don't worry about it.
You know that I dislike easygoing guys like him.
I strictly decline!
T-Then I'll see you later.
I'm so surprised! I didn't know Sayaka did...
Speak of the devil, isn't that him?
He looks pretty timid, but...
He's actually quite perverted! They were deep kissing, right?
I know!
Hello? This is the Kanzaki residence.
Nee-san? She's always working at this time of night...
Yes! I'll tell her you called.
You again? What do you want?
No...
Sorry, were you working, brother?
Silly, then I wouldn't be angry.
I'm just with a girl at the moment.
Sorry, we'll talk later then.
What is it? Just tell me.
L-Later is fine!
Is it about your girlfriend?
What's her name... was it Sayaka-chan?
Uh, no...
N-No!
It's fine, really! I'll call you later.
Your body has become so sensitive.
One month earlier
Welcome!
P-Please stop!
Huh? You don't like it?
My girlfriend liked it when I did this.
Then, d-do these kinds of things to her instead!
She left last week,
so can you be my new girlfriend?
I-I'm in a relationship with your brother-!
You must notice people's gazes.
You're over-servicing.
Are you ready to order?
This is great! Is showing your panties part of your service?
No-!
It's a pain if you're so self-conscious.
If he says it like that, any girl would feel uncomfortable!
Not again.
This is a place where we entertain guys by embarrassing the girls, you know.
No... I can't do this! I can't...
Would you rather be fired?
For your parents' sake too...
If you can overcome your shyness, you can keep working here.
Now, do it like I told you.
Thank you very much!
It's nothing when you're used to not wearing one, right?
Please have a seat here.
Some people insist on it, so...
Don't be so conceited!
Hey, we're here.
Thank you very much...
Nee-san? Your boyfriend came to give you your birthday present. I'll leave it on your desk.
I think he's waiting for your call. Be sure to call him back!
N-No! Why?
He'll hear you! My brother's room is next door...
W-What?
I brought you here, since you said you wanted to sleep.
Sleep-deprived? Is my brother too much for you?
No-!
Don't-!
S-Stop it already...
I'll have to give you a present too.
N-No! Stop it!
W-What? N-No!
N-No...!
Not there-!
No... don't...!
Don't! It's dirty there...
No way... No way...!
Sayaka, happy birthday.
I gave my present to you to your sister.
I hope you like it.
Don't hesitate to call me later on.
Bye.
I'll train you into someone who can perform services from the "special menu."
A few days later
How was my present?
T-This is a sausage wrap for you.
With this special menu, you can make a lot more money, right?
You coward...
But, I'm not going to keep you restrained by those photos forever.
I was actually just at an auction before.
An auction?
We usually don't allow employees to participate...
But, since you're my brothers girlfriend,
I somehow convinced them.
About your virginity.
You're about to suck me in...
No, no!
It's hot...
No-!
Not that-!
Not to my ear-!
Please... don't...
No-!
Please don't put the tip in!
Can you feel it?
No... Pull it out... Pull it out!
You can't feel it unless I put it in deeper?
N-No... No!
Pull it out!
If you make me cum.
Can I let it out?
No...
You could feel better if you wanted to.
I... I never will!
But you're squeezing me.
You're not admitting that it feels good!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Say it!
N-No, no! I don't...
It's so deep!
Did I reach the point where it feels good?
Go on, admit it!
I-It's... It's good!
It feels good!
You're admitting it now, huh?
Yes, yes it does!
It feels good deep inside of me!
So good-!
Let me hear it!
It feels good!
It feels really good!
No more, stop it!
Take it out-!
Don't you mean: "Let it out?"
Stop it...
Please! this is too much-!
Say "Let it out!"
No!!
So hot-! Please don't get so big!
No, no! Please don't get any bigger!
No! It's reaching my deepest spots-!
Let it out...
L-Let it out!
I just want it to end quickly, that's all!
Something's coming-!
Cum... Cum inside Sayaka!
Your semen... Let it all out!
So much...
Amazing... So much...
My insides are full of your hot semen...
What a troublesome girl...
Once you start, you don't stop easily, do you Sayaka?
I just want it to end quickly!
I'm allowed to let it out in your mouth, right?
Okay, I'm gonna let it out.
No!
We can't finish up otherwise!
Fine, let it out inside my mouth...
Huh? What?
Let it out...
Let it out inside me!
What?
Oh, hey... Why are you calling me at this hour?
I... I was talking to my sister...
Did you hear something?
E-Everyone's just thinking about it too much...
I haven't changed one bit...
No... It's not...
I'm fine! My sister is just up to some mischief...
I'm going to tell her off, so could you hold on?
Engaged
Hold
Stop teasing me!
Even though you're doing it to him?
Give him a break! He's my brother after all...
If you look at my face, I'll get too embarrassed, so...
Do it from behind.
No, not yet! I'm cumming!
Come?
What's coming?
U-Uh, my friend said they'll call soon...
It's come! The one I've been waiting for has come!
S-So, I'm hanging up, okay?
Sayaka? Sayaka?!
I've already told you the ladies etiquette!
Say it when you're cumming!
No! I can't say it!
It's too embarrassing! I can't say it
Even though you're an embarrassing woman!
I-I can't hold it in!
I-I'm, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum-!