Mmm! It tastes as good as usual, Hiko-chan!
Thanks for giving it out for free every year!
Our stall hasn't fallen so far as to take money from Wataru or Yuuho.
Your tight pussy is the best I've ever had!
I'm gonna cum!
Your semen is coming out-!
Thrust harder!
Your ass, it's clinging on to my dick!
I'm cumming again!
It's exploding inside my butt-!
Your tongue work is also top class!
Are you gonna cum again?
Yeah, I can keep going!
I wanna see the fireworks!
Sure thing! Once we're done here, I'll take you there!
Mizuki, what's wrong?
Jin, Tazai-san's acting strangely...
He's always strange.
Today he's acting a lot stranger!
He was doing it with that girl he picked up at Suzugaryou,
but he's totally gone today!
A sex mugger, huh?
What are they doing now?
They said they were off to see the shrine's fireworks, and then they both left.
Understood.
I've lost my damn protective charm...
uka
Kansen
Shikkaku presents
We're at the Mankitsu Alcalia, on the 5th floor of the Laser building in Shibuya.
There are eight survivors including me.
We're also running low on supplies.
If you, the rescue team is coming, please find us quickly.
Please help us.
It's been ten days, huh?
Your cock tastes great, Ayase-kun!
Yoshino-san! Please stop doing that!
C'mon, spurt your semen inside my pussy!
D-Don't do it!
It's already gone in!
I-If you do that, I'll-!
You'll cum? You're gonna cum already?
What's with Yoshino-san's eyes?
Ayase-kun! It feels great!
It feels so good!
Is this... Unknown Level 4?
Maruko-senpai!
Onii-chan!
Wataru!
Ren! Kousuke! Yuuho!
Let's escape through here.
This way!
Wataru!
To think that the school is connected to such a place...
Let's keep going along the Shibuya river and escape to the sea.
We took turns sleeping and ate.
We escaped through the tunnels.
I heard that the Unknown Level 4 virus went extinct in the northeast four years ago...
The eradication of the infected is close to impossible.
The virus has probably been in hibernation for the past four years.
But everyone took the vaccine...
The virus must have evolved in the past four years. The vaccine isn't effective any longer.
In any case, I wish we had some proper weapons...
In Hiko-chan's gang safehouse...
We found some weapons.
I never thought the day would come where I'd be holding a gun.
We've got grenades, too.
All that's left is food, huh?
After that, we arrived to our regular restaurant.
Oh, it's been a while since I've seen such a young cock.
Ama-san!
Ma-Maruko-senpai?!
Get ahold of yourselves!
No matter who they are, don't show mercy to the infected!
What was that just now?
What's wrong?
E-Everyone?!
No one move!
Kousuke?
Mizuki? You were still hanging out with this lot?
Come over here!
Um, everyone-!
Let's stop pointing guns at each other and calm down.
Then we can have something to eat, and take a shower...
I'm sure we're all hungry, and we all want to rinse off the sweat, right?
What the hell are you talking about?!
Hmph, you're right.
A-Aniki?
Shige, put yours away too.
Fine...
You're a pretty interesting guy to suggest meals and showers in this situation...
So, when are you gonna put your gun down?
Huh? Oh.
Along with Jin-san, Mizuki and Shige-san joining us to make a total of eight,
we finally had a proper meal which we haven't had for days.
Yuuho-chan, it's delicious!
As expected of the only daughter of the Kannagiken family.
You too, Maruko-senpai. Don't avoid the octopus and eat up!
Y-Yeah...
Escaping through the tunnels to the sea?
Then Shibarura, Takeshiba or Ouui are our options?
Yeah, let's figure out our escape route tomorrow.
What?!
This is bad...
All the major cites from north to south have been destroyed, huh?
Apparently there's a temporary government on Miyake Island.
I guess going out to the ocean is the best idea.
The problem is time.
The United Nation forces seem to be revising a rescue operation in Japan.
Is this-?
It's the news that was broadcast while we were underground.
This is like a battleground!
There's so many people, they can't be stopped!
A woman!
It's a pussy!
N-No! No!!
Thank you.
What?
If you weren't around, I think Mizuki would have suffered a similar fate.
You have my thanks.
Kousuke...
If that's what you think, then never let go of her again.
If I become infected, I wonder who I'll go for?
It'll probably be Onii-chan.
I'm wet already...
Onii-chan would despise such a lewd girl!
Can you see that, Onii-chan? My nipples are getting hard!
No, not there!
Onii-chan! You can't hold back, can you?
You want to put it inside me, don't you?
D-Do it harder!
I-I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
O-Onii-chan, lets cum together!
It's a shame to waste such a nice day.
Yeah, agreed. It makes me want to go somewhere to play.
We're gonna go to the beach soon!
Huh? More of them.
Hey! We're going back now!
A survivor? No, she's infected...
Hey, Wataru. Hurry up.
Y-Yeah...
Only cans and instant curry for dinner?
We can only get preserved foods...
Tsk, it can't be helped then...
We should get ready soon.
Yeah, let's leave in two to three days.
I guess we won't be coming returning to this town again.
We're at the Mankitsu Alcalia, on the 5th floor of the Laser building in Shibuya.
Including me, there are eight survivors.
If you, the rescue team is coming, please find us quickly.
Please help us.
It's been ten days, huh?
Kousuke, thanks for before.
Huh?
I was touched when you thanked Jin for saving me.
Y-Yeah...
Even though I'm the one who parted with you guys...
But... we were able to meet again.
I'm very glad.
Kousuke-!
Your breasts taste great, Mizuki...
Give it to me too!
It's incredible, Mizuki!
Your cock is so cute Kousuke! It's quivering!
I'm about to cum...
Then make me feel good too!
Kousuke, it's so hot!
My juices are flooding out!
I've never felt like this!
Kousuke, hug me! Cling to me!
I won't let you go! Until death comes, we won't part!
I'm so happy!
Kousuke, lets cum together!
No... I'm cumming!
This is a message from the United Nations.
Starting at noon tomorrow, we will be releasing toxic gas into all 23 wards of Tokyo.
Since it is very dangerous, please move out of all 23 wards as soon as possible.
I repeat, this is a message from the United Nations...
Noon tomorrow?!
This is so sudden!
We probably don't have time to escape to the sea...
They intend to kill the infected as well as the survivors?
No way...
Jin! Do you have a mobile phone with you?
I lost mine.
Yeah.
Please, answer!
Yes?
Sesuka? Where are you now?
Ojou-sama?!
I'm at the Nishi-ku ward in Kanagawa Prefecture.
We're about to escape the Tokyo area via helicopter, but where are you?
Sesuka, I'll tell you all the details later.
Including me, there are eight others here in Shibuya.
Please send over a helicopter.
Understood. Please wait ten minutes. I'll call back.
Please.
We may be able to do something about this.
The evac helicopter will be here around noon tomorrow.
The same time as the gas attack?
If we remain here, the gas will get us too.
Let's move to the rooftop helipad on the Celeste Tower.
What should we do about the infected on the way?
We'll have to do our best to remove them.
If so, we should wait till dawn.
Everyone! Let's check our weapons while we can.
It looks like there are others, too.
I hope they can all escape by noon tomorrow.
Us as well.
I think we have to live through this.
We have to live for those who we've killed.
If you hadn't saved me that time, I probably wouldn't be alive...
Thank you.
Thank you as well.
Huh?
I think that I've been able to make it this far because of you.
Wataru...
Yuuho...
You're very beautiful, Yuuho...
It's embarrassing!
No... No-!
N-Not there! I-It feels too good!
I'll lose it if you do it that roughly-!
Wa-Wataru, I'll do it to you, too...
You're getting hot here, Wataru.
I don't think I can hold back...
Me neither.
Put it in, Wataru.
A-Are you okay?
Y-Yeah, go ahead and move.
O-Okay.
Yuuho, t-this feels great!
It feels good for me too!
Your cock is entering me!
You're tightening around me, Yuuho.
I-I can't stop thrusting my hips!
Yuuho! I-I'm gonna-!
Yuuho, I love you, I love you!
Me too, I love you too!
I c-can't hold back-!
Let it, let it out, Wataru! Pour it inside me-!
Yuuho, Yuuho-!
It's coming out, your semen is pouring inside me...
I-It's hot-!
Yuuho, let's live through this.
Yeah.
Let's live together forever.
Okay, let's go.
They're coming!
Jin, Wataru, you guys go ahead.
Huh? Kousuke...
Don't wait too long.
What are you doing staying here?
You said that you wouldn't let go of me again!
Stick close, then.
Sure!
Alright.
The power to the elevators have been cut.
This should close off most of the infected.
All we do now is climb the stairs.
Kousuke! We've closed the shutters and elevators, let's meet up via the stairs!
That's great, uh we might be a bit late, so you guys go ahead.
Huh?
Mizuki and I will come up later.
Understood.
Kousuke...
Yeah, I'm sorry to make you worry.
See ya.
Sorry to get you involved...
Huh? I'm just happy that I'm with you.
Me too, I'm happy that you're with me.
We'll be together forever.
Yeah...
We'll be together forever...
This is the top floor.
We just have to leave from the rooftop helipad now...
We're saved, aren't we?
Yeah-
Everyone, hold it right there!
Shigeyoshi! What are you doing?!
We're gonna hide from the gas here.
What?!
Then we're gonna make our kingdom after the infected have died!
Isn't that a good idea?
What are you talking about?
Do it yourself!
Don't move!
Y-You idiot...
Jin-!
I-I can get serious when I have to!
He's bleeding too much.
Things has been screwing up ever since I lost that protective charm...
Protective charm?
Yeah... All it was was a blue marble strapped to the cell phone I gave you...
I freakin' lost it...
What a coincidence, my protective charm is also a blue marble.
A boy gave it to me when I went to the Hachiman shrine on my visit to see my mother's home town.
Oh really... You were that girl at the Homura general store...
Things like this make life interesting.
I thought I had already gotten everything I wanted, but...
I never had a true childhood friend...
I'm here for you!
Thanks, Marie...
Don't lose your protective charm...
Sure.
Goodnight, Jin.
Let go of Yuuho!
Don't come any closer!
Wataru!
Onii-chan?!
The ones who stand up to me will be killed!
Ouch!!
You bastard! How dare you shoot Wataru-!
You bitch, let go of me!
Tsk, I'm gonna kick your ass!
You shouldn't bully the people who're trying to protect others!
Bring it on-!
H-Help...!
The gas attack is...
Where's our rescue helicopter?
Didn't they make it?
Ojou-sama!!
Sesuka!
Yuu-tan...
Katou-kun...
Everyone, so this is where you were...
This time, bring me with you.
I'm back, Yuu-tan...
I've always hated this busy, loud, dirty, and smoggy city.
I've always wished that I could live elsewhere.
But now I think that this town is the place I wanted to escape to.
I want to one day return to this place.
Back to this city... The place where we were born, grew up, loved, and hated.
Yeah...