The life of the first Lemon Angel is in that man's hands...
And when it's complete, I'll destroy him.
That...
That?
That is... my revenge!
Miki-senpai...
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Hokano dareka ga iya
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Please accept the real me.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
In the middle of the night
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Suki wa aru no kana?
Retrieve the password and login...
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
and get to the heart of things.
kakushin ni furetai
The virus of love
Koi wo shiteru Virus
out of my control
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me)
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Hokano dareka ga iya
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
New Moon
H-Hey, wait a minute!
Was it you who did that with the program?
And you didn't tell me anything!
Because it didn't do anything that warned you?
It means... it means that from the start...
Miki-senpai...
Hey, what does this mean?
Why are you quiet?!
You pretended to be our friend, but you truly intended to get revenge from the beginning?
So that means that you didn't care about Lemon Angel?!
What's with that attitude?!
Say something!
Saya-chan!
Saya!
Nice act...
Manipulation was the only thing you were concerned about!
All the effort you supposedly placed upon the members here...
Those that have also left...
All that intense training...!
All the effort we put into our debut!
Saya...
I understand that Himuro is a bad guy.
But you, an important person to us...
Saya...
...calm down!
I can't take it anymore. I'm out!
I won't allow you to leave!
What?!
I'm in charge!
Now that I've come this far, you'll have to continue with me 'til the end.
That man destroyed the affectionate heart and life of Yui like an electric overload.
Now it's our turn.
We'll crush that man's arrogance.
And reveal Yui's torment!
Tomo, you'll help, won't you?
Together, we'll remove that man from the music world.
Tomo...
You're wrong, Miki-san!
It's strange to think that all this time...
If your intention was to manipulate everyone as if they were objects...
Then you would be doing the same thing that Himuro-san did with Yui-senpai!
...You would be the same!
Please, go back to the old Miki-senpai!
Tomo!
Do what you think is best!
Saya!
Miru-chan, you shouldn't in this condition...
Miru-chan!
Why? Why don't they understand me?!
Like that man...?
No!
Why...
Yui...
Hey, Kogure.
Yes?
Since when did Lemon Angel turn solo?
First Lemon Angel / 5 days left until the festival!
The first Lemon Angel announced that they will return!!
Music! News from the artistic world / Surrounded! The lost members of the second Lemon Angel participated in secret training?!
Secret training, huh?
We won without a fight?
the dream meeting.
Hey, would you go back to being yourself for once?
Please.
You didn't start to hate singing, did you?
No ...
This festival is great, isn't it?
Everyone is anxious to be with you.
With some music, we'll create an even better beginning.
That's it!
That's what Yui and I wished.
The real...
Yui-senpai...
I don't think Miki made it on purpose.
ENOUGH!
I don't want to hear about Miki-san!
Tomo!
Music is a good thing!
It really is a good thing!
Yes, about that, we would like to cancel...
Yes, true, I apologize.
Second Lemon Angel started!
Hello!
Are you okay?
Long time no see!
Sister.
First, let's act!
Act?
Yes!
It's always been like that, no?
When we arrived, it was like that.
When you went to the audition, too.
Unless you act, nothing will change.
You're right..
And the festival?
I guess it'll be impossible.
That really annoys me!
You're a Lemon Angel, aren't you?
Aren't you carrying everyone's dreams who were cut?
If I have to keep looking at your face like this...
The doughnuts will be awful!
Carrying the... dreams?
I am, aren't I?
Why am I asking to be comforted?
A rare client.
Won't they introduce themselves?
Don't know. That's for them to decide.
It's repeating..
That manipulator and her awkward feelings.
Got no patience either.
Her brain is too small!
Obey, or you'll regret it.
You didn't get it.
And what?
Found it?
The sound that surpasses mine?
You're probably working alone, but...
Are you creating a suitable sound?
Better than you, at the moment.
At least I can present...
...because the program obeys the commands.
This is true.
The dolls don't complain.
There's a person that's becoming exactly like you.
She's testing who will fall.
And like that, all will be decided.
If this situation continues, victory is yours.
But if you understand...
Understand?
You realize in the end...
The perfect sound I wanted that time.
That, if you understand.
Oh?... the solo singers returned...
Please!
Even with just you guys, it's something.
Three days left...
We'll train until we can't!
Yes!
Brilliant as ever!
How's things going there?
Perfect, we can say.
That's scary!
With an easy simulation, even the body will look real.
This time...
...with Himuro-san's sound and my influence, we'll change...
...Musical history!
Right! We'll stop here!
You've worked hard up to this point.
Compensate the lack of people...
...with energy and vigor!
Believe in yourselves.
And those two?
So, will this...
There's no other way.
It's just us.
Miru-chan...
Maybe...
...it was here?
The club's person spoke.
Club?
Ah, Yuki-chan.
And the others?
In the stadium.
Except Miki-san
I see..
I'm sorry.
I... sang up until now for Yui-senpai.
But... I'm becoming confused.
Fuyumi got mad at me.
What?
That Ann didn't exist.
Said that what I learned from Ann wouldn't change.
Wouldn't change?
I learned Ann's music.
So... I could rise up.
Ann really existed at that time for me.
Now, she doesn't exist anymore.
But people that are waiting for us, do exist.
What?
Someone has to make the music get to them.
The promise.
What?
The promise we made before.
When we decided on the main singer.
I asked if we could surpass Ann.
And you said yes.
I believe.
If it's with you... no...
Without you, I can't surpass her.
Sing!
Without music, it's not possible to rise above.
Sing to someone!
Miru-chan...
Yes, when I listen to you sing, I feel happy.
What?
So, will you sing for me?
Yui and I've always thought...
We wanted to produce real music.
Only by listening to music, people would find their strength.
That incredible kind of music!
Real music?
One that could surpass everything else!
Yui-senpai.
Yui...
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
hajimete negatta hi kara
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
Please, if for only a chance
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Whe girls
onna no ko tachi wa
are in love...
koi wo suru ta bi ni
...They become lonely.
sabishigari ni naru
As they do.
itsudaatte
Girls in Love
Girls in love
Because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
Girls in Love
Girls in love
Hold me closer
Motto dakishimete yo
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Yume no naka made tsuretette
Next Time:
I feel that it took me a long time to understand what Yui-senpai wanted to tell me.
Really?
I'm happy that you worked hard, Tomo.
What? Really?
Yes, but you are clumsy at times.
Y-Yui-senpai!
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 13, "Never Give Up"
I'll always be watching you.
Right!