I wonder how much time has passed...
Luring me out with useless information...
That's a good expression; it turns me on!
Senpai! I can't hold back any longer!
M-Me neither!
I'm gonna cum!
Welcome back, Hiiragi.
Hey... Huh?
No, it's nothing.
Hey Hiiragi, do you have any plans this Sunday?
No, not particularly.
Then let's go to town!
Yeah, let's go, okay?
What is this, all of a sudden?
She's late.
Sorry to make you wait!
How do I look?
What do you mean?
If I dress like this, I look more like a girl, right?
Well, yes...
You are a girl after all.
What's with this all of sudden?
Just come along with me, okay?
It's a date!
Our
-----first
date!
Nozomi
Raika
It's just like... that happened long ago...
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Volume 2:
The End of
the Mad Feast
Volume 2:
The End of
the Mad Feast
Wa Wana
Now then.
We'll finish here.
Haruna-sensei, thanks for all your hard work.
Y-Yes, thank you too.
What's wrong? Aren't you going to go back?
Or did you want to do some private tutoring?
T-That's not it! I'll be off then!
Nothing has happened for the past week, but...
Ouch!
Saku-!
Hey, wait!
That's mean! Onee-chan, what's with this?
Didn't I tell you not to come here?
But...
Go home, right now!
C'mon, you're going home!
But lately you haven't been coming to see us anymore!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Sakuya.
But I can't let you stay here.
This... This school is...
It's too dangerous!
Please! I'll do whatever you say,
even if it's for just one more day, I want to spend time with you, Onee-chan!
All right then.
That's right, I want to protect her smile.
He committed suicide on this day,
but he had his lessons for the following days carefully planned in detail...
Misaki Yasuji didn't commit suicide.
Wait!
Sorry!
Tanemo-sensei, you didn't happen to see a student with a strange mask running around here, did you?
No, I haven't.
I see, thank you very much.
That rascal...
I can't rest easy until he's caught.
Oh Haruna-sensei, are you going home already?
Haruna-sensei, you know Misaki-sensei, the one who committed suicide last year right?
Eh? W-Why are you asking...?
Um, I was just wondering if I could have saved him since I'm the school nurse...
So, I was reading Misaki-sensei's teaching schedule, but...
But...?
But the more I look at it, the more it seems like he wasn't planning on committing suicide.
I-Is that so...
Um, what was Misaki-sensei like?
Eh? He was a very good teacher.
He was very dedicated to teaching, and he was very honest.
He's somewhat like Misawa Raika-kun...
Um, I'm sorry! I should get going.
Oh yes, sorry to have held you up.
It's fine. See you later, then.
This feeling, I just can't get enough of it!
Hey, hurry up! There are others waiting!
It seems like there are more of them every day...
No! That hurts, that hurts!
Hey, don't take it out!
Am I going to have to do it with everyone? It's impossible!
Why did I say something like that to her...?
Onii-chan wasn't exactly fond of heights...
Onii-chan took me to the carnival once. We rode the ferris wheel,
but he had his eyes closed the whole time.
Sorry! I didn't mean to randomly go off on a tangent like that.
It's fine.
Hey, Hiiragi...
Um...
Why didn't you tell anyone about me?
Do I have to have a reason?
No, it's not that, but...
I had an elder sister.
You had an elder sister?
I wonder how long ago it was...
She committed suicide.
Eh?
And for a long time, I couldn't move forward until I accepted it.
I was wondering if you were in a similar situation yourself, so...
Hiiragi...
If you want to find out the truth, keep looking for it until you're satisfied.
If it goes on, you're not going to be able to move forward, right?
Hey, Hiiragi...
Thanks.
Sure.
I didn't mean to tell her that, but...
Please help yourself!
It looks delicious! Thanks for the meal!
Have as much as you want!
Where is he going at this hour...?
Student council room
Tomorrow is finally the day.
Yeah. We're ready, right?
What's this? I can't hear them very well...
Yes, leave it to me.
This is the grand event for the student council.
Jeez, what a sly student council president you are.
I'm doing this to make sure that all of the students' wishes come true.
Yeah, I'm sure everyone will be ecstatic.
I'm sure respect for you will go up, too.
The whole school's grades are on the rise, as well.
It seems everyone tries harder when there is a delicious reward.
A reward?
Yeah, I guess you couldn't ask for a nicer reward in an all boys school.
Misawa, are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
I'm the one who told her to keep looking for the truth until she was satisfied...
She still came to this school despite changing her name and the way she looks.
She must have been prepared for some difficulties...
I know! Why didn't I realize something so simple?!
I won't cry... Like hell I will!
I said I wouldn't cry anymore!
What's up?
What are you doing?
I'm going out for a bit.
I may be out for some time, but don't worry.
S-Sure...
But where are you going at a time like this...?
Here.
I'll give this to you.
If you have that, you can go into the resource room as well as the rest of the school.
Hiiragi...
I've got a really bad feeling...
Should I go back?
Even though there's no school, why is the atmosphere so tense?
Someone really was here.
But it's not Maiko-sensei.
Like it matters, we've got to take them all.
Right.
Why...? I locked the door.
She's-!
Don't go on your own! We've gotta take her down all together!
Right!
Let me go!
Like hell I would! We've got you now!
What?!
No!!
Sakuya!
Let her go!
Let Sakuya free!
Please! Let Sakuya go!!
This is your fault, Haruna-sensei.
W-What did you say?
Taking your little sister into the teacher's dorm...
Onee-chan, I'm sorry!
I'm the one who was wrong!
I came to school, despite you telling me not to...
Sakuya! Let Sakuya go!
I don't care what happens to me, so-!
What heartwarming familial love you two have!
But we have to punish your sister for trespassing.
Don't do it! Let her go!
Please, not Sakuya!
Sakuya!
We'll give you a front row seat, Haruna-sensei.
Now then, how about we do some counseling from the front and behind?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Hey, you guys! Make sure you get a good look!
It's a rare opportunity to get to see a girl lose her virginity!
No!! Onee-chan!
Onee-chan!!
Oh my, oh my. What a cute pussy you have.
Let's have your sister and the others take a good look!
No, no!!
Now then, how about we do a countdown?
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
zero!
No!!
This is quite tight!
I-It's like my dick's gonna snap off!
A virgin pussy sure feels different!
How does it feel?
How does it feel to lose both of your virginities in front of your sister and others?
Now then, how about we cum inside you on your first time, like we did to your sister?
That's a good idea! Get ready!
Huh? N-No! No!
No!
N-No, it hurts!
No, no-!
O-Onee-chan, help me!
H-Help me!
N-No, no-!
Why are you refusing? Your nipples are already hard!
No, no!
This is amazing! When I squeeze her nipples, she tightens her butt!
N-No!
Yeah! Her pussy is tight, too!
Her breasts must be very sensitive.
No-!
How about we shoot our first load into her soon?
Yeah! With it this tight, I won't be able to hold back for much longer!
Right then, we're cumming!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
C'mon, c'mon!
No-!
I'm cumming!
No...!
I'm gonna cum-!
No, no-!
That was awesome!
Looks like they're all here.
Eh? Sakuya-chan?
And... eh? What is this?
Now then, how about we begin our main event?
Go ahead and use the prey, now do what you like with them!
This is your reward!
No, no!
This feels amazing, Sensei!
I wanted to do it with you, even if it was just once!
Me too, Sensei!
I've always fantasized about shoving it in your butt like this!
A-Amazing!
As expected of a recent virgin!
Your pussy really is number one, Sensei.
It's the best!
Onee-chan, help me!
Sakuya... I'm sorry, Sakuya...
Are you crying with joy at being able to get the cock you've been deprived of for weeks?
Everyone here is going to take turns, so enjoy it to your fullest!
Hey, how about this?
These breasts are great!
Sensei, take it in further! C'mon!
Sensei... Sensei-!
C'mon! Suck on it properly!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming-! I'm gonna cum now!
That's it!
I'm gonna cum in your mouth, Sensei!
Sensei, I'm cumming-!
She's not as energetic as before...
C'mon! Keep going!
That hurts! Please stop it-!
Does it really feel that good? How's this then?
See? That felt good.
C'mon! Your mouth isn't being used!
That expression! You're so arousing, Sensei!
Sensei-! I-I can't hold it in any longer-!
I'm cumming!
No!!
I'm cumming too!
Sensei... Sensei-!
Faster, do it faster!
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming-!
Looks like she's getting used to it now!
Well, she is Haruna-sensei's sister after all!
I came!
Eh? Then I will too!
Sensei-! I can't get enough!
Maiko-sensei-!
I'm cumming-!
Me too! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum soon!
I'm cumming-!
What a nice sight...
Jeez, what feeble male students we have!
Even though they said they would come right back after they'd recovered,
not a single one has come back!
You bastard...!
Oh, that's right.
I promised that I'd tell you something about Misaki Yasuji, didn't I?
I'll tell you, since it's not like you can do anything about it.
Misaki Yasuji...
was murdered.
He was only pushed off the top floor after he was murdered.
The one who killed him was, well...
It was me.
I've never seen such a hate-filled expression.
Y-You...
Do you hate me? What are you going to do about it?
N-Never...
I'll never forgive you!
Unfortunately, you can't do anything about it.
The only thing left for you is to become one of us, a guy's sex slave for the rest of your life!
Y-You...!
Can you cut it out with that annoying voice of yours?
Hiiragi?
Jo-Jounochii-sensei!
You bastard-! What are you...?!
Do you remember when a classmate of yours committed suicide while you were a student?
While I was a student?
W-What are you talking about?!
There was a classmate of yours who jumped from the top floor during graduation, wasn't there?
Graduation?
I'm... her brother.
S-Stop it-!
Have you ever stopped when you heard those words?
No matter what anyone said, you never listened.
As much as I want you to suffer forever,
be thankful you can die like this.
There was one more. They couldn't have gotten far...
Hiiragi!
Watch out!
Ta-Tanemo-sensei...
D-Damn it-!
H-Help me...!
Help me?
How many times have you heard that before?
Hiiragi...
Tsk, goddamn leftovers...
I'm, I'm not gonna die!
I'm going to grab hold of everything!
That's why I set Yasuji up from the beginning!
No way...!
I had my eye on Haruna-sensei!
But that darn Yasuji stole everything from me!
That's why I asked for help, help from a Senpai!
H-How dare you...!
I-If I'm gonna die, let's die together, Sensei!
Let's die together, Haruna-sensei!
O-Onee-chan...!
Right?! Haruna-
Y-You...!
Now!
I must live...
I promised...
I promised I'd live for him...
I mustn't die...
That's what Yasuji-san...
Onii-chan?
Yasuji-san said that I had to live.
Haruna-sensei...
I came to this school because I had information that the two people who made Onee-chan commit suicide were here.
And I have been investigating it ever since.
Eh?
They changed their names...
Who would have thought that I'd fall for such a simple trick?
I wanted you to have your revenge, but...
Sorry about that.
Sorry that you had to go through all of this...
I don't care if you forget about me.
Rather, you should forget this school, and this whole incident.
Hi-Hiiragi?
Good bye, then.
D-Don't-!
N-No!!