Maa-kun senpai is petite and cute,
so he's even popular among the girls.
When I learned for the first time that he liked me,
Excuse me... mind leaving her alone.
I was really happy.
But he's not that reliable as a man.
So I can't help but fantasize things like...
No... Kai...
The cock's going deep inside me...
Even though I know it's not right...
Your pussy's already getting hot.
I bet you masturbate a lot.
This is terri-
Try apologizing.
Get down on your knees and say, "I'm sorry."
As your security guard, I always had my eyes on you.
I already know everything, my lady.
That's not...
No...
What a lewd pussy you have here.
No, no!
That big thing might end up piercing my womb...
It's being sucked inside.
This is the worst!
So cruel...
Why did it have to be like this,
Stop crying like a baby!
Well, I guess I'm the one who's being rough on a kid here...
But who cares if I'm rough?
It's wrapping me tightly anyway.
No...
Any further and it will penetrate my womb...
Why are you acting like a victim?!
The incident that happened on this island is all your fault, you know.
The tone of your voice changed.
So this is where it feels good, huh?
No, no. That's not it! I don't want this!
No more...
Don't...!
Or maybe it's better to push deeper? You dirty bitch!
I don't want any of that!
It's intense!
Don't push inside!
N-No, I don't want this!
Senpai!
Maa-kun senpai!
If you keep on thrusting in me like that...
...I'll totally lose it.
You're loosening up quite nicely.
Oh look, is that your love juice flowing?
That's not.
Makoto,
I'm going to save you now.
You're going to escape with me.
And where do you plan to escape to?
This tanned woman sure loves to day dream.
Sakai...
This one also!
If you had escaped earlier, you wouldn't have been captured by me.
It would have been better that way...
I went ahead and borrowed Minami-senpai's stocking without asking, but...
it's an emergency, so it can't be helped.
Besides, she's already...
For me to wet myself at a place like that...
I want to die already...
I wonder if there was any odor left there...
Ah, I hate this...
Geez, designing traditional toilets at this age...
This is sexual harassment!
Hey, Nakazawa!
I already told you not to enter until I said so.
And how much more embarrassing can this get?
I can't possibly use this everyday!
Wh-Who are you?
So it's not your first time, huh?
I did it with Arai-kun from the Soccer club...
But it was only once... I...
I'll impregnate you, then.
No, no!
Stop!
Anything but...
Please, stop that!
I won't. Here, how's this?
I'm cumming!!
Making such a good expression when I pull it out...
Your princess here is a total pervert.
Please stop!
Anything more and...
I...
So you've gone crazy for my cock, huh?
Your mother's mind was also broken forcefully like that by your father,
and in the end she became nothing but his pet bitch.
The child that was born out of that man's nightly tainted sessions...
...was you.
You have that tainted blood.
By the way, this country seems to have been forsaken already.
The Unknown Level 4 has already spread everywhere...
There is no escape.
It means that not only this island, but also the entire country, will be blown to pieces.
Until that happens, let's just enjoy the party to the fullest...