Kouichi!
You're already so wet, Suzuna.
Don't say that. You're embarrassing me.
lt looks like you're ready...
No...
No, Kouichi! l don't want you to look at me like this.
What are you saying? l've seen you like this so many times.
But no matter how many times we do this, it's still embarrassing.
Then l'll make it easy for you.
Now you don't know where l'm looking, right?
Yeah, but...
Why does it feel so good?
Why?
You're one horny girl, Suzuna.
Well, well, looks like the little Miss already came.
l told you.
lf you can't see, you can focus on the sensation in your pussy, right?
More, l want more...
Deeper, please deeper...
l want it deeper...
Soon, when the Expecting Moon Ceremony is over, l will be...
l am glad that you made it tonight.
Well, it is my duty as the master of the house.
l'm very impressed since you were with Miss Suzuna only a short while ago.
lt's easy to see that you don't approve of a punk like me being your master.
l think no such thing.
Anyway, for tonight, l have prepared something very special...
...for the Master to enjoy.
Master! Please wake up!
Master, it's time to wake up!
Just a little longer...
No!
Master, Miss Suzuna is waiting for you.
You must bathe in the sun and purify your body with sacred water today.
Now, let us change you into these.
Oh my God, Master, you're naked!
What are you talking about? You're the ones...
l-l'm sorry.
lt's just that you have such a big manhood, so l just...
Don't get me wrong, this is...
lf you just told me so, l would've helped you with it.
What are you doing, Tomomi?
l would do anything to satisfy you, Master.
H-Hey...
lt's not fair! l can satisfy him too!
Stop it!
lt feels great!
Why are you wearing your glasses?
l'm as blind as a bat without these.
Come on! Take them off!
Those girls...
They're having fun.
Will you guys stop yapping?
Oh, come on now.
l'm sleepy.
You don't have to get so mad.
Just what part of this is the purification?
Please don't fight.
l'm not fighting.
Please just wait a little longer until the purification, Master.
Um...
Okay.
Tomomi, have your breasts gotten bigger again?
Yes, they have. This bathing suit is from last year, so it's tight on me.
l envy you.
l wish my breasts were a little bigger.
What are you two talking about?
These right here are big enough!
Right, Master?
Don't stare at my breasts like that!
Rain...
Should we get back to the house?
Not until Master and Miss Suzuna get doused with the water of purification.
This is the water of purification...
ls it over?
Yes, but you must not let your skin touch anyone else's after this.
Take your clothes off here and swim across the pond.
We'll be waiting on the other side.
Did you hear that?
Let's swim to the other side and get this over with.
Okay.
Please wait for me.
l'll go first.
Wait, l'll come with you.
Suzuna.
What's the matter? Hurry up!
Y-Yes.
Get out of there before you catch a cold.
Can't you be a little nicer to Miss Suzuna?
Please get out and come here, Miss Suzuna.
Will you please lift up your arms?
Like this?
What's this about?
lt's a little embarrassing...
This is to protect your purified body.
Let's go back to the house.
l don't know why but my body's getting hot.
Me too.
lt's not fair that l can't even touch you until the ceremony...
Miss Suzuna.
l have to ask you to wait in your room, Miss Suzuna.
The Master still has some preparations to make.
We will take you two to your rooms.
l guess we can't stay together for a while...
lt can't be helped, if it's a rule.
l guess so.
Well, l'm looking forward to seeing you at the ceremony.
l will accompany you to your room.
Master, please follow me.
Um, do you know why my body's getting hot?
That's because the wrap that's on your body has special medicine...
...so the ceremony will succeed.
M-Medicine?
l'm sorry, but l can't help you with anything today.
l'll come back the time for the ceremony comes.
l've been waiting for you.
So what's this ''preparation''?
H-Hey...
What the hell are you doing?
l thought you weren't supposed to touch me.
Miss Suzuna must not touch anyone until the ceremony, but...
...you must be in contact with women constantly until the ceremony.
Master, please let us take care of you.
With your stamina, l thought those two might not be enough to satisfy you...
...so l have brought three young women from the village.
l can't hold it anymore...
Oh no, l'm going to come...
l'm coming!
That was amazing...
l want more...
l'm coming!
Go ahead, please, shoot it in my mouth.
Thank you very much. lt was very thick and delicious.
Next. Your turn.
That's right. You're doing very well...
l'm coming!
Yes, Master!
How did you like it, Master?
lt was great.
Now line up the three women, l want to see their pussies.
What a great view...
Miss Suzuna, the time for the moon ceremony has come.
Everything is ready.
The crescent moon becomes full tonight.
Now we shall begin the Expecting Moon Ceremony.
The Expecting Moon Ceremony...
He seems ready...
And she is also ready for the ceremony.
Now l shall turn back time.
l'm coming!
Kouichi!
No, don't look, Suzuna!
Don't...
l'm okay, please take me!
Finally, l am going to be resurrected!
He has turned into nothing but a creature of lust...
...if he becomes one with the priestess, he will be purified and die...
How foolish...
l would like to help you, Mistress Yuriko.
What can you do to help me?
l will do whatever you wish me to do...
Suzuna, are you ready?
Kouichi, do you love me?
Yes, l love you, Suzuna.
l'm going to come...
What is going on?
The Kuraki mountains are resonating!
Kouichi, let's come together...
Suzuna, l'm coming!
l'm coming!
Suzuna, l love you.
Kouichi, please give me everything you have!
T-That's...
Kouichi...
Suzuna...
lt seems like this is the end...
What?
The Kurakis have the same fate as the moon...
lt waxes full, and then wanes.
Suzuna...
Kouichi...
Kouichi.
Suzuna.
l love you.
Good morning, Kouichi.
Wow, it snowed last night.
lt's all white!
Look, Kouichi! lt's so pretty!
Um. Yeah...
Hey, Kouichi...
Let's go outside and play!
Uh...
Or do you wanna stay in bed?
Hey Kouichi, let's do it the way you like.