Your juice is flowing inside me!
Well, it looks like you haven't
masturbated with this hole...
But l can't believe you fainted.
Now how do l get my thing to calm down?
Well, l'm getting hungry.
l guess l'll have that woman
fix me some dinner.
l'll let you have this instead of my cock.
ENCODED BY SHINKIRO
Menage a Twins
Vol. 2 Concerto of Pleasure
What's wrong? Are you gonna climax?
No, do you wanna go to the veranda?
l want to see the pretty stars in the sky.
You mean like this?
We can't go out there like this.
Did you know?
You won't see anyone outside
depending on the time.
Yeah, but...
Come on.
Hey...
You're being coercive.
l can't believe it...
He put this inside me...
lt feels good...
What's wrong? You seem to be holding back.
Well, we can't make much noise like before.
Don't worry about it.
There are many young couples
living in this apartment building.
No one's gonna care.
What?
That's not right...
Well? Does it feel good?
Good, it's good!
ls this true?
ls he really doing Yuko-chan too?
Why is he doing this?
Looks like you're awake.
Then...
Wait, l hear someone's voice...
Really?
Maybe someone's watching us.
Someone's probably
masturbating while watching us.
l should play with your tits as well.
No, don't squeeze them like that!
But your hips are starting to move faster.
Plus it's amazing...
Your juice keeps flowing out.
Don't say that.
No, make it stop...
Let me wake up if it's a dream!
Amazing, it's bigger than before...
l'm about to climax...
l'm very excited!
l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
Here l come!
Well?
What did you think about
Yuko-san and l having sex?
Say something will you?
Ah, so you keep on climaxing huh?
You look real tired.
Why?
Why did you have to do
such cruel things to Yuko-chan?
Cruel things?
lt was consensual sex.
l have to admit, the truth was
a bit too much for you to take.
But what's the point of taking it out on others?
You're gonna feel empty inside right?
What are you trying to say?
You can't get back what you lost,
but you can start over again.
Thank you for your opinion, but...
No, what are you...
You're telling me that with your cunt all wet.
That's because you...
You still don't get it do you?
Minoru-san...
You just lost your virginity,
but now you're enjoying this?
That's not...
You're getting better at this.
Why are you holding back? Let yourself go.
Why don't you scream
out loud just like Yuko-san?
You're pretty stubborn.
l wonder how long you'll last.
l like this feeling.
Please stop!
Oh, so it's that good huh?
Then l have to do a much better job!
Don't you think it's unfair to climax first
after you pretended not to feel anything?
You listening to me?
Oh well...
What the hell? l thought
you were half conscious...
...but you're getting real tight again.
You're one fine slut.
Even though you moan without much energy...
You obviously know where to tighten up.
Ok, here l come!
l want you to wear this
for the tripartite meeting.
l can't wear this and go.
Today's tripartite meeting is due to
the fact that my grades are slipping!
You're the one who's responsible for this!
What are you doing?
lf you put it on like that,
people are gonna notice.
Put it on the other way around.
Remove your panties and place it up your cunt.
What?
l thought you liked the vibrator.
Guidance Room
As far as his grades are concerned...
He has to do better, and you
have to help him along as well.
l'll arrange for the makeup exam.
Thank you very much.
By the way, you don't look very well.
Were you working all night?
No, it's not like that.
Maybe l did a bad makeup job.
lf you're not feeling well, then
we can do this on another day.
No, it's really nothing.
Sorry about all this.
Hey, your cell phone is ringing.
You can take the call if you want.
l'm sure it's job-related.
Yes...
Kusunoki-san?
Yes.
Don't you have to answer the call?
l don't mind if you do.
Wait...
l'm sorry, it was my phone.
Kusunoki...
You want me to deduct points
from your progress report?
l'm really sorry.
You shouldn't leave your cell phone on.
Hey, don't you think that was bad?
Well you're the one who started it.
But you didn't have to shout at me.
Think about where you are.
So let's try not to do this in public.
Who do you think you are?
l was nice enough to tolerate your crap!
Are you gonna act like a hypocrite
and show your kindness again?
My teacher was a good-looking guy right?
You were trying to entice the
guy with this thing inside you.
What?
Stop...
Stop it...
You were able to talk about my
grades when you were this wet?
Stop...
What are you trying to do?
This is a school. lt's a place for study and...
ln a way, this is part of studying.
Anyhow, we're going into
an unchartered territory.
No!
What are you doing?
What a great view.
But l'm surprised you were able
to talk to the teacher like this.
Don't say that.
But the way things are, the
chair is probably all sticky.
l'm sure it's all smelly by now.
What?
Ouch...
lt hurts!
Stop it...
This is a school.
Even if it hurts, l'm not gonna quit now!
You're just gonna have to
pray that it gets better!
l can feel your vibrator!
Man, l'm full.
Let's go this way for a walk.
Yes, l like that look.
To me, this is the best dessert.
Lean on that and stick your ass this way!
No! What are you planning to do?
What am l planning to do?
You know what l'm going to do.
No, we can't do it here!
Don't move.
You wouldn't want your clothes to get ripped.
No, we can't do it outside!
But look, you're all wet!
The vibrator isn't even on yet,
it's just a stick inside you...
You were probably thinking that
someone's gonna be watching you right?
Of course.
Even if it's the inner part of the
park, people might still be watching us!
But you like that don't you?
Why is it that...
What do you mean why?
You're enjoying this aren't you?
l'm not enjoying this...
lt hurts!
Then how do you explain this wetness?
No, if you do it faster...
l don't care if your crotch gets ripped or torn.
You're so mean!
But you don't seem dissatisfied.
My cock got dirty from doing your ass.
Clean it up for me, mother.
Don't get me wrong.
This is called mending our family ties.
Even though we're not a family, l want
us to love and be close to each other.
l want us to be close, just like a real family.
You're such a slut mother.
You're feeling good already?
That's not true...
Really?
l always knew you were a masochist.
l see, you're very excited too huh?
No, no!
That's why you're getting so tight.
l'm about to climax...
l'm releasing it inside, so let's merge.
No, take it out!
Here l come, Tomoe!
l'm gonna release it!
l'm gonna do it inside...
Stop! Anything but that!
No!
Oh, it's from Akane.
l treated that woman cruelly but
she still has interest in me...
lt's true that Akane became
pregnant after being raped.
But she had an abortion.
Akane thought it was a
bastard child inside her...
So she had an abortion
and was deeply saddened.
Then she was asked to be a surrogate
mother and she gladly accepted.
So basically, l'm a child
born from Akane's stomach...
But since she was artificially inseminated...
...l'm not related to both
Akane and Tomoe by blood.
Tomoe thinks it's her fault that l got raped.
What do you mean?
Some guy tried to ask out
Tomoe, but she refused.
And he was a companion
to the guys that raped me.
Truth is covered in darkness.
But the couple that requested
me to be a surrogate mother...
...meaning your true parents...
When Tomoe found out that they had
been killed in a car accident...
...she decided to take care of you.
So she did it in order to atone for her sins.
l would've expected that
from a saintly woman like her.
You and l aren't even related.
Right?
You gave birth to me but we're not related?
Then what made you come and see me?
You wanted your own son to
fulfill your sexual desires?
l guess you and l think alike.
No!
Can't you be more gentle?
You don't need me to be gentle.
l know you like it rough.
Here.
That's not true!
You get excited when l play rough?
lf you keep doing this, l'm not gonna last long!
No! My breasts are gonna break...
No!
Don't stop!
lt hurts!
l can see that you and Tomoe are twins.
You both have the same reaction!
Don't bang me that hard!
Stop whining!
lt's coming out, lt's coming out!
These are like water balloons.
What's wrong?
You're unwilling to do it,
but you're still sucking on it.
Yeah, use your mouth as well as your tongue.
Hey, who told you to rest?
lf you're tired of just moving your mouth...
...you have other ways to do it you know.
By moving your head back and forward,
it makes a whole lot of difference.
You're no good.
Forget it, l'll force you to do it.
Well? Do you like being forced to suck?
You just won't let go.
You're such a slut.
Ok, here l come!
Swallow it well!
Here, gulp it all down.
Good, you drank it all.
Now here's your reward.
Don't hesitate to take it.
Take them out!
What's wrong? l only put the tip inside.
Take them out...
Take them out now!
lt hurts!
No!
lt went in smoothly!
What a view.
Your crotch is all bubbly and twitching.
l guess l'll make your wish come true.
lt feels very cool.
Man, it feels so tight.
l don't think l have to move at all.
What do you think? But maybe
you should move a little.
l think l'm going insane...
My body is shaking...
You're getting drunk.
No!
Stop it!
You'll be feeling good in no time.
No! Don't move any faster!
l'm feeling dizzy!
We're not done yet.
This is where l start to get my revenge!