Dear Yui-senpai, We're going to train to record the CD.
From now on, everything will be my first experience, so I'm really excited.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by a single millimeter.
Hounto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai no Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
Angels Of The Summer Resort's Forest
Cool, cool, cool! It looks like a mansion!
What a stylish studio!
The sofa is very soft!
Look, the garden is also huge!
True, true!
Wow, the night will be...
Hey, you! We didn't come to play.
Control yourselves.
Instead of you all, look at Miru's calmness.
Ino-chan, cute.
It even has a name.
Rules.
Rules?!
In case of quitting, you'll be disqualified from Lemon Angel.
Really?
Is that a Miki joke?
N-No, Miki thinks that's absurd.
We don't need girls that don't try hard.
Ah, he's arrived.
I'll introduce him, this is the new music director for Lemon Angel.
I'm Katagiri.
Nice to meet you.
N-Nice to meet you!
I'm going back to the company, so obey Katagiri-san's instructions.
Yes!
This is the training schedule.
Training Schedule: 4:00 - Wake up | 5:00 - Run  -> 10km course| 6:00 - Bodybuilding | - Abdominal - 50x (3 sets) | - Push Ups - 50x (3 sets) | - Crouching - 50x (3 sets)
Wake up at 4am, run, abdominals, crouch, then coffee and dance class?
7:00 - Morning Coffee | - Menu: Rice, Fish, Soup | 8:00 - Dance Class: Capoeira,  Rock, Jazz | 12:00 - Lunch |
- Menu: Rice, Hamburger, Salad, Soup | 13:00 - Dance Class: Hip-Hop, Street Dance, Cossack | 17:00 - Bath
Doing vocal exercises during all training.
18:00 - Dinner | - Menu: - Bread, Mixed Eggs, Salad, Orange Juice | 19:00 - Body building |
20:00 - Sleep | Do exactly as the menu says. | The use of cell phones and text messaging is forbidden.
Ah... it's too hard...
Do you think with actual techniques you could record something?
What?
You'll train correctly until I say it's okay.
Ehhh?!
If anybody has any complaints, leave now!
It can't be...
If we stop doing the activities, we'll be disqualified.
What are you doing?
Pick up your bags and get ready!
Y-Yes!
Will they be okay?
They'll keep up for sure.
But he accepted that role easily.
To tell the truth, it was Katagiri-san who asked for it.
What? Really?
Finally, an ofuro.
Note: An Ofuro are part of a Japanese ritual of bathing. They are not used for washing, but for relaxing.
My body was all wet from so much sweat.
Ah, how nice! Really feels great.
Hey, Tomo, let's get in.
Yea, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
My body is already sore.
I thought I was going to die.
Quiting already?
It hasn't started yet.
My stomach's hurting. I can't take it anymore.
Come on! What'll you do if that's the only thing that gets you tired?
Why do we have to do this?
I don't understand anything.
I thought we were going to a beautiful studio!
This is hell.
I can't take it anymore.
I didn't know that dancing and singing at the same time would be so tiring.
You demon, You mustached demon.
A mustached demon?
For being a demon with a mustache, he's an Onihige.
Doesn't change anything.
That's enough. Let's go to the next one.
I'm sorry, I don't feel so good...
Yumi! Are you okay?
Let her rest for a bit.
Stupid thing, if you all stay best-friends, you won't survive in the professional world.
This isn't a joke, Yumi's part of this group.
Then you'll all run around the lagoon until Sakaibara gets better.
What?
Isn't she from the group?
So, be solidarity responsible for her.
Um, what lagoon?
That one.
That's not a lagoon, it's a lake!
Uh, I'll go too.
I'm sorry, it's my fault that...
Don't worry.
That Onihige is weird.
What?
What?!
Ah!
Yumi, your skin is so soft!
Especially this part, it's very soft.
Erika!
It's to know you better.
No!!
What are you guys doing?
You had that kind of relationship?
Of course not!
In a while,
It'll start in a while, Yui.
Control your abdomen better.
Breathe on three.
Use your abdomen to do vocal exercises.
Yuki!
Y-Yes?
You'll be in charge of the food.
What? Me?
You worked hard this morning.
Hurry up and prepare lunch.
Lucky!
I'll go first.
Ah, so lucky!
Let's go!
Maybe I'm not so jealous afterall.
Yeah.
Let's go.
What?
Now that Onihige's gone, we can rest a bit and...
Let's work hard.
Is there any meaning for training so hard?
Accept this wonderful lunch that I, Saya made.
Thank you for the meal.
Th-This taste...
That's not taste, that's...
Is this food?
What?
Seriously?
You're joking, right?
Katagiri-san!
Thank goodness! At least he looks like he's liking...
What?
He fainted!
Whaaat?!
I'm home.
What's wrong, Saya-chan?
Keiko-san!
They all have blue faces...
It's because of Katagiri-san's infernal training, isn't it?
Ah, this lunch looks tasty.
Did Saya make it?
Looks delicious!
Very good!
The next opportunity we get, how about we write that your speciality is culinary on your profile?
Saya-chan, you can't lie on your profile.
Katagiri Hitoshi and Erika Campbell.
You brought together really interesting members.
I don't like Onihige much, Katagiri-san.
Me neither.
He only wants to stress us more.
Really?
It looks like he hates music.
I wonder if he's trying to make us quit singing?
It couldn't be novice's massacre?
I'm sure Kogure-san and Keiko-san are being fooled.
I won't forgive that!
I don't want someone who doesn't like music, recording Yui-senpai's music.
Hey, let's throw him out?
What?
How?
I've got a good idea!
Will that work?
It will, it will.
Leave it to me.
Every human is afraid of spirits and ghosts.
It's common all over the world.
It's even common for spirits to be in a recording studio.
With that, we'll scare him and make him go away.
Doesn't look too scary.
Miru, I told you to get rid of that plushie!
You think that's the problem?
What's that noise?
Sounds  like he's sharpening something.
Could it be a knife?
Hey, is Onihige really a demon?
Of course not!
He isn't, right?
Let's go.
When we get in, we'll all scream, got it?
Yeah.
One, two, three!
I'm a ghost!
D-don't go near him!
What's wrong? It's really a demon!
What? What?
Katagiri-san!
I couldn't sleep with all the noisey wind.
W-What's wrong everyone?
Demon...
Miki-senpai, we're not keeping up with that director's strong rhythm!
Foreign magazines?
It's Katagiri-san.
In this magazine also.
This one too.
Here's a special on Katagiri.
Wow, impressive!
In this famous magazine too.
We knew that Katagiri-san was an amazing person,
but it looks like he hates music.
That's very unlikely.
We can only imagine!
That's nonsense!
Katagiri-san...
What do you mean by that?
What's with him?
What an irritating man!
Why did he say "That's nonsense!"?
Looks like he didn't hear us.
Five, four, three, two, one.
I-I'm sorry!
What happened to the other three?
That's, um...
They said they're not feeling well.
Let's go.
Guys...
He's gone!
Can we let it be like this?
Yes, it doesn't matter if we take that nonsense training.
I can't keep up with anymore of Katagiri-san's training.
He's a reporter of an artistic magazine.
I'm Kousaku.
From today until the last day, he'll collect information about you.
If you slack off, he'll even take photos of you slacking, so be careful.
N-No, we won't!
Right, right?
Y-Yes.
Very good.
Saya-chan, get closer to Miki.
Yes.
So, now we'll take photos of each one, okay?
Tomo-chan first.
Yes.
Hey, Tomo! You're a professional, aren't you?
Do it right!
This is different from Onihige's work.
Tomo-chan, pretend you're singing in the microphone, okay?
Y-Yes!
Tomo, Are you okay?
The new Lemon Angels are really good friends, aren't they?
T-That's right!
I'm anxious for your debut.
I'm really anxious!
Hey, Tomo!
All right, the last one is Erika-chan. Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready to do any pose.
With the way you look, Erika-chan doesn't look too much like Takumi-kun.
What?
Some time ago, I had an interview with your brother, Takumi-kun.
You're siblings, Aren't you?
W-We are..
We don't look alike?
No, not really.
People say that a lot.
Yui!
Yui.
What is it?
Why that sad face?
Yui, say something.
Yui.
Yui!
Yui...
Why?
I can finally return it to Katagiri now.
What do you mean by "What're we going to do?"
About killing the training.
Why are you so down?
Because...
Good evening! You're having a secret meeting so late a night?
No.
That's...
I know, you want to see the photos from today?
Show us, please.
Hey, let's talk about something other than work.
Other than work?
Yes, Katagiri-san's old stories, for example.
You know?
Yeah, a little.
For example, the reason why director Katagiri's going abroad.
To test his own power?
That's right, after losing his power in Japan.
What do you mean?
Five years ago, Katagiri Hitoshi destroyed the throat of Japanese music's precious princess.
What!?
Do you know of the name Alice, at least?
That singer who appeared like the wind and retired the very next year?
Yes.
Katagiri was Alice's producer.
He destroyed an incredible singer like her.
You're also in trouble.
With a troubling producer and a big dark fact.
Two scandals together.
A big dark fact?
What are you talking about?
Famous group,
Third Takumi Meaning. | Living With His Beloved.
Takumi's living with someone?
There's also a fact about that.
The partner is a Lemon Angel member - Erika Campbell!!
What do you mean by living together?
We're siblings, a family!
Family?
How strange!
What do you mean?
You two don't have the same blood, do you?
You're not true siblings, are you?
That's not...
Troublesome director and Takumi's partner.
And attention to the debut music of the new Lemon Angel.
If that scandal comes up, it may produce several interesting things.
It's true, me and Takumi don't have the same blood.
But that doesn't mean we have that kind of relationship.
We're a family!
Nowadays, nobody looks for the truth, impact is enough.
You suck.
That's nice of you, thank you.
I got a good interview.
Takumi is the only one I need now.
Having an interview with someone that hasn't got your family's blood.
What?
I-It can't be...
If he finds out...
Erika, calm down.
Erika!
Long time no see, Katagiri-san.
Already been five years, hasn't it?
What are you doing here?
Five years ago,thanks to you,a really interesting story came up.
"Producer steals Byba's song."
That was really true?
You were still in Japan?
Did you think I had completely vanished?
That time I didn't know what to do after losing my job, thanks to you.
Do you want me to tell you why I still work in it?
To avenge you.
Kousaku.
Takumi is an orphan.
My father and mother adopted Takumi when he was a baby.
But Takumi doesn't know that yet.
That's something he needs to know.
Even if we don't have the same blood, we've always lived like a family up to this day.
I have to find Takumi quick.
You can't, Erika.
Erika-chan.
Erika, if you go now, you'll be disqualified.
Hey, this isn't the moment to say that!
Miki-senpai.
Girls, we have a problem.
Dear Friends
When I woke up, her bags weren't there anymore.
She really went to Takumi.
So, that means that she's disqualified?
It can't be!
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
It was a joke that Erika was disqualified, wasn't it?
My sister was disqualified from Lemon Angel!
What do you feel about Erika, Takumi-kun?
A love thing?
You really love each other?
Yes, of course I love her.
Why?
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 9, "Symphony of Sorrow."
I don't want Erika to be disqualified!!
I don't understand the conversation.
Symphony of Sorrow