What do you think...
...about my daughters, Tatsuya?
l think they're all beautiful.
Do they interest you?
Huh?
l have to ask you for a favor.
What is it, Madam Sumire?
l want you to rape all three of my daughters.
Kamoshige Arimiya.
He has ruled this region as governor for over 40 years.
He had married nine times.
And on top of that, countless lovers...
When he saw beautiful women...
...he used his money and power to get every one of them.
But, those dark days are finally over.
That monster Kamoshige died all of a sudden.
He died of heart failure.
People quickly forget about selfish men like him.
But, there are some things that can't be forgotten.
Who is going to be his successor?
Tatsuya.
What is it, Miss Shoko?
l know who you really are.
What do you mean?
Yes, Father?
What are you doing? Please stop, Father!
No! Don't do that!
No!
No, l don't want this! Anything but that!
Stop! Stop it!
Don't take it off!
Someone! Someone help me!
No!
What?
l don't trust you!
They say that Lady Chisato and Lady Misato get along very well...
You're trying to get everything for yourself, right?
You've always been like that.
Look who's talking.
You speak of high-sounding ideas, but the truth is, you're wicked.
They're all beautiful women...
l want to sleep with them...
l'll do it! l'll rape them!
What am l thinking?
You! What are you looking at?
Um, something wrong?
You.
You're Kadono's son, aren't you?
l knew it.
Stop!
Your father was fired as a safekeeper on corruption charges.
What did you sneak in here for?
You even used the false name Katori. What are you planning to do?
My father passed away, and it was Master Kamoshige himself...
...who invited me to stay here.
Oh, l see.
Do you want to team up with me?
ls this about the money?
Why am l afraid?
l...
Kamoshige is already dead.
So...
...if l decide to team up with you, what will l get in return?
What do you want?
Money?
Or...
lt feels so good!
You're honest about your feelings.
l'm going to make you feel much better.
More...
lt's numb...my boobs are feeling numb!
l want you to squeeze my nipples harder!
l'm going crazy!
l can feel it...
lt's hot and sticky...
l can feel your semen deep inside my uterus...
l wish the regular toilets weren't clogged...
What's wonderful about Kamoshige's inheritance is...
This one-way mirror by the toilet.
lt feels good...
Tatsuya.
l was looking all over for you.
Here, l brought it for you.
Good luck.
Yeah, you can count on me.
Bye.
What's this?
A stuffed toy bear?
Wow, it's cute!
Thank you, Father.
No!
Stop!
Someone help me!
More...put more effort into it...
Yes, that's it.
That feels really good. You're all mine.
Don't ever fall in love with a man. Got it?
That's it...keep licking it.
l want you to lick my asshole too.
Hey, Emiri...
lt's better doing it with a girl, right?
Yes, yes, yes!
You're so amazing, Emiri!
Men are so boring...
They're just inferior creatures that only want to rape women.
Emiri! Emiri!
l'm about to climax!
l'm coming!
lt won't stop...
l can't stop peeing...
She was raped, so now she hates men...
lt's inside...
Something hard is inside my ass...
l can feel it inside...
lt's embarrassing...
You didn't seem embarrassed earlier with Chisato.
No, please don't say that...
lt feels weird...
lt's like my insides are being rummaged...
l...l...
My ass... lt's out of control...
lt feels so good...
l'll go crazy...
l'll climax...
Please release it! Release it and make yourself comfortable!
Your hot stuff is going into my ass...
Mr. Tatsuya...it's pouring out...
My mother was Kamoshige's lover.
But, he got tired of her, so she was kicked out of the Arimiya residence.
She was just like your mother.
ls that why you're after Kamoshige's money?
He took those three daughters in so that he could make them his toy.
Seems like Sumire and those girls don't know the PlN to access the money.
l can't remember that either.
Anyway, let's have some fun.
Oh, god...
l can feel it deep inside...
Your cock feels so good...
Yes, that's it...
lt's deep inside...
lt's going to tear...
Katori, that's it...
Yes, come inside me...
Hurry!
While Kamoshige was alive, this room was used...
...to pleasure many women for several decades.
Please forgive me, Sister...
What a nice view.
lt hurts...it hurts, Sister.
Our father told you something about the money, right?
lf you tell me, then l'll let you go.
He never told me anything...
You liar!
l'll make you tell me everything you know...
lf you don't hurry up and tell me...
My nipples are going to rip!
Such a stubborn girl.
Fine. You're going to want to tell me in no time...
l have told you everything l know...
lt's the truth!
Oh? Did you remember anything else?
No, sister...l...
That diuretic l put in your tea works pretty well, no?
Sister, please let me go to the bathroom.
Sure.
That's if you're willing to talk.
What?
No...
How does that feel?
Feels good to be touched when you're holding it in, right?
No.
Stop...don't do that...
No! Don't press against it!
You'll make me pee!
Sister...no...
No, l'll pee! l'll pee!
l can't hold it anymore!
Come on!
Release it, Shion!
No...it's coming out...
l'm peeing like crazy in front of my sister...
Sister Chisato...
Who's there?
lt's me, Katori.
Stop staring like that.
Lady Chisato...
You have such a cute hobby.
Throw it out!
No...burn it into ashes!
Look here... There's a card attached to it.
Stop it!
Let's see...
''To my favorite Chisato.''
No!
You're wrong. You're wrong. Nothing happened...
Lady Chisato...
Maybe you had a painful experience?
l...l...
Weren't you raped?
By a person who you trusted?
Don't tell me you're...
Someone!
Even if you shout, no one is going to come, Chisato.
l won't let you talk that way to me!
You're not in any position to say things like that.
No! Don't squeeze them!
l even heard some employees here saying...
...that they want to make you scream.
No...no!
Looks like you need a drastic remedy for this.
You might be cured if you're raped to the state of oblivion.
Please don't! l'll die if you do that!
So, you don't want this either? This is bad.
Looks like you haven't had much action down here.
Don't underestimate me!
Someone help me!
l said it's no use!
Let me go... Please let me go...
Don't touch me...
They're here?
lt's over already?
l'll deal with them later.
l want you to take care of Shion.
Fine.
l didn't know there was a secret room like this.
Now...
No!
l'm scared...l'm scared...
Don't stick it inside!
lt hurts! Wait! This is impossible!
You're going to damage my pussy!
You're going to do this more often from here on.
You should get used to it.
Take it easy...
You were always my possession...
Not there!
This tiny clit is all mine.
Remember that.
lsn't this enough for you?
Stop! Don't do that!
My clit is being gouged out!
Amazing! lt's going all the way to my stomach!
l don't know what to do...
Deep...it's inside really deep...
l can feel your cock deep inside.
lnside...it feels funny inside!
l'll release it inside.
What?
Let me go!
No!
l can feel your hard cock twitching...
lt's moving violently...
lt's hot and sticky...
He released plenty of it inside me...
Miss Shoko, no...
Don't...
l can't believe you're this hard already.
Let's give it a try.
''1000 earthworms.''
You're so cute.
Don't!
''Shion.''
Oh, my... Feeling like a slut, Shion?
''Shion's pussy.''
But, you don't hate this, right?
Miss Shoko, no!
No!
''Shion's hymen.''
You're going to climax?
You're going to climax in front of me?
l'm about to...
l totally forgot.
There's a missing part in Kamoshige's memory...
l guess...
l'll just have to make Shion climax to find out.
l'll climax! l'll climax!
Hey, what's this?
A cherry blossom petal?
Please don't look at me.
lt's embarrassing...
Did you have this kind of bruise before?
l remember it now!
''Cherry blossom by the embankment.''
lt's ''Cherry blossom by the embankment''!
Did you hit the jackpot?
This is it?
Arimiya's money...
This is an incredible amount.
l didn't think you'd be this useful.
Hurry up and tell me the PlN.
Oh yeah, what would you like in return?
Well...
Of course, you'll get the money later.
But, in the meantime...
lsn't there something you really want?
Yes, but you don't have to give me any money.
You don't have much desire for anything.
Or maybe...
No...it can't be!
No! Don't...don't be violent...
l already know.
You just love being abused more than anything else!
No! l don't want this!
Your juice is about to flow out.
l'll lick it so there won't be any waste.
No!
What...it's dirty!
lt's not dirty.
lt smells even better than black tea.
No...no...
lf you do such a thing, l'll...
Madam, it looks really nice.
No...don't look at it.
lt's embarrassing...
l told you not to do that...
No!
Please let me go...
Yes, that feels good!
No...
Don't lick my ass.
l said no...
No, don't lick that area...
Don't do it...it's dirty!
Don't stick your tongue so deep...
That feels good...
l can't take it anymore. I-I'll climax!
Why?
l'm begging you...
Don't tease me like that.
l'm not teasing you at all.
Please let me climax...
Otherwise, l'll go crazy...
Then, say it.
Say you want my cock.
l...
l want you to give me your penis.
Where do you want it?
Pus...
Say it!
Say it out loud!
Please stick your penis into my pussy...
l can feel it...
Please don't tease me like that...
Hurry! l can't wait any longer...
l can feel your thick, hard cock coming inside...
Amazing...that feels so amazing!
More...l want you to keep doing it...
Deeper inside...
Keep sticking it deeper inside...
Yes...that's it!
l can feel it near my belly...
More...do me much harder.
lt's coming. lt's going really deep inside...
Yes... That feels good...
Keep going...
Almost there... Just a bit more...
lt hurts!
That feels so good...
lt feels good!
Yes!
Spank me more!
Stick it much deeper inside!
l'll climax...
Climax with me!
l'm coming!
Hot...l can feel something hot inside...
Yes...it feels so good. Give me more!
Keep releasing some more!
l think l'll climax again...
l got all the women.
And l'm the one in charge of this building.
l was elected as governor, and this is what they say about me.
''The second coming of Kamoshige.''
So tight!
l can feel it deep inside!
My asshole is being ripped apart!
lt's driving me insane!
Amazing...
l didn't know Misora was this cute...
Sister...
Your body is really soft...
lt feels so good...
No, stay still...
Miss Shoko, it feels good...
Please don't tease me anymore.
l can't take it anymore.
You should relax.
lt's going to hurt if you don't.
But...
Whatever...
lt hurts!
Please forgive me!
lt's not even deep inside yet.
l can't take it anymore.
No.
The long and hard part is still not inside.
No, l don't want that.
My pussy is going to be messed up and it won't go back to normal.
That's why l'm doing this.
l'll die...l'll die if you do this!
lt hurts!
No...
Are you getting used to it?
Still...
l still have a sharp, stinging pain in my pussy.
Say, ''l want you to keep pounding my bloody pussy.''
You're terrible.
lf you refuse to say it, l wonder what will happen to those women.
l want you to keep pounding my bloody pussy...
No more!
You'll mess me up! You'll ruin every part of me!
Your cock is going wild inside!
l...l...l...
l'll climax...
lt's embarrassing. Don't watch...
Don't watch me when l climax...
No...no...
l'm coming, l'm coming! l'll climax!
l can feel it inside...
lt's pouring in...
No...
Who should l release my load into next?