It feels so good...
Doctor...
Please I beg you...
Not just my butt...
I also...
What's wrong?
Can't endure it much longer?
I'm itching for it.
Doctor, my pussy wants to...
...cum already!
Shall I make you cum first, then?
Doctor, I'm so happy.
No! Not with your fingers...
A cock... I want a cock!
No! Don't...
Spread your legs some more.
Like this?
It's all exposed, you know?
I'm embarrassed,
but it's twitching inside, and it feels good...!
I'm cumming.
I'm... cumming-!
Quite the orgasm there, even though you
didn't want me to use my fingers.
Don't! I am already...
No...
No...! If it gets pulled out now...
I will cum...
It will all come out!
Doctor, please don't...!
I see.
Though this is an experiment,
it'd be troublesome to make the lobby dirty.
I won't pull it out then.
What...?
I'll push it in!
I'm going to lose control of my butt.
Well then, let's continue with our experiment.
Ge-Geez.
Make the next preparations quickly.
We still have about 50,000 items to check.
Oh Doctor, you...
What's funny?
Give me more orders, Doctor.
FORBIDDEN WARD
Special Psychiatrist, Yuusa Sousuke's Medical Examination Records
Currently,
the Pediatrics and the Gynecology
department are fully occupied.
Sorry for the inconvenience, but please wait a while longer.
Gynecologist Yamano Shin...
Please head to Examination Room 21 immediately.
The distribution according to the data contents will...
No.
That's...
Don't rub that lewd thing on me.
I'll go crazy.
Doctor, my heart is throbbing...
What do you think this is?
For you to secrete so much liquid, well...
Your hole seems to be longing for this thing.
Doctor's cock is...
...entering, entering me...!
It's going inside!
It hurts, it hurts!
No!
Don't move so suddenly.
Doctor, it hurts...
Don't shake me around!
If we do this a bit longer,
it will start to feel good.
Don't worry.
Doctor, I have Androphobia.
For me to do this lewd thing,
while I still have to go to school...
I can't tell my friends about this...!
The longer we continue our sessions like this, the
faster you will get rid of your Androphobia.
I'm getting treated...
I'm slowly and slowly being cured!
This is embarrassing.
It's in plain sight.
It's getting stretched...
And I'm starting to go crazy!
Does it feel good when you say that
it's embarrassing and that it hurts?
So you're quite the masochist, eh?
Okay, here you go, masochist Sara.
Have you noticed that we are on camera?
Oh no, it's embarrassing...
I'm not...
I'm not some sort of masochistic pervert...!
I see, let's put on a more detailed show then.
No way...
No, I can't...
My heart is throbbing...
Doctor, you're way too intense, I'm going to break!
I see, then we'll stop right here.
No, I didn't mean...
Please don't stop!
P-Please, Doctor...!
I... feel good...
Are you acknowledging that you're
a perverted lewd masochist?
Yes.
I'm a pervert who likes to expose herself.
I am a lewd masochist.
Listen up, if you act more honestly in front of men,
you'll get properly rewarded like this.
Remember that.
I'll remember.
My pussy will remember...!
Then continue to move and squeeze it out pervert Sara.
Wow, it feels good.
Something's coming!
Coming!!
Please release it more inside.
It feels so warm inside.
Did I...?
Did I...
#unrecognized text#
...have my Androphobia cured?
I'm jealous.
If my body weren't like this,
Doctor may have been doing that to me already.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you have a moment?
Of course.
I'm Kenzaki, the patient who is scheduled for 5:00 pm.
Yes, I know.
Can you please sign here and wait?
Umm...
Is there something wrong?
Doesn't it smell a little weird?
A little like... semen, or some other thing...
No way.
There's no way semen could have...
S-Sorry!
I guess that's not possible, right?
No, it's not.
I'm the only one here.
It's probably your imagination.
The Forbidden Ward
doctor Yuusa Souske
Ms. Kenzaki's data is in the DD folder.
Understood. I leave further monitoring to you.
Yes, I'll handle it.
Kenzaki Reina-san.
Job, job Akihabara-style net idol
Proportions:
Breasts 90
Waist 60
Hip 65
It's so-so.
Thank you.
Is this yesterday's video?
Yes.
That's the video that I was told to bring.
Please come again, thank you.
Reina, I will be coming to your next handshake event.
Thank you as always.
Reina's hands are so soft!
My hands aren't the only part that's soft, you know.
I'm happy that you came again today!
For real?
It'd be bad, if you push too strongly.
So-Sorry.
It's a wonderful, manly hand.
Reina, it's hitting your breasts...
It's big and stiff.
My heart is starting to throb...!
It's getting fiddled around...!
No...
I'll get horny...
Reina-san, I'll buy three copies of the game!
Wow... you'll buy that much?!
Thank you! Three copies, please!
Also, put one lotion as freebie in the package please.
Get yourself wet and slippery often, okay?
Thank you, please come again!
Next customer!
I'm... going to buy 10 copies!
Wow, that's great!
Now I'm starting to get slippery and wet.
Really?
It's true.
I'm quite horny, you know.
don't really want to do this job to be,honest.
Stinky hands of those creepy otakus.
And they touch mine every chance they get.
Their hands are coated With a weird smell with
some kind of liquid that feels sticky all over...
That filthy smell, seems to seep into me.
I really don't like it, but...
But, I can see that you're getting really aroused from it.
That's not...!
The keyword for your condition seems to be "stinky".
For you to release this much in secretions
just by imagining stinky things...
You're really quite the pervert.
That can't be...!
You don't need to worry.
I already have the perfect treatment in mind.
Extraction Room
Male Use
What's this place?
Managing Doctor Yuusa Sousuke
As written, this is a place where you extract sperm.
In other words, it's the masturbation room.
Why are we in here...?
You'll find out once we are inside.
What's this smell?
It's the smell of semen.
We don't clean them, even after the subjects are finished.
There are pictures of me.
Now then, sit down.
I'll start the treatment.
In here?
What is this?
It stinks.
Could this be semen?
Oh no...
It stained my blouse and skirt...
If you don't want the dress to get dirty, you better undress.
I can't just...!
Now, try to suck on this.
Do-Doctor...
This is your treatment, leave it to me.
Y- Yes.
What's this?
The smell is intense.
So this is what a cock smells like?
At the moment, it still Has The scent
of four other patients I had today.
What does that mean?
It means it has the smell of four lewd people.
It's dirty...
Now, open wide.
It stinks...!
This stinky thing in my mouth?
But, my heart is really throbbing.
Stick your tongue out and open wide.
It stinks!
Take it up to your throat.
The smell is strong.
What's this?
My body feels hot...
You seem to be aroused by the smell
of males and female's lewd fluids.
Those otakus that have a strong smell...
A room that stinks of semen...
The smell of a penis that has fucked lots of women...
You love those kinds of stinky smells.
I'm not that kind of a pervert!
Even if you say that,
you're already getting drenched in different juices yourself.
My mind is going blank with this smell and taste...
I'll investigate the condition in between your legs and breasts.
Take off your underwear.
Okay.
Doctor, this is embarrassing...
Oh, but I only see you as a pervert who is totally
aroused and dripping with love juices.
My body already feels hot.
Unable to hold it in anymore?
Doctor's cock and semen...
Okay, I'm going to release it all over you.
Where do you want it?
I feel hot in here, so here is where I want it Doctor.
Right here please!
My pussy, is already getting weird...
Touching my pervy pussy like that.
Oh no!
I'm going to cum...
It's coming out!
I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming!
If you want more, then rub your pussy on it.
Please rub my insides.
It's entering in me...
I'm about to cum again...!
I'll release it here as well.
Ram it into me, please!
It's coming...!
Doctor's semen!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to release it. Open your mouth.
Give it to me, please!
Doctor's semen stinks...
My nose is going wild...
But...
This smell is so thrilling...
From here on out, you'll only be satisfied by cumming
with the stinky smell of those otaku's semen.
You'll now become a true otaku idol.
The Forbidden Ward
Everyone! I, Kenzaki Reina will explain
the details of today's event!
Please keep you spirits high and wait patiently.
About today's video tape:
Fuyuno-than and I were the ones who took it.
I see.
It's a body suit!
It's cute!
Thank you all for coming today.
Today, I would like to practically experience
a part of the game story with everyone.
So I chose to wear this body suit!
This suit is the damaged version!
All of Reina-chan is exposed in plain sight!
It's the armor when she's about to get done in!
To tell you the truth, I'm actually a pervert.
I get aroused by men's sweat, saliva,
pee... and specially semen...!
of everyone's smell here.
Right now, my pussy is drenched because
Is this for real?
Mine too!
I want to put it in so badly!
I can't endure for much long!
Everyone, look!
I'll stroke your cocks with utmost sincerity!
Please look at my pussy and stiffen your cocks!
Oh man!
Reina-chan is a real life pussy doll!
I think mine's already going to cum...
I'll assist in helping you folks cum!
Reina-chan!
It's okay!
Cum a lot!
It's coming out...!
Lots of it...
Reina-chan...!
I'm going to take this!
Please let my raw cock into your pussy!
It's okay.
Please thrust your stinky cock into me.
It's a dirty beast!
Reina's insides are convulsing wildly.
I'm getting squeezed!
Release it!
Release it in me!
Cumming inside feels great!
Please give me more...
of everyone's built up, stinky semen!
I can't endure any longer!
Was Reina-san this lewd...?
I can't get enough of this stinky smell... I want more!
I'm cumming!
I'm also... cumming!
Wow, oh wow!
Hot stuff is coming out!
It's perfectly fine. Please look at my lewd body.
Release all your stinky semen onto me!
Thrust all of your lewd and smelly cocks in me.
More! Give me more of your cocks!
Give me more semen, more of these stinky stuff!
Reina... is a pervert...!
Set her next medical exam appointment.
Okay, understood.
So, I'm setting her next appointment for tomorrow at 5:00 PM.
Something smells...
Fuyuno-chan?
Sorry, it just stiffened...
Stiffened...?
Fuyuno-chan, is that a cock?
So that's your physical complex, eh?
Yes.
I also want to have your counseling for this, please.
Show it all to me then.
Yes.
Doctor, p-please take care of me.
Fuyuno-chan's cock is getting really big.
Don't play with it like that...!
Please be gentler... stop...!
Even if you say that, there is already
pre-cum at the tip of your cock.
This is embarrassing...
Please don't say that...
So you're also feeling it here at the same time.
Doctor, I might not be able to hold this in...!
Rine-san...! Don't!
I am too sensitive there!
Don't!
No! Doctor, don't...!
I'll cum!
I'll cum!!
I'm cumming!!
Her cock and pussy came at the same time.
So you can also ejaculate...
I'm sorry.
My body looks gross, doesn't it?
It's nothing like that.
You're very cute, Fuyuno-chan.
I so want to cum with this stiff cock.
Okay.
If you're alright with my cock...
You're still so stiff, Fuyuno-chan.
Here I go, Fuyuno-chan!
This is embarrassing, Rine-san...
I took Fuyuno-chan's virginity.
Rine-san, your pussy is so hot inside...
It's getting really wet...!
How's this?
Squeezing?!
Don't squeeze my cock in!
If you squeeze it tightly like that, my...
I'm going to ill this one too.
Doctor, let's do it together.
Wow...
I'm being taken on both sides...
Everytime your pussy gets raped,
That's because...
...having both my pussy and cock taken at the same time...
Put your backs into it!
Doctor, I...
I'm about to cum... again...
Fuyuno-chan's cock feels great!
Wow, I'm going to cum!
That's good.
You too Fuyuno, release your cum inside Rine this way.
No...
Cumming inside Rine-san...?!
I-It's okay.
Release it inside!
I am also about to cum!
I'm cumming.
Let's cum together!
I'm also going to release it all in here.
It's hitting... inside me...
I'm also cumming!
My pussy and cock are cumming!
I'm cumming...!
Fuyuno-chan, your cock is still twitching.
No, don't say that...
It's embarrassing!
Fuyuno-chan, let's do it again, okay?
Now you have nothing to hide anymore, Fuyuno.
Yes, Doctor.
I don't have to worry about it anymore.
Both of you are now going to be my assistants.
Understood?
Yes.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to stay with you forever, Doctor.
Take good care of me too, Doctor!