Haramasete Seiryuu-kun!
Episode 2: Harem Pregnancy END
Okay!
Boys and girls, we've arrived!
Thank you for your patience!
This feels great, Tougo!
I-If that ride had been any longer, I'd have been in trouble.
Motion sickness, Tougo?
Pathetic behavior from my future husband.
That has yet to be decided!
Tougo is going to be my husband.
"Husband", my foot!
Titty-tiger bitch!
Say what? You snotty little president...
Be quiet, you two!
We have an announcement from the Sports Committee.
We are conducting our retreat at a luxury
sports arena resort this year.
The competition will occur one week from today!
Until then, if you wish to enter,
please complete the qualifying rounds.
For everyone else, there will be classes
held in the culture room at the hotel.
We have various different sports clubs
all together here, so be sure to mingle.
This luxury sports resort is under the
care of our school commissioner,
so if you just flash your student ID,
you can take full advantage of all the amenities!
Dinner starts at 07:00 PM,
in the main hall.
Until then, it's free time, so do what you like.
The room assignments are posted in the lobby.
Take a good look, okay?
Tougo, you're sharing a room with rne.
After all, we're engaged.
Just a minute, Akiha. When did you become engaged?
It seems that you've forgotten that Tougo chose me.
Tougo, I don't mind authorizing a room change
so you can stay with me instead.
Tougo didn't choose you, Senpai. You tricked him and raped him!
Please don't misunderstand.
And besides, Tougo and I are already well acquainted.
Right, Tougo?
What? Is that true, Tougo!?
Well, um...
Right?
You huge-boobed bitch!
You used some sort of dirty trick, didn't you!?
I did nothing of the sort.
Tougo and I are seriously in love.
What did you say? You huge, saggy-titted bitch!
This deceitful bitch needs to back off.
Stop messing around!
Three days ago...
Tougo...
I want you to do the same thing to me as you did to...
Sorry.
Akiha,
I can't.
Why did you choose her?
Why not me?
I've only had eyes for you since childhood.
We've always been together!
So why?
Why won't you choose me?
A-Akiha...
Tougo, if you won't choose me...
then I'll kill you and kill myself!
Why?
Why her?
Why not me?
Tougo, you idiot!
I love you so much.
I love you so much, Tougo.
So why won't you...
Tougo, you idiot!
Tougo... Tougo!
You're so cruel.
So cruel, Tougo.
Tougo, you've gotten big, and it's hitting against my abdomen.
Akiha...
I'm sorry, Tougo. I'll make you feel really good as an apology.
Tougo's semen...
It was delicious. You're so...
Let's see. This is the hole, right?
Ow, that hurts!
Tougo.
Suzaku-senpai...
She didn't tell me it hurt!
It doesn't hurt at all!
If Suzaku-senpai could do it, then so can I!
Now I'm the same as Suzaku-senpai.
Finally, we're bonded.
Now I belong to you.
And you belong to me.
Stop it, stop it!
Why you, why you...
And so, that's how Tougo and I were finally joined as one.
You're the one who tricked and raped Tougo!
I don't wanna see a scene like that!
To-u-go-kun!
Kitami?
And here we're rooming together. How dare you leave me!
Kitami, what's with that against-school-rules swimsuit!
It's because I'm Tougo-kun's present!
Not!
What a shameful appearance!
And why are you sharing a room with Tougo, for that matter?
Because we're both boys.
Stop becoming a boy when it's convenient!
As Student Council President, I decree a change in rooms!
Naturally, Tougo and I will be roommates.
But why? Tougo is my fiancée!
Tougo-kun is...
the type of guy who loves 'em cute and sexy!
Then you haven't got me beat!
Tougo.
This reminds me of the time we first bonded together.
Would you like to do it again in the pool?
S-Senpai!
No, Tougo. This time, let me please you.
Shit!
They say a man never forgets his first woman.
Let's show him every man's dream: bandage bikini!
If you choose me, you can take these off.
If you're a bandage bikini, then I'm a band-AID bikini!
Oh, my! I get the sensation that the manifestation
of my love with Tougo is already taking shape.
I think you're mistaking the origin of it.
You probably picked up that parasite somewhere else.
This is why I dislike girls of poor breeding.
She's mouthing off in that ridiculous bikini.
What a despicable Student Council President.
You should talk, titty-tiger bitch!
Oh, now you've said it, you slut!
How dare you speak to your Student Council President that way!?
Note: "Seitou Kaichou" means "Student Council Presedent".
Yah! Seitou Kaichou, Seitou Kaichou.
However, it is written here as "Monster Bird Sex Freak".
All this talk will get us nowhere.
Let's duel today and settle once and
for all who Tougo belongs to!
As you wish, Senpai.
Because Tougo belongs to me.
Dueling before the final duel date is prohibited.
That's all!
This reporter is signing off!
What?
Tougo!
Wait up!
I won't let you have him!
Whoa, Akiha-chan!
I won't let you escape!
One-two-one-two-one-two...
Just slipping ahead of you, Akiha.
Try not to drown.
Flag: Natsuhime For Life
I won't lose.
Wait up!
Kitami, cut it out!
I won't let you be taken from me.
Your dick...
Tougo-kun, you're so tasty.
W-Wait!
I can't hold it back!
Tougo-kun's semen...
So this is Tougo-kun's semen.
I want to drink it!
Tougo-kun is inside me. It's so tasty.
Tougo-kun, you're still big.
Take me in my other hole this time.
Tougo-kun...
K-Kitami!
You!
You can't get pregnant, can you?
I'm saved!
Hurry, untie me.
Tougo!
Natsuhime-senpai, let's settle the matter here, okay?
Very well. Let's decide which of us is better for him.
Between me and Akiha,
let's see which of us pleases Tougo more.
Using either mouth or pussy, whichever
one of us gets him to cum more wins.
Amusing.
I've never lost in martial arts or scholastics.
Especially not to a tiger-girl.
When it comes to Tougo, I know everything
about him, down to the moles on his butt.
Then it's a duel!
Ow...
Suzaku-senpai, your pussy is so smooth.
Don't laugh!
It'll pull your nipples off.
Shut up. Your goods are peeping out.
I'm not as big as you down there, Senpai.
I don't really care either way, but could you at least untie me?
A-Akiha...
If you say you'll marry me, I'll untie you.
Suzaku-senpai...
Forget about it. If you just cum in
me right away, it'll be over soon.
Fine. I get it!
Then I guess I'll just fuck both of you over
and over again until you're both pregnant!
In exchange, do exactly as I say.
Yes, darling husband!
Then, both of you lick it.
Yes, husband!
Your wish is my command, husband.
Then, both of you on that boulder.
Stick your asses in the air, spread your
thighs, and show me your pussies.
But really, that's embarrassing!
Is this good, Tougo?
No, no, you need to spread yourself more
Yes, yes, I see your holes want me.
Juices are dripping out of them.
Tougo, this is still embarrassing.
Hurry and put it in, Tougo. I'm embarrassed.
Very well, very well. Don't get jittery.
Tougo! Don't be with just Suzaku-senpai.
Do me too!
Wait your turn, Akiha!
I only have one dick.
Tougo, my pussy is so hot.
Akiha, I didn't know that you were kind or a slut!
No, don't say that.
Ngh! I'm cumming!
Here I cum!
I'm cumming!
Hmm!
Tougo...
Tougo, I'm putting it in, okay?
Easy does it.
Tougo, your nipples are so cute.
This feels kind of strange.
I want it inside of me.
Put it in, please.
It's all her. But I want it too!
Tougo's semen...
Akiha!
I'm cumming! Ngh!
Now Tougo-kun belongs to me.
Good morning, Tougo.
Several months later...
Good morning, Seiryuu.
Good morning, Suzaku-senpai, Akiha.
By the way, Seiryuu, we're setting it straight today.
Which of us will you marry?
Me, of course.
Tougo.
No. It's me, Tougo.
Well, um...
To-u-go-kun!
Good morning!
Good mo...
Kitami?
Kitami-chan, what happened?
...to your belly?
By the power of love, I crossed the gender barrier!
And naturally, the fathe is...
To-u-go-kun!
Seiryuu! How is this possible?
Tougo, don't tell me you screwed a guy as well?
Tougo-kun, what should we name the baby?
Save me!
I'm not marrying anyone!
What did you say?
Then what will happen to our clans?
Wait up, Tougo!
Seiryuu!
Tougo-kun!
I'm fine with being your mistress. Just love me!
Wait a minute.
What happened with the athletics tournament?
Yeah, who won?
I win every year.
What the hell are you saying? I beat you at one thing, at least.
Fat chance.
I defeated the tiger bitch and the bird lady,
and now I'll live a sweet life with Tougo-kun!
Gimme a fucking break!
Bye-bye.
See ya later.
For more details, check out the game!
Hope you do.