It's very good!
Dear Yui-senpai, finally I was selected as a new Lemon Angel member!
But I can't relax now.
It's very good!
Because there are still a lot of things to do.
Hey, hey, don't you think it's weird?
What do you mean, Saya?
Why is Fuyumi in the middle?
Eh?
You all know who should take the number one spot to attract more attention, don't you?
Ah, I'm sorry!
Please continue.
So, please!
Hey, it's not that...
It's me who has to stay in the middle!
M-E!
If it's not me, it's absurd.
Is...?
You're trying to make me look like a clown?!
Ok, ok, I'll take the photo.
Can we make everything right?
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
I want to know you
Right! Left! Right! Left!
Turn.
Tomo-chan!
That hurts!
We stop here today.
Train so that you six synchronize better.
Yes!
Let's all try our best.
Team work!
Good work.
Miki-senpai?
But it's the radio interview after this...
She has other appointments now.
What's that?
"PIN" work?
No... I don't know what's it about...
What's so funny?
Less rivals, better, no?
Rivals?
And today's guests are the new members of Lemon Angel!
Goo-...
Good Afternoon!
Looks like the members were decided through a test...
Yes... and like I imagined, many viewrs went and I got nervous.
Heh... and the other members, how was it?
This girl didn't speak at all in the beginning.
Eh, really?
Yes!
I got nervous with the mistake I made!
You chose a piece from the ones Yui selected during debuts.
Yes, exactly. As her older sister I thought "What will become of her"!
Yes!
And... what shall we do with the main singer?
So now, let me ask about your dreams.
For now, I think only Minaguchi Tomo.
Well... In my dream there was a big cage, but when I woke up, it disappeared.
Hey, not THAT dream!
And your dream, Fuyumi-chan?
I want to be any kind of artist.
They're newbies, but don't they hold their upper lip stiff?
To be... But aren't you already a Lemon Angel?
Ah, something different from Lemon Angel.
Hey!
A-Ah, no! Well...
What do you mean by different? You're thinking of abandoning Lemon Angel in the middle?
Yumi? Is that it?
That's a shock!
No, it's not that...
I guess she's apt...
Nagisa Miru.
What?
If you analyze the capacity to sing, only she is appropriate.
Miru?
So, and your dream Miru-chan?
Me?
I want to be Ann.
Ann as in Ann the first Angel, I want to be the main singer.
Miru-chan...
Looks like that's what she wants...
But...
An audition!
Huh?
Minaguchi or Nagisa, we'll decide who is going to be the main singer through a test.
Right?
These were the new Lemon Angel members!
Thank you very much!
Have you all decided on your signatures for the autographs this afternoon?
AH!? The signature? What do I do?
Ah, it's easy... Look!
Látod!
Wow... incredible!
See mine.
What do you think?
Wow... cool!
And yours Yumi?
Ahm... I thought about it, but...
It's this.
Don't you think it's cute?
It's cute, but...
You can't really call that a signature...
I'm sorry... I was having fun while I was writing, and so...
And yours, Miru-chan?
Beautiful handwriting, but isn't that Shuuji?
And yours, Tomo?
Yes, please write!
Can I do it?
That's... writing?
It's Japanese worm!
Hey, isn't that a bit cruel?
It's not so bad...
Of course!
You all got together to make fun of me?
Kogure-san!
Huh?!
Kogure-san is choosing the song for your debut.
How exciting!
Debut song...
But is it alright to let him choose such an important piece?
He doesn't look too dependable...
Yesterday there was a time when Nani-sensei was very mad with him.
Is it true?
Well, Gure is working hard in his own way.
Gure?
Yes, I decided that his nickname will be Gure.
Good idea!
Poor fellow, you shouldn't nickname him without him being here!
If it's to nickname someone, nickname someone who is here.
Rabbit!
Rabbit? Now that i think of it, Gure's better!
So it's decided!
Okay!
Could it be a cold?
Himuro and Kudou?
And also Kazanaho.
Miki? Weren't you supposed to be in the interview?
It's not my work.
But when you, the leader, aren't there, the group discipline will...
Anyway,go to where everyone is.
You're late!
Can we really do it?
Yes, it came as a confirmation from her. There's no mistake.
Isn't it a trap?
It's your job to examine, isn't it?
Got it... Let me work steadily.
She's late.
Normally you're all getting along fine, right?
Of course, because we all respect each other.
What? Saya, you always say that i'm a fool.
Hey, don't say unnecessary things!
Me too... Saya-san always gets mad at me.
Hey, hey, it's all a joke!
It's not a joke... Saya's eyes are always serious when she speaks.
Ahhh... Leader!
No need to stay so thoughtful.
Hey, wait, what is it?
What were those three doing?
Could it be... again...?
An internal audition?
What's that?
Whoever wins this internal audition will be the new main vocal of Lemon Angel.
The ones who will participate in this audition will be Miru and Tomo, you two.
What? Me?
Just a minute...
I don't agree with that!
Saya.
Why only these two?
Well, it's because--
Normally, the best one is chosen to be the lead, right?
Yes, but...
If it's like that, I'm the main one!
If you start with that opinion...
Say it, Gure!
What? "Gure"?
Yes! I invented it.
Fits nicely.
Hey, hey, without my permission!
Gure, I'll also participate in this audition.
What? Wait!
You want to face the producer?
Gure, stay quiet.
Erika and Fuyumi?
I don't want.
I'll leave this to you.
So, it will be the three of us.
I wasn't expecting this...
Miru and Tomo, you'll participate?
I'll do it.
I want to be Ann.
If there's no other way than to do it, I'll become the new Ann.
Miru-chan.
So, this Saturday, at 1700 hours, the internal audition will be held.
The participants will be Saya and Miru, and also Tomo, These three.
Is this Ok?
It is.
This Saturday.
What? Next Saturday?
Let me see... actually Himuro asked you to go.
Yui-senpai...
I...
I'll really be back by the afternoon, right?
Sure.
It won't take much time.
Ah, got it...
In the afternoon--
Only... if you yourself choose to go back.
Maybe you'll choose otherwise.
This is Himuro Shinya's studio.
A-Amazing!
Drums,I don't need you anymore.
You're not following my instructions...
You're instructions?
Hey. I'm not your robot.
I can improvise a bit, right?
No need to improvise beyond the arrangement which I've done.
What?
Is that music?
Enough!
This is your "live music"?
What did you say?
Stop!
Let me go!
Hey, Himuro.
Anyway, hurry up!
Yes, yes.
Working together with Himuro Shinya was Kohno Yui's dream.
Really?
Lemon Angel was born with a Kohno Yui and Himuro Shinya collaboration.
Yes.
And why's it necessary to continue without him now?
Because...
Lemon Angel, without Himuro, will not make the expected success.
Suwa Miki and Kogure only want to use the Lemon Angel's name to win money.
It's wrong, the two aren't...
So why not make exactly like the original?
Because Himuro transmits the Kohno Yui's spirit.
It's no use...
We don't have anymore time.
Leave her be.
You don't choose as the main singer a person who is late to an important test.
Miki-senpai.
Isn't today the test for the main vocal?
It's because, senpai...
Actually, until a while ago, I was at Himuro's studio...
Himuro?
I don't mind if you want to quit being a Lemon Angel.
Sakura no hanabira hirahira maifurite ikuyouni
Cherry petals fall like snow
Listen to the truth about Yui's death and then decide.
Odayakana
Calmly
The truth?
Kokoro hitoride mitsumeteta
Looking for only a unique soul
Kanashiniha ataerareta wakega aru
Has a reason to offer
Dareni demo
To anyone
Yasashisano tane naraba kichinto sodate ikou
Treat well the goodness' seeds.
Maybe... I could be like Ann.
Miru's song is really very nice.
I promise you kitto
I surely promise you
Hey, and mine?
Of course Saya's song was also good!
You make it sound like mine was worse.
Don't look back kitto
Don't look back, surely
Oh, come on.
Thank you very much.
What happened to Tomo?
If it continues like this...
Tomo.
I'm sorry for being late!
Tomo!
You're late!
I-I'm sorry!
Tomo, you can sing, can't you?
Yes!
Yui-senpai.
Almost a year and a half ago, Yui and I built an artificial intelligence named Lemon Angel.
Nagai kaidan nobori tsuzukete
Climbing the long stairs
Through Nouvelle, Angel was exposed to the public and attracted a lot of attention.
Tadoritsuita doa nokku shita no
When I arrived, I knocked at the door
And Nouvelle, thinking that this project would be good business...
Omoi tobiraga hiraite soshite
Opening the heavy door
...hired a producer.
Deaeru hazu, datta... Minna no egao ni
I surely would find ... Everyone with happy faces
That producer was Himuro Shinya.
But the Angels were changing like that man directed.
Doushite? Maru de shiranai hito mitai
Why? They look like unknown people
Doushite? Tsumetai kotoba kizutsukeru
Why? The cold words hurt
Like that, they were nothing but marionettes.
This sort of music isn't yours, Yui!
This isn't the Lemon Angels you wanted to build.
I know that, but it's no use.
Searching for myself
Hajimete no kanjou hitomi kumorasete
The iris, the first feelings
Why!?
Taking that man off the project is easy, isn't it?
If it continues like this, that man...
Stop!
Stop speaking bad about him!
Searching for myself
Utagau koto shika dekinaku narisou
Maybe I could only reach
Yui, trapped between her feelings for Lemon Angels and her love for Himuro,
Kono mamaja iya hayaku ~Watashi wo Sagashite~
Don't want to be like this fast ~Find me~
thought about a solution.
That was to hack the Lemon Angels and destroy that archive.
Posing as a hacker named Arukan whom she invented, she destroyed the Artificial Intelligence that she built herself.
With that, she thought she was finally free.
And then she told him about it.
But that man told Yui to rebuild those archives.
Nagai yume kara mezameteshimau
I just woke up from a long dream
Eh?
So what was that?
What do you mean by "What was that?"
Mabushi suguiru sora zutto miteru
I look toward a very bright sky
Me... you...
Yui, you're a very talented person.
But looks like your mistaking things.
Kagami no naka no kokoro ha kitto
Surely, the soul inside the mirror
I have absolutely no interest in you, unless it's for the programs that you make.
Naiteru hazu, nanoni ... kinou to onnaji ne
Surely, it's crying ... like yesterday
For him, flirting with Yui was nothing important.
Doushite? Nanimo nakatta koto ni shite
Why pretend that nothing happened?
He only wanted a program that could give economic power to his own music.
Doushite? Onnaji uta wo utaeru no?
Why can't I sing the same music?
And when after that illusion-shattering conversation, Yui left Nouvelle...
Searching for myself
Hajimete no henka wo chanto uketomeyou
Accept perfectly the first transformation
That's the truth.
S-So Yui-senpai...
What you'll do, is left for you to decide.
Searching for myself
Inouru you ni tada mamoru to shiteru
Trying to protect me through prayers
Tsuyokunaritai no dakara ~Watashi wo Sagashite~
I want to be strong so ~Find me~
Ohh...
Tomo song... sure has changed.
Looks like it now touches the soul deeper.
Hoshi mo mienai to iu kono machi no yoru demo
Even in this town that you don't see stars at night
That is...
Very good.
...Ann.
Chiisa na hikari sagasu youni...
Like searching for a little light...
Tomo is really good!
I got all emotional!
In addition to coming late, you made us listen to a song like this...
Can't help it, I acknowledge you.
Saya!
Make Tomo the main singer!
Is it alright?
It has to be her.
It's ok, Tomo?
It's decided. Well, it means she's not so useless after all.
Yui.
I thought I could have been Ann, but you can surpass her.
M-Miru-chan.
Good evening.
Ah, it's you.
I'll build the real Lemon Angel.
Ok, with Himuro?
No.
How's that?
I want to sing Yui-senpai's music with everyone.
You'll regret it.
If I regret it...
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
Tomo-chan, and the training?
I'll boycott such meaningless training.
But he's a singer's coach. Wouldn't it be bad to do that?
I don't care... I can't keep up that meaningless training.
Kogure-san isn't here either, looks like it's going to turn into a big mess.
On the next Lemon Angel Project, episode 8: "Summer Angels in the Resort's Forest."
I hate the mustache demon!!!
Mustache demon?? You're referring to director Katahige?
Angels Of The Summer Resort's Forest