www.SubDESU-H.net
UD Academy
Cheerleading Club
Wait Onee-san...
I-I can run by myself.
Makoto left you in my charge,
so this is me being stubborn.
Let me show off.
As expected of Makoto's lover.
You've got a butt that competes with mine.
Looks like this bunch is excited to see it.
Damn it.
You really got a great butt.
Epidemic Disaster Outbreak
Hanazawa-senpai...
No...!
If you want your brother released, obey my orders.
I'm not going to lose no matter what you do to my body.
Hey.
If you can still say that after one hour,
then I'll let you and your brother go.
I will hold you to your word then.
W
Kansen
One    「Rape Harem」
Don't avert your eyes, lady Akane.
You love that kid, right?
He's really grown down there despite having such a cute face.
Thanks to the pheromones you and your friends released,
things have gotten restless here.
Mako-senpai...
Just hold on for a little more, Makoto.
I'll definitely save you!
What are you... doing?
Stop that...
No...
Stop...
Your face has started to look more feminine now.
Stop fooling around!
Makoto... I'll resist this
and we'll leave here together...
Here, eat up.
That's quite bold for a kid.
What a slut!
Your family has shunned the world and continued their research on it, right?
It progresses very slowly,
so until the brain falls apart
it preserves the infected one's personality.
Are you more interested in that one?
You bitchy whore!
Don’t say such rude things!
Why don’t you try masturbating over there?
Just like last night.
Tokyo kids are really an erotic bunch!
Something really big is in me.
I just can't get enough of that expression of yours when I insert my cock.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Just how much do you like cocks?
It's good.
Get pregnant.
Get pregnant!
I'm going to that it to you as well.
I won’t accept that you trashy pervert!
You're not very honest with yourself, are you?
Stop!
Damn...
Why is this...
So you can still put up a face like that.
Such a cute girl.
Don’t mess with me, you trashy pervert!
Now it’s ready.
You slutty bitch!
Dammit...
This is unfair...
I hope you won’t forget this trashy pervert's cock.
You're hitting the same spots over and over again.
A confused look on the face.
That means nipples are your pleasure spots.
You pervert!
My nipples... don't feel good at all...
Damn...
Don't move.
Don't dig deep into that part.
Your pussy seems to be really sensitive.
I can see it in that orgasmic face of yours.
No, no!
Why don’t you show your slacken face to your brother?
Try to give him assurances with that aroused voice of yours.
No.
That's not it...
Makoto!
No...
What's this?
Your pussy's lewdly trying to pull me in, you sow!
Where’s your spirit from earlier?
Your pussy's already broken!
Stop...
Stop already.
Don’t release it inside.
No way.
Squeeze it in.
Hold it tight while I release my cum inside.
No, it's coming out.
Stop...
Get pregnant.
Get pregnant right now!
This thing went around inside me a lot of times earlier.
Damn, it’s still hot.
It's still stiff even after releasing that much cum.
I don’t know anymore.
What's happening to me?
When I take it all in my mouth, it suddenly feels good.
Don’t move anymore!
Shall I make your desires come true too?
I shall bring out everything as I dig in here.
I'm sorry, Makoto.
Big sis is gonna lose.
His cock is just too great for me.
Now I understand why the lady likes you, boy.
You release quite a lot.
There, it came out.
You can't endure it anymore, can you?
Sorry to keep you waiting, you sow.
www.SubDESU-H.net