Takamine Chika.
Extremely beautiful, and has amazing boobs to boot.
If Takamine became a Public Comfort Station,
it'd be really bad.
It's because of her appearance.
None of the boys in school would keep silent.
She'd be raped anywhere.
Will be always cummed inside of.
And would be constantly drenched in sticky liquids.
She would get a taste of a hellish pleasure that has no end.
This womanly style looks rather cute on you...
Ryou.
Or should I say, my dear Comfort Station.
Are you feeling horny with your asshole now?
It's already getting big.
No, you can't go wild just yet.
Just keep on giving me pleasure.
Just keep it up.
Pathetically.
Shamefully.
How unsightly.
And you even squeal like a woman.
Even more lewd and obscene.
Here, take this reward.
Well?
Does it feel good?
If it does, then try to bark.
Say "woof, woof!"
Woof!
How cute.
Here I go.
I'm cumming.
Sex Tool. Takamine Chika
Sign: Please use the Public Comfort Station neatly.
It won't stop.
My body...
Ryou, hurry up and come to me.
Ryou....!
You there, the one holding that bag.
Can we bother you for a while?
We have a little request.
Please, okay?
Let's play.
Ryou?
Sorry, but I'm not Ryou.
Oh, and one other thing.
He's not coming.
I think right now he's already...
Looks cute, it really suits you.
No resting now.
Wow, that's a nice moan.
Have some more of my cock.
Then I'll have yours.
It's thick, and delicious.
Release it.
Release lots of it, into my mouth.
I want some more.
Give me more.
More, more...
This is really good.
We're just getting started.
Suck everything, and don't leave a stain on it.
Just enjoy it with everybody else, okay?
Stop...
Let me go.
No...
Pull it out.
Pull it out...!
His cock is hitting my insides.
It's thrusting very deep inside.
You're getting really wet here.
I'm going to cum lots inside, okay?
Stop.
That's cute.
I'm cumming now.
I'm cumming.
It's coming out.
Please no.
Stop this.
Stop!
Please...!
I don't want this.
No...!
That's a great facial expression.
Let's enjoy it some more then, Takamine.
Oh wow, these are some tender boobs!
I'm cumming in your mouth now.
Drink it all up, okay?
It seems you're getting quite horny already.
You know...
I want you to feel the ecstasy more.
It's true.
Oh, so this spot is good eh?
Here, rub, rub, rub.
Your expression shows the ecstasy that you feel all over.
It looks a lot cuter.
Now then, I'm going to make you cum.
I think it's about time that I get my part of the service.
Oh no...
My body... feels too weak already...
Here, lets put mine in.
I love that expression... it says "you're nothing but some jerk".
Your body seems to be feeling great.
Ryou!
They've already started.
He's under these girls now,
he will fall into his pleasures, and become their sex toy.
If you want pleasure as well, you'd better cooperate obediently.
Right now.
That's great.
It went all the way in immediately.
What's wrong?
You can move if you want to.
Indulge in your own pleasures.
This feels great, Takamine.
These freaks...
They're playing with Ryou...
And...
I'm also...
Your hips are shaking.
Give up already?
Feels great, doesn't it?
See, what a nice moan you have.
Let me hear some more of that.
Give it to us as well.
Okay Takamine?
Here, say "ah."
More...
More...!
I can't stop...
Great words.
Give me some service too.
My body is...
More...
Here, Takamine.
Hey, hey, don't push her too much.
What? She likes cocks, right?
See?
Here l go Takamine.
Please make me cum.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Ryou, I'm sorry, I...
I'm no longer.
Why don't we inish this by peeing on her?
Do you feel happy Takamine?
Pee...
I'm happy...
We're still far from finished, Takamine.
Yes.
I can't turn back.
Takamine, you're our sex tool from now on.
We'll just make it look like you openly volunteered for it.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Now that's a really interesting expression.
What a waste of his beautiful face.
Vibrator, incoming!
Our dear servant.
Our sex tool.
Let me hear them...
Your climaxing screams.
Here, get on with it already.
Woah, that some face she's got.
Oh but look, it seems like she's enjoying it.
Takamine?!
No way, she really became a Public Comfort Station?
You're kidding, right?
Everyone's looking.
Looking at my unsightly self.
How terrible.
Look at her face.
But, I think...
I like it.
Jerk!
Takamine.
She's going to take it in, right?
While everybody's watching.
I'm...
Do you understand now?
You really are a Public Comfort Station, since we've come to this.
Takamine...
So she really did became one.
This is really terrible.
It's as if she's some wild animal or something.
No, this looks disgusting!
I'm really disappointed in her.
This can't be real, right Takamine-san?
I want to be seen.
I want to be seen more.
It feels great to be watched.
I'm already...
Even my heart and mind have accepted
the fate of a Public Comfort Station.
Look, everyone.
Look at how a Public Comfort Station finishes it.
I'm cumming.
Takamine.
Takamine, let's do it too.
Can I, Ishida?
Go ahead.
Ain't this great Takamine?
Everyone said they're going to 'use' you.
We'll all make sure to take good care of you.
Oh, but I won't do it that way.
Because I'm going to use her like a torn rag.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...
Your cocks... feel very good...
Your girlfriend is being used as a Public
Comfort Station even as we speak.
That's really cute of her.
I have to go.
I have to save her.
Chika.
Chika!
You're getting a little too noisy.
Wait for me.
I'm coming to get you, Chika!
Just shut up, will you?
Give it up already.
You're now our slave.
Onee-sama, that's not enough.
You also need to tell him physically, not just verbally.
It's gotten big already.
Like a wild monkey.
But that's okay.
Be horny all you want.
Onee-sama, the front please.
Here.
Chika...
Chika...!
Shut up.
Hey, take it in properly will you?
You said something there?
Not me.
This really feels good.
Why don't you give up?
She may have forgotten about you already.
Even if you reach her, it might be too late.
I want to...
...see Chika...
It fell out again.
Her ass just isn't that great.
Why don't we insert a plastic bottle then.
Oh, it fits quite perfectly.
Now, start yappin' will ya?
Wow, look.
It looks like she's really enjoying it.
Stop saying her name already!
If you really want to save her, then why don't you just do it?
Chika!
I'm cumming.
This Comfort Station is just no good.
She just cums too quickly.
She's totally a sex tool now.
Chika!
Somebody  hold him down!
Ryou!
Chika!
Chika won't be returning to you.
Now, show it to him.
Stop!
There, that's how you do it.
It felt great taking all of our cocks in, right?
Don't look, Ryou...
It feels like it suddenly got tighter.
Watching closely from over there, Ryou-kun?
She's really enjoying it.
You want this, right?
Look, she's even shedding tears of joy!
That's really great.
I never thought she'd really feel that great.
Chika...
Now let's show him your cum.
While he can still see you clearly.
Ryou...
Please don't look.
It feels good.
Yes, that feels great Chika-chan.
Ryou is watching me...
Just look how she's really enjoys it, her
pussy's getting really wet and tight
That's right, just let yourself go Takamine.
That's good.
Besides, you're already a Public Comfort Station.
You two aren't meant for each other.
Lies!
I'm sorry...
Oh please, you don't really feel that way.
Say "It feels good".
Ishida-sama's cock... feels good.
See?
It feels good.
Ishida-sama's cock, feels good.
That's right.
Ishida-sama's cock, feels good....
Ishida-sama's cock, feels good...!
Your cock, feels good.
Good girl, Chika.
Ryou, I'm sorry.
I'm a Public Comfort Station now.
After that Takamine Chika was raped by
all of the boys in front of Sakurai Ryou.
Wow, she's really covered in cum.
Feeling happy already?
You're a great Public Comfort Station, Takamine Chika.
Comfort Station... Comfort Station...
Get off me!
Chika!
Chika.
Ryou.
Yeah.
I'm here at last.
You have no place here.
You can just leave.
Shut up!
Chika's a Comfort Station?!
And she can no longer turn back?
That's bullshit!
Then I'll have to try my hardest too!
Because I'm also a Public Comfort Statibn!
Chika is my Comfort Station!
And I'm her Comfort Station!
Anyone got a problem with that?!
I love Chika!
Shall I now?
Yes, yes you can.
You really can.
I...
I also love you.
I love you too.
Me too.
I love you.
I love you...
I love you very much.
I love you.
I love you!
I love you, Ryou.
I love you.
I love you...
I love you!
I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you! I love you!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum now.
Cum, and I'll cum too.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
A plan that surpassed a Public Comfort Station?
Damn.