Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
out of my control.
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokani no dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
Dear Yui-senpai, I've made it past the first round of selections!
At this point, I just have to give it my best effort.
That's what I'd really like to be saying right now, However...
No one told me there'd be a swimsuit photoshoot right away!
Okay, here we go!
Yes, yes. Smile, smile, smile.
Be more lovely... And there we go.
Yes, that's good. You're very cute!
But you can be even cuter. Okay, relax.
Mmm, so cute! Keep it up!
This time...show me a wonderful pose.
Okay, pose!
Okay!
Great! Now give me another one!
Okay, then how's this?
I'll take it!
Okay, now try moving around more!
1, 2, 1, 2.
Elegant! Most wonderful!
Oh, this is the ideal Japanese beauty.
Step, step!
What's up with her? Way lame!
That's it, show me some more!
What is she doing?
Yay!
Yes, Okay.
Thank you very much.
You sure are an interesting child. That was great. Do your best during the next part, too.
Uh, okay. Thank you.
Okay, everyone take five! I have to powder my nose.
Hey, Tomo! Japanese radio dance is so wonderful. It moved me.
I might actually be cut out for this modeling thing.
Hah. Flailing around like that, and not realizing you're making yourself the laughing stock? Stupid.
Eh?
Since you have connections with the producer, i guess it doesn't matter how much of a laughing stock you become.
And I keep telling you...
Quit playing dumb! There's no way someone like you would be here without connections.
After all, how could a child like you expect to be in a swimsuit photoshoot? Underestimating the job, amateur?
What do you think you're doing?
Saya, you have a nice bust. I'm envious.
Huh? You picking a fight?
Okay, sorry to keep you waiting...
Next is Yuki Saya-san.
Ah, Okay.
She's not very nice.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Thank you for having me.
Okay. Well, let's start.
All right, good. That's the spirit.
Excellent!
SEXY!
Beautiful!
Great!
Oh, marvelous!
Wow.
Pros sure are a step above.
You're doing great!
What was that you said?
You can't come in, we're in the middle of a photoshoot. Only people involved are allowed in...
Shaddup! Who the hell do you think i am?
Oi! Yayoi! Yayoi, where are you?
Well, well, there you are.
Who's that? He looks like trouble.
He's the head of Ophelia. They say he's got family connections.
Yo. What's this? Weren't you gonna go off and sing?
President Muroi.
Rather than continuing this out here, let's retire to a meeting room.
That's right, we wouldn't want to be in everyone's way.
Yuki-san, too.
Everyone, please continue with the photoshoot.
MEETING ROOM -A-
Why the hell did you come here?!
I asked you why the hell you came here?!
Yuki-san...
Hoshi Yayoi, 16. Associated with Ophelia. You said you quit last month, right?
That's right. I'm no longer Hoshi Yayoi. I'm Yuki Saya.
NO. You are still Hoshi Yayoi. Hey, Shikina.
Yayoi-chan, Ophelia still hasn't annulled the contract you signed.
Huh?
Which means if you don't go through us, you can't work.
You're lying.
Kogure-san, if she were selected to become part of the Lemon Angels,
then she would become part of Nouvelle Music, wouldn't she?
That's true.
If that happened, then you'd be in breach of contract, Yayoi.
But you said i was fired!
As if. You're an important talent of ours.
Quit jerking me around!
Yuki-san.
Kogure-san, this isn't the sort of trouble you want. I'll expect compensation.
Understood. Once the higher-ups have evaluated the situation, i will get back in touch with you.
Great. Later, Kogure-kun.
Hey, Shikina, get your ass in gear.
Yuki-san, I intend to back the talent i've chosen, but you're still a part of Ophelia.
That fact can't be changed.
Hey!
I wonder what's up with Saya.
Yeah.
Is that one of the legendary gangsters? Maffia?
I think you might be wrong.
Ahh... wait, why am i worrying about Yuki-san? Just thinking about her pisses me off.
Yuki-san?
She looks a little upset.
Yeah.
Show your face, pops! Open up, dammit!
What do you think you're doing?
I should ask you the same thing. Stop meddling in my life!
Let me go! Put me down you...!
Now you should be a little more grateful.
Hand it over!
It's because i appreciate your value. I came all this way to bring you back.
Cut it out!
What was that?
Hmph. As i said, as long as i have this contract, you're mine. You'll never be a part of the Lemon Angels.
Give that back, you coward!
Don't worry, you'll have plenty of work. I'll get my money's worth out of that body.
I'm not going to let someone like you throw my dreams away!
Give it a rest already.
Understand, if you want to continue to work in this town, your only choice is to return to me, Got it?!
Hey! I'm not done talking! Pops!
Ah, what to do.
Just do whatever you want.
This is just great.
Did you see that? How frustrated Yayoi looked!
Umm, boss...
Huh?
I think it would be better to take into account Yayoi-chan's feelings in the matter.
She doesn't have that much talent. Besides, i thought of an interesting promotion.
A really sexy Lemon Angel candidate photobook. It'll sell great.
Saya, you okay?
This has nothing to do with you two. Don't butt in.
How can you say that?
Dammit! What can i do?
That twisted old jerk. Even if i return, there's no way he'll let me go back to work.
And after i finally made a chance for myself, i have to end it here.
Dammit, then having those amateurs come and pity me, that takes the cake!
Huh, i never took you to be so pitiful. You know, given the way things stand...
I know!
Why not just go and steal the contract back?
Just kidding.
That's the only choice left.
Hey, i was just trying to make a joke.
I'm going to sneak my way into Ophelia!
Wow! Sneak! I've always admired Japanese ninja!
Uhh, that's not what...
That's not quite what's going on here.
Fine. You can come along.
Umm, isn't it illegal...
It was your idea, so you'll be coming along too.
But, but...
Let's go, Tomo.
Dear Yui-senpai, I'm becoming a criminal!
I am a Japanese ninja.
Death is the code of the Samurai.
Umm, I think you have the wrong idea.
Does it look good on me?
Uh, yeah. By the way, what's that?
That's my ninja sword.
I don't see a blade... whoa!
It's actually a nightstick. A real one would require ignoring the law.
Uh, yeah...
Hey! How long are you two gonna play around? It's almost time.
You know, maybe this isn't...
Emergency Exit
Come on, we shouldn't be doing this... What are you saying? We've already come this far!
But...
Can it!
You're working late!
Oh, Yayoi. Didn't you quit?
Totally not.
Oh, okay.
By the way, where's the boss?
Huh? That old fart? He left an hour ago.
Is that so?
Huh? Who are the two girls behind you?
Uh, oh, they're a few talents that want to join up.
Emergency Exit
Huh? T-Talents?
You two, be sure to watch Yayoi and learn well.
She's always working late taking singing and dancing lessons.
Oh?
Working until she can barely stand up.
Cut it out.
Don't be modest, it's the truth.
Hmmm? Oh?
What?!
Oh, nothing.
Ah! Someone's here.
Please, i'm asking you to just talk to...
Oh...
Yes. But if you could just listen to the demo.
She was with the boss here earlier today.
Yes. Ah, her premiere didn't work out.
Please, I would like to find her a singing job if at all possible.
Of course. She's an unusual one, willing to work hard to succeed.
Yes. Oh. Isn't there anything you can do?
Okay. Please.
Of course she hasn't worked as a singer yet...
Yayoi-chan?
Keiko-san, you don't need to do this, since i have no intention of returning.
Anyway, do you know where the contract is?
You can't...
You can't do this. If you were caught...
I don't have a choice.
Umm, are these...
Saya's recordings?
Yeah. They have demo songs on them.
This many?
Keiko-san, any singing jobs?
No. Only photoshoots.
Sorry. And this time it'll be some pretty risque swimsuits.
That's okay.
Huh?
I'm still working my way up, so i can't complain.
Wow! How'd you manage to borrow a place like this?
Don't let the boss know.
You mean, your money's paying...
Don't worry about it. It's all part of a manager's job.
This is no time to be down. Now go in there, make some demos, and sell, sell, sell!
'kay.
I'm sorry, Yayoi-chan. I didn't have the pull to arrange anything better.
Nonsense. It's finally a singing job, and you went all out to get it for me.
That's plenty.
And the fact that there are actually a few people interested in hearing me sing makes me happy.
I thank you for all you've done, but as long as that boss is still here, there's no chance.
I want to grab hold of the chance standing right before me, and to do that, I'll do whatever it takes.
Thank you.
Come on you two, let's hurry up and look for that contract.
Wait! It's not here.
Hmph, don't let important things out of your sight?
It's what I'd expect from him.
All right!
Find it?
That's odd. I remember it was right here this afternoon.
Everyone...!
You can search all night and not find it.
You four disgust me, stooping so low as to attempt this sham of a burglary.
Boss, this is all my fault...
Silence!
Listen carefully, Yayoi, and I'll fill you in on something.
If you think you can make it under your own power, you're mistaken!
Don't get full of yourself!
Yuki-san...
Kids should know their place.Just pay attention to what I  tell you!
That's not true. What makes you think that that's how things should be?
Yuki-san is working her hardest. To achieve her dreams, she's going all out!
Why can't you see that? Destroying her dreams is cruel!
Hey...
Let me go! Let me go, dammit!
Let me go!
Even if you do as you're told, don't give up! Otherwise, you'll just be a puppet.
That's enough.
Huh?
Yayoi-chan...
It's just as the boss says. I've just been living in a dream.
You're right after all. Talents are just a product to peddle, and shouldn't presume to have dreams.
Boss, I'll return to Ophelia.
Well, well, as long as you understand that...
Y-You bitch.
Like hell I'm coming back to the likes of you! You twisted old man!
How dare you kick me...
Hey boss.
Ouch!
Jesus!
Are you prepared?
I'll never do as you say!
I'm gonna achieve my dreams under my own power!
Like hell! Don't think you're gonna get away with this scot-free!
I'm calling the cops!
Boss, will you please stop this?
What was that?
How the hell do you know about...?
So i guess it's okay to tell your wife as well.
Do whatever you want.
Move! You're in my way! And get out! You're both fired!
Bastard! How long are you planning on sleeping on the job? You're useless!
Boss, very no...
Ah, thank God.
Keiko-san, you know everything, don't you?
Sorry, it's my fault that you were fired too, Keiko-san.
No, don't worry about it. You should be focusing on your dreams.
Keiko-san...
But next time don't do something this reckless.
Well, since you have connections, you've got nothing to worry about.
That again? Give it a rest already.
But you were talking all friendly with Kogure-san.
Huh?
He's talked to me too.
Eh?
He's pretty friendly.
But!
Yayoi-chan, is the Lemon Angels a group where connections can get someone in?
Uh...
It isn't, is it?
Oh. That means Saya jumped to conclusions.
You're too hasty!
What! It's because your skill level is way too low!
hey boss...
Excuse the intrusion, but I'd like to talk to you about Yuki Saya.
Hmph. I fired her.
Huh?
Just go do whatever you want!
Dammit, why'd she kick me...!
Fired?
Hey, hey. The lessons that start today, what do you think they'll be like?
I was so worried, that I couldn't sleep last night.
I'm so nervous.
Dear Yui-senpai, the picture taken at that photoshoot was horrible,
though, thankfully, it wasn't very big.
Someday I'll be able to do a pose as a cool...
Huh?
You couldn't do it even if you had a hundred years to learn.
What do you mean by that?
Exactly what you think it means.
After all, with that flat chest, it doesn't matter what pose you try.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
You should talk, what with all this extra padding you have.
Leave that alone! I'm in the middle of a diet!
Oh? And you're flabby here too!
What are you saying, you flat-chested child!
Stop saying flat-chested!
What's wrong with calling someone flat-chested, when they are flat-chested? Stop that!
Can't those two give it a rest? Way uncool.
What was that, Miss Flabby?
Flat-chested! Flat-chested!
Don't worry. Tomo and Saya are just good friends.
Flabby! Flabby!
What was that?
Hey, Fuyumi!
Flabby!
Ah, yeah.
Care to say that again?!
I'll show you, no matter what!
Well, if you work at it, you might be ready in ten years or so.
Look, that's what...
Wait, didn't you just call me by my name?
So? What of it?
Hey, you two, if you don't hurry, you'll be late!
Ah! Oh, no!
It's all your fault we're going to be late, Tomo!
What was that?!
Yui-senpai, I'll do my best!
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...they become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time
DANCE STUDIO A
Eh?! Fuyumi-chan! Erica is the older sister of that Takumi?
Having a younger brother in the group Third Sense is great.
She's so lucky! Wait, so the reason Erica is auditioning for Lemon Angel is to keep up with her brother?
Next time, Lemon Angel Project number 4, "Smile Means Love."
Now that you mention it, didn't you hear a cell phone playing one of Third Sense's songs?
I wonder who's it was?