Kamoshige Arimiya.
He has ruled this region as governor for over 40 years.
There have been nasty rumors going around...
...about the way he has been able to stay in power for so long.
But, the way he was able to threaten people and stay in power...
...was his sensuality which far exceeded other's.
He had married nine times.
And on top of that, countless lovers...
When he saw beautiful women...
...he used his money and power to get every one of them.
Mr. Gouda, are you leaving now?
Oh, Miss Yuhara. Say hello to the madam for me.
But, those dark days...
Of course.
Have a nice day.
...are finally over.
That monster Kamoshige died all of a sudden.
He died of heart failure.
With his death, everyone thought that their suffering would come to an end.
But...
Katori.
Good job.
But, many people at this Arimiya Tower are...
...plotting to take the power and fortune...
Good job to you too, Miss Shoko.
...left behind by the late Kamoshige.
What do you think about my daughters?
l think they're all beautiful.
You can tell me the truth, you know.
They may be cute, but they're all sly.
They give me such a headache...
And so, l have to ask you for a favor.
Yes?
l want you to rape all three of my daughters.
Excuse me.
Hold it right there!
Oh, Lady Misora.
You just came out from my mother's room.
l wonder what you talked about this late in the day.
l was just asking her about my work from here on.
This late at night?
You two all alone in my mother's room?
You...
You're Kadono's son, aren't you?
l knew it.
Your father was fired as a safekeeper on corruption charges.
What did you sneak in here for?
Sneak in? You have to be joking.
You even used the false name Katori. What are you planning to do?
There's been a misunderstanding!
Come with me...
l misunderstood? Then, tell me the truth.
After my father died, l was asked to come here.
lt was Master Kamoshige's wish.
Oh, l see.
So, l don't see why l should be treated like a trespasser.
But, you could've refused, right?
Well, yes, but...
Do you want to team up with me?
What are you talking about?
You heard about it, right?
From your late father.
Money that was stashed by Arimiya.
My father didn't leave me anything.
Serves him right.
Kadono told you about it, right?
About what?
The PIN for the safe with his money!
lf you find out, what are you going to do?
l'm going to outwit that bitch!
The person who has access to that money...
...will also gain power and become the successor to Arimiya.
l can't just watch that bitch get all that money!
l see.
By the way, if l decide to team up with you...
...what will l get in return?
What do you want?
Money?
Or...
This way.
Steamy hot.
That feels good!
lt's very sticky.
You really wanted this, huh?
No! That's not true!
l'm about to...
Climax?
Then climax!
lt looks like you're the only one who climaxed.
l'll make you feel good.
Amazing...
lt's so big.
Well? What do you have to say about this?
Yeah...not bad at all.
Oh, l see...
You're satisfied now, right?
l don't know about that.
But, it's not fair for you to keep doing me like this.
l have to make you feel good too.
Wait a minute!
No!
Don't!
You may be saying no...
...but your body is saying yes.
Well, here l come...
Yes...
How do you feel, my lady?
No, l'll come!
l'll climax!
Then, let's do this!
My boobs...
Play with my boobs!
Sure.
l did as you asked, my lady.
How do you feel?
Yes! That's it!
That feels so good!
Amazing...it's amazing!
l think l'm about to...
Shall we climax?
l'm coming.
So hot...
l want you to rape all three of my daughters.
What did you just say?
You're surprised because you heard what l said, right?
But don't get the wrong idea.
l'm not asking you to rape them by force.
l want you to teach them the happiness of a woman.
Happiness of a woman...
Basically...
...what do you want me to do?
Now that Master Kamoshige has died...
...you're the one who has all the power in the Arimiya family.
But, your daughters and a number of others don't approve of you.
Since you're just a stepmother...
...your daughters only think of you as a thief that's after the inheritance.
You're pretty smart.
l'll be honest with you.
l want you to make my daughters into women...
...and make them do anything you say.
By using that.
l'm sure...
l'm sure you can make them yours.
l can tell.
Do you know Chisato's weakness?
My sister's weakness?
Yeah, any weakness will do.
l need to know in order to control her.
l know her weakness.
Tell me.
My sister is in charge of the maid, right?
Plus, she seems to have lots of fun with her.
This is what she does to punish her...
Chisato is a lesbian?
She's always talking big, but this is just different.
Who knew that she's into women?
So, what you did to me won't work on my sister.
You're right.
One down...
Next one is...
Mr. Tatsuya!
Emiri.
You're cleaning the room at this hour?
l'm sorry.
l was told to do other errands...
Well, l guess you have no choice then.
You're going to stay here starting today, right?
l'm happy to serve you once again.
Thanks.
By the way, there's something l want to ask you.
Yes?
You shouldn't do this...
lf my lady finds out about this...
She'll punish you again?
How did you...
Don't worry.
You can trust me.
Here, suck on it.
When your master summons you, what kind of punishment do you receive?
That's...
Tell me, Emiri.
No, not that!
What's wrong? About to climax?
l...
You can climax if you want.
This is...
This is my first time doing this...
Here l come, Emiri.
What?
No, not there!
This is fine.
Don't do that...
Yes!
lt's going to tear!
My asshole is going to tear!
That's it...make it tighter!
l'm going to climax again!
l'm coming!
So hot...
You'll tell me everything now, right?
Yes?
Oh, l'm sorry...
Yes.
Oh, hello. This is Ushio.
lt's nice talking to you again.
Well, l'm calling about next month's party.
Good morning.
Oh.
Thank you for attending, director.
Um, that's my seat.
Someone had to cover for you.
Sorry.
Was it really rough last night?
What?
l'm talking about Emiri.
l thought l told you not to get involved with her.
l passed by her this morning in the hallway...
...and l noticed she was more mature.
Maybe it was just your imagination.
My imagination?
You're late, Katori!
You're late because you lack morale! Understand?
Yes...
Ushio.
Never mind Katori. l need to talk to you.
Just give me a second.
Master Kamoshige passed away...
...and now we have plenty of business to take care of.
Why do you think the madam provided you with a room?
lf you know the reason why, then work like there's no tomorrow, you hear?
Yes.
Hey, Ushio.
l know.
Anyway, there are rumors going around about you.
lt's only a matter of time till Lady Chisato finds out.
No, you see...
l can't cover for you other than work.
Linen Room
You don't look so well.
Are you okay?
Mr. Tatsuya...
Mr. Tatsuya!
Don't worry.
You just have to deny it.
Besides, there's no evidence.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
l'll help out in case of an emergency.
Mr. Tatsuya...
My father on his 88th birthday...
Stop it!
Please don't say it, Sister.
l'm the one who wants you to stop.
When you call me sister, it makes me sick!
You're just a nobody, and yet you're a member of the Arimiya family.
Lady Chisato.
Don't you think you're being too harsh?
What did you just say?
You should mind your own business!
You're just a regular employee.
l'm sorry.
Actually, l came here to talk to you about this.
What is it?
Sister?
Lady Shion, you should just let me handle this.
B-But, my sister...
lt's all right!
l want you to go back to your room.
Well, you heard Lady Chisato.
Please head back to your room.
Yes.
Well.
You have some time for me, right?
Shall we go?
What are you going to do with those pictures?
Looks like you're really enjoying it.
But, the other girl doesn't seem like she's having much fun.
When did you become a lesbian?
That's none of your business.
Well, l just think it's a waste.
You're such a beautiful woman.
You don't like men?
Or are you afraid of men?
Come to think of it, you're the stepdaughter of the previous wife, right?
So what?
l believe that wife, l mean your mother...
...was disowned and kicked out of the residence.
So, why did Master Kamoshige keep you in the Arimiya residence?
l don't know...
Maybe he thought of you dearly...
Or...
Come to think of it, l heard that Master Kamoshige's favorite hobby...
...was to take virginities of young girls to bring him luck.
Stop it...stop it...
He did it to you too, right?
Stop!
Along with Lady Shion...
Stop it!
No...that's not true...
He didn't...
l guess l was right.
Poor thing...
lt must've been painful.
Stop!
Men are only interested in humiliating women!
That's not true.
lt's true!
You don't know what that man did to me.
l'm not Kamoshige.
What?
l'll prove to you that l'm not Kamoshige.
Try to relax your muscles.
No...
Don't worry, you'll feel good in no time.
Lift your hips.
No...stop!
You like this, don't you?
l think l'm...
l'm about to...
l'm coming!
Was it good?
You're not afraid anymore, right?
Oh, my...
That's it, keep going.
So hot...
l think l'll burn up...
You're good.
But...
l don't think you can hold it any longer.
You can climax whenever you like.
l can't take it!
l'll climax!
Why don't you just stick it inside already?
l'm just going to stay still.
Amazing! l can feel it near my stomach!
lt's really amazing!
Amazing!
Please do me!
Do me!
Yes!
l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming!
What are you going to do with me?
Hey...