How long...
...do l have to do this?
That must be Suzuna Kuraki.
Really?
Huh?
What?
No...
Bad boy!
Tomomi!
M-Miss Suzuna.
Oh no, l'm sorry!
l told you, l don't want you picking me up!
But Miss, well, this is my job...
l like being left alone!
Oh, Miss!
Excuse me, Miss...
You just don't give up, do you?
Mrs. Yuriko wants to me to escort you to the Kuraki Shrine safely...
...especially now, because your most important ceremony is around the corner.
Hey Tomomi-san, do you have any idea what l'm going through at the shrine?
lf you only knew, maybe you'd understand how l feel.
The scent of the woods around this time of the year is the best!
lf l ever have to leave this mountain...
...l'm sure l'll miss it so much that l'll probably have to return.
l can go the rest of the way by myself, Tomomi.
But...
lt's not like l haven't been doing this for a while.
l know exactly what to do once l've come this far.
For generations...
...the women of the Kuraki family have been shrinekeepers on Kusaka Mountain.
As the highest ranking maidens in service to the Kuraki shrine...
...we have been managing the ceremonies.
My generation is supposed to be a special one...
...because l am the shrine maiden for the...
...Expecting Moon Ceremony that takes place every few decades.
Suzuna-chan!
You are quite late today.
Huh?
Your face looks red.
You must be exhausted.
Oh, l have an idea!
Why don't you take a bath before dinner, Suzuna-chan?
lio, didn't l tell you to stop calling me Suzuna-chan?
Uh, sorry, Suzuna-cha--
l mean, Suzuna.
Go ahead and eat dinner without me!
ls something wrong, Suzuna-chan?
l did it again, sorry!
This can't be happening!
l was counting on lio to be a hunk when he grew up...
...instead, he grew up to be a pretty boy.
A childhood friend turns into a prince...
l guess it doesn't happen in reality.
A prince...
Who is that man, then?
The man who always appears in my dreams...
...and touches me everywhere without my permission...
And...
What is happening to me?
Lately, l always feel funny after the ceremony...
Miss...
Well...
l was just checking to see if anybody is here because l heard the noise...
Oh, l must bring you a change of clothes.
Don't worry.
But...
l'm fine like this.
l just wanted to cool my head...
What's that dress?
Oh, this...
Do l look funny?
That's not my point...
Well...
l thought l could understand how you feel a little better if l dress in this...
lf you only knew...
...maybe you could understand how l feel.
But you didn't have to...
l am sorry.
lt was a silly idea...
You are so funny!
Wild raspberries!
l love them!
l used to look for them on the mountain.
Your grandfather brought them here.
lt's sweet!
Yes, it's really sweet...
Wait, Tomomi!
You should be careful not to catch a cold...
What are you saying...
To soothe your flushed body after the ceremony...
...is also part of my job...
Tomomi!
Does it feel good here?
Then how about...
No, not there...
No, no!
Stop!
What was that?
The fuzziness that l always get after the ceremony is going away...
Mizuna...
Tomomi!
l'm terribly sorry.
l was dozing off...
Um, Tomomi...
...last night, the two of us...
Your grandfather thinks the heat must have gone to your head.
You didn't show up at the dinner last night...
So when l went to look for you...
You were on the bathroom floor.
ls that true?
Don't you remember?
But...
Then that was...
Miss Suzuna!
You are naked!
l'm sorry.
l must have been in such a hurry, l forgot to dress you.
That's right...
This is the Tomomi l've always known...
Yuriko-sama, was that okay?
Everything was necessary for her to prepare for the Expecting Moon Ceremony.
Yes...
Was it really a dream?
The touch and everything...
What am l saying?
What's wrong with me?
Who is it?
Please, l am not trying to bother you.
You're not from around here.
l wasn't peeping.
l was just passing by...
Please trust me!
...but l snuck out to take a walk in the woods...
...because l wanted to enjoy the morning sun.
l am a TV actress.
l am in a show called ''Living in the Mountain'' written by the dramatist...
...who wrote ''From Ohio with Love.''
Whoever you are, this area is barred to outsiders.
You should leave at once.
l am not lying!
Wait, you forgot this!
They are beautiful as always.
Surely, the gardener must be quite skilled.
Just like women, flowers require tender care.
l am putting my whole soul to them.
Gohei-san, l think l warned you before.
l suggest not standing behind a woman when you are talking.
Pardon me.
How naughty...
Someone has no manners.
Good morning, Suzuna-chan.
What were you talking about, Suzuna-cha--
l mean, Suzuna.
Nothing...
l don't like him very much.
l think he's a bit weird.
l sometime can't believe he's Harukawa-san's uncle...
What is that?
No idea.
This is the script for the soap opera that Ruri Yamabe stars in...
Who is this Ruri person?
You know?
Everybody knows her, she used to be a famous child star...
Well, l guess l'm not everybody.
Don't you remember?
...ln that TV commercial for ETO Butter with the Snow Emblem logo...
...she became a phenomenon for her cute acting, and...
..in that fire scene for the morning TV series ''Glaring eyes'' ...
...she impressed everyone by performing her own stunts.
ln ''Home Girl'' she played the leading role.
Her line ''l don't want your money, l just want your sympathy'' ...
...was the most popular phrase of the year.
She was the talk of the town, right?
lmpressive, you know quite a lot about her.
Oh, Harukawa-san!
Umm, well, l'm not a fanatic or anything...
...it's the sort of information that everybody knows, right?
l just knew about her because Suzuna's father is a big fan of hers.
My father?
Yeah.
Don't you talk about this kind of thing with him, Suzuna?
l haven't even seen him for a half year.
He doesn't even say hi to me.
My mother also...
Mother?
Suzuna-chan?
l am sorry, l just...
lio...
l think my mother died a few years ago...
Are you talking about me?
Wow, the camellias look gorgeous today...
Look, Miss Suzuna.
So, what were you saying, Suzuna-chan?
Huh?
Well...
l forgot.
Now, you must get ready.
M-Mizuna...
What's wrong with me?
lt doesn't matter if it was a dream or reality...
That night, l had tasted...
...the forbidden fruit they call ''pleasure.''
The man in my dream began to appear even when l was awake...
As the secret affair went on, he became accustomed to my body.
And just when l was beginning to see his figure clearly...
He appeared...
This is a joke!
l am absolutely not wearing that!
But this is really cute.
Why don't you wear it then, Sayaka?
l don't like your temperament.
And besides, it's a custom, you can't run away from it.
The hell with custom, There's no way l'm going to get married to a guy l haven't met!
Miss Suzuna...
You shouldn't be so difficult, Suzuna.
Mother...
Madam!
Suzuna, your marriage was arranged by your grandmother...
...not only that, it's your father's last wish.
But we don't know if he really passed away or not...
He has been missing from this mansion for a year without even a phone call.
He is no longer qualified to lead the Kuraki.
Now, you must prepare yourself for the bridal bed.
Your husband is waiting for you.
Tomomi!
Yes, madam.
Why don't you help Suzuna freshen up?
l don't need any help with that!
...Tomomi is really good at it.
Madam...
Suzuna.
Yes?
The Kuraki's thousand years of history hinges on your marriage.
Don't you ever forget that.
Do you understand?
Yes...
l-l think they suit you..
You can use whichever you like!
Except this one!
This is my favorite.
l don't need any.
l-lt seems your husband is exhausted from traveling.
So please be easy on him.
l'm the one he needs to be easy on!
Nobody is here...
He's asleep.
He's got some nerve.
He's already made himself at home...
He is kinda okay-looking...
Beautiful...
This feeling...
lt's just like the one in my dream...
No!
You horny bastard, you pervert!
What the hell?
Well, at first l thought she might be an angel, but now l know l was wrong...
Please take it easy.
This is the first time for Suzuna, so you should be the one to lead her.
l don't care who you are...
...but l want you to explain what's going on here so l can understand.
That Camellia tree is very important to us.
That pond exists only because of the tree...
That bastard!
l am going to kick him out, definitely!
l will talk to my grandmother myself!
Sayaka?
What is it?
Don't come in without knocking!
Hey!
Tomomi!
No!
Please stop!
No, no!
Stop!
Somebody, help!
Don't!
Please, stop!
lt is the fate of all flowers to bloom and fall.
My name is Sayaka Kurihara.
l'm a maid at the Kuraki Mansion, l take care of Miss Suzuna...
...and before that, well...
Who am l?
Moonlight Lady, second night: Sunflower.
On sale in spring of 2002.