What? What is that?
Kya!
Y-Yui-senpai...
Who's there?
I'm in a pinch! A big pinch!
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Out of my control.
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokani no dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I wasn't trying to spy on you! I just saw Himuro-san head up this way and...
Kogure?
Huh?
K-Kogure-san?
You, go back down to the lobby.
Huh?
Please, just go!
Okay.
What are you doing in here of all places?
Now, this is where i work. Why should i have to ask for permission?
Kasama-san! Why are you working on this too?
Relax, it's just a little research.
Research?
This system costs a bundle. The higher-ups wanted us to spend a little more time on it.
The first group is already over.I'm busy making a new one.
You've become full of yourself, Kogure-kun.
You bastard!
Cut it out! If you're gonna fight, take it outside!
Let's go, Himuro-san.
Himuro-san, what are you planning?
Eh?! Lemon Angel was a program?!
Shh! Not so loud.
Gimme a break, it's top secret!
But you've got to be kidding?
Why would i have a reason to lie to you?
Eh? Ah, but...
I understand how you feel. After all, the person who made the Lemon Angel was a genius.
Kohno Yui.
Yui-senpai?
Yes. Lemon Angel was actually called L.A.P. test program in artificial human intelligence.
Test?
She wanted to hide the fact it was a program and see how many people would accept them.
Wow. Yui-senpai was amazing! But Lemon Angel not being real is a bit of a shock.
See? This is why we can't make an announcement.
It's late. I'll give you a ride home.
Umm... about our earlier conversation...
Hmm?
What about Toro? Wasn't Toro, Suwa-senpai?
Oh, that. Miki initially helped Yui in developing L.A.P.
Huh?
If Yui was the genius, she was the producer.
And the first model she chose for Lemon Angel was Miki.
Miki was originally against it, but Yui wore Miki down with her smile.
Yui was stubborn that way.
Ah, that i understand.
And lastly, Ann, the main vocalist, was modeled after you.
Huh? Me?
Yep. Yui was always saying how much she liked you, which is why she used you as her model.
Senpai...
Dear Yui-senpai...
I feel like i'm gonna cry.
I had no idea that you felt so strongly for me. If you were here right now, i'd give you a big hug!
But because senpai is no longer among us, it tears at my heart.
Is it okay if i ask you something?
Hmm?
Why was it that Lemon Angel was disbanded all of a sudden?
The program was destroyed by a hacker.
Did that have anything to do with Yui-senpai passing away?
Nah, that was unrelated.
Oh.
Anyway, the Lemon Angel Program ended.
Yui said, "I don't want my songs sung by a machine, but by a person."
yeah.
Which is why you should...
Are you okay?
Yes, i'm fine!
About the next audition, would you consider giving it a try?
I don't know what sort of skill you have, and i can't guarantee you'll pass.
But i'd like to see what it was that Yui saw in you.
Okay. I understand.
Really?
Ah, but remember, i'm not sure how it'll go.
Uh-huh. That's fine. I just want to hear your singing voice.
Dear senpai,
I'm finally here.
I finally got to meet Kogure-san, also.
Lemon Angel Audition \ Reception
Move it, you're in the way!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
You're Hoshi Yayoi, aren't you?
You mean you're trying out for Lemon Angel, too?
Recruitment is open to everyone whether they're a pro or not.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Minaguchi Tomo. We'll be auditioning together.
So what?
Ah, hold on...
Audition
Waiting Room
Locker Room
Wow, i can feel the tension here. Boy, do i feel out of place.
Hey, you! You shouldn't complain like that. Just relax, relax.
Uh, umm...
Me? I'm Erika Campbell.
Ah, I'm Minaguchi Tomo.
Tomo, huh? Nice to meet you.
You too, Erika-san.
No, no, just Erika is fine. Don't need to add "san."
Ah, 'kay.
Ah, sorry.
S-sorry.
I wonder if i made her mad?
Well, there are all sorts of people here, so it's nothing to worry about.
Uh, 'kay.
She was probably just pissed off. Not everyone is like...
Hey! Would you cut out the jokes!
I said that the gloss was almost gone! So why didn't you buy more?
But...
Huh?
S-sorry.
She really pisses me off!
Yep. There sure are a lot of different people here.
Uh, yeah.
Everyone, quiet please. Before the audition, i felt i should introduce all of you to the staff members.
I'm Kogure Ryouta, the producer.
I look forward to all of you giving the first Lemon Angel a run for their money.Do your best!
The coaches are Yamashiro Lisa-san, Danny Yamaguchi-san, and Jounouchi Takashi-san.
And also our video producer, Kaga, and the head of our sales department, Kagoe.
Eh? Himuro isn't here?
Yeah. Wasn't the first group produced by Himuro? Isn't it gonna be him again?
If Himuro isn't a part of it, then it feels like something's missing.
Yeah.
And then we have...
Sir!
What is it?
What happened to Himuro-san?
Ah, about that. Himuro Shinya won't be participating in the project this time.
You're serious? Why not?
And lastly, the leader from the first Lemon Angel, Suwa Miki-san.
I'll be asking her to take on the role of leader again this time.
She's not part of the staff, but i thought to have her sit in to see how everyone does.
The audition will begin in thirty minutes, so until then, everyone please get yourselves ready.
Okay.
Umm, Suwa-senpai...
G-Good morning.
Why did you come here?
Uh, Kogure-san said he wanted me to come..
Umm, senpai...
O-One moment, senpai...
Didn't i tell you this already? I said never speak to me again.
Um, excuse me. I'm Yuki Saya. I've always been a Lemon Angel fan.
I was so excited thinking about today, that i couldn't sleep a wink. I'll do my best today!
Aren't you?
Yes. I've been working under the name Hoshi Yayoi.
But i quit in order to focus on singing for the Lemon Angel.
Oh.
Do your best.
Yes, i will!
We're different as night and day.
D-Dear Yui-senpai,
Why am i being treated like this? Does Suwa-senpai really think i'm that hopeless?
You're acting pretty quiet today.
Uh, Kogure-san?
What's up?
Umm, is it okay if i just go home now?
Huh?
Is what Miki said bothering you?
That's part of it, but this just feels like a different world. I don't think i'll fit in as a Lemon Angel.
Can't be helped. At least give the mic a try, and if you really think you can't, then it's okay to quit.
Really?
Yeah. May as well stick around to watch after coming all this way.
Ah. I can, can't i?
Finally cheered up. That's more like you.
Huh? But even i feel down sometimes.
Who is that girl? A friend of the producer?
Which means she's guaranteed to pass?
But just eat something sweet and you'll cheer right up.
Yeah, i guess...
That's fraud!
Just shut up and do your job as you're told.
I want to sing. I didn't sign on to only look pretty for pictures like this!
I've had about enough of that sort of stuff out of you!
Yayoi-chan... Boss, i'll talk with her about this and get the whole story...
Shut up! It's too late! Plans have already been made for the magazine. You alone can't...
Like i care!
You trying to embarrass me?
Embarrass? Like hell. Just change the schedule, you conservative old fool!
W-Why you little...
Well, if you can't stand me so much, then why don't you fire me?! I'm sick of this place!
Fine! Get the hell out of here!
Okay, i'm gone. Sorry to have troubled you.
Ignore her!
Yayoi-chan...
Ophelia
Onnaji SUPIDO de hashi no mukou he yukou.
Let's cross that bridge at the same speed
Yayoi-chan...
I'm no longer Hoshi Yayoi, i'm Yuki Saya.
sou sureba itsumo hi ka aeru sono basho de
If we do that, we can meet at that place someday
Don't worry, i'll be fine. This isn't gonna make me give up. I'm taking this chance.
hatenai yume wo ai wo asu wo utagai wo sezu ni
Without doubting my limitless dream and love
I'm taking this chance.
oikaketeta hibiga futo yomigaeru
The days i've been chasing come back to me
sore wa minna ni omoi de sosoida la la mahou no jyumon da wa
That is the magical spell we all put our thoughts into
sutecha damenanda shinjiru koto de
Don't throw it away, believe in it.
Hoshi Yayoi... i mean Yuki-san is so good.
So why hasn't she become a singer already?
It's not just Yuki-san, but everyone's really good. Maybe i should quit now.
Thank you.
Okay, well done.
Isn't your turn next?
Huh? Uh, yeah. Actually, i think i'm...
Well aren't you a piece of work. No matter how bad you are, you're guaranteed to be accepted.
Huh?
Just because you have connections with the producer, don't get overconfident.
This world isn't that easy.
Eh? Now hold on...
You're next, aren't you? Hurry up and sing so we can hear how bad you are.
Hah, if this producer thinks you have a chance to succeed, then i doubt he has what it takes.
He must be crazy.
You over there, silence please.
Next. Number 50, Minaguchi Tomo.
Yes!
Yui-senpai, i've had enough! I can't stand this any longer!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Now show me...
Now watch me surprise all of you with how well i can sing.
I thought so.
Tomo...
Horrible. Why is she even here?
This is no good, no good.
Sorry!
She really did quit.
What is it?
Sorry! One more time from the beginning please.
Okay, but only once more.
Okay. Thank you!
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you,
It's no use. I can't sing like Miki-san.
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
for some reason my heart can't seem to rest.
Really? But i happen to like your singing.
C-Cut it out please.
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
I guess it can't be helped, if you compare yourself to Miki.
Hmm.
I think what's important is the way you convey your feelings through your singing.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance.
Feelings?
Yeah. When i listen to your singing, i get a feeling of happiness.
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
Huh?
So, please? Sing for me?
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...they become lonely.
What's important is to convey feelings.
Senpai, please listen.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do.
It's not that great.
This is the singing Yui admired so much.
Okay. Well done.
Yui-senpai, did you hear me?
Thank you very much.
I threw caution to the wind, but i still feel embarrassed.
Don't be. It moved me.
That's it for the first round of auditions. You will be sent the results in the mail.
Thank you.
If that's your best, i wouldn't get too happy.
What did you think?
Think?
I'd like to hear your impression of how it went.
If we're talking about ability, there are plenty of others that can match her.
I don't see what Yui saw in her.
Though i didn't ask you about her specifically.
That's one step forward, i think.
Ah, Tomo.
Going to your club?
Yeah. What about you?
Heading home.
Oh yeah, did you get a responce from the audition last week?
Hmm, nothing yet.
Oh. Well, i'll treat you to some cake later, so don't get too down.
What did you say?! You're talking as if i'm guaranteed to fail.
Later.
Geez.
I'm home!
Mom, where are the snacks?
Hm? Huh? She's not here.
Minaguchi Tomo
Erica Campbell
Sakakibara Fuyumi
Sendou Haruka
Nagisa Miru
I made it.
All right!!
Second Lemon Angel group, 20 have passed the first round of selection.
What was that? Yayoi's trying out for the Lemon Angels? That brat!
Huh? Yeah. Oh...
Well, if that's the case, then i'll have to do something about it.
Hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
Nazeka kokoro wa nemure nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
Dewa suru yuuki mo nakawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
Tomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
Onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
Ko wo suru tabi ni
are in love...
Sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
Itsudatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
Girls in love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world i can only dream about.
What are you stressing about, Tomo?
B-B-But, Erika, we passed the first round of selections for the next Lemon Angels.
Not only that, but we have to participate in a swimsuit photoshoot.
Don't let it get to you.
Not only that, some weirdo forced his way into the studio.
Oh, it seems he's here to cause trouble for Saya.
Next time: Lemon Angel Project episode 3, "I Will."
I feel a contract coming on.