It's been a while since I came here.
It's quite a nice place, isn't it?
My ass is numb from all the shaking around on the path here.
Although, that was nothing compared to the fun that we're going to have.
Shu-Shuji-kun, I can't hold back...
We're really allowed to have sex with those two, right?
Hey, you don't seem to understand that you're an extra here.
I'm going to tell you my intentions now.
My wish is for them to have the utmost discipline.
For that reason, we can't just rape them; we have to train them.
Now then, let's start Kurata Ibuki and Miyauchi Akira's training, shall we?
Episode 01
Presented
by
Shikkaku Fansubs
A week at a summer resort!
I'm looking forward to it!
Yeah! I've never won a prize before.
It looks like this summer is going to be great!
I agree.
Say, Ibuki...
Huh? What is it, Akira?
Ibuki... Ibuki!
Akira... we're here already?
Shuji-kun?
Ibuki...
Hey, what's with that attitude?
I'm a sensitive person; you'll hurt my feelings.
Why are you here, Shuji-kun? Where are we?
I'd also like to ask where we are!
Yakushima! Why did you kidnap us!?
You don't have to shout, I can hear you.
As for the first question...
This place is something like my summer resort.
And the reason we brought you two here is...
"We"?
We're here to rape you and train you to be obedient slaves.
Y-You've gotta be kidding! You kidnapped us for that!?
Shuji-kun...
Yakushima, I bet you feel that you've won, but you're wrong.
Right, Ibuki?
Yes! Our families know that we're on holiday.
If we don't arrive at the inn, our families will be notified.
That's right! What you guys are doing will be exposed soon enough.
Quit being assholes and let us go!
Should we tell them the news, Kazuma?
The vacation contest isn't real.
In fact, I made it all up.
In other words, the whole vacation was a setup.
What? T-That means...?
That's right, you'll be with us for your week-long vacation.
W-Why does it have to be us?
You probably don't have trouble getting girls, right?
It's probably that look...
Look?
I told you to move! Yakushima Shuji!
Are you listening to us, Shuji-kun?
You two are the only ones who despise me at school.
Forcing those with sharp looks in their eyes into submission...
It's my favorite activity!
Right then, who should we start with?
F-For an entire week...
You want me to be your playmate, right?
I-Ibuki?
It looks like it.
Then... I'll be the one!
So don't touch Akira!
H-Hey, Ibuki!
I'm the one who entered the contest,
which means I was your original target, right?
Please release Akira.
W-Wait up! I'm the one who despises Yakushima the most.
I'll be your playmate, so don't touch Ibuki!
Akira...
I said that I'm training you both.
If you don't touch Akira, I'll become your playmate without a fight.
However, if you even lay a finger on Akira, I'll never forgive you!
Hey, Ibuki... I said that I'm going to do it...
Fine, then.
In honor of your beautiful relationship, we shall only train one.
Shuji!
Then I'll do it.
Ibuki, I said that I would!
Right, Akira. We shall train you.
Shuji-kun?
Since you did suddenly punch me when you woke up...
We shall teach you manners as well.
Hmph, what's wrong with hitting the bastard who kidnapped you?
Isn't this great, Ibuki?
Now then, let's begin.
Don't-! Shuji-kun!
Akira...
Akira!
I'll have you keep your promise.
Akira! No!
Oumori, sorry to keep you waiting...
This is your cue.
Akira hates you the most,
so you can start off.
W-What?!
Didn't you hear my order?
I'll definitely be killed...
She's good at karate, right?
It's fine, she agreed beforehand that she'll keep her promise.
Don't tell me that just because you don't want to,
you're going to let this thing have a go at your friend?
This thing?
R-Right, I'll keep my promise.
So you better keep yours, too.
Akira...
She said that it's fine.
Oumuri, what do you want her to do first?
G-Give me fellatio.
What's a fellatio?
Fellatio is when a girl sucks a guy's cock with her mouth.
Don't tell me that you don't know that at your age.
O-Of course I know that!
I just have to lick it, right?
I-It smells...
It's bitter!
Akira...
P-Put it in your mouth...
D-Didn't you say just to lick it?
I-I'll teach you real fellatio!
I'm c-cumming!
N-No...
Okay, now for the real thing.
R-Real thing? But I just...
Don't tell me that you thought that was it.
Well, I guess you're not the type to enjoy it rough, but bear with it, okay?
And if you don't agree...
Fine, then.
Very good! Now I'll have you first.
Huh? You don't want me to?
Then Oumori, will you do it?
R-Really?
W-Wait! Anybody but him...
Jeez, which are you going to choose, Akira?
T-That's...
You don't have to choose.
Well, it just means that we'll take Ibuki's virginity instead.
Yakushima is fine...
You sure are hated, Oumori.
N-No way...
Well, that's what she wants.
N-No...
No!
Your underwear is wet.
Did holding Oumori's penis in your mouth make you wet?
No, it's sweat! It's because I got sweaty!
Is that so?
T-That hurts!
Stop it!
Stop it! It hurts!
It can't be helped.
Then I'll...
No, not there!
No-!
I-It's too stimulating!
No, really! It's too much...!
No! I'm gonna...!
Seeing that you're this wet, you want me, right?
That's not true!
W-What are you doing?
Why, but of course,
I'm putting it in.
N-No!
I-It hurts-!
No!
So you were a virgin.
Well? How does it feel to be a woman?
No...
Pull it out, pull it out!
Hey, if you fidget that much, I might cum inside you.
N-No!
D-Don't you move-!
I told you not to move!
S-Stop it!
So deep-!
Don't do such weird things!
It feels good to take your virginity.
How about I cum inside you?
N-No, don't do it!
Not inside! Absolutely not inside-!
No! I don't want it!
Pull it out, pull it out-!
No-!
N-No! It's coming out! Lots of it...
No! No!!
No! It's filling me inside, I-I'll get pregnant...
Well now, the curtains have now been raised.
Akira, now we're ready for the main act.
Stay away... Stay away!
Please stop it!
Akira! Akira!!
Did you sleep well?
There's no way I could sleep.
Moreover, what do you want?
I have a suggestion.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
No, please stop it already... I'm feeling funny-!
How does it feel to lose both front and rear virginities in one day?
It just hurts!
How tough-minded.
Oumori, how did it feel to have Akira take your virginity?
It feels really good!
It's like I can cum as much as I want!
Not inside, please!
Use your tongue properly!
Don't slack off.
Over here too, please.
I'm going to cum soon...
Don't! No-!
That's right, Akira, fight back! Don't fall into acceptance!
Please stop it!
I'll break!
T-This is too much... No-!
Haven't you had enough? Please stop it...
Don't be silly,
none of us are satisfied.
How could I forget?
Moreover, stop this idiocy and release us at once!
About Akira's training...
A-After doing all of that to her yesterday, are you going to continue today too?!
Well, I'm not such a bad man.
I bet she'll be tired after doing all that yesterday.
Then...?
But the training isn't over yet, so we can't stop now.
Well then, do you want to train in Akira's place?
Oh, we'll keep Akira's promise, of course.
We won't take your virginity, so how about it?
You're saying that if I take the training, it will be easier on Akira, right?
Yes.
Alright, then.
However, you have to promise me that you won't do anything more to Akira-
I know, I'll keep my promise.
Akagi, I'm leaving it to you.
I'm not really interested in shy ones that don't fight back...
But, if you insist...
N-No-!
Not a pose like this!
P-Please don't!
No, don't lick there-! It's dirty!
No-!
Please don't lick me there!
Are you getting wet already? Then...
W-What is that...?
You don't know?
This tool is called a rotor, and it's used to please lonely women.
Like this.
No, not there!
S-Stop it-!
I guess I'll shove it in you.
No... No more...
Don't toy with me down there!
No-!
Don't lick such a dirty place!
Please! I beg of you!
Your voice is getting more lewd.
Does it feel good?
For me to feel good there...
There's no way-
She's quite tough.
Akagi, give her the final push.
N-Not my butt!
N-No...
You did good. Thanks to you, Akira has it easier.
Let me praise you,
even if you have turned into a horny bitch who cums from anal.
Shuji-kun, h-how does this look on her?
It suits her well.
So does this mean that you're Akira's master?
T-That's right! I'm teaching the maid who wet herself.
That's no good, Akira-chan!
You have to swallow all of it!
What? No way...
I-I'm sorry.
Do you deserve punishment?
Punishment?
Lift your butt.
His hot thing is...
Nii-sama...
Why didn't you choose me?
You're the only one. I don't need anything apart from you, but...
Oh, and about that,
I'll definitely join in.
I will be the one breaking the minds of Kurata Ibuki and Miyauchi Akira.
Nii-sama's plan was to kidnap Kurata-senpai and her friend, Miyauchi-senpai...
And to make them obedient.
Don't-!
It should be me, Karen, who Nii-sama loves!
No-one would pay any attention Karen...
Since she was the daughter of father's mistress...
However, Nii-sama was different!
He... he would watch over Karen.
For me to be doing such things...
He wouldn't like such a lewd girl, would he?
But when I think about Nii-sama, Karen gets...
I won't give Nii-sama away...
Nii-sama belongs to Karen!
I should hate it, but my body becomes aroused and I nearly get washed away with pleasure.
Even though I'm doing it instead of Ibuki,
I've gotten used to this absurd treatment...
I need to find a way to escape...
Who is it? I've already...
Y-You're...?
Yakushima's little sister?
Are you here to save me?
Why do you continue to despise Nii-sama?
W-What?
I think that this feeling I'm getting is called "annoyance".
The feeling of being shown something that I've really wanted for a long time.
Y-You...
What kinds of words did you use to seduce Nii-sama? You whore!
I-I didn't...
Akira?
Ibuki!
What's happening?
Akira tried to escape, even though you were trapped here.
By manipulating my sister, no less.
Ya-Yakushima, you bastard!
Stop with the bullshit!
You did try to run away, though.
T-That's because your little sister...
So, Ibuki, I think you know what I'm wanting to say...
If I take Akira's punishment, then you will forgive her, correct?
N-No, don't do it, Ibuki!
It's fine, since it pains me more to see you suffer than me being defiled.
Please understand, Akira.
Looks like it's settled.
As for you, Akira, we will have to punish you for breaking your promise.
So what are we going to do, Shuji?
Should we take turns pounding Ibuki in front of her?
Or should we do some extra tough training?
Let's see, we should take turns.
Her good friend became a woman before her,
Ibuki also needs to become one.
If you don't want to look, that's fine.
However, this is just a warning.
Please bear with the pain if it hurts.
Since it's to make up for your friend's mistake...
I understand, so why don't you hurry up?
Okay, let's have fun, Ibuki.
Stop it, Yakushima!
S-Stop-!
N-No!
T-That hurts! Not so suddenly-!
I can feel your hymen against my fingers.
See? It's right here!
No way... There's no way something that large will fit inside me!
N-No-!!
It hurts!
Please don't move!
Stop-!
Hey, stop it-!
I-I'll break!
N-No! Not inside! Anything but inside!
Oh really? So you're going to abandon your friend?
That's not it!
But if you cum inside me, I'll...!
I'm cumming, my dear Ibuki!
No!! It's coming out! It's filling me up!
Y-You came so much...
Ibuki...!
Akagi, it's your turn.
Anywhere you want...
H-Hey...
S-Stop it!!
You're splitting me!
S-Stop it!
No! My butt is being split open-!
This feels great!
Doing this from behind is exhilarating!
Kurata!
You're probably a high class girl elsewhere, but now you're just a horny bitch!
Get ready, I'm going to fill your asshole with semen!
No, don't-! Don't do such-!
Don't fill my butt-!
N-No!
It's... It's coming out inside my butt...
Ibuki!
We're done with foreplay.
Now let's start with the real punishment.
Doing her in such a hazy state isn't so bad.
No more! I don't want to cum anymore...
I-It's hitting me, it's hitting my deepest parts!
Are you about to cum, Ibuki?
I'm about to! My mind is blank...
With my insides being pounded...
Don't cum inside me anymore!
No more, I'll become pregnant! No more semen, please-!
I'll end up having a baby...
She's still aroused even after this?
Maybe it's that girls have a longer sex drive.
Don't you think so, Akira?
It's no good, Shuji-kun!
She's been like this since we started doing Ibuki-chan.
Seems like she's abandoned her friend...
I dug your asshole out with this.
Better clean it throughly, eh?
This is all your fault, Akira.
It's because of you that this is happening.
Well, I guess you don't need to take responsibility,
since you willingly gave yourself for Ibuki's protection.
It seems as though it has deepened your relationship.
S-So hot...
From now on, why don't you get Ibuki to take over?
Don't you dare defile Ibuki any further!
I'll take the training...
So... So please-!
Yes, that's the spirit!
Even though she's unconscious,
I'm sure Ibuki would be delighted to hear that.
I'll bear it all...
So...!