Dear Yui-senpai,
My summer vacation starts today.
I should be feeling all hyped-up, but...
Hey, Tomo,
stop singing with that creepy voice.
But they're strict.
I'm not even good at dancing in the first place!
There's nothing else you can do,
even though you don't know the basics yet.
I'd like to help you,
but I already have a busy schedule.
Hey, are you paying attention?
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
And get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokani no dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Better Off as Friends
Are you okay?
Jeez...
This is the first time I've ever seen someone fall asleep while standing.
Oh?! They look delicious!
Uh, Umm...
Would you like to have some?
Can I?
Yup, I have plenty.
It's so delicious!
Where did you get these?
I made them myself.
That's amazing!
The way they're shaped is so cute.
A bear?
Umm... that's a ca-
Bears are so cute, aren't they?
This is delicious!
Umm... it was actually a cat...
But I'm sorry, a bear is fine too.
Whenever you get tired, don't you ever want to eat something this sweet?
Doughnuts are the best.
Aren't they?!
They are, aren't they?!
Doughnuts are the best.
They're sweet, crunchy and yet very chewy, and it has a hole,
so doughnuts are the best of all sweets!
Uh... so, um...
Umm...
So, in other words,
doughnuts are very delicious.
I normally make doughnuts for my friends.
Oh, would you two like to have some as well?
I have plenty.
Thank you.
No thanks.
They'll make me fat.
My body shape is part of being an idol.
That doesn't sound really convincing...
Shut up!
Fuyumi,
can you come here for a minute?
I have something very important to tell you.
Uh, okay...
Uh, so what were you going to tell me?
Oh, would you like some doughnuts too, Haruka-chan?
You loved sweets ever since you were little.
I made this specially for you, Haruka-chan.
I'd be really happy if you ate them.
I hate that Saya girl.
I'm pissed off after being called "naive."
Remember that time we went to visit Tankumi?
Uh, yes.
So I was thinking of crushing her.
Crush?
Minaguchi and Erica are also annoying,
so maybe I should do them all at once.
And you'll co-operate with me, right?
Here, take this.
I'll probably ask you to do more favors for me later,
so thanks for coming.
Haruka-chan!
See you later.
I told you to practice on your own!
I-I'm sorry...
That's enough already.
Seems like we're starting to see the personalities of the candidates.
It seems so.
I hope they can all last until the end.
Aren't we at the point where people should start dropping out?
Dropping out?
People will start to run away because the lessons are very hard.
Why are you crying?!
If you have the time to cry, then go practice instead!
That's scary...
Only those that remain here,
will be the ones to get the special lessons.
So it's been confirmed?!
Yes, I've received a message just now.
He was a dancer with charisma, I heard.
Young people nowadays don't know him.
Enough already. Next, Minaguchi!
Uh. Yes!
I-I'm sorry,
may I go to the restroom?
This isn't kindergarten!
I'm sorry...
What's up with that?
I'd be really embarrassed.
It looks like you actually gave her that water.
And you've obviously taken care of Saya as well?
Yeah.
I can't wait.
Next up, Yuki!
Yuki Saya? You're not here?
I'm sorry, I spilt juice on my clothes.
What?! What would you do if that were your costume?
I've had enough!
Wait a moment!
I can dance like this!
Please let me dance!
All right then.
Go ahead.
She's pretty good, as I expected.
She'll look very nice on stage.
Shit, how can she..
That was so uncool.
You don't have any real talent, do you?
That turn should have been easy, right?
I can do that without even practicing.
Wow! You really are amazing!
Just wait a second,
Aren't you misunderstanding me or something?
You shouldn't even be practicing,
you should be supporting me instead.
Give this to Saya.
Uh, okay.
What is this?
A fake schedule.
And even if she believes it and goes,
she'll be waiting for nothing when no one isn't even there at the stage.
I thought she'd quit, since I messed up her clothes.
I'll definitely get her this time.
W-We shouldn't be doing this.
What are you saying?
You're guilty of the same crime.
You can't run away anymore.
You mean...
Let's crush them, okay?
Huh, so that's what it was about.
What a joke.
You were very good, Fuyumi-chan.
If I can see you, mother, I'll do my best.
I'm Haruka,
What's your name?
I'm Fuyumi.
Fuyumi-chan?
Let's do our best.
Okay!
Why?
The doughnuts don't taste good today.
Oww!
Can't you be a little more gentle?
Oh, sorry.
Ow, ow, ow...
But it's terrible that someone would put thumbtacks in your shoes.
Did something happen to you too, Erica?
Me?
Oh, yeah, that reminds me!
Oh, very cute.
I thought it was a surprise present.
That's definitely a form of harassment.
It hurts a little, but I should be fine.
Okay then, let's practice some more.
I don't know who did it,
but let's show them that we won't give up.
Let's do it!
Hey, you just wait there.
Saya, you're late.
Huh?
What's the matter, Yumi?
Uh, nothing...
What's that you're holding in your hands?
I-It's nothing!
Isn't it an "important message"?
No, it's nothing really.
I'm sorry.
Wait, Yumi-chan!
If you want, why don't we practice together?
Oh, Yumi! It'll be more fun with everyone together.
Let's dance.
But...
Okay? Come on.
Hey, aren't you...
I'm sorry.
I'm not good with this...
It's nothing bad or anything, but you're just too tight.
Just calm down and relax.
You think so?
See, your back isn't straight.
Straighten it up.
Y-Yes!
Yumi, smile, smile.
Yeah, yeah, smile.
You're smiling too much.
You didn't have to say that.
What? Well, it's the truth.
But you're always saying stuff that's unnecessary.
So what, I'm saying the truth.
So what?
You fatty.
Are you stupid?!
Why are you being so friendly with them?
But...
No buts!
I told you to crush them!
What's with that face?
If you want me to forgive you...
You understand, right?
This isn't what we should be doing.
Oh yeah, I just thought of something good.
Put this in it.
They'll eat it so happily.
Stop it!
You'll do it, right?
No...
I can't do this anymore.
This isn't right.
I want to work with everyone, Haruka-chan.
They're all kind people.
You should just be friends with-
Hah. You're annoying.
I said you're annoying.
Friends? What are you talking about?
That's so sickening.
And why do you have to look like you're my friend in the first place?
Wha-What...
I just wanted to use you as an assistant.
If you can't listen to me,
I don't need you.
Hey, you just hit rock bottom.
Were you listening?
If you're going to shout that loud,
I'd hear it even if I didn't want to.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Doing stuff like this just because you don't have any talent.
What? Your attitude is pissing me off.
No, no fighting.
Big news!
Huh?
What?
Um... uh...
Ray is coming.
You mean... that Ray?
Yeah, he's going to come watch us dance.
Isn't that amazing?
Oh?
Isn't that just perfect?
We'll have to see who'll do better then.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you'll forgive me if I apologize,
but please let me say sorry.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
I can't practice with you anymore.
And I still think of Haruka-chan as a friend.
But I really enjoyed practicing with you guys.
Hey, Yumi!
Yes?
Sto-Sto-Stop it please!
And that's our payback.
We're now even.
It looks like I have no other choice...
Eh?
Let's practice together.
It's more fun that way for us.
B-But...
I think that even though we're rivals,
we can still be friends.
And it's all thanks to these two,
who I didn't give in to hard lessons or harassment.
Okay, Yumi-chan?
So, let's practice together like we did before, okay?
Okay?
Are you sure it's all right?
Of course it is.
Thank you.
I'm Ray.
Let me see you dance how you normally dance today.
And let me feel your method.
Yes!
If the teacher tells you to stop dancing, you are to stop.
Be sure to watch those who still remain very carefully.
Yes!
Are you okay?
You're right in the middle of this.
Hmph, and that's it for those guys.
It's all their fault for getting involved with Fuyumi.
I'm sorry, it's my fault...
See, your back isn't straight.
Be confident.
Saya-san...
Let's enjoy this some more.
Smile, smile.
Okay!
Why doesn't he stop them from dancing?
If that's how it's going to be.
You may rest now.
Hold on!
I don't understand.
Weren't you watching my moves?
I was much better than those people.
It's true that your dancing is good.
Then...
But there are plenty of other people out there with your level of technique.
Huh?
I don't care how good you are.
I just want to see some potential.
That's why I came here today.
What?! That's all nonsense!
Stop acting so disgracefully.
Haruka-chan! What do you mean you're giving up the audition?
That's bad, isn't it?
It's so stupid anyways.
Hey, Haruka-chan.
Didn't we promise when we were little?
That we'll do our best together?
We promised not to use that dialect.
[Haruka is referring to the Nara dialect Fuyumi uses.]
Because it's not cool.
But...
Hey, can you give me doughnuts?
Doughnuts! You have some right now, don't you?
You always made them,
but I never got to eat them, did I?
Hmm. It's kinda good.
Hey, Fuyumi...
I hope you do your best.
I won't be able to cheer for you,
but I won't get in your way, either.
Later then.
Sendou-san quit, eh?
Yeah...
Don't you dare pity her.
Those who are still here have to work extra hard for those who leave.
Yeah, that's right.
All right then. We don't have time to daydream.
Yup.
Himuro-san?
hajimete negatta hi kara
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
Please, if for only a chance
onna no ko tachi wa
When girls
koi wo suru ta bi ni
are in love...
sabishigari ni naru
...They become lonely.
itsudaatte
As they do.
Girls in love
Girls in Love
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
Because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
Girls in love
Girls in Love
Motto dakishimete yo
Hold me closer
Yume no naka made tsuretette
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Next Time:
It's finally the second audition, Miru-chan!
Let's do our best and make it.
Yeah.
Watch me, Yui-senpai.
I'll definitely become a Lemon Angel.
Ann...
Eh?
I am...
Next time on Lemon Angel Project, episode 6, "Promise You".
I want to be like Ann...
You mean that Ann from Lemon Angel?