Ah, Kou-chan, good morning.
Yeah... Good-mor-ning...
Your basketball game is today, right? I'll come and cheer you on!
O-Okay...
Your pussy tastes so delicious, Ren-chan!
W-What are you saying...?
You have wonderful breasts too!
You're already wet!
I can't help it, it feels too good...
Well then, I'm putting it in.
It feels so good, Ren-chan.
Your pussy is so warm and wet! It's the best!
Kou-chan! D-Don't!
No!!
Now it's my turn.
How lewd, Kou-chan.
Your cock has become so big.
Oh? So you're into this kind of stuff?
What a pervert.
I-It's not like that...
But your cock is quivering.
Embarrassing, isn't it?
You're feeling good merely by being rubbed by my feet.
You couldn't possibly let the others see that.
Yay! You've become even bigger!
Fantasizing about having others see this excites you!
Ren-chan, I can't-!
You're about to cum.
P-e-r-v-e-r-t.
You should just gratefully cum thanks to my feet!
You're the worst.
You sullied my body. Lick it off, everything.
Yes, ma'am.
How adorable.
You're my slave now.
Let's make Onii-chan one as well.
Shikkaku presents
Kansen 3 Shuto Houka
To think that the school is connected to such a place...
It's not just Tokyo which has tunnels like this, many old cities have similar mazing tunnels.
We have to be very careful not to get lost.
It depends on those guys.
Let's go.
Didn't Unknown Level 4 become extinct in the northeast?
The infection doesn't become extinct.
The virus has just probably been in hibernation for the past four years.
What should we do now?
Be quiet.
Huh? Didn't I just hear my Onii-chan?
Ren!
Wait!
Let's wait a little longer.
I knew it! It is Onii-chan's voice!
Onii-chan, open the door already!
The way she's talking!
Wataru, don't open it.
Ren is infected.
What?
Onii-chan, hurry up and open the door! I want to see you!
Ren-chan is... infected?
Yuuho-chan?
You're telling him not to open it, aren't you?
No, I didn't!
Yuuho, stand back!
So Maruko-senpai is with you?
How cruel! Are you two trying to steal my Onii-chan from me?
No, we're not!
Yuuho!
Yuuho-chan, Maruko-senpai...
I'll kill you!
I will kill everyone who tries to take my Onii-chan away!
Ren, calm down! Please!
Ren-chan, what happened?
Kousuke? Don't tell me...
What are you doing?
What happened, Kousuke?
Yoshino-san? Waka-chan?
They're all infected.
Yuuho and Maruko-senpai are in there.
Hey, open up, please!
Have sex with me!
Ayase-kun is in there? Open up!
Open the door!
Open it!
Onii-chan, I love you so much more than Yuuho and Maruko-senpai!
I'm sorry I couldn't save you...
Let's go, Wataru.
Maruko-senpai?
Give up on her.
But!
Why did you risk your life to save Yuuho?
Was it so that you could die together in here?
I got it.
Wataru...
Let's go, Yuuho.
Farewell, Ren, Kousuke.
If they managed to break down the door, we wouldn't stand a chance against them.
We should go to Hiko-chan's safe house.
The
Depo
That's it for our weaponry.
Next is our food supply, I guess.
Will this be enough to escape from Tokyo?
It seems you're not infected.
Even if we were, we wouldn't have hidden.
Neither of us would have.
Mizuki!
Wataru, Yuuho!
You know them?
Yes.
We're childhood friends. We were in the same grade at school.
So she's the odd one out, is she?
Same goes for you.
What about Kousuke? Isn't he with you?
Sorry...
I see...
Escaping to the sea via the underground Shibuya river?
It's better than barricading ourselves in here.
For now, we should go to the manga cafe below us and use the Internet there to check out what's happening outside.
Let's take a shower first.
Coming here was a good move.
There's panic throughout Japan.
The politicians seem to have taken shelter on Miyake Island.
This is...
Dad!
This is a broadcast from the Tokyo Mouse Kingdom's underground restaurant.
As of right now, food and water are still sufficient. But we have yet to see any sign of a rescue party.
So he's fine...
What's the date on it?
That's the news from three days ago.
So we can't say for sure that he's still alive...
Don't worry, I'm sure he's fine.
Yeah...
We should go to sleep now and make plans for our escape from Tokyo tomorrow.
Yuu-tan...
Women...
Onii-chan, where are you?
Just like the roar of animals...
So this is where you've been.
I couldn't sleep.
I wonder why it turned out like this.
What did we do to deserve this?
The Lord's wrath burns the land.
The children under the fire's fury do not help each other.
Instead, they hunger after consuming the ones on the right.
Still unsatisfied after devouring the ones on the left.
Now they maul each other.
Is it from the Bible?
It's the 9th chapter of Isaiah.
So Unknown Level 4 is God's fearful wrath?
To me, this could be even salvation.
Unknown Level 4 is salvation, you say?
From our perspective, it may seem like the pits of hell,
but how do you think they feel about it?
C'mon, thrust me more!
Pride.
Envy.
Wrath.
So good!
That's it, I'll let it out!
Sloth.
Greed.
Delicious...
Gluttony.
Lust.
How cute!
They're enjoying the seven deadly sins to their heart's content.
Don't you think that they're in a state of bliss?
C'mon, properly lick me better down there!
Unknown Level 4 just releases our earthly desires, which were suppressed by logic and morals, pushed on to us by society.
By acting according to their desires, they enjoy themselves to the fullest.
Then aren't they the same as animals?
There's not a big difference in the first place.
It may be the case that the infected show the true form of humans,
where as we, standing on the side watching them,
might be the strange ones.
If you like it so much, why don't you go ahead and infect yourself with it?
I don't like having my brain destroyed in exchange for pleasure.
The cost is just too big.
It's the same as drugs, huh?
Well then, I'll be sleeping downstairs.
The infected are showing humanity's true form...
I don't want to believe it.
I guess you're right.
There's less information day after day.
The day before yesterday, it was Hiroshima. Yesterday, there wasn't any information from Kobe.
What is it, Wataru?
We've lost communication to the underground shelter in Tokyo Mouse Kingdom as of yesterday.
We have received information that infected have appeared, and that they are now under a state of alert...
I repeat...
Not only Ren, but now even Dad has...
Wataru!
Are you alright?
I'm going to get some fresh air on the roof.
Mom... Were you able to meet up with Dad?
Is it a fever? I should take some medicine.
Is Yuuho still sleeping?
I'll go check on her later.
Her face was a little red yesterday. Maybe she caught a cold.
Yuuho.
I brought you some-
What's with this mess?
Wataru...
Yuuho, what's wrong with you?
I'm hungry...
I brought you some food, so eat up.
Yuuho... Are you possibly infected...?
N-No, it's nothing, nevermind.
I'm full, so I'm going to bed.
Yuuho...
Welcome back.
How's Yuuho?
Seems she caught a cold.
Anyway, she said she'll take some medicine and stay quiet for a few days.
I'll bring her meals to her.
Is that so?
Does it taste good?
Yeah... It's yummy...
I see, thank goodness.
Wata-ru, pee...
What?! Oh wait! I'll take you to the toilet!
I didn't make it...
No problem, I'll wipe you clean and change your clothes.
Okay...
Look, you're clean now.
Now put on your pants.
No... I want more...
Make me feel good...
Yuuho...?
Please...
Your finger is rubbing me...
Wataru... Move your finger!
I'm so happy, Wataru...!
Does this feel good?
Yes...
Now lick my clitoris...!
Ah! Amazing!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
This time I will make you feel good.
Wataru's penis is so cute...
Yu-Yuuho, I-I'm about to cum!
Wataru's fresh semen... is so delicious...
This time, I'll give you my breasts.
Your penis has become grown again...!
Well then, let's please each other...
Yu-Yuuho!
Your large cock is entering me!
It feels so good!
Yuuho, if you move this much, I-I'll-!
You'll cum?
Wataru, pour your hot semen inside me!
Okay-!
Your insides feel too good!
I-I can't hold back anymore!
I'm cumming too!
Good night, Yuuho.
The Japanese authority seem to have set up a temporary government on Miyake Island.
The timing isn't a coincidence.
The United Nation forces seem to be revising a rescue operation in Japan.
So that means that their secret discussions with the UN have finished.
Most likely. That probably means they're going to make arrangements with the other nations.
It's just like a war.
I'll bring Yuuho some dinner.
Yuuho, I brought you dinner.
Wataru, I'm gonna part ways from you guys...
Because I think I'm at my limit...
Yuuho...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry to cause you trouble till the end...
Yuuho-!
Looks like I can't even move...
Kill me...
Before I kill you...
I can't!
Wataru...
I love you...
I love you too!
That's why you have to shoot me...
Thank you...
Don't be an idiot!
Please let me die!
Do you think Yuuho would be happy if you did?!
Yuuho died because she wanted you to live.
Yuuho-!
How is he?
I forcefully gave him some antipyretic and let him sleep.
Mizuki and I are going to secure our escape route, so keep an eye on Wataru.
Okay.
With Mom, Dad, Ren, and Yuuho gone...
what am I living for?
The
Depo
At the Laser building, Maruko-senpai or Jin-san will probably stop me...
But here, I can die without any interruption.
Maruko-senpai?
I-I can't stop-!
My vagina is hot!
My clitoris is getting hard like a penis!
W-Whoa...
It feels so good that I might die!
I'll die!
I'll die-!
I'm,
I'm-!
S-She came!
M-Me too...
It's no use, it's not enough.
It's... not enough!
Wataru... Lick me here...
What?!
Who is it?!
Wataru, were you watching?!
Yes...
I'm sorry... Go ahead and think of me as a lewd girl.
That's not true! You were wonderful, Maruko-senpai!
Really...
Um, are you erect?
Huh? Oh, yes! Very much so...
If you don't mind, could you... actually lick me here?
Please! I can't satisfy myself any longer!
Maruko-senpai?
C'mon, Wataru! Please lick me!
Y-You're surprisingly good!
Suck my clitoris too.
Yes!
That's right.
It's so good!
You were amazing, Wataru...
Let me lick you this time.
You're quite sturdy despite your cute face.
Se-Senpai-!
I-I'm-!
You let out so much-!
Also, it's thick like jelly!
You're ready to go again?
I won't let you go until I'm satisfied.
Yes please!
Then I'll put it in.
You're tightening around me!
I can feel your cock pulsing!
Please caress my breasts!
Yes!
Se-Senpai!
I-I'm, I'm gonna cum-!
I'm about to cum too!
Cum all you want!
Yes-!
I'm cumming-!
More!
Thrust deeper!
Mess me up!
I'm, I-I'm cumming-!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming-! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
So good-!
I'll die! I'm gonna die!
Se-Senpai-!
I'm gonna cum again!
Cum! Give me every single drop of it!
It's coming out-!
Wataru's thick semen is pouring inside me!
I think I'm infected.
Yes, your eyes are bright red.
Your eyes are burning red too, Wataru.
Looks like we're both infected now.
What's so funny?
I'm not sure, it's fun.
Perhaps being infected isn't such a bad thing.
Or rather, maybe it's the perfect thing to soften the fear of death.
Yeah.
We're back! Wataru, how's dinner going?
Marie! Wataru?
They're gone?
To Jin-san and Mizuki,
I'm sorry, Maruko-senpai and I have been infected.
We're leaving for town so that we don't infect you two.
Thanks for being with us, even if it was for a short while.
Good bye.
Wataru...
Maruko-san...
Jin!
It's a much better plan than suicide.
So lets have dinner.
We're gonna leave tomorrow, too.
Onii-chan?
Ren.