Are you ready?
Yes!
Miru-chan!
Where have you been?
I was...
...with Tomo.
What?
You found her?
But if she didn't come with you, then...
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me...(Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayonaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry!
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
What are your intensions?
Yui... you used Yui!
Program.
Eh?
Lemon Angel was only a program.
For Yui.
Why are you saying that?
Besides the program, what were you...
You're wrong.
It was a crystal.
Crystal?
A crystal of formed talent.
Mainly for Yui..
You're saying you cheated her, right?
To make Yui nothing but an object.
Object?
Before I got to know her, Yui and I spent hundreds of hours together...
If you say the Yui of that time was an object,
then I was an object also.
I was the person monitoring, looking for the perfect sound.
What are you saying?!
Yui didn't want a singing program!
So...!
Who can?
Who do you think can reproduce a sound so pure?
The program was the only thing that could take us...
You're wrong!
Tomo?
There'd still be time if they arrived soon, right?
That's right.
No.
I can't wait like this anymore.
If by any chance we fail on stage...
You're wrong.
We can't transmit our feelings with just programs.
There's no way!
Have you forgotten?
How successful have you become because of Lemon Angel?
Looking at them, people gain strength.
People gain many things.
Or do you think this is all insignificant?
That's not what I mean...
Then what's wrong?
You say that people can carry the same qualifications that program possessed?
No more!
Sorry...
What is it, Tomo?
Don't tell me you're nervous?
You don't seem like yourself!
You don't like it?
You wouldn't want to audition to become a Lemon Angel?
I want to grasp that chance by any means.
I'll do anything for it!
Tomo, Saya, I'll work hard too.
I'll work harder to become a Lemon Angel!
And then I'll become your best rival!
That's right!
I'm sorry, because of me...
Look, your back is bending again.
Trust yourself!
Saya-san...
Let's have more fun!
Smile! Smile!
Okay!
I thought I could become like Ann.
But you surpassed Ann.
Sing!
Without music, it's not possible to rise up.
That's why you have to sing!
With music, we'll be able to bow happily.
That was what Yui and I wished.
The real...
Everyone...
But also...
One thing that only people can do... is to share strength!
We're normal girls.
But because we're friends, we've grown stronger to this point.
Can programs do that?
Can they laugh together?
Can they cry together?
Can they warm each other?
Together... together, can they stay strong?
It's possible because we're humans!
It's possible because we're humans, I think.
Yui?
So Miki, will you lend me your strength?
You're persistent!
I already said that I don't want to!
But...
Why do I have to be the model for Trowa?
Don't say that!
Look!
You did this without permission?!
And that doesn't look anything like me.
What?
You think so?
I don't make that kind of expression.
Of course not!
When you smile, you look pretty.
That's why I want you to always smile.
Even if you ask that, it's impossible.
Please, Miki-senpai, smile!
First, I want you to be happy, Miki-senpai!
With Senpai happy, I want to sing real music!
That... That's...
It's okay, now you're not alone anymore.
I'm not alone?
Look, your hand is really warm.
We're not alone.
Let's go, Miki-senpai.
Everyone is waiting!
Let's go, Miki.
Everyone is waiting.
You'll end up knowing...
How I wanted the sound to be like.
It's time for the marionettes!
It's time to put on the music.
Where are the projections?
There!
Ann.
What?
It looks like magic.
Himuro-san!
Is everything going according to plan?
Yes, it is.
Look at the guests' faces!
Okay, show me.
What is it that the program can't do?
No...
It wasn't like this...
Hey, we'll perform after this?
And all of them aren't even here.
Don't be scared.
Gure?
You can't miss it!
Miru, I'll leave you to be the main singer.
You're not the same as you were at the audition.
I believe in you.
What Gure said is right!
Yup!
Yeah!
Go, Go!
Only four?
And the leader isn't there?
What's this?
Go back to the 1st!
That's right!
No...
This way...
Tomo?
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yeah!
Hurray!
Tomo!
I'm sorry.
Senpai...
I couldn't forgive...
Yui's precious heart...
It was also stolen...
The same for Himuro.
And...
But Yui has always treated me well.
I got lost in hate.
And didn't even think what Yui thought about me.
Thank goodness for you.
If I continued on like this...
I...
Miki-senpai!
Damn!
Hey, do what we agreed!
Hey, hey, are you serious?
Do it!
What?
What's going on?
A power outage?
What is it?
A blackout?!
Quick, find out what happened!
And the auxiliary system?
It's inaccessible!
People...
W-What's that?
Tomo?
This is...
Yui, are you listening?
Impossible!
I'll also collaborate.
The lights!
Are you ready?
Damn you, What're you doing?!
Himuro-san...
Himuro, this is the sound that I couldn't do with you.
They made it.
Uh, Tomo!
Yuki-chan, you're going to practice now?
Yes!
Tomo, you're already going home?
Of course not, I also have work today!
Good luck!
You'll get left behind!
Senpai, I'll get there first!
Tomo, you actually work hard with those little legs!
Ooh!
I won't lose to you!
Right! Let's see who gets there first!
Hey!
Guys!
Fuyumi-chan, Miru-chan, let's race!
Ah, okay!
Dear Yui-senpai...
I... will sing forever!
Together with my dearest friends!
Yes.
While there will be people... that will listen to us...
Never give up!