SubDESU-H Presents
Okay, wait a second while I mark these.
Well... this is wrong... wrong...
I just had to I get stuck with Sanae tutoring...
How the hell is she such a good student, anyway?
Masato this one's wrong.
You see, here?
Here this y shouldn't equal to zero, right?
Y's minimum value is minus 18, so it equals 3. Understood?
Hey... Dont stick too close!
Don't tell me you got turned on!
Then lets take a break from studying and have sex
Idiot..Hurry up and give me the next question.
Darn...
Hey!
C'mmon... you can be forward about it! We go way back so I'll have you for real.
...noying.... annoying... annoying!
Stop it.. I'm not interested in you.
But your interested in sex right?
I'll squeeze your dick here, make it all slippery
and suck you while I do you with my tits.
Sounds good, doesn't it?
It's not like pressing that flab against me will turn me on.
You're just nervous it's your first time...
Let go! You're not helping!
It's alright just leave it to me!
C'mmon... let's do it...
Would you stop that!?
Aw man.. I'm drenched...
Great... now the carpet's all stained!
What's with the attitude...
Worry about me for a bit will you.
Gosh, will you shut up!
Dammit... I'll get you a change of clothes...
No, it's fine...
It'll dry if we leave it be.
We can't just leave it like that.
But...
You know... It's kind of embarrassing...
I'm a girl for one....
Don't say weird stuff. Hurry up and change.
Don't Peek alright!
There's no way I would!
What's up with that!?
Just now she was suggesting we had sex...
Now she gets all awkard...
What's with the hot body?
That's right... she always wears baggy clothes so I never noticed!
Hey! what are you doing?
It's your tighs's fault!
I can't stop myself!
Don't make fun of me! My legs are fat and ugly, right?
Wait!
Stop it. Don't lick it!
Masato! Stop it!
No! I'm sweaty!
I came..
Sorry...
Why did you get off from my legs?
It's weird...
My bad...
I only care for those plump legs of yours!
Is that true?
If you want to, you can go on.
He's getting that hard from my legs?
He must really like legs...
I want to do it too...
Sanae...
Masato..I want it!..I want your cock!
Sanae!
When I was doing Sanae's legs I wanted to come again, right there.
But it would be too rude for her...
It's awesome inside...
My dick is slipping inside that wet thing!
This is seriously good!
Masato... kiss me...
Sanae...
Masato... Masato... I love it!
More... do it more!
More! Mess me up with it! Do it!
1-2 Days Later
Good Evening!
Oh Sanae-chan. Sorry for leaving my idiot son in your care.
Not at all.. excuse me!
Hi...
Oh, hey!
Idiot..Don't stare at me like that.
It's embarrassing...
Crap... I might seriously get addicted to her...
There, you like this right?
Lick it like you mean it!
I've had them on during practice..smells good right?
Wow... what a spunk!
Getting off from licking feet... You really are a perv...
Right... Hashimoto-Senpai?
Ever since Yaoi-chan got her hands on my weakness...
We've been involved like this...
Are you getting horny from my feet?
Tell me sempai...
It feels good...
I want to cum with Yaoi-Chan!
Her feet... her breasts... I want to cum all over her!
Okay! That's all folks!
Too bad senpai!
Gosh this penis... its the best!
Ever since we started this.. she hasn't let me cum once.
I always knew she wouldn't do it 'till the end...
But was nearing my limit.
I held back my feelings of aggression the best I could!
Now... if you come I'll punish you!
It all started a week ago.
Yaoi-Chan's really cool!
She's usually very discrete, but
during practice her presence doubles!
So nice... and cute to boot!
It's no wonder you like her...
Idiot! Don't say it out loud!
Truth is I wanted  to have Yaoi-chan right there.
That day I heard that the cheering club had left
for a joint rehearsal in another school...
All I can say is I felt as if possessed by evil!
Ya-Yaoi-Chan!
S-Senpai... what are you doing?
Ya-Yaoi-Chan
Wa-Wait... it's not what you think.
I got in by mistake.
What's with me today...
Ya-Yaoi-Chan?
What are you talking about, you pervert?
That's when my days of being played with by Yaoi-Chan began.
What a lame expression..
Awesome!
At first it was just as pranks...
But it kept escalating... And now...
So..how about this....
Get bigger for me.
Il take a lot more embarrassing photos.
Hey... I made the effort of showing this to you!
Maybe this then...
Is it good?
Come on senpai... you can cum if you want to.
But if you do I'll spread those photos.
So... how long can you hold on...?
It's the first time she used her mouth... no way...
She never licked anything until now...
I can do way better!
It's... so good...
Doesn't even compare to feet or hands!
It's warm and soft...
If this keeps up I'm gonna...
Bad... boy....
I'm not letting you cum yet...
He didn't notice it did he...?
I can't take it anymore!
I..I sucked Senpai's cock.
I did fellatio!
It was so hot and pulsing.
If I stick it in here, I can feel even better.
Oh gosh...
I have to hurry or someone might come.
Now then.. how should I tease you next?
Where did he go?
What?
I...I can't move. Senpai was this strong?
Stop..stop it... it's like I'm some sort of usable woman thing.
I'm sorry.
You're supposed to be my toy.
You come and enjoy yourself on your own.
It's not fair!
I'm gonna enjoy it much more than you now!
Y-Yaoi-Chan.. I...
It's fine... just shut up...
Could it be your first time...?
Shut-up! Don't say it idiot!
Senpai... move...
But..
Just do it... Hurry!
It feels so good I don't know what's going on anymore.
My mind is fading...
Yaoi-Chan is all that matters now!
If you do it that hard I'll go crazy inside!
Yaoi-Chan!
I'm sorry...
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I'll make you my toy thing for good!