Papa... Mama...
Mama!
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
Honto no watashi wo uketomete
Please accept the real me.
Mayanaka ni shinobikomu anata no kokoro
In the middle of the night
Suki wa aru no kana?
I wonder if there's a way into your heart.
Password te ni irete Log in suru wa
Retrieve the password and login...
kakushin ni furetai
and get to the heart of things.
Koi wo shiteru Virus
The virus of love
out of my control
Tomerarenai Angel Addict
...cannot be stopped. Angel, hurry.
Watashi dake mitsumete yo (Only me...)
Just look at me... (Only me...)
Hokano dareka ga iya
Don't want you looking at anyone else!
Todokanai kyori wo ichi miri Motto chijimete...
Shorten the distance between us even if by only a single millimeter.
honto no watashi wo
It's the real me.
honto no watashi wo dakishimete
It's the real me... so hold me tight.
It's finally today.
Yeah.
Hi! Bonjour! How are you holding up?
Don't worry about others today,
you should be worrying more about yourself.
That's true.
No matter the result - no regrets, clear?
Yeah.
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Ah...
Miru-chan.
Good morning.
Everyone, you've all done your best.
Today, the new Lemon Angels will be born.
Do your best. I'll be watching from the audience.
Talent Waiting Room
Okay!
What should I do? I'm so nervous. My heart is beating so fast.
Yumi, when you're nervous,
the best thing to do is to relax and focus on something else.
I-I have to do my best. 'Cause even with all the training, I'm still not that good.
Tomo, don't overdo it.
One, two, three and fou-
I'm sorry. Who's is this?
This is yours, Miru-chan? I... I'm-
Everyone on standby.
Hitoshi, time to go. Hitoshi?
Hitoshi!
Huh?
What should I do?
Tomo...
Huh? The rip...
I just patched it.
That was fast.
Go give it to her.
'Kay.
The audition will take place any moment now.
Miru-chan, here.
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's been mended.
Uh, not by me though.
Thank you.
I-I was the one who ripped it after all...
Are you cold?
Au... di... tion...
Huh?
Self introduction. Make it appealing. They said.
Ah. Oh.
Yeah,it's gonna be a tough one.
I'm not quite sure how to handle it myself.
I think if you just act natural, and sorta greet everyone...
Ya know, "Hey, how's it goin'."
"How's it goin'?"
Yeah.
How's it goin'.
That's not acting natural...
Huh? It's time already? Miru-chan, hurry and change.
Finally, I've made it this far.
Ya ya ya, welcome to the night of destiny...
to see the start of a new legend!
Lemon Angel, Act 2, The Last Audition.
You remember how they exploded onto the scene? Yeah! Lemon Angel!
Drawing off their success, today we have a real show for you.
It'll be okay. It's just like being in the studio.
That's right! Ten finalists! So, come on, here we go!
This is just like...
Just like...
Nothing like the studio!
They look a little stiff.
He's fine,
just have to leave him alone.
And he is?
Katagiri Hitoshi-san.
Katagiri...
Áh! Katagiri Hitoshi? Him?
Now it's time for the Self Intro appeal.
Entry number one...
...Yohko Taguchi!
It's nice to meet all of you. The reason I want to become a Lemon Angel is...
...ever since I was little, I've always admired idols.
I thought someday I wanted to be just like them,
and when I found out about the audition...
Evening, everyone.
I've been going to singing school since way back. I'd like to thank my teacher from back then.
But I think the reason I became a candidate was because...
On your days off, please fax me your drawings.
I have my own blog, so please come and read it.
The blog is called Asami's Miracle...
Next! Entry number five, Fuyumi Sakakibara.
Yumi, go for it.
Haruka's watching.
Huh?
You have to give it your all. Not just for you, but for Haruka too.
Haruka-chan... yep, I gotta.
I may not look it, but I'm from the Kansai region.
I've been going to a school for the performing arts since I was little.
An old friend of mine from there made me promise to do my best until the end.
And I think it's okay, even for me, to try and see a dream through to it's end.
Bonjour! I'm Erika.
In the country I was born in, bonjour means good morning.
Though saying good morning at night? The world of show business has weird customs, I guess.
Hello, hello, everyone. Actually, I'm not used to being here.
Yayoi-chan!
You've done photo spreads!
Hey, you! Don't call me Yayoi! I'm Saya! Yuki Saya!
Wow! A string of cool comments. Gives me the chills.
And next we have entry number 11, Tomo Minaguchi.
Now my turn?
Tomo-chan's walking is off.
Yay!
Whoops...
I-I'm Tomo!
Tomo!
Everyone!
Yes!
Happy?
Happy!
Do you know...
Yes?
All about me?
S-Seriously? No one knows?
Even with this many people here?
Tomo! Say something!
Now hold on! It was in the magazine. At least one of you should have checked it out beforehand!
This is no laughing matter!
What?
Nothing.
You're all teasing me!
I said nothing.
Okay, okay.
I'm Minaguchi Tomo, now remember that next time!
Interesting.
That doesn't even begin to cover it.
And now the last one. Entry number twelve, Miru Nagisa.
Good luck, Miru-chan.
Okay, shall we go!
Miru-chan?
Hey, hey!
Miru-chan!
C'mon, let's hear your voice!
Say something!
Speak!
What's wrong? Hang in there!
Go for it, Miru-chan!
Who selected her?
Some people are very reserved, though not many take it this far.
She can do the whole "pretty as a picture" thing fairly well.
Okay, appeal time is over. We'll continue in 30 minutes. See you!
It lacked something! This is not good!
That was nothing, the real challenge is just starting.
Hey, Miru. Don't worry about it.
You too?
Why are you looking so depressed?
Losing my temper, and picking a fight. Hey, Saya, tell me the secret to stay calm.
There's no such thing.
But, Saya, you're used to the stage.
Huh? Saya...
Even for me,if I mess up the next part, it's over.
Judge Waiting Room
How was it, Hitoshi? See anyone you think fits the bill?
I slept through it.
Suwa Miki. Wear fewer neckties. That rag will just kill your voice.
Instead wear things with elastic collars.
Huh?
I can't do this. I'll never reach Ann...
That's so sad. Both her parents are dead.
Excuse me, could we speak with the survivor?
They say she hasn't said a word. Recovery will be very difficult.
You're babying her. It's been long enough, time to stop.
Yeah, we should have her go outside for a little bit, even if it doesn't help.
It should be soon.
Won't you come out, Miru?
Miru-chan, your aunt and uncle are worried about you.
Miru!
Miru-chan!
Nagisa-san
Good morning. We will now begin our broadcasting day. Capitol TTTV TV.
The only thing we of the Lemon Angels can do is send out our songs to everyone.
But I think that's actually a way to make us more alive to everyone.
I'd be happy if I could bring some encouragement to everyone, even if it's just a little.
The song we recorded this week will be a good representation of us. I think.
For those out there who wish to grow, and find a way to become a new person.
Lemon Angel... Ann...
Miru-chan.
Miru-chan, why are you back here all alone?
Aren't you worrying about the same thing I am?
Thinking about not having done so well...
It's not the same thing. You managed to talk.
Eh?
But, I...
You'll be fine, since you sing so well.
Ah, oh, yeah. Want to listen together? It'll cheer you up.
This song...
Okay, I'm off.
And now it's time for the results.
And the winners are:
Saya Yuki!
All right!
Erika Campbell!
Winner!
Fuyumi Sakakibara!
Eh?, Huh?, What?
And Miru Nagisa!
Miru-chan, congratulations!
And lastly...
The final Angel is...
Tomo Minaguchi!
All right, Tomo!
Way to hang in there!
Saya!
Now don't slow us down.
Yeah.
And the leader, Miki Suwa! C'mon!
It's time that we all clapped our hands. Yeah!
Congratulations. Here we now have the new Lemon Angel.
Now go forth and surpass the legend, my six lovely stars!
It still doesn't feel real. We're really Lemon Angels, right?
It's like a dream.
Yeah!
What are you saying? We're only finally at the starting line.
The dream is still ahead of us.
Yes. This is where it starts.
I'd like to congratulate everyone.
Huh? What? Keiko-san?
I'm Sukina Keiko,
and I've been asked to be the manager for Lemon Angel.
Whaaat?
Really?
Kogure-san asked me if I would come on board,
so I hope we work well together.
All right! With Keiko here, there's nothing to worry about.
Don't go overboard Yayoi-cha... I mean Saya-chan.
Yes! Okay, everyone, let's take over the top.
Yeah!!
Yeah!
Yeah.
Busy day. Though it's just the start.
Dear Yui-senpai,
I did it! It's a miracle! God must've made a mistake.
But I'll do my best.
I'm here to sing your songs.
I wonder who this could be? Hello?
It's been a while. I wonder if you remember me.
Ah!
Huh? Next Sunday?
That's right. Actually I was asked by Himuro-san to please have you come by.
Whoa, no way! Don't tell me, it's something special for having passed?
Heh, well we'll see.
If you do come, you'll definitely see something interesting.
See you then.
Thank you!
Himuro-san did that for me? No way!
You'll probably enjoy it. Much more than joining the Lemon Angels.
Since the first day i laid eyes on you
hajimete negatta hi kara
For some reason my heart can't seem to rest
nazeka kokoro ga nemuren nakunatte
I don't have the courage to pick up the phone and call.
denwa wa suru yuuki mo nai kawari
Please, if for only a chance
toomawari guuzen wo kiri
When girls
onna no ko tachi wa
are in love...
koi wo suru ta bi ni
...They become lonely.
sabishigari ni naru
As they do.
itsudaatte
Girls in Love
Girls in love
because when in love, this feeling says no one else but you will do
nee kono kimochi kimi igai wa arienai
Girls in Love
Girls in love
Hold me closer
Motto dakishimete yo
and take me to a world I can only dream about.
Yume no naka made tsuretette
Next Time:
We've really become Lemon Angels!
So why are you so nervous?
Heh? But, Saya, aren't you wondering who'll become the main vocal?
Well, if it's about that, it'll be me, of course.
Huh? Really?
Next time on Lemon Angel Project, episode 7, "I want to know you."
I wonder what Kogure-san thinks.
Who cares what he thinks.
I want to know you