Hello.
Welcome back.
Superintendent's office.
This is Aoki...
Hello.
My husband's out tonight.
There'll be leftovers, so won't you come over and eat here?
Yes, l'll come over.
ls something wrong?
N-No, i-it's nothing...
Really?
Yes. l'll see you later.
Takeya & Hinako Aoki
l'm sorry. l'm almost done.
O-Okay!
Hinako-san!
What is it?
W-Well...
J-Just once...
l want to see you wearing just your apron!
That's what l thought...
No?
You're such a pervert.
Turn around.
Right!
Keep your eyes closed.
Right.
Well?
D-Don't stare at me like that. lt's kind of embarrassing.
No!
ls it because l'm not wearing a bra?
l spilled some rice.
Your meal is ready, Hayami-kun.
l hope you like it...
Yes, l will like it!
Wow, looks delicious!
Well? ls it good?
Yeah, it's very delicious.
l see... l'm glad you like it.
Hinako-san?
What is it?
l...
...can't take it anymore!
H-Hold on, Hayami-kun. We'll do it after we eat. Okay?
l want to eat this.
Y-You're hopeless.
You're getting real hard.
lt's very tight, isn't it? l'll take it out for you...
Hold on.
Young boys like you are full of energy.
lt feels good...
Hinako-san, you're really wet.
So slutty...
Hayami-kun, l want you to stick this inside me.
Sure.
Please stay still.
Hayami-kun, hurry up and stick it in.
l'll stick it in now.
l-lt's amazing!
l can feel it deep inside me!
Hinako-san, you're really tight!
More... Do me harder!
lt's really amazing.
Hinako-san!
l'm about to come...
Fine... Shoot it inside...
Right!
lt was good...
For me too...
Hayami-kun!
Good morning.
T-Thank you for dinner last night.
You can come by anytime.
Good morning.
Good morning...
Hayami-san?
Yes?
About this Sunday...
Sunday?
Oh, the cooking class.
Yes. You're attending too, right?
Of course.
l have to get better at cooking.
No, you're very good at cooking.
Stop it. You're better than me.
Sunday's Cooking Class Onion Gratin Soup
Okay, everyone.
Please start preparing the food.
Okay!
l-lt's nothing, everyone.
Please get back to work.
H-Hayami-san, what are you doing?
No, Hayami-san. Everyone's watching.
lt's okay. They can't see us.
W-What?
That's right.
They won't notice if you stay calm.
But if you get too wet, they can tell by the noise.
B-But l can't help it...
Never mind that. Look.
lt's okay.
They're busy cooking.
So, Kyoka-san...
Kyoka's Original Recipe File
Amazing...
lt's so hard...
You're doing good, Kyoka-san.
Hurry up and get it over with.
lf you stroke it that hard...
They'll notice.
Hurry up and shoot.
Since when?
A short while ago.
l see...
You were having an affair with Hayami-kun too.
Too?
l'm also having an affair with Hayami-kun.
l-ls this true?
l hadn't had sex with my husband in a while and couldn't take it anymore.
l felt frustrated and at a loss...
Then l decided to have an affair with Hayami-kun.
Me too.
My husband is busy with his job...
...and didn't have much to offer at night.
l talked to Hayami-san, and he was very kind to me.
Then...
l see. What do you think, Hayami-kun?
W-Well, l...
U-Um...
l like you both.
Then we have no problem.
We can have a three-way.
You're full of energy. And really perverted.
Go ahead, Aoki-san.
Really?
Yes.
Then l'll go first.
Hayami-san...
No, l'll...
A-Amazing...
lt's getting even bigger inside...
l-l'm coming...
Me too...
l'm very satisfied.
lt was really good...
Me too...
We should do this again sometime.
Y-Yes...
Well, l'm leaving now.
Kyoka-san.
W-What is it?
Do you want to go shopping tomorrow?
Shopping?
Yes, l also want you to do me a favor.
Shall we take off your coat?
Yes.
Shall we go?
Here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
l feel like everyone is watching me.
They must be...
Do you feel that l'm watching you too?
Y-Yes...
Kyoka-san, l found a good one.
Really?
Well?
Let's see...
l don't know...
Let's just try it on.
Let's go.
Why are you in here?
l can't take it anymore.
What?
No, not here...
Kyoka-san, you don't mind, right?
You don't mind doing it like this, right?
Kyoka-san.
Amazing... l can feel it rubbing...
lt feels good for me too.
More... More...
ls everything okay?
Yes, i-it's nothing.
l see.
Just let us know if you need anything.
R-Right!
Kyoka-san, are you about to come?
Yes! You too?
Yes. Let's come together.
Oh.
You two.
Where did you go?
N-No, we just bumped into each other right there.
T-That's right.
Aoki-san, do you want to come over to my place next Sunday?
Let's have some tea.
You too, Hayami-san.
Sounds good. l'll definitely go.
Welcome. Please come in.
Thanks for having me.
Here.
Thank you.
Aoki-san.
Yes?
Do you have a minute?
Sure.
Hayami-san.
Hayami-kun.
Yes?
Oh my.
Now, Hayami-san.
You can do whatever you want.
No, don't suck on it too hard.
Too much...
lt's so good. lt feels so good...
l might not last.
That's a no-no.
We have to continue in bed.
l'm not home right now. Please leave a message.
Hello? lt's me.
Anybody home?
You won't even pick up your cell phone.
Where are you?
lt's so tight.
l can't find my documents.
l'm feeling tense.
They might be at home.
You know...
Call me when you hear this.
What are you going to do, Sagara-san? Are you going to call?
l'm about to come!
Hey, don't you have to call?
K-Kyoka-san...
l guess she made her decision.
You know what l mean.
You want to do the same, right?
l want your cock.
Please...
A-Are you sure?
Yes...
You're really sure about this?
Stick it in...
Kyoka-san!
T-This is how it feels inside Kyoka-san...
lt feels so good!
M-Me too.
lt feels so good...
No fair.
Sagara-san gets all the action.
Sagara-san, make me feel good too.
Y-Yes! Amazing!
You're really good!
Hayami-san, l'm about to... So please shoot it inside.
l'm going to come too!
Hayami-san!
Hayami-kun!
lt's so hot...
Yes!
Ah, welcome!
Thanks for inviting me.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming on your day off.
lt's my first time going to a house party. l'm really excited.
Huh? Where's Hinako-san?
She's running late. Where's Kyoka-san?
She went out to buy something she forgot.
She wanted the party, and she's not here to greet our guest.
Y-You're really tight, Kyoka-san.
Hinako-san's cunt is tight as well...
That's because my husband is right by us.
This kind of thrill is a first for me. Right, Sagara-san?
You agree, right?
Yes.
Plus, it feels really good.
Sagara-san, i-it's amazing.
For me too, Aoki-san... For me too...
F-For me too...
You're amazing, Hayami-san. l can feel it rubbing...
Hot... lt's hot!
l'm about to come...
This is becoming a habit.
You're right.
Let's call it a day. l don't want your husbands to get suspicious.
l won't let you go yet.
Stay a bit longer.
A-All right then...
The End