Come on, no slacking!
A doctor's note?
All right, you can go.
Thanks! I'll visit the hospital.
Sick again? Isn't she just skipping?
What can I do? She's just not motivated.
Put some energy into it, people!
Oh, hi.
Mamoru, what's up with your sister?
It's nothing.
Nee-san's been avoiding me lately.
~ My Sweet Elder Sister ~
senior. 2 Mischievous Angels
Aneki...
Nee-san...
Hey, Mamoru... let's do it.
N-Nee-san!
Only you get to see... these...
Nee... san...
Mamoru, come to me.
Nee-san... Nee-san...
Nee-san!
N-Nee-san...
Well, what do we have here?
I had no idea, Mamoru.
And with my panties, no less. You weirdo.
I'm-I'm sorry.
Look how big you got.
Dirty boy.
You're not complaining?
Don't tell me you're enjoying this...
N-No...
You're loving it, aren't you?
What's wrong with me? She's my sister...
Mamoru, you're a real perv!
Aren't you! Aren't you!
Nee-san, I...
You came? Seriously?
Talk about premature!
I'm sorry.
For that.. you'll have to be punished, Ma-mo-ru!
Just look at you! What a laugh!
It's embarrassing.
You just came, but you're still hard.
Does your dick need more teasing?
Well? What do you say?
I-I want more.
Do it!
How's that, you like it?
Nee-san...
Pervert.
Wait, Nee-san... we can't...
Come on, you're harder than ever.
Wow... so wet already... oh, God!
What's wrong, Mamoru? Don't you like it?
Enough... Nee-san... No, wait!
What? This is what you wanted, isn't it?
B-But, we're siblings...
Step-siblings.
What's the harm?
Nee-san...
Mamoru... I'll make you feel really good.
Let's stop now!
No, you wanted this, we're not stopping.
I'm sorry, Nee-san...
I didn't know it was your first time.
N-Nee-san...
We're not, stopping.
Nee-sa-
Mamoru, grab onto me.
Nee-san...
No...
It feels good!
So... deep!
Nee-san... Nee-san!
I'm going to...
So am I!
Hold on...
Let's cum together.
Finally.
I finally lost my virginity.
Nee-san...
Brother and sister, going at it. Kind of freaky, eh?
Yeah.
Mamoru...
What are those two up to?
Don't be picky, at least they showed up.
Team practice is starting.
Swim team members, front and center!
Let's get started.
Gotta go.
Try not to stare at me, I'll get flustered.
Nee-san...
A... ne... ki
Huh? That reminds me... where's Yamaguchi?
Sick today?
Go for a strong finish!
Keep it up!
I'd been on this hardcore swim team for six months.
Swimming's fun and all, but that's
not why I hung on so long...
Where's Yamaguchi today?
Yamaguchi?
Unbelievable...
Yamaguchi? Where are you?
Yamaguchi!
Yes!
What are you doing?
Come on, practice has started!
Sony.
You really test my patience.
Today... is the day!
Admirable Ritsuko-sensei
This was a bad idea.
But, Ritsuko-sensei's in there...
Yamaguchi?
What's going on?
You had this all planned out... camera and all!
Do you realize what you've done?
It's criminal to spy on people like this.
I-I'm sorry.
Well, whatever. Boys will be boys, right?
You can't be serious!
Of course we can't just let him go...
Obviously.
Show us your dick.
Yes. Show us your-
Wait... What, Chinatsu!?
It'll be good for him.
What are you talking about?
Show us, or we'll tell everyone...
...about how you tried to take nude
photos of Ritsuko-sensei.
Chinatsu!
The choice is yours, Yamaguchi.
Okay, I'll show you.
This has gone tar enough.
A young cock... so tender!
It looks too tasty to just let you leave.
Look at him. He knows what's going to happen.
You've been hiding your best trait.
Don't you think, Ritsuko?
Chinatsu...
I can't believe this is happening
in front of Ritsuko-sensei...
It's not the hardest I've had, but
it sure is smooth and yummy.
Have some, Ritsuko.
Ri-Ritsuko... sensei!
It... It's hard...
Ri-Ritsuko-sensei!
How about that, Yamaguchi!
A blowjob from your favorite teacher.
Let me help.
Chi-Chinatsu...
My God... so much cum...
Just how long are you going to suck that thing?
Let's take this to the next level.
Wait.. Chinatsu!
No...
It's Yamaguchi's turn to go to work on you.
This is embarrassing.
Ritsuko-sensei!
Go for it.
Don't spread it like that, Chinatsu...
Um...
But I...
Y-You don't want to?
It's not that...
Ritsuko-sensei, I...
Come on.
Se-Sensei!
That's good!
Wow! I never thought Id see
Ritsuko-sensei fucking her student.
Don't talk like that!
I originally wanted to use this on you, Ritsuko...
...but this could be fun, too.
Chinatsu!
It's almost like I'm fucking you, Ritsuko.
N-No!
It feels so good... too good!
Se-Sensei, I'm gonna...
Me, too!
Cum inside me!
Stay here.
Ri-Rltsuko-sensei...
We should do it in the pool next time.
What's wrong with you, Chinatsu? Jeez!
In the pool?
Oh, God! Water's getting in my...
Oh no... just thinking about it makes me hot.
Sensei?
Jeez! Unacceptable!
Ouch!
Ritsuko-sensei!
A... ne... ki
So, Mamoru, how shall I punish you today?
No more bondage, please.
What's it gonna be?
Come on, that's enough.
Get a room, lovebirds.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Pardon me.
What was that about?
She was a hottie.
I bet she was wearing red garter underwear...
No, maybe black...
Damn, I'd like a piece of that!
Stupid. Keep dreaming like that and
you'll end up a virgin forever!
All right...
Wha-What the!?
Could it be... that woman's...
Sorry! I was just... with the... because you, uh...
Sony, I'll be going.
Wh-Whoa!
That's right I was using it.
I knew it was wrong, but that just made me hornier.
Please, let's... fuck.
Actually, this is my first time.
It's my first time in a public bathroom.
So... try to relax.
I've been enjoying myself.
Now, let's enjoy each other.
You're young.
Your dick is throbbing.
Is this happening? It's so surreal...
...but I like it.
Don't hold back. Cum when it feels right.
Here we go...
Wow, she's so warn and wet inside...
Do me from behind!
Like that!
Good! So much better than masturbating...
You're right.
Grab my breasts, too!
Oh no... My nipples... are getting hard!
Oh, shit...
It's okay, don't stop, shoot your cum!
I'm going to cum, too!
I don't know how I netted such a beautiful woman.
The world works in strange ways.
It could even happen to these two.