Good morning.
Shun...
Good mor...
I see...
Yesterday...
Make sure not to be late, okay?
Um, Shun...
Yesterday, you were rather forceful, but...
It was wonderful.
I enjoyed seeing you wake up as well.
D-Don't look at me, please!
Your sleeping face was cute, too.
J-Jeez!
Pervert!
Idiot!
You silly.
Shikkaku fansubs Presents
Episode 02 "This must be... Love"
I can't look at Sensei's face...
What should I do? What should I do?
Y-You're not being fair, Sensei.
It's always Ibu-chan.
You're not being fair.
W-Wait, Uesato.
Calm down.
I'm not sure what I'm saying here myself.
I feel bad for doing this to Ibu-chan...
but I can't keep quiet anymore.
Please do it with-
Don't!
Have some self respect, okay?
Just a little, Se-
I can't.
If you want to do something like that, then I won't like you.
T-That's so mean...
Is it really okay for you to say something like that?
U-Um, I...
Are you all right, Uesato?
Sensei...
Would you move, please?
I should lay this down.
Sensei... Thank you.
Uesato, what are you-!?
Sensei...
I know we shouldn't be doing this, but...
It's getting harder...
Uesato...!
It's getting really big...
Sensei's cock...
Amazing... It's throbbing...
I made it grow big...
T-This is...!
Are they all this shape?
Do they all look like this?
It's kind of amazing...
It somehow feels fleshy...
Amazing. It's reacting to me...
It's so hot!
It's as if it a different animal...
I move my hands like this, right?
No...!
His thing has gotten bigger again.
I can see the veins.
Sensei, does it feel good?
Uesato, don't...
Stop... that...
You're still saying something like that...
Even though it's gotten this big...
It's so hot...
Something's coming out...
I wonder if it will fit inside my mouth...
So suffocating...
To think it's this big...
Sensei's thing is inside my mouth...
I can feel its shape in my mouth...
I can feel it throbbing...
No... Sensei has his eyes closed, enduring it...
It feels good, doesn't it?
I- I'm gonna...
He's pushing his hips towards me!
Is he about to cum?
So much came out...
It shrank...
Sensei...
I think I heard something in here.
I wonder what it was.
Was it just our imaginations?
Maybe...
Well, the door is locked, so...
Let's go.
M-My bad.
I'm really sorry.
Are you hurt?
I'll tell you this now. Everything that just happened...
Forget about it.
Yes...
What am I doing!?
I knew you would be here.
Oh no...
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
I-It's already late, so I have to go back...
No...
Take your hands off...
You'll mess up again if you're too hasty.
No I...
You're unfair.
Shun!
Hey Shun, we really shouldn't-
N-No! Not here!
Don't worry, nobody will come by this late.
Shun...!
You're my teacher...
Yet you're always teaching stuff you shouldn't!
Don't-
N-No!
Shun's fingers are rubbing me...!
No...
I haven't taken a shower yet...
I don't mind.
Because it's you, Ibu.
I-Idiot!
Pervert!
No...!
No, this position is...
Hey, Shun...
You're being loud.
Please, this position is too embarrassing...
Shun, please!
Otherwise...
No, I can't hold my voice!
Shun-!
No!
Wait-! No-!
You're so mean.
Shun, that was too forceful!
Didn't you say it was wonderful?
T-Then...
I want your...
Your thing is so big that it might burst...
That's because it's you, Ibu.
Don't say something like that so plainly...
You're always teasing me...
Shun-!
Shun, you're too rough!
Ah, it's so good-!
Shun-!
So deep...
Shun is so deep inside of me-!
No-! Shun! Shun-!
Shun! Shun!
Don't-! Shun-!
It's so good, Shun!
I'm gonna-! Shun-!
O-Ouch...
Jeez, you're always putting me in weird positions...
Also,
doing it here is just too outrageous...
Are you going to stay over again?
No.
No, staying with you makes me feel safe...
You're so cute, Ibu.
I love you.
I told you not to say things like that so plainly.
Sensei, I've been a bad girl.
I knew it was bad.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
It seems I was acting a bit weird.
Uesato, um...
Doing things behind someone's back is bad, isn't it?
I won't do it again.
Well then.
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Here.
Deleted
See you, Sensei.
You're hopeless, Ibu.
We still have time until the next lesson starts,
so how about going to the infirmary?
Shu-Shun...
Is there really nothing else besides this?
You've got to bear with it until your clothes are dry...
It won't do, will it?
I-It suits you...
You say that...
but you just wanted to see me wearing this, didn't you?
I'm starting to change, aren't I?
You don't like it?
No, please change me!
Ibu?
H-Huh?
But before you can change me,
I have to change you too.
Himari came to me this morning.
She told me about what happened between you and her, all the while in tears.
Ibu...
I'm a bad girl.
I slapped her.
But I told her that I don't want to lose you no matter what...
That you're mine alone.
I'm sorry, Ibu.
No, I didn't know that I was so strong willed...
I made a new discovery.
This made Himari cry, right?
What a bad boy.
So that it won't ever leave my side...
I have to change it.
D-Don't stare at me so much.
This is embarrassing.
You should feel good if I do this...
How is it?
It feels good, Ibu.
O-Okay.
You don't have to hold yourself back. It's alright.
A-Amazing...
Shun, did it feel good?
Shun... already?
Today, I'll do it.
It's going in!
It went in!
It feels so good!
N-No way!
No!
No, this is...!
No... I came all by myself...
No way, not so quickly...!
Don't-!
Shun-!
No, I'm gonna-!
This is too quick!
No! Shun-!
Let's cum together!
I-I'm gonna-!
I'm gonna-!
Shun...
Himari...
Ibu-chan, that's too perverted...
W-Why is Himari here?
H-How did it turn out like this?
Huh?
But I've been here the whole time.
I started without you realizing it.
That's... um...
Ibu-chan, are you... um...
The withdrawn type?
W-What's that supposed to mean?!
What do you mean by "withdrawn type?"
It's...
It's not like I wanted to peep at you two.
But if you show me something that lewd... It's...
Wait... Himari...
You can't...
My body is so hot...
It's your and Sensei's fault.
Silly...
Hey, Sensei...
Please...?
Sensei!
Himari...!
Ibu-chan!
Amazing! It's deep inside me...
It's so good!
It's thrusting into my stomach!
Sensei!
Ibu-chan you look like you want something...
Y-You idiot, Himari...
Don't say that-
That's too rough-!
Shun's cock is...!
So good-!
I've never felt this good!
Shun!
Do it with Himari at the end!
Ibu-chan, what about you?
Sensei's cock is stirring up my insides!
No-!
Shun's hand is teasing my pussy!
Oh no!
I'm soaring!
That's my sensitive spot-!
I'm gonna...!
Me too-!
Ibu-chan, I'm gonna-!
No!
It was wonderful!
This is too much...
Huh?
It'll become a habit...