Three days ago,
I went through the first Ritual.
And so...
all of me
and my virginity
were taken away.
The Kingdom's beloved Princess of the White Knights
the arrogant and conceited sister, Lilia
is now blowing my cock.
How does my cock taste, Lilia?
Can't even understand human language? You lowlife Princess.
Shut up! I'm not a lowlife.
It stinks...
I haven't washed it since that day, now lick it all clean for me.
A Princess indeed, you learn quick.
Keep going and I'll come inside your mouth.
What?  What is it?
No... I don't want it.
This is your food.
You'll die if you don't eat.
Who's going to eat your...
Then I'll ask your mother, how about that?
No...
So which will you choose, Lilia?
You or mother, I don't mind either of you doing it.
I'll swallow it, don't you dare touch mother.
You're saying this, but you really want to swallow my sperm don't you?
It's not...
I see.
Let's ask mother...
Please Master...let me swallow your sperm.
Come again?
M...Master, please let me swallow your sperm...
Seems like I can't help it then, you slut.
If you want it so much, I'll give it to you.
Stop...it's hitting my throat.
I'm coming...here's your meal.
Now swallow it. Don't you dare let a drop out.
Lilia's swallowing it like it's so delicious...
I feel so great.
Yes...
W-what kind of expression is that?
You're always seeing me as some kind of animal...
I hate it when you're like that!
You are now my personal plaything!
It's still quite tight.
No...take it out...
Good... make some more noise...Nthe more you do, the more your pussy contracts.
Bas...tard...
The bastard you're calling is now doing you, Lilia.
Good...
Good? Great? Best?
No... No... Good...
You're feeling so good this way eh? You slut.
No way, my mouth just moved on its own.NI'm not feeling good at all...
You're getting horny, your pussy is all wet now isn't it?
Why does it feel so good?
Come say it out why is it so good?
No way...
Come on, say it.
Dirk's cock is moving inside me non-stop...
Did you say Dirk?
N...no...Dirk-sama...
Say it clearly!
Your cock is inside my pussy... rubbing it non-stop...
It feels so good...
I see, it feels good!
It's so tight, your pussy is the best, Lilia.
I'm coming now.
No, wait! Don't release it inside!
Now, I'm coming, I'm coming.
No, please don't...NPregnant, I'll get pregnant so don't.
My sticky sperm is going to fill up your pussy.
It's coming, take this!
No way...how could you release it inside?
It's going in...
That was a good session.
Did you come too, Lilia?
I don't want it... I don't want to bear Dirk's baby.
Why are you concerned about that?
Didn't the White Knights release it inside your pussy too?
That damned expression again.
By the way, let me tell you mother's location.
Yes, in that tower.
I only need to raise this finger...
No, stop... don't do anything to her.
Then you'd better stop showing me that face!
If you dare go against me, I'll take away her life anytime I like.
Yes, thats the way.
Face your ass towards me.
Let me teach you now that you're no Princess, but only a lowly slave of mine.
Good...
Your ass is already in such a state?
But this is going to be your first time...
N-no...Dirk, what are you doing?!
I'm just relieving myself into my slave like a toilet.
Stop it! That's so disgusting! Stop!
Do you understand now?
You're no longer a Princess.
You're not even human.
Yes, you're a toilet, a toilet that I can freely unload myself into!
No...
Mother!
I've been holding my piss for quite sometime.
So much... I can't hold any more of it.
How was that, Lilia? Do you have an idea what you're worth now?
Please... let me to go...
What? You want more from me?
No, please... let me go to the toilet...
Huh? How does a toilet go to the toilet?
But I won't let you dirty my room.
So how about releasing it at the balcony?
Let the people have a good look at your ass.
No, I can't do that... please let me go to the toilet.
No way, if you're not going to take my orders then...
Now, let the folks down there watch Princess Lilia relieving herself.
I'm not a toilet...
I'm not.
But for mother... for the sake of mother, I can only... I can't... can't hold it in anymore!
So this is Rufen's Princess of the White Knights.
Pissing infront of me, right infront of me.
Beast...
Pardon me, Dirk-sama.
What is it?
Chirico-sama wants to show you something.  Please go to the Arena gallery.
Alright.
Clean this place up and bring Lilia back to her cell.
Lilia-sama...
Chirico. Chirico, where are you?
Dirk-sama, this way please.
What did you want to show me?
Over there.
What is that?
What a big-ass monster.
This is an Orge, a Demon Cannibal.
Why did you bring it here?
In order to tame Lilia-sama further,NMaou-sama allowed me to bring it here.
Letting them fight?
No, the Orge does not take human females seriously.
The discharge that comes together with it's sperm can reside within humans.
However, the Orge is a brutal beast.  It swallows humans alive if it isn't tamed properly.
Also... why don't you take a look.
No... help...
What the? The Orge has 2 cocks?
That's right, it can enter the pussy and ass at the same time
then releasing its egg into their bodies.
The egg lives on in the body by the ecstasy caused by the Orge's cock
taking in nutrients from the body and finally giving it life.
Is the Orge a female?
No, they are both male and female, evolving according to needs.
And then... when they are not satisfied with their woman...
Wh-What?
Sperm would be released with such powerful force that it kills her.
Dangerous creature...
Lilia will be alright wouldn't she?
For that, I would have to tame it first.
Dirk-sama, so...
What?
It's time to take the dogs out for a walk.
Dogs? Oh, I see, I'm glad to hear that.
Lilia-sama, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Oh Princess, are you heading back now?
You guys...
P-Princess...
We're very sorry.
I can't face the Princess anymore.
Lilia-sama...
Recently, Dirk-sama obtained these slave dogs, Princess.
No way, that's too much.
They should be thanking me for keeping them alive
as dogs though.
Come, let's go.
P-Princess!
Rutten.
Lilia-sama, now... escape while you can!
Lilia-sama!
You guys...
Lilia-sama! Faster!
Now! Princess!
Rutten...
Fools.
You should've just behaved yourselves.
You'd better know what to do if you don't want to end up like him.
How could you...
P-Princess, let's go.
Lilia-sama, please forget about us.
Do you know where she'll take the White Knights to?
They should be taken to the underground arena, to be imprisoned in the beast's cage.
I beg you, please bring me there.
That's not possible.
I'll get punished for that.
I won't try to escape, I'll just check their injuries then come back.
So please...
No way...
Get a hold on yourself, Rutten.
It's splitting, my ass hurt so much.
It's been treated...
Sorry, only letting you...
Don't mention it.
This body isn't worth anything anyway.
Lilia-sama, this way, here, here.
If Dirk-sama discovers this I'm going to get killed.
I'm sorry.
Lilia-sama...
L-Lilia-sama...
Princess!
Run!
The Orge went berserk and trapped Lilia-sama in the arena.
Wh-what?
Why would Lilia-sama be at the arena?
Ch-Chirico, Lilia-sama is going to be safe won't she?
No, it's not tamed enough yet, it's still too brutal right now.
Chirico, you...
I won't forgive you if something happens to her!
Lilia-sama!
Stop!
Lilia-sama, look out!
Metze-?
Li-Lilia-sama...
Lilia-sama!
Help! It's eating me!
Stop it, release her!
No, this is so embarrasing...
W-Wait, stop...
It's wet and ready for my cock.
N-no...
It's splitting...
Hurts... it hurts!
Too big.
Too...too big, stop forcing it in!
Lilia-sama!
I can't...!
Chirico stop, order it to stop.
Please wait, Dirk-sama.
What?
Seems like it's safe, see?
The Orge has taken a liking to Lilia-sama.
Lilia's expression...
She's feeling good.
The orge's motion is getting smoother somehow.
Dirk-sama, that huge cock is inside Lilia-sama's pussy...
It feels really good, she seems to be enjoying it.
It can actually fit...
It's opened up so much.
A woman's privates can stretch rather well.
Even when such a huge thing is inserted, it doesn't tear.
So that's why...
Pussy... rubbing... feels good...
Pussy...
No, I can't anymore... good...
Lilia-sama!
Help me!
Lilia-sama is certainly enjoying herself.
Chirico.
What are you doing, Dirk-sama?
Chirico, you've once pledged loyalty to me haven't you?
Yes, I'll always belong to Dirk-sama.
Then I'll have you pledge your pussy to me as well.
Dirk-sama, you're such a horny man aren't you?
Just like that Orge.
You're longing for a cock too aren't you?  My cock!
Dirk-sama's cock is quite huge indeed, others are simply incomparable.
I've only lost to that guy over there.
No... no... stop...
It's my first time doing it with a Demon. It's not bad at all, Chirico.
It's an honour that you're feeling good.
What?
It's huge... too big...
Meow, my pussy is going to expand alot now.
Stop... it hurts.
Help me, Lilia-sama!
Stop, I'm losing it...
Such a huge cock... in me...Nrubbing against my insides non-stop...
Lilia-sama, I'm at my limit!
D-Dirk-sama, h-how could you... all the way in!
All the way in... it's all the way inside me!
What's the matter Chirico?  Getting so excited?
Dirk-sama, no... don't do this...
I'm going crazy... but... this feels good.
It's tearing apart...Miya's pussy is going to tear.
It's inside... feels so good... cock...Nso huge... doesn't stop moving...
No... it's tearing... it's tearing...
I'm coming!
No... stop... no...
I'm coming, Chirico.
No!
Here goes!
Shit! A mere human...
I'm done for... Miya's pussy is torn now...
Good... having my insides, rubbed and penetrated feels so good...
How is it, Chirico?
Can you collect enough energy?
Sand, are you here to hurry me?
Orders from Maou-sama.
If we can't collect enough, couldn't we simply turn in Dirk-sama's head?
Or do you want his head right now?
Credits:
Beta Translation:Nbobyc
Timing:Nrenz
Typesetting:Nrenz
Editing:Nrenz
Quality Check:NhinotoNEchelonV
RAW Provider:NCaotics
Encoding:NEchelonV
Special Thanks:NBokudan
Presented byNX-Shinigami Amateur Subbing Guild (X-SASG)
Please visit us atNhttp://x-shinigami.browsehentai.com/blog/forum
Thank you for watching.