You're...
Dirk!
Damn.
Dirk, you bastard!
Princess, hold it.
Lilia-sama.
Let go of my Mother.
Damn it!
Lilia.
Stop it!
No!!!
Miya...
I'm sorry, I woke you up.
I had a bad dream.
I only hope that I can save my Mother.
Miya, are you leaving me too?
I've heard there's going to some sort of Ritual tommorrow.
What Ritual?
Who knows, I'm not sure of the details.
Anyway, this may be a good chance for us to meet Lilia-sama directly.
If only we can get to Lilia-sama...
we can regain Lilia-sama's trust...
if things go well we can even finish off Dirk-sama.
What are you trying to do, Dirk?
You aren't a man who would do such things.
Why did it turn out like this?
No.
Stop it Dirk!
That time...didn't you say this too?
Eh?
I've longed to toy with with these huge breasts this way.
S-Stop it Dirk.
Stop...
Stop it Dirk...
It's the same as that time.
What are you doing, Dirk?
Mother, allow me to satisfy your needs on behalf of Father.
You have to stop this, Dirk.
It's been so many years hasn't it?
I know Father has been unable to satisfy you in the night.
No... No...
Mother's horny body is hungry for me.
See, this is what you've wanted to do isn't it?
Dirk!! W-What are you doing?!
L-Lilia
Bastard!
What have you done to Mother!
Stop it, it's a joke...a joke.
Damn you, you'd better not come close to Mother again, you lowlife!
You do this again and I'll report it to Father.
I know, I know so please stop hitting me.
Are you going to continue being treated this way?
Lilia-sama is sure to report this to the King.
Even if you're the Prince, you're still going to be sent into exile, or worse...
Chirico, what should I do?
Who knows...
Help me out, Chirico.
I'll do anything, I'm willing to do anything.
Anything?
And then...you borrowed Maou's power and you...you killed the King?
That's right. If only you have accepted me at that time Mother, this wouldn't have happened.
Dirk...
You and I are Mother and Son, don't you know that?
No matter what, you're still at fault.
N-No way.
Miya, is Mother really in her room?
That emblem is...
S-Stop Dirk!
You're mine now Mother.
How's that? Does the inside of Queen Leila feel good?
Y-Yeah.
Seems like Mother's vagina hasn't been used much, it's still so tight.
D-Don't say that.
Now, let me start to guide her along.
What are you doing?
It hurts!
That's right, making a hole at the nipples causes breast milk to flow out.
If it spurts out, an orgasm will feel ten times better.
No...no don't do this.
Interesting! If I make her come it will shoot from her nipples?
Do you want to see it?
Stop... stop this Dirk.
I certainly want to see it.
If so, let me help you.
Stop... stop moving there.
What? In there...are those tentacles?
Are you feeling good? Dirk-sama.
These tentacles are sure convenient, it's the first time I've felt this way.
If you like it, let me lend some tentacles to you.
What? Is that possible?
Dirk-sama, now what do you feel?
H-Hey, is this going to ok?
Don't worry, those things will move according to your will.
Really?
This is so convenient, I love it!
I'll borrow this for a while, Chirico.
Yes, please do so.
Juices that flow from the tentacles can stimulate Queen Leila's senses.
Once in touch or bound by it, she should be coming real soon.
I-I can't hold it anymore...Dirk...stop.
Not yet.
I'm going to let you come again and again, Mother.
No...No...
I'm sorry...My Dear.
I'm coming.
My my...Princess...hiding there peeking isn't a nice thing to do.
Oh Lilia, do you want to join in too? You are slut too aren't you.
I'll do you as much as I like in front of everyone.
Shit, I won't allow you to.
Seeing those tentacles violating Queen Leila gets you so excited, you've got some potential at this don't you?
With this, my strength isn't going to lose anymore.
Look forward to the Ritual tonight, Lilia.
Well then, Mother, come help me clean it.
Yes.
Tasty...
Mother...
Princess Lilia, did you summon us?
Oh all of you came, our loyal and elite Knights.
Lilia-sama, what kind of Ritual are you holding tonight?
Tonight?
Tonight I will have you guys pledge loyalty to me.
Yes, we the loyal White Knights are under your command Princess.
We hereby pledge to the Princess.
That we will never go against the Princess' orders.
Isn't this a good thing to hear, Lilia?
Then?
Then...I shall put your loyalty to test.
Lilia.
L-Lilia-sama...what are you...
What on earth is happening here?
Even if it's you Dirk-sama, we won't let you make Lilia-sama do such an insulting act.
So what are you going to do to me?
F-Forget it, this is all my own doing.
How about you guys strip yourselves too, together with those weapons hidden on you?
I don't remember allowing you to bring in weapons, are you guys planning to revolt?
If it's a revolt you ought to be punished.  Chirico.
Stop...Dirk.
Oh? Are you thinking of saving the White Knights? Lilia.
If thats the case, let's see what Lilia-sama can do.
How should we go about it?
Fill this cup with sperm.
Oh? Let them release it in here?
You already know that they release whitish liquid from there, don't you?
What do I do?
Lick it and carress it, give those guys pleasure.
Using the Princess' slutty body.
Now then Lilia, if you can fill the cup within the time set by this hourglass
I will spare the lives of the White Knights.
Don't just stand there, the sand is already falling here.
Princess...we are very grateful.
Lilia-sama...
I-I appreciate it.
Lilia-sama, we are grateful for this.
Lilia-sama...if you keep doing that...
Lilia-sama's...fingers are...
Princess...Princess is sucking on my...
Lilia-sama...this is like a dream...
Mother...
I'm really sorry...Princess...
Lilia, you're not going to make it this way, there's only half a minute left.
The White Knights don't seem capable of helping the Princess.
We're all dry...Princess!
Don't give up.
But...I'm already...
More...give me more...
Rutten...didn't you always boast about being good at this?
Don't give me that Metzer, didn't you say you do this every night?
Like I said...I can't come anymore.
That's my sister for you...filling up the whole cup with the White Knight's sperm, what a slut.
No...I'm no slut...
Since you've put in so much effort, why not swallow it all?
No way...
L-Lilia-sama
This was collected from the White Knights for the sake of the Princess, why would she mind swallowing every drop of it?
Princess! Don't do it!
Stop it! Princess!
Dirk-sama, is this good enough?
My brother Dirk, I shall present my virginity to you for your coronation as the new King.
Please do what you want with my...
Vagina
Please enjoy my Vagina...
Can I? Even when we're born of the same Father?
Yes...all of me belongs to brother Dirk.
What is this? Are those tears of happiness? You White knight Princess.
Now, it's all cleaned up.
Oh the seal that guards the creator of all things, in the name of the Demon King, I present to you Lilia-sama's Holy Soul.
I've been waiting, Lilia.
Waiting for the time for me to penetrate your precious cunt with my cock
You're feeling horny even with the slightest touch don't you, you've become such a slut after these few days.
You can't control yourself anymore.
What's this? My body is weakened by such a slight touch.
Why, what's happening?
Come, lick all of this.
Although I'm not sure why, but this feels good.
I'm starting to understand why my Mother...
You're almost a complete slut, Lilia-sama.
Lilia...
I'm going to put it in.
Don't do that, let me go!
Could it be the Princess at that time?
Hurts, it hurts! Dirk stop!
I've been waiting so long for this, after countless thoughts of raping you Lilia.
Finally, the time is here.
Inside me...it's starting to react inside me, no...
My cock is rubbing against Lilia's pussy.
No...no, how can I let you... how can I let Dirk...
Give it up already.
You're mine now.
You can't...no...
Getting excited already? Isn't this the one who Rufen hails as the Flower of the White Knights, Lilia?
You're a slut now.
I'm not feeling anything at all, you beast.
You're starting to move on your own.
No...it's not...
No more.
Such a slut.
It's penetrating me repeatedly.
No more...my mind is gradually going blank...
Coming...I'm coming...
I'll release it inside, I'll fill you up with all my sperm.
Don't release it inside, or I'll never forgive you!
No...it's coming...coming...I'm coming...
A bit more...let's come...come...let's come together
I-I'm not coming, not by you...
I'm coming...coming inside Lilia.
No, not inside!
I didn't... I didn't come...
Dirk-sama, the Holy Energy from this is still far from enough.
You need to do her more rigorously.
That's just what I had in mind.
White Knights, come over here too
if you plan to do it with your beloved Lilia-sama
No way.
This is the King's orders, and it's also what Lilia-sama wants.
Well then, come and fill me up with all your load.
Lilia-sama...
It has just begun.
Princess Lilia.
Who's there?
Dirk-sama, we have received Lilia-sama's energy.
But it's not yet enough, we'll have to impose on you once again.
Disgusting fella...
Lilia, I'm going to toy with your body so much you'll lose yourself.
Credits
Beta Translation:Nbobyc
Timing:NMasterL
Typesetting:NMasterL
Editing:NrenzNMasterL
Quality Check:NEchelonVNMasterL
RAW Provider:NCaotics
Encoding:NEchelonV
Special Thanks:NBokudan
Presented byNX-Shinigami Amateur Subbing Guild (X-SASG)
Please visit us atNhttp://x-shinigami.browsehentai.com/blog/forum
Thank you for watching.