This is a country bordering the mainland, Rufen.
It's a peaceful country blessed with good weather, crops and windfall aplenty.
With Iceland to the north and a wide sea to the west.
And to the South, the great State called Zaxsen.
There was once a brief period of dispute with Zaxsen.
But right now, we are at peace.
Trade and commerce is flourishing Nand the city is lifely and energetic.
Rufen can be referred to as the Kingdom of prosperity and peace....
Fire! A fire has broken out!
It's an attack!
What's happening...who's there?
Y-you're...
Dirk-sama, the generals are here at the gate.NThey want to see the King.
Don't let them in until I'm done.
But...
Tell them its the King's orders.
We have captured Queen Leila.
Good, bring her in.
Princess Lilia and a few of her servants are trying to escape from the courtyard.
We will capture her.NYour orders, sir?
Good, don't let them escape.
I will arrest her personally.
Follow me!
Lilia-sama, please hurry.
Many soldiers are injured in the castle.
Wait, why is that?
Aren't the Black Knights with us?
But you see...
Reports say that the Black Knights have all turned into undead beings.
Impossible.
They seemed to be possesed by the Demons.
For now, please take shelter in the south Shrine.
But mother and father are still in danger!
I'm going back.
Please don't.
The Black Knights are in that direction.
Let go!
I'll let you see them.
Alas, the King is not in this realm anymore.
You are...Dirk!
Father, what have you done to father?!
Now, don't rush.
Get out of the way! What's happening inside?
The King's orders. You may not pass.
Shit, we can't wait any longer.NWe'll have to force our way...
Out of the way or die!
What's going on here?
Li-Lilia-sama!
Are you alright?
Are you guys plotting something against my father?
No, why in the world would we?
We just wanted to make sure the Princess is safe.
But...there seemed to be a fire breakout in the castle.
Seems like that was an accident but the fire has been put out.
It's already late, go back and rest.
Yes, but...
Are you disobeying me?
N...No we wouldn't dare.
As you wish...
W-What?!
They're really possessed!
No way...how about chopping your heads off.
What are you doing! She's just one girl!
Dirk, you bastard!
You're still so useless after being possessed.
Hurry and stop her!
H-Help me!
Princess, please hold it.
Lilia-sama... what have we here...
M-mother!
Ah, Chirico! Help me out here!
Please let go of Dirk-sama...Lilia-sama.
No way, what are you going to do to her?
If the Princess let's him go, then she'll be safe.
Let my mother go, or I'll kill him.
Lilia...
Go ahead, it's fine with me.
What?
H-Hey, Chiriko!
What a shameful scene this is, Dirk-sama...
Princess Lilia, I'll give your mother backNif you take Dirk-sama's life.
Chirico, you...
I'm fine with whatever happens.
Fine.
That is certainly a clever choice, Princess.
Lilia...
Chirico, you...
I'm really fine with anything, you know...
Shit!
With this, I'll be the ruler of Rufen Kingdom.
You seem very satisfied, Dirk-sama.
I've also played a part in this.
Are you totally sincere?
Are you suspecting anything?
That time...
Are you not happy with anything?
Y-you're...
Maou-sama's servant, Sand.
What's your business?
I'm here to speak on behalf of the Demon King.
Please pay the price of what we've agreed upon.
What's this agreement and price that you're saying?
Have you forgotten?
What kind of agreement is it, Chiriko?
Well, you've borrowed the power of Maou-sama.
In exchange, he will obtain the Holy Energy.
Oh, did I ever make such an agreement?
Are you trying to breach it?
I remember it, I remember!NI was just distracted recently.
Dirk-sama, it's not advisable to play petty tricks on the Demons.
I understand that, I understand...
Do what you want...
Holy Energy, comes from one who releases her purest energy after being violated.
Human's souls exists in different levels.
As long as one with Holy Energy is violated,
a large holy energy can be obtained upon orgasm.
I won't let you do that to me.
Dirk-sama, how would I do it to you?
What do you mean?
What Maou-sama needs is the energy from Princess Lilia.
Lilia?
I see, Lilia sama's energy alone can compare with the energy from all women of the country combined.
Is she that powerful?
In this country, the Princess' soul belongs to the highest order.
What do I do?
What Dirk-sama has to do is simple.
Simply violate Princess Lilia and turn her into a lewd and lascivious woman.
If you do that, Holy Energy can be naturally extracted from her body.
But, why do the Demon King need such power?
Holy Energy is the Demon's source of power.
If Maou-sama can obtain Princess Lilia's Energy,
bringing all other Kingdoms under control would be an effortless task.
The time given is 1 month. If sufficient energy isn't obtained by then,
We would then take Dirk-sama's life instead.
Well then, I'll report this back to Maou-sama. Good luck.
Hey...wait!
Well then, I'll begin to guide Princess Lilia the day after tommorrow.
What happens after that would be your responsibility.
How was it, my sister?
Did you sleep well?
Dirk, did you really murder our Father?
Well, I'm not so sure about that.
The same blood flows in us, why would you do such a thing?
Mother, your dear King is not in this world anymore.
Right, Lilia?
Bastard!
No matter what, the throne will be taken over by me, the first choice for successor.
I'd like Mother and Lilia to pledge loyalty to me.
"The one who overthrows with violence cannot be the King", that's the rule of Rufen!
I didn't kill the King, didn't I say so earlier?
Now pledge that you'll follow all my orders.
No one will pledge to you!
Did you really not kill the King?
Mother, the King died due to the fire outbreak last night.
Liar!  Then what about the Black Knights?
They were possessed by Demons, weren't they?
Nonsense, where's your proof?
I guess you won't pledge no matter what.
Of course!
Then you leave me no choice...Ndo you remember that choker I put on you?
Yes, that one.  Wear it on those two.
Do you want to see what happens to those who go against me?
What?
What are you planning Dirk?
Chiriko.
Dirk-sama, you'll just have to point your fingers toward the choker.
I see... that's easy.
I-It hurts!
Stop it!
What is this?!
You beast!
What wrong did she do?
Nothing really.
S-Save me, I'll do whatever...whatever Dirk-sama says!
So please, please..
Stop it! I acknowledge you as King so stop it!
Dirk, why did you...
Didn't she already say that she'll obey you?!
It doesn't matter, she's just a servant.
I only need Lilia and Mother to obey me.
I see...
Wait! I understand.
I submit.
I want absolute submission.
Mother you too, or else Lilia's neck would also be...
The King have passed away due to the fire outbreak last night.
Therefore in this month, please put on your mourning clothes to mourn the King's death.
A day before the mourning ceremony, the coronation of Dirk-sama as the new King will take place.
No matter how you look at it, Princess Lilia is definitely the better candidate.
Yeah, that's right.
Dirk-sama, the news release was carried out as planned.
I see.
But Lilia is still a problem.
What should I do?
You just have to make a her a slut and the problem is solved.
Simply forcing her would do I guess...
No, the Energy obtained would be greater if she is violated slowly and insultingly
rather than forcing it once from the start.
I see, then what should I do?
First, let's hold her a session to bring her shame.
Letting her masturbate naked in the midst of the City.
All her Princessly pride would surely be lost.
Lilia-sama's virginity would then be taken from her in the best way in the Ritual.
What? We're going to hold back?
Alright, I leave it to you then.
Dirk-sama and Queen Leila shall enjoy the show from the castle tower.
Come! Come over here! We're holding celebrations for Dirk-sama's coronation!
The show is about to begin, be sure not to miss it!
Come Lilia-sama, let's enjoy this.
What do you want me to do?
Nothing much, simply the thing Lilia-sama would usually do when she's alone in her room.
What do you mean?
Don't you understand?
Self-gratification by touching your privates and carressing your breasts.
N-No, I don't do that!
Oh I see, then we'll have this dwarf here help you out in doing that.
F-Fine, I'll do it myself.
But your identity would be exposed if you were to go out like that.
Wear this.
Please put this on.
And this wooden cork that would give you so much pleasure once you put it in your mouth.
This things...
If we can't see your face...
Lilia-sama, you'll be able to pleasure yourself without holding back.
Why is the she masked?
Look here, she is our new performer for today.
If you want to see her face, please pay and enjoy her in the shop.
But today there's a bonus service!
This girl is going to show everything here for you!
Hurry up and let us see!
Dirk-sama and Leila-sama is watching you from the castle.
Now, let's get started.
I can't show that to everyone!
Come help out.
Lilia-sama, please leave it to me.
She's such a Princess...
That's it Lilia-sama, that's the way.
Those who want to relieve themselves can do it here.
Release them all into this big bucket here.
I can't hold it in anymore!
Please release your cum inside here.
I-I'm letting it out!
Me too.
What?  What's up over there?
No idea...
Why are you doing the same thing over and over?
Carress everywhere and change position.
Let's give our customers a better view.
Here, let everyone take a good look at your pink asshole.
No.
Don't show there...
N-No, please stop it already.
Where did she come from?
So embarrassing...
I'm doing this in front of everyone.
I'm...
But, if I...if I don't do this, mother is going to...
Mother is going to...
I'm... for mother's sake, for her sake...
But...
I want to do it with her.
Come those who want to do it, we have many girls waiting for you in the shop.
However, the show has not ended yet!
It's not too late to come in after the show!
Let's see how much you can take...
Stop!
Lilia-sama, don't move so much.
The Princess is going to discharge uncontrollably infront of everyone here.
No, don't look!
Please stop!
This... no, don't!
N-Not bad, that girl...
Wretched bunch!
How dare you do this while mourning for the King!
Go home!
Chiriko, don't think that as the right hand of Dirk-sama, you can go do as you please.
This is simply business but I will have this stopped right away.
Shamlock, Metzer, Rutten...
In front of you, I've...
How was it, Lilia?
You beast! You're...you're...
Are you already thinking of submitting to me?
Seems like you're going to be more horny after today.
I'll take a look too.
It felt real good yesterday didn't it?NIf you want more please say so.
Today, a Demon creature will take it's relief on you.
Relief...
W-What?
Now, let your body experience it.
What is this? S...stop!
N-No... don't!
If you're carressed everywhere at the same time by so many tentacles
you're going to feel really horny.
It's disgusting!
This is quite a spectacle.
D-Dirk, stop this.
Ask her to stop this!
With this, she should be ready to orgasm rather easily with less effort.
I see, I'm looking forward to the Ritual.
Weird... something is really weird...
Lilia-sama hasn't shown herself since that day.
I say let's go back there and find Lilia-sama.
But going back won't be easy with the soldiers on guard.
This is terrible. Dirk-sama's methods and those Black Knights...
Whatever happens, let's think of a way to get to Lilia-sama.
M... M-Miya...
Miya... you...
You found this place?
Really? You looked for me?
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
The day after tommorrow is the Ritual.
I've been waiting for this, Chirico.
Taking away Lilia's virginity and making her mine.
The White Knights seem to be plotting something.
Let's take this chance to make them ours.
What? Would they pose a problem to us?
No problem, please leave them to me.
I-I see... alright then.
Lilia...Nfinally, everything you have is going to be mine!
Credits:
Beta Translation:Nbobyc
Typesetting:Nrenz
Timing:Nrenz
Editing:Nrenz
Quality Check:NEchelonVNMasterL
RAW Provider:NCaotics
Encoding:NEchelonV
Special Thanks:NBokudan
Presented byNX-Shinigami Amateur Subbing Guild (X-SASG)
Please visit us at:Nhttp://x-shinigami.browsehentai.com/blog/forum
Thank you for watching.