No, don't stop, more...
Hurry, come... hurry!
Great... great!
So... great!
All I wanted was for you to smile...
Necromancer -Resurrection-
Breakfast is ready so you better wake up.
I overslept again.
It's my dream to take care of my brother but it's always the other way around...
They sure are close.
I know...
Their mother died when they were young, and in place of his father,
Lester takes care of his sick sister, Mith.
Just a love between family...?
What do you mean?
See how they look at each other?
It's as if they are a couple.
You're over reacting.
No, I can see what she means.
You see?
I think you girls are just jealous because Lester won't look at you two.
T-That's not it!
Followers of God, such an immoral topic!
I thought it was the principal!
I just wanted to tell you girls that Mith isn't the only one you should worry about.
Well, what do you mean!?
At the outskirts of Paltia Kingdom lies Aqualis, a town filled with brilliant scholars.
So, what about this school?
It means even people of royal blood attend this school.
I don't get it.
Oh, Les... Whoops, you're not a normal civilian like us.
Sir Clieford, good morning.
Stop that, Agil.
All right, as always.
Lester, big news!
Great General Rainzett's daughter is coming to this school!
Really?
The beauty that even people in the royal capital talk about!?
That's big news!
Before we start, let me introduce you all to a new student.
Sir Rainzett's daughter, Lady Pusel.
I am Pusel Rainzett.
It's only for a short time until graduation, but I will be learning with you people.
Pleasure to meet you.
Lady Pusel, may I ask a question?
What is it, Crift?
If you have a question, make it quick.
W-Well, nice to meet you, my name is Crift Mictis.
Um, Lady Pusel, what brings you to this school?
Also, do you have a fiance?
Crift, was it?
Y-Yes.
I would like to answer your question, however
A peon like you shouldn't ask me questions!
Ah, The Book Aria, Complete Magics.
Sir Olfan...
Not even all the teachers could read the transcripts written in Elemen.
Oh?
Talking about complicated books with Sir Olphan, Brother?
Oh Mith, how do you feel?
Yes, thanks to the medicine you make...
Well, I don't want to bother you two, so I'll be going.
Brother, I'll make dinner so be back early.
Yes, I will.
That smile... reminds me of my grand-daughter.
I couldn't save her, but I will save Mith.
Lester, you have the knowledge and power.
I'll have you make Mith's medicine.
Um... oh, OK.
Looks like Sage Olphan trusts you.
You know Sir Olphan?
You know about the demon hunt at the royal city?
I've heard rumors where the church is hunting down people who are using alchemy.
It's not a rumor.
The knights need to hunt down these evils to keep the peace!
You don't stutter looking at me.
You're different from the other students.
Maybe because my father is a priest at the royal capital?
Can you tell me your name?
Lester Clieford.
Clieford?
You must be Xenon Clieford's son!
Your father's service is popular!
I attend his sermons often.
Trying to find a cure for your sister...
Sir Olphan lost his granddaughter to the same disease.
Because of it he dedicated himself to finding the cure.
The knights think that Sir Olfan came to this to avoid the demon hunt.
But I see that is wrong according to you.
To be honest, I came here to look for a cure for my mother.
For her...
Why don't you have him look at your mother then?
Yeah...
Oh, my Prince is being seduced by the princess...
Stop it, Crift.
Give up, Linus.
He is not our kind.
You don't need to remind me...
You can think of me as your prince...
So warm...
It hurts, Crift.
Be more gentle.
A-All right.
Oh no, this is making me...!
Not so loud, he'll hear your.
M-Meanie...
It's so great!
Feels...!
Gentle, Crift...
Crift, let me...
Pusel... no, I can't hold it...
Please cum!
Crift...
Yes, all right...
Crift, not there...
More down... there!
A bit... up.
There...
Cumming.
No... hold it!
G-Great, cumming!
Me too!
Pusel!
Brother... who is she?
I see. A new student from the capital...
Yeah, she's a bit tom-boyish, but she has the same perfume that mother always used.
Brother, you were that close to Pusel?
Mith, hold on a second.
Here, for you.
What is this, Brother?
I know it's two days early, but... happy birthday, Mith.
Pusel helped me choose.
Thank you, Brother...
Good, looks like she likes it.
Mith!
M-Mith!
Mith, take your medicine now!
Good, her fever is down too.
Lester!
Sorry Pusel, but Mith isn't doing too well.
I have to go to Sir Olfan's place now.
Your sister?
All right, I'll go with you.
I want to tell him about my mother.
Let's get going.
All right.
I see, we need a new method of medication.
Lester, come with me.
You should learn it just incase I'm not around.
OK.
Pusel, please wait a while.
We'll talk about your mother later.
Please, don't worry about me.
I wonder what that is?
This is...
Sir Olfan!
What is this!?
Is this a homunculus made by alchemy!?
Calm down, Lady Pusel.
This is a doll.
Yes, just a soulless doll.
Doll... this?
It's true, Lester... homunculi at best are only 30cm tall...
As Sir Olfan says, that's only a doll... should be...
Yes, thanks to Sir Olfan's new medicine... Sorry to worry you two.
Looks like Sir Olfan is a great doctor.
Pusel, Mith really likes the music box you chose for her.
Yes, because of the music box, I can wake up well rested every morning.
That's nice, to be honest, I was a bit worried.
I mean, I do act like a boy.
Really? You looked like you were certain.
But it's amazing you felt that way.
Meaning?
Eh, nothing.
A peaceful time...
However, that night... Mith's condition got worse.
Sir Olfan hurried, but it was too late...
When Mother died, I cursed God.
But I also prayed to him to save Mith, but...
Sir Olfan and I decided to use the forbidden teachings...
The soulless doll that looks like Sir Olfan's granddaughter
I knew he was making a new type of homunculus...
Mith's soul in a soulless container.
I decided to use the homunculus.
However, Sir Olfan says it's impossible to get a soul to dwell within.
But if I get the help from a demon...
I finally found a book.
The Black Book...
I, the one under the moon.
Call upon the greater one!
Spirit of gold, fairy of silver, element of bronze!
Oh great one, please hear me out!
I am the summoner.
My name is Lester Clieford!
You're the one who summoned me?
I am Neipher.
Not Ashlum, the one you were trying to reach.
That means Mith cannot be...
You should be happy that it was me.
If it was Ashlum, he would've killed you on the spot.
I will grant your wish.
Really!?
For a condition...
I'll do anything...
Let me taste your soul.
How does it feel not being able to move your body?
You like...? You're more sensitive than normal.
Here I go...
Great! Feels good!
For a human, you are really good!
What... already?
I won't grant your wish unless if you satisfy me.
More, more!
Yes, yes, more!
Come, fulfill me!
I-I can't believe I'm going to cum too!
You need two things to bring her back to life.
One, a container for a soul.
That is already taken care of.
We also need a sacrifice;a virgin's blood.
Any ideas?
Virgin's blood!?
I can see your thoughts!
Begin!
Come Lester.
Cut her head off for her blood.
What's the meaning of this, Lester!?
Did you sell your soul!?
Be quiet, Sacrifice!
What's wrong Lester? Why are you stuttering!?
Pathetic...
Fine, we'll have to do this differently.
Lester, have intercourse with her on the circle.
Blood from a virgin womb will be able to do the trick.
There's no reason to be stuttering now.
Hurry it up.
Come Pusel, suck on this.
Lester, wake up!
Pusel, it's great!
Stop!
Stop...
Stop... Lester!
So, you're a pervert who likes to be tied up.
No!!
I don't want my first time with you to be like this...
I'm glad to know you like me, then...
Stop, Lester!
Stop... ouch, Lester, stop!
Hurts... Lester... ouch!
My hard thing inside Pusel...
Widens as I thrust forward...
Continue violating her.
I feel Lester... although he's!!
That boyish Pusel is very feminine now that my manhood is inside her and accepting me...
Cumming and can't pull out!
Your womanhood is tightly gripping me and I can't...!
Cumming inside!
Not inside!
Open, the gate that lies quietly in hell.
Listen...
Dispell the chain that holds the soul...
The whisper of the breath... give life!
You will find me at the dream lands.
I'll give you this container for your soul!
To be continued...