Yamato...
SubDESU-H Presents
～You Miko～
This big ass of yours is amazing.
I can see everything.
What a nice hole.
No way...
Your already this wet? How immodest of you.
No... stop...
What's with "no"...?
A perverted juice is flowing out.
No...
You haven't done it in a long time right?
I can't tell you that...
But your body is telling the truth, it thinks that it will receive it soon so it got excited.
Don't say that, it's embarrassing...
If you do that anymore...
You wanted this for so long right? It seems the juice is already flowing out.
What? Did you think that I would put it in immediately?
No I didn't...
Don't push your self, you want this to penetrate you deeply right?
You've waited for the feeling of a dick deep inside you for a long time right?
Let me hear your honest voice, so that I can change my mind.
I love people who obey their desire.
Honest feelings?
If you do that... It will go in...
What are you saying?
Say it honestly, what do you want me to do?
Please...
What do you want?
I want it to be put inside my pussy.
Put what inside?
You're such a lecherous woman. But, I don't hate people like you.
This one... this one... I wanted this one!!
How lucky of you, the one you wanted finally put inside.
Wow... amazing... it's hot...
It's coming... it's coming in deeper.. Yamato-kun's hard thing is going deeper.
Are you that happy?  Did you really like a young dick this much?
No I...
No...I want it more.
It's so good.
Deeper, it affects all of my body...
It seems your already broken.
Are you going to accept my sperm? Tell me what's happening to your pussy right now.
Say it...
It's spreading.
It's... spreads so wide...
It's so... it's so good!!
More... more... thrust that hard thing deeper!
Then I will release it inside, ok?
No... you can't release it inside... you can't release it inside!
It's hot... it's hot... he's releasing it... he's releasing it inside!
Yamato-kun's is!!
Inside my stomach is so hot... It will be filled up with that hot stuff.
Yamato-kun's sperm will fill it up.
The feeling of being released inside is so good!!
Yamato! Mom!
Yamato! You... what is that appearance...?
What... It's just Mikoto and Takeru.
Tachibana-kun...
What did you do to mom...?
Yeah, she was delicious.
What? Do you want to fight with me?
Miko-chan, Take-chan, stop it.
Mama!
Mom...
Don't push your self, you fell in that great pleasure, your waist won't hold you right?
I think it's the same for you.
This is...
Did you not noticed it? I already put in an amulet at the beginning.
To transfer all of your energy into me while we're doing it.
What...?
I put a seal in it to seal away your body.
I see, you got me this time.
Oh... you're so obedient.
I like obedience and desire too, but you don't think that this spell can seal me forever right?
No...I think its effects only last a few days.
But that time is enough for Miko-chan and Take-chan to...
Mama!?
Mom!...
Hmp... I see, well, do your best...
Yamato!
There is a dangerous element living inside Tachibana Yamato.
That was the evil Yamato.
Yamato was born of a human father and a demon mother.
There's evil living inside Yamato which we don't know when it will rage out.
I brought that orphan Yamato to raise him up as a human.
I went on a journey to find a seal that could seal away the demon inside of him.
But...
There was no antecedent about the mixed race of demon and a human.
And I wasn't able to find a seal to deal with it.
But I tried to repeat different kinds of operations.
I was successful at freezing Yamato's soul temporarily but...
The demon continued growing inside Yamato's body.
And finally it came out.
Yamato...
Uhm... What is Tachibana-kun's condition right now?
Yamato's soul is in a dormant state because of Hatsune-san's spell but...
It is still just a spell made to escape for that moment.
Also, I think we can't let Hatsune-san use the same spell again.
Yagami-san... is there any plan to save Yamato?
Yamato's power is beyond expectations.
If we do it normally, not only could we not be able to seal the demon but we could even hasten his awakening.
But...
Tell me anything! I will do anything that I can!
Tell us Yagami-san!
We can't leave Tachibana-kun like this!
I understand... There's one way...
We will use a demon to seal the demon inside Yamato's body.
And that demon is made by humans.
That's...
Yes... I want you to bear that demon.
That mean, the demons will make us pregnant.. right?
No way...
Such a thing...
A woman who bears a demon is called a Hamiko in ancient ages, and that woman should wield a high spirit power.
There are only you two capable of it.
I will give you time.
Let me hear your answers after you think properly.
Soon, there will be someone we will like,
Get married and have a child... I thought of it loosely but...
Sis...
Takeru...
Sis... I will do it. I think I will become a Hamiko.
I decided to also.
This is to save Yamato. Really, that fool is nothing if we aren't by his side...
You don't have to push yourself Sis.
Sis is still a virgin right?
I... it's not my first time... and it's already stained...
Takeru...
It's enough that I'm the only the one to be disgraced, I will bear the demon for you.
So...
Hey wait!
You're saying that you've been rapped or you're already stained but I think that kind of reasoning is wrong!
But Sis... can you imagine having sex with a demon?
Have you ever thought of the sperm of demon coming inside your body?
I don't want you sis to experience that horrifying moment...
Takeru...
Then even if it's like that, I don't want Takeru to shoulder all of it.
Sis...
And I really wanted to do it.
I have the feeling that I don't want only Takeru to do that but I...
I want to save Yamato with my own powers.
To tell the truth, I'm afraid to have sex and bearing a child of a demon.
It's more scary to bear the child of the demon.
But I'm afraid of losing Yamato all over that.
I can't bear to lose Yamato.
Because I... I... Yamato...
I understand Sis...
Let's do our best sis...
Yes...
If it's decided then, let's bear them a lot.
Mikoto... Takeru... You're ready right? Let's start.
Let's go...
This place is the...
Mikoto... don't be afraid... That is the demon which will be used for our spell.
Yes...
I chose a small rail so that your hymen will not be damaged.
Sorry, this is all I can do.
Yagami-san, this is to save Yamato, I must do my best!
N...o...
But it's really gross!
What's this...
This is for Yamato...
No...
It's coming in...
This is... good...
This is my first time but... demons are good...
No... My hymen is going to ripped...
It's coming in... The tentacle came in to my womb...
Inside my body is hot... Don't rampage that much... My womb will gonna be ripped.
It's so good...
Is this demon's egg?
It's coming inside my womb...
The eggs are coming inside my stomach...
The eggs are coming inside my womb!
It's coming out... the sperm is coming out!
A lot is coming out... inside my body... in my womb a lot!
I feel it... The sperm and the egg...
They're starting to fuse together!
How reminiscent.
I remembered this stinky place...
When I was already stained...
Let's start it...
So you're the demon which will lay an egg inside my body...
As Yagami-san ordered, let's have sex.
Even though I know this is not good but I'm already stained.
I can't forget the pleasure I had with the demon before.
Please caress me... devastate me...
Thrust me with your hard dick.
Put a scar on my body with your sharp beak.
Wrap me with your huge wings.
Let me feel your body...
I can't stop the attack of my stain...
But I don't care about that right now... so have sex with me faster.
I can't be satisfied with a human anymore.
That's great... Give it to me faster...
It's big... it's big... amazing...
I wanted this so much...
My ass... good... I like it so much... I liked it with my ass...
I... I feel so good being raped by this demon.
This humiliation... facing an ass to a demon... it's so good.
Hey... rape me... please ruin me...
That's good... good...
More.. more... stir it deeper...
This is my first time...
Nice dick... so good...
I... I'm going to die...
This is...
Mikoto... laying of the egg was successful, that amulet is for the growth of the demon.
Yes...
Are you alright?
Yes... Yamato will be saved by this right?
It's still early to be happy, this time will be the main job.
Yes...
It's growing inside my stomach...
My womb is spreading inside...
Do your best Mikoto! Inhale, exhale, breath properly! Breath properly!
The pain is gone...?
My womb... the opening of my womb...
The womb started to open... Good... a little bit more, do your best.
Yes!
This... something is trying to get out... it's so good...
It's good... I feel good...
Good... go on...
When the demon will born, there will be a juice flowing out from the body which feels so good.
It's coming out... it's coming out... from the womb... to the vagina... my baby is coming out!!
It came out... It came out... good... so good...
The pee... I'm peeing...
It's so good... It's so good...
My nipples are being sucked...
Our baby with the demon is sucking my nipples...
I... I...
Mikoto... It seems you made it...
The remaining is Takeru...
Yagami...san...
No way...
Mikoto!! Get out from here quickly!!
Yamato is...!!
What's with... me?
What's the matter?
Did you think that I will stay put until your spell would disappear?
Damn... Hatsune-san's spell must have taken its effect for few days.
That was your calculation right?
My power which awaken has increased.
Yamato...
You're just doing a useless thing.
Dman...
Takeru!!
Stop it Takeru... Stop!!
That's useless...
Give Tachibana-kun back to us!!
Stop it Yamato... let those two go!
Shut up.
Good job everyone.
This is my turn starting here.
It's so good...