www.SubDESU-H.net
Please forgive me!
Hey, Duke.
What do you think of this world?
Milady!
Please stop!
Oh yes!
Duke!
I beg of you, please make her stop.
Take a good look, Ariya!
Look at her.
I'm, cumming!
Milady!
Oh, that poor thing.
She's totally lost it.
And this one seems to be broken as well.
Duke.
Reiya!
Y-You bastards!
It feels good.
You've gotten really good at this, Lady Hilde.
Stop it, Loki! What are you doing to Milady?!
Milady!
Please stop this.
Duke, I beg of you.
She tried to save the pathetic humans...
... and became a sex-slave for filthy demons.
Great, suck on it more, Lady Hilde.
Even god won't save you war-maidens.
God, demons, humans...
They're but maggots in this world.
However you look at it, Duke...
... I also hate this world.
W
Ikusa Otome
Valkyrie
~Twilight for the War Maidens~
Chapter Two
「                         」
Avid of Lust
Milady...
I'm sorry, Reiya...
I...
I can't...
That's right. If you had been stronger, it wouldn't have come to this.
Rape me until you're satisfied.
You fucking heretic!
No matter what you do...
... you can't control us.
How funny. You war-maidens all say the same thing.
This is suffocating!
I can take...
More than the likes of you!
Scream and cry, Ariya!
The cry of a prideful war-maiden...
... let me hear it!
Stop! Stop it, please! My insides are...
Are you feeling it from a demon's cock, Ariya?
No, you-
So you do have some sweet moans, Ariya.
What are you saying?
Odin-sama...
This...
Are you begging for god's forgiveness after getting turned on?
No, wrong. Do you really think I'd feel anything from this?
It feels horrible.
Are you in pain, Ariya?
Y-Yes. This feels...
... painful.
If that's the case, I'll end it quickly for you today.
You've been raped non-stop since the day you were captured.
But today is special since the moon has been taken out of equation.
N-No way!
Yes.
Today, the moon is concealed.
The day of the eclipse!
You, the war-maiden of the moon, gain bodily protection according to the state of the moon.
However during an eclipse, when the moon is completely concealed...
Stop, stop it!
... you'll get pregnant if I cum inside of you!
Stop it!
This will be the night a filthy demon impregnates you...
... as deep as possible!
No!
I don't want!
I don't want this!
I'll get pregnant!
I...
... don't want this!
Please, don't cum inside me!
Don't impregnate me!
It's getting bigger and bigger...
... inside of me.
Please...
Anything but that!
This is pleasing.
To see a filthy demon throw a war-maiden into such despair!
Please, stop!
Stop it!
Please stop, I beg of you!
You're pathetic, Ariya!
For the sake of god, the humans, and this world...
You risk your life...
You try to protect everything...
After centuries of fighting, the result...
Is this!
Stop!
I, a filthy demon, devoid of reason, stole your virginity...
I'll give you brave ones a reward!
Tonight, you can have your way with the meat of war-maidens!
Lady Hilde!
Ariya!
Onee-sama!
Father, help me!
Milady... Reiya...
You bastards, stop this!
And that pure body of yours....
... is being used as a toy by the instinct-driven demons...
... and the humans you desperately tried to save.
Just like that, humans! If you rape them, I'll spare your lives!
People... please...
Be strong!
Please stop this! We're your allies!
Stop it!
If god... If Odin-sama hears of this...
What did those low-lives...
... do to you?
Oh my.
Demons and Humans... they made you drink lots of cum.
Sending you women into battle...
... and sitting peacefully in a place where they knew no harm. Gods.
As a disgraced war-maiden...
... they've abandoned you entirely.
Now, you can bear a demonic child!
No, please! Stop it!
I don't want to!
Please!
No, no!
This rotten world...
Do you war-maidens really want to save it?
Right, Duke...
... this world...
... should simply fall apart.
War-Maiden Valkyrie G
Duke, I'll put an end to this filthy world.
Demons, who creep around solely on your instincts...
... foolish and fragile humans...
... lethargic gods...
... you are all parasites to this world.
You may now watch...
... how this filthy world will be destroyed...
... and vanish together with your filthy and ugly beings.
It's the beginning of Ragnarok!
You seem to be having fun.
I won't let you have your way.
Duke, why?
Duke, no.
I'm...
... doing this for you.
When did I tell you to destroy this world?
Why?
You traitor!
Duke, please...
... please forgive me already.
Loki, you've been raped...
... for so long.
I'm... cumming... again!
He's cumming inside again!
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
Duke, why are you showing this to all of us!
You're still going on?
What are you saying?
This woman intended to destroy this world. She is a grave sinner!
Please!
Let me rest!
You all are indulged in lust while the world is on the verge of annihilation.
And I, a mere demon, saved this world!
You war maidens couldn't do anything even with your supreme principals and powers.
All three of you are an incompetent bunch!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
Loki, you're a hermaphrodite?!
No!
Don't look!
You're have such a hard on...
You want more, right?
No! Don't look...
I'll treat your beloved asshole!
No! Not in the ass!
Please, anything but that!
No, don't-
Your cock is...
... in my ass.
My ass is hot.
If you do it so hard...
... my ass will tear.
My insides are stirred up.
Everything inside me feels sticky.
Duke, don't do it in there.
No!
I'm cumming!
I'm about to-
Cumming!
Don't.
Don't go on.
My ass and cock are numb from the constant orgasms.
What's wrong, Reiya?
You wanna join?
Reiya?
Reiya-onee-sama!
Reiya!
Don't!
Please stop!
Reiya-onee-sama!
Don't do that!
My cock and pussy are going crazy!
Have mercy, Duke!
I'll do anything, please forgive me!
Loki!
It seems you still don't know how to behave.
I understand.
Please!
I'll do anything!
Please forgive me!
Duke!
Loki!
As the child of a demon and god, you received only hate...
In this world, there was no place for you.
That's why you tried to destroy this world.
I'm the child of a demon and god as well.
I understand your feelings very well.
Duke...
But...
Unlike you, who has felt nothing but disdain for this world, I am different and actually find it interesting.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Duke...
Loki...
If you swear yourself as my meat slave...
... I will acknowledge your very existence.
Duke!
Thank you very much!
I will be your meat slave!
I swear it.
So hot inside!
It's coming! So much sperm coming out.
I can't stop cumming.
How's that, Reiya?
You must want my cock by now, right?
Duke's cock... I want it too...
I want your cock, Duke!
Reiya!
N-No way!
You've become a war-maiden of darkness, Reiya.
This! This! This!
I wanted this cock so bad!
Yours is the best!
My pussy is so happy!
Good!
Duke, no other cock compares to yours!
Others weren't satisfying enough.
I love your cock most!
This is amazing!
My pussy is going crazy!
My pussy is too happy because it's been so long since I had your cock.
Reiya-onee-sama...
... she seems so happy
This feels so good!
Duke-san's big thing is pounding her so hard...
Make me feel more good by your dick!
I...
It's spreading... the meat in my pussy is spreading my ass open!
So good!
I like it deep. Your cock is grinding my insides.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.... I'm cumming!
No!
Milady...
Milady!
Duke!
Please give me your cock, too!
Milady!!
That makes two.
Your cock feels great!
It's been so long since I had it.
It's just like Reiya-onee-sama said...
... his cock is the best!
No good, Reiya-onee-sama!
Don't waste his cum!
You're spilling it from your pussy!
Such a waste...
... so I'll drink it up.
The cum from inside of Reiya-onee-sama.
It's so good!
Lady Hilda!
Do it more!
Drink Duke's milk from my dirty spot.
Drink it all!
Ariya-onee-sama is...
...watching.
She's watching me be so lewd.
Milady...
My pussy is getting fucked and making lewd sounds.
If Ariya-onee-sama watches...
... it turns me on!
Duke's cock...
I love it!
So hard!
The insides of my pussy are turning inside out.
It's been so long...
... since I had this cock, so...
... my pussy is really dirty.
I'm... about to...
I'm not letting this cock go.
I don't want to give it to Reiya-onee-sama or Ariya-onee-sama.
I want your cock deep inside me!
Impregnate me in front of Ariya-onee-sama!
No...
No!
Now!
What do you want to do, Ariya?
No!
No, no, no!
I don't want to see you fucking someone else!
I don't!!
Duke.
Duke, your big thing is...
... filling me up.
Duke, I'm so happy.
Harder, do me harder!
Have your way with me!
Loki, do my ass harder, too!
Ariya, ah, no!
Please let me rest!
What're you saying, Loki?
You've gotten so big in my ass.
That's... ah... no... please forgive me.
Duke and Loki, both of you together inside me...
No...
... your ass feels too good!
No!
No, that feels too good!
My hips are moving on their own!
More, please screw my insides more!
Duke's...
... and Loki's...
They're hitting each other!
A-amazing... oh no...
Your ass...
Ah, no, I'm cumming already!
War-maiden of the blue sky, Reiya...
... Hildegard, the first war-maiden...
Yes...
... war-maiden of the moon, Ariya.
Yes!
You've all fallen to sin and became war-maidens of darkness!
I'll forgive everything.
Because you all...
... are going to live as my meat slaves!
Duke!
We'll give you everything!
This feels good.
So good.
Me too...
... let me be your friend.
If I'm here...
Huh?
I'm...
Why?
Why did I hate this world again?
I don't care about the world anymore.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Tatakai ni kono mi o sasagete
I offered my body to war,
Kako o sute
forsook my past,
Ayumi tsuzuku ikusa otome to shite no kono michi
and continued to walk along the path of the war maiden.
Seigi no tame to oshi-goroshita
In the name of justice,
Mune no oku no yokujou ga
I pushed back the desires of my heart.
Mezameteku
But they’re beginning to awaken.
Yoroi o matoi mamori tsuzukeru
I put on my armor and continue to protect.
Kegare shirazu datta goro no
I used to not know what it was to be dirty.
Kizukanu uchi ni okasarete yuku junketsu mo some kaere
But before I realized it, I was violated and my chastity was soiled.
Yogotte yuku
Now I drown in filth.