Here I go!
There!
A training that can suppress your social anxiety?
Yes.
Because I'm so anxious, I can't even use
half of what I learn during practice,
whenever I play during a real match.
I understand how you feel about it,
but I'm not really sure what I can do about it.
I think I can do anything, if I'm with you Sensei.
No matter what kind of training it is.
Even if... it turns out to be really "dirty"...
What?! For real?
Is she for real?
Well, that might be quite difficult.
Training?
With only the two of them?
High School Girls' Posture
Part 01 Beach Volleyball Club Chapter
Don't hide them now.
Show them to me properly.
O-Okay.
I understand.
There is usually a lot of people watching the match.
You must be able to endure the feeling of embarrassment.
But... this is still very embarrassing for me...
We're doing this kind of thing whilst
I'm wearing my sexy swimwear.
This is already a normal thing for you and your boyfriend, right?
I don't have a boyfriend!
Then an orgy with a few middle aged strangers, perhaps?
I-I'm not...
You're constantly giving blow jobs to
a number of them in a hotel room.
What should I do?
Lots of cocks are in front of me.
I'm going to get really messed up here.
Not just in the mouth.
But in this part too.
No, Sensei...
Don't rub it too much.
In the end, they're going to spray it all over your cute face,
and then take lots of pictures of you covered in their cum.
Sensei...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming...!
Did I tease you a bit too much?
However, this is still part of your training.
Sensei...
H-Hey!
Please let me suck it.
I never thought you'd take the initiative to suck my cock.
I'm impressed, Saori.
Oh no, after Sensei said all those obscene things,
I'm gradually starting to feel horny.
It just won't stop.
This is bad.
I don't think I'll be able to stop myself now.
But... I can't help it.
My student is sucking my cock of her own choice.
Who wouldn't be aroused in this situation?
Saori!
His cock is twitching.
He's about to cum.
It feels like my mouth is a sex toy.
She has that indecently delighted expression.
I feel like teasing her till the very end!
Wait Sensei.
This is...
This is the hallway.
If someone comes...
Onee-chan, what in the world are you doing?
It hurts.
It hurts...!
Saori, could this be...
Your first time?
Yes.
It hurts, but I'm happy.
S-She looks so cute.
Oh no, if they keep this up, I'll start to feel excited myself.
Sensei, this is really embarrassing!
I-If somebody sees us...
This is perfect for your training, right?
But this is...!
Oh no...
Oh no...!
No... no...
Don't look at my pussy...
Don't look at my wet pussy whilst a cock is moving inside...!
Your pussy is wrapping me nicely.
Are you getting aroused by the thought of something?
No, I'm not...
I'm not.
O-Onee, onee-chan...
It looks like she's really enjoying it.
I can't hide anything in this form and position.
I'm totally exposed if someone sees us.
Saori...
Your pussy is the best!
I feel really horny now.
I want everyone to see me naked, to see me having sex!
I'm going to cum.
I'm about to cum...!
Saori, can I cum inside?
Yes... cum inside, Sensei.
Please cum inside my pussy.
Someone, somebody please come!
See how Sensei cums inside me!
Look at me!
Look at me...!
Well?
Do you need another round of training?
Yes, I would love to do it again next time, Sensei.
You also need training?
Yep!
I want to undertake the same training
that Nee-chan took with you.
Well, but that's...
It's okay Sensei!
Actually, I saw the whole thing.
I can keep my mouth shut about this,
but only if you agree to train me.
So... you're quite the pushy type.
You're the one who seduced me.
But I just...
I just wanted to experience the same thing...
And here I was thinking you'd be angry with me.
I was surprised at first,
but onee-chan...
looked like she was feeling really good.
The next thing I knew, I was already masturbating
whilst watching you guys.
So that means you were envious of her.
But, I'm not particularly interested in you.
So please don't misunderstand.
Okay, just keep that skirt up.
O-Okay.
It's already wet.
Actually, it's very wet.
S-Sensei, how does my pussy compare to onee-chan's?
Both look very pretty.
To the point that I'd love digging into it.
Oh? You came already?
Umm, can I suck your cock too?
Okay.
Straddle over my body.
So it becomes this big when aroused.
This is the thing that went in and out of onee-chan.
Sawa, your pussy is twitching wildly.
So you're feeling very horny now?
Oh no, this is embarrassing.
The moment I thought about his cock, my pussy started to throb.
It feels good, it feels good.
Sensei, I'm going...
I'm going to cum again.
You keep mentioning your sister.
It seems you have a sister complex.
You need to know how a guy feels first before
you start swinging in that direction.
It's going to enter me.
He's going to insert it in me.
It's really tight.
That's a virgin pussy for you.
H-Hey Sensei,
your entire cock is inside me, right?
Oh? Is my cock that small?
I don't mean that.
It's just that it's a lot less painful than I expected.
In fact...
In fact, what?
If feels good.
Now, now, say it properly.
It feels great.
My pussy feels great.
I'm getting really horny.
It's rubbing, and making a really indecent sound.
What are you saying? You're the one who's moving on your own.
Sensei.
I think, I might want to make Sensei mine.
I'm sorry onee-chan.
What?
My butt!
There's something in my butt!
I never knew.
So Sawa is also receiving the same training from Sensei.
O-Onee...?
Well, this is...
There's a really good reason behind this...
I don't really care.
Sensei and I aren't dating anyway.
And I'm the one who wanted to do it.
Onee-chan, what are you doing?
It looks like your butt also got aroused.
So I'm going to insert this for you.
Hey, wait...
No...!
No!
I don't want anything else inside me other than Sensei's...!
Pull it out from my butt! Pull it out!
Sensei, if it was me, I'd let you have
anal sex or anything you wanted.
It'd be more exciting than playing with Sawa's boring body.
This is amazing.
It's getting rubbed really hard inside.
Onee-chan, please.
Stop it already.
Don't thrust it in too hard!
S-Sawa's also very tight in her ass.
I can feel the sensation in my pussy.
No way, I'm really getting aroused by it.
I'm getting penetrated by two cocks at once!
It seems like I'm the perverted one, no matter how I look at it!
I'm about to reach my limit!
Me too.
I'm about to cum already.
I'm going to cum.
Yes, I'm cumming!
Sensei, why don't we decide the winner by
seeing who can make you cum the most?
Hey, don't just decide things like that!
Fine then, winning will be easy.
It's not just size that makes you feel satisfied, right?
In the end, I feel tike I'm just being tossed
around by two high school students...
So then...
Sensei, let's have sex!