Y-Yui...
Dad!
Stop this!
No...! Really!
Dad, you can take a bath now.
Huh? Ok.
Photos? What's up?
T-These... These... D-Dad, a-aren't these-?!
Hmm? Oh, those are of Atsuko, aren't they...
Why is onee-chan...?
Huh? What? Why? Huh? These are...
Those photos secretly taken and put up on the board... These are the originals.
What? No way!
Don't tell me... that onee-chan...?
She was called out by the headmaster,
apparently she tried to seduce a student.
Lies! You're lying! Onee-chan wouldn't...
She wouldn't try to seduce a student!
She must have been b-blackmailed to do it! Otherwise I know she wouldn't!
That Atsuko...
I thought she was still a kid, but she turned out to be such a lewd woman!
Huh? Dad?
Isn't she happily about to suck that guy's cock?
She has such a lascivious look.
Dad! What are you saying?! Onee-chan has a lascivious look? Hey!
Those once tiny breasts have sure become large!
It's going to happen to you too, isn't it Yui?
You'll seduce men just like Atsuko, won't you?
That isn't good, is it Yui?!
I think I'll have to punish you.
Dad? Wait! Hey! Listen to what you're saying! Hey! Dad!
N-No! Dad! Let me go!
Oh? You've grown up nicely!
D-Dad is groping my breasts!
N-No, Dad...
Hey, stop it. Stop it!
N-No! Dad stop it, no not there!
D-Dad!
Huh?
This isn't right.
We're family, right?
Yes we are, I am your father.
So you'll listen to me, right?
No~!
No, Dad is touching me down there...
What's this, Yui? You're wet?
N-No!
No no no! No, Dad!
Please stop this, onee-chan will be home soon!
Getting wet from such things as this, Yui...
No, don't look at me like that!
Dad, why are you doing such horrible things?
It's because you're cute!
Dad...
No! He'll see everything!
Dad... Please, what's happened to you? Hey, Dad!
No, Dad! No, not there!
Don't lick me there!
Dad is opening up my pussy and licking it!
Yui, you feel aroused from Dad licking you, right?
That's not true...
Dad! You're kidding, right?
We're not really going to, are we-? No, no!
No no no! Dad, you can't! We're family!
You can't put that inside me!
No...
No way, Dad's cock is hot... It feels unpleasant...
Wha, D-Dad... Dad!
You can't! You can't! You can't!
It will only hurt for a moment, okay Yui?
No... It's entering me... Dad's penis is entering me!
Ow... Dad, it hurts!
Oh no... I was made a woman by Dad's cock...
It's warm inside you, Yui.
O-Ouch! Dad! Ow... Ow...
Dad looks happy...
He's pleased with putting his cock inside his daughter...
Dad's cock is going in and out!
It feels unpleasant...
This is wrong!
Wha? No Dad! It's painful!
Dad... Hey, don't! Don't! You can't let it out inside me!
No Dad! Not today! Hey, today’s a dangerous day! Dad-!
No-!
Noo~!!
No way...
Dad made me become a woman...
Is he going to make me a mom, too?
I can't get it off... I can't get the smell off!
I... I can't consult onee-chan about this!
Yui, what's wrong?
Onee-chan, where were you?
Sorry, I had a ton of extra work, so I stayed over at school.
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
Oh... Is that so?
Yui? Are you feeling sick?
Huh! No, I'm fine!
N-No... I can't tell her...
Yui... Dad can't hold back any longer...
D-Dad, we can't keep doing this... Okay?
Oh, oh sure, this is the last time,Yui... this is the last...
I didn't know the pain from this goes away this quickly...
My pussy is making lewd sounds, I'm feeling flushed...
It's okay, let it out!
Since that day, onee-chan hasn't come home.
Even if I ask Dad, he just says she's busy with important work.
Dad! What happened to onee-chan?!
Last time, you were doing lewd things at school to onee-chan like you did to me!
Yui, Atsuko came to me by herself to beg for my cock.
By herself?
Nonsense! Onee-chan wouldn't do such...
I guess she wasn't satisfied with the student’s cock...
That Atsuko...
Anyway, Yui... Dad wants to...
Noo!!
So this is-?
D-Dad!
Please stop doing such things!
Yui! You're soaked!
Have you become a lascivious girl like Atsuko?
Don't tell me that you lure guys for the want of their cocks?
D-Don't be stupid!
Neither I nor onee-chan would want such-!
Then why are you so wet?
I-I don't know...
No... Everyone will see me!
How can Dad let it out in such place?!
No, his pulsing cock is rubbing against my thigh!
It's hot... He's about to let it out!
So much is coming out... It'll stain my clothes!
What happened to Dad?
He's doing such lewd things! Even to onee-chan...
Is it because we don't have a mom?
But we're his daughters! Dad...!
What do you want?
If you do, hurry up-
Wait, aren't you that guy from onee-chan's class?
W-What! What do you want?
Why are you getting scared? Disgusting.
H-Hmph! I don't want to be told that by some pervert who's aroused when their father molests them.
W-What are you talking about?
No way! He was watching?
Y-You're the same as your sister, Takagi-sensei!
S-Shut up! I don't want to be talked to by such a pig!
W-What?! I-If you say such things, I'll spread this around!
T-That's... Why do you...?
Isn't that spying?
I knew it!
N-No! I wouldn't do that!
I obtained these through legitimate means!
Like I can believe that.
Anyway, since you're the headmaster's son, you can get away with almost anything, right?
I-I wouldn't do such...
Oh, t-that's not all.
I-I'll spread this on the Internet!
I thought that daughters being molested by their fathers happened only in porn games.
What are you trying to do?
H-Hurry and get on with it! You're wasting my time...
You're feeling aroused by this?
T-That's not true!
It's-!
You don't need to be embarrassed!
W-What are you-?
No! If he keeps rubbing me there, I'll-!
You're feeling good from my technique, aren't you?
D-Don't be ridiculous! There's no way-!
H-Hey, Wait just stop for a sec! I'll be right back!
As if! I bet you're going to run away telling me that.
No... I'll leak! S-So-!
L-Like hell I would! I can't let you pee...
What are you saying?
B-Be serious! H-Hey! Please, let me-!
No! If you keep rubbing me... H-Hey, stop!
Hey! Please, please! Hey?!
N-No... No, stop! No!
I-I can't hold it in!
I-It's coming out!
N-No!
No...
You wet yourself? How old are you?
You're jetting it out! Looks like I'll have to put it in and reset you!
N-No...
Please, stop! H-Hey!
So you're alright with these being spread round?
Along with sensei's photos?
F-Fine, I get it.
H-Hurry up and put it in!
Hmph!
A-Amazing!
What's with this guy? Doing me in such...
No! Don't! W-Wait! You can't!
N-No! No way!
He let it out inside me! Today isn't safe...
You sure are getting aroused by my technique for not wanting it.
I'll make you feel good another time.
You fat freak!
Don't be mistaken, you quickshot!
Hmph!
Atsuko, Atsuko!
No! Yui, this isn't what you think!
No, even though Yui is looking, my pussy won't stop!
No, Yui! Dad, don't!!
What's happening? Has everyone lost their minds? Have they left me...?
Attention, Takagi Yui-san from second year, group A.
Please make your way to the headmaster's office immediately.
This is... Onee-chan!
Onee-chan?
She's here.
So you're Takagi Yui-kun.
I heard from Kenji...
Um-!
I hear that you kicked my dear son.
You and your family are fired!
What?
Get out of the academy immediately!
U-Um...
Save your excuses, we don't have a place for you here.
That is all.
N-No way...
I can't believe it! We're fired? I... Onee-chan... Dad!
I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me, so, um...
However, it seems Kenji has taken quite a liking to you,
so it's not like it's not negotiable...
Huh?
If you please Kenji, we may reconsider...
Right, Kenji?
Yeah.
So it ends up being like this, when a guy says to please them.
Takagi-sensei could titfuck me, but you don't look like you can.
This bastard! I knew he did something to onee-chan!
You sure are bad at this.
Sensei was much better.
I'm going to make the likes of you finish quick!
For me to be sucking on such a guy's cock...
No, it stinks! It's disgusting...
But if I make him feel good then-
W-Wha?!
Quit stalling!
W-Where does he think he's touching?!
Does this tickle?
N-No! No way!
No! He's playing with my ass!
Unfortunately, I'm only interested in here...
Did you know you can feel good here, too?
No! His finger is entering me!
N-No more!
If I loosen you up gradually, you'd be surprised how big it can get.
It's entering me again! Why does he go for my ass?
N-No! I-It's dirty!
Your asshole sure is beautiful.
W-What?
Did he just call my ass beautiful? My ass is composed?
It's untouched? It's not like it's ever been violated...
No!
It's getting quite loose now.
I can't hold back... I'm taking this end!
N-No! Not there! No!
N-No, you can't talk!
N-No... Why is he putting it in my ass?
It won't fit!
No way! No!
It's hitting my ass, it feels unpleasant!
You're quivering over here, do you feel good?
What is he saying?! Of course it doesn't feel good!
This can't be happening! I can't take it in both ends!
Why...?
I can't think straight!
No! It tastes strange... N-No more...
Why! Why?!
Dad! Why?
You said you wouldn't do Yui, that's why I...
O-Onee-chan...
N-No! Don't look...
I was seen by onee-chan doing these things...
Doing such embarrassing things!
Oh! You're tightening around me!
Yui! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
This... This shouldn't be...
Please, let her go! I'll... I'll take her place! You said it would only be me... Then why is Yui-?!
Ask that guy over there.
You two were sold to this town.
By doing so, we can do anything we want with you.
No way... Lies... No way...!
Onee-chan is... crying...!
I... Must protect her!
Onee-chan, I'll be fine... okay?
Please, don't do anything more to Yui...
Please, I'll take her place! So, just don't...
What are you saying, onee-chan?
I'm the one who's going to protect you, onee-chan!
Give me more... Give it to me up the ass!
Yui! Yui!
Onee-chan is crying...
It's okay, as long as you're with me, I can-
Since you're with me... My body is getting flushed...
You're getting even more turned on by your sister watching you?
You're such a pervert!
No, that's not true! I'm just embarrassed that she's seeing me like this!
My body is getting hotter from embarrassment!
You say this feels good? How can I feel good with such a thick thing up my ass?!
What?
Dad?
Atsuko...
D-Dad! What are you doing?
No, no! Dad! We can't!
Onee-chan-!
No Dad! We can't!
Onee-chan!!
Yui... Yui!
Yui, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Onee-chan! Don't cry! I'm fine!
When you're with me, my ass starts to feel good!
Even if it's my ass, it's starting to feel good!
No! Yui! Don't say that! Yui!
Onee-chan, are you feeling good, too?
You look happy when Dad is mixing up your insides with his cock!
T-That's not true!
I don't-! My pussy isn't starting to feel good-!
Onee-chan, my ass is... I'm going to cum!
No-! My ass, it feels too good!
No-!
No...
No!!!