Look how hard you are...
The poor thing...
No... no way...
We shouldn't... Miss Yukino...
It just keeps getting bigger...
You must've really been holding back...
No... we can't...
Don't worry about a thing Seiji...
Just leave it all to me now...
Oh...crap...
If you keep this up...
Don't hold back.
Just let loose on my breasts.
I... I can't... I have... I have...
I... I have Ai.
There... you look like you're about to cum.
Do it. Shoot it...
Shoot it all out...
Wow, so much!
You were really holding a lot...
Why...
Why did it have to turn out this way...
Good thing you got released earlier than expected!
Right, Sei?
I've been released but I can't move
freely until I get the cast taken off.
Just take your time...
Even the doctor said you were recovering fast!
I'll help with anything I can after school.
Thank you Kokoro.
That would really help us out!
I was just thinking of getting another job.
You know... the hospitalization costs a lot of money, right.
I just want to help as much as I can.
Ai...
C'mmon, don't make that face...
I'll go visit you as well too... okay?
There's one thing I kept secret from Ai...
Two million, you said?
It's awkward for me to ask this when
you're the one who got hurt in the accident.
Why?
I can't be...
Fact is, the car I was driving was a rarity.
One of the few of it's kind in the world.
It's not the kind that you can find
pieces for in the shop on the corner.
That accident was your responsibility.
I won't ask for the full sum, but I must have you take responsibility.
I'm sorry but my car wasn't insured...
I see...
We'll discuss the compensation after your released from the hospital.
Understood?
Yes.
To my surprise, the helping hand that
reached for me was Tomioka's wife, Yukino.
As for the money, I could arrange it for you
if you keep it a secret from my husband.
Are you serious?
In return, I'd have you do me a favor...
Our love life has completely died out...
It's been a while since I enjoyed this...
Wait...
I'll take care of the money issue...
So please... satisfy my body.
I couldn't... I mean...
Or would you happen to have any
other way to arrange the money?
It's embarrassing, but watch me... Seiji...
I'm.... I'm already dripping wet like this...
So... go on...
I can't... not that....
It's gonna be fine... okay?
Amazing...
Your hot stiff thing is...
Feel it all...
I'll do you good with it too...
If you do it that hard I'm gonna...
It's good... so good...
That's it... that's it...
I'd forgotten this feeling...
That's so good...
Poor things... the poor things...
Please, the breasts... the breasts as well...
Yu...Yukino...
There...
More... do it more...
Tease my nipples!
Good...
Punish my shameless nipples nice and hard!
I'm going numb....
My cunt is getting numb!
Oh god!
I'm... I'm gonna...
Feel my dirty hole...
Take it... enjoy it all!
I can't hold it any longer!
It's okay. Just shoot it all inside!
Shoot your milk inside my cunt!
Yukino, if you keep that up I'll cum for real!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
I want to savor the pleasures of being a woman again!
Please...
Shoot your cum deep inside me!
Sei seemed so pleased...
He never made that expression with me.
You would be Ai, correct?
Mr. Nakamura's partner?
Mister Tomiyoka?
Brandy?
Here's some good tea. It'll warm you up.
Thank you so much.
I still can't believe it...
I can't believe Sei did that...
I too am perplexed...
I knew she had visited him a few times
but I never thought they'd be in such a situation.
Is something wrong?
No...
I'm feeling some dizziness.
I've put too much?
Wait... Mister Tomiyoka?
Well we've both been betrayed by our partners haven't we?
Let me help you ease the hurt in your heart.
No... we can't!
Don't worry about a thing... Just leave it all to me...
I can't...
No...
No... no...
Stop... please stop...
Why...? Why am I so sensitive?
I never felt this good even with Sei... why?
Forget everything else...
I can't... I can't...
It's embarrassing but...
That's right... don't hold it...
I want to hear more of your voice
No... no...
Not there... not there...
Don't... don't touch me there...
Ai... you're feeling it, right...
I... I'm...
Say it out loud... I want to hear it from your lips.
It's... It's good!
He'll leave a kiss mark...
My body is no longer Sei's alone.
Mister Tomiyoka! I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum... I'm gonna cum...
You're gonna cum, Ai?
It's alright. Don't hold back.
But... but...
Now... cum with my fingers!
I'm really... I'm really gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You're just as I thought...
You were marvelous, Ai...
Wh...what...
What's this rugged thing?
Can you feel it? Mine is a special kind.
Am I going with this trough the end?
I'm gonna move, Ai...
A...Amazing...
It's rugged and way thicker than Sei's.
I've never had this...
I can't believe it... I can feel it so much...
Don't be afraid... focus on the pleasure only...
No...! It's so good I can't bear...
I've never felt this before!
Feels good doesn't it, Ai?
Yes...
It feels good...
Yes... my cunt feels so good I'm going crazy!
That... that's amazing!
Can you feel it? I'm hitting your uterus!
Yes! I can feel it!
My uterus! It's good!
I can't hold it anymore!
That's good... cum as you please!
Again... again...
I'm cumming again!
Ai... you didn't visit today...
I'm cumming! I can't stop cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna let it out inside, Ai.
It's hot... it's hot...
It's melting... my pussy's melting...
No... no...
My sister?
Yes, she suddenly felt ill so she's resting here.
So that's it... I couldn't reach her all this time...
I was worried as well.
I've prepared a car to fetch you.
You can ride it here.
Yes, I understand.
It's been three days since then.
I haven't been able to reach Ai and Kokoro.
They haven't gone home to their apartment.
They haven't called school or work either...
Where have you gone Ai?
Finally awake?
Wha...what??
We've been waiting...
For a chance to invite you.
Mister Tomiyoka?
Listen... can you hear it?
The sound of their pleasure...
Sis... it feels good...
Me too... I can feel it too!
I can feel your pussy!
No... no way...
No way...
Sis... Seiji is looking at us.
Being watched by him is making me feel strange...
Kokoro, do it more! Rub your cunt!
Sis! Our clits are touching! It feels electric!
So good... my pussy is getting all soaked!
What do you guys think of today's playthings?
They're both very juicy... looks delicious.
Their rubbing is also marvelous...
I'm looking forward to later on.
I'm being watched...
My pussy is being stared at so much!
We're going to be raped!
We're going to have sex with everyone now!
What should I do... my pussy is pulsing...
I feel it so hard!
Ai... Kokoro...
Seriously, they're such debauched sisters...
That's right, we're lewd... we're both helplessly lecherous!
Sei...Sei... I'm sorry I'm such a slut... I'm sorry!
But it's so good!
We're sluts! Sis and I are sluts!
I feel our slutty cunts!
Feel free, slutty sisters...
Cum all you want!
We're cumming! We're cumming!
Both of us slutty sisters are cumming together!
Watch me and my sis come together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too! I'm cumming too!
I'm cumming!
Now I'm getting hot from watching this...
You want to eat them too?
Stop...
Please stop...
Don't defile them any more!
It's big! Dick feels good!
Ai, is your ass prepared?
Hurry! Hurry and do me with your dick!
My ass and pussy are itching for more!
Wow, I'm filled in both holes!
Put it all in! More!
Shove your dick a lot please!
Her pussy keeps squeezing... begging for more!
That's right! I want to be covered in semen!
Hurry and fill my filthy cunt!
Very well! Tonight we'll have our servants give you a lot!
They're all watching me! They're jerking off to me having sex!
If you look at me with those hungry eyes I'll get more aroused!
My ass and my cunt are all full!
It's so good!
What a dirty girl...
Hard to believe you were a virgin three days ago!
They're grinding inside!
They're both grinding all over inside!
She even feels it in the ass. Truly gifted...
It's hitting me! My ass feels great!
It's throwing me around!
As sex objects I'll train you both thoroughly!
No... sex toy is too much!
Kokoro... if you say that your sister won't like you any more.
I'll do it... I'll be everyone's sex toy!
My pussy... my ass too!
Do what you want with them!
Kokoro I want it too!
Let's both be everyone's sex toy!
I'm so happy! So happy!
I'm a sex toy!
My whole body is a sex toy!
I'm sorry Ai... Kokoro...
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you...
Pour it! Pour it please!
Pour all your white stuff! Pour your semen!
Wow, if I get all this I'll cum again!
I'm cumming!
Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!
Please, spread your dick's milk over us sisters!
Make us drippy inside and out with your semen!
It's hot! Your cum is hot!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from all the thick milk!
I can't hold anymore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
With both! With both!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming....
I'm sorry...
I'm not... I'm not Sei's girlfriend anymore...
I can't become your bride...
It's alright Ai...
I mean...
After watching you like this even I...