I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
SubDESU-H
Ai
sai
Ni
kki
~Aisai Nikki~
Keisuke-san,
welcome back from your month-long business trip.
Thanks.
Did anything happen while I was away, Sanae?
No.
Anyways Keisuke-san, you're back earlier than expected.
The work finished quicker than I expected, and...
And, I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
Oh, Keisuke-san...
Sorry, don't worry about lunch,
I should head into the office and file these report summaries.
Is that so...
I'll be back soon.
Yes!
I married Sanae four years ago after meeting her through my boss.
I was able to marry that beautiful and capable wife...
I'm sure everyone thinks I am a happy husband.
However, am I good enough for her?
I was always troubled.
Sorry...
Don't worry about it.
Will I ever be able to make my beloved wife happy?
Also, is Sanae wishing to enjoying herself with others?
I... thought of a plan.
Beloved wife diaries
Beloved wife diaries_100089
Miyakoshi-san, not here!
This is me and Keisuke-san's precious place!
Don't say such things this far in, Sanae-san.
No...
Not here!
This is my subordinate Miyakoshi Ryouichi.
Since I can't have sex anymore, I asked him to make Sanae happy instead.
If so, why did you invite me in?
That's because you said that you had something important to discuss about Keisuke-san...
Please stop this!
We've only just started with the fun...
No...
No... Your tongue is-!
He's... being so aggressive!
Now, we're getting into the main act, Sanae-san.
Miyakoshi-san, please stop this!
What are you saying?
N-Not there, not there!
Hey, you're so wet already!
Sanae-san, you were getting wet from when we kissed weren't you?
Don't look at me~!
Gosh, you're not being very honest.
No! Don't touch me there-!
Well then,
I can put it in now, can't I?
N-No...
Miyakoshi-san... Not that, anything but that!
Don't worry~!
I'll put on a condom.
If I do, it'll be okay right?
Well...
Sanae-san! You've got a great pussy too!
Can you feel it?
You're sucking me in!
No!! So deep...
No way, it's hitting the end...
N-No! Don't thrust it into me~!
You've got an amazing body Sanae-san...
You're feeling good too, right?
It's rubbing against my insides!
So deep... So deep!
Penetrate me harder!
Sanae-san, I'm gonna...
I've never felt this way-!
You're squeezing me!!
Let's have fun again sometime, Sanae-san.
Amazing... You let out so much...
Sanae...
My wife is shaking in pleasure from young Miyakoshi.
Watching that, I...
I...
I am overwhelmed with an excitement that I've never felt before!
Beloved wife diaries_100090
Are we going to do it here, like this Ryouichi-san?
Doing it while you're naked in an apron is every man's dream!
If I was senpai, I would have requested it already.
Oh my, you're so big down here!
It's so hard...
I'll let it out in your mouth like always.
I'm cumming-!
You let out a lot, Ryouichi-san.
You sure are energetic!
You've improved, Sanae-san!
Hurry up, put it in Ryouichi-san!
Okay!
Whoa! So suddenly...
It's in so deep...
Yes! Fondle my breasts more!
Right there, my nipples... Squeeze my nipples!
More... More! More!!
Okay then!
N-No...
Not my g-spot! No!
What are you saying? You like it here, don't you Sanae-san?
No! I'll lose it if you rub me there!
No... No more! I can't keep standing up!
No way! My mind, my mind's going blank~!
Then... Shall I stop?
No! Don't stop!
It's good, it feels so good!
more, do it more!
S-Sanae-san-!
Amazing...
I can feel Ryouichi-san's cock quivering, and his semen coming out!
So warm...
Sanae-!
You can't, Ryouichi-san!
Keisuke-san is coming home today-
Then, we have to throughly enjoy ourselves before hand.
You're always so persuasive~
It feels good Sanae-san.
You're wearing such exciting underwear!
You've sure changed, Sanae-san.
It's your fault, Ryouichi-san.
Right there, my clitoris feels good!
I'm gonna cum!
Your cock is sliding between my breasts!
Sanae-san! That feels really good!
My breasts and mouth are being filled by you!
Sanae-san... I'm... gonna...
I-I'm cumming!
So hot...
So much came out...
Give me more of your hot fluid!
This time...
Release it in here, okay?
We're not using a condom?
Today's a safe day.
Please fill up my uterus with your semen!
My pussy is being spread-!
Your raw cock is so hot Ryouichi-san!
Sanae-san, your insides are clinging to me!
My uterus is being hammered! You're knocking against the edge!
My breasts... More... squeeze my breasts more!
So good! Hammer my uterus!
So good-!
So good!!
Make me... Make me feel even better!
Not my clitoris-!
My clitoris, my clitoris is being pinched!
Amazing-! It's slamming against my uterus!
I'm losing it-! My mind is g-going blank-!
I'm gonna lose it~!
We gotta finish it off from behind...
Yes!
Sanae-san! I'm gonna-!
Cum! let out your semen!
Can I really? Can I really release it inside you!?
Let it out-! Pore lots of your semen into my uterus!
Is it really fine with me?
I, I actually want Keisuke-san's more!
Keisuke-san! I want Keisuke-san's cum! I want Keisuke-san to cum lots inside me!
Dammit! I'm so jealous of him!
But, at the moment, I want your's!
So, so let it out! Let it out inside me, pore your hot semen inside me!
So rough-! I'm, I'm gonna cum!
I'm... I'm... I'm, I'm cumming~!!
So hot... It's filling me up... Ryouichi-san's hot semen... It's poring into my uterus! So hot!
Feels so good...
Senpai?
keisuke-san?
Sanae...
I've... I've-!
Welcome home, Keisuke-san!
Truly, welcome home.
Does it feel good?
Keisuke-san... Ryouichi-san...
Keisuke-san... I can't... hold back...
Keisuke-san! Please put it in!
Keisuke-san-!
By watching Sanae be seduced by Miyakoshi, I was able to become a man again.
Keisuke-san is getting larger inside me-! You're gonna cum again? Let it out!
Sanae!!!
So hot... It's hitting it... Keisuke-san's semen is filling up my uterus!
You let out lots...
Keisuke-san.
Now it's my turn, Sanae-san.
You're not allowed to put it in my pussy~!
Since my uterus belongs to Keisuke-san,
please get by with only using my ass, Ryouichi-san.
Sheesh! I'm so jealous!
M-My butt feels good! My pussy feels great!
Ryouichi-san and Keisuke-san are rubbing against each other inside me!
For some reason, Miyakoshi continues with this strange relationship.
Well, even though I asked him to, maybe it's his way of apologizing for cheating on my wife.
I'm gonna cum~!
I'm cumming!
Sanae!
Sanae-san!
My uterus and butt feels hot!
Keisuke-san and Ryouichi-san are both cumming inside me!
Let's think of the babies name together.