As the train runs in the city,
you're hemmed in by a bunch of strangers.
A bunch of people you don't want to be touched by.
Even cute girls are shoving you...
You must not touch those skin of those maidens.
Shinohara Yukari
Occupation: 1st-year girls school student
Blood Type: A
Hobby: Lacrosse
In this closed room within society,
This lonely city makes your son grieve.
Takahashi Akane
Occupation: 1st-year girls school student
Blood Type: B
Hobby: Gaming
You're damned if you touch,
and you're damned if you don't
Maehara Izumi
Occupation: 1st-year girls school student
Blood Type: O
Hobby: Violin
If you don't listen to me, "the finger" will attack you
molester group
Chikan Juunintai
Ten
Please co-operate with us.
Please watch your step.
The next station is...
The doors will close. Please be careful.
The doors will close. Please use the next train.
It's dangerous to rush in, so don't do it.
Guess who?
Morning!
Hello.
I'm surprised!
You...
Don't scare me like that.
It only happened because you were daydreaming.
I don't want to hear that from you, Izumi.
Yukko, have you completed your assignment on traditional Japanese language?
Yup.
Really?
Let me borrow it, let me borrow it!
Again?
Tomorrow will be the deadline.
It's all right.
It's not something you can just lose.
Let me also be carefree sometimes.
It is my favorite subject, though.
You don't have such a thing, Akane.
I have something to request of all passengers.
Please turn off your cellphones when you're near the priority seat.
Switch your phones to silent mode and refrain from making calls.
Please cooperate with us
Akane again?
No way... a molester?
Where's Akane?
No...
No... my hands...
Oh... no...
Akane... Izumi...
Where are you? Help me...
No... Stop...
Stop it...
No....
No.... no...
Nooooooo!!
The
twilight
of
the
prey
W
Are you alright, Yukko?
That really pisses me off.
You should have punched him.
Why didn't you call us?
We were so close by.
Because...
Here.
Cheer up.
Yukko also makes mistakes.
What do you mean?
You have some openings, that's why the molester groped you.
No way... you're so mean.
Your skirt is so high, you should lower it.
I won't. It's unfashionable.
You could try stepping on his foot.
I don't know which foot to step on.
How about stepping on all of them?
I can't do that! I can't even move!
Don't get mad at me.
How about bringing some pins?
No way...
Do you always bring those, Izumi?
Have you tried it?
Not yet.
I haven't encountered any molesters.
Then why do you bring them?
Megu told me that it's useful against molesters.
Oh... yes, Megu seems to encounter them quite easily.
Well, she does have big breasts you know.
Wait, Yukko.
Here are the notes on traditional Japanese language.
Thank you!
You should do it by yourself sometimes, Akane.
Oh my, Yukko, do you like to do it by yourself?
Stupid...
So you're doing it...
I don't!
How come?
Want a vibrator?
I don't need it.
You must be immune to it, Yukko.
You don't do any self-training.
That's why you can't feel it or escape when you encounter molesters, right?
I didn't feel it.
By the way,
do you know about Chikan Juunintai?
Chikan Juunintai?
What's that? Are they comedians?
No!
They're the real molesters.
Megu told me...
About what?
The ten of them will appear when you ride the train.
It's just as it's name says.
Like... Synchronized molestation?
Nope, they'll only grope one girl.
The others will surround them so that other people can't see.
No way...
It's unbelievable.
And since they can't be seen by other people,
they'll do something more intense than normal molesting.
Something more intense?
Yes, it's like rape.
It is said that they'll strip a girl of all her clothes right on the train.
No way... that's scary...
And then, when you're about to leave the train, your clothes are given back,
and you'll be given 10,000 yen for your allowance.
No way... is that true?
So, if ten people grope you, will they give you 100,000 yen?
Um, I don't know.
But it's Megu who said all this, right?
I think it's a lie.
You know Megu, always fooling around.
What will you do if it's true?
Then it's all right, you'll be given 10,000 yen anyway, right?
No way... it's gross.
Is that so? It's all right if you're in a good mood.
No way... it's impossible.
Akane, let's get off that topic already.
Yukko is in shock over this morning.
Right?
Oh yeah, how about going to the game center?
Sorry, my dad's coming home tonight.
I need to cook for him.
What a dutiful daughter.
How touching.
How about you, Yukko?
Sure, I'll go.
I'll be going then.
See you tomorrow.
Do your homework!
Roger! I'll return your notes tomorrow morning.
Really...
Let's go.
Oh... OK.
Molesting is
a crime!
Don't touch!
Next stop will be Neshiro, Neshiro, the right side door will open
Yes, yes, I'm alright.
I'm nearby, so let Miyuki help you.
OK then...
No way!
I've been surrounded.
Don't tell me...
No...
No way.. I can't move my hands.
No... stop...
Stop... stop it... please...
Uh... no... stop...
No...
No... stop it...
Izumi?
No...
Akane... what's she doing?
She's not picking it up?
It did ring, though.
I think she's on the train.
She picks up even when she's on the train.
Yukko, try calling her.
No... stop!
Please... stop calling...
What...!?
No...
It's gross.
Stop it.
I don't... want this...
No one's ever seen my...
No one's ever touched my...
It's too cruel, it's too cruel!
It's hot.
It's hot... it's hot... it's hot...!!
The person you are calling is out of range, or their cellphone is turned off.
She's not picking up.
It's turned off.
What happened to her...?
That's not like her.
She even didn't pick the phone.
Did she not charge it?
Did you call her house?
It's the same story...
I'll try going to her house later.
How about you, Yukko?
I'll stay.
I see.
Tell her I'm mad at her.
It'll be her fault when my grades decline.
What happened to Akane...?
A molester?
Why?
You...
Stop it...
So they really do exist...
I see... I can't do anything anymore.
Thank you for riding...
Next stop is Nagata no bama, Nagata no bama.
Please stay behind the yellow lines.
*Censored* Station, *censored* Station.
You must change cars for the *censored* line.
No way... Please don't look there.
Faster... faster...
The train is going...
Faster...
The train is taking off!
No!
Wow... uh... what's this?
This is a man's...
No!
Stop... no...
Please... no...
No...
Stop...
No... stop...
I'm sorry...please
Forgive me, please...
Stop... please...
Izumi? How was Akane?
Izumi?
Izumi? What's the matter?
Can you hear me?
Hello?
I can hear you.
What happened, Izumi?
Nothing...
Nothing? Are you sure?
How about Akane?
I didn't meet her.
What really happened?
Are you listening to me?
I won't know if you don't tell me.
...ster...
Eh? what?
A molester...
Wait for me, I'll be right there.
Where are you?
Oh, my...
Eh?
Don't tell me...
Chikan Juunintai...?