It's sunday after all...
Akira-chan is an idiot.
Akira..chan.
Good..good..It feels good...
Cumming..cumming...
Cumming~!!
Akira-chan...
Offside Girl
This is really awful to look at...
This isn't really a real club's room.
There is so much cold spray and trashcans all over the place.
That's because the last manager transferred
after summer holiday.
Please, captain. Please do something about this problem.
What do you think, Akira? If this problem continues,
It's not gonna be good for us.
Look's like I don't have any choice, but I guess
I have someone in mind to fill in.
I'll try to ask her!
That's how it looks, Nanami! Please do a favor for us
and be our soccer team manager!
No-way, why I should do something like that?!
Don't say that..please, Nanami...
I don't have anyone else to ask...
No way, I'm refusing it immediately, right now!
I really hate soccer and I'm sure
you know about it, right?!
Can you do something about it...
You're good at chores and laundry, even though you said you hate soccer
but you know that most girls really like it.
Right..right..It's okay, even for half a semester.
You don't have anything to do, right?
I'm sure we can focus on training if you're there.
I really want to think more about soccer.
Go out~!!!
Damn it, why is she doing something like this
to a senior like me?!
So, it's impossible after all?
But I have something up my sleeves. If I remember correctly,
our advisor is also her class teacher right?
He...
Huh?
That's why, so you can start by cleaning up this club's room.
Damn, you're playing a dirty trick on me!
It's lucky that I asked our advisor,
I'm sure you don't have any problems with that.
Please don't make me fail my final test, okay?
I know it..I know you can do it!
I don't have any excuse...
I got it, I'll just do it!!
You're in my way, step out~!!!
A moment later...
He's really using me after all...
Akira-chan's locker.
I'll open it.
I can smell Akira-chan's...
Why can't I be honest and tell Akira-chan
that I really like him...
Um..Nanami-san...
NO~!!!
A..Akira-chan..is it possible you heard that?
Sorry..I don't mean to eavesdrop.
Is that so..you heard about that...
That is..what is..It's not like I hate you...
It's not that I hate your style too...
Though you hate soccer, but what do you think of me...
The truth is I don't really hate soccer that much.
It's just..that Akira-chan thinks of soccer too much
and never looks at me.
Eh?
So, I'm jealous of that...
Cu..cute! Nanami is really cuter than before!
I've liked you too for a long time now...
Akira-chan...
Hey, Akira! Did you find our next oppenent's data files?
What took you so long to find...
Eh? He's not in here...
Even Nanami-chan?
Hmph..why do we have to hide like this?
No..it's not..I just feel something fluffy in my chest right now...
So..sorry..I can't hold it much longer.
Can I touch your breasts?
Idiot, what're you doing?!
Don't raise your voice.
But...
Amazing..you have amazingly indecent breasts.
Akira-chan is touching my breasts...
My nipples are getting hard by themselves.
No..you can't pinch my nipples.
If you're doing that..It's gonna come out...
Didn't I tell you to keep your voice down?
It's not..it's not like that..the milk...
the milk is gonna come out!
What is this?
Is it possible that you're pregnant?
It's not like that..I used to do that by myself...
Why's that Nanami? You're really erotic.
No...
If you're doing more than that...
Come..come out..It's coming out from my nipples!!
Where's he going?
Heh..that Kawakami finally took his leave from here.
Akira-chan...
Hey..why don't we do more of it?
This time, let me do that for you.
Nanami, this guy...
Akira-chan's penis..I'll do it with my mouth.
Akira-chan..your penis..is getting big...
Idiot!
My penis...
Is hitting the back of Nanami's throat...
I've been thinking a lot about Akira-chan's penis...
Even when I'm masturbating by myself...
Nanami-
You've released it...
Sperm..Akira-chan's sperm...
Akira-chan's sperm is really warm and has a good smell to it.
Nanami.
I can put it..inside of yours, right?
Yes, please put your penis iniside my perverted virgin pussy.
Inside Nanami is really hot and drenched,
my penis is easily getting inside of it.
Me too...
Akira-chan's penis..it really feels good...
Did you feel it?
My penis...
is hitting the back of Nanami's pussy...
No! Down there...
No! You can't spread it!
My asshole...
If you're spreading it like that...
Good..good!
My ass feels good too!!
Cumming..cumming...
Akira-chan~!!!
There..you go.
Huh..?
It's getting clean isn't it?
You're the new manager, right?
Um..who are you?
Azuma Shizuru, the soccer team coach.
To be continued in the 2nd half