PANTHEON, a Synthetic Sports Facilities.
Many of Japan's sport representaive,
hope to get their bodies trained in this facility.
Ball games, skating, judo, and others,
have been prepared in this cutting edge facility.
I just started a part-time job at the ORCUS office lately...
You have a wonderful hands, don't you?
It's a good hand.
[Saibara Fumiko - Sports Massager]
Eh, Saibara-san...
Among the 100 people out there, your hand is the golden hand.
What does that mean?
Your hand, let me check it for a moment.
Right~, as I thought!
You have a talent for bringing out a girl's hidden talents.
Bringing out?
You know don't you?
Girls have a stimulation spot in that place, that is...
I know it, but that's not related to sports though...
He~, you don't understand do you?
You know that all the representatives here are aiming to be in the top three, right?
They don't have any time to think about love and sex right now.
But, we all here realize that it's important to them.
If they're not releasing it properly,
it could make their bodies damage itself.
Is that really true...
Their valuable talents can't be wasted because of that.
That's why they need a special massage.
Is that... spouting?
That's right, you have a talent to do it.
For the sake of Japan and for the girls, you must cooperate with us.
SubDESU-H
-Binkan Athlete-
[One month later]
Ooyama Megumi,
I'll be taking care of you with a special massage.
[Volleyball - Ooyama Megumi]
Yes, pleased to meet you too.
Err..., as I've been told, I came here without wearing underwear.
Right, then if you would please lie down over there?
Yes.
All right, let's begin.
Yes... please.
It's fine, you just have to relax like that.
Wha... what is this...
It's only a massage, but why's it feeling like this?
Wa... wait!
Over there...
This is treatment, for girls this spot is a vital part of it.
That is... mm...
How is it? Does this make you feel good?
That is... what does "feeling good" mean?
Wait, stop it!
I'm trying to release Megumi-san's stress.
Please, leave it to me.
Is this really treatment?
Of course.
I can't...
No~!
See, it's getting wet there already.
That is... embarrassing... NO!
That hurts, wait!
No~!
This is the first time...
This is treatment, please bear with it.
It feels like the inside of my body has been massaged.
Then this time, let's start doing a breast massage.
Bre... breast?
Over there, it's wonderful.
What's important is Megumi-san feeling good.
That's why, please feel better with it.
Even if you say it like that, what should I do?
It's better if you have pleasant feelings with this.
Don't hesitate to tell me what you want me to do.
I... I understand.
Please play with my nipples more.
My... my breast...
Are you okay with this?
I feel like an awfully indecent girl.
If you think more about it,
there's nothing wrong with being indecent.
Is... that really true?
Right now, you just look like an indecent one.
Right now..I'm being the indecent one, right.
Go... good!
What do you want to do next?
That is... I want you to touch over there.
It's embarrassing~
Then let me loosen this up.
Eh, that is...
No, if you keep doing it like that...
Over there~
How is it in here?
Over there, my clitoris, it hurts...
Ple... please, be more gentle with it.
Could it be that you rarely masturbate?
I rarely masturbate.
Inside of me feels good... coming out.
Something came out from inside of my body...
It's coming out!
That's the time for you to say "coming out".
Coming out, is it?
Something is coming out~
A lot of it is coming out, sorry about that.
Err, you okay over there?
N... no, this is...
It's just fine, if you're feeling good, I'm doing just fine with it.
Th... this time, why don't you let me do it?
That is...
Because of me, your thing is like that.
I don't want you to hold it in.
I haven't done anything like this before,
does it hurt?
Yes, it feel's good.
Please don't think that I'd be doing this for everyone, okay.
Your thing is very hot.
Me... Megumi-san, you dont have to do that...
It's fine, if it's with you,
I'm feeling good too, that's what makes me happy.
A, Megumi-san.
Being eaten like this, it feels good doesn't it?
Me... Megumi-san... I can't hold...
It's coming out, right.
Please let it come out in whatever place you like.
Ah, the sperm.
This is... your sperm.
It's warm.
So... sorry, it came out all over your face.
It's fine, earlier you made me cum a lot too.
-Binkan Athlete-
Can I slide too?
It's fine, today we're the only ones left in here.
[Figure Skater - Yaginuma Nao]
But, I don't have ice skates though...
Even with the usual shoes you could slide without any problems.
[Figure Skater - Yaginuma Shizuku]
We'll be supporting you.
Wait... wait a minute!
Right... right, just like that!
Unexpectedly, I could slide with it.
Right, just do it like I told you before.
Then, next one just a little...
You're left behind~
Even you if you say that.
If you're too worried, it could be more dangerous.
It's fast... it's too fast!
Sorry about that~
But, don't you think it feels interesting?
It hurts... that's too much from the both of you.
This requires a little punishment for you two.
Are we really gonna do a special massage over here?
Being seen like this, it's embarrassing.
If you're staring this much...
Did you like looking at my thing?
Finger... your finger is going in my thing,
touching it... like it's gonna penetrate.
Being touched like this, it feels strange.
It's indecent... Nao's thing, it's indecent.
I feel like I'm turning into a naugthy girl!
All the time on the ice rink,
during tournaments too, I'll feel indecent like this.
Shizuku-san, being erotic is a beautiful thing.
Erotic? I'm erotic?
Right, over there has been opened like that.
Being wet like this...
I like erotic girls, you know.
True... is that true?
Then I'll become more erotic,
more erotic than anyone.
I'm rapidly becoming dirty minded.
Wonderful... it's extremely wonderful!
Why... why did it become like this?
Is it possible you want to do it yourself?
Don't want to... it look's like I became a naughty girl...!
Right, you're the same... doing it like this with us,
it's something you imagined, right?
Rapidly it became..became more filled with it.
Good... it's good... I'm feeling your touch.
Over there and my butt is drenched already.
Your finger... the way you're touching it,
I feel like I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming!!
No... no, it's coming out.
I'm feeling hot over there, still your finger is stimulating my thing.
I just can't hold it... I can't...!!
If it's like that... me too... I can't...
Coming out... it's gonna flow out from inside of me.
I'm cumming...
Me too... I'm cumming... I'm cumming~!
Put it... put it in,
Over there... inside of my thing.
Please put your thing inside me.
Please make my thing more drenched with it,
as my thing is already oozing something.
I'll... I'll put it in, okay?
It's in...
It's inside of it!
Inside of me!!
That big thing... right now,
it's inside of Onee-chan's thing... already.
Please don't look at it like that, Nao.
The way you're licking it is wonderful.
I'm feeling it already.
Moving it, I'm moving it by myself.
Even Nao's looking at me~
You're licking a girl's important thing.
The place where I'm feeling it is drenched...
It's getting bigger,
Your thing is getting bigger as I'm moving it.
Onee-chan's movement on it is getting faster.
Not... not on my breasts, over there is...
Your nipple is getting this hard.
I know it, cause my nipple too is feeling it.
It's indecent~
Nao too... being licked like that, I'm feeling good too.
My thing... it's sopping wet~, did you feel it?
It's because... because being licked like this makes me feel good.
More... I want you to lick me more~
It's... it's hitting inside of me.
More..I want more...
I'm... I'm moving it myself~
No, I can't hold it anymore~
Cumming... I'm cumming.
No~
Onee-chan, you're so indecent,
even if it's Onee-chan...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!
Let it out..let it come out.
Your hot... your hot sperm, let it come inside of me.
Wait... wait Onee-sama, I'm gonna cum too.
I'm cumming... cumming while Nao is looking at me.
Getting this drenched all over my body...
The smell of sperm...,
with Onee-chan, I got covered with sperm.
-Binkan Athlete-
Fight, Asaka!
Fight!!
Score it, Asaka!
[Beach Volleyball - Miwa Asaka]
Chance!
That day, Asaka-san became one of Japan's representatives.
After interviews and victory celebrations one after another,
at last we had a moment to meet, but it's already midnight.
You look good in your swimsuit.
Is... that true?
I feel a little uncomfortable in it though...
But if you say it like that, it makes me happy.
Anyway, at the last day of evaluation,
it's great that you got good results on it.
Right, but now I can't go to Pantheon everyday.
That is...
Ee~, can you do it once again?
Ah, right, if it's a massage we could do it,
when we get back to the hotel.
Not there, I want to do it right here.
Today I don't just want a massage, I want to have sex with you.
No... you're touching over there...
Only through my swimsuit?
It's not what I want.
Asaka-san, why do you want to do it?
Do I have to tell you about it? No, it's embarrassing.
Do you really want to hear about it?
Yes, I want to hear it.
No... I don't want to, but if you insist on it...
Over there, in my pussy... I want your finger in it,
inside of it...
I want you to stir up inside of it!
I... I said it...
It's inside of me! Please..give me more of it.
Cause today is a special favor from me...
There... over there... the way you're touching inside of it,
it feel's good...
Wait... I'm about to cum...
Cumming... I'm cumming.
It's out... it's coming out!!
It... it came... it came out... it came out...
Your body is completely indecent now, isn't it?
Cause... because you're always doing it...
Even like that, I'm surprised that you'd go this far.
No... not like this...
Do you not want me to be more like this,
or do you want me to be more like an "indecent one"?
If I've gotta choose, I prefer indecent girls.
I'm... glad to hear it.
Asaka-san?
This time... let me make you feel good, okay?
Your thing is going in and out between my breasts.
It feels good.
It's okay to move it.
If you're feeling... even my breasts are feeling it too,
my breast and your thing rubbing against each other.
Can I move little faster against it?
Do as you like, feel free to use my breasts as you'd like.
Your thing is getting bigger, you know.
My breasts... my breasts are getting squished.
My breast and my thing are getting hot over your thing.
Your... your hot and hard thing, it's gonna cum.
It's tickling enough and coming out, right.
Asaka-san, I'm...
Yes, right... it's fine.
Let it... let it out, let your sperm come a lot.
All... let it all out...
Let my breasts get drenched in it, let it out!
It came a lot...
your sperm it is...
It feels like I'm completely one with your thing.
You're gonna take it off?
Do you feel shy about it?
Be... because it looks strange, right?
A trace of sunburn remains on it.
That's not a problem.
It's hot... your hot thing is bumping it.
It's in, inside of mine is full with it.
It clearly stands out, your thing and even your butt hole.
No, I don't want it.
Look over there... I don't want you to look at my butt.
It's embarrassing.
The way my thing easily went in your pussy, it's like it was made for me
Be... because..it's hard and overflowing like this....
Everything is  being seen~
Asaka-san, I'm starting.
Come... come in...
Want this... I really want this.
It's hard... hitting in and out like this... getting big...
Your pussy is overflowing and your thing is unbreakable,
even your nipple is getting like this, it's so indecent.
Be... cause you keep stirring it up,
my nipple gets hard and over there is sopping wet.
It feels good, right?
It's fine... it's okay even it's overflowing everywhere.
More... more of it, I want you to pound my deepest thing...
Want it~
You want to get more rough than this?
Yes, I want you to smash it.
I... I really love it, love it!
It's good... it's good... it's good... it's good~
Asaka-san, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I really want to thank you.
Eh?
Thanks to you, I can get over my slump,
I can be Japan's representative too.
Not like that, I just...
No, because of your support,
I can't think of being embarrased.
Today, that's how I feel in my match.
Asaka-san...
That's why today's victory, it's all thanks to you.
For that, I want you to accept it with pleasure.
Your thing is standing up again,
do you want to do it once more?
-Binkan Athlete-