www.SubDESU-H.net
Back
Futa
Niimura Akane
Dick Specs: None
Even though she's in that position,
she seems to be quite satisfied with it.
Technically the sex toy of the Futa-Club
and joined the club as their "service" member.
Seeking new excitement in her life,
she was invited by Sumika,
The only one who isn't a Futanari among the characters.
She's kind of like the MC of the series.
She becomes anemic when it gets stiff,
but prepared herself to be president despite this fact.
Before Akane joined, she had problems getting
fully satisfied sexually due to its enormous size.
The girl holding the top class gargantuan dick.
Futa-Club President.
She enrolled as an advanced-grade student.
Specialty:  Extraordinary size, extraordinary cum rate.
Stroke it once and it can squirt lots.
Cum rate: Immeasurable
Thickness: 12cm
Length: 41cm
Dick Specs:
Asakura Mao
The one who recruited Akane to the supposedly non-existent secret club.
Using her personally collected data, she constantly searches for potential club members.
She hides the fact that she's a futanari,
though she dreams of eventually being able to build a place in school where
futanaris can stay peacefully.
Manages potential members.
Founder of the Futa-Club and the current vice-president.
Specialty: Flexible and long. She uses various techniques
utilizing its elasticity and length.
Cum rate: 200cc
Thickness: 6cm
Length: 40cm
Dick Specs:
Oohashi Sumika
Has adequate body proportions with a big breasts to match.
She normally does everything with Ai.
She seems to like Ai,
though she always express these feelings of affection by teasing her.
A tough girl with a loud personality.
Regular member of the Futa-Club.
Specialty: Thick and stiff. She also has a big and rough dick head. She likes ramming it in to widen somebody's "holes".
Cum rate: 250cc
Thickness: 10cm
Length: 20cm
Dick Specs:
Itou Aya
Leave her be and she'll cum for an entire day,
thus she's the club's "milk" manager.
Before Akane joined, she held the underling
position in the club.
A bit of a spoiled brat though, this is reflected quite
a bit in her child-like stature and childish mentality.
Likes to go at it with Aya a lot but she is often
simply treated by her as a toy...
Specialty: Quite small compared to other futanaris,
but boasts the most impressive amount of cum.
Her largest cum record is constantly changing.
Cum rate: cc
Thickness: 5cm
Length: 10cm
Dick Specs:
Aihara Ai
Futa-Club!
SubDESU-H
Part one
Akane, did you bring your clothes?
Yes, they're in here.
Once you enter, there's no turning back.
Okay, I understand, Sumika-senpai.
Oops, my bad.
Just shake your butt a bit more.
Aya-chan, your thick thing is rubbing hard inside me.
Ai, you're getting pretty tight here already.
No... No need to start using mine too.
Or else I won't be able to stop!
Everyone.
This is our long-awaited new club member.
Hello there.
This is 2nd year Itou Aya and 1st year Aihara Ai.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
And this is our new member, Niimura Akane.
Pl-Pleased to meet you.
Jeez, I already told everyone that a new member was coming today.
Sorry, I completely forgot about it.
I'd not forgotten about it though.
What did you say?
Umm, excuse me.
Oh, I forgot.
This is the Futa-Club's president.
2nd year Asakura Mao.
President, you lack presence here.
I was just reading something.
I know what you want to say.
She may not look like it, but she's actually skipped a few grade levels.
Now then, this club started activities several years ago in the old school building.
It has been a place exclusively for futanari girls,
but she will be...
The very first normal girl in this club.
Ooh, her pussy looks beautiful!
Also, she will be admitted to the club as its service specialist.
Alright!
Now there's someone even lower than me!
I don't think that's going to be the case though.
Anyway...
Now that you'll be joining...
You need to have the right partner.
So everyone really has a dong.
Let's try a little blow job shall we?
It's a real dick and it's twitching.
It also feels warm.
Dicks sure feels softer than I thought.
Akane-san, you can undress if you want to.
I will.
I'm going to take my clothes off.
Good, keep it up Akane-san.
But, my dick is quite long.
I won't feel quite good if you don't suck it in deeper.
Your throat feels nice.
Akane-san, I think you're good.
Your hands feel great.
Please rub it more.
It's your first time, so why...?
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum soon!
Oh no, it's coming out.
Me too, let me cum too!
All of this cum...
This semen is...
We're already doing these kinds of things?
Everyone's so mean.
These are my first dicks, you know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just got carried away in my pleasure.
But, if you can't take it now,
you probably won't be able to last long here.
Ms. Service manager.
Well, it did feel good.
Huh? What about our president?
Oh, President!
President, let's do it too.
No, umm...
Now, now.
Wha-What's the meaning of this?
Keep her that way.
President, this is...
Are you curious?
Actually...
It's small and petite.
It looks cute!
That's a bit too sudden.
I'm going to rub it for you.
N-No, don't.
Well, can't do anything about it.
My dick's sheath is...
Your dick looks very pretty.
President?
What are you going to do about this, Akane-san?
This is...
If this becomes completely aroused...
Wha-What should I do?
What will happen?
Oh no, at this rate, I'll lose...
President!
Hey!
What are you going to do about my dick?!
You do realize that your clothes have been changed, right?
Our clothes were soiled already so we sent them to the laundry and took a dip.
Since we're here, we all decided to wear swimsuits.
So this club even has this kind of facility.
The Futa-Club sure gets lots of funding.
Besides, the president just got even tougher after fainting with her aroused cock.
You're amazing!
Even Akane's wearing a swimsuit!
Everyone planned this all along!
You're already wearing a swimsuit as well,
so don't complain.
I will!
Let me do it already!
Okay then, Akane-san, what will you do now?
I'll try to calm the President down.
Wow.
It's still getting bigger.
Hey, you were taught to suck it until it reaches your throat, right?
Use your tongue as well.
I can't take all of that in!
I'll die!
You're the one who made it this stiff.
You're not quite done taking responsibility for this yet.
No way...
Oh, I know!
Then...
How about this?
So it has come to this.
Your dick is starting to get really hot.
You're quite good.
But since we're here already,
let's try doing the real thing.
The real thing?
It's your first time, right?
It's okay.
I've already penetrated it with my toys.
Then, without further ado...
Am I going to be okay with that size?
We'll just have to find out.
It's really thick.
President, it feels really tight!
We're not done yet.
It's okay, don't worry.
I can feel it getting deeper inside me.
The taste of a pussy after a long time...
It feels really good!
Is that so?
Does my pussy feel good?
It can even take my monstrous dick in,
so your pussy is just as monstrous.
You're at the very tip.
It's a dead end already.
I can push it in just a little more.
It's hitting me...
It's hitting me inside.
The tip is...
Amazing, right?
This might be the first time that I'll cum inside a pussy.
Your hot thing is filling me up.
I'm going for one final push!
Don't push me up with your dick.
It's rubbing and stirring me.
I think I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
It's at the deepest part.
It's cumming inside my deepest part.
We're not done yet.
Pull it out.
Pull it out first!
My insides are going to break.
It's okay.
It's going to be alright with your monstrous pussy.
Sumika-san?
It’s not good to bully our new member.
Do you want to break Akane-san on her first day?
But, Akane-san had just...
Besides, you just left us all here,
to enjoy all of this by yourself.
President,
you've just unloaded your thick thing again.
I don't want this to end!
I want to cum some more!
I understand.
But you have to let me enjoy this first.
President your pussy feels great too, you know?
Hey, you have your own thing to do in this situation, right?
Huh?
Spray it all over.
We-We're going to cum all over you?
Roger!
You don't need to be so excited about it!
Why not?
I can do whatever it is that you'd like me to.
Spin, spin, spin!
Don't!
It feels great...
My pussy is getting stirred...
Even my dick is feeling it.
It's coming...
I'm cumming.
I'm about to burst with pleasure.
You and I are about to cum.
Let's... Let's cum together!
Akane-san, I'm really sorry.
I got too full of myself.
No, I want to say sorry as well.
It was my first time to feel that kind of pleasure.
Please do it again sometime.
In any case, you're now welcome as the club's new member.
Welcome to the Futa-Club.
I hope you can get along here.
Nessie!
Nessie, Nessie!
www.SubDESU-H.net