www.SubDESU-H.net
Ozawa Stationery Shop
No!
My hands won't stop.
Kazuki, what should I do?
At this rate I'll...
W
Last Volume   Nightmare's Encore
DVD Reads: To Kazuki
The DVD's from the unknown sender,
kept on arriving here each week.
As it got past the 10th DVD,
Otome-nee was
no longer the Otome-nee that I once knew.
Your horselike cock seems quite lovely today as well, Uncle.
Delicious.
Your cock's tastes really great.
Otome-chan, you really are a genius when it comes to satisfying men.
Really?
I'm glad.
I'm about to cum.
Otome-chan! Here, say "ah".
Please give it to me.
Please give me more of your cum... in my mouth!
Oh my, what's this?
Isn't this a bit too extreme?
Otome-chan, let me remind you,
this is part of your "training".
No way.
Could it be that I will be taken from both sides in this position?
I'll probably lose it if you take me that way.
You already lost it a long while back,
you sex maniac, Otome-chan!
Because it feels really good!
Being thoroughly used while having my breasts caressed...
It feels so good and that's all I can think about now!
Here, I'm coming from the front, Otome.
This is good, Otome!
Your insides are the best!
No...
This hot sensation is starting to swell up.
It's coming.
Both cocks are trying to compete for my insides!
I can't let go Otome, with your asshole gripping my cock so tightly.
It feels good to be fucked intensely like this, that's why!
But really, compared to anal it's the pussy fucking that's better, right?
I don't know!
I just don't know!
Idiot, just say that you like it in your pussy better.
Sloppy and wet.
This is...
No, I'm cumming!
Wait, we're also about to release it too.
Please cum quickly!
Or I'll lose this built up sensation!
It feels great!
That's good.
Otome-chan, you really are an angel.
Let's do it, Uncle.
My cock's been aching to enter your pussy since yesterday.
Uncle, your cock is the best!
These breasts were made to make a man go wild.
Ouch!
No, Uncle.
Please don't tease me like that.
Sorry about that, but you’re just too cute.
Hey, put your tongue out.
I can't stop myself anymore.
I love it.
I love sex!
It feels too good!
My hips are moving on their own!
No, not like this. Your cock's hitting deep inside!
It's constantly penetrating my womb!
Oh no, this is amazing.
No, no!
I can plainly see your cock entering my pussy from this angle.
So, whose personal property are you Otome-chan?
I'm yours!
My erotic loose breasts,
my pussy that can never let go of your cock,
everything!
All of these are yours Uncle!
Okay, then I'll make sure to mark you with my semen to keep you from others!
Please!
Release it inside me!
Take this, Otome!
I've been marked with semen.
By the way, you don’t care about Kazuki-kun, anymore?
Kazuki...?
Kazu...
Ah, I don't care about him anymore.
Because I really like you all now.
Hey Kazuki, what was that noise?
Why Otome-nee?
Why did you become like that?
Wasn't I the one watching, taking care of you long before them?
Then how did this happen? Why?
This is all messed up!
Oh, so have you brought "that thing"?
Here, next week's DVD.
Thanks!
But what are you going to use it for?
If there's a slight chance that this gets out...
It's okay I tell you.
I just plan to use it a bit for personal reasons.
Is that so?
Then that's good.
Then, Rinka-chan how about after this...
Hmm? What?
At the place where you did it for the first time?
You geezer...
Otome-nee...
So you see, it's gonna be another masterpiece.
I see.
Maybe if I go to our high school campus... then...
Quite nostalgic...
You really still remember that?
Then let's use the toilet over there.
What's this?
Why is Rinka...?
What the hell is this?
I said you can't.
I'll become sensitive.
I'm getting you sensitive Rinka-chan.
Just telling you Uncle,
I'm gonna kill you if you say that I look like some small fairy again.
But why?
I'm just saying that you're cute.
Listen here, that's really gross.
Come on, I'm gonna perform fellatio so level your hip a bit.
You really look more docile whenever you engage in sex.
But then again that's also one of your charm points.
Are you an idiot?
Fellatio and talking can't be done at the same time you know.
There there, gonna throw a fork ball, just kidding.
Wow!
Rinka-chan, I want more...
I know, I know.
I'm going to do it even if you don't plead.
Here, you can come.
Do it like a beast.
Rinka-chan!
But you're also quite cruel yourself.
Handing over Otome-chan to a group of perverts like us.
When I saw that picture of Otome-neesan enjoying the gonzo with you all.
I got angry, and just thought I had to do something with it.
I'm sorry Rinka-chan.
I don’t have to tell you this, but if you release it inside...
I know that, you're so scary.
Well, it's quite regretful but.
It's hot...
No, this feels like I'm the one entering!
I'm already cumming!
Rinka-chan, stroke my cock.
It's hot!
No way, I feel it!
It's going to ejaculate!
That was really good.
Rinka-chan? Can you hear me?
Rinka, did that...
With the DVD...
And those guys...
I don’t know what's going on anymore.
The curtains are finally raised,
and pure darkness started to spread out.
This is my, room?
Now brother's virginity is mine.
I'm bound and I can't move!
You woke up?
My big brother who gets his cock excited inside his sister's pussy.
Rinka, what's going on?
Eh? You don't understand yet?
It's all your fault brother.
What are you saying?
Remember when we were kids,
when you were asked who would you take as bride,
you chose Otome-nee.
Because you're my sister!
That doesn't matter.
I was really in love with you.
It was just after that, I think,
that I was raped by a pedophile middle aged guy.
After that, I was treated as their pet,
and at any time, and any place,
they would continuously have sex with me.
No way...
But, it's not fair right?
Otome-nee and you acting like lovers,
while I get raped every single day.
That's why I switched places.
Now Otome-nee's the pet,
while I have you.
Look at this.
It seems that Otome-nee got pregnant.
I'm glad that I'm the one who gets to bear your child.
I'm glad!
I'm really glad!
See, I finally got you brother.
But you haven't got anything.
Do you understand?
At that time,
you really thought that even without doing anything everything would go well, right?
But this world isn't created for everyone's sake.
I see now...
I'm...
You don't have to hold back, ok?
Please, brother.
Brother!
Brother?
This is intense brother!
Brother!
And until dawn, my brother's semen kept on flowing in and out of me.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
My poor brother who's lost every single thing...
But I'm the one who got him.
You're my possession now, brother.
Papa, I got surprised!
What's wrong dear, are you alright?
Huh, Otome-nee?
What's with that old way of calling me?
You're all sweaty,
did you have a nightmare?
I see, so we got married.
Otome!
I want to hug too!
There is something on your face, Megumi.
I was eating hotcake!
You're not going out today, right dear?
Yeah, I'm going to sleep.
What would you like for a souvenir Papa?
I'll leave it to you Megu-chan.
Okay!
Let's go.
Maybe I'll sleep in some more.
That's...
A DVD?
A video file?
Did we have this?
Huh? Isn’t this our bedroom?
What is this?
No way, wasn't it just a dream?
Otome-chan, your child is growing quite well.
This not real, this isn't true!
Thank you very much doctor.
This is a lie, tell me it is, Otome!
Doctor, why don't you examine this a little further?
Oh my, you've really become quite perverted.
You still want to taste a cock even though you’re pregnant.
Stop, stop that!
This is something that I really need to examine.
Look Otome-chan, it's hitting the bottom part of your baby's cell.
Don't do it roughly.
You really want more?
Otome and my child, my child!
Then I'll give it all to you!
This is good, give me more!
Pull that out, pull that dirty cock out of my Otome!
Oh yeah, I did a check, and finally confirmed that Megumi-chan is my daughter.
Huh?
I'm glad, then I'll introduce Megumi to her real father next time.
That so enviable, I bet that this next child is mine.
What are you saying?
This child is my child.
While your husband's away, you’re here sucking other men's cocks.
Stop this!
Otome, the one you’re supposed to do it with is me!
Using both her hands like that and with her hips moving passionately!
I'm sorry dear!
Hey, either apologize first or suck the cock first.
This is quite big.
Then we'll be drinking all of this.
Okay, as thanks for letting me drink it,
I'll have your child drink mine first.
Faster!
I'm going to cum!
Otome!
Let my child drink it!
Please let my child drink from the real father!
Otome!
I'll be glad to make Otome-chan pregnant anytime.
We'll have to get his husband to work more.
We're home!
We're back!
Yay, Papa!
Oh? Is something wrong dear?
It’s nothing.
Welcome home.
Please let me quickly wake up from this dream.
This is too cruel.
www.SubDESU-H.net