I'm home!
Welcome home, darling.
W-What?
Um, that outfit...
Naked apron.
Well, today is your birthday, right, Shuichi-san? What do you think?
Thank you, Nanami! It's the best present!
Sore Demo Tsuma o Aishiteru
Even So, I Love My Wife
chapter two: sins the wife can't tell her husband
Darling!
Sorry, I can't hold off! I'm putting it in!
Your... your thing is in me!
Nanami... you're getting tight... around me...!
S-stop... doing it... doing it here...
Being held by you here... it's embarrassing after all...
I'm the way all in... do you understand?
I understand. Your penis is all the way inside of me.
Darling... you're more violent... than usual...
No... not... so violent!
Darling... darling!
Thank you, Nanami. This present is the best!
I'm so glad.
I know that having your penis in me makes you really happy.
I can tell how aroused you are...
My head feels funny!
Darling, darling... more, do me more...
Do me in every nook and cranny...
Darling... darling... It feels good!
No! No!
Darling, you're... somehow more amazing... than usual...
Because you'd like it, I'll dress like this more often...
Honestly, seeing my bare bottom in the naked apron is, like, really embarrassing,
but knowing that my body would make you happy, made me happy.
I'm going crazy having you in me like this,
I might be completely lewd.
I love you, darling, I love you!
You're going all the way into me, darling!
You're making me more indecent than usual!
Do me as you'd like it! Inside me, my tits, my ass, make them all yours!
No, no!
Somehow this is cuter than usual.
I think I'll take a picture and send it over there.
Don't, don't! This is an embarrassing position -- if anyone but you sees me like this, I'll die!
This is totally embarrassing!
Being embarrassed turns you on, Nanami?
No! Don't say that!
That's like saying I enjoy being like this!
Darling! Darling!
Like this is so embarrassing... so embarrassing...
But I can't stop, can't stop!
Don't!
So good, so good!
It's coming, I'm going to cum!
Darling, I love you! I love you!
Me, too, Nanami, I love you most in the world!
I'm so happy, darling, you make me blissful!
Darling, is it good? Does it feel good?
You're making me feel so good, it makes me so happy.
Please make me feel even better!
No, this is wrong, this isn't it, this isn't it...
My body is acting on its own...
No, no, this is so shameful!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
You have such an embarrassing and vulgar wife.
I can't stop it!
It feels so good I can't stop it!
Darling, darling!
Your thing is getting so big inside of me!
Please, let it out inside of me!
Please let me have all of it!
Fill me up so that we can have a baby!
Deep inside of me, plenty of it...
Nooo!
You came so much into the baby's room.
Thanks, Nanami.
I'll do anything to make you happy.
Nanami, what do you want for your birthday?
I'm fine. I already have what I want.
I want your baby.
Thank you, darling, for the baby.
Nanami!
Did you possibly want to do it again?
No... Darling, darling!
That feels good!
Darling!
That's good, isn't it!
Nanami, this is a review of every night in your married life!
It's the best, isn't it?
Darling!
Without even stopping, going straight into the body, huh?
Trying maybe a bit too hard to have children?
Darling!
Your husband is frantically thrusting his hips.
How many months has it been since I became Kamata's slave?
My relationship with Kamata is still continuing.
I can't help but worry about what Kamata makes me do.
Also, I don't know when I'll get pregnant, and if it'll look like Shuichi-san, so every month I go back.
Darling! Darling!
I've become dirty, but I absolutely don't want Shuichi-san to find out.
Kamata has dirtied everything I hold dear, one after another.
Misaki, who has just arrived,
and my little sister Chihiro.
Do you like to do naughty things, little lady?
What? That is...
You want to eat this... don't you?
You're peeing, aren't you?
N-No, I'm not!
My little sister Chihiro was in the manager's room, she was caught by Kamata looking at his books.
And the newly arrived Misaki was invited to a home party by some male friends,
and the place she was brought to was my house.
May I ask a favor?
W-what? No!
And then... Chihiro and Misaki both,
just like me, entered an existence that was purely for the sake of Kamata's sexual desires.
When Shuichi-san is away overnight for work, Kamata brings men to my house.
We make dirty movies.
Really, you're being too timid.
Don't struggle so much between my boobs like this.
Such a good smell...
Oh, no, were you getting that?
Getting all swollen like this...
Cum on me, let a lot of cum out on me...
Come on, quickly!
Semen, so hot!
Stinky, delicious!
Onee-chan, it feels so good!
Chihiro, I feel good, too!
Chihiro, your pussy is all sticky!
No, that's embarrassing!
Embarrassing, it's embarrassing!
Chihiro, have you gotten aroused?
No, don't say that, onee-chan.
But, but, but, Chihiro is really aroused down there!
Hurry... Put it in quickly!
Come on, beg like usual, Chihiro!
Onee-chan, put the usual into Chihiro's pussy!
Onee-chan, me too!
I'm putting it in.
Do it.
It's embarrassing.
Chihiro, you're so nasty.
It went in! Amazing!
Move it!
Onee-chan, your penis is making me crazier than usual! Do it!
So good!
Onee-chan, it feels good!
That's a great scene.
Sisters becoming nasty perverted women together.
My hips are moving on their own!
It's feeling good!
I'm getting used to people...
It's embarrassing!
No, don't!
I'll cum, I'll cum!
Onee-chan, onee onee-chan!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Me, too, me too!
The perverted sisters' friend totally loves this, too!
More!
Cum in my dripping pussy!
My pussy is so surprised by your throbbing hot dick today!
It's too strong!
Your cock is banging in my pussy!
You're squeezing my tits too hard!
They'll be torn off, my boobs will come off!
This dick, I love it when it rubs against me...
When it pulls against my pussy...
Hey, wanna be my fuck buddy?
I don't want to let this tight pussy go!
It's not fair when you talk while rubbing my pussy with your cock like that!
Don't!
Your cock is super huge!
Like hell I'd go out with you!
If you want wild sex like this anytime, you should become my fuck buddy.
Don't stir me up like that... no, no,
don't order me to become your fuck buddy with a penis like that!
Amazing!
Your cock is so hard in my pussy!
It feels too good!
Let me cum!
Whatever is fine, let my pussy cum!
You want to cum? I'll make your pussy, which is for my personal use, cum with all its strength!
Let me cum! You're coming in from behind, so let me cum!
Call me nasty things or whatever, but let me cum!
It's fine whatever you want to do, so hurry up and let me cum! Ejaculate!
I'm going to be filled with the cum of a man I've just met...
Fill my pussy with tons of cum!
Nanami-chan, if you do too many big dicks, your pussy will get floppy, and wouldn't that be a pity for your husband?
Let me take care of you with anal.
I'm so happy.
One hole, the ass is the best!
Chihiro loves anal, too!
Chihiro's ass, inside my ass, a penis came in!
Is it really such a big thing packed into you, Chihiro-chan?
Penis, a penis!
It's like you want to devour my penis!
It's like something big is going to come out.
It hurts. It's embarrassing!
Whoohoo! Great, isn't it!
No, don't, it's impossible!
No, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My ass, my ass is cumming!
Nooo!!!
It's crazy tight!
I'm cumming, cumming!
I love Shuichi-san. That is true.
But I have gone to point of no return.
I mean, being held by Shuichi-san is,
in comparison to Kamata and the men he invites,
has become not as pleasant a memory.
Darling, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Today I'm going to fill up your pussy with cum!
Delivery!
Nanami?
Hino-kun...
This is your home, Nanami?
Nanami, what's happened?
Hino-kun, please... help me...
I'm leaving a towel and a change of clothes here.
I'm sorry, Hino-kun.
Nanami, what happened?
Hino-kun, I'm no good, either.
I'm the worst, aren't I?
What should I say?
Hino-kun, you used to scorn me, right?
This polluted me has become unworthy of being in love with Shuichi-san.
Nanami, you are not polluted!
Nothing about you is dirty, Nanami!
Hino-kun!
I love you. I've always loved you, Nanami.
Ever since I first met you at college.
Hino-kun...
I've always regretted that I never told you I loved you.
I've always wanted to do this to you, Nanami.
Hino-kun!
N-Nanami!
It's fine, like this is fine, please!
Um, well, actually, I have no experience...
So I don't know if I can do it well...
It's fine, so... please...
Put it in.
I'm going in.
Huh? This is strange. sorry...
It's here.
Hold it at the top and take your time entering.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Move!
I'd never have thought my first time would be so good, Nanami.
Really, no one until now?
Yeah. There was just you, Nanami.
I'm so happy!
Hino-kun, amazing! More, more, I'm feeling more!
Hino-kun, do me from behind!
Nanami!
More, do me more! Please!
I'm sorry, my hips won't stop!
It's fine, rougher is fine!
But!
It's fine! Move as you'd like to, Hino-kun.
So you won't forget anything!
Nanami!
Nanami, Nanami!
It's hitting, down there is amazing!
Hino-kun...
Good!
Hino-kun! It's intense!
Hino-kun, I...
I... no...
I'm cumming!
Hino-kun, Hino-kun, ejaculate! Inside me, please!
Thank you, Hino-kun.
But, the sins I cannot tell Shuichi-san have yet again increased.
It's already like this.
You can't cum, so you can't stand it?
I can't take it anymore.
But today is our wedding anniversary!
Nanami, leave that man to me.
On that day that I was with Hino-kun, he told me that.
A few days later, Kamata disappeared completely before my eyes.
All of my images of Kamata have been replaced by those of Hino-kun.
But Hino-kun won't tell me what he did to Kamata.
We have been freed from Kamata.
I was completely happy.
I'm happy to have my peaceful daily life back.
But I still haven't confessed my sins, so I am still a dirtied woman.
Hino-san comes to my house a two or three times a week.
At those times I let him use my body.
I think I'm being bad to Shuichi-san, but I can't ask Hino-kun to leave.
Looks like I can get home early today.
I wonder if she'll be surprised when I just show up!
Nanami, your pussy is the best!
You only know mine, though, right?
I know. I know you love your husband, Nanami, but right now you're mine!
I can be, right now, I can be your woman, Hino-kun.
Make me feel good by giving me your cock all the way into my pussy!
So good! I can feel it!
So hot! The inside of my pussy is so hot!
I'm doing you, Hino-kun, I'm having sex with you!
It's good, fuck me more, we can do it now.
It's hitting, all the way inside!
It's reaching all the way to my uterus!
No, it feels too good!
I'll have to clean the floor later!
So good, it's so good, it's moving!
Does it feel good? Does sex with me feel better than with your husband?
Don't say that... but it's good, sex with you is better, Hino-kun.
I've already been with Hino-kun many times.
I've already betrayed Shuichi-san many times.
It's hitting, it's so good!
I love Shuichi-san.
My heart belongs only to Shuichi-san.
Hino-kun has saved me.
That's why at the very least, I can let him do as he wishes to my body.
I... can't take it anymore...
Amazing, amazing.
But this relationship cannot continue anymore.
I have to stop it before Shuichi-san notices.
I love only Shuichi-san.
I should not extend my sins any further.
I'm home!
Cumming... I'm cumming!
Today is our fourth wedding anniversary.
There are things I have to tell Shuichi-san when he gets home.
I wonder if he'll be happy.
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Shuichi-san, I'm going to have a baby!
Lots of things have happened, but this baby is yours, Shuichi-san!
Even so, my wife I love
Even so, my wife