www.SubDESU-H.net
In a secluded place,
there stood a lone demon and her magic pet.
Her name was Twiska.
Being a Succubus, she would attack towns filled with men...
Suck their semen dry... and live a free and prosperous life.
Or at least... Until she had that fated encounter...
Episode   The Cute Boy is Minnnnne!
W
I guess that’ll do.
Hey, Nerin, we’re checking out that town tonight.
I-It’s a demon!
Run for it!
Mercy, please!
There’s one for tonight’s catch.
Just give up, boy.
My pussy is amazing, you know.
Now, I wonder how much longer you’ll last?
Oh, please. He already came.
Were you a virgin?
I guess you’re a bit unripe...
But you have a nice strong flavor.
Prepare to die, damned demon!
There’s my second one...
Got’cha!
The loser’s ejaculation is so warm!
Well then!
Where’s my next prey?
Just my type!
The cute boy is MINE!
You’ll be my dinner tonight.
Please stop it!
Please return my Theo!
Stop yourself, Miss!
You mustn’t get close to a demon!
Just let him go.
No! Theo!
Theo... Theo!
What an annoying bitch.
What did you do to her?
No need to worry. She’s just having some pleasant dreams.
Now. It’s time for us to have some fun, too.
What a soft tongue.
Makes me want to swallow it.
How did your first kiss taste?
Oh...oops?
Was it really that intense?
Then... this one’s next!
Please don’t do it.
Don’t complain.
I’m going to give you a taste of ecstasy.
Don’t lick it – it’s dirty.
What a cute little dick.
I’ll make your dick so naughty you’ll stop covering your face in shame.
You tongue is moving my foreskin...
Don’t take the foreskin off...the insides will come out.
Looks like you’re very sensitive there.
After his first kiss, now I get his first fellatio!
D-Don’t lick so hard.
It’s throbbing and feels funny...
Now it’s coming.
Don’t...!
I’ll pee!
It always tastes the best when no one else has tasted it before!
I’m sorry.
That wasn’t pee, it was semen.
Well, Theo-kun? How does it feel to be an adult?
I’m not sure...
My penis feels strange.
Now I can’t put my pants back on.
He’s still hard after cumming.
Come on in, Theo-kun, my dear.
I want to show you the thrill of plowing a woman’s pussy.
I don’t want to.
I think that’s dirty.
It’s not dirty!
Your mommy has one of them too!
N...No way!
Well, I suppose mine is hundreds of times better than hers, though.
The was done by SubDESU-H, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
You’re rather big...
Oh, no. Why am I so excited?
I almost came by being penetrated by a virgin.
Oh, yes... being the first makes me so excited.
Makes me want to move my own hips.
Please don’t move!
What are you saying?
It won’t feel good unless one of us moves.
Doesn’t it feel good to have your penis rub the inside of my pussy?
Oh, that’s the spot!
Oh, you’re so precious!
Theo, you’re so cute!
Oh no...
It feels like something is coming out of my penis again...
Please stop it... Ohhh!
Cumming inside feels the best.
You can cum inside, so cum plenty, okay?
Oh no!
He came inside. Awesome!
Eh? Wh-what?
You really got swept away by your own ego there, didn’t ya.
You shitty bitch!
H-He transformed?
That’s NOT cute.
Who the hell are you?!
You tried to seduce and kill a fellow demon?
You’re way too inexperienced for that sort of thing!
T-That hurts!
This can’t be...
I’m being raped by a human?
Oh no...don’t!
This time let’s take things by MY pace.
Take that!
No...It’s amazing!
All the way into my womb...it’s so thick...and so hard!
Th-that’s little Theo?
What’s going on here?
Oh! That looks like the “hero” of which the legends speak.
“H-Hero”? He is?
He just looks like a street tough to me.
Hundreds of years ago, a man defeated the demon clan.
Theo must be his direct descendent.
I suppose that when Theo was raped by the Succubus, his old blood was resurrected.
Not so...rough...please...I’ll...break...
Maybe I SHOULD break you – then you won’t be able to go back to your old tricks.
N...no!
Talking back to me? You immature bitch!
Take that. And cum!
Wow...so much inside of me.
This hot semen is driving me nuts.
Why does it feel so good to have him cum inside of me?
Okay! Who wants revenge on this demon girl next?
First come, first serve!
What?
I am... a proud bearer of the ancient Hero’s blood.
So I cannot let the demon escape.
That was a close one.
But it sure felt good.
He sure was cute.
I hope I see him again someday.
And when I do, I’ll fucking KILL him!
Just you wait!
www.SubDESU-H.net