P-Please, I'll masturbate but at least let me wear my panties.
I just can't let... I can't let anyone seen me masturbate with my pussy bare.
It's so embarrassing, I'll die!
I won't know what you're doing if I can't see.
Please get on with it.
Do it like always, Princess.
It looks beautiful, Princess.
You...
Dare make me...
Do something like this..!
You're punished when you fail to complete your mission.
No matter how important you are, even you, Lunatemis-sama.
That's the law in this Great Lunarium Kingdom, isn't it?
Being seen by a man when I'm masturbating like this...
It makes me want to die of shame!
The panties of a princess are of high quality, just as I thought they would be.
Wh-What are you doing with my panties like that?!
If you have a woman's panties in your hand, shouldn't you smell them?
They certainly have a strong smell.
No! Stop it! You know I always wear clean panties every day!
They shouldn't smell like that!
But I can see the stain, Princess.
There's nothing like that!
I don't want this anymore... How many times should I do something like this?
You're getting wet from masturbating while being watched by a man who's holding your panties like this...
You're such a pervert, Princess.
I can smell your sweat and pee from your panties, Princess.
It can't be...
I always clean them.
You can't get rid of the smell from such well-worn panties so easily.
I'm being insulted by my own servant because of my panties...
No, I can't stop!
No, I shouldn't do this in front of my servant-
I guess it's about time.
Princess, please spread your legs more.
Stop it, you can't touch me like this!
No... I can't resist.
I'll... I'll cum while being watched by men... With my servant like this-
Cum... I'm going to cum...
No... I mustn't... I mustn't cum...
Cum... Cum... Cumming... What is this? I can't... Stop it!
Emblem Steal!
No, I can't... Move any more...
What are you doing in there?
W-Wait, isn't the punishment already over?
I just can't help being like this, after watching the Princess masturbating like that.
Stop it... Don't come near me... Don't you understand me?!
Lunatemis, stop moving and listen to me!
I can't move my body...
Don't you like doing something like this, Princess?
Stop it... Please...
I never do things like this... That's why...
Is that so? It looked like you'd masturbated before.
It'll be over soon, just lie back and look at the ceiling.
No... No..!
If you don't accept it, it won't feel very good for you.
No way... My body is so sensitive after masturbating like that...
Here you go... I'll go deeper into you.
It hurts... It hurts...
My virgin blood...
No, don't start moving so quickly!
Inside my stomach...
It's so big and hard...
I can feel it!
It's so wet, I'm gonna go crazy!
No... Stop it... I can't take it any more!
Please... Be gentle with me.
No! If you do it so hard, I can't hold back!
If you punish me more than this...
That big thing... Feels good...
It's so good... No!
Don't squash my breasts like that...
I... I feel strange inside...
I'm gonna cum!
It's starting to feel too good...
No way, I'm feeling so good!
Cumming... I'm gonna cum again!
I've only ever masturbated by myself before...
Now I'm gonna cum with my servant's penis!
I'll let it out inside you, Princess.
No, you can't let it out inside... You can't..!
No... Cum... Cumming... Cumming!
I'm cumming!
Came... You came so much inside me...
Even though I said you couldn't...
W
Aku no Onna Kanbu
You dare punish me!?
Don't joke with me!
Where do you think you're sitting?
This is the throne room, where the princess holds court.
Then, I'm gonna win the throne.
I had enough with your rudeness when you were playing with my body.
Now you dare say you're gonna win my royal throne?!
Well... You don't have to get so angry, Princess.
Silence, I'm getting rid of you right now!
Lunatemis, come to my side!
A-Again... My body is...
As I thought.
Wh-What do you mean by that?
Princess, your pussy is soaked... Did you actually like having sex with me before?
It's not like that... It's just because we did it before...
I can't move my body.
Were you expecting something from me when you were looking for me before?
You... You.... Insolent fool!
I'll explain it to an indecent Princess like you.
Lunatemis, suck my dick!
My body is moving on its own...
There's a moon ability to rule everything in this Great Lunarium Kingdom,
It's an ability given to us at birth, and its power is decided at the same time.
For those at the top, like the Queen, it's Twin Moon.
Then for the Princess it's Full Moon.
This is the ability which you had before.
The upper classes are Half Moon.
The lower classes, like me, are Crescent Moon.
For the lowest level soldiers, it's Peace Moon.
I just took your moon ability from you before.
What is that?
It's called Emblem Steal, which can steal someone's moon ability and make it yours.
Is that possible?
The proof is that you can't resist my orders.
I can't accept that...
Your level, having lost your moon ability,
Is even lower than a soldier's moon ability level.
There's no way you can resist my orders now.
That can't be!
You just lost your virginity, but you're already getting good at this.
I'll let it out, accept it with your lovely face!
No... You can't... Cover my face with that...
No way... It's dirty...
Lunatemis, don't clean up your face!
Why...?
I feel disgusting...
I'll let you remember the smell of my sperm so you'll know your master from now on.
There's so much sticky stuff on my face...
I don't want this...
Why should I have to suffer like this?
You don't have to worry.
I'll keep the secret of your lost moon ability quiet.
I'll return it later.
Is that true?!
Sure, that will make my plans easier.
But, I'll make you do something more before that.
What should I do?
As I expected of a Princess like you, you're getting easier to talk to.
The Half Moon ability which the aristocrat Kaguya has...
I want you to find out her weakness and bring her to the punishment room later.
That's-
There's no pressure on you to do it, but right now your fate is in my hands.
That... Can't be...
I can't hear your answer, Princess!
I'll... Do as you say.
You're gonna punish me again... today?
Isn't that obvious, since you can't find Kaguya's weakness at all.
It's punishment for that.
It's inside!
It's impossible for me to find out Kaguya's weakness like this.
We're given the mission to get more information on how to rule Earth,
and also to make another moonland on Earth as proof of this.
But lately, the mission isn't being done with a partner.
Also, you've transferred into an Earthling school to find out more about them, right?
That's because...
Isn't finding Kaguya's weakness an easy mission for you?
There's a lot to do.. Like homework and tests...
Then you make me do something like this every day.
That's because you couldn't fulfill the mission I gave you, Princess.
You're playing with my body like this... Every night... Every night...
No... You can't! You can't move my body like that!
You're really enjoying this, do you like my dick that much?
This isn't me, there's no way I'd want to do it with you like this...
You... You can't touch there!
Stop... Stop.. Stop it... Anymore than this...
If you do something like that... I'm gonna...
No!
Is it possible that you want to cum?
No... No!
I don't want to cum!
With someone like you-
You say something like that, but you spend every night with me.
I really don't want to cum with someone like you.
I don't want to cum... But if this goes on...
I'm..!
Cumming... Cumming... Cumming!
Please... Stop it... I've got to go to school today...
You're making me do it again...
Please... let's stop it for today.
I've got to... I've got to go to the academy right now.
No... Not again...
I'm cumming!
You came inside me again...
You... Came inside my womb...
You pervert!
Isn't the Princess the perverted one?
Then it's time to go, Princess. Go to the academy like that.
I feel so disgusting like this.
Princess, I'll accompany you to the academy.
Katsuma, I've found Kaguya's weakness.
You can give your report later, I'm gonna see if you obeyed my order from this morning.
You can't be serious... In a place like this?
Then, if you'd be so kind as to show me...
There could be somebody here who might see...
Please do it quickly.
What are you talking about?
You've been doing it since last night and your body smells like cum,
and you're just using your clothes without cleaning it up first.
There's a lot of cum inside of your pussy right now,
there are vibrators on your nipples and in your pussy,
and you're just acting like the usual honour student in class.
That's... Because you told me to do it this morning.
Even though you've cleaned your face, I can still see some cum in your pretty hair.
No... Not again.
Maybe there's even someone in your class who has realised what a pervert you are, Princess.
Please... Stop doing it already...
You're getting excited so easily, aren't you?
Your panties are stained with cum, you know?
Hm... Is it possible that you're wetting yourself, Princess?
That's not true!
I can even feel pee coming out of your pussy.
That's not true! That can't happen to me...
How foolish, in a place like this...
You can't do this, there might be someone watching...
Being fucked from behind by my servant like this...
Please don't move so quickly...
My body's really sensitive after being fucked so much since yesterday...
If someone were to see me like this...
That's true, someone's gonna see the Great Lunarium Kingdom's Princess being fucked in a park in the middle of the day.
No... Don't say something like that!
I'll spread this within the Great Lunarium Kingdom, Earthling, even within our organisations.
No... If that happened then I couldn't bear to live any more!
No... There's a loud noise coming out from the back of my body.
It's too intense... Please be gentle!
Your lovely moaning voice is louder than the noise coming from your hips, Princess!
I wonder how long you can keep from moaning.
There it is again, your lovely voice!
Then Princess, can you tell me Kaguya's weakness?
You want me to tell you right now?
If you tell me, then I'll reward you.
That's...
If you're able to say it, then I'll satisfy you.
No... You're moving slowly now...
There's no way I'll be satisfied with something like this-
No... You can't... Please stop moving!
No... Stop it... I just can't hold it...
Forgive me, Katsuma...
K-Kaguya's weakness is you, Katsuma.
You and she lived together before...
There's no way that she could get rid of you from her life.
Is that so? So Kaguya feels like that...
K-Katsuma... Are you two in a relationship?
Princess, is it possible that you're jealous of her?
I-Idiot, there's no way I would be!
Do you think that Kaguya would take my dick all for herself?
It... It's not like that!
I never realised that you had such a cute side to you.
I-Idiot, I said it's not like that!
For a cute and perverted Princess like you, I'll give you a reward.
It's... Deep...
No...
Please... Make me cum...
I can't believe that I'm gonna cum outdoors like this...
It's fine... I don't really care if there's anyone watching me.
No... Cumming...
No... I'm cumming... No..!
Your cum is overflowing within my pussy...
It'll be your turn next time, Kaguya.
Kaguya, you're so foolish. If you'd just left me, you wouldn't have had to fail your mission.
It's not your fault... If I had just had enough power back there... I'm glad you're fine, though.
No, Katsuma... What are you doing?
Something perverted, of course.
The punishment is that kind of thing?
I just want you to feel ashamed a bit.
Is that so? If that's so... If it's Katsuma, then I...
Hm, did you say something?
It... It's nothing, just do it quickly.
No, what is this?
No... No...
No... I don't want this kind of punishment...
You're touching my pussy like that...
If you rub your hands on my pussy that way...
You're already this wet... You really are an indecent woman, aren't you?
No... No... Don't say something like that... I'm not that kind of indecent woman...
Katsuma, you're so cruel... Why must you punish me like this?
But your pussy is soaked, it seems to like this.
No... There's no way I can be like that.
Gonna go crazy... I'm gonna go crazy!
No..!
You can't do that, Katsuma!
It's coming, there's something coming from there!
Isn't that enough, I feel so embarrassed...
Next, shall I put that big and hard thing into your pussy?
You can't be serious... Katsuma, you're cruel... So cruel...
No... You can't, I can't let you have my first time like this...
No... I can't... I can't stand like this, Katsuma.
Geez, you're so weak against an old friend like me.
I'll stop for now.
Katsuma...
Change of plan then. Hey, come inside!
Princess, wh-what's the matter with you?
Katsuma, you took your time... Can't you see that I'm already like this?
What does this mean, Katsuma?
From now on, the three of us will enjoy ourselves together.
Lunatemis, come here and make Kaguya feel good.
St-Stop it... Please stop it..!
Kaguya, you have beautiful breasts and a lovely virgin pussy, don't you?
Please... Don't look at it...
I had lovely pussy too, but after having sex with Katsuma every day its shape changed to this.
P-Princess...
Kaguya... You're so delicious...
Katsuma... Princess...
You don't have to think about anything right now... Just enjoy the pleasure, Kaguya.
Lunatemis, if you can make Kaguya feel good then I'll give you your reward later.
Is that true?!
It... It's not that I want the reward, so I'm doing this because I want to.
No... No way, this kind of thing is strange for me.
Katsuma... Don't look, don't look at me..!
No...
Your finger feels too good!
No... My voice... This perverted voice of mine...
Katsuma is listening to my voice!
Princess, please stop this... I'm gonna go crazy if you keep doing something like this to me!
It's about time I put my dick in you, isn't that what you want, Kaguya?
K-Katsuma, the Princess is here.
What's the matter with that? I'm sure your pussy will be so happy to have sex with me and be seen by the Princess.
That's... I'm gonna be watched by someone my first time doing it...
Katsuma, what about me?
I'll give you my dick later.
Now we're dealing with Kaguya first.
A woman's body is also delicious, right?
Kaguya's body is delicious, but Katsuma's penis is even more so.
Princess makes me feel... This good...
I'm scared...
You'll have to take responsibility... If I get pregnant from having unprotected sex...
Sure, I'll take responsibility.
It... It hurts... It hurts... Hurts...
Pull it out... Pull it out!
What a lovely person you are, Kaguya.
No... I don't want to have my first time being watched by someone...
...Being watched by the Princess in this way.
Isn't it great to feel a dick for the first time?
There's no way I can feel good from this embarrassment and this pain.
Please don't watch, please don't look at me right now!
Being watched by the Princess... While I'm having sex like this... I just can't live with it...
No way... You can't do this kind of perverted thing.
No... My body feels good from Katsuma's movement...
I can't... I can't let myself feel such pleasure... My dignity as an aristocrat...
Then I'll give you so much pleasure everyday from now on with this kind of raw sex.
No! I'm gonna go crazy if I have sex like this every day!
I'll give you this dick every day, and after you bear my child I'm gonna let everyone watch you having sex like this.
No... No... No... I can't let anyone else see me having sex like this!
You're feeling happy being watched when having sex like this.
You're so perverted.
It's cute, Kaguya.
That's... That's because I didn't know that having sex like this could be this good.
Do I look like a pervert, getting excited from being watched while having sex?
Don't look at it... Please don't look at me... If you look at me, I'll...
I'll cum inside you, Kaguya.
No... You can't cum inside..!
I can't let you cum inside in front of someone else like this, please cum outside...
I'll let the Princess watch as you get pregnant from this!
No... I can't let the Princess see me get pregnant! No!
No... Your penis is getting so hard inside me!
No... No!
Emblem Steal!
There's a lot of Katsuma's sperm inside of me, I can't be an aristocrat any more.
Katsuma, it's my turn next.
Katsuma's penis is really good, my body felt so hot when I was watching you earlier on!
I want you to do it more!
Katsuma, does it feel good? I feel so good right now.
Even though we're not married, or even lovers,
I let Katsuma cum inside me like that...
In front of someone else as well.
I never though Katsuma would have that Emblem Steal ability, but I want you to stop acting so recklessly.
You don't have to do this to make me obey what you say.
Kaguya, don't you dare get rid of me like this!
You just have to help me make Katsuma's penis get hard!
Don't be rude to your master, servant!
Katsuma feels much better when having sex with me than with you, servant!
That... That's not entirely true, we've known each other for a long time, so I'm sure Katsuma would also feel good doing it with me...
Do you feel excited?
There's no way I can't be excited with perverted girls like you, right?
Pervert...
You're getting excited with that kind of servant's pussy...
My pussy is much better than hers, right?
There's no way that my royal pussy would lose against the low quality pussy of my servant.
Lunatemis's pussy make me so hard, I want to cum inside again.
Princess, please don't get in my way.
You feel the way you do right now because of my pussy, right?
My fresh pussy is better than hers, right?
Look at how good Katsuma is feeling.
That can't be true, it's because of my perverted pussy that his penis can be this big!
Hey, hey, don't you two get jealous of each other.
Idiot, who's getting jealous of her?!
That's right, I'm just obeying your orders...
Just cum quickly... Don't you see that my pussy is already soaked?
We're doing these perverted things like lovers do, so please cum quickly!
No! I'm gonna let him cum from my pussy!
No... No! I can't stand it when your tongue keeps licking my pussy like that!
My hips are moving by themselves again!
Your big penis is inside... Deep inside me!
It... It feels good!
It's coming! I can feel it in my pussy... Hot stuff is gonna come out..!
Cumming... I'm gonna cum again with a man's penis like this... I can't hold it anymore... I'm gonna cum!
I can't hold back either... I'm gonna cum together with the Princess.
Cumming... Cumming... Cumming!
Cumming... Cumming... Cumming... Cumming!
I can... I can do this.
With this Emblem Steal, I'll make...
those evil and arrogant aristocrats obey my orders!