Soaked in his sperm, the woman became a slave to her sexual desires.
He was a peculiar man.
A renowned playboy, he attracted several lovers with his wealth and talent.
But his father was hardly pleased.
In the Foreign country of Victorvarg.
The children of upper-class gather.
The Prestigious college, Royal Viccia Academy.
He will be forced to study there.
Chiba Kagetora, the son Japan Premiere Group president.
He hid his nature in the academy.
He shown him self a fool.
He’s scorned and despised by the people around him but.
The fate of their encounter was born.
The princess of a small country.
Ridim, The Silver Yuki Hime.
Princess of Victorvarg.
Shasty, The Golden Rose Princess.
The daughter of a large company.
Yukino, The Black Orchid Princess.
Kagetora, his heart has been taken by the three female students who’re honored as princesses by the other students.
And at the same time a dark desire creped out from deep inside his heart.
He's going to show his true nature.
To obtain those girls.
He had his devoted maid Meirin to aid him.
He made his move, taking the advantage of his ability, to make those beautiful princesses fall into his hands.
Eww, it’s the clown.
He’s still bringing his maid here, he’s like the upstart countryman.
Don’t mind them.
Leave them alone.
Yes.
Hmp...
I don’t know who cummed first but.
Silver Yuri Hime, how weird.
Ridim-sama, are you ok?
No... it's nothing.
She can’t handle the effect of my sperm.
How long can you handle it?
Princss Ridim, the flower in the party.
Thank you Shasty.
Oh, it's Shasty-sama.
Next is the Princess of this country.
Golden Rose Princess, Shasty.
It’s the Golden Rose Princess.
Wonderful.
But it’s started ripening.
Maybe it's already the time to harvest.
Ok, how about the other prey...
She’s not here.
Chiba-sama.
I’m a messenger of Yamato.
I have a letter to give to you.
From Black Orchid Princess Yukino?
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
No...
My body is reacting...
No, I must not do this in the office.
But...
I’m at my limit.
Come in...
I’m coming in.
What a great honor to be called by you Black Orchid Princess.
So, what kind of "business" are we going to talk?
You know that already!
The maiden clothing fits you Yukino-sama.
That’s what I expect from president of Yamato.
The traditional dress looks good on you.
Even you confuse me with that kind of compliment.
Do you really wanted your dirty body to be purified? You even wear those clothes.
You wanted mine so badly since I took away your virginity right?
N-no.. that's not.
I’m not feeling good so that’s why.
That’s why.
The one gets soaked with my sperm will crave for my hot dick.
You will get hot even from the sperm squirted on your body.
But you can’t handle it if I release it inside.
That part still tingles even now right?
No its not!
Then? What’s the reason for calling me here?
The medicine, give me more medicine that eases this ache.
This one you mean?
Yes, that is.
You really wanted this?
It tingles more after the effect of medicine ran out.
I can’t even sleep at night.
This one is diluted with my sperm.
It can ease the symptom for awhile.
But the more you take this the more you’ll be my slave of my sperm.
You already used the entire one I gave you?
This one is not one I can easily give, even to you Princess.
I have no money, but for exchange let me do this.
Hey, what are you going to do Princess?
For the cost of the medicine, let me do it with my mouth like before.
I smell the sperm.
Please give me the medicine.
It’s very different than before.
I can’t think this is the one done by Yamato Nadeshiko.
If you wanted that much, then I’ll release a lot.
Here!
Please give me the medicine.
What are you saying?
I can’t be satisfied if you do the same thing.
No way!
What are you. . ah!
You must pay with the mouth on the bottom today.
How brave you are to call a man without wearing panties.
No it's not.
Most of the time it is.
It's wet already.
How wonderful of you to bear it all this way.
Stop this already..
Don’t say stop if you feel it this much.
I’m not feeling it!
How strong are you to be tough?
It's not clean there.
No...
Please don’t touch there.
What are you saying? You always feel it in this part.
Yukino is a pervert that likes to be touched here.
No-o-o!
This sensitive body, it’s not only because of my sperm.
Are you satisfied with this?
What are you saying? You’re only the one who's cum.
Are you going to have sex with me?
Of course.
I only raped you few times, but the pussy takes it so easily.
The first time it was just a tight hole.
Ouch ouch!
Stop it.
No!
No-o-o!!!
This man’s sperm is going inside me!
What’s this!? Its still releasing?
I’m going to break!
My purity is ruined by this man!
No... don’t thrust it like that!
I’m becoming a knothole by having sex with a man who is not my husband.
I.
I’ll release it inside again.
Are you going to release it inside me again?
Don’t do it...
I’m going to break if you do that again.
I’ll release it directly in the cervix and make you pregnant.
What’s this?
I’m going to break.
No-o!
Stop this.
My cervix will break.
Become pregnant!
My cervix is cumming.
The sperm is shooting inside me!
I’m going to get pregnant!
The cervix is full of sperm.
There’s no time to rest.
Next, we’ll pay with this hole.
In asshole!?
As I expected, you like it in this part too.
Stop it, putting a dick into my asshole is ruining the modesty of Yamato Nadeshiko.
So what if Yamato Nadeshiko?
You're feeling it as I thrust into your ass.
No I'm not.
My mind is white as my dirty hole is being thrust with that big dick.
My ass will be ruined if we continue this.
I’m going to pass out with this immodest doing.
Let’s finish this!
No-o!
Here it goes!
A lot of sperm is going into my stomach again!
It's harder than the constipation!
Plenty of my sperm soaked into your front and back right?
It's coming out.
The sperm is coming out from my ass and pussy.
It’s ejaculating from the cervix.
The sperm is coming out.
It feel so good!
Meirin, please take care of the rest.
And share the semen ample with Yukino.
Yes sir!
How long can you resist the sexual desire?
Stop it.
If you release any more, I’ll really be pregnant!
You’re the one who said put it in the front right?
It’s because I’ll be no longer my self if you do it again in the ass.
I can’t be no longer a Yamato Nadeshiko.
Then be quiet and get pregnant!
No-o-o!
I can’t make a baby yet!
No-o!
Don’t thrust deeper!
I’m going to cum!
I’m going to be raped again!
He ejaculated again so much!
No-o-o-o! It feels so good, I’m going to break.
You lost consciousness.
Then I’ll take the main dish.
I’m here Princess.