SubDESU-H
He loved me.
But... Sensei.
W
Hakoiri Musume Yuutou Sei Yukino
「Princess Girl Honor Student Yukino」
I haven't spoken to her since then.
I thought things were going very well.
Kirihara-san? What's up?
Kirihara-san!
Are you okay, Kirihara-san?!
What should we do?
Hey! Someone call the teacher!
I got it. Teacher! Teacher!
G-Good morning!
Take it easy - you've been asleep. It's 6 PM already.
It's 6 PM? Am I...?
You are a little anemic - you need to rest a little bit more.
Sensei, have you been here for a while?
I am on watch today.
Are you still thinking about the things from earlier?
That's not it.
This is...?
This kind of mail comes every day.
What can I do?
I am very sorry Kirihara.
I think I have to leave this school.
N-No, please don't!
I don't want to hurt you anymore.
No, I'm not hurt, I'm fine 'cause I love you.
Love? The man who raped you?
Because you're the only one who seriously listened to me.
Great!
Oh, Sensei!
Kirihara, you're so wet.
N-No am not, this is just sweat!
Really? what a sticky sweat!
My body feels funny... I feel like I'm floating on air.
Kirihara, I knew you were sensitive here.
I'm about to cum... no!
Kirihara, you are a very dirty girl.
Don't tease me like that.
Here I come, Kirihara.
You have to take off your clothing.
It's okay like this.
Sensei, I feel your dick inside of me!
S-Sensei? Do you feel good?
Kirihara, you are wonderful.
I'm very happy!
Can I fuck you harder?
Yes. Do whatever you want to!
Your voice is so cute!
You're pushing so hard... It feels so weird.
You don't like it?
N-Not that I don't like it!
How do you feel? Tell me honestly.
It feels so good!
You are a good girl.
Sensei's dick is deep inside me.
This hard fucking is making me go crazy!
Forget everything bad in life and just enjoy it!
My head...
is empty!
Oh, it's you Kirihara.
I just want to say thank you, Sensei.
You mean about that email?
I don't get those emails anymore, thanks to you.
I'm glad.
Umm, Sensei...
She is really like my sex slave.
Time to test her loyalty now.
I've gotten your picture, you're so cute...
S-Sensei, what's happening here?
She's the one who sent you that email.
Y-Yumi did?
I envy you Yukino, your tits are so big!!
Stop, Yumi!
Forget the bad stuff and just enjoy this.
No way, this was all just a farce?
Of course. I made it up because I wanted to fuck you a lot Kirihara.
Please tell me you're just kidding.
Put your hands completely around your tits.
I played the nice teacher role and waited until...
you wanted me.
I think this is... just a dream.
Kirihara, you wanted sex. That's why you came here, right?
Well I'll fuck you a lot!
No!
I knew you loved it deep!
Stop the deep fucking, please.
No... stop that!
N-Not again...
I'm going crazy!
My stomach is full of hot cum.
Your pussy feels really good. I could do it forever.
I-I can't think about anything.
Sensei's dick is deep inside me.
Use the word "pussy".
My pussy is being squeezed from the inside.
I can't take anymore!
What a slut the rich Kirihara group's princess is.
It's been many weeks now.
Kirihara hasn't came to school, and I can't connect to her cell phone either.
The back of that uniform... Could it be...?
Kirihara?
Sensei?
Long time no see, Sensei.
What happened all of a sudden - did you quit school?
I left my parents' house and I'm living alone now.
Don't worry. I know how to make money.
Phone Msg: "Love Email. Welcome! Yukikko-sama."
What the hell, Kirihara?
Stop that!
This is none of your business.
Wait, Kirihara!
Do you want to fuck me?
I was a good girl, like a princess.
Except now I'm not satisfied with just you, Sensei.
Hey, Kirihara...
You've gotta hurry up - the next guy is waiting for me.