Blood pressure 85 over 65.
Respiration, 100.
Pulse, 140.
I, an ordinary male student, suddenly collapsed one day.
It was just too late; there was nothing they could do.
My only option was to quietly wait for death.
I see. The cancer has spread through his entire body.
I was trying to come to terms with my imminent death, when...
Looks like your readings are off the charts.
A woman from the pharmaceutical company came to my hospital room.
-But don’t worry
This drug is still being tested.
And there are...
... great risks associated with it.
To be honest, I was really captivated by her huge tits...
If we're just do something like this.
So I wasn’t paying much attention to what she was saying.
And... the result...
Musashino Takumi-kun here...
Has been turned into a girl by the drugs that saved his life.
H-Hey.
Y-Yo
Takumi was
Changed into a woman
And is fucked here, there, and everywhere
This is the tale!
W
What? Seriously?
What will you DO
once you become a woman?
Fucking unreal!
Is that even possible??
Is that really you, Takumi-kun?
He’s so pretty!
Uh, being called 'pretty' doesn’t exactly...
H-Hey, Takumi, can I touch your tits?
S-Sick, dude! I’m still a boy, you know?
-Hey, that’s hella rude
But Takumi! If you’re still a boy, then you must understand how we feel, right?
If I don’t squeeze your tits right now, I think I might never squeeze any tits as long as I live!
Aw, shut the fuck up.
Now you’re making me feel like the bad guy.
Fine, get it out of your system.
Woah, shit!
Takumi... Why don’t you touch these yourself?
It’s fucking awesome!
Of course I touched them... but it was strangely pleasurable.
Oh! They’ve gotten firmer!
The nipples... They’re all perky.
Does this turn you on?
N-Not really...
Oh, crap. I feel like I’m gonna moan.
Guess it’s not bad...
I need to calm down.
So soft!
So glad there’s no bra in the way.
Takumi! You smell so good!
What are you doing?
Is this some new kind of game?
Um... like you’re pretending to be pro-wrestlers?
Ah, just stop it!
Stop squeezing my boobs!
Aw, just a bit more!
Suguhara...
Oh, I’m sorry.
But I’m just surprised that you really became a girl.
Your frame got more delicate,
And your uniform is all baggy on you.
Yeah, all my other clothes don’t fit anymore either.
Wanna come over to my place after school?
I’ll give you some of my old clothes.
I wonder if we’re the same size.
These are fucking sexy!
I’m surprised you wear such dirty underwear.
Try on whatever you want.
G-Girl’s panties sure are tiny.
If I still had my dick, it’d be hanging out.
Ew. Don’t say weird things like that.
I don’t wear those clothes anymore, so take what you want.
Sugahara’s old bras and panties, eh?
If I told the guys about this, they’d hate me.
Now, don’t talk like that.
And you need to fasten the bra properly or your boobs will get squashed.
Since you’re a girl now, you need to learn how to wear a bra properly.
A girl, huh?
Wearing something like this really makes me feel like it’s actually happened.
And you’re such a pretty girl, too.
So we need to dress you up cutely.
If we do that, I’m sure the boys will be all over you.
Though that doesn’t make me happy in the slightest.
All over me... eh?
Yes!
Just like a girl!
Awesome!
Isn’t it nice?
Though virgins like you guys would never get something like this as long as you live.
What? Takumi! You’re a virgin too, ya know.
Idiots.
Right now, I’m... a girl-virgin!
I’m not like you guys.
I have no comeback for that!
Hey, Takumi! At least show us what a woman is!
What about poor me? I wanna learn everything about womanhood!
Stop embarrassing yourselves... Um, what do you want me to do?
Tell me you like me.
Or hold my hand.
Or kiss me. Or date me!
Just do something!
Okay, fine, you’re grossing me out!
Fine, I’ll do whatever you want.
Oh... Th-Then...
I love you! I’ve got it bad!
Woah, my heart’s pounding!
This’s intense!
I love you, sweetie.
I love you!
This is just practice, so you have to say it back, otherwise it doesn’t count!
I-I love you... You’re the man for me.
Hey, that hurts!
Be gentle!
Like this?
Like this, right.
Hey! Where’re you touching out of nowhere!
Where? We need to practice the hand technique.
'Hand technique'? Are you fucking retarded?
We don’t want to be told we suck at it if we actually get the opportunity to do it for real.
Yeah, but still... not out here...
Someone will see us!
Don’t worry, we’re surrounding you so no one can see.
Real female panties!
Stop it!
Takumi! You sure are pretty!
That strange voice... Was that me?
Show us your pussy!
Your pussy, wet and dripping from my fingers, it’s fucking hot!
Really?
L-Let me touch it too!
Woah! Her pussy really is wet!
I can’t... I can’t stand up...
I only ask because it’s you, Takumi...
Could you, um... perform fellatio on me?
Put your dick away, dude!
You fucker!
Please, Takumi?
Just once in a lifetime is enough, I want my dick sucked!
Why me? It stinks...
My friend is so hard because of me?
What’s wrong with me?
I don’t like guys...
Swallow it all the way.
It’s so thick.
And... sort of salty...
Harder... Suck it harder!
Yes, that’s it!
That’s hot!
Takumi’s mouth is awesome!
Takumi... You’re a pro!
Being praised for my dick-sucking technique feels weird.
But it doesn’t feel bad either...
Takumi... You’re so good!
It’s cumming!
Seriously... He’s cumming from my sucking?
What an asshole.
But fine then! Go ahead and cum from my technique!
I’m... cumming!
Ack! It’s cumming in me.
The smell of semen... I can taste it.
Blehhh, what’s this taste?
Those people who say semen tastes good... are fucking liars!
Gross.
I got my dick sucked! Felt great!
N-Next, will you suck me?
That's enough.
If you do any more, you’ll be caught.
R-Ryou?
Sorry about that, making you walk me home.
Well, maybe I took the joke a little too far.
Seriously.
Those guys are such losers.
Even though I look like a girl, that’s just too much.
What are you trying to do?
You fucking whore. Bring Takumi back!
Let go!
He’s strong!
I’m scared.
Men sure are... scary.
Stop it, Ryou...
I lost my ability to stand.
Your panties... They’re soaked through.
Th-That’s because just now, they fingered me...
Wait! Not...
No! Not there! Don’t touch it directly!
You slut. You want this, don’t you?
Ryou’s cock... It’s huge.
There’s a dick on my pussy... Am I gonna lose my girl-virginity?
A cock...
It’s my... hymen... It’s breaking...
It hurts...
It’s inside.
Seriously.
What the fuck is this?
I’m backed into a corner, I guess.
But it feels great.
My hymen breaking feels good!
Not so sudden!
I think this might be nice...
Ryou...
What? It’s feeling even better.
Because I’m kissing him?
My pussy... and my uterus... Every part of my woman’s body is thrilled!
This feels great!
Oh shit.
This feels too good.
Ryou... Ryou is amazing!
R-Ryou...
Ryou... Stop...
Shut up, you fucking pig!
I can’t breathe!
Don’t be so rough.
Be gentle...
You and your slutty pussy...
Are you really okay with this?
Weren’t you looking forward to it?
You ass! Of course I wasn’t looking forward to it.
Why would being treated so roughly feel so good?
It’s still... moving...
Yes... Just keep going...
I’m cumming.
Even though it hurts, I’m cumming! Impossible!
Shit. You fucking pig!
I’ll cum in your dirty pussy!
It’s cumming. His dirty semen. In my dirty pussy!
Oh, yes. Cum inside.
I’m cumming!
Awesome...
I’m gonna... die...
So this is a woman’s pleasure!
It’s awesome.
My pussy is so hot.
It feels like it'll melt!
This is fucking excellent!
It’s... coming again.
Over and over.
I... can’t move at all.
What’s gonna happen to me now?
Can I keep living as a girl?
A month has passed since I became a girl.
When I lost my virginity, I discovered 'female ecstasy'.
And recently... I’ve started to masturbate all the time.
My food is my own body.
Even yesterday, I tickled my pussy all night.
But it’s different...
Unlike that time... something... something is missing!
I’m cumming... cumming...
I thought so... Something is... missing.
Blood?
It’s almost that time of the month.
What? Are you serious?
Yeah.
It’s probably your period.
But this means you really are a real girl now.
It means you can get pregnant.
It means you’ve... got that kind of body...
Bleh. I don’t wanna think about that.
After school, let’s go shopping to get you some pads and painkillers...
Being a girl sure is a pain in the ass.
N-No... Takumi-kun...
M-Molesting?
T-Takumi-kun...
Are you okay, Suguhara?
Yes. Thanks.
T-Takumi-kun?
It’s okay now.
It’s nothing!
What’s this?
His finger's in my asshole.
What an idiot!
I’ll scream out and get him caught!
No way... My voice won’t come out.
Why?
He’s fingering my asshole... What if someone sees?
It’s... not right...
It’s not right.... I’m scared... I don’t know this man... Don’t look at me.
I’ve become a woman.
It’s so embarrassing.
T-Takumi-kun?
Are you okay?
Now I see.
How funny.
Wh-What is?
Because of the genetic therapy, your sex drive is much stronger than normal.
M-My sex drive is?
That can’t be!
Really?
Just take that thing off.
I thought so.
There's no mistaking it.
Oh... Oh shit.
This feels too good.
N-Next... Is that my stop?
Only 4 stations? 5 stations?
Why is he just touching my ass?
This part... This part of me is lonely!
I’m losing my mind.
My ass... My ass is turning me on.
I’m cumming... cumming... cumming!
Oh no!
Just from having my asshole fingered, my pussy is throbbing!
What should I do?
If this keeps up, Suguhara will notice.
But I can’t hold back.
I want it... in my pussy!
I want it!
Fuck... me!
Hurry!
Why?
Why am I so overjoyed about this?
Yes! This is the stuff.
Takumi-kun? What’s wrong?
Your face is bright red.
Don’t worry about me. It’s... nothing...
B-But...
No, seriously, it’s nothing.
It’s all the way inside!
Awesome!
Yes! That’s the stuff!
T-Takumi-kun?
This feels so good!
I could never feel this way from masturbating.
I love cocks!
I don’t care whose cock it is. My friend’s cock. A stranger’s cock.
Oh yes!
Yes.
There’s both in my holes.
So awesome!
I’m losing it!
Awesome!
A stranger’s cock is so awesome!
Even his fingers are salty.
My head is buzzing!
I’m cumming. Oh, cumming.
I’m cumming inside you.
I’m cumming!
Wait!
I’m cumming...
Don’t... I’m a real woman! I can menstruate! And I can get pregnant...!
I don’t get it anymore.
I can’t think anymore.
We will soon arrive at Sakashita Academy.
Sakashita Academy.
The end of the line.
Please don’t leave anything behind.
I thought I was in trouble there.
Takumi-kun! Are you okay?
So hot...
I’m so glad I’m... a girl...
That felt so great.
So great...
Oh? Suguhara-san, right?
Do you need something from me?
Takumi-kun changed sexes through gene therapy, right?
Yes.
I have a favor to ask...
Hey, what is TSF Monogatari about?
Let’s see,
Takumi changes Sex.
And is... Fucked here there and everywhere?
TransSexual Fantasy.
In other words, a sex-change genre story.
By the way, isn’t this supposed to be a preview?
Oh! Whoops.
Molester! Gang Bang! Sexual Feast!!
TSF Monogatari, Trans. 2
will go on sale in the winter, 2012!
In the next episode, Takumi-kun and I will...
Right?