www.SubDESU-H.net
Cele Kano
W
It's been one week since I returned to my apartment.
I'm having nightmares every night.
It smells nice.
Kotoha?
Good morning, did you wake up?
Why are you here?
Oh right...
... that time...
... when I first met her.
And since the time I became aware of her secret...
... we've been into a sexual relationship.
"Who can make the other one cum first?"
We've had such days.
Doing it in the mansion...
... and at school...
... Everywhere...
... anytime...
Then, one day, this girl with huge boobs appeared...
... and I got in a "tight" situation, being tied up.
I have someone I love!
But Ms. Kotoha was there and...
If I recall correctly, you are...
Kurimina Main-san, right?
Would you stop it already?
I understand that we want the same thing, but...
... could you stop picking up things I've thrown away and behaving like a stalker?
What? I'm trash?
I'll make this clear. You're annoying.
Yay, Kotoha said a lot to me.
What should I do?
U-Uhm, listen...
... about that... we didn't do it.
What are you saying?
All of this isn't my problem.
Also, you have someone you love, don't you?
T-That's...
Oh right.
I'll give you permission to have sex.
I'll also give you some time, so why don't you go play around with your crush?
But, please continue your work as a butler.
Hold on, you idiot!
What did you say, you butler?
A-About the girl I love...
... that's you!
What?
You always feign ignorance like that.
And act as if you could do anything by yourself.
But in reality you're lonesome and scared.
Wh-What are you trying to say?
If you push even me away...
... you'll really be alone then, won't you?
Even this situation now... wasn't that just to test...
... if the pet dog stays loyal?
W-Wrong. That's not true!
When I thought you were taken away, my legs gave way.
So you are scared.
Shut up, idiot.
I...
... haven't been confronted this directly with feelings before.
Sorry.
No, it's ok.
It made me happy.
Oh Katsuragi...
... I love you.
Yes.
You love boobs, so...
I love this here too.
N-No.
Don't.
You're amazingly assertive.
I've never seen you like this before.
I'm so wet...
... it's embarrassing.
No, it's wonderful.
Now it's my turn.
Ok.
Can I...
... hog your thing all for myself?
Yes.
No.
That's...
...stop...
I won't stop.
But it's dirty.
It's not dirty at all.
Your pussy tastes delicious.
Good... so good!
You're...
...so lewd.
So are you, Milady.
You idiot.
So that's what my pussy tastes like?
Yes.
Well then, I'll put it in.
I didn't tell you that it's okay, yet.
Wow, is it because you licked me...
...that it feels so good?
Don't... don't, Katsuragi.
If you keep going...
... I'll lose my mind.
Katsuragi, kiss me!
I want to cum while kissing.
Okay.
Kotoha!
Katsuragi!
Amazing, you're dick is pounding inside my hole.
Katsuragi, I love you, I love you, I love you so much!
Katsuragi, I can feel you.
Cum! Cum a lot!
Ah, this is happiness.
I want to stay like this forever.
Listen, I've decided.
You're fired!
What?
Huh? Why? Was she angry after all?
Yes. I was fired that day.
At least, I thought I was fired.
If you weren't we couldn't be alone, right?
I left home. I came here alone.
I rode the train for the first time.
Be grateful.
Kotoha...
Milady!
That's dangerous you know?
Kotoha, I'm so happy.
H-Hey, already using no honorific?
You're getting carried away.
Then what's with this outfit?
You plan on making me horny, don't you?
I want to make you happy.
You did, of course. I'm jumping with joy.
You really love them.
This too.
You idiot~♥
Don't just use your fingers.
You can stick it in my pussy.
Affirmative.
Oh man...
Yours feels so good.
Kotoha!
You dick is the best!
Your pussy too.
I'm cumming!
Unbound from her home, Kotoha was...
... shining so bright...
... and we were living a couple's life, independent and carefree...
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
... and spent our time having fun.
Every day was filled with happiness.
Of course...
... same goes for the nights.
Good!
I feel it!
I like riding on top after all...
... I love it!
The neighbors will hear you.
Let them hear it.
That's not good. We're not in the mansion here.
Kotoha, I'm about to cum already.
N-Not yet!
Now like this.
Yea.
A lot. Give me a lot of your cum!
The exhausted Kotoha is so cute...
... and so lovely...
And that is different from when we were lady and butler.
We were enjoying our lover's relationship to the fullest.
But the one enjoying being a lover...
... was just me.
We can't keep on like this, can we?
If this keeps on...
Good morning.
What's going on? Why the dress up?
Could you accompany me for a bit today?
Yea, okay, but...
T-This is...
This is your home.
How mean. You're planning on returning me, right?
No, you're wrong. Let's have a good talk with your parents.
About our relationship.
What?
They seem to be away for quite awhile, so let's just wait.
This is futile. My father would never even hear of this.
When I tried to talk to him, he wouldn't listen.
I'll just be forced to return home, so let's leave before it's too late.
Well, how about some sex then?
What, now?
We're about to meet them.
It's fine. Let's just strengthen our bond.
What if someone sees us?
Before you were saying "Let them hear."
T-That's...
B-But...
Don't!
We did it a lot on this bed, right?
Oh you...
You really love boobs, don't you?
Not just boobs, here too.
Don't!
I can't even count how many time we had sex.
That spot you feel...
... I know all about it.
Unfair!
Look, it's already dripping wet.
You idiot!
No, don't. Stop it.
What are you-
I told you not to!
You want to do it, too, right?
That's true, but...
It's saying it wants to do it, here.
Don't... I can't hold it much longer.
So, stop then?
You're a tease.
You said "let's do it" first, so...
That's why you're so wet.
Don't say it like that.
You're mean!
Don't suck!
I'll start moaning!
Well then, how about here?
That's my ass. It's dirty.
Licking a spot like that... You're a pervert!
I... can't...
Please, I don't want this sort of foreplay.
Please, hurry up and put it in!
No, not just "Put it in!"
I won't put it in if you don't ask nicely.
What?
I want your cock...
I can't hear you when you whisper it like that.
Say it louder or I won't put it in.
Cock...
What?
Cock...!
What about this?
Please put your cock in my pussy.
Please make love to me with your cock.
Yes. Affirmative!
There...
No!
Don't tease me!
I'm feeling it, I'm feeling it!
How about here?
You love it, right?
I love it!
But do it like you always do, hard and fast.
Grind me!
If you stare at me like that I'll go crazy. Hurry up and cum!
I'm the one who decides that.
Wait, that's too intense!
Don't cover your mouth!
But someone will hear.
Let them hear us making love.
No, it's embarrassing.
Katsuragi...
... I'm about to...
Me me cum!
I won't make you cum if you don't say "I love you!"
No, you're a big tease!
Let me cum!
I... can't...
I love you!
I'll be with you forever!
I'm cumming!
His cum reward... I'm so happy!
I'm... wow... cumming so hard!
Then...
... we talked to her parents who had returned...
... about our relationship.
Her father instantly objected angrily.
But with one word of her mother...
... they agreed to keep an eye on us and see how it goes.
That was...
... "become a butler".
You somehow returned to being a butler.
I'm fine with leaving here anytime.
It doesn't matter where we are, since we're together.
What had changed, was...
Ryuunosuke, let's go.
Affirmative!
... that she now calls me by my first name.
I think.
I'll be going!
Kotoha acknowledges me as her boyfriend...
Fondle them!
I won again.
... she acknowledges me, but...
But I still can't outlast her!
www.SubDESU-H.net