I can’t breathe!
So hot!
This’s strange...
Oh, don’t!
W
Kijutsushi x Majutsushi (Magician x Sorcerer)
The Case Files of Ousaka Academy’s Detective Club.
-The Lone Shadow Cackling In The Night-
Occult Appreciation and Research Club
Spiritual Communications Meeting
Aim for it!
Okay! A spirit is here!
Now, spirit, come down to us, please.
Th-This sure is nice!
Keisuke-kun... Keisuke-kun...
What is it, Jun?
What you’re talking about isn’t the 'school assembly', right?
Shizuku agrees with that statement.
Hey, Pres, we Detective Club people really need to think of what we’re going to present for the school festival.
It’s already been decided.
A very special plan has been set in motion.
Is that so?
Then I’ll take my time enjoying Himiko-chan...
You think I’m finished?
I’m talking about the special plan!
Oh, that’s nice.
Himiko-chan!
You’re not listening...
Silence, fools! Silly Detective Club people!
A spirit has come down to see us!
Please excuse me. Now, let’s continue.
Spirit, spirit, please come to us now...
Is it here?
No one paid attention to me... I’m Michiru. I’m so lonely!
Okay! Michiru-san has possessed Himiko-chan.
W-Which Michiru-san?
On the corner of the fourth block...
You... You can’t mean...?!
Cigarettes
You mean that squish-squish pudding tits Michiru-san?
Michiru can’t hold out any longer!
Daddy!
Hurry!
The spirit is now squishy squishy pudding inside of Himiko-chan!
Michiru... Oh no!
Nice!
Himiko and Michiru in one body.
Both flavors combined are so yummy!
IT’S SO GOOD TO BE ALIVE!
Here! Here, here! Daddy’s right here! I’m your Daddy!
Shoo! Shoo!
'Daddy', she says?
'Daddy' indeed?
This’s freaking bullshit.
It’s obvious she’s faking it.
Is this in the script?
Umm... I wasn’t aware of it.
Just because you want to be accepted into the Occult Club... Cheating is -
- a bit much, isn’t it?
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
Stay out of this, will ya?
A lie is a lie.
Now, let me show you what REAL paranormal activity is.
What the...?
I can’t move...
No... No!
Himiko-chan!
Shit!
I can’t... Move...
But I guess this part would still move.
Now, the real show can begin!
I will have this girl experience the thrill of magical ecstasy!
And this begins the magical ecstasy show!
Did you all enjoy yourselves?
Well, I'll take this girl with me now.
Farewell!
Himiko-kun?
Himiko-kun... Where did you go?
Stop joking and show yourself.
She... She disappeared?
Yeah...
Pres!
Is this a case?
A case?
You mean... A kidnapping?
Himiko-kun?
Okay! We’ve got a case!
Now’s our time to shine, Detective Club!
Yeah!
Let’s look at the clues.
Thorough investigation is the basis of detective work.
... Caught the culprit yet?
J-Just thought I’d remember the scent to see if we could trace it...
Are you a freaking police dog?!
And so, we, the Detective Club at Ousaka Academy, began the case of -
- the mysterious magician.
Kidnapping! Kidnapping!
A teen girl was kidnapped by a mysterious masked woman during a performance on stage!
The mysterious MAGICIAN appeared.
Sakae Himiko
Phantom at the Spirit Communication Event?
President Okado
So what does it say?
'Along with a mixed-sexes event that we cannot put into print,
the girl was taken away into the darkness.'
So? What’ll we do? This crime happened right before our eyes.
If we don’t get the answer soon, it’ll reflect really badly on the Detective Club.
He’s right. It’d be embarrassing since we saw it happen.
We would be crushed indeed.
The case has just fallen into our laps!
This Detective Club has been active for 75 years.
However, it was only asked to solve 7 cases during that entire time.
That’s barely even one case per decade.
B-But! A REAL case has appeared for our generation!
Come, logic! Investigation!
We’re solving this case!
Let’s all work hard, guys!
Yeah, fine... But why do you always push the investigating on us?
I’m fine with it! I prefer to be the Watson of this group.
Right? Ozumi-kun.
I’m just not sure about it...
I’m just not sure...
Come on, guys! Just go out and investigate already!
And so, the Detective Club went out to investigate...
But didn’t really find anything.
The kidnapped Sakae Himiko,
even though she was doing such scandalous things on stage that day,
is actually an ordinary girl.
There weren’t any signs that she would be the target of a crime.
So even if it were a real kidnapping, there didn’t seem to be any motive for it.
What does this mean?
I get it!
If there really was no motive, then the kidnapping itself was the motive!
So does that mean that a 'boob fetishist' is the kidnapper?
Ew. She’s right.
Umm, that’s not exactly what I meant...
I don’t really care either way.
But Keisuke... Aren’t you forgetting something crucial?
Clues are always at the scene of the crime.
How do you expect to find anything if you don’t look?
Guess you’ve got a point there.
Okay! Let’s go to the scene of the crime!
Let’s see...
If that phantom ran away on two feet...
Then he must’ve come through this way.
What a noisy hallway.
This building hasn't been remodeled since the school was opened.
And the Acting Club hasn’t changed its exercises since it started either.
Since the start, eh...
Anyway, let’s check it out.
It’s a forbidden phantom magician costume?
Yes. Long ago, someone in this club wrote a play about a phantom magician.
But then...
The actor who was supposed to play the lead suddenly went missing on opening night.
The reason for her disappearance was never found.
And she was also never found.
All that was left behind was the costume she was supposed to wear.
And what’s more, ever since then, whenever we try to put on this play,
Whoever is cast as the phantom magician has lots of bad luck.
'Bad luck'? Like what?
They get severely injured in accidents,
or they experience some impossible-to-explain paranormal phenomena...
So there it is! The Seven Secrets of the Academy!
The Acting Club’s forbidden play, eh?
It’s a banned production.
The costumes and the script are all locked in storage.
It’s this way.
Phantom Magician.
It’s gone!
What does this mean?
Perhaps the culprit stole them?
That’s still unclear.
But if this was the work of the kidnapper, then...
I don’t know!
But that reminds me, there’s something I just remembered about the Phantom Magician.
Phantom Magician
Hiiii.
It’s tape... His costume is held together with tape...
Well, well, well. If it isn’t my friends at the Detective Club.
Oh my, do we have a rookie here?
Nice to meet you.
I'm the president of the Phantom Magic Club, Nikaido.
Thanks. Nice to meet you too.
Okay! As a sign of my good will, let me show you some nice magic.
As you can see, I’m holding a horizontal striped handkerchief.
And with just one move...
Ta-dah! It’s been changed to vertical stripes!
Awesome!
Okay! Then next up, I’ll show you this mysterious ring...
Look, Jun. It’s over here as well.
You’re right. Those pictures look just like him.
Ah yes, those are photos of all the presidents we’ve ever had.
Listen, where do you keep that costume?
I think Kamichi-sensei has it.
Sensei?
Huh?
Right now... I’ll take it off... Argh... It’s not coming off... Why? You little...!
I’m kinda wiped.
For real.
I’m staying overnight at the school tonight.
What for?
I’m guarding our class’s entry for the school festival.
It’s my turn tonight.
Huh?
What could this be?
I’m back!
What’s wrong?
Notice:
Next victim will be Watoizumi Jun.
It’s your turn.
Tonight, I will appear before you.
- Magician
But how did he leave a letter in here? This room was locked.
Isn’t it obvious? He used magic!
Hozumi, Jun is going to be kidnapped!
What should we do?
I wish I knew...
Don’t worry, Senpai, you’ll be okay!
Fine. I’ll set a trap for the magician!
A trap?
I’m surprised this suits me. I could get used to this.
Oh, Jun, it’s you?
This whole plan is pointless if you’re here.
But somehow I just can’t calm down.
I guess it’s, like, tough to stay calm when you know someone’s trying to kidnap you.
What do you suppose is happening between these two kids?
Oh please, Keisuke-kun, you started it.
Well, I thought it was a good idea.
Jun... It’s the best way to protect you.
This feels, weird...
It’s my first time, but I’ll do my best.
It’s okay. Come in.
Jun...
Keisuke, we’re ready.
Okay, I’m counting on you.
Wato-chan has... Wato-chan has disappeared!
Suu-chan went back to class and then to the club room to see Wato-chan.
But then when she went back, Wato-chan was gone.
This was all that was left.
'Banquet on the roof.'
Shit! He got us!
Look, up there!
For real?
Jun!
And why Suzuko too?
Shit... You bitch!
Well then, I've captured my latest prey.
Until we meet again!
Tomorrow night, midnight, I will present a magic show. - Magician
Invitation
Shit...
Keisuke, it’s the phantom again!
This time I got a good shot!
Really?
Yep.
You’re awesome!
Develop it... We need to develop it right away!
Okay, leave it to me.
Fuck! None of these are clear!
In development...
What do you mean you 'got a good shot'?!
... Are you retarded?
Ah, this one’s no good either.
That guy, huh?
I got it!
I’ve got it. I know who the Magician is.
It’s time.
Welcome to my magic show.
Before you begin, I’d like to expose your treachery right now!
Prepare to be humiliated!
You mean to say you’ve exposed the secrets behind my magic?
Yeah.
You had an accomplice.
And it was the clever covering from your accomplice that masked your -
- mistakes until now.
After you kidnapped Himiko, you escaped to the hallway and waited for your accomplice to help you.
That’s because you’d be in trouble if people heard your feet creaking over the old hallway.
The roof was the same scenario.
You were successful because of your accomplice.
You seem amused, famous detective.
But the real fun begins now.
Remove the curtain of your lust and surrender to deep passion!
Wh-What the...?
Eat my magical ecstasy!
There’s still more!
Something’s happening to me.
Be happy! You will receive my blessing.
Yes... Yes... Yes...
Okay!
I won’t be deceived anymore, Pres!
The accomplice who helped the magician kidnap Himiko, Jun, then Suzuko!
Her name is...
The first culprit is YOU!
Magician.
Mori Aki, our club president, is the one who made all of this possible.
Right after the incident at the school assembly, you made us all leave.
So that the Magician could escape.
And the one who sent Jun’s notice to the Detective Club,
And the one who kidnapped both Jun and Suzuko was our club president.
She blamed it on you, but everything that happened after the assembly was all her doing!
Just give up, Magician.
And I’ll show you a REAL magical illusion.
You bastard... You’re not really Keisuke, are you!
See? Like David Copperfield, right?
Not so fast.
Shit!
I’m still not finished solving all the mysteries.
The other culprit is someone with an identical earring.
Kurisugawa Chris!
Kurisugawa-san, your father is a famous hypnotist, Mister Chris.
Using his hypnotic techniques is what allowed you to create those illusions.
What a silly child’s game.
Those who use it...
Get this done to them!
No...!
You’re so wet... Must’ve been from watching us all fuck earlier.
Yes... Yes... Yes...
Yes...
Scoop, scoop!
We have an unexpected twist to the serial kidnappings!
You have to see the movie to find out!
Pres... This case was training, wasn’t it?
That’s right. It was a joint effort between myself and the acting club.
There were talks of doing this right before the school festival.
And then we thought we’d add some eroticism to it to spice things up a bit.
And that’s how the current plan unfolded.
It was also a personal test to see how good your reasoning skills and action under pressure were.
What the hell?
But you were very impressive indeed.
That illusion you performed... How did you do it?
Uh? Actually... It wasn’t an illusion.
Hozumi-senpai, you were really cool!
Shizuko thinks she might have a thing for you now.
Even so, I’m surprised a dog’s whistle brought you back to your senses.
Yeah, well, it doesn’t matter how I did it.
Don’t focus on the little details.
You guys had fun, right?
Sorry.
Wait, didn’t she say 'movie' back there? Could it be...?
Special movie screening!
Super Erotic Suspense, 'Midnight Magician'.
Coming to a screen near you at once!
Stop it!
What does exist is fate.