www.SubDESU-H.net
After losing my husband,
I went to live with my daughter.
My family chastised me for being “useless”,
and my husband’s nephew has moved in with us.
But...
... this man who resembles my late husband...
He's started to violate my life and my daughter’s life.
Mother-Daughter Bowl
With Extra Tits On Top
Juicy With Breast Milk
Don’t stare at me like that.
That will make me... really feel like a woman.
Yes.
At some point, he has...
come to see both myself and my daughter Rumi as women.
How has college been recently?
Did you get a girlfriend?
You want me?
And you’re not interested in other girls?
B-But, don’t you want a younger and prettier girl?
Why so sudden...? What are you doing?
You say my tits are ideal...?
What are you saying?
No!
What are you... doing?
Oh no!
Please stop it!
Don’t...
You...
Can’t go any further...
Or I’ll really...
I’m home!
Mama?
I’m thirsty.
Huh? What the hell are you doing having tea without me?
I want some too!
Ah, it’s chocolate!
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
Hey, Mama, I got sweaty at my club practice today, so shall we take a bath together?
Okay, okay.
You’re still my baby, aren’t you?
Mama, your boobs are so pretty every time I see them.
Oh, Rumi, you're silly.
Are you sure you didn’t suffocate Papa to death with those boobs?
Oh, please, that would never have happened.
Stare...
Big boobs sure give you a larger presence.
Really?
But Rumi-chan, I think yours are plenty big.
You think so?
But...
I really think I prefer ones as big as yours.
Just kidding!
Hey, share some of your boobs with me, okay?
Now, Rumi-chan, stop kidding around.
Oh...
What’s wrong, Mama?
My clean pair of shorts... I think I forgot them.
Oh Mama, even you seem to be out of it sometimes.
Though that’s part of what makes you lovable.
Even though you’re an uncool “Mama”.
Oh, Rumi-chan, you're silly.
Don’t tease me.
Why...?
What are they doing here?
Is this stuff...?
They’re so... soiled..
So much... with this deep smell...
It smells like my husband’s semen.
It’s so strong... it’s making my mind numb.
No!
Why?
N-No!
Get out of here!
You want to see it... that bad?
Me... masturbating?
You “need” to?
That badly?
If you beg that hard, then... I can’t refuse... I guess.
After making my underwear so dirty...
You’re a naughty boy.
But I suppose you’re at that age.
Well?
Do you like... my boobs?
Being watched...
Makes me ashamed...
But... but...
Mama...
R-Rumi-chan!
Both of you! What are you doing?
You bitch! You had Papa, wasn’t he enough?
So, please...
This guy... is for me...
I wanted him.
Rumi-chan...
I’m sorry.
I’ve always liked him.
I knew you liked him too...
Rumi-chan, please forgive me.
But... I’m lonely too.
So...
Let’s make this a threesome.
Wait, Mama, what’re you...? Ah!
You don’t wanna do it with Mama?
I’m pushing you to do something so shameful...
I’m a failure as a mother, aren’t I?
No...
I love you too, Mama.
And there’s only one you, so... we can’t help it.
Be... gentle, will you?
Rumi-chan, you’re very cute.
So perky. And your nipples are so pretty.
Jeez, Mama, don’t say such embarrassing things.
And you too! Get that silly grin off your face!
So gentle...
And your hand is so big...
Not so hard...
If you massage it that hard, I’ll...
You’ll be... my first, to...
You should... thank me, okay?
Mama...
My boobs being massaged... feels so good... I didn’t know!
No!
Not there... it’s so sensitive!
Stop it!
My nipples... are erect...
They’re horny.
I’m so turned on!
I’m so sensitive right now.
My boobs are hot!
Don’t tug too hard!
Milk will come out!
What?
Ew!
I’m not even pregnant... but milk is coming out!
Rumi-chan, I feel your soft nipples... rubbing against mine...
My daughter’s nipples... are fucking me.
Awesome... your nipples are enveloping mine.
Your nipples... are so warm.
Rumi-chan, your milk is delicious.
Yours too, Mama.
It’s so thick... and so naughty.
You want to squeeze more out of us?
But we can’t...
You’re just so selfish.
But since you got your hopes up so much...
If you squeeze gently, I’ll...
Rumi-chan... you’re squeezing my boobs.
My daughter is squeezing my tits. It feels so good.
No!
Don’t watch! I’m lactating!
Me too! Don’t look at me!
Rumi-chan, your milk... so much came out.
From your... boobs, too...
So much... came out...
Rumi-chan.
My milk... is it delicious?
Yes.
Your flavor... has a very nostalgic flavor to it.
This is my first time...
How am I?
It’s very sweet.
Just like condensed milk.
It’s coming out again!
Me too.
It feels so good.
Do your best tomorrow, too.
I’ll make you some semen milk in the morning.
Are you awake?
Look at the luxurious way we’re waking you up.
Doesn’t it make you happy?
Mama, I think he wants some milk.
Well, seriously.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
He can’t wake up without breast milk first thing in the morning?
What a naughty boy.
Come on now, say “ah”!
He looks like he likes it as he’s drinking it... It makes me happy.
Yes, I feel my insides starting to throb.
Well... have your fill.
You still aren’t full, right?
Suck me.
Oh... it’s almost noon.
If you don’t get up soon, you’ll miss breakfast.
So strong!
If you squeeze that hard, I won’t be able to carry the plates.
We still haven’t eaten breakfast yet.
How can you have so much energy?
Oh dear!
So much is coming out.
Me and... my Mama...
Make great milk... don’t we?
This time, you suck me first.
I still didn’t have enough at lunch.
Mama, you look so needy.
You really are a slut, but a beautiful one.
So you need to... hold back for a while.
Rumi-chan, you big tease.
Oh, you’re just so spoiled.
Your dick is stroking my boobs.
Rumi-chan.
I envy you.
I want it too.
Your dick is burning my boobs!
It’s setting me on fire!
Hey! You haven’t cum yet!
Rumi-chan, your jealous face sure is cute.
But this dick belongs to Mama now.
Mama, you meanie!
Then I’ll make him cum faster!
If you do that, then...
I’ll... I’ll...
Oh, Mama, you really do look pleased.
Hey...
Don’t lose focus.
And give it to Rumi fast.
I can lick it while titty fucking this way.
Rumi-chan...
Your boobs are shaking so much.
Being young sure is great.
Oh, Mama, you’re being too greedy!
Well?
If I squeeze it this tight... it feels better, right?
So much thick stuff on Rumi-chan...
A boy’s scent...
Be sure to fuck my titties too.
Harder!
I’ll squeeze you... tight...
Oh, it’s going crazy!
Going crazy in my tits!
Such warm semen.
So much semen... you squirted on me.
What a waste!
Let me share.
It’s still so thick and gooey... delicious.
This time, all three of us together, okay?
After all that, he’s still so hard.
He works so hard for us.
We must thank him properly.
Oh, the dick... it’s throbbing again!
Such thick, hot semen... squirt it all over us.
That was so... so hot.
So much came out...
We’re soaked in semen.
Work hard for us lots tomorrow again.
First thing in the morning, we’ll help you make lots of semen-milk
www.SubDESU-H.net