www.SubDESU-H.net
This phone, which was designed and sent to me by my father,
has the ability to carve pleasure into the hearts and minds of my cute slaves that I hypnotized.
Yuna-chan,
Nagisa-chan,
Lady Himeno,
and Sayuri-san.
These girls and I are playing a gamble.
W
Hypnotized School Slaves
~I hated you just a while earlier~
「No, I 'm not pregnant yet」
Period
End
Once pregnancy is confirmed,
the intense pleasure that came from my "training"
Period
End
will leave their bodies unable to feel arousal from anyone except me.
Someone like you must die
I will then return their minds to the point just before they were hypnotized,
Too stinky to be physically sound
and then I will make them choose.
Satou-kun is just a friend
Preserve their self-esteem, fight against their desires
How filthy, even lower than a dog
and go back to their boring, mediocre lives.
Someone like you must die
Too stinky to be physically sound
Satou-kun is just a friend
How filthy, even lower than a dog
Or, they can throw away everything, become my sex slaves,
I can't be without your cock
Release it inside and make my insides cum
I can no longer live without you
Rape me intensely and make me pregnant
and give birth to my children.
I don't want to admit this, but...
But it just won't stop throbbing.
My body just keeps getting hotter!
I can never live without Futoshi-kun's cock.
I'll do anything, so make me your love slave!
My horny pussy will never be satisfied if it's not Futoshi-kun's cock.
I'll be sure to carry and take care of your children.
So please rape me more!
Doing this in front of my fiancé...
I can't!
If you fuck me like that, I'll no longer be myself!
Being aggressively fucked like this... Entering my butt like that...
I'm forced to have sex with this dirty pervert!
Not just my body, but now my heart is also losing to this dirty pervert's cock.
I'll swear it!
I'll give birth if you want!
So please mess me up!
Sakurazawa Yuna
Serizawa Sayuri
Mizushiro Nagisa
Tatsumiya Himeno
So not even one of them was able to leave me.
Unfortunately, Himeno suffered from miscarriage, but...
I was really fooled by Nagisa-chan.
She said she'd give birth but ended up aborting the child.
But still, her unending craving for me is quite cute.
She's a real "tsundere".
Well then, why don’t I finish my session with Kaoruko-sensei.
She seems to have taken a liking to tit-fucking due to arousal from her breasts and genitals.
I'm cumming!
It's all coming out.
Now, let's have the teacher make her final choice.
Sensei, let's kiss.
I love kisses!
W-What was that?
Why am I...?
Here it is, the technique that reverted her mental state to just before the hypnotism.
Why?
No way... Why...?
What kind of reaction will you have now, sensei?
S-Satou-kun... W-What kind of terrible thing is this?
Hypnotizing women,
r-raping them,
and doing so many dirty things...
This is unforgivable by human standards!
I don’t think that's convincing enough when we are in this position, Kaoruko-sen-se-i.
N-No...
No!
What's wrong, sensei?
You won't escape?
If that's the case, then let's continue the sex.
This is wrong. I already have my fiancé, Shinya-san.
Let's stop this.
Oh, look. Kaoruko-sensei is saying all of these things during sex, Minazuki-sensei.
Shinya-san!
This... T-This is not...!
The one that I love... is only Shinya-san.
Shut up, you slutty bitch.
Shinya-san!
That was terrible!
What's terrible?
Even though I am your fiancé, you didn't even let me kiss you under the excuse of "maintaining purity" before marriage,
yet here you are letting someone like Satou cum inside you anytime he wants.
No, I am not doing this because I like it!
But didn’t you like anal sex during our sessions?
You wore that wedding dress, gave me your virginity, and we even exchanged vows, right?
Stop this!
You’re even willing to cosplay for sex even though you are a teacher.
You’re the worst.
No!
Satou-kun told me to wear this.
My, my... So you were even hiding this kind of hobby from your fiancé?
That's just terrible, sensei.
No! This is not the real me!
Sensei, if you promise to bear my child,
I am even willing to hypnotize Minazuki-sensei, for you two to be happily wedded together.
Stop fooling around!
Who would bear your child!?
But sensei, isn't it a bit too late?
Did your period come this month?
No, that can't be...
We have been having sex every day, and I always cum inside you.
No, you're lying. I can't be pregnant.
Sensei, I'm about to cum.
No, release it outside!
I can’t be pregnant yet!
Then all the more reason to do this.
I'll make sure you get pregnant.
No! Please, release it outside.
Don’t release it inside!
No!
Climaxing in front of your fiancé while riding another man, even letting him cum inside.
You really are a slutty woman.
I'm breaking off our engagement. Be happy with your master.
Wait! Shinya-san, this isn't... Please don't leave me...
Oh, so you were completely abandoned by Minazuki-sensei.
That can’t really be helped,
since you climaxed in front of your fiancé from someone cumming inside you.
N-No... This is not it. This isn't...
What do you think?
If you just accept my deal, your slutty self would still be loved by Minazuki-sensei.
By Shinya-san?
If you bear my child, you can get married to Minazuki-sensei.
This lewd body will be too much for one to handle alone, so continue to experience pleasure as my fuck buddy as well.
I can’t just...
Not there!
You want to be married to him, right?
If Kaoroku-sensei keeps her lips sealed, no one will find out whose child it is.
I can even hypnotize everyone to make them think that Minazuki-sensei is the father.
Now, swear to me!
Not there!
It's big.
If you swear to me, you'll obtain happiness.
Happiness with Shinya-san...
I swear!
I promise to bear your child.
No, I'm cumming!
Deal completed.
Now, Kaoruko-sensei is my sex slave as well.
I'll train you in such a way that you will never be able to think of anyone but me.
Please stop this already.
Doing those things to me everyday...
I'll say this straight now.
If you do any more terrible things to me,
I'll complain to the teachers.
You're doing exactly as I told you today.
No! If you keep doing this to me, it will come out.
If you do that, it will stand up!
You still don't understand your position it seems.
If you continue to resist, aren't you the one who is gonna suffer?
Everyone will be quite surprised if I spilled your secret on the school's official site, wouldn't they?
The fabled and beautiful transfer student is but a lewd hermaphrodite
who can't even control herself and masturbates in school.
Stop it!
What's worse is that this beauty is actually engaging in sexual encounters with the most hated pervert of this school.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
No! You were the one who...
The result will be the same no matter what.
If your secret comes out, you would even be pushed around by other guys.
And if that happens, delinquents will cum inside you everyday.
You'll surely get pregnant.
No!
Oh, so you were aroused by that thought, huh?
So you're aroused by the thought of getting pregnant?
Then let's keep on having unprotected sex.
No, stop this.
I won’t defy you anymore,
so please use protection!
If I get pregnant... doing this everyday,
I can't possible live anymore.
"You'll get pregnant with anal sex".
That hypnotic suggestion seems to be working better than expected.
I don’t want this anymore!
If I were just a normal woman, I wouldn't have to suffer like this.
You don’t need to lower yourself like that. I said it before, didn't I?
Your body is so beautiful. I love it.
No, don't look! Please forgive me!
Then please come to the usual place today.
I'll turn the vibrator on if you come late.
Oh, and one more thing.
Please hold on to this until after school.
There's also a lewd photo of you inside, so please don’t lose it.
Aihara-san!
Yes?
I have something to tell you. Got a moment?
You've just transferred and you're already claiming other people's property, aren't you?
Girls swimming club
room
What do you mean?
Don’t fool around!
Of course, I am talking about that fatso!
Fatso?
That dirty geek Satou!
That is a misunderstanding!
I'm not related to Satou-kun.
It hurts!
My breast will tear off.
This must be the reason.
So you seduced him with these lewd boobs, didn't you?
And here I was wondering why I wasn't called for a whole month.
Turns out he got himself a new woman.
Are you Satou-kun's girlfriend?
Girlfriend? Are you kidding me?
Who would want that guy!?
He's my serv... my servant! Yes, he is my servant!
Then please make him stop.
I'm already tired of being his fuck buddy or sex slave.
You're his sex friend?
Do you want to be his lover!?
No!
The fact that he threw me away and he's doing it everyday with you is pissing me off.
Very well, I'll make sure that you can never use that mouth of yours again.
No.
W-What is this I'm touching?
No, please stop.
I'm sensitive there...
You're...
A tranny!?
N-No! I'm a girl.
Now, I have a good idea.
No, stop this!
Don’t take embarrassing pictures of me.
And there's even a vibrator inside your butt.
If I release these pictures in school, boys would probably rape you instantly.
After that, as you wished, the fatso will dump you.
Oh, but you have that vulgar cock of yours, so no one would probably even touch you.
N-No! That's a clitoris!
I'm a girl so I don't have a cock.
Then what was that you released on my face earlier?
That was how my clitoris releases when aroused.
Are you a fool?
That was an ejaculation no matter how you look at it.
Well, it doesn't matter. I'll be using this lubricated toy and...
this little device to record that so called "release" of yours in detail.
What are you planning to do?.
Stop, please let me be!
No, no!
Please stop. Don't move it around!
It fits perfectly inside this masturbation toy. What clitoris are you talking about?
No, it will come out again.
I'm cumming!
Oh, my. Came already? That's no good.
You are a woman, so you have to say it when you are about to cum.
Alright, another try.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I apologize... No!
I'll make it you feel better, so spit it out.
No, I can't! I don't want to cum again.
It's already time. Satou-kun will get upset.
I don't want to release!
Hiding your clit-penis, but still masturbating in school...
It seems you messed up.
If you don’t want people to learn about this...
Let me cum inside your virgin ass.
No, I'll get pregnant if you release it inside.
No!
Don't!
I'll cum, I'll cum again.
You're such a pervert, cumming in this hole countless times even though you are a woman.
Yes, I'm a pervert, so please let me be.
Oh, but if you’re a pervert, this must not be enough for you.
I wonder what I have to do to please this perverted dickgirl.
No, please stop already.
That's correct. Shouko-chan won't be satisfied with just that.
Fatso?
Entertaining, right?
What were you doing, Nagisa-chan?
W-Well you see, you weren't around so I thought that I would train this tranny in your place.
I'm impressed, Nagisa-chan.
But Shouko-chan is not a tranny. She is a real woman, right?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
My womb is going numb.
Stop!
Stop...
P-Please stop...
No...
If you cum first before I cum inside Nagisa-chan,
then I'll also cum inside you.
No, please. If anything more is released inside my ass...
I'll get pregnant!
No, I'm cumming!
It's going to release again!
You came before me, didn't you?
Then I'm also cumming inside Nagisa-chan!
No, it's really not safe today!
I don’t want to be pregnant anymore.
Don't release it inside me!
You say that, but your womb is waiting eagerly.
No!
I'll kill you if you cum inside.
Fatso, I really will kill you!
It's being released straight into my womb!
I'll get pregnant!
I don’t want to be pregnant!
Now it's your turn, Shouko-chan.
No, please don't release it inside.
I'll do anything.
No!
This ass-fucking feels really good.
Your body is the best!
No!
Since we're like this, let's have Nagisa-chan join us.
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop!
No! Both my clit-penis and butt will break!
Now, how will we bring down Shouko-chan?
More fun is yet to come.
www.SubDESU-H.net