Mutou Wakana.
A young wife divorced from her husband since 15,
with a 3-year old son.
Wakana, what are you doing?
I just thought I'd lick it for a bit.
Y-You, you can't do that!
What if your son wakes up?
Besides, we're by the roadside so somebody might see us.
It's okay, it's okay.
No one will see us.
Besides, you've been busy these past few days.
You don't pay attention to me at all.
So it's at times like these that we can be together as a couple.
Something like that.
Wakana, I'm about to cum.
Papa-san.
You can't do that yet.
Hey, Papa-san...
The road's already clear so,
don't you want do it with me already?
Naisho no Wakana-san.
Here,
put it in already Papa-san.
Yes.
Papa-san, do it more.
There,
that felt good.
Wakana, I'm about to cum.
You're cumming already Papa-san?
Jeez, you're such a...
Here, please have a drink.
Oh, thanks.
It's finally over.
You did really well Auntie.
Yes, and good work too.
By the way, I haven't seen Takashi-kun around.
Wasn't he here today?
He's locked up in his room, studying I think.
He's failed at least twice already.
Oh, is that so?
Takashi's already a grown up,
he could've at least left a greeting.
It's quite troubling.
Why don't you tell him off too Wakana?
Okay, I'm going to visit him later.
Finally, my Ta-chan's asleep.
You're going to stay for the night right?
The bath's already prepared.
Why don't you refresh yourself there?
Who's there?
Is that you Papa-san?
That's strange, I thought there was someone here.
Huh?
My panties are gone.
Could it be...?
Takashi-kun.
It's Wakana.
Can I come in?
Ta-ka-shi-kun.
Y-Yes!
What are you doing Takashi-kun?
You didn't come out to see everyone so Auntie's worried.
You know,
you need to do something different for a change.
It's not like anything would change if I went
out and attended that memorial service.
Besides, I need to study more.
So this is part of what you're studying eh.
These are my undies you know?
Maybe I should mention this to Auntie.
I'm sorry!
Wakana-oneechan.
Takashi-kun,
are you interested in girls?
If you're not honest with me,
I'll tell everyone all about this.
I am.
Okay,
then I'll leisurely tell you everything about us.
Wakana-oneechan?
Takashi-kun.
You can look closer if you want.
Wakana-oneechan!
Takashi-kun, no need to rush.
Look here.
It looks like it's wet.
Your tongue...
It's entering...
Oh no.
There, that feels good.
Show me your thing too, Takashi-kun.
It's so different from Papa-san's,
it's still young so it's stiff and lively.
Wakana-oneechan.
Wakana-oneechan!
I'm about to cum...!
I'm sorry, I'm cumming!
So young, and it came a lot,
and it's still very lively.
Hey, Takashi-kun,
do you want to insert it in me this time?
Yeah.
Yes... yes...
Wakana, where are you?
Wakana-san.
Wakana, where have you gone?
Wanna have more sex with me?
Wakana-oneechan, I'm...
Look, it's in.
Takashi-kun, no...!
Yes,
that's good!
More, do it more.
More. More!
Deeper!
That's right.
That's good,
keep it up.
I'm cumming.
Your hot thing is pouring inside!
My womb is being filled by this youthful cum!
This is a secret between us okay?
Hey, Takashi-kun.
Once more...
Please.
It's okay.
Come at me from behind.
Thrust it in.
Thrust it in more!
Deeper!
Hit it deeper!
Yes!
Yes, that's good.
That feels good!
More, more!
Yes!
Go deeper.
There.
It feels good.
That's right.
Yes. Yes!
Huh?
That's strange.
I heard Wakana's voice somewhere.
Wakana-san.
Where are you?
Wakana-san! Wakana-san! Wakana-san!