Hey, if you run that fast you're going to trip.
I'll be okay.
You worry too much, Onii-chan.
Really?
I'll be just fine.
That's why I told you before...
You've always been such a klutz.
Thank you.
O-Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, you're a pervert!
Onii-chan, you're a perverted guy.
Kasumi's also growing up, huh?
That's not...
That's not what I mean.
A dream, huh?
It's not like anyone other than me will get the door, right?
Honestly, stuff like this happens all the time.
Onii-chan, that's for me.
Sure, I know.
Onii-chan.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
If you sleep in there, you're going to catch a cold.
I'm not sleeping.
The first symptom is you getting lazy like that, and
that's been the first sign in other cases.
I'm not going to get like that.
I've also read lots of articles which sound like Kasumi's case, you know?
I get it.
I don't believe you.
I've already suffered with Kasumi.
I get it already.
Hey, Mom.
What is it?
Why do you think that Kasumi would become a NEET like this?
I don't know yet.
Didn't you read about it in books?
It's different in each person's case, there's no way I would know why.
I wonder what her reason is.
To be honest...
Hey.
Did you already get a boyfriend?
Do you want to know?
No, not really.
I was just wondering if you already had one or not.
What about you, Onii-chan?
Do you want to know?
Not really.
Oh, is that so?
There was that time, right?
Kasumi attitude's gotten a bit strange.
Eh!? You won't able to come?!
What happened? Anything urgent?
Like I said, there's a TV drama I want to watch.
But, when you promised me yesterday... you didn't...
That's why I said I forgot to tell you about that.
B-But...!
Hey... You know that I don't like persistent guys.
Ah... No-
That's right.
If you want to watch that drama, then we can't do anything.
Well, another time, okay?
It's a shame that we couldn't go.
Just when I was about to go on a date.
Am I just unlucky...?
It's all because of that TV drama.
I have to cancel that restaurant reservation.
That would be a waste.
Kasumi?
I made a reservation for myself and my work colleague,
but she said that she had something to do.
It would be a waste to just cancel the reservation, right?
That's why...
Then... let's go on a date.
She's been lurking in her room for ages.
Her hair is always messy.
She smells like sweat every day.
Not just that,
does she ever actually bathe?
Well, why we don't get something to eat together?
You see, we've never gone out together like this before.
I know that you might not want to go out with your brother,
but I think it'll be good for you to go outside for once.
R-Really?
Then after I'm finished at work tomorrow, I'll meet you at the restaurant.
Eh...
Um...
No, I was really surprised that you...
The truth is, I've never been able to get a clear look at Kasumi's face before today.
Her face is always hidden behind her long bangs.
She wears a long sleeved shirt all the time.
She really seems to have grown up.
No... No... She's my little sister, after all.
I'm sorry, Kasumi.
Maybe I should rest for now.
What was I thinking back there?
Am I really attracted to her?
Why is it getting like this...?
Looking like that at my own little sister...
Kasumi?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Stop joking around!
Hey, I said stop it!
This isn't a joke anymore!
It's getting hard.
No... this isn't...
I really...
want to do it...
with you.
Hey, Kasumi!
I can't-
It's cumming!
It's cumming a lot, I'm so happy.
Y-You're doing something like this...!
Did it feel good?
Well... yeah, it felt really good...
I shouldn't have said that!
We're siblings, you know?
Don't you know that we shouldn't do this?
It's because I like you.
I've really liked you for ages.
You're always nice to me, and you even said that I'm cute.
That's why.
Or is it as I thought,
you don't even like...
someone like me?
Kasumi, you're making that gloomy face again.
When you're being honest with me right now,
it seems I'm just a failure of a brother.
No, maybe I'm just too happy with your confession.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan,
I can't hold...
I'll put it in, okay?
It's so tight.
Kasumi, are you okay?
Onii-chan's doing this with me.
I'm so happy.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
I... I'm so sorry.
Today... It'll be just for today, I'll be your little sister again tomorrow.
Kasumi, don't say anything.
Hey.
Um... Are you really okay with this?
Never mind that,
are you really okay with this?
Hey, if you run that fast you're going to trip.
I'll be okay.
You worry too much.
Really?
I'll be just fine.
That's why I told you before...
You've always been such a klutz.
Thank you.
O-Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, you're a pervert!
Onii-chan, you're a perverted guy.
I've been touched by Onii-chan.
By Onii-chan...
It's already night.
Welcome home, Onii-chan.
I'm home, huh?
You should stay like this, Kasumi.
I just want to say it anyway.
Kasumi?
It-It's only for Onii-chan sake after all, I wouldn't do this for just anyone.
I'm just doing it with Onii-chan.
Look Kasumi, don't you think this inn is great for us?
There's an outdoor hot spring by our room.
I'll make a reservation and put in the down payment.
Just in case, you know?
Wow, look at this, Kasumi!
This is our special outdoor hot spring, you're going to be okay with this, right?
Shall we get in?
Or shall we get in after dinner-
I want to get in together with you.
I never thought that I would do something like this with you.
I never really thought about doing something like this with you before.
This time, let me make you feel good, Onii-chan.
Kasumi, that's good.
Kasumi!
Onii-chan.
Here I come.
I can't hold it!
Me neither.
Together.
Cumming!
A lot of...
Onii-chan's...
As I thought, that hot spring is really good.
Shall we go in again after dinner?
Alright, we'll go in ten more times before going home!
I want to have sex with you,
not just in the hot spring, but in bed as well.
No... It's just... that we're so close to the hot spring...
And then doing it ten more times...