The origin of heaven, the fruits of the earth and my people's livelihood...
When was it that I didn’t have to worry about those things?
The past seems nothing but a faint illusion now.
Queen Illeana, have you finished changing your clothes?
Yes, I’m almost done. Wait a moment.
SubDESU-H Presents
“BUTA HIME-SAMA”
Please, come this way.
Excuse me.
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you gonna stand there until morning?
No. I’m coming right away.
Look, Tasha, she is a sow of your new friend.
How do you do?
I’m Tasha, the minister’s servant.
All right, well done.
How disgusting, to do such a thing with her mouth.
What? Are you chickening out?
No, not at all.
We’re queens. Let’s stay close.
I heard about you from King Dhorme, Queen Illeana, and I wanted to see you soon.
Y-Yes.
King Dhorme, Tasha worked hard.
I loosened up my own pussy and applied some ointment deep inside.
Finally, you're beginning to get used to it.
King Dhorme...
My body belongs to you.
I’ll do anything if you hold me.
It feels especially good today.
B-Because...
I got it.
Does it feel better when you're
watched by your new friend?
Being watched by others makes me excited.
I'm cumming, I'm almost cumming!
I can’t... I can’t take it anymore!
Please give me the usual!
Please give it to me, deep in my pussy!
Well then, I’ll give it to you.
It feels good!
What is it?
What are you scared of?
Come over here.
Um... Well, I’m coming.
Lick it thoroughly, gently.
Don't put me in a bad mood.
Certainly, right away.
I-I have never seen such a big cock.
Move it!
Hey, suck my cock all the way to the base!
Look at me! I said, look at me!
I’m not satisfied yet.
It’s time for some fun.
What a nice view, Illeana.
You're too good for being the queen of this
out-of-the-way place for the rest of your life.
Let me see how good this is.
Illeana, tell me how the inside of your horny pussy feels when my I stick my finger in.
I can’t say how it feels...
I said, tell me!
King Dhorme’s finger is flexing in my vagina and moving like crazy.
That’s good.
Never disobey me!
Ahhh, I’m cumming, I’m cumming!
It’s big... It’s so...
Don’t give in just to something like this.
With all due respect, at this rate, my body is going to be broken.
P-Please slow down.
If this goes on, I-I...
I’ve never experienced anything like this before!
Hey, there's no time to rest. Move!
Good!
No! I'm going to break!
I can’t take this anymore!
Shut up! Don’t disobey me!
My order is absolute!
Do everything I say!
Yes.
I won’t disobey you.
I’m almost going crazy!
My pussy is starting to go numb!
All right then, cum, cum now.
I’m gonna cum!
This feeling, this desire... It's completely changed me!
Ahh, no, my nipples...
I can cum just from nipple stimulation!
Queen Illeana, your pussy is already all wet.
That’s not true. I’m not...
No, no!
I am sorry...
This is as vulgar as can be.
King Dhorme, please forgive me.
I’m sorry. Please forgive me.
Don’t play dumb with me!
Until I say okay, you gotta wait.
I'm sorry...
You are a hell of a pervert.
I-I am not...
Geez, you don’t understand my language?
No, I don’t mean it.
Kiss my ass!
Please.
Let me cum, please let me cum!
No way.
Please, please, please!
Not yet. Are you listening to me?
You pervert!
I-I can’t take this.
But why am I so sensitive...?
That’s because of my special aroma oil.
I’m feeling horny, King Dhorme.
You’re all set.
Now, serve me, dirty bitch!
I’ll serve you as hard as possible!
My breasts are just like genitalia!
My body is so happy, King Dhorme.
Illeana, this is a great view.
Thank you very much.
It’s my pleasure.
Queen Illeana, does it feel so good?
Yes, my nipples have become leering genitalia.
Oh no, Queen Illeana, how shameful!
Tasha’s fingers...
Tasha, rub my pussy harder!
Queen Illeana!
Deeper, deeper!
Queen Illeana, does it feel good?
Your fingers...
All female humans have no principles.
I’m gonna cum!
I guess I have no choice. Open your mouth.
I’ll pour my sperm on your faces.
Yes, please.
Good.
Swallow down.
You’re just like dogs eating food.
As a pet owner, I’ll train ill-behaved pets strictly.
King Dhorme!
It feels good, Tasha.
Thank you very much, King Dhorme.
Tasha, I feel jealous of you.
King Dhorme’s penis is churning my stomach.
You feel good, don’t you?
King Dhorme, I’m cumming!
I’m gonna cum!
Tasha, you’re beautiful.
It’s your turn next.
Yes, please.
My pussy is crying because it can’t wait any longer.
Please use it!
Don’t be so greedy. I’ll put it into your pussy now.
Wow... My pussy, my pussy...
King Dhorme, please fuck me harder and deeper.
My pussy is twitching.
I can’t...
Good, well done.
I’ll give you my sperm.
It’s deep.
What’s the matter?
You wanted it, right?
Hey, don’t give out soon.
Good... More... Deeper, harder...
Please.
I-I can no longer live without your penis.
I-I...
You finally got it?
Please give me your sperm!
Please give me King Dhorme’s strong sperm!
Since then, my new husband invaded neighboring
countries with unparalleled force in a very short time,
conquering region after region.
My home country, Histoire, was forced to enter into a one-sided treaty as a vassal state.
And I...
That’s how it is.
From now on, I’ll deploy my troops at frontline bases.
The advance guard will be stationed here.
Yes, sir, your wish is my command.
I-I’m about to cum.
Men, I’m cumming disgracefully in front of you.
Tasha, she's interrupting the war council.
Take care of her for me.
Yes, King Dhorme.
Now, Queen Illeana, let’s continue over there.
Don’t show such shameful behavior in front of the soldiers.
What’s the matter with me?
I’ll excuse myself.
Are you having a good time?
I’m going to cum soon!
I’m gonna cum like a wild crazy slut!
Please, look at me!
I’m cumming! I’m cumming!
Tasha, I can’t take it anymore!
It can’t be... Corneo...
Don’t be such a baby.
B-But...
Now you're all grown up.
Stop it already!
But...
Oh well.
As a reward, I’ll let you use my anus.
I’m gonna put it in, Tasha.
No! Don’t rush.
T-Tasha, it feels so good.
Harder, hollow it out inside.
It's warm and pulsing inside you.
Yes, good, Corneo.
Good! It feels good!
You’ve gotten very good at it, just like I taught you.
Tasha, Tasha, cumming, I’m cumming!
It’s okay to cum inside me.
I-It’s coming out!
Tasha, I did as you said.
Will you love me more?
All right.
Tasha, I wanna put it in your pussy.
Well, I can’t do it so let me ask her.
Come here.
It’s very beautiful.
It’s twitching.
Thank you.
This is how I do it, right?
Y-You’re good at using your tongue.
Please lick it deeper.
I can’t take it anymore.
Don’t rush.
This is where you put your cock in.
Can you see it?
Put your big hard cock in here.
Look at my pussy carefully and push your cock deeply into my pussy.
Can you do it?
Slowly, yes, right there.
Slowly, slowly.
His cock is so big!
Slower. Take it easy.
I can’t do it slowly.
My pussy is being raped!
Oh yeah!
So good!
Don’t thrust your cock up that much.
Harder...
The more I hold on to you, the more I get swallowed by your pussy.
Great!
Great...
Let’s cum together.
I’m cumming, too.
Ejaculate all the way inside my pussy.
I’m gonna cum!
Give it to me, give me your sperm!
Make me pregnant!
I’m cumming, I’m cumming!
I want more and more!
I want more sperm!
Good! You’re a good boy.
Thrust your penis deeper and deeper in me until my pussy is broken.
I’ll thrust my cock until I run out of my sperm!
I'm cumming!
You’re a good boy.
Is it still coming out?
You pussy is so tight.
Corneo, give me more!
It’s amazing!
Come inside me!
Give me your sperm!
Give me Corneo’s sperm!
Your penis is hitting my uterus.
My uterus is gonna collapse.
I’m cumming again!
I’m addicted to orgasms.
I'm breaking...
My body can’t take much more.
This was how I spent the rest of my life as a wife of the beast king.
I started a new life as a beast.
Well, I’m home.
King Dhorme, you achieved a wonderful victory in this war.
I knew you could do it.