Come here, come here!!!
The items in the wagon are all 1 yen!
So come here!
Excuse me.
I..
Want that..
No matter what.
My name is Hinata Aya.
I’m a girl working at Cosplay Café at Akihabara.
Cosplay Expose Research
Kosuroken
1st day
Translated by SubDesu-H
I always walk to work because I don’t have money
From the 5000 yen/month room I’m renting to Akihabara,
I round trip it like I’m hiking
Do you know, I have some debt.
I'm having trouble repaying it.
I’m doing all kinds of work.
Own made trading card game
Found it!
We can use this.
Collecting garbage resources
Own made trading card game
I got it.
Acting Mahjong Player
Collecting garbage resources
Own made trading card game
Acting Mahjong Player
Here.. if you push this here.. then..
Look, it won’t lose right?
Bra demo selling
Own made trading card game
Acting Mahjong Player
Collecting garbage resources
Bra demo selling
Doing this and that, from 50 million, I already repay 40 million.
I’ve done my best.
I’m not good these days.
My body is fine and strong but..
What’s this..?
Am I getting tired with this?
My work, it was stimulating when I worked at the café..
Stimulating huh..
I see the stimulation!
I lack of stimulation!
I’ve got an e-mail.
Is it from the manager?
You’ve got mail, do you want to open it?
Yes.
ZNo.
File (F) | Edit (E) | View (V) | Tool (T) | Message (M) | Help (X)
Order
Come to Kotsumie Cosplay assembly hall wearing the
uniform of the Coslay Cafe. I’ll give you any amount of
money you want.
Attention
You must be obedient of men’s requests.
Order.
Come to Comitse Cosplay venue wearing the uniform of the Coslay Cafe.
I’ll give you any amount of money you want.
Attention.
You must be obedient of men’s requests.
What? What’s this?
Is this a prank?
But he knew that I work at a Cosplay Café.
I think this is a disgusting prank.
Yes I think.
I know the Komitse.
That is the thing that the nerds are selling, and doing Cosplay of the comics.
The nerds take pictures for the people Cosplaying.
The people will look at me with their dirty eyes and take pictures of me.
Am I going to have my picture taken?
I’m feeling weird.
My body.. my heart is pumping..
I think I need the stimulation but..
What will happen if I go there?
Do I really want to go?
I’m thinking that it's disgusting being pranked.
But my body is hot and expecting something.
Am I going?
It's better to come here than think of it.
It's a Doujin market and comic Matsuei a.k.a Comitse.
It looks like it's an event that can't lose to Comike.
I’m not mistaken coming here right?
I think I’m not mistaken.
I don’t have to be afraid.
The stimulation,
I came here to obtain the changes!
My boobs.. is this nerd’s sweat?
It's disgusting.
I want to go home.
I shouldn’t have believed that mail.
I’ll go home.
I’ll go home!
Huh? What? What happened?
Uhm, can we take a picture of you?
Can you take a pose?
I’m begging you.
Uhm it's..
Is he there in this photo taking?
Can we?
Huh? Uhm…
I got a paying service in the shop.
It's embarrassing but I need to obey right?
Nerds have high ideals so I think I’m cute for them.
I just need to bear for a while right?
Oh.. uhm.. sure.
This one?
They are watching me.
It's embarrassing.
I’m not wearing a bra so it’s showing out.
You’re a bit stiff.
Smile.
I need to smile right?
You’re cute!
I can’t smile wearing this embarrassing attire while watched with this bunch of people around me.
They are taking pictures of my boobs all the time.
They are all perverts.
What should I do?
Hey, squeeze your boobs more.
Yes?
Good good.
Open your legs a bit.
The legs?
Here.
What a lot of cameras.
They are only watching me.
I think I’m blushing right now.
It's embarrassing but.
I think I like it.
Wow. I didn’t think that this cute girl was born.
Yes she is.
Hey, what’s your name?
My name? are they asking my real name?
Oh uhm…
It's..A.. A.. Aya.
I see, you’re Aya-tan, your name is cute too.
Nooo it's already a real name.
I was careless, I must used the name like Yuki or Saki.
Oohh, your embarrassed look is also cute.
It's an outstanding talent! 2x
What if the other people saw me with this attire?
The strangers will look at me, they will look at me.
I’m weird.
I don’t like it but my body is hot.
Ok then, Aya-tan.
I have a request.
Can you try showing your boobs?
My boobs?
Ok.
Hey wait, I can’t!
That's absurd.
It said you must obey in the mail but,
I can’t agree with that.
I’ll help you.
Which one you are helping?
Does he mean he’ll do it with force?
Nooo.
It's beautiful.
Damn, he got it.
You perverts.
They saw it.
The tip, the cute tip.
They saw my boobs and it's been taken.
Are they going to use the picture in weird way??
Weird thing..
Men will do something weird with my boobs..
My  body,.. my body is hot..
She’s really reacting.
Aya-tan.
You’re honest, you’re really honest.
Ok then, show this part too.
I can’t bear it.
It's erotic!
Nooo.
Stop it!
Heyaaa, I’ll take it!!
No you shouldn’t!
It's been taken!
My dirty place is being taken.
Well then, which part you want to be taken?
Which part?
No!
This part?
I see the core part.
The dirty dick is touching...
My panty is all wet already.
The wet pussy.
The chubby thighs.
I can’t bear this!
Nooo, my clit is getting bigger.
It's not being like this before.
Stop don’t push me.
The clit is showing and..
That part will seen like I’m peed my self.
My nipples are getting harder.
Am I getting horny?
My body is hot.
It's all wet and they are taking it and.. it's dirty.
Ohh what a beautiful nipples.
I saw it, it's beautiful.
They haven’t seen it all right.
I think this is alright.
Your boobs are showing.
Hey!!!
Don’t act violent.
I’ll hide it.
Stop,, hey stop.
It's regretful, that I’m being used by this disgusting guy.
He will notice that my nipples are getting erect.
My panty will rub and stuck in it if I move.
Don’t touch it.
It hurts if you touch it roughly.
It's erotic Aya-tan.
My memory is isn’t enough.
This scoop is my pride, I’m honored with it.
This crowd, if you come near..
It's all wet and erecting.
And they are looking at it.
This is my favorite.
This is my favorite white panty.
But it will leave a stain!
It's embarrassing.
Don’t take a picture of my panty.
Am I showing that dirty face?
Because it's hot and too good.
Don’t move.
I’m moaning.
They know it, they already noticed it.
What should I do? I’m already a pervert.
The dirty juice is flowing out.
It's flowing out from my panty.
I’m cumming.
My clitoris is… in this embarrassing place..
I’m cumming, I’m cumming!
I thought what might happen at first but I’ve taken a great picture.
Really, I didn’t think that Aya-tan is that erotic.
You’re really at your limit.
This photo session, it’s my first time!
Really, yes it is.
It was horrible a while ago but I think this is my first time for feeling this good.
They are looking at my ass.
They are looking at Aya’s ass.
They are patiently taking the picture while looking at the embarrassing part.
Aya-tan, raise your ass more.
I can see that part clearly.
Ok.
Is it like this?
I can raise it up no more.
No, I can’t hold it anymore.
Me too.
What? What are they doing?
It's already a prostitution.
They are starting it.
Wow its red-black and..
There are many sizes.
If they show it, my pussy will going to wet.
They are not watching it right? Its embarrassing.
It's wet and it's so good.
It's wet.
The juice is flowing out.
It's wet.. they are looking at it.
And it's flowing out!!!
If I rub the pussy with my finger I .. ahh.
I feel it!!!
Aya-tan also feel it
Erotic Godess!! we’re synchronizing with her I can’t bear it!!!
I will release my semen into Aya-tan’s white skin!
They are masturbating while looking at me.
Look at it.
Look at my erotic body! And release all you’ve got!
This is crazy but I can’t oppose.
There is no use.
You guys are so erect… you got horny while looking at me right?
Ok, don’t hold it and let's cum with me.
Aya-chan.
Sorry I’m going first.
No.. this is male’s ..
What’s this? It's hot.
It's so hot.
The dirty milk is..
It so smelly.
Hey, I want to see Aya-tan’s ass hole.
I want to watch too.
eh? my ass hole?
You bunch of perverted nerds..
I’ll do it because i have no choice.
I’m not even doing this when I’m alone.
I’m doing this while people are looking at me.
I haven’t done this pose in the café.
And I even masturbating.
I’m masturbating and it's so good.
It's so embarrassing.
They are looking at my ass hole.
I can’t stop masturbating.
My clitoris can’t hold it any longer.
They are masturbating to release it all to me.
Here..
Please release all your hot milk in here.
Please release all your milk in my pussy.
The hot and smelly one..
You perverts.