Hey, Nii-san, what about that one?
Not sure. It might not suit you, Saki.
Are you sure?
Well, don’t fret.
Let’s go check out the others first.
That’s a good idea.
We’ll do that.
Nii-san, you’re so silly…
Today, Nii-san and I are having our long-awaited date.
Lately, Nii-san has been very moody with studying and whatnot,
but he’s finally accompanying me outside.
And because of that…
Is something wrong?
Um, well… my friend suddenly asked me to do some shopping for her.
I’m sorry, but can you wait here for me?
That’s fine. I’ll stay here so go do your thing.
Thanks!
I really appreciate it.
I’ll try to come back as quickly as possible.
It couldn't be... not again...
SubDESU-H Presents
The girl raped by the
Sinister
NERD
Semen Spurting
He’s jealous of my Nii-san so he wants to hear me make naughty noises as payment?
He must have rigged some way to listen in on me.
I’d better do as he says…
Stalkers are not people you wanna make mad.
The sounds of my pussy are squishing all around.
I think I WANT people to catch me.
S-Someone caught me!
Here I am, exposing my pussy in a restaurant in broad daylight.
He’s caught me masturbating!
So embarrassing...
It’s squishing around...
My pussy is so embarrassed...
But I... I still... can’t stop myself...
Oh no!
If he watches me do it, it’s so embarrassing.
I've never been so embarrassed.
I’m such a slut.
The naughtier the stuff I do, the more it turns me on.
I’m a slutty bitch.
Saki, you’re such a fucking whore.
Watch me.
I’m getting my juice on my asshole like a dog.
Oh, I’m so embarrassed.
Masturbating with my pussy is so shameful.
It’s so embarrassing to have my pussy dripping wet, but... the embarrassment turns me on.
Oh, watch me! Watch me more!
They’re watching!
They’re all watching me be so nasty.
So embarrassing.
There’s no turning back.
S-Sorry...
But I can’t... can’t stop.
My slutty pussy just can’t stop it.
Oh no, don’t take pictures…
It’ll turn me on even more!
Oh, masturbate!
Slutty masturbation!
Feels so good.
My pussy...
It’s sopping wet.
I’m horrible!
I’m such a horrible, slutty whore with a wet pussy...!
My pussy...
I can’t stop the slut-juice!
I’m fucking myself...
All the way deep in my vag...
Deep into my uterus!
My pussy is throbbing so much it’s falling out!
I’m the only one who can protect Saki.
I’m the only one!
Mizuhara Shuji!
Texts from my stalker continued after that.
And scenario that started out as a “date” were repeated over and over.
But in time, I came to look forward to these encounters.
Until I was drowning... in a world of pleasure.
I’m so sorry, Nii-san.
My friend called me over to help her again.
But I promise I’ll make some delicious dinner even you would be proud of.
I know about it.
Huh? What do you know?
That you’re being blackmailed by a psycho... and that he’s raping you.
I knew it all along, but I couldn’t save you!
But... why did you...
He told me.
And he showed me video of you guys doing…
I was scared to rat him out because I didn't know what he might do with the footage!
So I couldn't do anything!
But I want to!
Saki!
We’re lovers, aren't we?
Let’s go back to the way we were before, Saki.
Really? Are you really okay with me the way I am?
You’re you, Saki.
My beloved Saki. You haven’t changed a bit.
I finally was bonded with my beloved Nii-san.
And while my heart enjoyed it... my body was completely dissatisfied.
Good work, Saki.
Yesterday was really hot. I was really turned on.
I want us to meet face to face when we make love on our next date.
“Meet face to face”?
I’ll be waiting.
I’ll be so happy if you come.
If you don’t wanna come and if you stay home…
Then it’s all over.
And if that happens, I’ll throw away all our memorabilia.
Because waiting for you will only make it harder to get over you.
If you don’t wanna come and if you stay home
Then it’s all over.
And if that happens, I’ll throw away all our memorabilia.
What does he mean by this?
What does he mean by “it’s all over”?
That he won’t do anything to me?
That if I don’t go to him, he’ll abandon me?
But he made me feel so good… why would he leave?
Ohh, she came, she came!
We were growing impatient, Saki-chan.
How do you know my name?
We ALL know your name.
We’re your biggest fans.
W-Who are you?
Woah shit! What a hot body!
Hey, let’s strip her down!
Awesome tits!
I can’t believe it!
Her nips look pretty, too!
Don’t look!
But don’t you like being watched?
We've got a video of you masturbating in public, you know?
And you LOVED it.
Video?
I was excited to be watched?
Very nice, Saki!
I’m so pleased you came here.
What’s going on here?
I've  had lots of fun with you so far.
I’m so happy that I raised you into such a perfect little slut.
But I’m putting an end to it today.
An end to it?
But I came!
I won’t contact you anymore.
So have fun with those guys instead.
Well then… have fun.
What’s happening?
Then why... why did he...
I betrayed Nii-san and chose him...
And because I betrayed Nii-san... is that why he also abandoned me?
I really was abandoned…
Awww, don’t be so down.
We’ll take good care of you from now on, Saki-chan.
That’s right.
Really? You’ll really take care of me?
Of course we will!
We’ll fuck you so good you’ll wanna die.
Then... Then please do me!
I’ll do my best to please you all!
So please fuck me up bad!
Fuck me hard!
I’m begging you!
Fuck me so much!
I’m no good.
I’m finished!
Then, Saki-chan, drink this.
What is it?
It tastes weird...
We got some interesting drugs.
Interesting drugs?
What’s this?
My body... it’s falling apart!
Awesome!
She drank more doses than normal.
Really?
Isn't her brain gonna fall out?
My pussy is throbbing... my clit is screaming!
It’s overflowing!
Come on, look at it.
My pussy’s bigger and it’s never felt this intense before. What’s going on?
It’s the drugs.
It's amazing, right?
And it doesn't only just get bigger...
Oh no!! Can’t stand it!
We’ve given you way more than the normal dosage.
What... My pussy! My butthole! Suck them! Finger them! Fuck me!
Looks like the drugs are flowing through her whole body.
Sorry, but we’re too busy to fuck you now.
Finger me!
My pussy!
Hurry!
My pussy must be touched or I’ll die!
Is just touching okay?
Or would you prefer this?
Ahhhh, a cock!
Put it in my pussy!
Bury your thick cock in my pussy now!
Hurry!
Saki is a slutty fucking pig!
If you don’t thrust your cock into her, she’ll lose her mind
I’m a fucking whore who needs cock in me all the time!
This bitch really is a whore.
Then I’ll plow you hard. Be sure to scream for me.
Yaaaay! Fuck me to the moon!
Make my pussy even naughtier!
Cock, come in!
Come in!!!
She came just from insertion.
Don’t get too caught up in the ecstasy from cumming.
If you do, we’ll take out the cock.
N-No, don’t…
Keep the cock in me…
You don't have to tell me twice.
Your thick cock feels so good!
Your thick godly cock is making my pussy sing!
I’m cumming!
I'm cumming again.
Your awesome cock is making me cum again!
Cumming is good and all, but how many times does that make?
Th-Three times!
My pussy’s cummed three times!
Ohhhh, I’m cumming!
Hey! Don’t drop out now while you’re cumming!
I’m not even finished... With that my cock I’ll cum right away
I’m cumming again!
Are we lonely up here?
My nip-nips!
Oh yes, that hurts and feels great!
Oh, yes!
Squeeze them so much!
Squeeze them off!
My naughty nips….get themmmm!
My uterus!
It’s in my uterus!
Oh, my clit!
Not there...
I’m cumming again.
Oh, my pussyyyy!
I’m such a slut.
Ohhhh, I can’t... can’t...
I’m cumming!
Not my clit!
It’s too sensitive!
Oh, I can’t take it!
I’m cumming constantly now!
How... How many time now?
I’ve lost count!
Oh no!!!
My slutty pussy is ripping apart.
My clit... I’m losing it...
All inside my ass!
Yes! Both! I can do it!
Both cocks are ripping me apart!
My asshole is loving this!
My pussy and asshole are rubbing against each other!
I’m cumming again!
I’ve cum too much...
My pussy~!
It’s all inside of me.
I’m filled full of cum!
I’m cumming!!
Come on, come on, don’t crap out on us now.
You did well, Saki.
Good girl.
What now?
Now you will serve ALL of these men.
You must try harder.
But if I fuck any more, I’ll die!
Didn’t you want to be fucked to death?
Just be honest with yourself, Saki.
You must beg all these men,
“Please fuck me to death.”
Please… Please fuck Saki…
Fuck Saki plenty.
Any hole is fine.
Just fill ‘em all full... with your cocks.