My name is Haskata Ren.
The public... no, people, seek me out for help and I can't turn them down.
To men, I'm a good woman.
As a model and a talent,
there are occasionally things on Internet blogs about my love affairs that could make one sweat,
but that's all past stories.
My current work is as a district welfare officer.
A district welfare officer takes responsibility for the social welfare of her people,
and takes the side of the community when issues blaze up.
That is my manifesto.
I hold great pride and passion and meaning in my profession.
W
District Welfare Officer Woman
~Haskata
Is number two not good enough? ~
Who is it?
It’s open, come in, whatever.
Excuse me.
Abe Naoto-san, right?
What do you want?
I'm the District Welfare Officer, Haskata.
What does a District Welfare Officer want with me?
I've come to classify your heart.
A door-to-door missionary?
Not likely.
Abe-san, for two weeks you've been absent without permission from your shop, haven't you?
Just take a look.
I have no interest in real-life women.
I’m a strict masturbator of twenty years. Call me a ‘Masturbatist’ if you will!.
Even so, nothing I see now gives me a hard-on.
I’m in no condition to work!
It's okay. I've come to save you.
Then how about this?
It's big...
A shame to waste it on masturbation.
By all means leave it to me.
Like I said, real-life women are useless-
A-Are you by any chance that talent-
Haskata. My name is Haskata Ren.
Being a talent was my past job.
Now I'm simply a District Welfare Officer.
I'm not a spy or anything.
Wow!! What a thing!
Where is it? Where is it?
Wait, wait... Where is it?
Here it is!
I can't count how many times I've masturbated to this gravure!
Oh, that issue! Why then, look what I have inside here...
I'm going to classify your soul now.
Classify... me?
Oh, no, it's a little... too small.
It's the same!
Oh, don't look so much!
Ren-chan has gone 3D!
I can feel it, it's coming up!
Is this a dream or an illusion?
No, no, Naoto here is coming!
I came...
With my special techniques, I will take you to an even more beautiful world. Come-with-me.
Ren-chan!
It feels good...
With something this big in my grasp, I can't hold back any longer!
Oh, that's good! So big!
Oh yes!
It's so big!
It's too big, it's going to go into my uterus!
More, more!
Deeper!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
How was it, the appeal of a real-life woman? It's the best, of course?
Um, well, that is...
State it clearly.
Or I’ll confiscate that.
Well, for me, after all, this is...
Is it okay if you're number two?
Number two isn't good enough!
Who're you?
I've come to classify your heart.
Classify? Me?
It's okay. Leave it to me.
Leave it to you?
What does a District Welfare Officer know about me?
Your extreme premature ejaculation issue.
You can't hide anything from me.
We investigated everything about you.
W-What are you...
You're through-and-through a workaholic, and an alcoholic.
Making it a point to not take time during sex, leaving it to the women,
going from one to the other, predicting things coolly...
But it's all just premature ejaculation.
Your divorced wife, all the women you've had affairs with,
have all made fun of you violently for it.
I can't hold it back...
Not yet!
You're in my custody!
Damn! I was made fun of by everyone for my premature ejaculation!
This body that can't even make a woman happy!
My super levee penis!
Don't panic.
We have no need for your super levee penis.
Sex isn't just insertion.
I'm going to disassemble you and then give you your real self back.
Th-This is...
Yes, those eyes...
Like a religious missionary, you're going to be reborn.
Now, which will be first?
Good choice.
Come!
A-Amazing!
It’s whirling... whirling!
Time to cum!
No, we're still going!
It's hitting me!
Ah! This softness!
The human vibe is coming, too!
W-What?
Oh, yes!
S-So intense!
Delicious!
Good! Good, so intense!
Yes, that’s the stuff!
Come! It's good!
This time, I'm cumming!
I... came.
That's as far as you can go?
As for you, the thing you should aim for is membership in the premature ejaculation society.
Th-That can't be!
Isn't it enough to be number two?
Of course it's no good to be number two!
People who are bad at calculating and arranging should just go home, you asshole!
It’s whirling. My pussy is whirling.
I got accustomed to the adjustment a long time ago,
so what would you want with an old geezer like me?
Oh my, an old geezer?
And what about you is an old geezer? Your power doesn't swell up?
Whichever way, it seems the aphrodisiac worked.
Aphrodisiac?
I hear it's ten times more powerful than Viagra. This aphrodisiac.
I took the liberty of putting it in your tea earlier.
Whatever for?
We're going to Shangri-La together.
You're a clever old hag.
I'm sending that line back at you several times over!
That hurts!
I love domineering snobby women like you.
Today I'm going to teach you my kind of love.
Like that, just like that.
You're starting to like this.
Here we go!
What a nice view!
I haven't even touched you and yet you're glistening.
No, don't say that!
I wonder if you can stand my secret techniques?
Yes!
Amazing...
I'm going to cum!
You want this, you bitch dog?
Y-Yes.
If you want it, put it in yourself.
You're being mean.
Good, that's so good!
Don't stop!
OUCH!
Ouch!
STOP!
It hurts, it hurts!
Yes, yes!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
My name is Haskata Ren.
My job is a District Welfare Officer.
Perhaps the next call I make will be to your residence.
I should check and see if I can buy panties at the convenience store and change them...