Damn Yurine... It's all her fault!
Because of her, I found out that Ayaka-chan doesn't like me one bit!
I was happy with just being with her in my mind, but...
But-! Because of her, I-!
I... I really do love Ayaka-chan...
But she wouldn't notice my feelings!
It's Ayaka-chan's fault.
I should have done this a lot sooner.
It should have been like this all along!
More... More!
I want to rape more people! More and more!
I want to taste different kinds of women!
The excitement, the pleasure, the satisfaction!
I want to feel more of it!
That's it, that's it!
I'll do it, I'll do it again!
SubDESU-H Presents
Ouch...
I tripped again...
W-What are you doing-?!
Let me do you!
Do what?
Oh, that mask! You're from the Drama Club, aren't you?
U-Uh, my name is Sakurai Usagi.
I'm not that good at acting,
so I've been wondering if I should ask a member for some tips...
Then how about I train you?
Really?
I've always loved rhythmic gymnastics,
with its cute leotards and how you hop freely about.
But I've been falling behind,
so I'm here every day after school training!
Then try lifting your arms horizontally.
Sure. May I ask your name?
TL note: Usagi means a rabbit/hare and Kame means Turtle.
Since you're Usagi-chan, I'll be Kame.
Kame-san, is it?
Isn't that interesting!
Never mind that, could you lift your leg next?
S-Sure!
I-I think that my body is on the flexible side.
The more soft and flexible you are, the better your acting will be!
Isn't that right?
I guess so!
Ouch! Sorry, I tripped.
Are you okay?
This is a good time to do stretches.
Yes!
Okay, raise your legs.
I'll do my best!
Ka-Kame-san! I can't stretch them anymore!
The longer you do it, the more effective the stretching is.
So that's why we're going to hold you with this.
Eh?
T-This is difficult!
Training is a difficult thing!
T-The rope-! Uh, it's rubbing against my groin!
It can't be helped. It's training.
Usagi-chan, aren't you getting hot in your leotard?
Eh?
That should be better, Usagi-chan.
W-Why are you doing this?
This is my only leotard...
This is something that's required!
U-Um, how long do I have to be like this?
Let's see...
D-Don't! It's painful!
Where is it painful?
U-Uh, t-the rope, its digging into my groin...
I see, but isn't that because the leotard is sticking to you?
T-That's not true!
There you go!
That's it! This stretch will make you more flexible!
Ka-Kame-san-!
You should be happier, Usagi-chan!
Your body is much more flexible now!
I'll massage you to loosen you up.
Ka-Ka-Kame-san!
What is it, Usagi-chan?
Y-You'll get dirty if you touch me there!
N-No! Ka-Kame-san-!
See? Doesn't it feel good, Usagi-chan?
B-But-! This is training, so you can't say such things-!
Hey, it feels good, doesn't it? Aren't you feeling aroused?
This is-!
Doesn't it feel good?
Hey, take a good look.
My thumb is slipping right into your butt!
No!
I'm also rubbing and playing with your most embarrassing area!
D-Don't say such perverted things!
You're feeling good from me playing with your butt, aren't you?
B-But-! This is training!
Be honest! Can't you obey your coach?
O-Okay-!
I-It feels good!
It feels kinda itchy. I've never felt this sensation before!
Then say so from the start!
But, but-!
Y-You can stop with the massage now!
Huh? Do you still think this is a massage?
B-But my body is getting so much looser!
Can we finish up for today?
No way!
Do you know what this is?
Ka-Kame-san, isn't that...?
Yeah, that's right! It's a Kame-san!
Or Penis-san to be more precise.
Eh?
Usagi-chan, we're going to have sex now.
Sex?
Well, technically it's called rape.
N-No way! You're joking, right Kame-san?
I'm not!
No way, no way! It's entering me-!
No way!
Why don't you see for yourself?
It's reaching your deepest spots already!
No! It hurts, it hurts-!
It's really entering me!
S-Stop it! Don't thrust inside me! It hurts-!
Kame-san-! It hurts!
No way! I-I'm bleeding! No!
Stop it! Please stop it!
It hurts, it hurts!
No way! It feels too good for me!
No way-!
Just think of it as training!
Training to become a woman!
I-I don't want such training yet!
You're so lewd, Usagi-chan!
Lifting your legs up and exposing your pussy like that!
Isn't it good that you're a rhythm gymnast?
No!!
Oh! Don't struggle so much!
Can you feel it? It's going in so deeply!
It's painful! It's painful-! I'll be torn apart!
I'll make it more painful!
I-It's tightening around me!
Can you tell?
Your small breasts are being squeezed into an irregular shape!
No, no! Please stop!
You're small, but it fits so well! It's a perfect hole!
I'm gonna cum soon!
I'm cumming!
Something is filling me-! I-Isn't this-!?
Yeah, it's my love juice. It's called semen!
N-No way...
That felt too good, Usagi-chan.
Can you see? My fluid is gushing out of you!
Huh? No response?
I guess I'll play with you until you wake up.
That's horrible!
Isn't that Sakurai-san from first year?
Sorry to make you wait. Let's go, Mashiro-chan.
Thank you, Rumi-san.
How are you feeling today?
Take care of her, please.
Ouch! Ow ow ow!
E-Eh?! What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yes, sorry about this...
No-! W-What-?! N-No!
N-No way!
P-Please stop!
No-!
It feels good!
I-I don't want this!
I'm on my period!
I don't mind that. Rather, isn't it better this way?
N-No! No!
I-I don't want this-!
Despite your innocent looks,
you must be a dirty woman to shake your hips like that!
N-No, I'm not!
No-!
No!!
What's wrong, Misuhara-kun?
No!
S-Stop it, Misuhara-kun! Do you know what you're doing?!
Of course I do! I'm fondling the class rep's breasts!
No-! Why?
It's time to reveal your big breasts!
No!!
No, Misuhara-kun! Stop it-!
This is amazing! Slinky smooth skin and bounding flesh!
What do you eat to get like this?
I don't know, I don't know! I really wouldn't know such a thing, so-!
No!
Your nipples are standing up from my touch!
No-! They're not! Someone help me!
No! I-I want to die!
Oh really? Then I'll kill you! See?
If you fall from here, you'll die in an instant!
No!!
No, no!
Then do you want to fall with me?
Stop it!
They're so soft! I'll never get sick of this!
No! Lift me back up! This is scary!
Hey hey, you're the one who said she wanted to die!
No! Stop it, no! I don't want to die!
Then do want to die or be raped?
I don't want either!
No! I'll fall, I'll fall-!
Hey, if I lift up your legs even a bit, you'll fall right down!
Do want to die or be raped?
N-No! Don't kill me!
Which is it?!
Rape, rape, rape me!
Then it's settled.
Then I'll do as you wish!
It hurts-!
It's in!
No way... No, no!
Hey, you're the one who wanted it!
It hurts, it hurts-!
It's amazing. It's amazing, class rep!
Stop it, it hurts!
Your insides are so tight, and they're squeezing me!
It's like your body was made to please men!
No!
Oh, if you struggle too much, you'll fall!
Every time you scream, your pussy tightens!
I don't know, I wouldn't know such a thing-! Forgive me, I'm going to fall!
It's fine! As long as I'm holding you, you won't fall.
Then don't thrust so much!
Aren't you feeling aroused, class rep?
I'll fall! It hurts!
How's this?
No, I-I'll fall! No!!
Isn't this like a seesaw?
Stop-! I'll fall-! I don't wanna die! Forgive me!
That's it! Your scared and painful expression sends a shiver up my spine!
It hurts-!
Your pussies so small and tight that I might cum already!
No, no!
Even if you refuse, I'm going to fill you up!
No! Not today! It's the most dangerous day!
Please don't, please don't!
Then would you rather fall and die, or have me cum inside?
I don't want either!
Which is it?!
No, no! I don't want any of it! I don't want anything!
You want both?
Okay then! I'm gonna cum inside you first, since I'm nearly reaching my limit!
Don't-!
I'm cumming!
Don't!
No way...!
Eh? Is someone there?
Hello there!
The flowers smelled so nice that I wandered in here.
Hey, who are you?
Please don't.
You're bullying the roses.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm the guy who came to rape you!
Rape?
Mashiro-chan, I'm going to make you scream!
Scream? And what's rape?
I'll teach you from the beginning.
Oh, could you stay how you were?
Why?
I haven't shown you what rape is.
I should probably show you what sex is before that, though.
T-That's-!
It's puffy here, isn't it?
You shouldn't be touching such places...
W-What is this feeling?
Is this sex?
No, this is called "petting".
P-Petting?
I-I don't know that.
It's difficult to say, but that's where I go to the toilet.
Not quite.
This is your vagina; where you pee is up here.
Y-Yes...
That's my vagina...
That's right, vagina.
Some people call it a pussy too. Also, there are other names.
Please wait, m-my pussy, my pussy...?
Vagina?
V-Vagina...?
Yeah, but I'm rubbing your pussy with my finger,
so it's more like finger stroking than petting?
It's still over your panties, though...
Pussy, that is my pussy,
and when it's being played with by a finger, it's finger stroking.
Well, do you know now?
It's hard to understand...
Mashiro-chan, you've been letting out strange voices.
I don't know, it comes out on it's own...
You must be feeling good.
I don't know...!
Then I'll show you more.
You're cute down here, Mashiro-chan.
D-Don't touch such places-!
Your body is so soft, Mashiro-chan. What does this feel like?
I feel warm...
This may be the first time I've been able to touch a girl so calmly...
U-Um, what are you doing now?
Oh, I guess this is petting.
Rubbing against each other, that's what petting is.
This is petting too?
Petting feels good...
Does it feel good?
Yes!
I see, then should we do something that feels even better?
Something that feels even better?
That's right!
That's a good girl.
Your breath is tickling me...
What? What's this?
M-My voice is leaking out on it's own-!
What are you doing?
Are you licking me?
Yeah, I'm licking you.
It's dirty there, I don't think you should...!
I guess your urethra, I mean where you pee, smells a bit.
So-! Don't-!
No, that's what's good about it!
T-That's what's good about it?
I really don't understand...
There are lots of things that I don't understand...
My body is shaking and my voice is leaking out on it's own,
It's a little bit scary!
It's fine, I'll make you feel even better with cunnilingus.
C-Cunnilingus? This isn't petting!
Yeah, this is cunnilingus. Doesn't it feel better than petting?
Y-Yes!
Cunnilingus... cunnilingus-!
Since it's cunnilingus, it's okay to lick there...
Your urethra, pussy and clitoris!
They're all so small and taste great!
I know what my pussy is now, my urethra is where I pee...!
What is this?!
Can you tell? Where I'm licking you now is your clitoris.
C-Clitoris?
When it feels good, it gets bigger!
I don't know such a thing... Why, why?
That's because you're feeling good!
You don't need a reason to feel good!
Yes... It feels good! My clitoris feels good!
Then how about this?
That's my butt-!
That's right! From your butt to your pussy,
from your urethra to your clitoris! I'm licking all of it!
If you do that-!
T-This is cunnilingus, cunnilingus...!
Does it feel good, Mashiro-chan?
It does! It feels so good!
Do you want me to do more?
Yes! More, please do more!
Then how about this?
Right, this is a man's erect cock.
I-It's so hot...
Now, I wonder what will happen if we combine my cock and your slit?
I-I don't know...
I don't know anything about this!
Then how about we try it?
Your cock, it's-!
How about my clitoris? I want you to rub my clitoris...
I'm going to do something that feels even better than that!
S-Something that feels better than my clitoris?
Here I go!
I-It hurts!!
Whoa! You're so tight! You've got such a small pussy!
It hurts, it hurts!
It feels weird, what's this?
This is sex! No, this is rape!
Rape? B-But it hurts! It's painful!
Hey, this is the rape you wanted to know about from the beginning!
No! I don't like rape! It hurts, it hurts! It doesn't feel good!
That's right!
Rape is where the man forcefully does the woman who's in pain!
No!!
Your beautiful pussy from before is now messed up!
Why are you doing such a thing?
That's because you were born to be raped!
No! I, I-! What should I do-?!
Who knows?
I guess if you get pregnant and have a baby, then that'll be your job.
A baby?
Oh? You don't understand?
This what you do to make babies!
If I release my seed inside of you, a child might grow.
Apparently people find babies dear when they're growing inside of you!
A baby inside of me?
However! The father will be a rapist!
No! I don't want it to be a person like you! No!
I'm gonna cum!
No, no!
What on Earth is going on?! I-It hurts! Please stop!
I can't stop! It feels too good!
No, someone! Please help me!
Here I go! I'm gonna pour my seed inside of you!
Don't, don't-! Stop this! Please, please-!
It's tightening around me-! I'm cumming!
Can you feel it? It's entering you, it's filling you up!
His seed is entering me...
It's hot, I've been implanted...
That felt good!
See you later, then!