It's so hot...
Geez, I don't feel like doing anything in this heat.
Sub
DESU
-H
Presents
It really is hot, but at least I'll get a nice tan.
Sara-san, you're totally exposed to the neighbors!
Something like this is totally exposed!
Ehh?!
Oh neighbors! I'm fully exposed! Take a look!
S-Sara-san! You mustn't do that!
It's fine!
So hot.
Geez, my body won't last.
Oh yeah, Touya's father said he was going to send us something to give us energy.
Really? I wonder what it is?
Raw meat? Raw eel?
Umm, raw, raw...
Raw? I was thinking of another kind of raw!
Oh Sara-san, you pervert!
Nagisa-san, Sara-san! People will see you! Aren't you embarrassed?
I'm going to give them some more service by rubbing them like this!
N-Not you too, Nagisa-san...
It's fine.
These two get excited when people are watching.
E-Excited?
Oh yeah, last night I heard some lewd voices from your and Touya's room.
What was that about?
What?
I know!
Huh?
Touya-kun saw Amane-chan masturbating!
Yes, and as punishment, didn't you get him to masturbate too?
N-No, I....
I-I was the victim, so-!
But when you were watching him, you got aroused too, right?
T-That's, um...
Since you were rubbing and sucking on him...
You drank all his semen, too...
When I came to your room then, you two were doing something perverted?!
N-No... If I see him stroking his cock so much, I'll get excited too!
I-I can't hold back!
A-Amane-san?
It's hot...
Your cock is so hot.
I'll help you out, so you better cum soon.
Y-You dummy! This is...
This is your fault!
W-Wait, Amane-san-! That's!
Pre-cum is coming out of Touya's cock...
I-If you do that so much, I-I'll cum...
J-Just let it out already! I'm already stoking hot down here...
My body is getting hotter!
M-My pussy... My pussy, it's-!
H-Hurry... Hurry up and cum!
Amane-chan!
Are you in there?
P-Please wait a sec-!
Touya-kun, you were here.
Y-Yeah...
Sorry to disturb you during your studies.
Anyway, I'm going down to the convenience store.
Anything you need?
N-No, not really.
I drank it... I drank Touya's semen...
G-Geez, forget about me!
So, then what were those voices from Touya-kun's room?
Eh?!
I know about that too!
S-Sara-san-!
Rio-chan used my rotors to have sex with Touya-kun, didn't you?
That's because you left them in the bathroom, and-!
I didn't know that Rio-chan was interested in such toys...
B-Because I didn't know that rotors felt so good...
Rio-san, you pervert.
Y-You'd understand if you used them too, Amane-chan.
It feels tingly and you can't stop shaking!
It's no wonder Touya-kun got excited if you were that aroused, Rio-chan!
Both of you were playing with yourselves with those rotors...
I was surprised!
You even used it on Touya's ass, and you were covered in his semen afterward.
N-No Amane-chan. Don't say it in such a lewd way!
Y-Your cock.. It's getting so hard!
For you to get aroused from me playing with your ass... You're so dirty!
Your love juices are making the rotor slip-
Rio-san, it's going deeper and deeper...
So then Sara-san caught you two red handed!
You two were so aroused, it made me want to bully them.
I-It was so embarrassing teaching naked...
But I became more aroused since I was being looked at...
Touya-kun was so aroused too!
I think I understand, though.
My heart is beating faster from just thinking about it...
Maybe I should teach him naked too!
I wasn't satisfied with just that, and...
You put Touya-kun's cock in and you moved your hips, didn't you?
Sara-san!
I got Touya-kun to lick my pussy a lot, too...
So? How was it?
Did it feel good?
I came so many times!
I can see your lascivious body clinging on to me!
N-No! Don't say such things! It's too embarrassing1
I can't stop, I can't stop myself!
Even though it's embarrassing, it feels too good to stop-!
Let it out inside me! Fill up my uterus!
I-I-I'm cumming~!!
That's not fair, I'm the only one who missed out!
It's so unfair, I want to do it as well!
My lesson is first today, isn't it?
Right then...
Huh? Isn't anyone home?
Yes, I-I'm coming!
An international delivery from Touya's father?
What?!
Energy pills?!
Oh right, there was that one time when Touya-kun
came so much and was extremely hard, wasn't there?
Is that because of these pills?
I'm, I'm gonna-!
I've thought of something good!
Today's paper is too difficult!
This one has a lot of application questions, doesn't it?
How about you drink some tea to cool off?
I know that I have to use the formulas, but...
He's drinking it!
He doesn't even realize that I've spiked it!
This tastes strange...
H-Huh, what's this?
My body is getting hot-!
N-Nagisa-san?!
I wonder what's wrong, Touya-kun...
Getting large like this while studying...
Touya-kun, you pervert!
W-What? Na-Nagisa-san?!
But I just touched you a tiny bit...
I-I'm sorry! I-I suddenly got aroused, and-!
I'm all sticky; how about we take a bath?
Eh?
Kateikyoushi no Onee-san: the second
Does this feel good, Touya-kun?
I-It feels great!
Your breast are so soft...
Cum whenever you want!
Your dirty cock is going in and out of my cleavage!
That's a good expression!
My breasts are making you feel good, aren't they?
Your cock is throbbing!
Are you gonna cum?
Na-Nagisa-san-!
You came so much!
I-I'm sorry...
Don't worry.
We're in the bath, so cover me all you want!
D-Don't do that! I just came-!
You're moaning like a girl, Touya-kun!
R-Really?
I'll make you feel better...
Nagisa-san-!
If you do that, I'll-!
How is it? Are you gonna cum again?
Do you want to cover my face with your semen again?
More, let out more!
Nagisa-san, we can't keep going-!
No way! You're still hard!
B-But...
Hey, put it in...
I'm soaking wet already, pierce me with this cock!
Hurry!
I can't hold back!
It's going in! It's going in so deep-!
H-How is it?
Does it feel good inside me?
Your insides are hot and it's clinging to me! It feels so good!
I-It's moving inside me-
I can feel you pulsing inside me!
More, more-!
I'm about to cum again-!
It's okay, don't hold back.
Cum inside me, and do it harder!
Pound my dirty spot!
Thrust, thrust! Thrust more!
Nagisa-san-! If you tighten so much, I'll, I'll-!
L-Let it out! Cum where ever you want!
Amazing, you let out so much...
W-Wait Don't pull it out!
Na-Nagisa-san, I'm still...
Your cock is still hard, isn't it?
Do whatever you want, Touya-kun...
What happened?
What was that voice just now?
It's the voice of Nagisa-chan enjoying herself!
Nagisa-san, what are you doing?
Um, this is...!
How dirty.
No! Don't-! Don't pull out now!
Don't!
Y-You're cumming so much.
What on earth happened?
Kateikyoushi no Onee-san: The second
I see, so it's because of these pills you gave to Touya-kun?
Well, it was just a joke at first...
Geez, Nagisa-san!
This isn't the same stuff that Touya took last time;
it's much stronger!
No way!
Amane-chan, isn't there a way to fix this?
I'm not sure, but the only way is probably... Um...
I-I think making him cum is the easiest way.
But he hasn't calmed down even after cumming inside me so much!
Maybe it's still not enough?
Okay then! I shall fix Touya-kun!
Ri-Rio-san?!
You're a bit rough, but I'll help too.
Okay everyone! Let's make him cum!
Yeah!!
Ehh?
I'll do it first, then!
Amazing, it's so hard!
I'll make you cum plenty, okay?
I'll make you lick me here...
Please rub my breasts with your free hand...
Hey, I'll let you feel mine too.
I'll suck it for you!
You're throbbing so much! Go ahead and cum whenever you want!
Did that feel good?
Please let out more!
No, this is too much... I'm so wet...
Rio-chan, I want to go next!
I'll put it in, so please hang on...
Amazing-! Your cock is so hot!
It's amazing! Your insides are so wet-!
The tip is getting caught! It feels really good!
My turn next!
Me too! I wanna do it again!
Touya-kun!
Hey, Touya-kun!
Isn't it great?
Your cock is back to normal.
What?
It's all thanks to us!
I-I see...
Are you okay now?
Rio-san-! I-If you do that, again, I'll-!
Again?
You're going to get hard again?
That's okay, I'll do it as many times as you want!
What?! It's gotten large again?
I can still keep going!
I can too!
Let's change the order then!
H-Hey-!
I'm first!
What?! No fair!
It should be decided with rock, paper, scissors!