It's been ten years since I started my journey as a teacher, and this day has finally come.
From today, I am a teacher, and my employer is the famous Wakanua School.
Thank you God! Today is the best day of my, Hayasaka Maria's, life.
Gakuen
Maria
~Bakunyuu Teachers~
Principal’s Office
Thank you for coming today.
It's no problem, principal. Because, starting today, I too am a member of this school.
That's some great spirit you have.
By the way, did you read my introduction for this school?
Yes! The phrase "a teacher is the students’ mother, big sister and their lover" was really moving.
Also you wrote, "teachers are for the students’ service" -
I'm going to work hard using that as a model.
Well, that’s fantastic.
By the way, aren't you related to Haruka-sensei?
Yes. It was her influence that motivated me to become a teacher.
That's why I can't believe I can do the same profession as her.
It's like a dream come true.
I see, I see, how very big of you...
Principal...
I'm very sorry, they're so great that I just couldn't take my eyes off them.
No... they’re actually too big for me.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Are you sure?
They're also the reason I chose you.
Eh?
No, it’s nothing.
This is where you'll be teaching.
Haruka-sensei is teaching at the moment, but you can at least greet them.
Okay.
I'm finally going to take the first step of being a teacher.
I'm going to be a teacher, just like my beloved sister!
Go on in.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yes!
Nee-san?
Haruka-sensei's class is energetic as usual.
It’s not about being energetic!
Sensei...
Sensei!
I am about to...
Cum!
It’s okay! Cum! Cum inside me!
Se...
Sensei!
Sensei, that was good!
Nee-san?!
Oh, isn't that Maria?
Don't just greet me like that!
What is this?!
There's nothing to be surprised about.
This is the "ideal education" we give at our school.
Eh? This is "ideal education"?
As I wrote in that book, "a teacher should serve the students".
And in this school we take it literally.
So it was that kind of service...
Of course, if you can’t satisfy a couple of students
in the middle of puberty then you can’t call yourself a teacher.
This is another one of a teacher's esteemed responsibilities.
Um... I'm going to leave now... Excuse me.
Go on, you should fulfill your duty as a teacher.
I can't do such a thing!
I can't believe she'd do this kind of thing.
Take that stick out of your ass.
Nee-san!
What did you make me swallow?
What is this...?
Don't worry, you'll feel light headed for a bit.
Principal, is it okay to celebrate her welcome party?
Yes. Knock yourselves out.
What are you...?
Can't move my body...
Awesome!
So these are Maria-sensei's boobs.
No... don't!
It’s a pleasure to be taught by a big-breasted teacher like you.
It can't be... It's just the first day of my dream job, but...
Allright! Let’s rub our dicks all over Maria-sensei!
No!
Is this the effect of the drug my sister forced me to swallow?
Even though I'm being raped... my body feels so good!
But I can't hold on much longer.
Come on, dear, take it all off quick!
Yes, ma’am!
I can’t get enough!
It's still pink!
It’s all moist...
Go on Maria, serve everyone in class.
All right! Then please serve me first!
All right then, Aoki-kun.
Please take care of me from now on, Maria-sensei.
Such a gentle kiss even in a situation like this.
B-But...
I'm putting it in.
But still, no... Don't...!
Awesome.
It went in right away.
It feels so good inside of you, Sensei.
No!
I can't hold on any longer...
His sperm is filling up my womb!
You're the best, Sensei.
I'ill go next.
Don't!!
Is this "ideal education"?
I can't believe this is happening on my first day.
But what is this feeling?
A magical feeling is making me...
But...
Let me go!
What is this?
My resignation letter.
Why?
Why? Because I can't do that kind of teaching!
Really? You seemed to be doing fine to me.
And you too, Nee-san!
What happened to the hard working Nee-san who was so devoted to teaching?!
That is also teaching.
No, I think that is the true meaning of teaching.
I can't believe this.
I thought that this school was my ideal place but...
I'm very disappointed. Excuse me.
Oh dear. I thought she had a lot of potential...
Don't worry, she'll definitely find the correct path.
How can this happen?
I thought this would be the best day of my life since I became a teacher, but...
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
This is the worst day of my life.
Sensei...
I can’t hold on any longer!
No, that can't be teaching!
Yes!
All right! Let’s rub our dicks on Maria-sensei!
No!
Go on Maria, serve everyone in class.
Such... Such perverted things...
I'm putting it in.
Sensei's insides feel so good!
No!
Doing those... Doing those sorts of things...
And this...
No... Don't!
I...
No...
Why am I...?
Even though it was bad... just from remembering it...
Why... am I...
...doing... doing this?!
I think I’m...
Why did I do such a thing...?
I don’t even think I'm that perverted...
To masturbate...
Excuse me, can you pass the ball here?
You're...
Maria-sensei.
Wait!
Wait sensei, please, I want to talk to you.
I coach them in my spare time because they don’t have a coach.
You're kind.
I can't believe you raped me...
Well... that was...
Sorry.
Well, I heard from Haruka-sensei.
You didn't know we were having that kind of lesson.
We all thought you knew about it.
I'm sorry.
Aoki-kun...
Don't worry about it anymore.
You're forgiving us?
Well...
What's done is done, so...
Besides, I'm not teaching there any more.
You're going to quit?
Yes, because that isn't real education.
Not real education?
Yes.
It might seem like I'm just talking back to you, but I think it's a great way of teaching.
W-What are you saying?
Our school isn’t the best, but we have top grades, we’re good at sports,
and have no bullying.
Do you know why?
I think it’s because of lessons like Haruka-sensei's.
They're accepting us... rather than trying to get rid of our desires.
Accepting you?
Yes, and because of that we feel like we're trusted by our teacher,
so we're able to respect them back.
Trust between teacher and student?
Other schools never have that.
Now that I think about it, some schools I did my teaching training at...
I never felt...
No, the more experienced teachers also never felt trust and understanding between them and the students.
I think we can say that that is the true meaning of education.
True education...
Understand the students and accept them fully.
I kept on rejecting it because it was too different from what I’d imagined.
But in reality...
Yes, that time...
What was inside me... wasn't just ecstasy - there was something more.
A different sort of validating feeling...
And that sensation...
I was... longing for it...
Maria-sensei?
Aoki-kun, thank you. I've finally realized something.
I want to be a real teacher.
I want to do real teaching.
Sensei...
So can you please teach me how to understand you?
You're beautiful, Maria-sensei.
No... It’s embarrassing...
You are like a goddess.
Beautiful...
It looks like it's flooding.
No, don’t say things like that.
Then should I stop?
Meanie... Don’t stop.
I... I...
Sensei, you came a little.
You're so cute.
Sensei... Sensei!
Aoki-kun!
Sensei's insides feel so good.
It feels moist and hot, like I'm in a molten pudding.
Aoki-kun... Yours is so big and hot - it’s hitting me so deep!
Sensei...
I can’t hold on any longer...
Wait... Together... Let's cum together...
I'm cumming!
Aoki-kun's sperm is filling my womb.
Sensei, that was awesome.
More... I want to understand more...
Maria-sensei...
I want to take you all in.
Sensei...
Even though you're doing perverted things... you look so beautiful right now, Sensei.
More... More...
I'm getting sucked in to your moist, pudding-like pussy.
Cum! Please fill me with your cum!
I... I'm cumming!
Right now... you truly are... .a goddess.
All right, everyone, let’s get on with true education.
Yes!