Kurenai.
So, will you make a contract with me?
Kiriya Hakushakuke no
Roku Shimai
This is it.
Hey, Onii-san over there!
You're Tokitsu Daisuke-kun.
Yeah... That's me...
My name is Kiriya Botan
Maybe I'll be your big sister or even your little sister.
Huh~?
Then, shall we go?
It seems that this letter wasn't a prank after all.
I got strange letter when I lived in Tokyo,
that led me to come here.
The sender was an infamous female writer,
Kiriya Fujino.
But, she should have died 10 years ago.
We're here.
I'm sorry to make you wait like this.
Welcome, Tokitsu Daisuke-san.
I'm Kiriya Takaomi's wife in this family,
my name is Sumi.
Pleased to meet you.
You've already grown up so much.
Eh?
Of course you don't remember at all.
I can't blame you for that.
You were just a little kid and lots of problems happened at that time.
Um...
Over here is the head of this family, Kiriya Takaomi.
I'm sorry about his appearance,
but my husband has been under a lot of stress lately and he's not feeling well.
Is that so?
Pleased to meet you, I'm Tokitsu Daisuke.
Behind Takaomi would be this family's maid, Sagane Aya.
Hello.
Let me introduce my daughters.
The older one, Nadeshiko.
It's nice to meet you, Daisuke-sama.
The next one beside her is-
Well, I don't really have to introduce her, right?
What's that!? Introduce me properly!
Beside Botan is the third one, Ai.
Beside Ai is the fifth one, Kurenai.
The last one is the sixth, Sumire.
Pleased to meet you, Daisuke-sama.
There's one thing I need to ask.
I've was told in the letter to create something here...
That's not entirely true, Daisuke-san.
The thing about you having to create something was only an excuse.
I want you to take care of my daughters.
I want you to make one of my daughters pregnant and bear your children.
Sure... Eh? That's-
Daisuke-san, you've been chosen to be with one of the Kiriya family's daughters.
Then you'll have the only Kiriya family descendant,
who'll receive everything in here.
Daisuke!
Why don't you let Botan-neesan show you the mansion?
Wait, let me do that for you!
Da... Daisuke-san.
Why don't you give me a break...
Pleased to meet you.
You are...?
My name is Rudomiller Michaelovener Graschaft.
You can call me Ruda, Daisuke.
Sure... Why do you know my name anyway?
That kind of conversation should be just for the two of us.
Hey, you!
Ku-re-na-i, did you already forget?
Daisuke-san.
I won't lose.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
Kurenai.
Will you make a contract with me?
Did you sleep well?
Yes, sure...
What's the matter?
Why-
You're the only one who's sleeping here.
I just wanted to make sure you slept well.
Have you gotten familiar with the mansion?
Yes, Kurenai-san showed me a lot of places earlier.
Tomorrow, she's going to show me the garden.
Is that so?
Is something wrong?
Honestly, I don't even know what's going on here.
It's been already 10 years since the last time I visited this place
in memorial of the death of your sister, Kiriya Fujino-san.
That's the first time I got an invitation letter to come here.
Well, shouldn't you take a closer look within the invitation from that time?
Then why are you here right now?
Maybe that's because I'm kind of a magazine reporter now.
I thought there was something that would make a good article for me.
Excuse me, but I've been hearing such strange rumors about Count Kiriyas for a long time.
Hm, what kind of strange rumors have you heard?
It's not such a good rumor at all.
But, I'm doing it because I need my job after all.
Is that so?
I still think that what happened earlier was kind of a prank for me.
Well... well... You're doubting that thing, right?
I'm reporter after all, Um...
Then, let your sister clear any doubt from your mind.
Ukh... Na... Nadeshiko-san.
You've already gotten this hard.
It's okay, your sister will take care of everything.
Nadeshiko-san, today isn't the night of-
It's my duty to check if you're the perfect man for us,
as the eldest daughter here.
But, the "yotogi" is tomorrow-
Yotogi: Visiting someone during the night
The hardness, size,
also the length, is perfect in many ways.
I'm satisfied with it, but...
This time I'll let Daisuke-kun satisfy me by himself.
You don't have to rush, these breasts won't go anywhere.
Since the first time we met, I've been interested in these breasts.
Are you satisfied?
Onee-san.
Hm...
Daisuke-san, come in here.
Sure.
You're... a virgin?
Every daughter in the Kiriya family...
is waiting for you in the "yotogi" ritual,
we're protecting our virgin blood everyday.
Though it's harder than what I had imagined before.
It's not something I can't endure after all.
Well, don't hold back, move inside of me.
Then.
Da...Daisuke-san's hard... hard penis is-
Inside of me-
I feel so great!
Nadeshiko-san, there's milk coming out of your breasts.
When I'm feeling stimulation like this, even though I'm not pregnant,
Milk comes out of my breasts.
More... more... I want you to be more intense, Daisuke-san!
Sure.
That's good, there's milk coming out again!
Nadeshiko-san's milk tastes so delicious.
You're even tasting it...
Your milk isn't stopping at all.
Don't suck on it~!
Are you sure that I can't do that?
You can't do something like that with my breasts-
Nadeshiko-san's pussy is getting tender right now,
and it can suck my penis so easily.
Yes, my pussy is sucking on Daisuke-san's... penis.
It's sucking on your penis-
Your penis is stirring up my pussy...
I never knew that it would be this good~!
I'm... I'm about to cum soon!
Even though this is my first time... pussy... my pussy...
I feel... I feel like it's going to explode~!
Alright Nadeshiko-san, I'm... I'm also at my limit-
Together!
If you would, please cum together with me.
I'll cum with... my pussy.
I'll cum with my pussy~!!
I'm... cumming!
There's something hot inside of my pussy...
There's something hot flowing inside of me!
It's really... It's really hot~!!!
This is...
This is the duty of the Kiriya daughters.
It feels too good for me.
I'm going to be fine.
Then, don't hold back.
No, I don't wanna do that!
If I do that then Daisuke... Daisuke wouldn't be the same anymore.
I don't want that to happen.
It's a really vast garden isn't it~?
Our family is weak against sunlight and has been for a long time.
Oh, I see.
That's why there are curtains everywhere even though it's noon.
That's the reason.
Although I like this kind of sunshine.
Do you feel good? I feel good as well.
What's the matter?
This warehouse, what's it used for right now?
It's used to store Fujino-neesama goods.
Is that so?
Daisuke, did you forget about this warehouse?
You always played with Fujino-neesama and Sumire a lot in here.
Honestly, I've been remembering that I came to this mansion before.
So you really forgot about that.
I'm sorry.
That's okay, there'll always be chances to make memories from now on.
He's big!
Gon, this man is the Kiriya's guest.
If you've got it, then leave us.
Who is he?
He's Gon, our servant.
Although he looks scary, he's not a bad person.
Hey, Daisuke.
The "yotogi" is starting tonight, right?
Have you decided who's place you want to go to?
No, I'm still not sure if I'm going or not...
You can't say that!
This is an important thing for all of us!
Be serious, okay?
Sorry.
You lack respect!
Let me tell you something good.
The first time is always about what you feel the most, that's why!
Tonight, You should go to the place you have the closest relationship with,
that's what I had in my mind.
That means... I should to go to your place, right?
Si... Silence, "yotogi" is...
and important ritual for us, don't make fun of it!
I understand.
For sure... for sure, okay?
Sure.
Hm, Daisuke. You're also going to pray to god?
Not really, I was just walking around here.
I'm sorry to disturb your praying.
That's not a problem.
Hey, Ruda... is that "yotogi" is kind of important for this family,
and... why should I do it?
Sex has been such an important ritual since a long time ago.
And then,
If you want to know the reason why you've been chosen,
tonight and tomorrow, you should come here when it's late at night.
Ru-
I'm sorry, Sumi-san.
There's something I need to talk about...
The ''yotogi" would last for 4 days.
It makes us wonder who's going to be picked by Daisuke-san.
Yes.
Then, It's not a good time for Botan to come in here.
There's nothing to be worried about.
I'm sure that Botan already knew the importance of the "yotogi" ritual.
It'll be fine then.
Yes, come in.
Welcome.
You actually came here.
Kurenai.
Um... Wait a moment.
It's... Can I make you feel good first for tonight?
Please, can I do that?
Eh, sure...
You know... Kurenai.
Hm, what is it?
Where do you think it'll make me feel good?
I'm sure you're happy about it.
There you go.
As I thought, it's true after all.
That guys would be happy if some girl stepped on their penis like this.
Where did you hear that?
There... there... there... maybe in here?
It's cute when it's twitching...
Also it's really hard.
I can't believe that a penis would be excited like this while being stepped on.
There... there... You're feeling good, aren't you?
There's juice come out of the tip.
It's sticky and hot as well...
As I thought, you like it.
It's cute when you're blushing.
But I won't let you cum yet.
There!
Stop it-
Do you want me to stop? But your penis is getting hard from it.
If you're really don't want it, you should stay back by yourself.
It's great! It's sticky and twitching around.
Your penis is so cute.
Can you see it? Your penis feels good like this.
You should remember this, Kurenai.
Daisuke should remember this as well.
That your penis is cumming after being stepped on by me.
You should see it clearly.
Your perverted penis is cumming while it's being stepped on like this.
It's amazes me, there's so much sticky juice come out.
It makes me feels excited as well.
Is it coming out? Is the sperm gonna come out!?
There... I'll step on it as much as you'd like, okay?
It's out.
It's... amazing~
There's a lot of it and it's warm.
This would make me pregnant, right?
This time it's my turn, right?
Daisuke, I think we should stop for tonight-
I don't care if it's "yotogi", I don't like being forced like this.
I want you to stop doing things like this, okay?
Ye... Yes, I'm sorry.
Hey...
Will you come over tomorrow?
Yeah.
Is that true?
I promise it.
Geez... That Kurenai.
A... Ai!
Sorry, I didn't know that you were already in here.
I don't mind.
I've been waiting for you in here.
I'll bear Daisuke's child.
That would be my duty as a Kiriya family daughter.
It's still healthy, Daisuke.
I want you to put that thing inside of me.
Does it feel good, Ai?
I don't know, but... I feel strange.
Then in here?
Ai, you're already this wet.
Let's make each other feel good this time.
Yes.
Ai, I'll put it in.
I want that sturdy penis of Daisuke's to be thrust into me-
Ai, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Go on with it.
Sure.
It's hot.
I can feel my insides expanding and burning.
Ai, do you feel good?
I don't know.
Don't know, but-
Ai, It'll feel better if you move your hips by yourself.
Yes.
It's rubbing a lot inside of me!
Deep...
It makes me shiver when it's hitting so deep.
Ai, this feels good, right?
It's starting to feel good.
Daisuke's... hard penis... is thrusting inside of me.
No... No... It'll rip apart!
Ai, I can't...
Come on, let it out inside of me.
I want you to release it deep into my pussy~!
Ai!
It's hot... There's something hot coming inside~!
Ai, why don't we take a bath together now?
I have something to do after this.
Hm?
Is it the ritual?
If you want to know the reason why you've been chosen,
tonight and tomorrow, you should come here when it's late at night.
Daisuke.
Why is there such light this late at night?
Just what happened in here?
What is... this?