It's been a while since we've been able to relax...
My sisters have gone to the hot springs,
so it's just you and me, Kuri.
Since that happened, Kuri is still a cat.
Does that mean that the curse was lifted when we did that with Ryouko-nee?
Or does she change back when I'm not looking?
Eh?
K-Kuri?
Why did you change so suddenly?
Actually, it seems that Kuri's curse hasn't been lifted yet, nyan!
I-I see...
Yes! So...
You know what this means, don't you, Yuu?
H-Huh?
For me to turn back into a cat,
we have to do a lot of lewd things to let the juices out!
It's fine, isn't it, Yuu?
SubDESU
-H
Anejiru: The Second
I'll start off with my hands!
Your hands are so soft, it's as if you still have paws.
Doesn't it feel good?
I'm about to cum from this-!
It's fine, go ahead and cum!
It's not like you get tired from letting it out once, right?
W-Well... Isn't that up to you?
I see!
Then Kuri will try her best so you can cum plenty!
How is this, nyaa?
K-Kuri-! That feels too good-!
Come on, there's no need to hold back!
Show Kuri how you cum!
Kuri-! I'm gonna-!
Cum! Give your hot semen to Kuri's face!
Whoa, you sure let out a lot!
It's still coming out!
Hey, how was it?
Did Kuri do well?
Your hands were awesome, Kuri!
Where did you learn that technique?
I just copied what Kyouko and Anzu did...
So it was from them, huh?
Yeah!
I accidentally saw them doing it last time...
Oh? Kyouko is doing lewd things again!
Onee-chan's gonna show you herself masturbating,
so show me your cock too!
When you're ready, let's show each other ourselves masturbating!
Hmm, I wonder if she's doing the
"show each other ourselves masturbating" play today, nyaa?
I'm getting so hot here...
Can you tell? My lewd juices are making my panties sticky!
My nipples are hard too!
Onee-chan can't help but imagine things when she sees your erect cock!
I wonder how good it would feel
if we were to titfuck that hot, hard cock of yours?
A-And, if you were to thrust it into my pussy,
you would make me cum so quickly!
Please look at my dirty spots!
How's this? Isn't Onee-chan's pussy soaking wet?
Can your hear the perverted sounds?
She's moving her finger faster and faster!
Huh? I swear I heard someone here...
That was close, nyaa!
You have to look closely!
Look more at Onee-chan's wet pussy!
I'm servicing you so much, so please feel good!
I-Isn't this Kyouko-nee's voice?
Staring at my breasts and my pussy makes me feel tingly!
It feels so good-!
Your gaze is piercing me!
I can't hold back!
I'm gonna cum from my fingers-!
I'm gonna cum while being watched! I'm cumming!
I'm not satisfied with just my fingers...
I wonder if I should use "that"?
Jeez! If you're going to masturbate, do it in your room!
I'm going to imagine this is your cock, so please watch!
N-No way!
She's going to insert something that large?!
It's going in-!
I-It's amazing!
I-It's rubbing against my deepest spots!
Can you see? Onee-chan's pussy is so stretched out!
She's getting so wet!
I bet it feels great!
N-No-! This feels better than usual!
It really feels like you're inside me!
How is it? Can you see Onee-chan's lewd spot?
It feels so good!
It's rubbing me so deeply! I can't stop myself!
I'm gonna cum again! I'm gonna cum!
No-!
I-It's coming out!
She squirted out so much!
Does it really feel that good?
I haven't had enough...
You can keep going too, right?
C'mon-! Thrust your cock deeper inside me!
Make Onee-chan cum even more!
Rub your cock harder!
Let's cum together!
It feels so good-!
My pussy's throbbing!
No-!
I'm, I'm gonna cum again-!
I'm gonna cum right in front of you-!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Amazing... I came so much...
Oh?
I-It's not what it looks like!
I was just-!
Anzu, what are you doing there?
W-Well, I heard your voice from the bathroom,
so I wondered "What is she doing?"
...And you saw me doing this,
and you were masturbating too!
T-That's-! U-Umm-!
What great timing!
It's your turn to help our User masturbate!
Ehh?!
I wonder what's going to happen to Anzu?
Kuri's getting excited too!
O-Onee-chan... Do I really have to do this?
Of course!
Ryouko and I did it, so Anzu has to service our User too!
B-But...
If you don't want to,
should I tell them of the perverted things you and Yuu-kun did?
J-Jeez! Fine then!
I-I just have to help them, right?
That's right!
That's all you have to do!
O-Onee-chan, please don't be rough...
You'll be fine! You saw me use this before, right?
B-But I'm not the same as you, Onee-chan...
Don't be rude!
That makes me sound like I'm a loose woman or something!
Your butt is so cute, Anzu.
S-So big...!
It's too big! Please wait-!
I've already wet it with lotion, so it'll be fine!
See? It went in all the way!
N-No! It really is too big!
P-Pull it out!
If you want me to, then you have to help our User masturbate with that.
N-No way!
If you don't hurry, I'll make you cum instead!
W-Wait! I'll do it, I'll do it!
I-I'm gonna imagine this is your cock and lick it the best I can...
S-So please watch Kyou and masturbate too!
We've gotta show your lewd side too, right Anzu?
C'mon, you've got to look at our user more!
T-They're watching me... I'm being watched, aren't I?
I'm starting to feel strange...
It's fine! Just let yourself become aroused!
D-Don't! If you do it like that, I'll-!
Kyou bets that she's making a dirty face right now!
The vibrator is coming inside me...
So hot-! I'm getting hot!
Revealing your breasts like that... You're so lewd, Anzu!
N-No! I'm just doing this because I'm getting hot-!
Even if you say that, your pussy is so wet!
No-! Please don't move it-!
I'll really break!
That's good! Seeing you getting aroused like this-!
N-No! I'm gonna cum-!
I'm gonna cum like this!
No-!
N-No!!
She came!
It made Anzu cum!
P-Please! Let me go!
Please turn off that vibrator!
No way.
Our User hasn't cum yet.
So please make sure you suck that cock this time.
S-Suck this cock?
Oh? Did Anzu's switch turn on?
This cock is hot and tasty! It's just like a real one!
Kyou may have lost it!
Kyou looks like she's lost it from cumming from the vibrator!
I feel so dirty!
That's it, Anzu.
This time, cum at the same time as our User!
H-Hurry up and cum!
Kyou will do anything for you!
Kyou's l-lewd pussy is so wet from wanting y-your cock!
I-I can't hold on! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Please-! Please cum at the same time!
My sisters are incredibly perverted, aren't they?
What you let out before is nowhere near enough!
I want you to cum a lot inside of my mouth this time!
I could, but will you drink it all?
Of course!
Yuu's is delicious,
so I'll drink every single drop!
Amazing! It's getting harder than before!
Yuu's taste is spreading through my mouth!
How is it? Does it feel good?
Is Kuri doing well?
Yeah, your tongue work is amazing, Kuri!
Really!?
Not so much-!
I love the taste and smell of his cock!
You're making lewd sounds with your mouth again!
I want to make Yuu's cock feel even better!
His cock is throbbing inside my mouth!
Kuri, could you do it deeper?
Amazing-! It feels like my cock is gonna melt!
I can feel Yuu's veins making it bumpy!
He's quivering so much, he's about to cum again!
Kuri-! I-I'm about to cum-!
Let it out! Hurry up and let it out!
Fill Kuri's mouth with your semen!
That's amazing, Yuu!
Even though it's the second time, you let out so much that it overflowed!
That's because your technique felt amazing, Kuri.
I'll make you feel good this time, okay?
Then I want to do it like when we did it with Ryouko!
Oh right, you came so much that time, didn't you, Kuri?
No-! D-Don't-!
Don't lick me!
W-What-?!
W-Who are you?!
I'm Kuri!
K-Kuri-chan?! No way!
P-Please wait there!
You mustn't move!
Y-Yuu-kun-! Please come to my room!
Eh? Ryouko-nee? What are you so flustered about?
Just come quickly!
Something happened to Kuri-chan!
W-What are you talking about?
What happened to Kuri?
C'mon, hurry!
This is Kuri?
Hey, Yuu-kun, do you have any idea why this happened?
Now that I think about it,
there was an empty medicine bottle in Dad's room when I got back this afternoon...
Jeez! I wish Dad would stop collecting such strange things!
Ryouko-nee, will Kuri change back to normal?
Let's see...
If that bottle was the cause,
then if we make her cum, would that fix it?
Kuri wants to do lewd things!
H-Hey! Kuri-chan?!
Kuri knows!
Since you've started sleeping naked,
the number of times you masturbate has increased!
N-No! Don't say such things in front of Yuu-kun!
I-Is that true?
I'm so embarrassed!
Ryouko is sensitive around here, right?
You always touch around here!
J-Jeez! Who would have known that Kuri-chan was this lewd?
I-It feels so good there!
It's because you, Kyouko, and Anzu are all perverted!
Kuri wants to feel good too!
Don't-!
Don't suck so much-!
N-No! Kuri-chan! You're too good at licking-!
Ryouko-nee, can I join in?
Kuri's gonna lick Ryouko down there!
K-Kuri-chan-! Not there-! I-It's dirty!
It's not dirty!
Your lewd juices taste great!
Kuri's pussy is getting wet from licking Ryouko's dirty spot!
Don't suck there-!
I-I'm gonna lose it!
Ryouko-nee-! I might not be able to hold back either...!
I can feel your hard cock against my backside!
H-Hey... If you're gonna put your cock in, please put it in Kuri too!
Jeez, both of you! I guess it can't be helped...
Then let's all feel good this time.
C'mon, put your cock between our pussies...
Yuu! Hurry! Hurry up and put it in!
I'm putting it in-!
Your cock is rubbing between Kuri and Ryouko's pussies!
Your cock is getting hotter-!
D-Do you feel good too, Yuu-kun?
You're both so wet here! It feels incredible!
Kuri's never experienced something like this!
It feels like my body is melting!
Kuri-chan, you're letting out such a cute voice...
If you do this...
it feels even better!
N-Not at the same time-!
How is it?
Doesn't it feel good to rub our breasts together like this?
Y-Yes!
Even though it's soft,
the n-nipples are so hard and they're rubbing against each other-!
Ryouko-nee-! Sorry, I'm nearly cumming!
Wait-!
We'll go on top this time!
Kuri's pussy is overflowing with her lewd juices!
It's making such a perverted sound!
Let's both squeeze Yuu-kun's semen out with our pussies!
K-Kuri's feeling lightheaded! It's like I'm gonna float away!
I-I'm g-gonna cum-!
L-Let out a lot!
Pour your semen onto us!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum-!
I'm overflowing!
Sorry! It seems I changed back!
Can we do it again, nyan?
Eh?
Ehhh?!
Now then, thanks for the meal!
S-Stop it! Don't take it off!
Chomp~!