I...actually quite like the color red.
Rouge, and manicures...
Even high heels.
And of course, suits.
I feel devilish in the color red.
I used to not like standing out from the crowd.
But one day, I made myself wear red. Then all of a sudden,
I changed completely.
I felt that I wanted people to notice me,
the lady dressed in red.
However, as soon as I realized this, I ran into the toilets.
Perhaps I had wanted to get away from the nervousness.
But actually...
That red manicured right hand...
Would find its way into the embarrassing parts hidden within my skirt.
Likewise, the other left hand,
would aggressively rub my sensitive spots
underneath my red suit, on the gentle fabric.
Even these legs which I kept tightly closed in front of people...
Maybe due to the power of the high heels, my legs were open wide.
I was in a state where I couldn't control myself.
That is,
I couldn't help myself from becoming unraveled in such a place.
I think the red must have restored my lustful spirit.
From then on, I would wear red without thinking.
However, I always made sure that I wore white underwear.
Because if I did happen to wear red underwear as well,
I don't know what would happen to me.
Am I strange?
I am Miona.
Could you stick for my story for a little longer?
The act of a woman relieving her legs,
it is very much erotic.
Well, relieving them as I am with high heels...
That isn't something you see often.
For the mature woman I have become,
the way of folding one's legs to the side is the most suitable.
It sure is nice, isn't it.
Next, we shall raise a leg to a kneeling position.
Even if the user were to just be fooling around,
this position should quite excite the subject.
Also, as for position such as straighting your legs out like this...
Doesn't it helplessly provoke men?
This defenselessness might be the appeal.
Next is the excellent traditional Japanese pose.
There's the squatting position.
The intellectual individual can sit in this position without any worry.
This gap is extremely stimulating.
However, if one were to lift a leg like this...
Oh my, how mysterious.
Suddenly, the position changes to something highly enticing.
Finally, this promising pose of folding the legs.
However, unlike a childish girl arranging herself in such a position,
this is a pose for the mature woman tired from work and arriving home.
Please imagine sitting down like a duck would do.
Not being worried about the gazes of others, and the feeling of relief...
Truly, this is a treasure that isn't often seen.
Thank you for watching until the end.
This is Kisaragi Riona, the lady who becomes bold when red is worn.
Welcome home, darling.
Thanks for your work today.
How is this?
Darling...
If you want to have a better look at my panties,
feel free to lift up my skirt from behind.
Oh! Good morning, darling.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Um... Please don't stare at me...
It's embarrassing.
Darling, you said you wanted to see me
wearing something like this.
I went ahead and tried my best.
And, um,
also, there's a bonus...
Somehow, it ended up turning into something peculiar.
I was wondering if I should show you such a thing.
But I want you to work at the best of your abilities today,
so I'll show you.
Geez, don't do that!
Darling!
We don't have time!
You'll be late for work!
I work as a maid for a person who owns this mansion.
It seems that Master is very skilled in the making of of western maid costumes, which has made him famous.
For that reason, the costume that I wear is one he designed himself.
It's cute, that's why I liked it.
Liked it, until that day.
Several times before, I had noticed, but...
For instance, when I'm cleaning windows,
or making beds,
and when I'm mopping the floor,
I sense that someone is watching from behind.
However, I thought that it was just my imagination, and I brushed off the idea.
But one day,
while I was cleaning masters study,
several pictures fell out of a thick book.
When I went to pick them up...
That suspicion of someone watching me became clear.
I felt something stronger than anger...
Is this from when I accidentally took a nap on the sofa?
I was taken aback by the thought of Master seeing me in such embarrassing moments,
and I felt myself being overwhelmed by embarrassment rather than anger.
But what's more embarrassing is this ever so revealing costume made of leather for hot summers.
The chest is much like a bra, only with half the coverage,
and the skirt is so short that my t-back styled panties are clearly visible.
As for when I think about the photos that are going to be taken...
Naturally, I should feel that I don't want such things.
When I think "Master may be looking at me",
I actually feel a little flustered, and it's strange.
However, despite these events, I have yet to see my master's face.
I am Senou Asuka, 19 years of age, and I work as a nurse.
I am currently troubled by something.
At the hospital where I work, there is a questionable doctor.
He's normally a very good doctor.
However...
when my shift is over...
The doctor keeps me behind and, uh, well...
He does mischievous things to me.
So, let's have a physical health inspection.
But didn't we do that yesterday?
Please start.
Y-Yes...
That's right, unbutton and unzip yourself.
Let's relax a little.
By doing such things,
you can unwind from the stress of this job.
Yes...
Oh no, what do we have here?
It's not allowed for a nurse to wear a garter belt.
You might excite the patients.
Let's take it off right away.
I-I'm sorry.
Um...
With a normal one, I...
I get sweaty down there and it's no good.
That's why I have this on.
I'll be careful, so please let me wear this.
Then we can't have your precious breasts get sweaty, so lets take your bra off.
That's good, now don't you feel refreshed?
Now the only thing covering your body is one piece of clothing...
No, that's too embarrassing...
No, that's no good.
You have to take off the last piece and become completely exposed.
But sensei, I still have my nurse cap on...
Amazing! However,
you mustn't fully take off your panties.
Lets leave them there.
What?
This "nearly off" point is important, Senou-san.
Yes...
B-But... Sensei...
But what?
Um...
My nurse cap...
Nice to meet you, my name is Kannazuki Mai.
Forgive me for cutting to the chase. When a lady crouches,
like so,
do you feel that you may be able to peek at her panties?
However, that akin to the intellect of a child.
Please refrain from being opportunistic about women crouching.
That is why I am going to give a demonstration today. I hope you'll learn something.
Let us begin.
Are you set?
The highlight of when a lady crouches,
is where the calf and the thigh meet and create an abnormal shape.
To simplify things to diagrams, regard the size of the thigh as 2, and the calf as 1.
When crouched,
the thickness doesn't appear as 1 + 2 = 3.
It is always below 3.
This is because the body parts expand widthwise.
Therefore, such expenditure results in the power of such immaculate curvature.
For example,
this area of the thigh which changes shape is irresistible, isn't it?
It forms accordingly as a compression of the two parts.
The flow of the line of the normal thigh is ruined.
Next, if we are to lift up our knees like so,
other lines can be observed.
This excessively expanded calf
feels highly ugly,
and people like me become uncomfortable.
For a lady the likes of myself, the place that feels most unsightly is
right here, the line of the buttocks.
As the legs are split apart, the crevasse becomes greater.
I have some rather large buttocks, so the detail is drawn-out further.
What?
"While this is happening, what's going on in the front" you ask?
Uh, um... actually...
If we are to perk our hips out while crouching with legs open...
The buttocks compress together,
and the lips down there open accordingly...
And it becomes ready for some action.
I-I'm sorry, please excuse me.
Please! Don't tell Baron Masquerade about this...
Please keep it a secret...
What shall I do? For me to show my lustful side like this...