I...
I had anal sex...
I expected nothing less from the queen.
You had an anal orgasm.
It was a great start as a masochist.
N-No, I’m not.
But, don’t let your guard down.
The real mission of the queen is to put an end to love.
I don’t care about that.
It was your love that pulled out Rinko-chan’s
desire of becoming the queen.
You are loved and accepted by everybody.
That’s why you can notice someone’s hidden
desire and awaken her to her real self.
Huh?
Kotarou-kun asked me out. It's too ambitious for him.
But you hang around with me and...
...I don’t wanna hurt his feelings.
It’s not a real voice.
What?
Listen to what your body really says.
He asked me first to take a picture with him today.
He may be charmed by me.
Everybody calls me an Arisuga-kid,
but I have a nice feminine body.
I’ll let him know just how attractive
a pubescent female body is.
What do you mean?
Why can’t I talk to her?
You are the one who told me that...
...only Hinako-senpai could accept my love.
That’s why I went through the trouble of ditching
the lessons and studying by reading magazines.
Don’t waste my precious time.
Now is an important time for my sister...
...to morph into a masochistic queen.
That’s no answer, senpai.
First of all, don’t tell me what to do.
You're the same as my mom.
Geez... You put me in a bad mood.
I’m going home now.
It’s great, Rinko-chan.
It’s great to see a sadistic brightness on
your face when you despise someone.
You eyes are almost like the eyes of a queen.
But you need to know the heart of a slave.
Otherwise, you will never become a perfect queen.
“After-School Love Club”
Is sexual play an extension of love?
There is no accounting for love.
It’s more that we all have such a desire in our hearts.
That’s right. Love should be more enjoyable.
So...
Master, we are waiting for someone who can become
aware of our hidden sexual tendencies and set us free.
Masochistic training is a difficult
and important ritual in our lives.
We need someone who has good technique.
So, that’s what the After-School Mania Club is about.
When I become a female slave who can serve
independently, I can graduate from the club.
“After-School Love Club”
SubDESU-H Presents
“’After-School Mania Club’ I want something thick. The Animation”
I get tired from walking.
But I can’t ask for my ride
because I ditched the lessons.
“Collection 2 No Exit for the Spirit of the Mania!”
Wow, it stinks!
I guess the women’s restroom is awful...
...but the men’s restroom is worse than that.
It’s more than I expected.
It's more thrilling to be here than
to be at the park the other day.
I wanna fuck a high school girl who has a pretty
face, lily-white skin, and bristly hair down there!
No... Bristly hair...
Mine is not that thick.
What? Are you embarrassed?
We are girls.
Besides, I don’t think I have an embarrassing
skinny body. I’m confident with my body.
Kanami-san’s public hair was thick.
She trimmed her public hair neatly.
But Hinako-senpai’s public hair
is thicker than Kanami-san’s.
I want to learn about masochism with Hinako-senpai.
Huh?
You’re bold, Queen Rinko.
You’re bold enough to pee at the men’s
restroom without an attendant.
W-Wait, no.
Stop it.
I put a collar on the school’s
idol and treat her like a bitch.
I feel so good.
No.
Rinko, you don’t have any right to say no to me.
Don’t you forget what you’ve done to my sister?
I don’t mind showing pictures of
you in the restroom to your mom.
N-No.
Well then...
Oh, good timing.
S-Shindo-senpai.
No, Rinko, Rinko-chan?
I’ve waited for you, Kazumi.
I don’t recall letting you address me like that.
If you get cocky, I’ll hit you.
Humph.
I’m telling you I’m gonna hit you...
...h-hit you...
I-I’m sorry, master.
I thought you were a strong opponent
to tuck your shirt into your bloomers.
I was told to do this...
If I were you, I would show off...
...such a big butt like this.
I don’t like bloomers.
I don’t like the feeling of them riding up.
I’m sorry I forced you to wear something you don’t like.
N-No, I don’t mean that.
I’m just joking. I really like bloomers.
I wear them when I play basketball.
You haven’t greeted me yet, kitty.
I don’t want to do it here.
Shut up!
You ARE a bitch.
You have no right to refuse me.
Kazumi.
Yes, master.
Kazumi, if you don’t do it right, I’ll punish you.
I am disillusioned with the idol
wearing side-tied G-string.
Kotarou-senpai, you told me that a side-tied
G-string is a basic item for perverted girls.
Don't wear it out.
Geez.
None of your impudence, you bitch!
You are pampered by everyone and so full of yourself.
But you are nothing but a bitch in front of me.
No way.
I don’t want to be a dog!
Shut up!
You're not a girl with that collar around your neck.
You're a bitch that thinks only about master’s orders.
Bitch, bitch, bitch!
Kotarou-senpai, please don’t call me a bitch.
I'm... I’m gonna feel miserable.
Don’t call my name.
Dogs have their own language. Right?
If I showed pictures of you peeing to your mom,
she would be happy and say,
“Thank you for making a woman out of my daughter.”
W-Woof.
I can’t hear you.
Louder!
Woof.
That’s it.
My sweet bitch.
Are you ready to accept my love?
Woof.
Yes, I know.
I’m totally your bitch.
I promise you to serve you for the rest of my life.
Thank you for keeping me
company today, Onee-chan.
I found a place to walk around on a date
and bought the right clothes to wear.
I’m gonna knock Kotarou-kun out
with my sex appeal tomorrow.
Onee-chan, did you look at my bloomers?
Huh? No, I didn’t.
Is it sexy that I’m in bloomers?
Misao-san said to me that it was sexy that
cute girls like me put on bloomers.
What do you think?
Did you see it? Size M is not the size S
specified by Arisubara women’s high school.
In other words...
It's against the school rule.
Anna’s butt is against the school rule.
A woman inside of Anna-chan wants to come out.
I feel embarrassed being stared at.
Your size is no longer S.
Don’t check between my legs.
I had no choice. My butt always hung out of S size bloomers.
Anna, if you take a bath, do it quickly.
Yeees!
Oh no.
Mom... My friend is still here.
Anna-chan.
Can I take a bath with you?
I’m very lucky as a 'Maniac' that
I can take an anal virginity.
I-I’m embarrassed.
You don’t need to have any sense of shame.
If you say something annoying to me,
I’m gonna give you an enema.
No, m-master. I’m sorry.
Crap... Crap... I don’t wanna do it.
Oh, look who’s talking!
You forced my sister to take a
crap and your pussy got wet.
No, that’s not...
Are you saying that master said something wrong?
N-No... Everything master said is right.
I’m a stupid dog.
I got horny by giving your sister an enema
and forcing her to take a crap. I’m a pervert.
Finally, you realized what you are.
Woof, thank you very much.
Well, this is your reward.
Does it feel good?
I’m not sure, but I feel your penis moving inside of my anus.
I’m happy.
It’s big. Master’s is big.
I-I wanna pee.
Kazumi, I’ll punish you if you pee now.
Yes, I’ll hold it, master.
Her adolescent body always gives off a feminine scent
as a signal that she's ready to lose her virginity.
Onee-chan, take her virginity.
Anna-chan.
For a grown-up woman, I think taking care
of her appearance is not good enough.
Huh?
A sophisticated woman needs to clean
the inside of her body as well.
I’ll tell you later.
What? Oh, I know what it is. It’s an enema.
Is it a deep cleansing enema?
It’s an embarrassing thing to put into my butt.
It’s not embarrassing at all.
Everybody uses it.
No way. Besides, I don’t need it
because I’m not constipated.
Look, I do this exercise every
night before I go to bed.
It’s said this prevents constipation.
Misao-san said my pussy is big.
That means I have a nice pussy.
In my case, when a man’s penis is inserted into me,
my pussy will tighten around it at three points. Let's see...
Can I stop talking about this because
I’m too shy to continue?
One, two.
What’s wrong, big sis?
Anna-chan, Kotarou may want to try anal sex with you.
What? It’s too early for me to have sex.
But if he wants, I’ll...
Oh, that’s why you wanna give me an enema?
Do I need to clean my anus beforehand?
It’s not just an enema.
Oh, no.
I’ll clean your anus.
Please stop, master.
I'm still a virgin.
The bitch doesn’t need a hymen.
No, master. I want to give away
my virginity romantically.
You mean, erotically?
I-It hurts, master.
It may hurt you now, but it’ll feel better soon.
It hurts! It hurts!
No, her face’s gonna hit my pussy.
Master, if you move so fast, I-I...
Does it feel good? I know it.
Rinko is a masochistic pervert.
My pussy’s gonna be broken.
I won’t break it.
I’ll let you entertain me more and more.
I’ll do anything for you, master.
I’m almost coming, Onee-chan,
Onee-chan, you should be almost there by now.
If you raise your voice, your mom can hear you.
Well...
It feels cold!
A queen will be born within my sister soon.
Sleep-learning should work well...
...because learning through experience
is the best way for women.
I can’t hold it any longer.
The more you hold it, the better it
feels when your crap comes out.
B-But...
So, let’s pee before you do a crap.
Oh, I’m excited thinking of my sister’s bright future.
I'm... I’m gonna pour my sperm into your pussy, Rinko.
Take it with gratitude.
Yes, I will.
Please give it to me.
May I pee now, master?
Pee on Rinko’s face.
This is a baptism.
It’s coming out!
I feel master’s sperm coming out of his penis.
His hot sperm is filling my insides!
“No Exit for the Spirit of the Mania!”
Tanshii koto jamerarenai
I can’t stop doing something fun.
boku wa sukoshi oshiete ageru, afurereru egao no himitsu, koko ni aru kara
I’ll tell you a little about the secret of my bright smile, because it's right here.
tsuragi wa otou, fuue agetou
When I feel down, and feel uneasy
kigaeshitara, hajimeyou
We'll get started after I change my clothes
mail wo okuri, denwa de warattari, to
With sending emails and laughing over the phone,
kore kara ga isogashii
From now on it'll be busy
tomare ni natta ni naranai you ni ne
Make sure nobody will stop us.
ai mo omoi ni deteru. Inochikare de itai, watashi tacheru kisetsu, motto mankitsu shiraii
In the city where I picture myself as falling in love, our season is shining.
Daremo waramitenai
Don’t you wanna enjoy yourselves more?
okiniri no rouge
No one's seen my favorite rouge yet.
soutto kagami ni mukatte, egao wo nagekakeru
I gently smile at the mirror.
Yume miru koto jamerarenai
I can’t stop dreaming.
nee, isshoni eegai kekirai
Don’t you wanna draw together?
oosaro ni, nanairo no niji, kagayaki tachitta
A seven-colored rainbow shone brightly in the sky.
Yume miru koto jamerarenai
I can't stop dreaming
nee, isshoni eegai kekirai
Don’t you wanna draw together?
oosaro ni, nanairo no niji, kagayaki tachitta
A seven-colored rainbow shone brightly in the sky.