I really enjoyed the meal.
Oh, the pleasure was mine.
No.. you can’t!
Mama...
If you look at me like that... I ...
Only the mouth.
Bijukubo
Part 2
Translation by SubDesu-H
I don’t have any intention to make Mama cry.
But the devil inside me... I’m trying to take away the devil inside me for Mama.
I’m sorry Mama, but I’m going to cum.
Good bye, I’m going to cum.
Mama...
You’re like a baby Youhei-kun.
I’m always like a baby in front of Mama.
Hey, it's about time...
Mama... I’m going to move.
No.. if you move now..
Amazing, deeper! Youhei is thrusting me.
Mama.
Mama can you see it?
Mama’s is swallowing mine and being spread wide.
I want Mama to see it.
Youhei’s is...
Look at it.
Mama’s juice is flowing out and shaking.
Your clit got big.
Don’t use your hand, I don’t want to cum with your hand, I want to with your dick.
Mama....
Wow amazing!
Youhei’s so hard.
I’m going to cum Mama.
Release it, you can release it inside.
You can release it inside.
I’m going to fall.
So you went to that woman's place.
No it's not like..  it's...
Ikue-san had trouble setting up her computer.
So...
Ikue-san...
I see, even though Fumika and I told you, you’re still supporting that woman.
No I'm not, I have no intention like that.
Let's see.
You wanted to have a young master's life style in that place than here right?
No way...
Mom...
I’m worried about you.
I know that you think about me.
No you don’t understand.
You wouldn't have gone to that woman if you understood.
uhm..
It means... I’m worried so much.
Mom, maybe you...
What?
Got jealous?
No that's wrong...
You is a nice guy but you don't know about society.
You’re nice bait from the eyes of that witch.
Do you understand? You’re nice bait.
Those worries mean, your worrying about me as a man right?
Yes, I can’t look for another man.
It's how you desired, I can only look at you.
I’m happy that Mom is crazy for me.
I’m a bad boy that made Mom worry so much.
Yes, you’re really a bad boy You.
I’m happy that I'm in such a relationship with my beautiful mom.
Don’t say such things.
Switch off the lights.
Didn’t you say that we can do it in a bright place?
Yes I did but...
Please.
Your dick has grown up big.
It was so tiny before.
Mom...
Aside from that..
What is it?
Tell me what you really want.
Mom...
You never made himself clear since you were small.
Mom.. don’t tease me.
You know, I want yours already.
Don’t make a woman say things to humiliate herself.
Mom..
I want mom to do a tit-fuck.
Okay.
Is it ok like this?
Oh, no one requested this among the men you’ve gone out with?
No.
Anyway, is this alright?
Really?
Yes.
Oh that means among the men you’ve gone out with, no one understands you.
Ouch! You...
I knew it, I’m the only one that understands Mom.
You, don’t get carried away or else I...
Sorry, I got carried away.
You, you’re always like that since you were small.
Your desire to monopolize was strong and you were always saying.
“hey Mom, hey Mom, hey Mom”
I thought it would be hard if you did that to a woman.
Hey let's continue.
Ok Mom?
How is it You?
It's so good.
Why are you using formal words?
I’m going to cum Mom.
It's not my mouth where you should cum.
You, do it.
Mom, you’re all wet.
And your clitoris is already big even though I haven't touched it.
That’s...
I get it! You got wet while licking me.
Yes... so hurry.
You want mine?
You’re lewd Mom.
No way...
Don’t worry, no matter how perverted mom is, you’re mine.
The clitoris got bigger.
You can be perverted in front of me.
I’ll lick it.
Finally you moaned.
You, don’t lick it so suddenly.
No..
Don’t lick that hard.
Too good.
I’m embarrassed.
No…
No no no.
No I said!
No...!
I’m cumming, I'm cumming!!
Your drinking it.
You is drinking it.
It's too early to feel good.
Not yet.
Don’t move yet.
If you move so much, you’ll cum soon right?
But....
Mom will make you feel good.
Do you want to move more?
But not yet.
Mom.
I’ll move a little bit.
You still can’t be satisfied right?
No you can’t.
You must do what I say.
I can’t hold it if it's like that.
I won’t release it yet so feel it more.
If you thrust like that I’ll...
You..
The boobs, touch my boobs too.
Mom also likes it rough eh?
I like it rough.
But if I break, You will...
It's ok, Mom is only mine right?
You only do this for me right?
You ..You...You...
I love you You, I love you.
I love you too Mom.
Oh my, I’m going to cum.
Doing it from top, like a kid, she’s so busy.
Sis.
Sis...
Hey Sis.
What?
Uhm... it's.
Your only doing it with Mom.
Hey... that’s...
Sis.
How unfair of you, you’re always doing it to Kaho-san.
You’re more passionate when doing Kaho-san than when your with me.
That's not true.
Kaho-san said she is at war with that woman so she’ll use any method.
But really, she only wanted monopolize You-chan.
I even got nervous and confessed to you in that stupid situation.
Kaho-san is always wild and you’re the one seeking her.
I thought it was unfair.
You understand what I’m trying to say right?
You-chan is always doing it with Kaho-san.
I’m sorry.
I think of you two as equals.
And I’m sorry if I made you feel sad.
No it's ok, I’m satisfied being held by you.
I feel it with You-chan’s kiss.
You’re licking mine.
Wait, don’t smell it.
It's because Sis is so perverted and spreading your smell.
You-chan’s also smells so perverted.
I can't take it.
Sis, it's too intense.
But me too.
No... You-chan, don’t put it in so suddenly.
You-chan’s semen is so smelly.
My pussy is being stirred by You-chan’s.
Please grab my boobs, squeeze them.
You-chan’s...You-chan’s..  ..
I love You-chan’s dick.
Sis, I’m going to cum.
I’ll release it inside until it overflows.
Give it to me, I want You-chan’s baby milk.
It's ok You-chan, you can release it inside.
You can release it inside me.
Something has changed.
I hope it’s like this everyday.
You, I won.
So it’s my turn today.
Don’t just declare that you’re the winner.
How shameful you are, being with a man, with that 40 year old dusty uterus?
You’re the same as me, your also 40 right?
I’m just not serious playing with men.
I don’t want to be like them, even how a woman’s sexual desire is strong at around 40.
Right You-chan?
Righ You-chan? Right?
Sis, it hurts.
Hey Fumika, why are you cutting ahead?
You’re the one who lost at first.
Maybe you’re the legendary Fainting Queen?
Che.
Fumika-chan, weren't you taught not to be unfair?
I see, you’ve become a stupid girl being with this stupid woman.
Shut up, man drought.
Oh, I smell a brother complex.
Why is it?
What!?
Ikue! You called me a stupid just now right?!
What’s wrong with calling stupid people stupid?
You’re the one who is stupid, you idiot!
Youhei, who’s the one you’re going to choose?
Please give me a break