W
~ Angels’ Private Lessons ~
Air Mix
MegaPile
It’s dinner time
Ladies
Mizuo-senpai’s Sex in the Restroom
Hey, how did you manage to sneak out here?
I told them I had to use the restroom.
That’s honest.
That part of you... is so cute.
Was that your first kiss?
Y-Yes.
How amazing.
Just a kiss made you hard?
You sure are a horn-dog...
B-But...
Hey, Tomohisa-kun...
Fel... la... ti... o...
Want me to do it for you?
You’ve never had a girl lick your dick before, have you?
I’ll let you cum inside my mouth.
Th-Thanks.
You’re a lively one...
Looks like you’re already about to burst.
Look how much precum there is.
Just sit tight.
I’ll get your dick all slobbery with my drool.
This should do it.
Now your dick is all wet.
S-Senpai...
Senpai... Mizuo-senpai...
Look, Tomohisa-kun?
My butthole and my pussy...
Which would you prefer?
You can fuck up either one as much as you want.
Because everything belongs to you.
It’s cumming!
How nice, I didn’t get any on my uniform.
That would be bad if I got my uniform cummy - it would stain.
I’m sorry.
I couldn’t hold myself back.
Next time you cum, make sure it’s in my mouth.
I’ll swallow it all for you.
That was a lot.
You wanted me to swallow all of this?
Well, um...
Come on, watch...
There’s so much of it.
Aren’t you masturbating regularly?
Well, um...
Hey, the semen on my face... take it off.
Okay.
You sure are nice.
I’ll lick it off for you.
You’re even bigger than last time.
This time, I want you to thrust hard into my throat with this huge dick.
Thrust hard?
You don’t need to hold back.
Grab my head and push your hips hard.
Imagine my mouth is my pussy.
W-Wow...
Come on, Tomohisa-kun...
My tits and my pussy, you can do whatever you want.
Senpai...
Doesn’t it feel great?
Now, come closer.
Tomohisa-kun.
Mizuo-senpai!
Fluids are coming up from deep in my throat, mixing with his precum...
What sounds!
Senpai, are you choking?
Yes, I am. But I like that.
I love the sensation of it hitting the back of my throat.
You’re so hard.
You’re about to cum again?
Hey... Tomohisa-kun... more... go deeper... into my throat...
Senpai!
Your mouth is making me so slippery.
I can’t hold back...
Then cum! Deep inside my throat!
I want a direct hit of your cum!
It’s cumming!
No, don’t!
It’s swirling around inside my mouth.
Licking it directly makes you cum too soon.
Mizuo-senpai!
Senpai...
No, you don’t. Not yet.
Senpai!
I’m c-
Not yet, don’t cum.
Show some restraint.
Good boy.
Just hold back a little longer.
After school is over, I’ll drink it all up.
You held back pretty well.
Now you can let it all out.
Let it out inside me.
Put it in.
See? Your dick is getting buried in my naughty place.
Be sure to get a good look. It’s completely buried.
You’re cumming already?
Your semen...
Wow!
His semen is splashing in my uterus!
Wow... this feels great.
My brain is throbbing.
Wow!
Senpai!
I can’t stop cumming!
My insides... are all fucked up...
Amazing.
Just from holding it in all day, you’ve built up so much.
If you held back for a whole week...
Hey, let’s have you hold back for a week before we have sex again.
Okay, Tomohisa-kun?
Sex with Shibua-san
I’m gonna cum soon, Shibuya.
Hey, wait a minute, Maruki-kun.
Hey...
I’ll suck it all up inside.
Okay?
Don’t answer with THAT body part.
What?
You can tweak it.
But I've barely even spoken to you, Shibuya-san.
Doesn’t that make you even more turned on?
Yeah...
For some reason... you’re already sopping wet.
That’s because I’m really turned on.
Oh... you sure are good... Tanabe-kun...
Hey... Tanabe-kun, I want to touch yours too.
Let’s trade places.
Wow!
It’s so stiff already.
Sorry...
Oh, please. Don’t apologize.
Shibuya-san?
Doesn’t this feel surprisingly good?
Wow!
You’re getting even bigger.
I didn’t know...
Tanabe-kun, I had no idea your dick was this big.
Wa... stop! Stop!
Are you gonna cum?
Wait. Don’t cum yet.
You can cum inside.
So cum inside me, please.
It’s about to burst!
Just a bit more... hold on.
Wow!
I’m almost... also...
Shibuya... your hand... let go...
My pussy... I want you... to taste it more...
Your dick is so hot...
You’re so wonderful.
I... I’m at my limit...
Then, I’ll... let go... so cum lots!
All the way inside! It’s pouring in!
Tanabe-kun, that was very good.
Your cum... are you finished?
Yeah... I think...
But you’re still hard.
You can cum as many times as you want.
Keep moving.
Don’t! Not so rough... then I’ll... I’ll cum too!
Tanabe-kun... that’s so much...
You’re still so big.
Hey... wanna come over to my house?
Can I?
I’ll make sure... to let you pour all you've got left inside me.
My naughty experience with Mizuo-senpai in the bath.
Tomohisa-kun, I’ll wash your clothes for you.
Thank you.
Did that feel good?
Senpai...
Lift up your hips and sit on my knees.
Like this?
Think of it like a submarine periscope and raise it a little higher, okay?
Okay.
You can put all your weight on me.
Sorry if I’m too heavy.
Senpai... that feels... good...
It’s throbbing in my mouth. Are you gonna cum soon?
Senpai...
If you’re that rough, I’ll...
It’s okay. Cum.
It’s in the bath, so don’t hold back. Cum as much as you like.
I can’t...
Wow!
It’s so thick!
You’ve been holding back, I see.
W-Well...
Just stay like that.
You’re still so stiff.
And I am, too... from rubbing...
Your dick is amazing.
It’s so thick.
Senpai... you’re so slippery.
You wanna put your dick in my slippery place?
You can let it all out inside me, okay?
It’s in!
I feel so full... inside...
Senpai...
Wow...
Me too... I feel... so good...
Oh no. I’m... cumming!
I’m cumming!
Sorry... I came without you.
You can fuck me hard and deep.
Put it in.
So hard!
Tomohisa-kun... wow!
Your dick...
It’s so deep... and hot... hitting...
My pussy...
It’s like it’s on fire...
Harder! Harder!
I... I’m gonna cum again... cum again...
Let’s cum together... let’s cum together.
I’m cumming... cumming!
Surprise sex with Kirishima-san.
Kirishima-san...
Don’t get the wrong idea.
If you don’t make me feel good... I’ll stop right away.
Okay...
Hey, Tsuchiya, don’t breathe on it like that.
It tickles.
Hey, don’t stare at it.
Kirishima-san, you’re soaked.
Idiot.
Hurry... lick it.
Oh no...
You’re just stupid Tsuchiya... but you’re really good with your tongue...
It’s so deep.
I’m being licked all the way inside!
Kirishima-san, don’t forget mine!
Jeez! Recently you’ve gotten a bit cocky.
Fine, I’ll suck it, okay?
This feels even better than usual...
In this position...
It’s so embarrassing...
Oh no...
I can’t stop my body.
Tsuchiya’s dick... it’s so delicious and gets me off.
Kirishima-san! I’m almost...
Jeez!
Why’re you cumming?
I haven’t cum yet!
How erotic.
This is it... it’s more intense than before...
I gave you just a little juice.
Doesn’t it work wonders?
All it takes is a little stimulation...
And you’ll cum.
Oh no!
Not me too... I’m gonna cum!
Wait a minute!
You’d better let him put it in, or else bad things will happen.
Wow! It’s so hot!
Tsuchiya’s hot dick is going inside me.
Not so suddenly! Idiot!
Tsuchiya!
This feels great!
It’s so hot... filling me up!
It’s never been this good before.
I think... I’m a pervert.
I’m cumming!
I’m sorry. Did you get too hot?
Fucking Mizuo-senpai like we’re a real couple.
I’ll wipe off your body, so come on out.
Face me.
Do you want to finish what we started earlier?
So hot.
It’s been a while, how about you let me deep throat you?
Senpai...
Don’t hold back. Thrust it deep.
Move your hips as hard as you want.
Senpai... your mouth... it’s sucking so hard...
Did that feel good?
Yes... Senpai, did that hurt you?
It felt very good hitting the back of my throat.
Fuck my throat harder this time.
Senpai... your mouth... it’s so wet and slippery...
I... I can’t... hold... back...
Then cum.
Cum deep in my throat - shoot it all out.
It’s cumming...
Do you feel better, Tomohisa-kun?
There’s not much room in here, but let’s go ahead and try.
Sure... then I’ll try hard... to cum even though it’s small.
Tomohisa-... kun?
Right now?
Wow...
So hot!
You overheated in the tub, didn’t you?
Tomohisa-kun, you can do with me as you please.
Oh... wow...
So big!
It’s so big!
You shouldn’t yell so loud...
But it’s so... rough... and awesome...
It’s so deep... hitting... all the way inside.
Wow!
You’re so tight!
I... think I’m gonna... cum soon...
You’re getting hotter in me.
Keep going. Cum inside me!
Oh no, I’m cumming! I’m cumming too!
T-Tomohisa-kun... Did that... feel good?
To be released July 27th, 2012