Yes! Yes!
SubDESU-H.net
Well!
That Sugita-kun, where did he go to get a snow cone?
Yakisoba
Snow cones
What’s that? Her voice sounds strange.
Yes. Oh yes.
It’s so thick… it’s so deep inside me.
Harder… Get bigger and harder.
W-Wait, what the hell are you doing?
Hanazono-san!
So hot!
It’s throbbing.
Am I right?
M-Me too! I’m gonna cum. I’m cumming!
Oops.
Excuse me.
So this living vibrator belonged to you, eh?
L-Living vibrator?
What the hell are you saying?!
Sally, please be a replacement vibrator.
Understood, my lady.
Well then, have your way with me.
B-But…
No…
Stop it… no…
Your mouth says no, but your nipples are pretty stiff.
N-No…
The truth is, you want them touched more, right?
No. No, not there.
Not there, don’t tweak it so hard…
Let me go…
Hanazono-san, not you too…
See? She’s having fun too.
So move your hips more.
No more!
Not in front of Sugita-kun.
This girl is too slutty!
Izumi, you’re a girl but you’re so wet.
Don’t! I’ll cum.
Yes, please let me make you cum.
No… Not in front of everyone!
Label: Sugita Hinoki
I’m a heroine!
Save me, Pollinic Girls!
No…
Why?
I’m still not a full Pollinic Girl yet.
No. I, Sugita Hinoki, am weak in both holes.
Don’t lick so hard.
W-Wait, this is too much. Don’t put me in this position!
No!
Not my butt too!
Sally!
Do something about this!
I apologize, my lady.
But right now, I can’t…
I am preoccupied… with such wonderful feelings…
Hanazono-san! This is making everything a big mess!
W-Well, Sugita-kun, it was your fault… for fucking another girl…
If you’re gonna fuck someone… you should fuck me.
Me too… I’m gonna cum.
Good. Then cum lots.
I’ll cum… too…
I’m cumming!
Everyone… everyone… let’s cum together!
SubDESU-H Presents
Sorry for the wait!
「How many girls have you fucked?」
The Pollinic Girls Attack is about to begin!
Wow… so many Pollinic Girls.
With this, I suppose I won’t be able to go outside for a while.
Well then, that thing you were telling me about...
Let’s try it.
“That”?
You really want to do it?
I’m embarrassed, darling.
Must we… do this? Can’t I wear bottoms?
Nudity is natural for humans.
Alice, you should take it all off.
B-But, I must wear at least one bit of cloth.
Then don’t hide your bottom. Let me see.
W-Well…
So pretty, Alice.
Inside the parlor is bad enough, but being dressed like this at midday?
This really is perverted.
Good.
Then let’s enjoy naked life in our house from now on.
From now on?
Your wife is also naked?!
My husband, whom I just married this spring, is a go-getting business man.
But at home, he loves nudity.
He’s a bit obsessed.
For our honeymoon, we spent the whole time naked on a deserted island,
1 month ago
so I knew what I was in for.
Then, Alice, masturbate for me.
Masturbate out here?
That's embarrassing!
What are you saying?
Being naked outside and masturbating… usually we can’t do that.
Come on, hurry, hurry.
This was my special honeymoon and I wanted to please my darling.
So…
I’m doing something so naughty.
I’m buck naked outside, masturbating, having my video taken.
Very nice, Alice.
Let’s watch this at home later.
N-No! I don’t want to!
Just this time.
This is the only time I’ll do things like this.
Your body is throbbing. You’re about to cum.
Then I’ll get a close up of you.
Not so close, please.
No… no!
I’m more sensitive than usual!
In the end, after we came back from our honeymoon, we still continued our naked life.
It was a bit too intense for a modest person like me.
Alice… I’m about to cum.
Darling! Darling! Darling!
Cum lots, cum lots!
I’m almost there!
Naturally, the very next day, our naked life continued.
D-Darling… why am I dressed like this?
You said you were embarrassed to wear nothing at all, so I got this especially for you.
But isn’t this… sort of… more embarrassing than complete nudity?
And besides…
Ah yes, this happens every morning.
But we did so much last night.
You’re just so pretty and sexy that it gets hard.
Oh no...
Come on, let me bury it in you fast, or it’ll be like this all day.
Okay.
Ew. Wow. He already smells so sexy.
Yes, yes.
Just like that.
Since first thing this morning, I’ve been naked and sucking his dick.
I’m embarrassed, but I wonder why… I’m starting to get excited.
No, no, don’t stop midway.
Okay.
No, he’s tweaking my pussy with his toe.
Alice, you’re soaking wet.
Don’t say that.
It’s your fault that I’m becoming a whorish wife.
Wow. So much… cum…
Oh no, even my apron is all soggy.
Then take it all off and be naked.
B-But…
I’m embarrassed to be naked all the time.
That’s it. I’ve just got a great idea.
Oh no! What are you doing?
I found a solution.
To satisfy your desire to wear clothes and my desire to take them off.
N-No. Does this mean… just from having sex…
But you don’t dislike this, right, Alice?
Well… well… Because… Darling…
I’m so happy, I’ll cum.
I can’t hold back.
Oh no, it’s going deeper.
Your dick is thrusting so deep.
Darling!
It’s been so many times, but your dick is still so hot and hard and so sexy.
Alice, you’re also so soggy, hot, and so sexy!
No, don’t look!
I’m so full of you, Darling!
My pussy is dripping so much naughty juice.
Oh no… I… I…
I’ll… again…
No… no…
Please, close the curtains.
If we keep them open… the neighbors will see everything.
But you need to absorb sunlight through your skin to get vitamin D.
I don’t need any vitamin D right now!
Alice, I guess you would prefer semen.
N-No.
I… I've already had enough semen.
I’m all full.
Alice, I want everyone to see how naughty you are.
No... stop it!
I’m embarrassed!
Don’t watch!
Don’t watch me being slutty!
Oh, you’re getting tighter. I’m gonna cum.
Darling, please, cum quickly!
I’m almost… oh no…
Oh… I really can’t go on…
If we do this anymore, I’ll lose my mind!
Alice, how does the semen-shirt feel?
Yeah… it really does feel like a shirt.
So warm, soft, and comfortable.
So in the end, I came to like naked life.
And that’s my story.
"The Pollinic Girls Attack"
Next, I’m cumming… while wearing my uniform…
No!
Oh, customer, I apologize.
But I… I can’t…
Sign: Today’s pollen forecast
And continuing with the day’s pollen forecast,
both the temperature and the pollen count will rise this afternoon.
Sugita pollen and Hinoki pollen in particular will be in large quantities.
Those with allergies should wear a mask when going outside.
Otsumami
TL Note: "appetizer", also a pun on the name  “Mami”
Ew.
Wow.
The entire city smells like sex.
Oh… I’m almost…
My pollen mask is all wet.
That’s why you should have taken your allergy pills, Mami.
Sorry. I underestimated the power of the Pollinic Girls.
You can’t hold back, can you?
Yes… I don’t think I can.
I need to at least sneak away somewhere to change my mask.
Alligator Garden
Okay, I understand. Let’s cut through the park.
This is how it ended up.
Come on, raise your pelvis more.
Okay.
Okay, Mami-chan, I’m changing your mask for you.
I-Idiot.
Having your sensitive areas touched outside…
Doesn’t it feel good?
Wh-Why are you taking my top off too?
Before putting on your mask, I’ll clean you off.
Your whole body is wet.
No! That tickles! Stop!
I’ve always wanted to do this.
Darling…
Not on a park bench… I’m embarrassed.
You’re allergic to pollen so this is ordinary.
No, no.
Not again… the Pollinic Girls are coming to us.
That’s because you smell really sexy.
And you’re so wet.
Oh no, oh no!
Please, let me go!
Hurry… put on… put on my mask!
Sure. I think it’s about time.
Ta-dah!
A special mask with a beaded-tampon!
Wh-What is that thing?
That’s not a tampon!
Well, well, if we close it off, you’ll be okay.
Wait, stop!
Okay, just relax.
So big!
No…
Oh?
It’s not in yet.
No, stop it!
It’s… making me… so sensitive…
What?
Are you saying you like it?
No! Don’t!
It’s making me throb!
It’s so deep!
It’s so deep… making me crazy…
No… I’m gonna cum!
My pussy is so sticky…
Your new mask got all wet.
I don’t care.
Please, I want you!
Let’s fuck.
Really?
Everyone is watching us.
Here? Outside?
In the park?
In front of everyone, you’ll do real live sex?
No way… I…
I’m getting excited!
Um… you see…
I want to have live sex in front of everyone.
I want everyone to see how to make a baby.
Mami!
See? In one thrust, I got it all in.
Darling, fill me up!
Your dick, fill me up with violent thrusts!
A-Awesome.
This is the first time it’s felt this good.
Oh, yes, so good!
The dripping is making my brain melt.
Please. More, more, more, more!
Mami, everyone is watching.
Watching us fuck.
Oh yes. Darling, I love it!
This is great… I love my pussy…
And boobs… everything!
Mami, you are so naughty. I had no idea.
I’m so sorry. I’m sorry your wife is a whore!
Oh no, oh no!
I’m losing it!
No, no, not again… my boobs… my boobs…
If you tweak my nipples so hard… I’ll go…
Oh, darling, yes!
Fuck me up. I don’t mind.
I love you.
I love your cock, your dick.
Mami, your pussy is squeezing me. you’re about to cum, aren’t you?
My pussy is so wet. It’s throbbing. It’s gonna cum!
I’m gonna cum… I’m about to cum!
I’m cumming… Mami!
Fill me up!
Hurry, fill me with your milk!
Deep inside. Inside my uterus. Give me so much I’ll get a baby!
I’m gonna… let’s cum together… together… together…
So much… So much semen came out.
Then I’ll get pregnant…
M-Mami!
Wake up!
Mami!
The drugs are out.
And now I’m…
Oh dear, too much pollen?
Help me!
Pollinic Boys are cute too.
What should I do?
Mami!
I suppose having a pollen allergy can be fun.
No, not there!