www.SubDESU-H.net
Reiji-kun.
When we grow up,
make sure you take me as your bride, okay?
Good morning, Reiji-sama!
Yes, I'm going to take it now.
It's my turn next.
From this day on, Reiji-sama will be supervising the Kamiyama conglomerate.
He is now the master of the Kamiyama house.
W
Harem Time
Harem Time!
「Thank you for waiting, Master」
Thank you for waiting, Master!
Eh?!
Satou Reiji-sama, you will be the master of the Kamiyama house as of today.
W-wait a minute!
Why am I going to be...?
Your mother was the mistress of the house's former master.
There are no legal male heirs other than you who can inherit this position.
No way...
I just can't suddenly take the responsibility of a conglomerate.
Then please create a successor as soon as possible.
Your legal wife will be decided after that,
and then will be officially accepted as a member of the house.
In any case, we have gathered a few girls that would suit your tastes.
Why would you know my tastes?
That's as a result of our preliminary investigation.
Well then, everyone...
Reiji-sama, please come over here.
W-Wait... I haven't agreed to inherit the title.
My, you shouldn't disgrace a woman that way.
W-Wait...!
Please relax, Reiji-sama.
No way!
Oh, it's wonderful!
And it's big!
Please leave everything to us!
We'll make it a pleasurable experience for you!
Reiji-sama, use my boobs!
Amazing!
Your cock is getting bigger and bigger.
I'm glad you’re getting turned on!
This feels great.
A secretion is coming out from the tip.
Your nipple is getting harder.
It’s cute, Reiji-sama.
I'm already...
It looks really yummy.
H-Hey, that's not good!
I'll be taking this now.
No, it's about to come out!
Oh, no! I-It's going to...!
Wow! It released this much!
It's wonderful!
Don't... suck on it like that.
This is really great.
Its taste and smell are the best.
Let us have a taste of it a little longer.
I just came earlier.
It's just the beginning, Reiji-sama.
Well then, I'll be the first one to take Reiji-sama's cock.
Are you seriously going to use that, too?
It's big!
It's constantly kissing my womb.
So this the cock of the master of the Kamiyama house.
It's amazing!
It's going deep inside!
Wow!
My cock's being squeezed inside. It feels good!
I'm... I'm about to...!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!
Reiji-sama, please insert it into my pussy next.
If this is it, then I'll just do it all the way!
It's coming in and out.
A-Amazing.
It's amazing!
Your cock's amazing!
No fair! I wanna do it, too!
Reiji-sama's cock is stirring up my insides!
Please, give me your cum!
Make sure to... fill it up... inside!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
Reiji-sama's semen is coming out.
My insides are getting filled up!
Reiji-sama!
Whatever happens...
I'll make sure to... always remain horny for you!
Please make me all sticky!
No...
Not my...
Not my nipples!
If you suck them now, I'll...
Your pussy's really tight.
I'll really become pregnant with this.
We can do this with Reiji-sama's cock, right?
Wow!
Reiji-sama!
Release it!
Release it all!
Please release everything!
Make me pregnant by cumming in my pussy!
Oh no, I'm going to cum a lot!
To make everyone cum like that...
As expected of Reiji-sama.
You're on a completely different level.
Sorry if this came late.
I'm Kisaragi Alice.
I'm currently one of your legal wife candidates.
Eh? But even if you are a legal wife candidate...
That's right, Reiji-sama.
All of us want to serve you.
Please, I want to bear, your child.
Please, please do what you want more.
Please make a mess of me more!
This is amazing!
My mind's going blank!
I'm cumming!!
I'm about to cum!
Me too. I'm also, going to cum.
Let's, let's cum together!
Reiji-sama!
I'll become your legal wife,
and create the next perfect successor, okay?
W-well... It was great and all for you to do this for me, but...
Yes?
I already have someone I like.
That's why, umm... I'm sorry.
Wait, Junko-nee. This wasn't what we agreed on!"
If that's the case, then we'll just have to have sex until you forget about that girl!
What?!
A girl that has already captured Reiji-sama's heart...
This is something that's worth looking into.
Prepare yourself, Reiji-sama!
Wait, I can't... I really can't do it anymore!
Hey, wait... ah!
Take this!
Harem time!
Hiraizumi-senpai.
This year's Ms. Campus,
has already turned down several men.
Either she doesn't see them,
or she has very high standards.
Senpai, the streets are dangerous at night, so I'll walk you home.
Then, will you lend me your shoulder?
Hiraizum-senpai, you drank that much today?
I'm sorry, it was very fun, so I didn't notice that I drank too much already.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
But you’re not one to talk, are you?
Well, I also had quite a number of shots...
Well then, I'll be on my way.
You’re going home already?
It'd be troublesome if I miss the last train.
I never thought you'd be the one to approach me like that.
Senpai?
Did you think my invitation was just a coincidence?
You're new here, right?
Aren’t you interested in joining a travel club?
Yes, I am interested!
I was interested in you,
and you're not getting away.
I liked you, that's why...
Could you be a player?
In that case, I'll have to punish the bad boy.
It's true!
Senpai's tongue is...!
I-I'm sorry...
You seem to have a lot built up inside.
Then,
it’s your turn to do me.
Senpai...
It's like a dream, to have sex with you like this.
Did you want to do this from the start?
I want to hold your breasts first.
Then, hold them as long as you want.
Thrust into my pussy as long as you want!
Until today, I was always masturbating while thinking of you.
Those aren't true...
It's hitting deep inside.
I'm cumming!
Senpai, I...
You still want to do it?
Yes?
Then do it as if you want more,
as I also want to have more sex.
It's hot!
My breasts are being raped as if they’re my pussy!
It’s coming out!
More, please do it more!
Like this, senpai?
My butt's getting tingly.
That’s good.
It feels good when I get hit like that...
When I hit you like this, your pussy gets really tight.
It hurts, but I feel aroused.
Please, do it more intensely!
This is good...!
This is good!
This feels good...!
It's dirty down there.
Then I'll clean it up for you.
I want to lick your embarrassing parts.
Don't! If you do it like that, then I'll...
It's okay.
Release it on my face.
Release it all on my face!
Let it out strongly!
Strongly!
I'm going to release it strongly!
It's getting onto my face!
Oh, no! I'm... I'm going to cum again.
I'm slowly becoming more lewder!
Me, too!
So you feel great, too.
It's okay then.
Do whatever you please.
Your pussy feels great, I just can't stop!
I'm sorry!
Thank you, for letting this much out.
It's okay.
I wanted to be stained with your sperm from the start.
Please let me taste it until the end.
Oh, no...!
Hey, wake up now.
Senpai...?
Are you going to the university already?
Give me back my keys later, okay?
Let's forget what happened last night.
We were drunk,
and things turned out like this.
And that's how it happened.
Shouldn’t that be "And that's how my dream went"?
But it's true!
Hiraizumi doesn't get drunk, you know.
She has a very high liquor tolerance.
Hey, where are you going?
Senpai!
Did you come to return my keys?
Do you want to go have a drink with me tonight?
I can't guarantee...
...what will happen if I'm drunk you know.
Harem time!
A few days have passed in the Kamiyama house,
and Junko-san has brought another legal wife candidate.
But she was...
Hanazawa-san?
Satou-kun... So it's you...
Why are you...?
I was also chosen as a legal wife candidate.
So you already know what’s next, right?
This is impossible.
This is just a dream.
But, my sensation tells me it’s not.
What are you doing, Hanazawa-san?
It's my first time, so I don’t know if I can do it well, but...
Hanazawa-san!
I want to...
I want to have sex with Hanazawa-san!
I really don't think I can do this.
What do you mean?
The conglomerate made me a promise.
My Dad's company is about to go bankrupt.
They said if I have sex with you,
they would provide assistance funds.
But I...
If that's the case, then consider the contract canceled, okay?
Now I understand why my mother left the Kamiyama house.
You just simply use money to push and force around the powerless.
That's the way things are here right?
I guess I can’t really be Kamiyama house's--
Wait!
You are mistaken.
This is something that I had suggested.
It's true that my father's company is in a tight spot.
Besides, I was just a bit surprised earlier.
And...
When I knew that it was you, I was happy.
Eh?
That's why, if I can know more about you...
Can we start first as friends?
That's lame.
That's so lame!
Reiji-sama needs to choose as soon as possible.
We simply can’t accept this!
And so...
Have sex with him already!
Well then, let’s go!
No...!
It’s tight!
It's going inside!
Satou's thing is going inside me!
N-No, I don’t want my first to be like this.
Now, make sure you taste her well, Reiji-sama.
Hanazawa-san, I've always liked you from the start.
N-No way... Why are you telling me this now?
No, what's this...? It feels really good.
No way, it feels good!
Hanazawa-san?
I've decided now.
I really want to be your legal wife!
Eh?!
I love this!
I love your cock!
Because if I become your legal wife...
I'll be able to do this wonderful thing every day, right?
I love you!
I love you very much, so...
so make me your wife!
I'm cumming...!
So this means everything is okay, right?
I definitely won't accept this!
And so, this story will be continued!
Please look forward to next time!
www.SubDESU-H.net