SubDESU-H.net
It was the third day of summer vacation...
I went back to school to pick up some notes I'd forgotten.
When suddenly...
...I witnessed my classmate, Natsumi Sukumi, masturbating.
Come here!
And thus our perverted summer began.
W
Tsundere Inran Shoujo Sukumi
Tsundere Lewd Girl Sukumi
What?
Me, a shemale?
N-No, it was a dream.
...is what I thought at first.
You nuts?
I had something like this attached down here?
It's you who has this poking dick attached.
What about you?
Making a girlish face while having such a thick thing...
In fact, you should've seen my pussy enough to know, right?
Yeah...
What sort of things did you do to this pussy?
I-I rubbed it...
Rubbed it how?
Like that...
Just through the swimsuit?
No, directly too.
And then?
Stuck my finger...
...between your pussy lips.
Only that?
And the clitoris...
You got really wet.
I-Idiot. Don't say things like that.
Your dick is also...
Lie down right there.
No.
I still can't believe it,
that this fat, warm dick penetrated me.
My dick is in your mouth.
I cumming!
Why?
But if I put this on Sukumi...
Excuse me, master.
I beg you...
Please be so kind as to stick your penis into my vagina.
One more time, why the fuck do I have to wear a maid costume?
You don't have to...
Whatever, just hand it over.
Come on.
Ok, I got it. I just have to wear it, right?
Yeah!
So, what are you going to do to this maid now?
Well, speaking of maids...
Oh, I see. Cleaning, right?
No, not that.
So busy...
I-Idiot, that's dangerous!
I told you to stop.
Sukumi.
Yes?
You're the maid and I'm the master, right?
Yes...
Your speech doesn't fit.
I'm s-sorry, master.
Well then, come.
Understood.
Now, I'll punish you.
Master's fingers are...
...spreading my pussy lips... entering my fleshy pussy.
What, you've already started making sounds?
What a bad mannered pussy you have there.
I'm sorry.
It seems your ass can't hold it much longer.
Yes.
No!
I-If you touch me there like that...
...I won't... I won't be able to stand up anymore.
Then I'll have to make it so you can stand up.
Master?
How's that?
A penis! A penis is entering me!
No! Hurry up!
Hurry up and stick your fat penis in me!
Please stick it all the way in, I beg you!
Please don't tease me!
Reflected on your mistakes?
Yes! So, please, stick your penis...
It feels good!
Your fat thing's all the way in...
More, move more!
Oh, it feels so good!
Screw me hard!
Screw my pussy hard!
What's wrong?
You're pulling it out?
Why are you stopping?
You didn't reflect on your mistakes at all.
There...
You won't put it in there, right?
It's not a punishment if it feels good.
B-But...
A dick is entering my ass...
There!
It's going in...
A dick is entering my asshole!
You're really doing it?
Even if it's wrong, your dick's going in...
No way!
Even though I've not done this before...
Pull it out!
I'm telling you to pull out!
Your foul mouth still hasn't changed, it seems.
So big...
Dick...
Master's dick...
His dick is...!
It's only halfway in.
Please don't put it in any further.
I'll go crazy from my ass.
Then, I'll put it in to the very end.
No way!
Take this!
Don't move... my ass... It's spreading...
My ass is being spread wide by your dick!
Dick... Master's dick is... in my ass...
Is this anal sex?
How does it feel to have your master's cock shoved up your ass?
It's suffocating...
...but it feels good.
What a lewd maid you are...
...and so tight.
No way, master's telling me...
...telling me about anal sex...
No, I'm cumming. I'm cumming from my butt!
I don't want to cum from my ass!
No!
I can hear master's dick.
I'm going crazy. It'll shoot right into my ass.
I'm cumming... I'm...
This kinda thing is nice once in a while.
Not just once in a while. Every day's fine too.
Stupid.
Next time I'll be the mistress...
...and you'll be an absolutely obedient butler. How about that?
Isn't it always like that?
Oh, is it?
That was the last day of summer vacation.
Come on, forget about a boy like him.
Since your brother left you in our care, a weakling like him doesn't even compare to us.
You can always have sex with us, you see?
Don't! I'm cumming!
Yeah, just cum! Cum and forget that guy.
No, I won't cum. I'll only cum with Yui!
I'll only cum with Yui's dick!
Hold on Yui, I'll untie you.
I'm sorry it had to come to this...
They're the friends of my brother who is studying abroad right now.
That surprised me...
Having seen something like that... Do you hate me now?
No, I'm happy you chose me.
It got torn.
Want to change into your school uniform?
No, there's a swimsuit I want to show you.
Me?
Oh yes, and go change into your swimsuit too.
Ah? I didn't bring mine with me.
There should be one...
...the white school swimsuit you picked up somewhere.
You serious?
You have a girlish face, and you're short.
It should suit you well.
Come on. Change, change.
I hope no one comes here!
Well, at this time there shouldn't be anyone around.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sukumi?
How is it?
It's like a wedding dress...
And you're wearing the white tuxedo.
Will you pledge your everlasting love to me from now on?
Yeah. I swear.
I also swear it.
Then, to seal it with a kiss...
It's soft...
These are your lips, right?
Idiot.
What's the point in saying something so embarrassing now?
Because...
It's our first kiss.
Oh, I see.
It's gotten so big!
It can't be helped, right?
This thing I'm wearing rubs on me.
My, my, your dick is pretty big for someone with such a cute face.
Love you!
Me too.
Sit down here.
It looks like your pussy is showing through.
Oh, you idiot...
In this position, your dick will...
...go in as far as it can go.
See?
Your dick's deep inside... so deep...
The dick of someone who looks like a girl, is bigger than a boy's...
I'll make you cum today.
See? I'll rub your nipples for you. Feels good, right?
That's the Sukumi-sensation you love so much.
You're really aroused.
Your dick is pulsating.
Getting excited from being touched...
You most perverted pervert of all the most perverted perverts.
You're so hard inside my pussy.
I love you.
Look, both our nipples are hard.
You're making such girlish sounds for a boy.
Nipples feel so good...
Yeah.
Don't... Don't push it in so deep.
Deep... Your dick's so deep...
Your fat dick is moving inside my pussy.
The tip is reaching so deep inside me.
Why are you pushing in so deep?
I kinda love school swimsuits.
Could it be that you want me to say, "I love school swimsuits"?
Yup.
Idiot.
I love them! I love them so...
So please screw me!
Ram your school swimsuit cock deep into my school swimsuit pussy!
Alright!
So deep!
Not just deep!
This is amazing!
Your dick is reaching the deepest spot!
It's grinding inside me!
Fill me up with that milk which makes me feel so good!
Ok!
Your dick is... The tip is...
...always touching me deep inside.
I-I'm about to cum!
It's flowing out!
It's hot, so hot!
Your cum is reaching inside my womb!
Cumming, I'm cumming too!
More!
Ejaculate until my school swimsuit is snow white!
Sure!
Please spray all your cum into my pussy!
More, give me more!
Screw me with that dick of yours which is bigger than anyone's!
Your dick is rubbing on my pussy that just came!
My love juice is mixing up with your milk.
The juices mixing up are making it slippery, and the thrusting is making lewd sounds.
I'm cumming again!
I-I came too!
Please give me more cum! Make my pussy overflow with cum!
Fill my pussy up with your cum until it's molded to the shape of your dick...
...so that no other dick will be able to enter.
Make it your hole!
Right now I can be satisfied by any cock, so screw my pussy.
Fill me with your cum!
Ok, I'll give you plenty!
So much that no other dick will fit in there!
That makes me happy!
I love you, Yui!
Don't let go of me, okay?!
You bet! I won't ever let you go.
And like this... our summer continued.
However the seasons may change.