Don't tell me... It can't be...
I need to do something! Otherwise, Madoka will-!
SubDESU-H
Diabolus Kikoku
No! No!! No!!!
Dammit, what has happened to me?
Yuuki...
Don't call me by that name!
I don't know you!
That look you give me, it gives me the creeps!
Damn, I'm starting to see things...
I guess you really don't remember.
I'll play with you later, so remember!
Yuuki...
Things can't keep going on like this.
You really are the best...
So deep-!
I'm gonna cum!
Madoka...
H-Hey... Can you remember anything yet?
Before... Right here, you...
Not that again!
If you're so persistent, I won't do you anymore!
Yuuki...
This time, I'll be sure to save you.
Found you!
What do you want?
You're really Asahina Yuuki!
Oh, you're alone?
Did you come here to get violated?
W-Who would do such-!
If you do anything more to Madoka-!
You... I knew it!
I'm purposely avoiding maniacs like you...
Maniacs?
I'm not feeling it.
Does that mean you don't want to get involved with an enemy?
Huh?
An enemy?
He doesn't remember when we used to fight...
Have I raped you before?
I can't remember a single person.
You really don't remember?
You're saying the same thing as her...
I don't remember anything or know anything!
I just exist here!
What strong pressure!
See ya then.
What?!
He, I knew he wasn't a normal human being...
Sayako!
Madoka!
What's wrong, Sayako? Being up here like this...
Madoka...
S-Sayako?!
Madoka.
Do you remember that incident?
Yes.
It was exciting and fun...
However, there are some things I don't want to remember...
Even so, I like you, so I wanted to be with you as much as I could.
That's why I came back...
It's the same for me.
Yeah, but I remembered about those guys...
Those guys?
Asahina Yuuki...
I thought he was a bad memory, but...
But he died in that cave underneath us, right?
Yeah...
Asahina Yuuki died...
But for him to be here...
It's not possible!
I can't believe it, either...
So let's stop worrying about him.
Sayako, it's something that has already happened.
You can't keep stewing over things in the past!
Take a nap, that should clear your head a bit.
I can't take a nap!
I wonder what Madoka thinks... about that guy.
If only the others were here during times like these...
Yo!
You're skipping class too?
Y-You bastard!
You're not really my type, but...
I seem to remember doing compact girls like you before...
No!
If you're too loud, the others will hear...
However, I don't care if we're seen...
If you keep quiet, it'll be over soon.
I can't believe you're getting wet while in such a situation!
Now it's time for the real deal.
No! No way, not in such place!
N-No!
Be still for a sec!
It's entering me!
I-In such a place-!
It's tight...
Something is lacking here, but it can't be helped...
What's wrong?
You can moan all you want!
W-Who's gonna-!
Hmph! You're not bad, but I like that other one better.
Other one?
Your breasts are small...
I'm missing something.
I guess I'll continue the rest with her...
W-Wait! Don't go near Madoka!
You're not satisfactory!
What are you trying to do?
I'll satisfy you, so...
That's enough.
Stop it!
I-I'll try my best to do Madoka's part too!
I told you to stop!
If you want to be violated that much, I'll make sure to do it later!
Madoka...
What's with the hurry, Sayako?
Did you take a nap?
I'm so glad that you're here!
Huh?
Seriously, what's up?
N-No...
It's nothing...
If I take Madoka's place...
Then I can protect her from him.
Sayako?
Oh? Sorry!
You weirdo.
Yo!
If you chased me here, then you're fine doing it here, right?
I'm not fond of such places, but...
What uninteresting breasts...
No...
I finally want to do it now, so you can't stop me!
You're tight like last time.
The tightening effect is better than the other one...
You're being aroused by a person you hate?
T-There's no way I'm getting aroused-!
Your body doesn't lie.
I-I don't want this...
You indecent girl!
This is for Madoka, I'm doing this for Madoka!
I'm gonna let it out deep inside you!
No, no, stop it... No...
It's coming out... His semen is coming out inside me...
We're not done yet.
No one will come here.
I don't know about people peeping, though...
Oh yeah, this place was where I did that girl for the first time...
It was the best.
Does he prefer Madoka over me...?
If you try hard, maybe you can be good as her.
I'll try my best, so please leave Madoka alone...
That's up to you.
Make me feel good so I can forget her.
O-Okay...
Whoa... It's so hot and hard, It's entering my deepest spots...
C'mon, move!
It feels good...
That's it...
Like this, I can...
No, not my nipples!
No...
I don't want this, but... my body is...
You're just like a woman now, even though you're so small.
No, I'll cum-!
No, I can't hold back-!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's coming out again... Deep inside me...
It was good, but you're still not as good as her!
Madoka!
You're secretly seeing that guy, aren't you?
Er, what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
He was an enemy to us!
Sayako... Do you suspect something?
I know that...
But Yuuki is family...
Or rather, my only family.
Even so, if you're with him, you know what's gonna happen to yourself!
If Madoka becomes...
That won't happen again.
Because I know him better than you do.
What does that mean?!
Even though I'm saying all of this to you...
It's all for you, but...
I don't care! Madoka, you jerk!
Sayako... I'm sorry.
But I...
want to save Yuuki.
You... You're still having sex with Madoka, aren't you?
Forget Madoka...
Do it only with me.
Hmph, you're ordering me around?
You can't do her anymore!
Okay? You can do anything you want to me.
I decide what I do and who I do it with.
More! Thrust into me more!
This is great! Thrust deeper!
More! Stronger!
Geez, you've turned into such a whore.
Anyone here?!
Mado...ka...
Sayako?
Yuuki?!
What's going on?!
T-This is...
Stop this already.
There's no point in it. It's okay to stop.
The others aren't here anymore.
Right...
I don't want you to keep doing these things.
I did those things for you and Sayako.
You've got nothing to do here, so let it end.
Mado...ka.
If only I knew sooner, with you, I would have...
Madoka?
That guy, Asahina Yuuki wanted to clear his regrets.
However, that's not true anymore, is it?
He wanted to free the spirits of the other students trapped here?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Sayako.
I ended up getting you involved too.
No, Madoka, I'm sorry too!
It's time to make up!
Yes!
So then, back to patrol?
Can I come too?
Of course!