Hello, I'm a vampire.
I've come to suck out your soul.
Thank you for giving me such a formal greeting.
You're not surprised by me?
That's disappointing.
It's not that I'm not surprised with you coming here,
but I'm so astounded that I can't speak.
That's fine I guess.
Now I'll give you a pleasure most humans will never get no matter how hard they try.
W
Vampire
#
It's not "A", you know!
Then it's "I"?
Idiot.
"U"!
No, but it feels great though...
Normally, it would just come out
when I touch someone with my hands.
Is that so?
That's right!!
Hey.
Where are you looking?
Demon-san's breasts.
Yuuto, you're such a boobs alien...
Yes, I came from the planet boobies.
I'm a boobs alien.
Is that so... It's not working because I'm not using my breasts.
Then, I'll make an exception for a boobs alien like you.
Now, now, hurry up and cum already...
Serena-sama, you can't do it that intensely.
I'm going... to cum!
A lot of it came out!
Hey, do you want to enjoy my breasts some more?
So, why would you do something like this Serena-sama?
I-I'm not the human you know as Serena.
Is that a joke?
Va...Vampires never make jokes like that!
But, you said that you're not a demon...
I'm not a demon, I'm a vampire!
They're not the same thing!
Serena-sama, isn't?
That's wrong...
Did you think I wouldn't notice it? Serena-sama has a dark mole on her foot.
That's how I know it's you.
Hey, why don't you just change your mood already?
By the way...
Why did you come into my room like that,
and start licking my penis?
Serena-sama?
Even though it was only for a short time...
I... I don't really hate you, okay?
I'm the head maid of the Ijuin family,
my name is Hanyuu Mizuki.
Ye...Yes, I'm Akiyama Yuuto.
Pleased to meet you.
Every now and then, please use the back door.
Yes!
I'll show you around of the mansion,
please follow me.
He's fine, right?
Pleased to meet you.
What an idiot, even though you're gonna be our sacrifice...
Serena-sama?
I'm Akiyama Yuuto, pleased to meet you!
Do you find it interesting to look at my breasts?
Ye... Yes...
Yuuto!
I'm sorry.
You don't have worry about that.
Yuuto, that's enough for now.
Yes, Excuse me please.
Yuuto.
Is your life happy?
Yes.
Eh? Um...
Is it fine if I greet Retsudou-sama?
Retsudou-sama doesn't want to take his time to see everyone like that.
I just want to say thanks for giving someone like me a job here.
That's unnecessary.
Yes...
This will be your room.
This is the attic, right? This will be fine.
What should I say? It's like a secret base for me.
I totally like it!
Then I'll make you start your work right now.
Please prepare yourself.
Yes!
So, this is the way he's doing his job?
Yes.
So if he's this good, he surpassed our expectations?
Though if it's like this, there's no way
we can defy that old-man's order.
It's useless talk.
Yes.
That stubborn old-man!
Where's Yuuto right now?
He's by Serena-sama's side.
What's this?
It's a special mixed juice.
When Mizuki-san tasted it earlier, she said that it was good.
I'll taste it anyways.
It's really good!
Thank you very much.
Why is he in here with us?
He's present here in memoriam of Yuuno,
since it's where he belongs.
Yuuno? Did you say Yuuno?
He's that criminal's son?
Yes, It's that Yuuno.
But there's someone who couldn't accept that fact.
You dare say something like that to me?!
To your master?!
That's not what I'm saying, Retsudou-sama.
What?
You act like you're not aware of your position here.
If we thought something like that, It would be obvious.
This isn't gonna be the end of Retsudou-sama, isn't that right?
Hey!
Eh? Me?
Listen carefully, I'll let you know what kind of
existence you have here.
Your father is...
Your father is a traitor who brought shame to our family,
And you're that man's son,
disgracing us by being here!
Looks like you're shocked about the fact
that you're a criminal's son, right?
Possibly...
You listen to me!
You have to repay all of your father's sins while you're here!
Besides repaying all of that, you're going to be used by the Ijuin family.
And you don't have much time.
What are you doing?! Get out of here!
You don't have to worry about that.
Even though Retsudou-sama said that,
there's a lot of mystery about that incident.
Retsudou-sama wouldn't say something like that if he knew your father well.
Mizuki-san...
So Retsudou-sama has been mad at himself all this time?
Yes...
Retsudou hasn't smiled since that day.
What should I say... That's so sad...
Yes, after all it is true.
It's good.
Have you calmed yourself down?
Ah~ It's disappointing,
Just using Yuuto for something like this.
Can I ask you about something?
What is it?
It's been on my mind for a while...
Everyone has been saying to me "For a short time" or "You don't have much time",
Am I going to be fired?
It's death...
Who's going to die?
Is it Retsudou-sama? Did something happen to him
when he went to Mt. Fuji-
Idiot, It's you Yuuto!
The one who's die...
Is me?
That's right.
Um... For what reason?
Because you've been associating with me.
I don't understand at all.
After a vampire sucks a human's soul,
they will die the day after that.
Oh...
So, are you depressed?
No... Not at all.
I'm just surprised that something like that could happen.
It's unfortunate for you, that the truth is so cruel.
You were brought in to this house as our sacrifice.
Sacrifice?
That's right, It's important for a vampire like me
to suck out the soul of a human.
So, the reason Yuuto is here was for us to feed on.
Is that so?
Are you afraid of dying?
What's it like...?
I never died before, so I don't know that part.
Hey, Yuuto.
What is it?
Let me grant one wish for you, we vampires
have enough power to do that.
Is that true?
Of course, although there are some things we can't do.
Like destroy the world or change the past,
that's impossible to do
So, what do you want?
Long life.
Of course... that's not possible, right?
What do I want...
Um... What about if I wish that there'll be happiness
for everyone in the Ijuin family?
Um... You want to wish for happiness for all of us...?
Eh?!
Hm, what is it?
Do you understand what you just said?!
Yes.
I got it, so you don't understand it.
No, I totally understand it.
Even though I haven't been here long...
I would say that everyone here was likely sad about something,
Serena-sama, Marie-sama, Mizuki-san, and Retsudou-sama,
they all seem unhappy.
A-Are you an idiot?
Even though everyone would be happy,
It'll be in exchange for your life.
That's unfortunate for me.
I thought it wouldn't be bad to wish for happiness
for the people who'll live for the rest-
Are you an idiot?!
So, Serena-sama...  How 'bout my wish then?
I'll just go to sleep.
So I should be in a cold state when I wake up in the morning?
Hell is probably like the back of the roof...
Wait, this is the back of the roof isn't it?!
Good morning.
Mizuki-san?
Come in.
I think that I'm going to live for now...
Yuuto!!!
So, he's not going to die after all?
Yes.
What do you think?
I can't even say anything...
Whatever, It might just be a mistake.
We'll wait and see what happens for now.
Yes.
I'm going now!
Wait, you there!
Why are you acting like a fool? I'm talking to you!
You mean me?
That's right, this area is off limits to people without proper authorization.
But, Serena-ojou-sama told me that she's going to bring a lot of things today...
Can you show me some identification?
No...
Then leave at once!
By the way... Who are you?
I'm one of the employees here.
You don't look like one.
Huh?
You look like a cosplayer, and you're the erotic kind!
What do you mean by that?!
No... That's not...
Hey, Yuuto!!
Oh?
Serena-sama.
See ya later, Sister Boobies.
Hurry... Hurry... Here, take all of it.
It's heavy-
Don't say things like that...
That's right, Marie-sama is waiting inside of the car.
Let's go.
What's wrong with him?!
Hey, Serena.
What is it, Onee-sama?
There's a difference in our status you know.
Also doing something like that?
Yuuto didn't die after all, this is what you call-
Serena.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Not at all, I know he's your partner to taste after all...
So you must feel he's special to you.
O-Onee-sama.
What's the matter?
I didn't do that yet!
Is that so?!
I thought that you were going to go all the way,
since you're so lovey dovey with him.
Why are you laughing, Yuuto?
No, that's because... hey...
Well, It'll be just fine if he doesn't know anything about it.
Serena-sama, it's already hard to see the shuttle!
Do you mind if we stop?
That's fine, let's go get the other shuttle then.
Why isn't there a fence in this spot?!
Serena-sama, just leave everything to me!
Hey, could you hold me from behind?
Sure...
Please hold me higher than that.
That's right...  This feels good.
Hey Yuuto, touch them directly.
No way, Yuuto's hands feel so amazing!
Serena-sama, your nipples are getting hard aren't they?
No~ you can't!
But, doesn't it feel good?
You meany...
Yuuto...
That's-
Serena-sama is the perverted one, aren't you? Don't you usually do this by yourself?
Tha... That's not true, doing it with you is my first time.
Is that really true?
Doing this with you is my first time!!
Even you're getting excited from touching my body.
I wonder what that is that's been hitting my ass for a while...
Se... Serena-sama... That's... Wa...Wait-
What's the matter? So you trying to be tough is just an act?
That's because I'm touching Serena-sama's beautiful breasts,
There's no way I could resist it.
It's mean of you to say things like that to me...
He... hey... Yuuto...
Wha... what is it?
Do you want to cum?
I'll make it come out, okay?
The way Serena-sama moving is-
How is it? Does it feel good?
It... It feels good.
If you want to cum, you can just let it out.
The... Then... Let's do it together, Serena-sama.
Together...? Together is good.
Yuuto... Yuuto... Yuuto~!
It's coming out~!!!
Maybe it's because I'm with Yuuto after all...
Hey, Yuuto.
What's the matter?
Tonight, I want you to come to my room... Alone.
Se... Serena-sama...
That's...
Th... Then, I'll be waiting for you.
Wha... What is it? Do you have something to tell me?
Serena-sama, you act like you've decided that Yuuto is 'it'.
But Yuuto doesn't die after getting sucked by me!
Also the moment Yuuto touched me...
Tha... That's why the one back there was a special service.
That's what it was...
Serena-sama, please be careful with your actions next time.
Is that really true?
But, even if I go in there it's not like we're gonna do that.
Eh? Yes!
Yes?
Mi... Mizuki-san?
Eh? Eh?!
Mi... Mizuki-san, what's the matter with you?
As I thought, they're big-
Yu-Yuuto...
It feels really good!
Yuuto really is-
No... No, That's-
This is... This is amazing, Yuuto!!
Yuuto, I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum...!!!
Hey, you're a virgin aren't you?
Unfortunately that's true...
Then, you want to do it, right?
Yes, I can't say no to that.
Mizuki-san...
This... is bad...
Yuuto, why don't you just squeeze my breasts?
What's this?!
Yuuto... isn't coming.
That's good... More of it...
Yuuto's hand... Yuuto's hand is...!!!!
Mizuku-san, since the first time we met I've been-
Come, Yuuto... Let's see each other's faces for the last time.
Okay?
Mizuki-san, the kiss...
It's coming out.