August 6th, 8:00 p.m.
Ow...
An accident on the first day of a field trip?
Is no one else here?
Isn't anyone here?
Hey! Hayami!
H-Hiro?
Yuu! Where did everyone go?!
I don't know,
I just came to...
Oh...
Okay, let's find the others!
Yeah!
SubDESU-H
Kansen2
Inzai
Toshi
Everything looks in bad shape...
Hiro, over there!
I wonder what the ambulances and fire fighters are doing...
I guess the rescue mission hasn't started
since it's only been three hours after the earthquake...
Communications are out,
so we can't call, text, or use the Internet...
Do you want to call Alice?
It's not just Hayami...
Where did everyone go?
Hiro, that shopping mall we went to earlier.
The ground floor was an emergency shelter.
What?
Let's try going there!
Hiro! Over there!
It's the maid cafe we went to earlier!
Does that mean... We came out, and went that way?
Stop it already~!
Your warm pussy feels good!
I-It's tightening around me!
Wha?!
Help us!
Wata! What are you doing?!
You wanna do it too?
W-What are you saying?!
Did you take some strange drugs or something?!
That should cool you down!
Hiro, over there too!
Yeah.
Yuu, take this girl and go to that emergency shelter.
Sure!
This should be far enough...
I'm going to that emergency shelter, but what about you?
Are you injured?
Wait-! What are you doing?!
Hey, let's have sex...
Wait-!
You're getting bigger down here...
That's because you're pushing against me-!
This cock looks delicious!
Hey, could you lick me too?
What?
I'm overflowing! Please lick it up...
I'll put it in soon...
Wai-!
I-It feels good!
Doesn't it?
You can let it out inside me!
Y-Yes...
I didn't know sex was this great!
Hiroshi!
Hayami!
Why should I do such a whore?
Where are you going?
Leave your cock with me!
Pussy... Slimy pussy...
Let out your smelly semen!
It's tight, you're tightening around me!
P-Please, pull it out!
You're young, so you can still cum, right?
Leave me alone!
Not only Wata and the maid...
What's wrong with this town?
Stop this!
Titty-chan! Please suck my cock!
No, don't come any closer!
Hayami! Hide inside!
Hiroshi! Help me!
It'll be faster if you run away!
What are you going to do?!
I'll come in later!
Got it, please come quickly!
Can I really escape this...?
That took awhile...
I wonder where Hayami and Yuu are...?
Don't move!
Huh?
Wait! I'm not a one of them!
I can only do this for now...
Thank you very much, Anzai-san...
You should rest!
But...
You're worried about that girlfriend you mentioned earlier, aren't you?
It's not like Hayami is my girlfriend...
It sure is nice.
I envy this Hayami-san for having such a caring boyfriend...
Aren't you trying to find that Katsuya-san you were talking about?
Yes, I think he should be here.
Reception?
Hayami! Where are you?
Hi Hiroshi!
Um, we're on the third floor in East Town, in the furniture area.
I'm with Yuuki.
Here.
Where are you, Hiro?
Thank goodness, you were able to find each other...
I'm on the fourth floor in West Town,
in the lobby in front of the theater.
I think this place is connected to East Town
through the overpass on the third floor.
Then we'll be on our way.
No, I'll come\ over to you guys, so wait there.
But we're nearly at the overpass.
I'll bring Alice there safely, so just hold tight!
R-Right, then please do.
See you!
Hiroshi-kun! Are you okay?
Yeah...
You should lay down for a while.
Then I will...
Hiroshi-kun...
Hiroshi-kun!
Sorry to wake you up,
but take a look at that.
...has been spreading rapidly.
Huh? The T.V news?
Breaking news
Emergency disaster!!
Unknown explosion causes major damage
I repeat.
About nine hours ago, on the sixth of August at 8:15 PM,
an unknown explosion destroyed much of Sendai City.
The cause of the explosion is yet unknown, as...
An explosion?
I guess it hasn't affected too much around here.
Also, from 10 PM and onward,
a new virus has been rapidly spreading in the areas of Sendai City, Suzuka, and Sakatashi.
What?
The connection between the explosion and the spread of the virus is yet unclear.
An explosion and a new virus?
What a horrible combination.
The Ministry of Health and Welfare has named this new widespread virus Unknown Level 4.
Unknown Level 4...
The specified symptoms of this virus are:
loss of ethics, extreme euphoria, an increase in sexual desire, mood swings,
blurred memory, loss of physical strength, and a speech impediment,
making the virus infectious and very deadly.
Then all those people outside were...
The means of infection currently identified are:
Sexual transmission, oral transmission and blood transmission.
The time needed for the virus to take effect form infection is still unclear... However...
Shit!
Hiroshi-kun! Calm down!
How can I be calm?!
I'm going to become one of them soon!
You shouldn't give up!
I'm certain the rescue team will come soon.
Rescue team...?
Yes, since it's such a big disaster.
I'm sure the defense force has received its orders.
But... If it takes effect before they come,
I might assault you too...
If that happens...
I'll help kill you!
Yes, please do...
I'm going to take a look around the overpass.
I have to avoid the infected until I can get some medicine...
Hayami?
What happened?! Where's Yuu?!
Hiroshi...
Yuuki has...
What happened to Yuu?!
Don't tell me...
Yuuki,
he became like those people outside!
And he...
No way... Yuu too?
Hiroshi-kun, you're back?
Anzai-san!
Looks like no one's here...
Where are you?
Hiroshi-kun!
Please, run!
Hiro, this lady's pussy feels great!
Yuu...
Stop it! Let her go!
Huh? You want to do her too?
That's fine...
Y-You idiot!
Let's both do her...
Here! Her pussy is free now!
Please, Yuu! Get ahold of yourself!
What's wrong, Hiro? Let's do her!
Anzai-san, I'll help you!
No...!
Kill me... Kill me before the virus takes effect!
Please, Hiroshi-kun!
Hiro...
Put your cock up my ass, Hiro!
Fine then...
Yay, I'm so happy...
I've always wanted to have sex with you Hiro...
Katsuya-san...
Huh? That lady disappeared...
Oh well, Hayami will do.
N-No!
Why don't we do it again?
Hayami!
Hiro!
Yuu!
Hiro-!
Yuu... Anzai-san...
They're bound to see this from their rescue helicopter...
You're right...
Hayami?
I think I'm about to turn into one like Yuuki...
I'm gonna jump off before I infect you, okay?
Hey!
Wha? What are you doing?
Hurry up and run-!
Idiot, you'll become infected too!
Don't worry, I won't be.
Huh?
Even if I do, I'll retain my mind, and I'll cure you.
Hiroshi...
I don't know what will do it, but I swear that I will cure you!
Thanks...
Hey, you won't reject me no matter what I say, will you?
No, there's no point in rejecting things now.
I...
I love you... Hiroshi...
What?
See! You do reject things!
Because-! This isn't the time for you to be confessing your love!
But... I wanted to tell you how I feel before I lose myself...
Actually...
Actually, I wanted to dress in nicer clothes,
set my hair, put on a bit of makeup, and then confess my feelings.
It's no wonder I'll get rejected...
I won't reject you.
Really?
Yeah. I love you too, Hayami.
Hiroshi, do you dislike big breasts?
No, I like them.
But you look a bit angry...
I-I'm just nervous.
Don't suck on them so strongly!
Hiroshi's finger is inside me!
Hayami, your voice is erotic...
Because it feels good!
Don't stare so much, it's embarrassing!
You've got a beautiful pussy, Hayami...
Your pussy tastes great!
I want to lick you too!
H-Hayami-!
That feels so good.
I'm so happy!
Please feel better!
I'm putting it in.
Okay.
A-Are you alright?
Yeah, keep going...
You're tightening around me, Hayami!
I'm filled with your cock!
It feels great, Hayami!
Me too, Hiroshi!
This is amazing!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
I... I-!
I can't stop!
Hiroshi, does it feel good?
Yeah!
How about you?
I-It feels great Hiroshi!
I love you!
I love you...
So good...
I... I love you too!
I'm so happy!
Say it more!
I love you, Hayami! I really do!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Me too, me too!
I'm cumming!
It's the rescue team, we're saved...
No... It looks like they're killing off the infected...
If they're not going to save us,
I guess I'll run away with Hayami.
I don't know how long we'll last,
but lets live that short time together.