As the train runs through the city,
you're hemmed in by a crowd of strangers.
A bunch of people you don't want to be touched by.
Even cute girls are shoving you...
You must not touch the skin of those maidens.
Ootsuka Keiko
Occupation: Office Lady
Blood Type: AB
Hobby: Field Trip
Within this enclosed space within society,
This lonely city makes your son grieve.
You're damned if you touch,
and you're damned if you don't.
Shinohara Misuzu
Occupation: Housewife
Blood Type: A
Hobby: collecting small things
If you don't listen to me, "the finger" will attack you.
molester group
Chikan Juunintai
Ten
It hurts.
Next stop is *censored* station, next stop is *censored* station.
W
Real Commission
So he really has...
How about her?
She doesn't really look like my type.
Then perhaps the next one.
I think she will appear in the next fifteen minutes.
We won't catch our prey if we don't set the trap in time.
Yes...
We must act carefully this time.
Since this will be the real thing.
You want to do the real one inside the train?
Yes.
Well, we accept requests for molesting inside the train but...
the real thing is...
Are you sure about this?
You know, even normal molestation is difficult.
It's not an AV you know.
Even we use an actress, it's difficult to pull off.
If we're talking about the real thing, it means rape.
It's quite difficult to do it amongst crowds of people without being noticed.
I realize that.
Hey Mr. Customer, when you get arrested for molestation, you'll be treated as a sex criminal.
You could be imprisoned for not less than six months and not more than seven years.
You also must pay not more than 50,000 yen according to Anti-Nuisance Ordinance.
If we're talking about the real thing, it will be rape, violence, and public assault.
And if you accidentally hurt her, you'll be charged with bodily injury, so you're doomed.
If they found out that we are involved, then the case will be treated as a joint crime.
Even the victim won't report it, we'd still be chased.
It means there's Uradora too.
If they started detention, then we can't go out for ten days.
If we're caught molesting in that time then the company will surely close.
You're still of a good age; are you sure about this?
We are professionals when it comes to molesting.
We could easily secure your escape.
But when it comes to real thing, the risk increases greatly.
I have money.
Prostitutes are not good enough for you?
To tell the truth, I can't get it up.
It's embarrassing, but...
after all this time,
I got hard on the train the other day.
Hmm.
So, the money made you decide to do such a troublesome thing.
Tochi, how do you rate our chances?
I think that'll depend upon the plan.
When it comes to real thing, timing and location are crucial.
Komagome
Tabata
Nishi Nippori
Nippori
Uguisudani
Ueno
Using the route of the *censored* train line, about 26 stations and about 27 minutes for one full loop.
Okachimachi
Akihabara
Kanda
Tokyo
Yuurakuchou
Only the door on the left side will open, so
Shinbashi
the target can't escape if we drag her to the right-side corner.
Hamamatsuchou
That means we can't escape if we're caught either.
Eh?
Type E 231 Seat no. 500
In the first car and the eleventh car of Type E 231 Seat no. 500,
there's a space for a wheel chain.
We can secure a space there.
We can't drag the target there during rush hour because of the crowds.
We must do it after the peak period.
The problem now is the target.
We must select from the list.
Molesting is
a crime!
We can't choose just anyone to be the target.
It's the mark of an amateur to touch a target just because she's cute.
We must refrain from selecting a target who screams when she's being touched,
or else we'll be in danger.
What's that?
It's a list of targets suitable for this plan.
The woman who bears with it when touched, the one you can touch,
the one who wants to touch you, and the one you must not touch.
Also, the lists of the time, date, train line and the car number of their trips.
We have a stock of information from our previous jobs.
Well, there's no woman who desires to be raped, though.
We would choose our target from this list, and
find them outside the ticket examiner, or even inside it.
It's forbidden to choose a target in the terminal station.
It's unnatural to hang around too long without boarding a train.
We'll be noticed by the rail company cops.
Here she comes!
How about her?
Well?
You're really quite picky.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
What a pain.
That one is the last in the list.
What should we do?
I have another list for the rush in the afternoon.
Or, how about we find a new target for now?
Don't joke around, we can't do such a dangerous thing.
Oh?
Uh... that woman...
Bobby!
What's that?
It's a kind of litmus test.
Red for acidic,
and blue for alkaline.
We test to find out if it's safe to choose her.
Oh... I'm sorry.
It's NG if she got angry when bumped into.
The best targets apologize even when it's not their fault.
Then...
If she's a dangerous one, we must avoid her, OK?
All right.
It's kick-off time.
Oh my, I've gone out while wearing sandals.
OK, I'll tell you the first rule of molesting.
The most important thing to remember is it's forbidden to assault.
You must slowly touch her, and observe her reaction.
First, you must touch her using the back of your hand, and observe.
You must decide how you will violate her depending on her reaction.
If you know the target will not start screaming,
then start to touch her in the same place, but with your palm.
The target will oppose you at first, but don't give up.
Touch her until the target gives up.
N...no..
Please stop..
N...no...
Oh, hello?
My bad, I'm on my way.
Eh? What? I can't hear you?
He's so noisy...
Ahh.. .yes, yes. Go ahead and enter the shop without me.
It's OK for me to be a little late, you know.
Huh? Huh?
I said... I'm on my way there!
I'm on the train!
Using cellphones on the train is a violation of good manners!
Shut up, you fool.
I'm turning this off.
The reason for giving the target an reimbursement is not only to calm her down.
It's insurance if we're ever caught.
We can argue that there was an agreement between us and the target.
It also has the effect of lessening her opposition.
Negotiation Successful!
No...
Please stay behind the yellow line.
We have arrived at *censored* station, please check your belongings.
Please... I need to get off here.
Please, let me get off.
I need to get off...
The door for the third line, please be careful.
I need to buy a vacuum cleaner.
My cellphone...
I need to pick up my phone...
No... you can't do that...
Please...
Please... forgive me.. with this...
I have a husband...
Stop it...
It hurts...
N-no...
I have... a husband...
It's a molester!
This guy is a molester!
No I'm not.... please... I didn't do it.
What's with you? Didn't she just say you touched her?
I didn't. I'm not the one who did it.
Look, you need to get off at the next station.
OK?
We're having some trouble on *censored* line, so we're stopping right now.
We're sorry for the inconvenience, but please be patient.
No...
No... that man might see us...
No... stop...
The door will close. Please be careful.
We apologize for the delay.
This train will be three minutes late to its destination.
How cruel...
The next stop is *censored* station.
The door on this side will open.