I see... So you're looking for Aoi-kun.
I-Is Aoi sick?
She herself doesn't know about that though.
Takumi-kun...
Please keep this a secret from her.
And... This place is...
This place is a library.
It's full of records of the past and some records that can't be leaked out.
It seems I saw an illusion.
An Illusion?
Uhm... How should I say this...
Well then, it's good for you not to say that.
It's already late.
You seem to be tired.
You should take a rest already,
and talk to Yanagi-sensei or to me tomorrow.
OK?
Are you interested with my body?
Eh!? Wha-
You're virgin right?
If you are to have sex with me, how do you want to do it?
Eh!?
I'm not saying that you'll do it literally,
I want to know your sexual knowledge.
There's a difference in the mental structure of a person...
They think about either the anus or the vagina.
The effect of thinking of the anus is...
The fear against sexual maturity or reproduction.
The effect of thinking of the vagina is...
Destructive urge, authority and desire.
Uhm... Sensei...
Shut up.
Question: If we're going to have sex here,
which one are you going to choose?
Something like that... please listen to me first.
I see.
You had a dream in the underground.
What does this mean?
Come to my room tomorrow morning.
I'll take an exact record.
Yo! How are you?
A... Aamano-san!
W-What are you doing here?
It's just that, I saw you and the superior-san in the pool awhile ago...
And I came here to watch you masturbate.
M-Masturbating!?
You're doing it, right?
It's alright even if you're watched.
What are you saying..ah!
As I thought, it's already hard and big.
A-Amano-san...
I'm going to suck it .
Look at the moment I suck it.
I-It's going in deeper.
I can't hold it, Amano-san.
Why...?
I told you right? I like fresh boys.
Ok then, I'm going to rape you now.
Is this really your first time?
But your body seems know it.
I just released it now.
You've been provoked by that superior.
It's natural.
Look at this, it will enter here.
How is it? You want to put it in, right?
You want to put it in, right?
Look, it's your first time, right?
It's tight.
Thrust into it as you want.
Twist it.
There...
Thrust into it like... you're rubbing it.
Look...
Look at me cumming...
Look!
Amano-san, I'm at my limit...
Are you cumming?
Let me see...
Let me see you cum.
Here.
Translated by SubDesu-H
Loss
Firstly... move.
I already made my move.
Now then...
How is he gonna make his move?
What is he seeking...
in this small world?
Which piece is looking for the changes?
Is it the Bishop? Pawn? Or...
The King?
I saw their conversation with superior-san.
It's natural he can't hold it.
Well I think it's alright.
I'll just have to suck this.
I let him help me for making that as bait.
He's my type...
and also, he's a virgin from how I see it.
Go ahead, release it.
Release it inside my mouth.
I'll suck it all.
What's this...
What happened yesterday, was it a dream?
An illusion?
Hinoki-chan?
Oh, you're finally awake.
Good Morning.
You sure can sleep that long.
Hey, I can't clean up.
Wake up already.
No!
A bruise, scratch, internal bleeding,
laceration, sloppy... I can't count them all.
Are you alright, Takumi-sama?
It's good for such a fool, leave him alone.
I think this is not the time for a diagnosis.
Let's go.
Let's go Hinoki-san, lets go back to the room.
Hinoki-chan?
Hey you, go take a bath.
You're stinky you know.
The food here is of the same class as a Hotel.
Really?
Umm... Why did you do that yesterday?
I saw my parents having sex.
My mom was having sex with a man I didn't know.
I got horny.
After that, I peeped many times.
That's why, I get excited when I know the secrets of a person.
That's why you became a reporter...
Yes I am.
I couldn't hold it in when I saw you two in the pool yesterday.
Hey, help me out.
What do you want me to do?
Well, it's simple.
Just tell me the things you saw, heard, and what they did to you.
I'm sure that in this hospital, there's a big secret.
Give me some time to think about it.
I don't have a problem with that, but...
I don't think you have much time left.
Kurimi wants...
Aoi-oneechan and Takumi-oniichan...
to be my Mama and Papa.
We can't be just your onii-chan and onee-chan?
I saw the picture displayed on the wall.
It was Midori-oneesan's Papa and Mama.
But it's weird...
The director and Midori-san don't remember that.
Me too, I don't have that memory either.
It's only my mom that celebrated my birth.
I didn't have that person at first...
Eh? Sorry...
It's alright, I have Kurumi-chan now anyway.
It's like you're really my Mom now.
Somehow, that makes me very comfortable now...
I'm so happy.
Kurumi-chan, Good night.
I went to the underground yesterday, night?
Underground?
You can't go to the underground with that elevator if you don't have the Director's key.
Does Aoi know about the underground?
I haven't gone there, but...
I don't have any business there either.
Aoi, how does your body feel?
It's fine, why?
Your memory is flying at midnight or...
Dreaming about weird things...
Have you found scratches or bruises that you don't even recognize?
I... No! No! It hasn't happened!
It's impossible for something like that to happen!
Why are you upset?
I just...
Stop it already!
You perverted idiot!
Never tell me such a weird story again!
There, go back to your room already!
O...Ouch! Ok I get it.
That illusion...
Are you only seeing it in the underground?
No...
Then the first thing is, what kind of illusion are you seeing?
The thing I saw...
Was it really an illusion?
Are you saying that there's a possibility that it wasn't?
I saw it again this morning.
This time it was Amano-san.
And the partner was different...
it was surely, me.
That's a new case...
So, was there some changes?
It was... the same as yesterday in the night.
So, how far was it until the voice became clear and neutralized?
All were the same.
As long as I could remember... no... even those things I don't remember I clearly...
Hmm.. Even if it's an illusion, your memory changed even though it came back to you.
Like it was not Amano.
Why is that illusion the truth?
Whatever is happening with the other illusions,
but it didn't appear in the previous cases.
It's weird that you're the one who appeared in the illusion.
This is my opinion, but...
I think you're making what happened, in the past, become real in some way.
According to science the information gathered will be, regenerated and analysed to be played back.
Yes, It's the one in sensei's thesis.
It's weird, but I think this is the only way I can clearly explain it.
Are you saying it was all real!?
If we look at it's form.
I think it is the right opinion.
When all reality is input into you,
what will happen to your mental state?
Hm? Did something happen?
I went to the hospital's underground yesterday in the night.
I see, so there was...
No... I heard that it was only a stockroom and an instrument room.
There were some weird rooms.
Chains...
Operation table...
A weird chair...
There was a gross stain all over...
It's strange.
They might be doing something there.
Ok, let's investigate it tonight.
Investigate?
I mean, let's go looking around.
And by the way, have you made up your mind about helping me?
I understand.
But, don't think that things will happen as you want when the investigation is successful.
I don't even know what I really want anyway.
Ok then it's settled.
Hinoki-chan is...
She was a special patient here when this hospital was built.
Special?
It's like this facility was made for her.
For Dad's research.
The reason why I'm here,
is for her medical treatment.
Why are you doing that?
It's about the private matter of my dad.
You said that Hinoki was what Midori-san's mother was once called, right?
To tell the truth, it was not her real name.
She's wearing the same clothes as her.
This is what Hinoki-san wants.
Then what's her real name?
I can't... tell you about that...
I don't know the reason either.
It's like I don't understand the matter anymore.
I'm sorry.
I hope I can answer all your questions, but...
No... it's not a matter that Midori-san must apologize for.
Thank you.
Hinoki-san also seems happy.
I lost it.
What are you saying?
The brooch Kurumi-chan gave to me.
Ah, that leaf shaped one.
Yes...
I've failed as an onee-chan, right?
Why did you lose that important thing?
I didn't lose that thing as if I wanted to lose it.
It was with me last night before I went to sleep
Do you have any idea?
I went around to find it, but...
I can't find it.
I can't find it by myself.
I understand.
I'll help you find it.
Takumi!
Absolutely find it,
or Kurumi-chan will be hurt.
Ok?
Hey...
What?
It's free if you accept it, right?
I'll properly say it if you find it.
The "thank you".
I can't find it.
I think it's in someone's room.
Onii-chan...
Please be Kurumi's papa...
Not here, huh?
It's not here.
I'm searching for something right now.
I see.
What's the thing Director looking for?
It's a piece of the puzzle.
Please tell me if you find it.
Welcome! Let's start the class.
Oh no... I'm busy right now.
What? I'm busy right now.
Aoi's brooch...
Aoi hasn't entered this room.
Hey Takumi!
Good timing, I was looking for you.
Aki-san, I can't find Aoi's brooch.
Can Aki-san help me find it?
Hm? Ok, I'll help find it.
So could you apologize to that lively nurse?
What have you done?
Hmm... Well earlier, I just asked that girl named Kurumi...
Hey, could you let me see?
W-What do you want to see?
Please let me see you two kissing...
Ku... Kurumi-chan...
A Kiss?
The close girl and boy will kiss each other, right?
K-Kurumi-chan, who taught you that?
From that outsider named Aki-oneesan.
She said that those who become Papa and Mama will do that.
So Takumi-oniichan and Aoi-oneechan are close so you can do it, right?
Kurumi-chan... No way...
You can't?
What are we going to do, Aoi?
Let's do it.
Eh?
A-Aoi...
Stay still.
Close your eyes!
She's asleep.
I see.
Why did you kiss me?
We had no choice at that time.
Is that the reason?
Even though it was my first kiss....
I see.
Don't say "I see"!
You dull snob fool!
Ouch! Didn't Kurumi-chan say we should get together?
Yes we got together.
Don't be impudent, that that was my first kiss!
Ouch...! It hurts!
It hurts!
Amano-san is late.
I think I'll go look for her.
Director?
He's not here, huh?
This feeling...
Please rape me step father...
punish me...
Aoi likes shoes, eh?
I really think Midori needs my training always.
You shouldn't shake your ass like that.
This is a punishment you know.
It's wet, Midori.
What are you fawning at? This is a punishment.
Midori!
Don't pull back your hips!
Raise your ass just like before.
Good girl, Midori...
My dick is coming inside Midori...
Good.
Good Midori...
Yes... You're really a good girl Midori...
I'm cumming...
Midori...
What is it?
Amano-san is...
She said something about a Key and she went out.
As you can see I'm busy right now.
Where did she go?
I don't know.
Eh...  Uhm...
I said that I was busy, didn't I?
Sorry...
What is it? We're going to sleep now.
I'm looking for Amano-san.
I saw her a while ago, she said something about the key in the elevator.
I don't care about that.
What happened to her?
She took some medicine a while ago so...
I think she can sleep properly tonight.
A medicine? For the illness?
Promise not to tell about it.
It's weird, but every night...
I think Aoi-san herself doesn't want to know about it.
I see.
Takumi-sama, also needs to rest.
She's not here as I thought.
Kurumi-chan.
You're cute...
As I thought...
Playing Doctor game ... ... ...
I'm feeling so good inside my stomach
Please forgive me
Delicious mushroom.
Kurumi is... 18 years old.
I'm already an adult, so I know how to eat the mushroom.
I'll suck it a lot.
And... squeeze it.
I'll lick it with my tongue.
and...
I'll tickle it.
But I can't bite it.
If I bite it,
I'll get punched, spanked and kicked.
Please forgive me... please forgive me.
But... sensei is crying and hugs me tightly.
It's alright, it's not Kurumi-chan's fault.
He was so kind and did it many times.
Kurumi was so happy and crying.
I love sensei.
I love sensei's mushroom.
I'll eat sensei's mushroom everyday.
Amano-san, are you here?
Again...
Hinoki... why did you die?
Which part do you feel?
I'm having sex with that person...
As I thought.
Which part do you feel?
It disappeared!
Hinoki-chan... What are you?
Aoi?
Why? I thought you were injected earlier?
Aoi!? Aoi!
Again...
Who did this?
Aoi?
Or is it Amano-san?
Ouch...
Aoi!!!
Amano-san!!!