I really like your dick, Onii!
Only my dick?
Of course, I love YOU too, Onii.
Me too, I love you Onii-chan!
Then get along and make my dick feel good together.
Okay!
Wow! Onii's dick is so big! Isn't it amazing, Hiyo?
Yes. Y-You know, I love the perverted Onii-chan more than the normal one.
Hey Hiyo, that's not fair. I was thinking about kissing it first.
Wow, your dick is throbbing in my mouth.
Does it feel good, Onii?
Does Hiyo's fellatio feel good?
I have to meet Nee-chan's expectations.
Your pre-cum is delicious, Onii!
Onii-chan, you look so pleased, is Onee-chan better than me?
Onee-chan don't be so rough with him.
I'm about to...
Look, Onii-chan is about to cum!
It seems Onii's going to spray his cum hard.
Onii, please cum on my face,
Please cum all over Hiyori's face!
It's cumming!
Wow, you came a lot!
I'm cumming again!
Onii-chan, pour it all over Hiyori's face too!
So much semen! How was it? Were we good?
My pussy is so wet now...
I want to feel good with Onii too!
It's in!
Onii's dick is in my slutty pussy!
Amazing!
Go ahead please thrust it deeper in to my wet pussy
Hit the spot deep inside to make me feel good.
A-Amazing!
If you're rough like that I'll cum straight away!
D-Don't look at my asshole, you meanie!
You look so cute!
I'm cumming!
M-Me too!
Cum inside!
Let it out inside me!
I came... Onii, you meanie, you made me cum!
Onii-chan, please use my wet pussy to feel good.
Hiyori!
If you push in so deep you're going to break my pussy!
Your dick is thrusting in and out of my pussy!
I'm cumming!
You're cumming... You're cumming a lot inside my pussy!
I'm sucking in all your semen, Onii-chan!
Give me more! I want your semen in my pussy too!
I want more than Hiyori! Cum a lot!
Cum inside my pussy!
Do it rough from behind too, treat me like a dog!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... You're in so deep!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
W
Imouto Paradise!
Little Sister Paradise!
I-It was a dream?
Good morning, Nii-san!
Eh? A-Aya?
Wow, Nii-san, it's hard as a rock!
I came to wake you up, but you had a boner, so...
I thought I would calm it down.
Nii-san, is this good?
I'll lick it more.
If you feel good then I'm happy too.
Just doing this makes me so...
Aya, I'm about to...
You can cum in my mouth if you want.
I'll drink it all for you.
S-So good...
You can be rougher, Nii-san.
A-Aya...
Nii-san...
Amazing! It's in so deep!
Yes... Yes!
Please cum in my mouth!
Cum inside my mouth!
You don't have to drink it, you know...
It's fine, I want to drink it.
I'm fine with it...
I don't care whether it's my pussy or my asshole...
I'll do anything for you, Nii-san.
Aya...
Nii-san, do you hate a sister who does this kind of thing?
I don't, but...
I'm...
Nii-san?
Ok for now.
Aya... Thanks.
It's delicious, Onee-chan!
It was on sale at the supermarket...
I bought a lot of it.
Don't eat it all at once.
Ok!
Aya! Where did Onii and Rio-chi go?
He's in Rio-chan's room. She wanted to ask him about her computer.
Since we had sex for the first time...
Nii-san started to...
change a little bit.
Even if I ask for it...
He is never in the mood...
I feel like...
I'm being avoided.
What should I do?
~Let's do it more! Onii-chan!~
Wh-What is this?
This... this kind of...
Th... This is so perverted!
Huh?
But you're the one who asked to see a porn site.
Well... yeah... b-but...
I... um...
I don't really know much about sex...
I want to learn more about it...
And I thought Aniki would know about it...
Could it be that your pussy's already wet?
Eh!? Wh...
Wh-What are you saying? Obviously not!
Really?
You don't believe me? Then check for yourself!
Ok! W-Wait...! Really?!
Hmm...
It does look like it's dry.
See, I told you so!
But if you look carefully...
What!? Give it back to me now!
Rio!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Rio... I...
I have one more favor to ask...
Eh? Ok...
Why do I have to do something like this?
Rio, I told you earlier, didn't I?
Please say it for me... please!
Jeez... fine.
I'm a pervert who gives her brother a footjob and gets a wet pussy from it!
Rio, you're so perverted.
Doing these kinds of things and getting turned on!
You're the one making me say it!
Amazing!
Rio... it feels so good!
No way, you're leaking precum just from getting a footjob!
How's this? You're really wet now, aren't you?
Look at you! You're the one with a rock hard cock!
I'm about to cum!
It can't be... You're really cumming?
I'm cumming!
Cumming! I'm cumming from your foot!
No... So much... It's like you pissed on me...
My pussy is so wet I can't stand anymore! Please put your dick in!
Rio, you're such a slut.
I asked you properly, didn't I?
Please hurry!
Nothing has entered here yet, right?
Wait... That's...
No... it's going in! Your penis is in my asshole!
So tight...
My ass... No...
Amazing! It's going in so easily!
No way... Am I feeling good from my ass?
Rio, you really are a pervert...
Why am I feeling good just from my ass?
Be quiet, or else everyone is going to hear you.
No...
Who would've thought you would like anal so much?
Don't...
If everyone else knew about this...
Don't! Don't!
I'm cumming... Hurry up and cum!
Yes... Keep it up... Rio...
More! More! Do my ass harder!
Please tease me from the front too!
Rio!
Aniki, I'm going to cum...
from anal sex!
No... Don't touch... I'm going to go crazy!
Give it to me! Shoot your semen into my ass!
Spray it in me!
Spray your cum!
I'm cumming!
Amazing... so tight...
Aniki's semen is coming out!
Your semen is entering my stomach!
So much!
Nii-sama!
Huh?
Nii-sama, wake up.
Hmm? Michika?
Eh... What?!
What the hell...? My body is...
Be quiet.
You've been acting weird lately.
What you...
desire is also...
my desire...
I... this kind of thing...
See, Nii-sama... this is the proof.
How is it?
It's in so deep...
It looks like you're going to cum straight away...
I'll drink it all, so you can cum all you want.
Michika!
I'm cumming!
So this is how Nii-sama tastes...
You drank it all?
H... Hey, Michika...
You came a lot!
Nii-sama, you aren't satisfied with just once, are you?
Your semen is all mine!
You can cum in me all you want!
I'm cumming! I-It's coming!
Nii-sama, not yet... You'll feel much better if you take your time.
I'm cumming!
If I stimulate you here you should be able to cum many times!
See, you're rock hard again...
If I stimulate you even more...
You came a lot again.
Nii-sama...
I'll give you my virginity.
Wh-Why?
Because this is what I want...
Nii-sama, how does my pussy feel?
Being able to give you my virginity makes me so happy.
My duty is to pleasure your dick.
Nii-sama, can you see it?
Can you see your dick going in my pussy? Look at it!
I can wrap my pussy around your dick by squeezing.
Nii-sama, I feel really good!
Let my pussy make your dick feel good!
It's going in deeper and deeper!
It's hitting deep inside me!
Yes... your dick is saying it feels good!
It's about to cum inside me!
You can cum deep inside!
I'll make you cum deep inside my womb!
I'm cumming! I'm...
All your cum is outside...
That was really close...
Why, Nii-sama?
Well, that's because...
Michika...
I see.
What a shame.
Aya, where are the others?
Michika-chan went to the library.
Koharu-chan is at her club.
Hiyori-chan and Rio-chan said that they were going to a friends house.
I see.
Aren't you going anywhere?
We're rarely alone together these days, so...
Yeah...
I guess that's true.
N-Nii-san...
Nii-san, I...
have a favor to ask.
Aya...
Take a video of me masturbating.
It's embarrassing, but I have to do it.
Amazing Aya.
If I do dirty things Nii-san will surely get turned on.
Nii-san, are you watching?
Are you feeling it? Does my body look... dirty?
Amazing... Aya...
Is it ok, even if I'm a slutty sister?
A-Aya, thrust your hips up and show me.
Look!
Look at my wet pussy.
This feels too good.
I can't hold on much longer...
This... This is...
too dirty.
Nii-san, I can't stop!
I'm cumming!
This feels too good!
Oh no... Nii-san, I'm cumming from being videoed...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! This is a big one...
No, I can't hold it!
I... I came a lot.
Aya!
Give it to me!
It's embarrassing...
I can't hold on any longer...
Your pussy is so wet it went in straight away.
No... I just came so my pussy is really sensitive! I feel really good!
It's your fault, Aya...
It's because you did that...
Amazing... Aya, I can't stop!
It's in so deep... Nii-san's dick is hitting me so deep inside!
I can't hold on much longer!
It's okay, Nii-san... I just came a lot, so you cum a lot this time!
Look... So much semen...
Make me your private semen doll!
Aya... You're such a pervert...
You're this wet...
I'm going to cum straight away...
If you keep teasing me like that...
Cumming...
If you keep...
Cum a lot...
So much inside...
Amazing...
It's sucking it in...
Onii-chan...
He's making up with Aya at the moment, isn't he?
I'd be annoyed if they didn't.
We all even left the house so they could be alone.
Nii-sama... he refused to cum inside me...
Hiyori too... we haven't been together in a while...
It's because he's concerned about Aya...
It's hard to admit, but they do suit each other, so lets cheer for them, ok?
I wonder if he'll still be our Onii-chan?
We can't say anything about that.
It all depends on those two.
Yeah...
It's so embarrassing, but...
If Nii-san likes it, then...
I'll do anything.
Please...
Shove your dick up my wet pussy!
No...
Nii-san, you're too rough!
I'm cumming... Aya!
Okay... let it out... let it out inside...
Cumming! I'm cumming!
Amazing, Nii-san...
Do me more!
Cum inside me more!
I'm cumming again!
Cum inside!
Look...
Look at your semen coming out of my dirty pussy!
Aya...
You're too erotic..
It's delicious...
Nii-san, your semen is very delicious!
No... You're too rough...I'm cumming... I'm cumming again!
I... I didn't know you were such a slutty sister...
Nii-san, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... I'm cumming!
Cumming!
I came in again...
Let me eat Onii-chan's semen...
I'm cumming again!
Amazing... So much...
Nii-san, please cum all over my apron...
Amazing... Amazing...
Your dick's so hard...
Do it... Cum all over my face like you did...
Give me your semen...
So much... on my face...
Semen...
Amazing...
I'm filled with semen...
So much came out...
No... I can't...
I'm going to go crazy...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
No...
I'm cumming again...
I'm cumming once again...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
Aya, I'm cumming again...
Nii-san, it's amazing...
I'm going to break...
Eww!
What's this?
What exactly happened here?
Pervert!
It's because Nii-san fucked me so much...
Me? Is it only my fault? Aya, you also...
Goosh! What the hell is this?!
Getting yourself dragged off by this perverted Aniki.
I'm sorry... I was so happy that you guys left us alone...
The only reason we left was for research...
Yeah!
Even so, you guys have gone too far...
There is such a thing as a limit... a limit!
Are you listening? Do you understand?
Listen Onii-chan...
You're still my Onii-chan, right?
That's obvious!
I'm still your Onii-chan and I always will be.
I'm so glad!
Then lend him to me sometimes.
If Aya can have you, then I can have you too, right!
Yay!
What the hell are you saying?!
If that's it then I want him as well.
Eh?!
W-What?!
No, you can't!
Nii-san is mine!
No! Onii is everyone's!
Where did my human rights go?
Hm!
For a sister-lover like you...
There are no human rights!
There are no "human rights" in loving one's little sister. By Rio
W-Well, this isn't good.
Don't act all love struck!
Who do you think is the bad one here?!
You pervert!
Sister-complex...
Moron, fool, idiot!
You perverted brother!
And then...
I...
Died...
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, love me more, Onii-chan
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, motto suki shite, Onii-chan.
Uchuu ichi no ai o sodatete
Let’s create the biggest love in the universe.
Futari no paradise
Into our paradise.
Kisu kisu shite (chu!)
Kiss me, kiss me (smooch!)
Asa wa ohayou kou to yutte
I tell you good morning when you wake up.
Okocchau no nee ii deshou?
Why are you mad? I don’t see anything wrong with that.
(Nee, okite!)
(Wake up, sweetie!)
Kyou wa futari de dekakeyou yo
Let’s go out together today.
Te o tsunaide arukitai no
I want to hold hands while we walk.
(Hayaku! Hayaku!)
(Hurry! Hurry!)
Ano ne, sono ne, kore de yasashiku
But listen, well, you’re still sweet to me.
Atama o nadete kureru
When you pat my head.
Itsumo sore ga ureshiin da yo
That always makes me happy.
Kyou mo asu mo saki mo zutto hanasanai yo
Today and tomorrow and always, don’t ever let me go.
(Issho!)
(Together!)
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, motto suki shite Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, love me more, Onii-chan.
Kitto mitsume atta nara
I’m sure that if you look into my eyes,
Mou koko wa paradise
I’ll be in paradise.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, ooki na ai de, Onii-chan
Onii-chan, Onii-chan, with your big love, Onii-chan,
Mou konna sekai no mannaka de
I know the world we’re in is awful,
Futari no paradise.
But we have our own paradise.
Kisu kisu shiyou (chu)
Let’s kiss, let’s kiss (smooch)