Thick juice is coming out of the tip of your penis, Toya.
My body is getting hot...
Amazing.
Now it's even harder.
I can feel the blood vessels.
The scent of your penis is filling my mouth.
Don't hold yourself back.
Spray lots of your filth into my mouth!
Yeah, it's progressing very well.
Continue along these lines.
Yes, I understand.
You really have gotten a lot better Yumi.
That's because Kanzaka-san's advice is so good.
Yeah, yeah...
Then maybe Kanzaka-san should also look at my scenario.
Hey! Rumi I'll take a look at it so don't yank on my jacket.
Hey, Director.
I'll check your work too, so it'd better be good.
A-Ah, yes.
Kanzaka Itsuki-san.
We asked an advertising firm, the Souma Agency, to sponsor our creation of a new adult game.
He's the chief of SA.
He's such a good businessman that it's almost a waste to have him work at our start-up.
Not only does he take care of the business side of things,
he can also give us advice based on his experiences from working at a game manufacturer.
He's arrogant but friendly and handsome.
He's like a reliable older brother.
Well, that's about it. I've seen nice improvements in other areas.
I know, right?
Then there isn't anything wrong with giving a reward, is there?
Onee-chan!
Fine, but I've got work elsewhere today, so maybe next time.
Really?
It's a promise!
Yeah.
Then I'll be leaving for my other work.
FFFappers presents
Yume Kui ~Tsurumiku Shiki Game Seisaku~
The voice actor Fujinomori Akiho has been highly recommended lately.
Although she's a newcomer, she's quite popular.
I think her games will sell well.
I see photos of her quite often nowadays.
I see.
Last minute changes are tough, but I'll find a way to fit her in the cast.
As I thought, hearing this from beautiful Izumi-sama is the best.
You said the same thing about me.
And that was yesterday.
Was it?
Really?
Ah, Takatsuki-san, Welcome.
Long time no see.
Are you well?
Long time no see, Noe-san.
And who's that over there...
Kanzaka?
It's been a while.
Yo!
SFC business chief, Takatsuki-san.
What're you doing here?
I thought I heard you transferred to a major venture company.
I did.
I was dispatched to SA from there.
SA?
Aren't they our business rivals?
Our ties won't ever be cut, will they?
So what are you doing here?
Something...
I'm having a small conversation, partly to check out the market.
Don't do business at this sort of time.
It's troublesome for Tempu-san.
Honestly...
Hey, let's go.
Okay.
Who's that beautiful woman that's with Takatsuki?
Oh, you mean Kitahama Kyouko-san?
She works for Takatsuki-san and is the daughter of SFC's director.
Maybe she's following Takatsuki-san to learn the ropes.
The director's daughter.
Yo.
You're Kanzaka-san, aren't you?
Are you also here for business?
Yeah.
I see.
Is it okay for you not to be with Takatsuki?
He doesn't need me...
No one's expecting something from a girl who's only riding on her parents coat-tails.
You're really beautiful.
And that's your strong-point.
You can use it to get promoted.
No, I...
I see.
Your eyes tell me you aren't satisfied with how things are.
Read this.
This is the draft of our new game.
I want to hear your opinion.
This is the first time someone's asked me about something like this.
Payback!! Miko-chu!!
Pure Miko's Adventure Game.
Draft
Umm, if you wouldn't mind, could I send you an email or something...
I'd like a chance to talk to you.
Sure. I'll be waiting.
It's me.
I see.
Tomorrow at the recording studio, as usual.
Got it.
My stomach...
Inside my stomach...
I'm being stirred up...
No...
Toya-kun...
I'm so happy.
It's okay.
Cum!
I'll take all of your sperm.
Cum inside me!
Toya-kun...
This voice actor can really perform.
It's too bad Yumi couldn't come, but I'm glad you did.
Well...
I'm sure if Yumi heard this, she'd go red as a beet and faint...
It's probably for the best that she's not here.
I've got another reward in mind for Yumi.
Hearing the scenario I wrote being read aloud is really embarrassing, though.
And to boot, the voice actor's giving such a raunchy performance that it's turning me on.
Oh no, my pussy is getting wet...
And my nipples are getting hard under my bra.
I wonder if that voice actor is excited...
N-Never mind...
What am I saying?
I'm sorry.
You don't like it?
No.
It was just so sudden that I was a bit surprised.
Oh no.
I'm getting into a strange mood.
And on top of that, the way Kanzaka-san is holding me is making my heart pound.
You're breathing pretty hard there.
What happened, Rumi?
What is it?
Did the sound of lovemaking turn you on?
No...
T-That's not it...
Stop it.
D-Don't squeeze my breast like that.
No.
Don't touch my nipple.
My nipples are getting hard.
No! Don't look!
My pussy is wet.
It's embarrassing.
No, don't touch it.
If you start touching me there,
then it'll get really wet.
It's getting so soaked that it's making indecent sounds.
It's really starting to feel good...
No!
If you keep doing that, then I...
I...
NO!
Guess I overdid it a bit.
Thanks for the good work.
Yeah, thanks for everything.
I'm sorry for the extra lines at such short notice.
No problem.
I'm in a restaurant.
Want to join me?
Kyoko
Received
Reply
X
I'm sorry, but something urgent came up.
Next time, I'll take you to a delicious ramen place that even someone like you wouldn't know.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sorry. I drank a little too much.
Although I invited you, I've only caused trouble.
Don't worry. I want to talk to you about something.
My place isn't very big, but feel free to make yourself at home.
Okay.
Excuse the intrusion.
Kanzaka-san.
Who is that man?
Hey, why are you getting so frightened?
Kanzaka-san, what's happening?
I gave you the scenario before, didn't I?
Yes...
It said payback and Miko-chu, if I recall correctly.
Magical girl...
Was there something wrong with-
You showed that to Takatsuki, didn't you?
I did not!
Apparently, Takatsuki brought a new scenario to a magazine the other day,
and its plot devices are similar to our new work.
What's the meaning of this?
No! I didn't show it to anyone!
You won't even listen to my side of the story.
I only handed it to you because I trusted you.
It's really true!
Please believe me!
You can say what you want.
No!
Stop it!
Please, stop!
I really didn't...
S-Stop!
I would... I would never betray you.
That hurts!
No! Don't look!
You're the one who acknowledged me. I didn't want you to see it.
An accident?
Yes.
Long ago.
I don't want anyone to see this terrible wound.
You either, Kanzaka-san.
Yeah...
But I love it!
A beautiful woman with a secret hidden behind her bangs...
You're a lot more mysterious and charming than the other random swines.
Kanzaka-san.
Don't be so rough.
Hey now, you do realize you're being interrogated, don't you?
I'm forcing this on you, not trying to make you happy!
I... wasn't really...
Liar.
Just look at your wet pussy. You're loving it.
I really didn't do anything to betray you.
Is that so?
Then I'll violate you with this.
Now's your chance to confess.
I-I didn't do anything!
I see.
Then prepare yourself.
No!
As I'd expect from a virgin, it's really tight.
It hurts!
Well?
You'll keep denying it even though I've taken your virginity?
I don't mind.
It makes me happy that you're making me a real woman.
You...
What does make me sad is the fact that you don't believe me.
Please believe in me!
I didn't do it!
You think that much of me?
Then, Kyouko, will you follow me even if you have to betray SFC and help me with any crime?
Of course!
I'll do anything if it means I can be with you.
That's good.
From today on you will be my slave!
Master.
What?
What is this?
Inside of my pussy...
Master's dick is gouging me out!
I can hear it grinding!
I'm becoming weird!
Hey, come on. It's too early to get worn out.
It's...
so deep...
It's so deep that it's reaching my womb!
Master's dick is going to break my womb!
Rough...
It's too rough...
Inside...
You're cumming inside me!
Master, your hot semen is filling my womb!
I'm f-full of semen... I'm gonna get pregnant...
What is that?!
I thought I'd use this to prove that you're my slave.
Nipple piercings.
They look pretty swell, y'know?
W-Wait!
Yo.
Kanzaka-san.
You know...
my computer broke, so I came here to buy a new one.
Well then, I'll pay for it as an apology for the other day.
R-Really?!
It's a good thing that your apartment is near.
I'm sorry I made you pay for something so expensive.
It's really not all that much.
But you didn't complain at all and spent a lot of money on it.
I was surprised.
So are we even?
Y-Yeah...
You're really broad-minded and never complain.
So I felt you're kind of manly and cool.
Well, you'll have to work hard in return.
Hey!
What's with this half-assed scenario?
Did you think these dry, boring sex scenes were going to cut it?!
I've never had sex, so of course my scripts won't feel realistic!
Besides, why is the director here?
And who is that woman?
Hey, Kyouko.
Yes.
Why have you got those?!
I'm sorry, Rumi-chan.
I said we shouldn't do it, but Kanazaka-san forced me to.
Look. You look like you were feeling good in these pictures.
You can write the script well if you think back to then, right?
But if you say you can't...
Then there's no other choice but to give you experience.
What?
Kyouko.
Yes, Master.
No!
Don't lick me there.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Good! You understand, don't you?
Your resistance only makes my penis harder.
I didn't know that.
Stop it!
No...
D-Don't lick it.
Hey.
What should I do this time?
You can go masturbate over there.
N-No way.
No.
Hey.
We're trying to give you experience here, so don't go getting off on it.
Start typing on that keyboard so you won't forget.
That's impossible.
What is that?!
I thought that I could help you write a more erotic scenario.
You're lying!
No!
You can't!
You can't! You can't!
Don't rub your dick on my pussy.
Stop it.
Please, I beg you.
I'm begging you!
Rumi.
Have you seen what happens in an erotic game when they say "stop"?
No!
No! No!
It's my first time!
So you can't put something so big and hard in.
There's no way it'll go in!
I-It hurts!
Stop it.
Stop!
This pain is a unique flavor of your first sexual experience.
Savor it as much as possible.
I don't want this pain anymore!
It'll feel good soon enough.
That's what your scenario says, too!
That's different...
Don't be so rough
or you'll break my pussy.
Hurry up and type. If you don't make any progress on the scenario before I ejaculate, then I'll cum inside you.
T-That's...
Don't do that!
Hey.
Yes.
Wait!
Who are you calling?
Yumi.
She'll be getting worried about now.
You have to tell her that you won't be coming home tonight and that she doesn't need to worry, okay?
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
You don't want Yumi to kick up a fuss and have it wind up a tragedy for the both of you.
You have five minutes.
You have to deal with Yumi by then.
If you don't then I'll cum inside.
And if you say more than you need to, I'll coax Yumi into coming here.
Give me a minute!
Hello.
Onee-chan?
Yeah, Yumi.
Where are you now, Onee-chan?
Why haven't you called?
Ah...
I'm sorry.
I've just been really busy and haven't had the time to call.
Jeez.
You just went to buy a computer, didn't you?
The stores are all closed already and you didn't call, so I started to worry when you didn't come home.
Sorry.
So? Where are you now?
Well...
At a friend's house.
Friend?
Who are they?
Where do they live?
Is it someone I know?
That's a little secret.
Don't worry, I'll be back in not too long.
Not long? How long's that?
What did you have to do that was so urgent?
No.
I will back in a few days.
Onee-chan, what happened?
Are you all right?!
Hey, Onee-chan!
It's nothing, I'm fine.
I will back in a few days, so don't worry.
Unfortunately you're almost out of time.
Okay! I'll do it!
I'll work here! I don't have any more time... I'll do my work...
So please understand, Yumi.
Hey, Onee-chan.
What happened?!
Onee-chan!
No!
Don't pound me so hard!
It feels so good.
I don't want this.
I really don't want this.
My hips...
My hips started to...
His dick is getting me soaked.
My pussy is so wet and messy.
But it's so good.
I can't stand this!
It's time!
I will cum inside, just as I promised.
Wait!
My womb...
Not inside my womb.
No!
Semen is coming!
It's coming!
No!
Hey... Onee-chan!
What happened?
What was that sound?
What was so urgent?
Hey, are you all right?
She's fine.
You don't have to worry.