Hello.
Huh? He isn't around?
Why are we hiding?
She'd definitely misunderstand if she saw us like this!
No way.
There is  in fact a reason to misunderstand.
Could you keep quiet, please?
I'm going to ask her about the panties.
Wait!
Sorry.
Please be quiet for now.
Yuki-san's nipples,
are touching my arm!
Aikawa-kun, you're rubbing it hard.
I'm starting to feel kinda weird.
Not good.
I want to do dirty things to her again!
Crap.
What was that sound?
Is someone there?
Let's move in further.
We're so close to each other, and I'm reaching my limit!
Oh.
There it is!
Oh crap.
I have to take a bath and go to my part-time job!
What did you just do?!
I'm home.
Episode 4: If there's a hole, there's a way.
Welcome back.
Huh?
Unyuu-san?
Wait, why?
She's going to live with us now.
Say what?!
Unyuu-san, this is Shimizu.
I'm going to be blunt here.
Aikawa-kun did something dirty to you, right?
Actually, he did the same to me.
So I've been thinking,
it's dangerous for us to be alone.
That's why...
Just wait a sec,
three under this tiny room?
That's impossible, no matter how you put it!
It's fine, right?
I think. We've got different work shifts, anyway.
Wait, what about my life?
What's gonna happen now?!
Oh, sorry!
I didn't notice,
and I'm all sweaty here.
Then, wanna bathe with me?
Of course... we can't.
No problem!
Well... I have this upcoming play.
Help me out with my practice.
Please.
What kind of role is this?
But, I guess I'll just go with the flow.
Hey, want me to remove my towel?
Just stay like that.
But you can't bathe while wearing it.
All right already,
but I'm not looking.
I definitely won't!
Sure, sure.
But, I can still visualize her shapely body, so this is futile!
Hey.
Something's hitting my back.
We can't do anything dirty today, okay?
R-Restrain yourself.
I need to restrain myself.
Keep it under control.
Hey, come on.
You can't wash me properly if you don't look.
Here.
Restrain...
...What do I need to restrain again?