I want to ask you for that second favor.
I want to you to choose me, and only me, from now on...
Kei-chan!
Takato-kun...
My Senpai passed, didn't he?
Stop that...
We have confirmed entry with the key...
You may pass...
You will pass through in intervals from here onwards.
Once the interval has expired you will move onto the next level.
Everyone... I can see you're all tired.
You should try and recover as much as possible before the next interval.
Rather than rest, we should strategize...
There's no need, that voice told us all the rules. Just follow those and you'll be fine.
I don't argue with that. but I refuse to believe that we'll fail no matter what we try.
Rika doesn't want to do this. Isn't there a way we can try to escape?...
Even by just thinking about running away you risk losing your life in there.
Manaka-san! Don't say something like that, even as a joke!
Careful, your babysitter will get angry with you, little girl!
Let's not argue, we're just all a bit on edge right now.
Let's take a little break.
Excuse me, I'll be doing some research...
It would be great if there was a place to rest.
I'm so hungry...
Are you going out with Manaka-san?
You kissed her, right?
I...
don't want to tell you what happened.
You know, you can choose me instead, if you like...
You shouldn't rely entirely on Manaka-san... and if it's you... it's... it's okay...
Kanae...
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
Let's go!
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
Zero!
The check will now begin.
The players for the next game have been decided.
Participants, please step forward.
Please select your key.
30...
29...
28...
27...
26...
25...
24...
23...
22...
21...
Now, all I have to do is choose...
20...
19...
18...
I insist that you always choose me.
I don't want anyone to know my secret, that Nemu has...
What should I do?
What do I do?
Do I choose Nemu? Just like in the first level?
Or do I go against Nemu's wishes?
Whoever I choose, Nemu will never give up, never go away.
The most important thing is that I do what I have to do, and do it well,
without letting any of them know what I'm doing.
What should I do? Who should I choose?
I choose...
Hokari Kanae...
Would all participants please move into the next room.
Countdown has begun.
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
The key and keyhole have been chosen.
Of all the women in that line, I chose Kanae of my own free will.
I'm happy you chose me.
You don't have to be gentle to me, it's okay.
Let's leave here together.
Keyhole
: Vagina
Number of times to ejaculate
:  Once
Play
Hard
These are the rules of the game...
Play hard.
This is what I have to do... steal Kanae's virginity...  It's so sudden.
No! I have to decide what I'm going to do and just do it...
I chose her, it's my responsibility.
She's scared?
Not me.
I'm not...
I've seen this scene before.
Kei-chan, wait...
Kanae...
It hurts...
My virginity... it hurts...
I-It hurts, it hurts, Kei-chan...
Yes Kanae, that face, that pained face.
It hurts, right? Yes, it hurts!
That's good. More!
Your penis is... all the way inside me, slapping against me...
Are you going to cum? Are you?
Ow, that hurts!
I wanted to see your face twisted in pain... Kanae.
Level check...
Would the participants and keyhole please leave together.
Three rounds left, right?
Yeah...
I'm just going to take a shower, then I'll be right back.
This is going to get darker and darker, little by little...
my relationship with Kanae.
If it goes any further...
If it goes any further, I might not mind it.
... I wouldn't forgive myself, Kanae...
It wouldn't be right at all.
Why am I fantasizing about all of this?
My fantasies are stealing reality from me.
This white room is like a nightmare
It's become a way of life for us...
A dark, cruel way of life.
I don't want to be anywhere near Kanae.
Next is Round 2.
Are you going to choose Kanae for every round from here on in?
I have nothing to say to you. Leave me alone.
I won't...
What if I say that?
No matter what you say, I won't lose focus.
I love watching people fall from grace. I can't stand the pleasure.
So you're a voyeur, eh? Do you really think you won't get hurt from this?
Yes. After all, there's surely one woman that you really desire more than the others.
Shut up! Go away!
You just love making her scream.
She's just a body with holes you want to open up.
A big piece of meat called "woman".
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
You know you want to treat her badly,
fucking her while you see the pain and desperation on her face.
And then, amidst the extreme ecstasy, you want to cum inside of her.
Shut up! Shut the fuck up!
This school girl that I really want to hurt...
This girl with beautiful skin and body and hair...
The girl that I really want to fuck up...
Is this girl in front of me now.
Stop it...
Kei-chan... stop it... stop it...
Just when it was getting interesting, this little hussy had to get in the way.
Don't you know...?
Dying is the highest form of ecstasy...
Enough. Don't make Kei-chan any more hurt.
You think that just because he chose you, that you have the right to tell me what to do?
I know Kei better than you! I've known him longer and understand him better...
You're just a fuck-hole to him.
Even if I am, it makes no difference... because I love Kei...
I'm surprised, this piece of meat with a cute face is in love...
You may have known him when he was a child
But I know your boyfriend in ways that you never could.
You're lying!
Nemu! Stop!
I know his real nature better than you.
Stop! No more! No more!
It's okay, Kei. Whatever you say, it's okay.
Kanae...
She's stroking my cheek
So gently.
So gently... Just like the way she handled my instrument.
Please make your next choice.
Hokari Kanae.
The next choice is Hokari Kanae.
In the end, Kanae will smile.
She'll "smile"? Am I fucking insane?
Human Toilet
her mouth will be open. Kanae... Whatever I do, she'll take it.
That's why this is no good.
More. More!
She'll accept the worst of everything until she comes to desire it.
Hokari Kanae.
It'll only escalate from here.
Her feelings
My lust...
Our heartbeats...
It'll escalate without limits.
Hokari Kanae.
Participants have been confirmed.
Don't say that anymore.
What do you mean by "that"?
What you said to Nemu. Whatever happens, nothing will change your feelings.
Oh, that!
I just couldn't take it.
Holes: Eye, Vagina, Butt
Number of times to ejaculate
: Careful
Play
: Hard
I just didn't want Manaka-san to have you. I didn't want her to steal you from me.
I've always loved you, Kei-chan.
I've known you the longest...
Isn't that right?
Kanae...
I can do anything... so... Kei-chan...
Look at me...
Kanae's pussy is small, and the lips are light in color.
Her nipples are also light in color. She seems pure, but I bet there's more to the story.
I've never touched my own pussy...
You understand what I'm about to do to your pussy, don't you?
I want to see your face in pained pleasure
Yes. My body is Kei-chan's property.
It's all yours, my master.
You're my pleasure slave. My piece of meat.
Yes, master!
My nipples...
my nipples are falling asleep, soon blood flow to them will be cut off...
If this hurts, you'll never make it through to the end,
and if that happens, both you and I will die...
I can't let that happen!
I'll never let you die, Kei-chan!
Do you understand, Kanae?
There are vibrators in your pussy and your ass.
Electric pads on your inner thighs and clips on your pussy lips and clit.
Do you know which vibrator is bigger?
The one in my pussy or my ass? Which one is bigger?
I don't know...
Squeeze your pussy and ass and feel which one is bigger.
The one in my ass is bigger!
Thats right. Let's give you a reward.
Are you in pain?
My nipples and clit...
My pussy lips are tingling and my ass is vibrating.
I'm a little scared...
The vibrator in my pussy is rubbing against the vibrator in my ass.
My nipples are falling asleep. My stomach is vibrating all the way to my intestines.
Does that feel good? Your pussy is starting to get wet.
My tickling pussy is vibrating, getting tighter and wetter, and starting to drip.
From here on in, you will feel no pain, only pleasure.
You are now a nymphomaniac, and you need that pleasure to exist.
No, stop, I can't take anymore! It hurts!
No, you're wrong, Kanae. It feels good.
Whatever happens, it feels good. Get it?
Yes, I understand... It feels good, master.
Say it, Kanae...
Yes, it feels so good, this electricity...
Now, the next level. Does it feel good, Kanae?
No...
You're wrong, Kanae! Say it! Say it feels good!
It feels good, master! I love the electricity!
Well, if it feels good, you should be able to handle more, so I can turn up the current.
No, it's okay it feels good like this, so you can turn it up even more! Give me more current!
It hurts! It hurts!
Does it feel good? It feels good, right?
Do the vibrations in your ass feel good while your pussy and nipples go numb?
It feels good, it feels good, the vibrators are going crazy in my pussy and ass!
This is a level of electricity that would knock out any normal, unprepared woman.
There's only one way to get her to go over the top. I have to put it to full power!
This is... the final stage...
Unless you say it feels good, this will continue forever.
Your nipples, your pussy,
your asshole, your brains, until they are destroyed, it will continue forever.
Kanae...
Kanae... It feels good right?
It feels good! Ah, I'm pissing! I can't stop... I'm pissing!
Doesn't it feel great, Kanae? Say it!
It feels good, so good, my pussy cant stop coming, I'm going to pieces, it feels too good!
I've never seen Kanae like this before. Is this the real Kanae?
I took that kind little Kanae to this point of no return. I did this.
Kanae, does it feel good? It feels so good, doesn't it?
Yes! It feels good!
My lovely Kanae, my precious Kanae.
Right now you are far more beautiful than any Kanae I ever imagined. In such pain. So pretty.
It hurts!
Kei-chan...
Wait, Kei-chan!
Let me rest a little first!
Wait, Kei-chan, please!
Don't cum inside me!
It's so hot inside. Whenever you thrust in and out, my brain goes numb.
You're coming in deeper...
You're getting deeper.
Kei-chan, your cock is getting bigger inside me.
You're going to cum inside me.
If you cum inside me I'll get pregnant!
I'll have your baby, Kei-chan!
You're going to cum inside me, aren't you?
This is only my second time having sex,
but I can feel that I'm about to cum from you cumming in my pussy!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!!
Semen is flowing so deep in my pussy.
If it comes inside too deep, I really will get pregnant.
Kei-chan, what are you doing?
That's the wrong place! Don't put it in there! You're not really...
That's right... I have to see your face in painful ecstasy... More...!
My ass... my ass...!
Stop, Kei, stop! It hurts!
This, this is what I've wanted all along.
But more than that, I wanted to take care of her, I wanted to kill her with pleasure.
That person was Kanae.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming Kanae!
Kei-chan...
You came in my ass, your cum is in my ass...
We have seen the participants in action.
The level has been cleared.
I really tried hard.
Yes, you did well. I'm proud of you.
I was pretty pathetic, wasn't I.
Not at all.
I never took my eyes off of you at any time Kanae. You looked beautiful.
I see. I'm glad.
This is it, the game is over. Now we can all leave this place.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Yes.
Yes, the final door is finally open...
This is the ending... Now, for Kanae and I, a new beginning...
Hello. How are things going today?
Good. Good boy.
Now, let us take your temperature.
Oh dear, you've shot lots of white stuff out of your dickhole.
You already came just from that?
This boy, at this point can't even remember his own name.
Consumed by the beast's desires, until he lost his mind.
You're so cute.
You poor little Kei-chan.
But don't worry
I'm here for you.
And I will never abandon you.
Rest at ease. Your beloved is also here.
Water... Water... Please...
We'll be together... Forever.
W