www.SubDESU-H.net
Darling, we can finally have sex alone.
Your cock's always really big.
More...
Darling...
I love you...
More and more...
Can't we make Alice-chan the legal wife already?
I can't recall what I have already decided.
W
Harem Time
「I want a baby  ♥」
Misuzu-san,
is this okay?
『Happy Family Sleep』
Just do it quickly!
This is our chance!
I'm also going to sleep with you!
My wife, Misuzu-san,
has a daughter named Misaki.
I understand their situation,
but the problem started during our first wedding night.
Let's sleep together!
She even followed us on our honeymoon.
And even if we secretly go to a love hotel, she still finds us.
Everyday, it's always the three of us sleeping together.
Because of that, even though we're newlyweds, we can't even have sex.
Again no sex...
Misaki, why don't you try learning how to sleep by yourself?
Why? Mama and I have always slept together.
That's why... I'm also going to sleep with Papa!
Hey... Seiji-san, say something too!
Papa agrees with me, right?
If he doesn't, I'll hate him!
I'm originally an outsider between these two, so I can't really say much.
L-Let's sleep already then!
Yes!
Seiji-san, we can finally make love to each other.
I-It feels good, but this is just a dream, right?
Does this mean I really will have to go on without sex?
No! Wake up, self!
Delicious.
Oh, did I wake you up, Papa?
Oh, well.
I'll be squeezing Papa's milk out again, okay?
Wh-What are you doing, Misaki-chan?
Did you say "again"?
Yes.
I've been licking you everyday.
Misaki-chan, you can't do that!
Why?
Why are you...?
When I lick here, it always twitches like this.
You seem to like it here, too.
I have loved you for a long time already, Papa.
Since the time that we first met...
Misaki-chan...
Even so, Mama had to be the first one to take you.
I couldn't accept that!
That's why I won't ever let you have sex with Mama!
I'll be the one to make Papa's cock feel good!
So that's how it was, huh?!
Misuzu-san, you were awake?!
I already noticed it before,
but for you to go this far...
In any case, get away from him!
I don't want to!
Misaki!
Even Papa wants someone who's younger, right?
Mama already gave birth to me, so her pussy's already very loose.
I'm still a virgin, so mine is sure to feel better than Mama's.
Very well then, Misaki.
I'll show you the techniques that you can't do!
It's a challenge then.
I-I can't see my cock anymore. Amazing!
My cock's totally swallowed.
I-I'll cum easily with this.
Misaki won't be able to take it in all the way, right?
That's not true!
Misaki-chan, if you force it down too much...
There you go.
I can also do this.
Oh man, those amazing boobs are hot!
This is too much!
Well?
Misaki can't do it with her breasts, right?
E-Even I can do that!
B-Both breasts at the same time?!
They can wrap round it even though mine are bigger?
My breasts can compete better.
Victory for me!
You choose, Seiji-san.
Which of us feels better?
Wh-Which? I don't know...
I'm cumming. I can't hold it in anymore!
It's been a long time since...
Papa's milk!
There's so much of it...
This cum is amazing... Papa.
I can't hold it in anymore.
Misuzu-san, you're amazing!
No fair, Mama!
And I even planned on giving my virginity to Papa today...
No! You can't just have sex.
What are you going to do if you get pregnant?
I don't care if I get pregnant!
Because Papa is my destined one.
There's no one that I like more than Papa!
Misaki...?
I understand. You can have sex with him then.
Wha—? Wh-What are you saying Misuzu-san?!
But I am Misaki's mother!
Isn't it normal for me to wish for my child's happiness?
H-Happiness...?
Mama...
Because we're both women...
No... it's because we're family that I understand.
Misaki truly loves Seiji-san.
Thank you for understanding me.
H-Hey, are you serious about this?
Misaki, try to relax.
M-Mama...
Try to lower your hips a bit.
Seiji-san, try to move.
B-But... Umm...
I-I'm okay.
It hurts a bit, but my pussy wants to do it.
Please, Papa. Do it to me!
I-It's tight...!
My insides are getting stirred up...
This is...
Yes! This is amazing!
It feels good Papa!
Misaki! Misaki!
I can't hold it in anymore...
Papa, Papa...
Seiji-san, give me your cock, too.
Don't, Misaki!
What's this?
The cock's rubbing inside me...
M-Mama, Papa's cock is amazing!
Of course,
because it's the cock that we both love.
Papa, I love you!
I love you!
I came again!
I love you, Papa!
Wow, cumming this much...
I love you, Seiji-san!
Let's sleep together everyday, okay?
Two partners everyday, huh?
Gulp.
It's been a long time, so I feel weak...
Hey, Papa. Let's do this everyday from now on, okay?
Harem Time.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Harem Time
I like it.
I like Satou-kun's cock.
I love... Satou-kun!
So please, make me your wife!
W-Wow, his cock is getting bigger again...
It's hot!
Hanazawa-san, if you squeeze me tightly like that...
I...!
It's okay, I want to give birth.
I want to give birth to your child.
Please, please cum inside me!
Release it inside me!
Hey, what are you doing, Junko-san?
I just thought I'd d clean it up for you,
but do you not like it?
W-Well, it's not that I don't like it, but...
Do not worry.
I may be a doctor, but I am also quite experienced as an attendant.
Th-That's not what I mean...
That's...!
Is it... really okay for me to stay like this?
Umm... Reiji-sama, I would like to have a word with you.
Hey, wait.
Is this what we were supposed to talk about?
I don't think that it'll be possible for me to be chosen as a legal wife anymore.
That's why I want to at least service you properly as a woman.
Alice-chan, I've been thinking of rejecting the inheritance of this household.
Eh, why?
I will help in providing a successor.
I want to help Hanazawa anyway.
But in the end... I really don't think I'm fit to be master of a household.
I've been a free part-time worker this whole time.
Reiji-sama...
You and the others have done so much for me,
but you were only hurt.
I'm really sorry.
You haven't changed,
from when we were kids.
Don't you remember?
Before you and your mother left this mansion, we'd already met.
Reiji-kun, umm... when we grow up,
be sure to make me your wife, okay?
I see! You were that girl from...
Ever since then, I've always wanted to confess to the kind and gentle you.
Alice-chan...
Can I also say one thing?
Management of the conglomerate can simply be done by us.
But to hold the position of a master is to be able to pull and attract people.
Junko-san...
For that criterion, I believe you are more than qualified.
Reiji-sama, please don't say that you want to stop.
We are able to serve because it is you.
Everyone...
Umm... Can I say something?
Hanazawa-san...
About Satou-kun's legal wife...
If it's okay, can we settle by who comes first?
It's because Alice-chan has loved Satou-kun for a very long time,
but they were just separated, right?
I don't feel like it's fair for me to cut in-between them.
I see. Then Reiji-sama's firstborn...
The mother of the eldest will be the legal wife, correct?
So that means...
The first person who gives birth to Reiji-sama's child will be the legal wife.
Reiji-sama!
Get me pregnant as soon as possible, Reiji-sama.
Everyone, wait!
Oh, it's already become this big!
Hey, deciding on the legal wife based on who gives birth first...
Are you really okay with that?
That's okay.
All of us here just can't help but love you so much.
But that doesn't mean all of you need to do it at once...!
Even if you say that, there's already something dripping from your cock.
Wow, it's getting really wet.
E-Even we would start to feel good with this.
My nipples are getting swept away and it's getting stiffer.
Everyone's breasts and your cock's getting rubbed.
I'm at my limit!
Wow, that's great!
I've been thinking for quite a while,
that Junko-san looks a bit sad being left out.
You're really cute!
I don't really...
Your breasts and butt are beautiful.
Even my heart's starting to throb.
W-We can't... We're all girls...
Junko-san's getting aroused.
Gotta do it more over here!
I am Reiji-sama's secretary!
Don't...
... tease that part!
It's already dripping wet here, so I guess preparations are over.
J-Junko-san?
I'm sorry, Reiji-sama.
I can no longer stop myself!
Junko-san's a virgin?
That's totally unexpected.
No...
Don't just move your hips...
It's just my first time, but I feel... I feel good!
It feels so good!
It's wrapping me tight.
Yes, Reiji-sama!
Please feel more pleasure!
I'll make up for it. I'll make up for it with my virgin pussy!
Oh no, it's really getting erotic.
We might have turned something on inside her.
I'm happy.
For someone like me to have my first with Reiji-sama...
Junko-san, I'm going to cum!
P-Please, just cum whenever you want.
Oh, no. I'm going to cum, too!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum quickly with this cock!
It's hard, stiff and hot...
More... Please make a mess of me some more!
Please, release it.
Release it inside me!
I want to carry your child!
Me, too. I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Reiji-sama, let's cum together!
I'm already going to cum just by looking at it.
Please release it and make me pregnant quickly!
Reiji-sama, please give me yours...
Release lots of your semen inside me.
No... I'm losing it...
I really can't live without this cock!
I'm also itching to have it in me...
Give it to me.
Give all your semen to me!
Reiji-sama...
Are you feeling it, too?
Does my dripping... wet pussy... feel good?
It's okay.
Do whatever you please.
So release it.
Release it, release it!
Cum inside me and impregnate me!
It's already there. I'm cumming!
Yes!
I'm also about to cum.
Let's all cum together!
It's hot!
There's lots of it...
Semen is flowing inside me.
My womb is getting filled with semen.
It can't enter anymore!
Reiji-sama!
We love you!
After that...
So you've all given birth?
Yes.
We have all,
perfectly and safely,
given birth to 7 children.
I-I never intended to...
Junko-nee, its clearly obvious.
So we didn't settle it this time..
Seems so.
Make me pregnant again, okay?
Make me
pregnant
again, okay?
www.SubDESU-H.net