SubDESU-H
Presents
Takakura Yumi: I take her virginity
while studying at her home.
Sensei, I finished.
Huh? O-oh.
Then, let's check your answers...
Let's see, let's see...
All the answers are correct.
Just what I expected of you, Yumi-chan.
Yumi-chan?
What’s wrong? You don’t look well.
If you’re tired, we can stop studying for today.
I-I’m fine. It’s nothing.
Sensei! What are you doing?
Please let go.
Yumi-chan, you’re cute
I've always wanted to do this.
No! Let go of me!
No. Stop, Sensei.
Somebody! Somebody!!
Screaming is futile. Nobody’s coming.
Thanks to the power of my notebook.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
I trusted you.
It isn’t sudden. I’ve always wanted to violate you.
No way…
Didn't you notice? Whenever we were studying,
I'd always imagine you naked.
You’re amazing, Yumi. You have such wonderful breasts.
Noo, don't look...!
It hurts! Sensei, please forgive me.
You’re feeling it, aren’t you?
No…
What? Did you want me to grope you more?
Of course not. Hurry up and stop this.
You should be more honest.
Next is here.
No, not there!
You’re already so wet. What a naughty girl you are.
Honestly, look at you, getting this wet. You're a natural pervert, aren't you?
How mean. I am not perverted.
How about it? Since you're already this wet, it looks like it'll be ok to put it in.
What?! No! Anything but that. I’ve never had sex before.
If you tell a guy that, he’ll only want to fuck you more.
Yumi, you should learn something from this.
That’s…Stop! Nooo!
I’m all the way in.
Yumi, how does it feel to become a woman?
It hurts. Hurry, take it out.
Don’t worry. Soon you’ll feel much better.
How mean. Stop it...
You were a virgin just a moment ago...
You're already feeling good, aren't you, Yumi?
No, I'm not. But, why...?
It's looks like you've completely awoken to the joy of sex
If you do it so roughly...
I'm at my limit. I'm going to cum inside you, Yumi
Stop. I'm begging you. You can't do that. Don't release it inside...!
Nooo!
You shouldn't have... Released it so deep... Pregnant... I'll become pregnant...
Yumi. Listen. Make sure your family doesn't find out.
Since you're smart, you know what
would happen if you did, right?
Oh, Sensei. You’re leaving?
How are Yumi’s studies going?
Yes. Yumi-chan is excelling at her studies,
so don’t worry.
What? You came here again?
Oh, Shiori. Terrible as always.
Hey, don't call me as though we know
each other. It’s Shiori-san to you.
Don't be getting too close to my sister. You're not
looking at her pervertedly or anything, right?
What a close guess. I just took her
virginity a moment ago.
Shiori, you’re being rude.
I’m sorry, Sensei.
Not at all. I don’t mind.
I’ll be leaving now. I’ll see you later, Shiori-chan.
Thank you, Sensei. Please come again.
Stop calling me that!
As always, an impudent brat. I should use my notebook and punish her.
And I can't leave Misako-san alone either.
It looks like there'll be lots of fun from now on...
Shiori Takakura : I take her in one of the new photobooths in the arcade.
Over here, Shiori. Let's hurry up and take the photographs.
Yes. I understand.
Shiori, set up the machine, won’t you?
Yes.
It would be boring to rape her while the dream
note's power is keeping her calm...
Huh? What am I doing here?
Whaaa? What are you doing?!
What do you mean? We’re getting our picture taken, aren’t we?
But plain pictures are boring. We're going to take some erotic pictures of you.
No... let me go. I said let me go!
If you don't want it, then resist more.
But you really like it, don’t you?
Idiot! Of course I don’t!
W-What? My body’s moving on its own!
W-why? Oh, no!
I knew you wanted it.
Not at all!
Nooooo!
I-it hurts. Take it out.
Isn’t this great? Your pussy is in perfect view of the camera
Eh?
Noooo!! Don't take pictures-!
No… It hurts. Take it out. Let me go.
Hehe… Your cunt doesn't seem like it doesn't want it...
The hard thing is going all the way inside me...
Hehe… You really are feeling it after all? What's up with that perverted voice?
I don’t like it, it’s embarassing, but… I't's so hot down there!
Do you want more, Shiori? You want your perverted posture to be photographed more, right?
No... Not at all... But... I can't take it-!
If you want it that badly, I’ll give it to you.
It'll make you remember what kind of a perverted girl you are with my cock!
Nooo…
So hard...
The hard thing is... Deep inside me...
Don't... If you take these kind of pictures... Don't...
It’s embarrassing, don't take pictures of me being violated...!
You're about to cum, right? That's good. Just go ahead and cum!
Noo... Cumming while having your picture taken...
No... Don't... Don't thrust that hard... If you do that, I'll really cum...!
I- It's coming out... Hot sperm is coming out of my womb...
So hot... Your sticky sperm is overflowing...
I guess that's enough after I've released so much... Calm down and bear my child.
Misako Takakura: I will fuck her in the living room while she's on the phone with her husband.
Really? That sounds difficult.
So, when is your next meeting…? Yes, I understand.
Do you think you'll be able to come back this weekend...?
Really…?
S-sensei, what are you—
Is something wrong?
No, it’s nothing.
Please– please stop.
Hello, Misako-san. I just happened to be in the neighborhood.
I'd like you to service me with your mouth...
I couldn’t possibly do something like that.
Hey. Is something going on?
Sorry. I dropped a pot...
Well, then, please go ahead.
I don't want to. Put it away please...
That'd be useless. You know when a man's penis becomes like this, it won't calm down untill it's released it's load.
But...
What on earth is going on, Misako?
Nothing at all, dear. I just got a little caught up in a soap-opera on TV.
Here you go. Please, go ahead.
That's... Impossible.
You want it to be exposed? You're doing this with me...
That's...
I understand...
Huh? What are you saying, Misako? I can’t hear you.
I’m sorry. I’m just eating a bit of ice cream.
I’m sorry for acting a little distant, dear.
That's good, Misako-san. That expression...
How's this?
Good. I can't get enough.
Drink it all without leaving anything, please.
For a while now, you've sounded like you're out of breath...
I’m sorry, I wonder if I'm catching a cold or something...
Ah... Stop.
Please forgive me. I don't want this...
You're this wet... Are you sure you really don't want it?
You got horny while giving me a blowjob while on the phone with your husband, didn't you?
I'm not horny...
I'm sorry, dear... Doing this while on the phone with you...
Don't...
I'm going to release it inside.
No, stop...
Don’t... Don't...!
Don't come inside. I might get pregnant!
Forgive me... Forgive me...!
No... Noo...
I... I... I had sperm released into my pussy while I was on the phone with my husband!!
Forgive me, dear...
I'm having sperm released into my pussy...
Shiori Takamura : In Morihashi park, we go for a perverted stroll in the mist.
Shiori... You did as I told you to, right?
Yes... Master.
Open your coat.
Yes
Good girl. You did as I told you.
Yes. It’s was embarrassing, but I came nude.
That’s good. Next, I want you to urinate at the base of that tree over there.
P-P-Pee? I understand. It'll do as master says.
Hehe… What a good view.
Can’t you show me more, Shiori?
Yes
It’s so embarrassing.
My fingers are touching it.
Hey, hey, who told you you to masturbate?
I-I’m sorry.
Good grief, starting to masturbate just like that...? You're a helplessly perverted bitch, aren't you?
I’m... not a bitch.
Geez. Well said for somebody's who's having that much juice coming out of her pussy...
I’m sorry... The truth is, I really am helplessly perverted...
It's fine as long as you understand. Hurry up and finish peeing.
Yes!
The pee won't stop... It feels so good...!
Hehe… That was quite an entertaining scene, Shiori.
I bet the peeping toms are very pleased as well.
I was being watched? By complete strangers?
They were watching the place I pee with...
Now then... I should give the bitch a reward for properly doing as her master commanded...
You'll give me a reward, Master?
Here I go!
How is it? Will you be satisfied with this?
It's amazing. Even though I’m so tired, it feels so good.
If you scream like that, people really will look at you
It's fine if they look at me.
It feels better when I'm embarrassed!
It feels really good when I'm embarrassed!
You perverted bitch!
Do you want me to release it inside soon?
My pussy is tingling from Master’s cock. Please, release your sperm inside me!
I got it. I'll give you your beloved sperm!
I'm being impregnated... The sperm is filling my pussy...!
It’s amazing... I can feel the sperm inside even with my hand being outside...
Yumi Takakura: Public sex at the local swimming pool.
You're entering me... You're putting it inside me... Even though there are lots of people around...
If you scream out with such an erotic voice, of course the people around us will notice.
But... My voice just comes out on it's own...
I see... You want to be watched by the people around us?
Don't look!
Look, that guy in the pool over there, he's looking over here. He's probably looking at your erotic body while masturbating.
That's a lie... Looking at me while masturbating...?
Don't...!
Those two people over there are looking too. Everyone's looking at your erotic body while getting aroused.
You're wrong. I'm not that kind of perverted girl.
Yumi. Sit on the poolside facing me.
Yes.
Everybody are looking at your perverted posture and getting horny, Yumi.
You’re pounding me so hard, I’m going to cum.
I'll cum inside you while all the people around us are watching!
No, not that, I don't want that!
I'll impregnate you in front of everyone!
No, they'll all see... They'll all see the place where I get pregnant!
Your sperm is leaking out of me. You impregnated me while everyone watched.
Hehe… Let's get out of the pool and get in the shower.
Yes...
Yumi. If you cry out like that someone will hear you.
No, if anyone sees me like this, they’ll think I’m a pervert.
It’s too good, I can’t hold my voice back. We'll be noticed. We'll definitely be noticed!
Hehe… The truth is you want to be seen, and can't help yourself, right?
The truth is, I want everyone to see Sensei impregnate me. I want them all to see the place where I get impregnated!
Fine with me, I'll impregnate you.
Impregnate me! Impregnate me by releasing lots of your hot sperm inside my pussy!
I’m so happy. I’m going to have Sensei’s baby.
Yumi is completely my slave, now.
Next, those two.