W-What?
Stop it!
What do you intend to do, putting me in a position like this?!
How could you not know what I'm about to do to you?
W-What are you trying to do, pulling something like that out?
Don't act stupid, there's no way you couldn't know.
You're a traitor. Even if you try to pleasure me like this-
I-It hurts!
So you were still a virgin.
Do you think that by doing this, you can get through my heart?!
Because you let out such a shameful voice, I thought I would go nice on you, but...
N-Not shameful!
Fine, then...
What's the matter? Is it starting to feel good?
You're wrong, I wouldn't... with...
I'm not wrong, you slut.
No, you're wrong! I'm not-
What a sight you are.
And you still call yourself the number one female ninja of the village, Nagiiri?
N-No, you're wrong. You're wrong!
No...
I bet you want my seed just about now, don't you?
I'll make sure to pour it all right into you.
You wouldn't dare!
No! Not inside! I'll get pregnant!
Having a girl resist all the more just makes it more pleasurable for the man.
No, no, please, stop it, Nii-sama!
No!
S-Stop it!
No... you actually let it out inside me...
You were resisting so much before, but it seems you came too.
Not to mention you're stuffed.
No... Saying I'm stuffed after violating me...
I can't stand it!!
Nii-sama...
You should be fine now.
Try not to make me worry too much now.
Alright.
Nii-sama, umm... Have you ever thought about a husband and wife?
Hm, the only person I'd consider accepting is a respectable female ninja.
Nii-sama, I'll become that respectable female ninja.
Umm... If I do that... will you have me, Nii-sama?
Well Sakuya, if you can manage to become the number one female ninja of the village,
And we became man and wife, that wouldn't be too bad.
Really? That's a promise, Nii-sama!
SubDESU-H Presents
Kunoichi Sakuya
What's the status of the female ninja we captured?
She's currently locked in the basement.
I see.
Her body had yet to experience a man, so I took the pleasure.
I see, I see.
I had heard that the village of Nagiiri allowed virgins to become female ninjas,
But I didn't expect it to be true.
The female ninja that chased after you, a traitor,
Probably didn't expect to end up being violated.
Anyways, continue training that animal.
Be sure to beat it into her until she joins our side.
I'm coming in.
Enter.
How was she, the female ninja of Nagiiri?
She was a virgin, was she not?
I wonder how much she hated you, who had betrayed your village?
Why don't you tell me more about yourself?
I heard you're a rather powerful shinobi, so I have a slight interest in you.
We'll be working together from now on, so why not deepen our bond?
Your thing is just like I had imagined. It's amazing.
Your muddled semen is so delicious.
Put your dick in me now. Give it to my pussy.
I'm fine with that.
It's best this way.
It's so big... all the way to the back... your dick, it's so big!
It's piercing straight through my pussy and hitting the back!
How's my pussy? Does it feel good?
Yes. Akibi-dono, your insides are so pleasing.
I've only started.
Please, explore every inch of my body.
I can't just have you do all the work, can I?
N-No! The back of my pussy, it's being filled up with your giant dick!
It's reaching too far in, I can feel everything!
So good!
I'm going to come! Come inside me too! Fill my pussy up with your dick!
I'm going to come, I'm going to come, I'm going to come!
My pussy's being filled up with your semen...
That was amazing...
What do you plan to do this time?
I'll re-educate you as a female ninja.
Not the way of the Nagiiri village, but of this village's.
Like hell I'll yield to a conceited bastard like you.
I'll teach you plenty about the life of a man and woman now.
It was what you once seeked, no?
I'll teach you the true meaning of a female ninja, now.
No!
N-No...
Don't bite.
Alright. That's a good expression on your face, you seem to be enjoying it.
I-It doesn't tast-
I'll just shoot it all into your mouth.
Remember the taste of semen well.
This is terrible.
I'll come again.
I'll be sure to teach you the true meaning of a female ninja.
Don't forget what I've taught you.
I'm coming in.
A message from Hyoue-sama.
You seem to be doing well with Sakuya's training.
He said to relax and get rid of the stress at the bath.
Oh, and he also said to take Sakuya to the bath as well.
Meaning he wants me to continue Sakuya's training there?
I understand.
Be sure to get rid of that stress.
D-Don't touch... there...
You're already this wet. You definitely are a lewd woman.
No, you're wrong.
I don't feel this at all.
Really? Can I test that out then?
N-no, don't, stop, don't touch me there!
Please, stop doing it so roughly.
Don't! I-I'm going crazy!
Please, no more.
I can't hold it anymore!
I came... because of... because of...
That perverted body of yours, this isn't anywhere near enough is it?
N-No, if you do anymore I won't...
It hurts!
You're gripping on happily.
No, you're wrong! Please forgive me!
I'm... I'm cuming again!
A-Amazing, my stomach is getting hot and full!
S-Stop, don't move anymore!
I'll just let it out inside like this.
No, don't, please not inside!
You let it out inside again...
My pussy is... my stomach is... it's too hot!
What did you plan, by bringing me here?
I have to let the others know of your training progress.
No!
Stop it, what are you doing in front of all these people?
Your pussy seems to be enjoying it though.
No, don't look!
No, don't put it in.
Stop poking me in there!
I need to show everyone what a loose female ninja you've become.
You're wrong. You're wrong, I'm not a loose woman!
Amazing, she's so wet!
She looks like a lass, but as expected of the number one female ninja from the village of Nagiiri, this is quite something!!
No, you're wrong.. I'm not-
No, please, stop it!
What a naughty voice, are you getting turned on from being watched?
No, no that's not it!!
I'm not turned on...
No, this isn't- I'm not-
S-Stop watching, I'm... I'm...
She's just eating up the traitor's dick and enjoying it!
Amazing, the amount of juice flowing from her pussy just isn't normal!
N-No!
Stop, don't tease my nipples!
Be complimented more by everyone!
No, stop!
So she does like being teased at those big breasts of hers.
No!
I'll make you feel good in front of everyone, let everyone see how you cum!
No, I'm being watched! I'm going to cum!
It's coming out... The semen is coming out...
It came out... I'm going to get a baby...
You've came, again?
Of course, your training is far from complete.
Apprehension jutsu, the basic for any shinobi. I'll train you to appreciate these.
My body...
I-It hurts!
You look nice, Sakuya.
No...
What do you plan to do, putting me in a position like this?!
I told you, I'm going to re-educate you.
N-No, it hurts!
I won't give into something like this!
Fine, then show me how much you can handle.
No!
Your body's started to become accustomed to this. You have such a lewd body.
No, that's not it! It hurts, but why?!
Aren't you in a good mood now?
No, what are you doing?
I'll violate you, while you're still unable to move.
No, while I'm still like this?!
It's tighter than usual, do you like being binded? You pervert.
That's not it!
Not like this!
Do you like being violated while unable to move this much?
N-No, don't say I like these things!
N-No, it's hitting deep inside me!
I'm going to cum again! Stop, I don't want to cum again!
Your face is becoming pleasant, Sakuya.
Stop, don't move.
I can't... I... I can't hold it any longer!
Why, why is my body-
That is your body's true wish, you damn perverted female ninja.
No, I'm not a pervert!
No... Stop it!
What are you saying? You're already this wet. It's proof your body is enjoying it.
No, you're wrong! I'm... I'm not enjoying this!
Is that true? Allow me to find out.
Don't...
No, I'm going to go crazy!
You're just like an excited female pig right now.
I'll let it all out inside you as usual.
N-No, not inside again!
Don't, you're hurting my pussy!!
I'm letting it out!
No!!!
No... again... there's something in my stomach again...
It's all sticky...
It's full of semen again...
M-My pee!
No, stop it! Let me go!
What a lively fish you are!
S-Stop, please don't lick me.
What lewd breasts, like a cow's.
No...
Stop touching my breasts, please.
Your breasts are so lewd, my dick is already like this.
No, stop rubbing it! It's disgusting
Oh? It seems you're wet already.
No, you're wrong. This isn't...
See, it is wet? It's dripping wet.
N-No, don't put your fingers in there!
Stop stirring around!
Look at this, my hands are this wet from your juices.
Lies, it can't be this wet...
Well what about my patient dick? Let's let him in now.
It's going in, it's going in me!
This is great, Sakuya, I could almost cum right now!
No, don't cum inside me!
How's my dick? Doesn't it feel nice?
N-No, I can't say something like that!
Your body is though, what an embarrassing woman!
But-
You let out such a nice voice.
Make it more vigorous!
I-If I make it anymore vigorous, I'll cum!
In that case, how's this?
N-No, that's too strong! Stop stabbing my pussy so hard!
How is it, Sakuya? Eh? Eh?!
It's too strong! My stomach is going to break!
I'm not done yet, I'm going to make it stronger!
No! If you do it any stronger, my pussy will break!
I'll show you a better view with my dick!
No! My pussy, it's being beaten by your dick!
Stop, if you keep doing that I'm going to cum!
I-I'm going to cum!
Good, Sakuya! I'm going to cum inside your pussy!
Where.. Where are you letting it out?
Wait, are you going to put your semen in my pussy?!
I can't hold back, I'm at my limit!
No not there!
Y-You poured your semen in me...
I-I'm coming... I'm coming!!!
Do you see this?
Seeing your pussy, my dick is rock solid again!
It's getting hard in my pussy again...
My pussy is being beating again!
This is amazing! My pussy full of semen is being stirred up again!
Oh this is great, Sakuya, this is good!
Stop, if you keep doing that, I'll come again!
That's ok, cum as many times, this time I'll cover your pretty skin up!
You're going to pour it on me? My body's going to be covered with your sticky semen!
I'll cover you so much that it won't ever come off!
I'm at my limit!!
I-I being covered in your fluid! I'm cuming!
It smells...
Your smelly semen is all over my body... It's staining it.
My entire body will become smelly.
We're being attacked!
Who did this?!
So this is the shinobi of Maajidan? You're so weak you make me laugh.
I'll kill you with these hands of mine, nii-san, no, Oborobe no Hie.
I figured you'd run windward, knowing my jutsu's.
But you cannot escape me.
True, your jutsu are powerful, but without eye contact, they are useless.
If so, then you should be powerless at this distance!
This is the end!
You're a traitor, but this all ended rather quickly.
I'll go ahead and take Sakuya's life next.