Gitai Saimin Kouhen
Presented by SubDESU-H
The first drink of the day! It's great!
How can you drink such excretion so happily? You sure are a strange human...
You don't taste this with your tongue, you taste it with you mind!
But an alien like you might not understand this very well.
Hey, Na-chan...
Kasuga-sensei sure has changed...
Yeah, you're right. She totally has...
But...
She's way better like this!
Hey! Quiet, you two!
Well, you girls have good grades, so you may find my lessons boring.
I've never actually seen you attend a lesson before.
Are you going to complain, Little Gray?
No, it's nothing.
Also, on that note, my name is Hikari...
Library
Did I make you wait?
You sure are lewd, Hitomi-chan...
Jeez, Na-chan, you meanie...
Hey, hurry it up.
Hey, what is it like?
You taste good, Na-chan...
I see, that's good.
Hey, I'll do something more amazing after this...
Something amazing?
Hey, Hitomi-chan...
We're just getting started, you know.
Tada!
Don't worry. This is my first time, too.
Y-You too, Na-chan?
That's right, I'm giving you my first time.
Your first time is with me...?
So give me your first time too, Hitomi-chan.
I'm so happy!
Na-chan...
It's your turn, Hitomi-chan.
I'm putting it in, okay?
No! It won't fit!
I-It'll fit!
It hurts, it hurts! It won't-!
Hitomi-chan...
I want us to both do it.
N-Na-chan...!
I'm so happy!
Hitomi-chan, you're so cute!
Your nipples are getting hard, Hitomi-chan...
No, please don't say that!
Na-chan, kiss me, kiss me!
Hitomi-chan, you're so cute...
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from this!
I want your baby, Na-chan!
Na-chan, I love you!
Na-chan, Na-chan, Na-chan-!
Na-chan!!
Na-chan, do you want to come over to my place?
Sure...
Jeez, she's not pregnant this time either.
Hey you, are you sure you're not firing blanks?
Shit, shit!
Again... Again?!
Jeez, we just wasted our time again.
You should at least learn from it...
I can make it appear like I've transformed into anything...
Right?
Yes, theoretically.
It has to be perfect.
It is. It is flawless.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
Now then, for the next plan...
Let's say that Akari-chan is out walking.
Keep going...
I'll annoy some delinquents, but whilst in the form of Akari-chan.
It's possible; no problems there.
Of course, this'll happen.
Probably.
Help me!
And then...
I come out and look cool!
Isn't it perfect?
Not a bad plan for the likes of you.
Hey, did you see the look of admiration in Akari-chan's eyes?
Yes, I didn't think that it would go that well...
I said it would go well, didn't I?
But are you sure that it was fine to split up with her already?
You don't get it, do you?
Oh really?
Akari-chan's the type to deeply fall in love.
So...
So what do you mean?
An alien like you wouldn't understand the complex human mind.
Basically, we'll bump into each other again by accident, and I'll be able to quickly win her affection!
That's a pretty good idea coming from the likes of you!
Praise me more!
I didn't think he'd still be around, but he's really not, is he?
I'm sorry!
You're...
See you then, Sawa...
Yu-Yuta-san...
Yes, be careful, Akari-chan.
I will!
See? Isn't it just like I said?
Yes, so all those theories you had in your mind worked out.
She somewhat has a sharp tone...
How did it go?
I bet you know already.
I see.
She sent me what I thought she would, but...
Oh really.
Sorry to make you wait!
I want to see your room next time, Akari-chan.
I can't?
Seems I was being too forward...
Sorry about that.
Hey alien.
What is it?
Isn't it all going according to plan?
I guess it is.
I'm going to do it tomorrow.
Oh really?
I'll see you next Sunday, then.
A-Akari-chan?
M-Mom and Dad aren't home today...
Finally!
I already knew that! I was the one who made sure that they would be out today!
Yuta-san...
N-No!
N-No, that's not what I meant...
I was just a bit surprised...
Um...
Hm? What is it?
This is my first time. It's my first time, but my heart hurts...
I don't want you to think that I'm a lewd girl...
Don't worry, there's no way that I'd stop liking you.
Yuta-san...
That's right! There's no way that I'd stop liking you, Akari-chan!
You're my girlfriend now, after all!
Yu-Yuta-san...
I... I'm...!
Look, Akari-chan...
I-It hurts!
Are you alright?
U-Um, I'm fine, so put it right in!
But...
I want to become one with you, Yuta-san...
I'm gonna start moving.
Y-Yes!
I'm sorry I came inside...
No, today is a safe day, so...
Also, I don't mind if it's yours...
Thanks.
I'm sorry I said that it hurt and stuff...
But I'm glad that we were able to become one.
I'll see you again, then.
Yes, I'll text you.
I'll tell you this now; she's not pregnant.
Yuta-san, that's...!
Don't-!
It'll... it'll come out-!
I-I'll get started...
What's wrong?
When I'm doing this with you, my body gets hot...
It probably just means that your body is turning into that of a woman.
Into that of a woman? I'm scared... I'm scared, Yuta-san!
Don't worry, Akari-chan!
Your body is just changing to suit my needs!
A body which is only for me!
Yuta-san, Yuta-san!
Akari-chan, you're so cute!
Yuta-san...
Akari-chan! I'm about to cum!
I-It's okay!
Today is a safe day, so-!
Akari-chan!
Being together like this is so great...
I think so, too.
Did something happen?
Hey, wait up!
Sorry, I had a sudden urge to meet you...
It's fine, I wanted to meet you too, Yuta-san.
Say, Akari-chan...
Eh? We're gonna do it here?
We can't...?
If you insist...
It's fine, no one will find us at this hour.
Amazing-!
It feels better than usual!
Akari-chan!
You've become quite perverted!
Y-Yes! I'm such a lewd girl!
Your thing has made me such a pervert, Yuta-san!
So he was getting sick of his angel-like self.
Yu-Yuta-san?
I want to feel everything about you, Akari-chan!
P-Please be gentle...
Of course.
I-It hurts! It hurts, it hurts!
I-It hurts, Yuta-san-!
It's fine, it's fine!
My Akari-chan will be fine!
Yes! I'll try my best!
No, no!
Yuta-san? Yuta-san, Yuta-san!
What's this? You're squeezing more!
Akari-chan! You're being watched by these guys while you're being sodomized!
Then I have to try my best too, don't I?
No!
No, no!
It hurts, i-it hurts!
Please stop it, Yuta-san!
It's fine, it's fine! It feels really good!
Why...?! Yuta-san...?
Why are you...?!
That's because Yuta doesn't exist!
Eh?
The person you thought was Yuta and fell in love with was me, Nurakoshi!
Are you surprised, Akari-chan?
Akari-chan, your insides feel incredible!
No...
N-No...
This is-!
No!
Akari-chan, get pregnant!
No!!
See ya then, Akari-chan.
Hey you, was it really okay to leave Akari-chan like that?
She seemed to be in awe from all of this...
They don't say "A separated couple can never go back to as it was." for nothing.
I'll be going home, then.
I'll get revenge for Yuta-san!
Huh... Where am I...?
I saved you.
Why...?
I have a feeling of friendship with you.
Humans usually help their friends when they're in trouble, correct?
Am I wrong?
No, you're right...
We're friends, Hikari.
Yes! It means we're in a friendly relationship, doesn't it?
Yeah!
So, what are you going to do now?
Now...?
If you use my powers, you don't need to bother with doing them individually.
You could even be the ruler of the world if you wanted to.
You don't seem to be very enthusiastic...
Yeah, not really...
Would you like to come with us?
That is, if you don't have any attachment to Earth.
That might be a good idea...
I see. We would be very grateful if you did.
Really?
That's right.
What are you trying to...?!
Hi-Hikari!
Well, you're coming along with us as a test subject, are you not?
You just said so before.
But aren't we good friends?!
Hmm. You humans call your pets your friends, too.
Isn't this similar to that?
Give up, life is unfair.
Stop with the jokes!
Turn me back to my normal self again!
Billy from Dresden, who was abducted by Torafama-something aliens,
admitted to his destiny like this.
We should be passing by Titan soon.