Milky news
Milky news~~
Hello everyone, how are you?
I’m Nanase Akira.
I’m an active high school student right now.
This spoony guy is Nanase Kenji.
He is my stupid big brother.
He’s hick, old, cook, waiter, etc and owner of this profitless café.
He asked for help from Yuuki Rin-san to save his café.
And they decided to renovate the café.
Isn’t it Rin-san?
The code name is project Minerva.
Wow! What a code name.
And the name of the store will be Milky Way.
Anyway, the store was a rush work made of plywood and completely changed.
under construction
It still feels kinda awkward for me though.
But beyond our expectations, the café has prospered a lot.
And the Milky Way has become a popular store that it even causes a long waiting line.
Comfortable, cheap and delicious, this is what we mean.
But the main reputation of the Milky Way is their waitress and their costumes.
Well then, I will introduce to you the cute waitress work in Milky Way~~
She’s Yuuki Rin, who showed herself a while ago.
She is the CEO, owner and waitress of the milky way.
And she’s usually a nerdy one but,
she becomes the number 1 waitress in the café when she wears a costume.
Its hard to believe that she’s the same person.
Please leave me alone.
She’s Takahashi Chihiro-san.
She’s the daughter of the chairman of the company.
And she’s my stupid bro’s ex-girlfriend.
She’s upper class and whimsy though.
Anyway, she’s a careless one and many customers come to see her.
Leave me alone.
She’s Mikage Sakuya-san.
She has been working here even before the renovation of the milky way and she's super whimsy.
She likes Ice tea and collects a lot of under wears.
She’s a strange girl who easily gets frightened but in that way she comforts everyone.
Please leave me alone.
She's Kunou Ayumi a.k.a Ayu.
She’s my classmate and
she’s a pudding addict that eats 40 puddings per day.
She likes to be scolded and has a cute attitude.
I’m a bit worried because she has that kind of attitude,
she might tempt and be abducted by someone.
Don’t say that.
She’s Kousaka Mayu-san.
She’s Rin-san doujin colleague.
She’s a popular cosplayer and a doujin writer.
She’s usually a noisy one,
but she becomes a bright and charming girl when she wears a costume.
That’s what I expect of Rin-san's friend, she's the same as her.
Leave me alone.
Kusumoto Sayura
now
waiting
deposit
Ok next one, sorry for making you wait.
She’s Kusumoto Sayura-san.
Her main work is the information of the bank
She’s popular as a cute one and
here
works in milky way every afternoon.
She’s popular as a cosplayer and many customers come to see her.
She’s also Rin-san’s friend, and the same as her.
Please leave me alone, ok?
college
Toujou Rumi-san.
She looks younger than me,
but she goes to St. Marianne Girls only school which is a bit expensive school.
And she’s an active college student.
She’s started working here because she misunderstood that
she could eat the strawberries in the store all she wanted.
Leave me alone.
Toujou Haruka-san.
She’s Rumi-san’s big sister and
she works as supervisor at Chihiro-san’s father’s company.
But she started to work as manager in milky way to watch after Rumi-san.
Onee-chan nerds come all the way to café to see her in a costume.
What do you mean by that?
They waitress to a 40 seats cafe in milky way.
A lot of fans from nationwide come to milky way.
Please try and come to the milky way which was made by Rin-san and my stupid bro.
By the way, I’m not counted here.
That’s all.
I Nanase Akira and that’s all for the announcement.
The end of milky news
The end of milky news.
Hey, are we going to air this?
I.. I think we should not.
SubDESU-H
presents
Episode 1
You can have an affair
Uhm, I brought the apricot tea and the puddine ara moire.
Nya~
I’m sorry.
This is the mouth which mocks me right?
Stop it please~
Do some work Sayura-san.
Can I have some of that pudding?
Ahh, I’m really sorry.
Here, moan with a cute voice.
Stop it rujmi-san~
The expenses... the expenses...
The deadline...
Good good, this is good.
Is this alright?
Will this be alright?
Will this be alright!!?
I don’t care~
Thank you very much.
Good work everyone.
By the way, the milky way will have a 3 days-off so get some rest.
What’s that, its too sudden.
Yeah, its irresponsible.
Isn’t it Kenji?
Uhm.. yeah.
We had an agreement that you will not oppose the owner's decision, didn't we?
Well, that's true.
Kenji?
But.. it’s a promise...
But the store will go bankrupt through that.
Owner, what’s the reason to rest?
Of course, there will be an event that only happens twice a year on the day after tomorrow.
It’s a direct sale event of doujin magazines from all over the nation.
I see.
Mayu-san was always sleeping cuz she was writing a manga the whole week.
She should have rested in the house if she was just going to sleep.
We have no choice, everyone, the milky way will have a day off starting tomorrow.
Owner’s decision is absolute.
Ok, well lets do our best.
Yes?
The new work is for the onee-san character.
The cosplayer.
Owner, please take her some pictures.
Of course.
Being watched and taken a photo is the pleasure of the cosplayer!
Hey wait...
Hey sis, owner’s decision is final.
W-Why are you praying?
Its because...
We have no choice.
No way.
Good work everyone.
I’ll walk you home Ayu.
Thank you Akira-chan.
Ohhh, I’m tired.
Cosplay...
Don’t act so down.
Don’t sleep walk.
Sakuya, lets hang around on the way a bit.
No thanks~~
Lets eat some strawberries in the near store.
No thanks
Lets go, its Sakuya’s treat.
No thanks.
Whew, its going to be busy starting tomorrow.
We’ll get more popular with milky way.
The circle silk road will also spread.
We must get along with the staff and not to cause any problem.
Be careful not to collapse for working hard.
Its alright, I’m used to this.
I know that Kenji also gets tired every day in milky way.
Take a long vacation and get some proper rest.
I see, I won't see you for 3 days.
What are you saying? We've been inseparable since childhood.
There’s nothing to worry about if you don't see me for 3 days.
You can have an affair with other woman if you’re sad.
I want you to be free.
Don’t say that.
We’re not the same as we used to be in our childhood days.
Well, that's true but...
What are you doing so suddenly?
Rin...
Kenji?
I can’t hold it any longer.
But I have an event tomorrow.
Rin...
No... Kenji...
We’re inside the store...
But we’re the only the ones here now.
But...
You don’t like it?
No.
No its not that...
Rin.
Kenji...
Let me see your breast.
Do I need to take it all off?
No need, just the breast
Kenji, you’re dirty.
Let me see.
Sure.
Will this be alright?
No...
Kenji’s touching technique is so dirty.
Did your boobs get bigger?
You always touching it when we’re having sex.
All my bras got tight.
Then I’ll make it bigger.
No...
Rin, what do you want?
Suck my... nipples.
Suck it.
I feel it.
My nipples are getting bigger.
Its getting bigger and turning an erotic color.
I like to be sucked.
I feel it when you lick around it.
I like to be bitten.
I didn't know that my breast could feel like this until Kenji sucked it.
You panty is wet.
Of course, its because Kenji is touching it.
I just touched it.
It already got wet when you first called me.
I... I’m a pervert.
I love perverts.
No...
What are you doing Kenji?
People can see me from outside.
I want to show everyone the cute Rin.
No...
Its embarrassing.
Its alright.
Here...
No... I said no.
They will see my pants.
I said we’re showing it.
No~
No?
I don’t want to Kenji.
My embarrassing part will be shown.
Someone will watch my embarrassing part.
They will watch my body which is only seen by Kenji.
Rin, do you feel it?
I feel it, I can feel it.
What do you want?
Please put your finger in.
Put your finger inside my pussy from the side of my panty.
How is it?
I feel it.
It feels good.
Your finger...
Your finger is...
Is touching...
It feels good.
I feel like I’m flying.
I can’t hold it... I can't hold it in anymore.
What is it?
I... I want Kenji's so badly.
Don’t make me wait.
Say it properly.
I said....
Kenji’s this one...
I want this to be put inside my pussy.
Ri... Rin.
If you do that, I can’t do anything.
Are you ready Rin?
Sure, come here.
Please thrust me with yours Kenji.
Kanji's thing came in...
Yeah.
Kenji.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
Its so good.
How is it now?
Its coming in...
Kenji's is coming inside me.
How’s that part?
Its so wet.
Of course, its all wet.
Kenji.
Say it more precisely.
My pussy is being rubbed by kenji’s dick.
My pussy is all wet.
Its all wet as it can be heard by kenji.
No...
You can really hear it.
No.
Don’t listen to it.
Don’t listen to the sound.
Kenji.
Rin.
Rin, Rin.
I love you.
I love you Kenji.
I love you too Rin.
I love you.
Here I come.
Rin.
You can release it.
Release it inside me.
I like it to be release inside.
Give me your sperm.
So please...
Rin.
No.
I’m going crazy.
Why you are scared when you've done it to me.
Oh yeah, sorry.
Hey, its no problem.
I want kenji to do what he wants.
Rin...
Kenji...
I watched all of them
Hey you guys.
What are you doing here?
No, nothing.
Yes, we’re not watching what owner and store manager are doing.
What’s that?
What are you saying? Kenji is Chihiro-san's ex boyfriend.
She’s working at milky way though they have that kind of relationship.
Are you going to make a big problem?
What that mean?
That’s...
What does that mean?
Hey, you’re really a pervert Kenji.
If you do that, I would want to do it again.
Kenji...
Why isn't this getting bigger?
Is it no use if I’m the only one touching it?
Morning bath!
I can guess what happened but you should not hit your big brother Akira-chan.
Hmp
Don’t mind about me so have fun.
Ok, then we’ll be going onii-chan.
Hey Akira-chan...
We’re going.
Hey wait Akira-chan.
It was effective...
I’m Kokoro from Tokoro library.
Niko Niko Rin.
Will this be alright?
She's got different taste.
I don’t know.
My code name is Nymph.
The woman who enters the dimension silently.
Will this be alright?
The director made some weird content so... I think so.
I don’t know.
I’m a teacher, welcome to my sweet tasty honey class.
It’s a prior thing!
Will this be alright?
She’s so good.
Good good , 2000 of the magazines are sold.
The cosplay is also in good shape.
Lets keep this up tomorrow too.
You’re quite energetic Rin-san.
Rumi, why are you here?
Wait sis~~
Kenji, are you sleeping?
Kenji, you know....
I was jealous of Rin when we started dating.
I thought that Rin was still close to you even though we were lovers.
Kenji?
What? Is that Rin?
What!?
Chihiro?
What are you doing?
Why are you...
Hug me Kenji.
Even though we're no more lovers, please hug me.
I wanted to be hugged by Kenji.
But Chihiro, I have...
I know the part which makes Kenji feels...
Chihiro...
It feels good.
Rin.. Rin... I...
You can have an affair Kenji.
But... Rin...
Having an affair is what the men want right?
But...
I want you do what you want.
Is that so?
Kenji!
Good.
Its embarrassing.
Its embarrassing but it feels good.
Its flowing out.
Kenji's face will be wet because of my juice.
Chihiro, you try putting it in.
Ok.
I’ll put it.
I’ll put it in.
This...
Kenji's dick is touching my entrance.
Its coming in.
Kenji’s dick is coming inside me.
Its coming...
Chihiro...
It's all in.
Kenji’s dick came all the way in me.
Its thrusting...
Into my part...
Kenji's thrusting deeper!
It feels good.
Kenji's thing feels so good.
I love you.
Kenji!
Kenji.
Its good.
Does it feel good inside me?
Feel it.
Please feel mine more.
Good, my nipples feels so good.
Kenji...
You remembered where I feel good the most.
You remembered it.
I think this part too.
Yes, that's it.
It's...
Its great.
Its getting bigger.
Its getting harder.
I love you Kenji.
It feels so good.
My boobs, my pussy...
They feel so good.
More...
Give me more.
Please make me a good girl
Chihiro...
I love you, I love I love you...
I love you Kenji.
I love you Kenji!
I love you more.
I love you more than ever.
Chihiro... I’m at my limit...
Sure, come.
Release, release a lot of yours, Kenji.
Chihiro... Chihiro...
Manager!
Forgive me for suddenly saying this, but...
Milky Way is a very important place to me.
But such a rude action of the manager in the store is...
We’re going.
Eh?
Eh?!
This is...
Sa-Sakuya-chan?
Why are you here?
Fu?
Sakuya-chan?
Hey Sakuya-chan! Get a hold of yourself!
Onii-chan?
What is that stupid bro doing?
What are you screaming at?
Hey stupid! Don’t open it!
W-What's this!?
It’s a misunderstanding!
Onii-chan...
Akira, Ayu, this is a mistake!
It's a mistake!
red lantern
Good work everyone.
The magazines are sold and the cosplay was good too.
Its enough, its enough.
Lets celebrate the success of the first day!
Cheers!!
high sour
radish salad
whirlpool capelin
baron croquettes
cold tofu
deep fried chicken
fried egg
To be continued..
next
I can’t believe my stupid big bro, even though he has Rin-san, right Sakuya-chan?
Me!?
What do they like about that stupid bro?
Right?
I don't think it's like that.
The store manager is kind.
D-Don't tell me Sakuya-chan you too...
Yes I am.
Then I’ll do my best too.
Yes?
Next on milky way episode 2:
I can’t stop how I feel.
I will also tell the store manager how I feel.
That's my line!