Bijukubo
Part One
Translation by SubDesu-H
Don’t misunderstand.
This is my first time.
That's a lie.
Sis told me.
You’ve been going out with many men.
If you don’t believe me then, I’ll stop.
I can’t believe you.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t want you to be hurt.
I’m no good.
I feel uneasy if no one seeks me.
I thought of you as an important person.
Isn't that enough?
You say there’s no use if I’m not blood related?
My body is like cast-off skin if I don’ t have the warmth of a man.
Uneasy, uneasy and uneasy.
What’s that!?
I told you not to meet with Ikue-san.
It's enough.
No, you can’t do that, don’t go to that woman.
What’s this? What’s this feeling which enters into my every nerve?
I see, this is what I desire, to love my mom as a woman.
I know even if she promises, her immoral body looks for another man.
In her whole life.
I’ll give you my body if you want a man that much.
What did you say just now?
I love you mom since long time ago, since before the other men.
No.. even if we’re in-laws, we’re still mother and son.
I've loved you since long ago.
I can’t bear that you’ve been held by other men.
I understand, but this is all I’ve got.
Mom..
Wow.. it's big, it’s the biggest one I’ve ever seen.
This will be the first and last time.
Release all the bad juice and go back to good and kind you.
You want some boobs?
No.. I feel it, I feel it as you suck my boobs.
And your dick is getting bigger inside my hand.
Mom, don’t over do it.
It will come out!
I’m cumming, I’ll cum inside your mouth mom!
It's getting bigger and bigger. You’s dick is getting bigger inside my mouth.
Release it, release it inside my mouth.
You, you really love me a lot eh?
Come here.
Make me your only woman.
Put this inside mine.
And we will be one.
It's wet.
Mom’s that part is all wet and wants mine.
Yes, there.
Go on, thrust me with your big dick.
Good more more harder!
Mom!
I didn’t think inside of you would be so warm, it feels good!
I love you.
I love you mom.
It's hard and big, did I desire this since you were young?
This immoral thing?
Your dick is rampaging inside me.
I can’t obtain this pleasure from other men.
It's so good.
I feel like I’m being burned.
Maybe this is going to become a habit.
Why do I feel so good?
I see, this is because of our forbidden past.
Between you and I.
Mom, I’m going to cum again.
I’m going to cum inside you mom.
No, don’t release it inside me!
Don’t do it, I’m going to get pregnant!
Bear it and release it outside!
I’m cumming, I'm cumming!
Why did this happen?
I love my mom as a woman.
Yes, everything was ruined since that day.
A month before.
That was the time I started to go to university and it was my birthday.
You, be calm and listen.
You are not my real son.
Hey mom, it's my birthday today, don’t say such a joke.
Your father’s name is Youichi.
He’s my brother.
He eloped with a certain woman and you were made a long time ago.
But Youichi wasn’t used to his life style and he got sick and died.
It was like he was killed by that woman.
Uhm, what happened to my real mom?
She abandoned you and went back to her parents home.
Why she leaved me?
Her parents disliked your father.
They thought that your father deceived her.
But your real mom died after that.
So you mean you adopted me unwillingly!?
No it's not...
I didn’t have the confidence at first because you’re Youichi’s son.
You were really close to my real father eh?
Oh yes we were.
You only stopped crying when I held you, even other people tried.
I thought that you had chosen me, I decided to raise you at that time.
Mom...
I’m home.
Sorry, It got late while I was looking for a gift.
What’s wrong you two?
Did something happened?
You-chan, you’re trembling?
Don’t tell me kaho-san.
Yes, but You is already an adult.
He’s at age that he must part with me.
You-chan, listen.
I’m the daughter of Kaho-san’s elder sister.
We’re not directly blood related.
But I’m your sister ever since then right?
You-chan was so attached to me.
I’m still your sister who ever your mom is.
Me to! I’m still your mother even.
Can I still call you “mother”?
You, Fumika and I are your family forever.
That was a birthday which I can’t forget.
But it was just the beginning.
You-chan is late.
That boy, he could give us a call.
Where did he go?
Why don’t you try calling him?
Please wait here for a while.
I’m home.
I’m home?
Where have you been?
There’s someone moving in next door right?
I helped her and had some dinner there.
You could have just called me.
I was worried about you.
Sorry.
Oh by the way, our neighbor is here to meet you.
Oh I see.
Why are you here?
Long time no see, Kaho-san.
Don’t call me so casually, my body will shiver.
I’ll ask you directly.
Does Youhei-kun know about his mom?
Eh? My mom?
What are you saying? It's none of your business.
Sorry Youhei-kun, I didn’t want to surprise you and I didn’t want to say it before coming here.
But I’m a relative of your real mother.
What are you saying?
How insensitive of you to show your face to You.
Kaho-san, I want Youhei-kun to be the successor of the Motai family.
My father died the other day.
And you’ve become the messenger eh?
But how filthy of you to be able to act as a blood relative.
Kaho-san, I heard it all from Youhei-kun.
You’re doing well with him eh?
Fumika, take Youhei away from here.
Ok.
Come You-chan.
I was confused and didn't know what to do at that time.
It's just, I can’t think of my life without mom and sis.
And I feel there’s some secret between mom and Ikue-san.
Hey You-chan what are you going to do?
Do what?
Would you go if the family of your real mom is a rich family and choose you as the successor?
What are you saying?
They can’t move my feelings if it's just like that.
Sis will be my sis forever.
You-chan, thanks.
Sis.
Sorry.
I must restrain myself too.
Why?
I was told by Kaho-san.
She went home.
She called for support.
But the situation can’t be solved so easily.
So we decided to try to reach an understanding.
She’s too selfish!
Does she know how You-chan was abandoned?
She’s too selfish.
It won’t go like that.
Why?
It's... uhm... that’s...
She said that we’ll settle this at court.
How about you, You?
What ever happens, I’m still a son of this family.
Thanks.
But we can’t ignore her since she came all this way.
Be strong, don’t say such thing.
Yes, it all depends on you.
I understand, don’t worry.
If we let our guard down, she might take you away from us.
This will be a war with her.
What will happen if we lose?
Maybe we can’t meet with you anymore.
Aside from the secret between mom and Ikue-san, I didn’t know that mom and sis had that conversation at that time.
You-chan.
What is it sis?
I haven’t washed your back in a long time.
There’s no need, I can do it myself.
What are you saying, we just took a bath together last time.
You-chan, do you like me?
Of course.
Your boobs are touching and I feel it.
What? You feel it?
This is a war with her.
How about this?
No... We siblings should not do something like this.
Ok then, here in front.
No need, I can do it myself.
Are you sure?
I want to clean you up.
Stand up.
It's big.
And it's throbbing..
I can’t hold it, it's all hard and aching.
What should I do? Do you want my mouth or my hand?
Or this?
Youhei’s dick is so hard and big.
It feels so good.
Sis, it's so good.
I love You-chan since a long time ago.
But I thought we can’t be in a relation like this.
But I feel it.
My cervix feels it and wanted You-chan’s dick.
Don’t over do it sis.
It will come out!
Release it on my face You-chan!
Is it ok for you to lick it?
Yes, it's ok if it's You-chan’s.
It's fine, I’ll clean it up.
Hey. .
It's hard, big, You-chan’s dick is throbbing inside my mouth.
Don’t over do it, I’m going to cum again!
No!
Ouch.
What?
Big sisters must not do something like this right?
I love You-chan since a long time ago.
Since we’re not real siblings, can you take this off?
Are you sure sis?
I don’t want to be apart from You-chan,
I want to be one with you.
Here.
I feel it there.
You-chan is licking my sensitive part.
Don’t do it so rough.
My body is losing strength.
My whole body's become sensitive like a clitoris.
You-chan put it in already.
I’m going to pee if you continue.
No, don’t do it, it will come out.
The pee is coming out, it feels so good!
Hey sis, you always scold me when I pee while sleeping.
What a shame if you pee when your so old already.
You-chan, you meanie.
For the punishment, get on all four limbs.
I won’t, I want it normal since this will be my first time.
No, this is a punishment.
Here’s the punishment, here I come.
You-chan’s hard dick is entering inside me, it feels so good as my brother rapes me in the back.
How is it sis?
Do you feel me?
Don’t ever pee again.
Yes, I won't.
I feel it, I feel You-chan’s big dick thrusting inside me.
Please raped me deeper, to the cervix.
More more.
Break me more!
I want to feel You-chan more.
We’re one already, it mean your mine, you’re only mine.
I love you, I love you.
I’ll give you all mine.
I’m going to cum sis.
You can release it You-chan, it's a safe day today.
So release it inside.
Give me all you’ve got.
You-chan’s dick is getting bigger inside me.
You-chan’s dick is shaking inside me.
The hot juice is entering me.
I did it to sis...
What should I do from now on?
I sometimes though if in-laws can marry each other?
It was just groundless.
Uhm, I really can’t take the request.
Eh? There’s no need to give me an answer immediately.
My my, you still haven’t eaten your breakfast right?
Yes... they go out early.
But there’s some food in the house.
It's ok, we’re relatives anyway.
You can eat here.
Is it good?
Yes, it's just I’m hungry.
You can eat here any time.
Feel at home.
Ikue-san is beautiful and sexy.
She’s the finest example of an adult.
You can call me “mother” when you’re here.
But. .
Are you saving it for Kaho-san?
Well then, how about “mama”?
Mama eh? May be it's ok since she’s my mother’s sister.
I just thought of it recklessly.
Ma...ma.
Youhei-kun, thanks.
Thanks Youhei.
No... we can’t.
Why, didn’t you do that on purpose?
No it's not.. please understand.
Really, This is not the place where should I stay.
Wait!
You're so full of love since it's already like this.
Ok then, mama will do it with her mouth.
How is it?
Is it good?
It feels so good.
Ikue-san’s lips and tongue are soft and I feel like I’m going to melt.
Youhei, call me mama.
It's so good.
You’re so cute Youhei.
I didn’t even done this to that man.
I’m licking Youhei’s dick.
No... I should not do this.
But if I stop now, I’m going to lose Youhei.
No... this is just an excuse.
I’m looking for Youhei.
My pussy is all wet as proof.
My cervix wanted Youhei’s hard dick.
Mama, I’m going to cum.
I’m cumming, I'm cumming
Youhei you... mama will clean this up.
Youhei-kun, what are you doing?
Mama, I will do it for you.
No... stop.
Look, you’re all wet.
You want this right?
No... no...
Even you say that, you’re body is honest.
Mama look.
Youhei-kun, Stop it.
Mama sorry,
I can’t hold it any longer.