Now I can finally do it with you, Atsuko-chan.
Hachiya-san, it's too close.
Oh no, it's already this hard.
And it stinks.
Atsuko-chan, hurry.
It's big...
So, this is actually what their "counseling" is all about.
Correct, and it's mandatory for all women.
We've already informed Takagi-san of the matter beforehand.
In exchange, they are given the privilege to watch them in secret.
Watch them in secret?
It's a rule, and a responsibility in this town.
That's...
It's thick and stiff...
You can rub it harder.
Like this?
It got really stiff as I thought about taking your virginity.
Virginity?
But I already...
I already put in a request with the town
headman, so that I could get you first.
What should I do?
Atsuko-chan, I want to cum at least once
so please rub your breasts on it too.
Well, umm... all right.
Oh? A tit fuck, eh?
You're quite perveted, despite having a cute face.
I love that you know.
It's already...
How long do I have to do this?
Will I be doing this forever?
Huh? Your nipples are getting erect.
I'm... well...
Is Atsuko-chan a pervert that plays with her own boobs?
I don't do that!
Really?
Takagi-san!
Well, it's not really what you would call frequent.
Probably around two to three times in a month.
Dad, are you listening?
Wait, that's... huh?
I know everything about my daughters.
You always start with your right breast when you take a bath.
When you pee...
I said stop already, Dad.
I don't want to hear it!
Why do you even...? Jeez!
Why are you...! No!
It's your first time getting a taste of raw cock, right?
You see, mine's quite the bulky one.
Is that so?
Can you use your mouth too?
O-Okay.
I can't take it all in.
It's too big!
It's now in your cute mouth.
What?
How much did he just squirt out?
This is too much!
No way, it's supposed to get smaller after cumming.
Now it's calmed down.
Well then...
Wait Hachiya-san, just wait!
Not that I'm bragging,
but one of my specialties is to make a
woman cum during their first time.
Is it twitching right now?
How's the taste of a virgin pussy...
Hachiya-san!
Oh no, Hachiya-san's face is right in there!
Would it be wet and sticky enough?
Oh?
Where's your hymen?
Wait, he knows?
No way, oh no...
What should I do?
Hachiya-san, it hurts.
Hey, is this for real?
Yui-san, are you going home?
Oh John, yeah I am.
What should I do?
I can't handle these sorts of people well.
I'm about to go to my part time job.
That sounds hard, please do your best.
Oh no, what should I do?
Yes, it's true that she was still a virgin right before she came here.
I even checked her myself.
Dad, checked me?
Then, let's just leave it at that.
I heard she did it right after she moved here.
Perhaps... with one of her students.
Wait, I haven't done that!
I was completely fooled into thinking you were a bitch.
Umm... what are you...?
Did you enjoy pretending that it was painful?
No, I didn't...
I was really looking forward to getting a taste of your virgin pussy.
But I'm just as fine with used goods.
Used goods?
No, Hachiya-san...
That's not...
Oh, so this one's yet to be penetrated.
You're already experienced at blowjobs, right?
That's...
No, please not there!
This is weird, please don't!
Hachiya-san, don't put it there,
it's a bit...
You're really cute!
Man, I really would have wanted to break your hymen.
Stop!
Screaming in protest while still getting wet with these love juices...
I bet you did it often with your students, right?
I don't do that!
Teachers and students shouldn't be...
Oh well, I'll just have to do it with this virgin hole here.
Eh? What is he going to do?
In there?
It won't fit!
That's not the proper part!
It just won't fit!
Oh no, it's starting to go in.
It's going inside my ass!
No, it's pushing inside my ass!
What in the world is this?
It's now in.
His thing is now in my ass.
What's going on? Why?
He's started moving, but it's not where it should be!
It's gotten wet already.
I see your ass hole is also quite perverted.
No, it's not!
I'm not...
That's...!
The bitch teacher is now very wet.
That's not true!
No, no way...
Hachiya-san.
I don't want to do it in this position.
Stop this, Hachiya-san.
This is just weird!
You've been impregnated by other men already, right?
No, I've not!
Please stop!
If this continues...
This is weird, please!
No, stop!
It's pouring inside.
His cum is pouring inside my ass.
No...
Chief, can I have another round?
It may be better if you switch to your partner for the next round.
Yeah, that boy.
This is your punishment for being a used goods.
What are they going to do to me?
Hey boy, you sure got yourself a nice cannon there.
I'm quite surprised.
Umm... I can't hold back any longer, sir.
This voice...
Okay boy, just push it straight into her pussy, okay?
Got it.
A-Asuma-kun?
No don't, stop this, Asuma-kun!
This is just...
Sensei, I want to cum.
That's not it!
No, please.
This is counseling, Atsuko-chan.
You can't say no.
No, please really, don't!
Sensei, I'm going in.
I'm going to push my dick inside.
No way...
It's even bigger than Hachiya san's...
It's so thick, what is this?
It's already penetrating me!
I'm going to push the tip in a little further.
Eh? It's still at the tip?
No way...
This can't be, it won't it in!
That thing won't fit inside!
Onee-chan, Onee-chan!
Don't! Onee-chan? What are you...?
It feels so tight when it pushes in.
Oh no...
It's really drilling me inside!
He's really good despite acting quite feminine.
well, looks like I can't hold back either.
Even my ass...!
No way, I...
I'm...
Breasts...
The two dicks are rubbing against each other inside me!
Asuma-kun's and Hachiya san's!
I can't go on like this!
This is too much!
Hey boy, are you about to cum?
I'm nearly at my limit too.
Wait no, please Asuma-kun, Hachiya-san, I beg of you!
It's really a lecture with that guy?
What should I do?
Onee-chan... Sensei, I'm about to cum!
No way, I don't want this!
A lot is going to come out!
Oh no, please, no... this is...!
This can't be!
It's pouring inside.
Asuma-kun's going deep inside.
There are about 13 customers left.
After that, you'll obtain the quota for today.
Can we really not contact Onee-chan?
Like call her phone to see if she went outside for a while.
I don't think she'll respond immediately if she's busy.
Is that so?
That's volunteer work, right?
I wonder what she's doing.
Oh yeah, I heard it's a short-term training,
and Hachiya-san was with her.
Eh? That was the old man who molested her, right?
She's doing short-term training with him?
They say he teaches quite well.
Most people learn to do it well shortly
after he teaches them, it seems.
Learn to do it well?
We don't even know what she's doing.
Is that even real?
Atsuko was also a bit worried, but it eventually went well.
Is that so...
Well, I guess there's no point in mulling over it.
How about I go visit her?
It will start tomorrow, in the evening.
What is this?
I can hear weird voices.
Yui-chan! Over here.
Jeez, what kind of short-term training are you doing here?
No, this isn't it.
Umm... am I the only one who's doing this today?
Yep, and it's a special one-on-one session with you.
For you...
Well your breasts are quite small,
but I'm sure you'll get popular in no time!
Hey, don't say they're small!
So, what kind of volunteer work are they doing here?
Onee-chan never came home for the entire night.
I have absolutely no idea what it is.
You'll know soon enough.
Here.
Oh yeah, something bad happened recently.
Your wife run away from home?
Hey now, do you think of me as some kind of a bum?
Besides, she already did that a week ago.
Is this volunteer work something that everyone can do?
It's limited to women only though.
And it seems there is a surge in demand for it lately.
Just save the serious talk for later.
For now, let's just have fun!
Mister, you reek of alcohol already.
You've been drinking a lot, haven't you?
Are you all right?
Maybe I'm drunk already.
Mister, hurry up and tell me!
Okay, here goes.
They're petite, but the firmness is good.
They feel harder compared to Atsuko-chan's, though.
Hey, Mister...?
What are you doing? Hey!
Hey, just wait... Mister!
What are you... let me go!
Huh? I'm already showing it to you.
Now, stay still.
What are you saying?
You're telling me...
Wait... No!
It'll hurt if you try to resist.
So I'd advise you to just stay still.
Please, stop this already.
This volunteer work you see,
there are lots of people who come for it.
So you need to always be calm and collected for it.
No, stop.
Please, stop this.
Mister!
Hey John, p-please save me...
John, please!
Oh it's you, Yui-san.
I didn't hear you earlier.
Sorry about this, John.
Why don't you do it with me?
We're doing volunteer work practice.
What? Hey, just wait...!
H-Hey!
Good for me!
I'm ready to do it anytime!
As expected of you, John.
What is this? Hey, please stop this, Mister... John!
No way, what is this?!
What is this volunteer work?
Yui-chan, lick it as I instructed you.
It will hurt if you don't do it properly.
No, please stop this.
Mister, I beg of you.
Stop acting as if it's bad for you.
Or else I'm not going to play nice anymore.
No way, I'm going to lick this?
This stinky thing?
If you don't do it, I'm going to move your
head until you do it on your own.
John, stop this already, this is just weird!
Suck it already!
This is part of what you'll do.
No...
This can't be...
It stinks, and it's too big!
Suck it bit more gently.
You're going to suck many more in the future, you know.
This can't be... so this is the volunteer work?
But this is just...
Your boobs are quite small.
Atsuko's breasts are big though.
Onee-chan does things like this?
No way...
Atsuko-chan's breasts are quite popular.
And she usually puts dicks in between them.
Guess that's not possible for you, huh?
Ow, ow! Are you upset now?
I'm actually into this, but you can't just
use your teeth on other customers!
I'll just have to make it feel good until you cum, right?
Your technique is quite good.
Maybe you're actually fit to be a blowjob princess?
What? Don't call me weird names!
We usually choose one every month.
There's usually a point-based prize for the
winner so everyone does their best.
What?
Once they gain enough points, they're
supposed to get something special.
My wife's been racking up points on her own.
What's the meaning of this? What is this volunteer work really?
Is it doing something like this? This town is completely weird.
This is really a good town.
Stop kidding me!
Why does this town have such a...?
I can't hold back anymore.
Can I put it in now?
John, you can't have her yet.
Because she's mine.
Okay, please suck it so we all become happy.
What are you saying?
Your thing is...
Mister!
I can't take this thing in!
It's your first time, right?
You're going to become a woman with my dick.
Please, you definitely can't!
I really don't want this!
It'd be a bother to other people around if you keep being loud.
What are you saying?
Mister, your dick mustn't...!
Oh, this is a hymen!
You're the real deal virgin, unlike Atsuko.
They told me that she got a taste of
dicks just right after she came here.
No way, Onee-chan doesn't even have a boyfriend.
I wasn't able to break Atsuko-chan's hymen.
So I'll help myself with yours instead.
What, help yourself with mine?
You better stop fooling around now!
I'm taking it no matter how much you resist.
No, this can't be...
Why is my first time being taken away by this guy?
No way...
It hurts!
Virginity sure is great.
The sensation, the feeling, everything is great.
It hurts!
Your blowjob is the best!
Stop, stop. I don't want this, please!
I love Atsuko-chan's breasts, but I think I'll love fucking you as well.
This just can't be...
Why am I...?
If this is what volunteer work is, then Onee-chan
is doing the same thing too?
Your virgin pussy is already very wet.
Is your body the lewd type too, like your sister's?
Onee-chan's and mine aren't like that...!
You don't seem to know anything about your sister.
No way, I'm...
I'm at my limit, Hachiya-san.
Me too.
What? What is happening?
This is... their cum is pouring out!
It's starting to flow inside me!
This cant be, this can't be!
I'm being cummed inside!
Yui-san, now I'm your very first guy.
We're done for now.
Come by again if you want to learn something new.
Today's my day off.
Then, I'm going to start doing it again.
Those kinds of things...
Wow, you sure are popular.
Look at that long line!
No way...
For me to continue living here...
And for Yui to go to college...
I can't start complaining now.
Who is it?
The delivery guy?
Asuma-kun...
No, I have to be strong.
What's wrong?
Umm... Sensei.
S-Sorry.
Onee-chan probably won't become for a couple of days.
Because of work?
She seems quite busy.
How about your meals and other stuff?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, I see.
Well...
Sensei, Onee-chan you see...
What we did before was just part of that "counseling"... okay?
Onee-chan, always did it for me.
But she hasn't come home so...
Chikako-san always did what?
As siblings?
No way...
Wait Asuma-kun, this place is...!
Besides, this is...
My body is weak, that's why even if I do it at home,
Onee-chan can still fulfill part of her quota.
Her quota?
If the quota isn't properly reached, there will be
livelihood adjustments for that specific person.
So please do your best.
This is still a private matter exclusive to the town,
so please carefully watch what you say.
So it will still count even if I do it with Asuma-kun.
Chikako-san has been doing it,
and I guess it's far better than doing it with them.
At least with Asuma-kun...
Doing it with a student though is still...
Not something a teacher should do, but...
I understand.
If you're okay with that then I...
Okay! You're the second I love the most other than Onee-chan.
Oh, I took second place compared to Chikako san?
Okay, come on in, Asuma-kun.
It hurts.
You're pushing too hard, John!
Your pussy is very wet.
And it makes my dick feel very nice.
Are you out of your mind?!
I won't ever be aroused by this dick!
Idiot!
Oh, you're getting angry now.
John, please stop this already.
I don't want to be cummed inside.
Yui-san, I'm about to cum.
I do this to everyone equally.
You can't, John!
I said stop!
If you keep doing that...
Too late!
This is just...
You just kept cumming inside me...
Okay, I'm going to clean up the rest, so you can go home now.
What's wrong? You were very aggressive last time.
Are you embarrassed?
Try to relax a bit, here.
Does my breast feel good?
You can fondle it however you want.
Okay.
He's really good at this.
Asuma-kun, so you're really...
You're quite good at this.
Yep, because I frequently do this with Onee-chan.
I see.
Do it to me too, okay?
Oh no, his fondling perfectly balances gentleness and force.
Amazing...
So Chikako-san's being pleasured by this...
Sensei, me too, um...
His dick looks amazing.
This is the one that penetrated me last time.
Sensei, it feels good.
It feels the same as when Onee-chan does it.
Is that so? Chikako-san is...
But I can also make you feel good.
It's so big my mouth can't take it in.
Well?
It feels just as good as when Onee-chan did it.
So it's the same as your sister's.
I wonder how much she did it with him.
Oh no, Asuma-kun, that's...!
Asuma-kun, this is amazing.
What is this? I'm starting to really feel good now.
This is just...
Onee-chan told me that I should not do it with anyone else.
But I didn't really understand why.
Really?
I think I kind of understand her.
This is...
Onee-chan's not here, but you're here Sensei, I...
Asuma-kun, this is...this is...
Oh no, if this continues I'm going to
cum with just his fingers on me.
Asuma-kun, please I want your dick in me.
Sensei, can I really put my dick inside?
Push your dick all the way inside me, please.
Okay, here I go.
Oh no, Asuma-kun, don't push it in and out lightly like that.
You look cute when I do this, Sensei.
You're cute, Sensei.
Jeez, Asuma-kun you meanie.
It's in!
His thick dick is now inside me!
Oh yes!
This is amazing your dick is huge.
Sensei, you're amazing.
It feels as if I'm inside Onee-chan.
Asuma-kun, make a complete mess of me!
I'm going to make you feel a lot better than your sister.
Oh yes, your dick feels very tight inside me.
It's completely filling my pussy up!
I want to make you feel even better.
Asuma-kun, please stir my pussy more!
Push it harder!
Your dick is pushing upward.
It feels good, it feels great.
Sensei, it feels very good.
Your pussy feels even better than Onee-chan's.
Your dick is wonderful.
It's drilling deeper into my pussy!
I've been soiled.
I must... I must take a shower quickly... or else...
Right now...
Oh yes, I love this, Asuma-kun.
I don't think I can hold on much longer.
I'm starting to go crazy with your dick.
Your breasts are the best.
They feel even better than Onee-chan's.
Really? Even better than Chikako-san's?
Mine are better?
I'm happy, I'm happy Asuma-kun.
Push it in harder.
More, please!
Sensei, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming inside.
It's okay, just cum.
Cum it all inside me.
Make my womb drown with your cum!
Asuma-kun, cum inside!
I'll cum with you too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
This is your cum!
So much is flowing inside me.
Oh no... Everyone's still out, right?
I need to take a shower immediately.
I want to forget everything that happened.
It'd be awkward if Dad was here.
If someone finds out about this...
Huh?
These are Asuma's shoes.
He's here?
No way, if he sees me like this...
Huh? Nobody's home.
So, whose shoes are those?
I have to take a shower now.
Wait, Onee-chan's here?
Maybe she's tutoring him.
How cute, Asuma-kun.
You were so manly when you fucked me earlier.
You did your best until you reached your limit.
Yui, t-this is...
What is this?
So Onee-chan, you and Asuma are...
Onee-chan and Asuma are...
I'm such an idiot.
Yui, this isn't what you think.
This isn't...
What are you still denying it for?!
What should I think with you naked on the bed with him?!
What? Did you enjoy making fun of me the whole time?
Were you just making a fool out of me?
You knew that I liked him, is that why you wanted to do this?
What in the world is this...
Onee-chan...
Don't treat me like a fool!
Sensei, your breasts.
N-No, don't...
Not right now...
I said you can't.
Asuma-kun, no, it's gotten big again.
What is happening around me?
Onee-chan is...
Why did things have to turn out like this?
She's actually with Asuma-kun...
I don't want this anymore.
Stop, Asuma-kun.
Why are you...?
Amazing, I love your pussy, Sensei.
Right now, Yui is...!
We can't do this!
Yui-chan's breasts are tiny, so I love yours better.
Breasts?
Asuma-kun, that’s...
Hmph.
Oh yes...
This is great, Asuma-kun...
I can't hold back any longer.
We shouldn't be doing this, but I...
What a pathetic sight.
Asuma, I'll teach your dick exactly what
it means to make a fool out of me.
Yui-chan, it hurts.
Of course it does.
Because I'm making it painful.
It's far bigger than anything I've seen.
It still got hard and stiff even as I stomped on it.
You pervert!
Why are you doing this?
I'm going to tell Onee-chan.
Onee-chan, huh?
Speaking of which, you were having sex with my Onee-chan, right?
What do you think will happen if she learns about it?
You said you love her, right?
This is properly recorded, you know.
Yui-chan, just wait.
I was told not to do it with other people.
That's why...
But you did it with my sister.
I just did it because I love Sensei's breasts.
If it's breasts then I guess you can touch mine.
What's with that expression?
Are you mocking me?
N-No, that's not it.
But yours are small, so...
T-This guy...
Does he really understand his situation?
I'm pissed off now.
I was thinking of keeping my mouth shut.
But I guess I'll just have to tell everyone now.
Don't do that, please.
Not to Onee-chan.
I'll do anything, so I...
Oh, so you're willing to do anything, eh?
Yeah, that's why...
Well, that would depend on how you act.
Lick it.
O-Okay.
Wait, what is this?
His tongue is...!
This is just... oh no...
Wait, Asuma, just wait!
Jeez! Will you show a little restraint?
You're actually quite rough.
Maybe Onee-chan really just couldn't help herself if you're like this.
Hachiya-san, push it more, do it more intensely.
Atsuko-chan, I’m pretty much out of stamina.
Please cut me some slack already.
No, I want more of your dick!
I won't accept it if you're unable to satisfy my pussy!
Oh my...
You said you were going to satisfy me, right?
So push it deeper inside!
Asuma, this is amazing.
My pussy's about to go crazy.
I want more of it!
Yui-chan, I can't hold it in anymore.
I told you that you can't.
If you cum without my permission,
you won't be able to do it with Chikako-san anymore.
I'll allow it if it's with me, though.
I'll try to endure it.
It's just fine with me, right?
But I love breasts.
I like you, but you simply lack them.
You're being too honest.
I'm not letting you cum until I'm completely satisfied.
This ferocious dick in my pussy is amazing!
Hachiya-san, this is barely enough!
Yui already found out about me and Asuma-kun.
So I thought I'd just stick with you.
But this won't do.
Make me feel more pleasure!
I'm going to make your dick mine only!