www.SubDESU-H.net
Oh, that was a close call.
Well, I’m gonna borrow these clothes for just a bit.
Episode       I’m Off To Destroy The Hero.
W
Tadaaah!
The magic suppression bracelets seem to be working just fine.
If I continue on like this, pretending to be a human...
Here, sorry for the wait.
What was that for?!
You perverted old fart!
Drop dead, damn drunk!
Just because I have to suppress my magic so as to remain incognito,
it doesn’t mean I'm gonna let filthy humans...
... have their way with me!
Welcome, sir.
Step this way, please.
Thank you, Onee-san.
So... so cute!
I will bring you a glass of water!
Hey, what the hell am I doing?!
I am suppose to ambush the hero when he shows up at this place!
Kill the hero!
But I'm still allowed to have some fun on the side, aren't I?
Playing before a kill is very demon-like!
Excuse me.
I'm here to wash your back.
Oh dear.
I-I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Onee-san, what are you doin--
I'll wash you down to every last crack.
What a tasty looking butt you have.
Onee-san...Your boobs...
So slippery, doesn't it feel good?
My crotch is throbbing.
It's okay, I can bathe myself.
No.
What cute nipples.
Don't do that!
See? Now they're hard.
I wonder if this one is also hard?
Please stop...
This one is very mighty...
No, not down there!
This is a special towel with my scent on it.
Don't stroke it!
That white pee stuff will come out again!
We're in the bath - it's okay to get dirty.
Don't hold back - let it all out.
N-No!
What a strong male scent.
Even though you have such a sweet-looking face.
Don't smell it, please.
I'll pay you back with my scent.
Onee-san...
You're hard again.
In that case, I'll satisfy you inside of me this time.
My penis went inside of you, Onee-san.
That's right.
Your dick and my pussy are rubbing together.
And it feels very good.
It's... coming out.
More is coming out!
So much came out.
It squirted all the way to the top of my pussy.
Then next up, we'll...
Oh no! This is terrible!
If you don't wake up soon, I'll eat you.
Though I'll still eat you even if you do wake up.
Wait... you're that Onee-san from before.
Good morning.
Though it's still night.
Tonight, we'll have fun to our heart's content.
What? Please, don't do anything naughty.
Onee-san...
That's dirty.
Since I just washed it,
I think the flavor is a bit thin.
My penis is in your boobs!
Well?
It's soft... and fluffy...
And it feels good.
Onee-san... I'm about to cum.
Not yet.
You need to lick mine first.
Inside your mouth, Theo,
I want you full of my pussy-juice.
Theo, your face is shining with my juice!
Lick me more, like a pet.
Yes. Oh, yes.
See those things that look like flower petals?
Suck it!
Oh dear. Oh dear.
If you suck that hard, my clitoris will get hard!
Yes, there, yes there.
It's coming. Coming out.
Suck all my pussy-juice. I'm cumming!
Good grief.
I meant to tease you, but I was the one who ended up cumming.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Well, now it's time for the long awaited penetration!
What was that voice?
Could it be, Theo, that you like this?
Do you like your dick rubbed by a wet pussy? You pervert.
But no!
I won't let you cum that way.
You need to cum in here.
Thrust it in here and I'll suck out your semen.
Don't hold back - squirt it all in!
Does it feel good?
Doesn't it feel good?
Your dick feels like it's going to explode!
Are you at your limit already?
Cum while looking me in the eye.
Look, look! your semen is being squirted into my womb!
Yes... So much strong semen is still coming in.
I sense a demon presence.
Uh, no way! My magic is flowing out?
How dare you have your way with me!
Ouch!
Who would be satisfied by such sloppy fellatio?
That's right. That's the stuff.
I'm cumming. Swallow it all.
No way.
Why is there so much? I can't swallow it all.
Huh?
I'm not finished yet!
No!
Have mercy!
Don't give me that shit, you fucking demon whore!
Who said you could have a break?
A hero's dick is so big!
See? Doesn't this feel good?
It f-feels good...
It feels good!
It feels so good!
Yes...Oh no!
I can't let him get away with humiliating me like this!
But...
Why does it feel this good?
I want to fight back, but...
My body...
It won't listen to me.
This must be...
The hero's power?
No!
And now the final blow.
Demon whore, get ready.
No!
The loathsome hero's semen...
... is making me cum!
Eh?
My bracelets would break if I was unable to absorb it... How  did you know that?!
Oh, shit.
Wait...
Aren't you that succubus I met earlier?
Wh-what's it to you?
I will destroy you here and now!
That's what I meant to say!
I came here in the first place to defeat you!
I lost!
Damn hero!
This isn't over yet!!
www.SubDESU-H.net