Senpai's breath feels like it's reaching my deepest spots!
It feels so good against my clitoris!
You're still so small right here...
Grow larger, grow larger!
Grow larger, grow larger! Grow larger!
Senpai! Don't grab my ass that tightly!
No! Don't play with it so much! I won't be able to hold back!
Amazing...
You're so big, now...
Your hard cock looks so cute.
You're really hard, so you must be feeling aroused, right?
Your pre-cum is coming out already, Senpai...
No-! You're eating my pussy!
Senpai, it feels so good!
It's so hard and it feels so good! Futaba's-! No-! Futaba's gonna lose it!
Amazing! Your cock tastes so good!
Senpai... You're so energetic so early in the day!
My pussy feels amazing! Your cock is so hard too!
Oh no-!
We'll continue later, okay?
Oh, Onee-chan! Senpai's awake now.
Your breakfast is ready.
Fukubiki! Triangle
presented by SubDesu-H
All you should do is watch me.
Senpai, you're going to be late!
You can't hold back either, can you Senpai?
You're overflowing already...
Futaba couldn't hold back, either...
She was playing with my pussy with a ballpoint pen during class...
Futaba-chan, we shouldn't do this here...
Class is about to start, and...
Geez, I know that you can't hold back either by the look of your cock...
Oh no-! The tip is in me!
It feels too good!
Futaba-chan-! Really, we-!
You're still so cheeky about this!
Senpai...
Futaba's pussy is filled with your cock, Senpai!
Your cock is getting bigger inside me!
Futaba-chan-! I can't-!
You can cum deep inside of me, Senpai...
Doesn't Futaba's wet pussy feel good?
Can you really hold back?
My breasts aren't as large as Onee-chan's, but they're still okay!
If you won't do it, then...!
Senpai-! Not so suddenly-!
It's so deep-!
No~! It feels too good!
Your cock is making Futaba's pussy feel too good!
You're thrusting inside me so much!
No-!
People might see us from below!
My breasts are pushing against the railing! It's cold!
Senpai-! More!
Right there-!
I want you to squirt your thick semen inside me!
So rough-!
Senpai-! That's good, thrust harder!
It's so deep-!
Your cock is so hard! Let it out like this!
That's it-!
Your semen is still spurting out...
What's this...?
U-Um, Futaba-chan...
How should I say this... We shouldn't do these things...
Things like this?
Futaba-chan... I'm sorry, we can't keep doing this...
I apologize for not being decisive...
Geez, Senpai...
I said that until Onee-chan's memory comes back...
Futaba wouldn't be a fussy girl...
See ya then, Senpai. I'll be shopping before heading home.
So don't wait up for me!
Onee-chan should be waiting too!
Oh no, am I seeing things?
Ushio-kun, I ended up coming...
Miharu?! How are you feeling?
U-Um, about that...
O-Oh no!
Y-You can come in now...
Thank goodness you had some spare clothes!
I'm really sorry, Miharu. I guess someone forgot to put that bucket away...
No, I'm fine. Don't worry about it.
This is going to keep happening, isn't it? Geez...
It's like training every day! I don't even get any time off!
That was close!
Ah, I guess you didn't need to hide as well...
Yeah...
I guess you're right...
But, this isn't bad-!
U-Ushio-kun?
It's hard!
U-Ushio-kun? We can't...
N-No, Ushio-kun! Not here-!
We'll be fine, just keep your voice down...
I said that we can't-!
No-! Ushio-kun is so big down here!
No, not there! That's my butt!
He mustn't touch me there! Ushio-kun...!
No-!
Huh, what? Did you say something?
Huh? No, I didn't say anything...
Really? Never mind then, lets hurry!
Wait up!
Geez, you're so slow...
U-Ushio-kun! That's my...!
Miharu, I'm gonna put it in now...
What-? T-There?
In my butt?
Or would you rather I did...
Huh? N-No...
N-Not my butt...
It'll be fine.
No-! So rough-!
Ushio, don't-!
M-My pussy's so full!
Your cock, it's-!
No-! U-Ushio-kun, that's-!
That's my butt!
No-! Don't! I'll lose it!
Don't play with it-!
Hey, it feels strange!
I'm-! No, stop it!
Ushio-kun-!
N-No! You can't-!
I want to see your face, Ushio-kun...
It's coming in me so deeply!
No-!
Ushio-kun-! I can't hold it in!
No more-!
S-Something that large won't fit!
It'll be fine, I've been playing with it all this time...
Noo-!
It feels strange!
I-Is it all the way in?
No, it's about halfway in-!
It's in!
T-This feels strange...
I-It'll start to feel good soon.
Really?
It will, it will.
N-No! Wait-!
This, it's-!
No, no! You'll pull out my insides!
Are you getting used to it?
No way, I won't-!
Why would I feel aroused from this? That would be weird!
I can feel it reaching my stomach!
No-! Ushio-kun, it feels strange!
My butt, it's... It's...!
No, it feels strange! I'm feeling strange!
Ushio-kun! I'm, I'm gonna cum-!
No way! You're filling up my stomach...
No... I came too...
H-Huh? Miharu, that's...
Huh? Oh this? It was in the pocket of my uniform...
It bugged me, and...
I'll put it on eventually, since it looks like I was overjoyed by it.
You're too wishy-washy sometimes...
Is this going to be my engagement ring? Or is it just a fashion item?
Please decide by the time we graduate!
C'mon, Onee-chan. Hurry up and take a bath!
I'll put your uniform in the washing machine.
Now that Onee-chan is taking a bath, how about I get Senpai to lick me clean?
Huh? Senpai?
So you ran away...
Fu-Futaba-chan?!
Since Onee-chan is in the bath, Senpai...
I'll relieve...
Sorry, but like I said before, we can't do this... Okay, Futaba-chan?
G-Geez Senpai, what are you joking around for?
It's fine.
Huh?
I don't want to upset Miharu, and it'll just be troubling for you...
W-What are you saying?
You were just a virgin before, and n-now you're giving me lectures?
I've... I've really been too laid back about this, I did a horrible thing to you two.
I deserve whatever you say about me.
I'm really sorry, Futaba-chan...
Senpai...
You're horrible!
Wha-? Futaba-
Pervert...! Freak! Lecher!
Pervert! Ugly! Shorty! Pervert! Incompetent! Poor!
Pervert! Sex maniac! Pervert! Virgin! Pervert!!
Pervert! Retard! Pervert! Hairless! Pervert! Precocious!
Pervert! Parasite! Pervert! Virgin!
Pervert! Ditsy! Pervert! Pervert!!
You didn't need to go that far...
You're such a dick, Senpai!
I'm the one who's about to cry...
Ushio-kun...
Miharu?
This is something that you begged me to buy...
You said that I was too wishy-washy...
So, I've decided...
Can I?
Sure!
H-Huh?
That's strange...
O-Ouch-!
Dam-!
It in...
Miharu, now we're...
No...
I said that it hurt!
Geez! You forcefully put it on despite my pleas... You brute!
Miharu! You're...!
Geez, what's all this about?!
Uh, huh?
Senpai, you brute! Argumentative! Lascivious!
Bleh!
Ushio...
You better explain this...
What? Memory loss?
Why d-did I...?
It was when you fell.
Fell? I fell? Why?
You tripped, and...
Lies! Why would I...?
It's the truth.
No wonder it doesn't feel like I've missed your cock, even though I forgot everything.
Don't decide it from that!
Although Futaba was with you all along!
Your cock feels so good!
So...
Huh?
How long was this cock inside Futaba while I had lost my memory?
Ow, ow! That hurts Miharu, it hurts!
Bear with it! Geez, doing it with my sibling while I was in such a state...
I'm really sorry!
I apologized to Futaba-chan too...
She's not the kind of girl who'll forgive you!
Futaba! How long are you going to hide there for?
What?
Didn't Futaba-chan just leave...?
Futaba-chan?!
Congratulations on finding me.
Having sex right after getting your memory back? How improper.
L-Look who's talking!
You... You slut!
Hmph, saying such overused phrases...
So then, when is it my go?
I won't give such good wallet- er no I mean, boyfriend away!
Futaba-chan made similar blunders, too...
Does it run in your family or something?
Y-You should just sit there and appreciate this!
This cock is only for me!
Oh really? Then I'm afraid I'll have to take it from you.
No-! It's amazing!
Your cock feels so good~!
No-! Don't poke my clitoris with your nose!
That's it, Ushio. Fill my pussy with your cock!
Onee-chan! You know that I trained that cock, don't you?
Huh? W-What the hell are you talking about?
No, I'm gonna cum from this-!
I'm gonna cum from Ushio's cock again!
Futaba feels good from Senpai spreading me with his tongue!
N-No-!
Fu-Futaba-!
I'm-!
Let's cum like this-!
Onee-chan!
Futaba's gonna cum too-!
It feels too good, and-!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
No-!
Your cock is so good!
C'mon Futaba, hurry up!
Geez, once is enough...
Futaba wants to drink the freshly-made semen too!
What on Earth is this girl saying? Geez...
Whatever! I'll sexually assault Senpai at school!
If you keep saying stupid things, I'm leaving you behind!
Sorry to make you wait!
...And then I was bacon.