Nii-san...
SubDESU-H Presents
The girl raped by the
Sinister
NERD
Loss of virginity
Good morning, Nii-san.
Yes, good morning Saki.
I got an e-mail from dad.
He said his business trip will take longer because he got a request from the university.
Eh? Again?
Even if he's together with mom,
for how many months do they think they must stay away from home?
I think its alright.
Dad and mom think they're always on a honey moon.
And...
And?
We can keep the secret about Nii-san for a while.
I'm Mizuhara Shuuji.
I was an orphan and the ones who adopted me were,
the new couples of the Mizuhara-family.
Her name is Saki.
She's my sister but we're not blood related.
According to my friends, we're in a relation that everyone is jealous of.
Long time ago, after a manga which tells the story about a lover that resembled us got popular,
Everyone's twisted desires became projected.
And now, me and Saki have been in that kind of relationship.
Indeed we're still platonic,
but our feelings are waiting for that day.
Nii-san...
I'm very happy.
Me too, Saki.
I'm certain that I’m very happy right now.
Cats are really cute, right?
I want to have one.
Uh? No you can't.
Mom has cat allergy.
Oh that's right, I think that's a bad idea.
Then, how about me becoming Nii-san's special cat?
Nya nyan nya nyan nya~~
Eh?
What's the matter?
No...
It's a mail from my friend.
Oh.
Uhm... I'm a bit tired so..
I'm going upstairs for now...
I see.
Get some rest quickly.
I’ll be the one to prepare the breakfast tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
Good evening, Saki.
To my only Saki.
You should not be too friendly with your onii-chan.
Even though you're siblings,
I'm still jealous.
No!
This... is me.
This room is...
I’ve been peeped at.
Calm down...
Its alright.
I need to calm down.
The mail was from the stalker.
He knows very well my daily happenings.
Also the person who is peeping called me.
And said to come to the next town on Sunday noon.
I wont go on a date with a stalker.
This is a spam mail, I must ignore this.
I have a date with Nii-san this Sunday.
But, why does he knows my address?
And...
What will happen to me if I don't go?
I know it clearly.
If this were to be uploaded to the internet...
I can't make Nii-san worry.
I need to make him stop this.
I must go and do something.
The basic of anti-stalker is:
To ignore all their request
If you accept their request,
He thinks he can get away with it, so the stalking will escalate.
Good afternoon, Saki.
You're so cute again today too.
Surely that uniform suits you best.
He's nearby watching me.
Then, I have a request.
From now please do as I say.
Spread your legs and show it to the public?
I must not accept the request of the stalker.
I know that, but...
I must do it.
If I don't do it...
Those perverted pictures...
More horrible things will happen...
to me and Nii-san.
The panty is breaking into that place.
It's breaking into my embarrassing place.
Everyone might think of me as a crazy girl.
Who's happy on opening her legs and showing off her panty?
They might think of me as a perverted girl
My heart is beating fast and I’m going crazy.
Inside my body... Inside my stomach is so hot.
Its hot...
What?
That part is starting to itch.
Even though I'm doing this embarrassing thing...
I'm so wet...
I’m so horny right now watching Saki.
Saki is the same as me, right?
Its because Saki's pussy is so wet that even the panty is stained.
I know it clearly.
N-No... I’m being watched.
I’m spreading my legs and...
Showing my panty and...
My wet pussy is being watched.
I don't like it cuz I'm being watched, but...
When I think of being watched,
More perverted juice start flowing out.
Don't tell me, I'm getting excited?
Am I feeling horny?
Not only outside but also I might be being watched from inside the store.
No...
Please forgive me.
Don’t make me do anymore embarrassing things.
This is...
Saki a while ago was so perverted.
It was the best.
This time, I want us to go to a place where we can be alone.
There’s a hotel named kaze no uta ahead,
so please go there.
The room number is 303.
I’ll be waiting for you my cute girlfriend.
Hotel means...
Not only will he watch, me but also to do that...?
Am I going to be raped by the stalker?
But I think this will be a chance.
Being alone together means,
I can face the stalker and talk to him properly...
Anybody here?
No! Stop it!
Let me go!
You're the one who sent me the mail right?
Yes, I'm your lover.
Lover?
Who are you?
Please stop it.
Don't look at it.
Don't look at my boobs.
No!!
It's big and so soft!
Stop it!
I don't want this.
Stop.
Don't lick my nipples.
It's disgusting.
My nipples...
No...
Its embarrassing...
Stop it.
Don’t suck it.
My boobs will become weird...
No, its embarrassing...
Stop it...
Don't play with my boobs...
It'll break...
My boobs will crush!
N-No...
Don't suck it that much or else...
My nipple will get hard...
It will get big and
it will erect...
I will feel it...
No...
Its hot...
My boobs are hot and my nipples are...
I don't want this.
I've not even been touched by Nii-san.
With this disgusting perverted guy...
My boobs are being sucked!
My nipples...
Don't bully my nipples...
Even though It's so disgusting...
Even though I don't want this...
My feelings have become sensitive...
I can’t hold it anymore, Saki.
There...
You can't do that.
If you strip away my panty...
I’ll...
No!
Stop it please.
Please don't look at it.
Oh? Saki's pussy is so wet.
Did you feel it when I licked your boobs?
It's not wet.
Please forgive me.
You're so poor if I tease you so.
I'll put it in immediately.
Put in what?
No!
Only that one...
I’m still a virgin...
And its my first time...
No-
No!!
N-Nii-san...
Sorry.
Nii-san...
Ouch!
It hurts!
Stop it!
It will break!
That place will break!
No! No!!
Noooo!
Stop it!
Don't move!
It hurts.
I-It will rip!
Even though it hurts...
Even though I don't want this...
Deep inside...
It's hot... It's hot deep inside!
No...
Its making a sound...
It's making a dirt sound...
My pussy is making a dirty sound...
It's going in deeper...
Ouch!
Stop... Stop it please.
If you thrust that much...
I'm going crazy...
My boobs are shaking...
And it really hurts...
Don't rub it...
Even though its my first time...
Why...
No...
My pussy is wet...
Its so embarrassing.
There's a lot of juice...
Please forgive me already.
Nii-san...
I only love Nii-san.
I only love Nii-san the most in the whole world.
Here I come, Saki!
I'm cumming!
The sperm!
No! No! No!
Take it out!
Don't release it!
I don't want to get pregnant!
Don't release it please!
Nii-san help me!
I-Its coming out!
The sperms are coming out...
No, if you release it inside I'm going to get pregnant.
I’ll get pregnant!
No! I don't want this anymore...
My pussy is sticky and full of sperms.
Take out the...
Please, your penis...
take it out...
my pussy...
Take it out...
It stinks.
What's this?
My pus... pussy...
Its getting bigger
It's getting bigger.
It's flowing out.
The sperms are being released inside my pussy.
Its flowing out!
The sperms are flowing out from my pussy!
I released this much,
I think Saki got pregnant with my baby.
To my beloved, Saki.
You were so cute a while ago.
Lets date some more again next time.
It can't be...
It can't be, right Saki?