Himegaoka Central Hospital
I can still hear my heartbeat.
No, I can’t hear it.
No, I can!
It’s because you desire for it.
Eh?
I’m sorry.
But this is your fault.
You should have known that this would happen.
I've caught you.
We’ll not let you go.
Isn’t it so good,
Inside us?
You can never get out.
Come.
Subdesu-H
Presents
Anata No Shiranai Kangofu
~Seiteki Byoutou 24ji~
Chapter 2
Please Stain Me Forever
"Ayanuma Chitose, the head nurse at that time knew everything"
Oh uhm, Juumonji-san?
I heard that there was a nurse who died here 3 years ago.
What are you saying?
I don’t know about that.
Then I will help you remember it.
Why?
Where did you get that?
Chitose-san, you were her boss, right?
Did you just leave her to be like that?
That’s...
The owner of the hospital told me not to get involved with that.
She’s beaten up.
And she hoped you would rescue her.
I’m sorry.
Please forgive me.
I'll teach you how she suffered.
What are you going to do?
Don’t come near me.
You...
You won’t be forgiven for this.
Then is what Chitose-san did forgivable?
Please forgive me.
This big one...
I can’t bear it if I see these big boobs.
Don’t touch it.
What's wrong Chitose-san?
It feels good?
It can't feel good.
Is that so?
It's hard enough.
Ouch...
Stop it Juumonji-san.
What a reaction.
Maybe you’re already wet.
Don’t say such dirty things.
It's not wet.
Here Chitose-san, lick it.
I can't... do that...
I see.
I think a more intense one was used on her.
No way...
Put more saliva on it.
What a dirty tongue technique.
You forced me to do it.
Chitose-san, you’re thinking of making me cum with your mouth, aren’t you?
Next, use the mouth below.
It came in... no...
It’s wet.
This is...
No...
What should I do if someone comes in?
That’s why you’re getting excited.
No...
No... please stop this...
You’re wet this much even though you’re saying you don’t want it.
Chitose-san is lecherous.
No I’m not.
I’m not lecherous...
Stop...
I’m gonna moan...
Its alright, show them the slutty Chitose-san.
They'll watching me.
This is embarrassing.
Don’t thrust so intensely.
Its good...
Is it good?
No...
No.
Its stirring inside and its tickling.
No...
I’m shaking my hips...
I’m going crazy.
I...
Chitose-san’s pussy is twitching.
You’re cumming right?
No...
I can't...
I can’t...
You came even you though said no.
No...
I...  I...
Please... forgive me...
She’s another victim...
Hm?
Is anybody here?
Are you alright?
What!?
You finally came.
Hiratori-san.
What?
Open your legs wide please.
Stop it...
We saw it.
You and Juumonji-san having sex.
No... that was...
Please entertain us too.
No.
Its embarrassing.
Please.
Stop.
No.
No!
Stop it.
Help me.
Yousuke-san.
I want to tie with you deeper.
Please come deeper.
Inside me...
Take out the vibrator.
Someone will see me.
Its not embarrassing for this charming body to be shown off.
He said its walking.
What kind of walking is that?
This pet dog is a bit special.
She’s lecherous.
I’m not a dog.
Don’t put it in deeper.
Wow.
It’s a beautiful pink color.
No... don’t play with it.
Don’t look at it.
If you stir it too much, I’m gonna pee.
By the way, you drank a diuretic a while ago right?
You forced me to drink it right?
No...
I think you need more discipline.
Your ass hole is twitching.
Stop it...
Its embarrassing.
Don’t look.
Does she like to be spanked?
No...
I don’t like that.
No... it will flow out.
No...
I’m cumming.
Oh no...
I feel weak.
No... it will come out.
Don’t look.
It’s nurse’s pee!
I can't stop it...
No!
I can’t hold it in any longer!
Someone... help me!
Stop...
In this place...
What a dream, to be given a hand job by this beautiful nurse.
The big one is thrusting inside me.
It’s punishment for peeing.
It hurts.
I’m sorry.
Please forgive me.
Your squeezing technique is great Akira-san.
I wont do it again.
Please, I’ll do anything so don’t hurt me.
Anything?
That will be my compensation.
I can’t go back.
Give me a lot of it...
Sperm from your dick.
That was the time the snow starting to fall.
It was just one, just a few millimeters of mistreatment.
It disordered my life.
At that time, I prepared to do anything just to compensate.
But...
It was hard for me to compensate them all by myself.
It was so bitter and lonely.
Yaji-san, please release me...
Is that the word you can say to my fiancé who just died!?
I’m sorry.
The smoothness of this breast is great!
Ouch...
Don’t be violent.
I’ll release it.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me...
Hey, don’t just open your mouth and suck this.
They would inject me with sperm when I was hungry.
They would hurt me if I was going to go unconscious.
Inside the dark, I didn't even know how many days had passed.
From that day, I wanted to commit suicide.
Forgive... me.
You’re all sticky.
Is she Amane?
Amane!
Are you here?
Amane...
Aname.
Forgive me...
Yousuke-san...
Its over.
Yousuke-san.
Its cold.
Don’t go.
I won’t go anywhere.
So you too, do something which will make me happy.
Please be my Amane whom I desire.
Become the one you desire?
Yes, you must be dirtier in front of me.
Dirtier...
Good.
Its warm...
Its like you’re wrapping me and feels so good.
Good.
No...
You feel it right?
Its because...
Yousuke-san... I...
I’ll do it intense.
Yes, do it more intense.
Say "please".
Please...
Yousuke-san.
Its good.
Where?
Inside me...
My pussy is being pounded by your dick and... ah...
Good.
Your dick is good.
I’m all wet because of Yousuke-san's dick.
The dirty Amane is the best.
I’m dirty...
My heart is beating when you thrust into me.
My boobs...
Touch my boobs more.
My pussy too.
Thrust deeper inside my pussy.
Good, Yousuke-san it feels so good.
More.
Please caress me more.
I’ll caress you.
I’m cumming.
Me too.
Release it where ever you want to.
Its so good.
No...
I’m cumming too!!
Juumonji-san, please bring me to heaven.
Sure Chitose.
I’ll invite you anytime.
Wow, it feels great.
My pussy is hot.
I’m cumming.
Me too.
No, Juumonji-san.
You can’t cum yet.
Good.
Onii-chan.
Nana is a bad girl.
Please punish me more.
Nana, you're a bad girl, you might go to hell.
Its ok.
I’ll go anywhere with you.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan.
I’m cumming.
I’ll cum first.
Please cum next after me.
I’ll be waiting.
Juumonji-kun, you’re the only one...
You’re the only one I’ll take care of.
You can cum too.
Its all over now.
Good.
Good, Juumonji-kun.
Release your self.
I can’t hold it.
I’m cumming!
Juumonji-san!
Onii-chan!
Juumoji-kun!
Yousuke-san!
I’m cumming!!
Yousuke san's  hot sperm...
is coming inside me.
I love you Amane.
Yousuke-san...
So you’ll only have to come with me.
Ok?
I’ll go with only you.
This is enough.
This is...
You can’t reach the thing you desire if you drive it.
Your true self.
Your suffering is the same as mine.
Is my world.
Are you the one who will save me?
"Are you the one who will save me?"