SubDESU-H.net
I'm sure it's the first time she's worn such a short skirt.
It's nice, but what's even better is what's underneath it.
Lovely Day
~The Seven Days With Her~
I'm just going to get something for us to drink, wait right here.
Okay!
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, could you please pass our ball back?
Okay, here you go!
Oh!
For real?
What's up?
Thank you!
She's not wearing any panties! Just to show off!
Don't you think that was a bit too intense for him in broad daylight?
Please give back my panties!
But Hazuki, you're the one who got all wet just now in the restaurant.
Don't say that...
Not just that, seeing you without panties in a public park made me like this...
Can you do it to me here?
You just have to put it in your mouth, you don't even have to move.
Okay?
Don't spill any, swallow it all.
Thank you.
I'm so embarrassed, Shin-chan...
Okay, let's do something even more embarrassing together...
Oh no, stop, everyone can see my pussy!
The louder you moan, the more people will notice.
I'm going in...
Hazuki, you're even wetter than usual - is this turning you on?
I don... I don't know!
But even your clitoris is so much harder than usual.
What? N-No way...
Stop struggling, you'll rip your skirt.
No...
Please don't... I'm really... really embarrassed...
That's why we have to do it before anyone comes, right?
I'm sorry...
Is this... okay?
Y-Yes...
Th-Then, hurry...
I'm such a freak...
After teasing her like this, I'm so turned on.
Hazuki... is it okay?
Hurry...
Hazuki, I'm sorry... But it was so good.
Thank you.
It was good for me too...
Three days left...
That's right, after yesterday, we...
Nao's so warm...
What's this...?
It's somewhere between soft and hard... It's bouncy, too...
It's different from usual.
I'm always too shy to take a good look, so this is my first time actually seeing it.
So this is what goes inside me.
It's so hard, hot, and wet... Amazing...
Um...
Don't stop, keep going.
I was so surprised to wake up and find you playing with me.
I wasn't.
You're sucking it! And touching yourself at the same time!
Was I really doing that?
Yes, you were!
Look, your clitoris is rock hard!
No, stop... It's embarrassing!
Come on, keep going.
I'm almost there.
We can't do this, it's so perverted!
I said no, Nao... we need to leave...
Huh?
We'll be late!
But look, when I touch my cock here, Hazuki's body pushes up against it.
No... you tease...
It feels good, doesn't it, Hazuki?
N-No...
Say it feels good.
It feels... good...
Wow, you're getting hotter.
Doing that just now turned you on!
I'm not sure if it did...
What did you like the most about it?
Raise your voice louder.
My pussy feels so good...
Why? Why does it feel good?
Your cock... Your cock feels so good...
No, stop, you can't-
But you enjoyed this yesterday.
The one in front and the one behind are rubbing against each other. You like it?
Not both... Not both holes...!
My insides... My insides are so wet!
You're gonna cum from your ass and your pussy. Say it!
My ass, my pussy...
I'm cumming... cumming...
Cumming!
Damn, we missed the role call.
And even worse, there's only one more day.
Today is the last day.
My family will be away on vacation for a week...
So while they're gone, Nao... I want you to do so many nasty things to me!
Even for me, that was a pretty intense week...
Though it's not like I'll have to stop doing things like that to her from tomorrow.
But...
Umm... Hazuki...
Y-Yes?
Did you wash my clothes? I need to pack, so I'll need them.
Alright.
Show me your pussy...
You're wet already...
I'm sorry...
Me too, I'm dripping.
I'm sorry, if you want me to stop, I will.
What should I do?
I've become such a bad perverted girl.
Please don't hate me...
Of course that won't happen.
You've done all those perverted things for ME.
I would never hate you...
In fact... I really love you!
You're so shy and you still do all of this for me.
Well, it's because I love you so much!
I love everything about you! I'll let you do anything to me! So...
Umm... Let's fuck!
Yeah!
Are you still shy if you're blindfolded?
Well, I can't see, so it's a little scary.
Spread your pussy a little more.
L-Like this?
Yes, like that.
Hazuki, you're so hard.
You used to be so soft.
N-Nao, don't!
Move slowly.
It's so hot! I feel like my finger is going to melt!
Hazuki...
Nao's smell...
Your mouth is so wet.
Do you love my cock?
They slide in so easily...
It's still inside...
Or rather, you're still squeezing it.
You... I want YOU, Nao...
Even after that, I tried to keep it going for another twenty four hours.
Wait, what're you...
All we did was fuck.
You can't...
We fucked... and fucked... everywhere...
Our amazing week together came to an end.
I'm sorry that you have to go, my parents seemed to like you.
That's ok.
I'm glad they didn't find out I'd stayed over.
Take care on the way home.
Ok.
I'll text you when I get home.
I'll be waiting!
Just like before...
No...
Even more than before, Hazuki and I are going to have some really fun times.