SubDESU-H Presents
Seme Chichi
Second Volume
Kis-sama...
Kis-sama's bed...
Such a great smell.
Slacking off from work to masturbate
in your master's bed, huh?
E-Ehm...
What an unbelievably perverted maid...
This was what you wanted, right?
Suck it.
You guys really would do anything
for money, wouldn't you?
I'm cumming! Make sure to take it all!
How was it?
Was your master's sperm delicious?
Y-Yes, it was very rich and delicious sperm...
Renka! You're there, right?
Come on out here.
Y-Yes.
Looks quite good on you,
doesn't it, Nanaly?
You...
Noblemen should act like noblemen, and
prostitutes should act like prostitutes... Right?
"Act like a prostitute" is okay, but...
What are you planning to do
in the middle of the day?
We've still got work left to do too, you know...
I can do it whenever I feel like it.
That's right... It's Master's whim, right?
Kis-sama... Doing it like that...
You two are quite good, aren't you?
How is it, Kis-sama?
That's good, Nanaly.
Kis-sama...
How do my boobs feel?
Your soft boobs feel quite good on my dick-
That's good. Both of you service it.
That's good...
The balls too...
I can't hold it anymore. I'm cumming!
That's right...
Suck out the sperm that's left inside too.
How was it, Kis-sama?
Did we satisfy you with this?
What? "Satisfied", you ask?
What about you?
No... No! Stop it, please!
It's going all the way in...
Shut up!
You wanted my dick, didn't you?!
How'd he turn out like this?
Maybe we overdid it a little...
It hurts!
Seriously, you don't care who you fuck, do you?
Wanting to let this woman meet my mother...
There must have been something wrong with me...
Your kindness and smiles are all lies, right?!
T-That's wrong!
You... You were nice to someone like me...
And you'd look straight at me!
Kis... Sorry for interrupting your fun, but...
I've got your first job for you.
Sell it? That painting?
But that was for the art exhibition...
And I haven't really thought about selling it...
More like-
Anything that looks good can be sold.
To sell or not to sell. I'm leaving that up to you.
That'll be your first trial.
Ehh... I'll give it to him for building
such an ugly house...
Ehm... Was it really alright for us
to come along as well?
You want me to... Bring Nanaly and Renka with me?
Yeah. He wanted the painting's
model to be there too.
You're the party's main attraction.
I see...
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
No, no, I'm honored to have
been invited, thank you.
Oh, so you're Kis-kun, huh?
I've heard about you from your father.
I'm sorry, but... The painting
is a hobby of a sort...
I'll double my offer.
So young, yet you really know how
to bargain... As expected of his son...
I'll pay you triple then.
Oh! You're that painting's model...
My name is Nanaly.
I see... Nanaly, huh?
You're perfect as the highlight of my party.
Alright. However...
Publicly exhibiting the painting
wasn't my real intent, therefore...
I have one more condition.
Ah, I see...
Well, then, let's go and discuss
the conditions in more detail.
We're going to negotiate now.
You guys wait here for a little while.
Yes.
Yes...
Lowlife.
We're sorry to have kept you waiting so long.
Tonight's bunnies have arrived on stage!
Nanaly and Renka!
Ehm... Was there really a need
for Renka-san to come as well?
I like this kind of thing. It brings
in a lot of money as well.
But... Are you really ok with things like this?
Won't you regret it?
It's ok...
I hurt Kis-sama... And we didn't
match even from the beginning...
Doing this is the best for a woman like me.
Honestly, you really are a good girl.
It's too bad that idiot isn't
in the audience though...
That's... I don't want that.
Oooh... Amazing
Hohoho... Those Bunnies
are starting to feel it!
Look at how hard they're fucking that pole!
I can't take it anymore!
That fits that prostitute!
That's right. This is for the better.
After watching Nanaly's performance,
my dick became hard like this.
Hoho... It seems it's ok to fuck
the performers today...
Well, then, us too...
Inside your mouth, your tongue is... Burning hot!
The way you suck me down there, it's... Amazing...!
This bunny-chan kind of makes
me want to tease her...
I'm cumming!
It keeps on coming out... It won't stop!
Hey, swallow it all properly!
How does my sperm taste?
Yes...
It's very thick and soft.
Nanaly-chan, me too... Will you suck me too?
Lick it! Lick my sword too please!
It's amazing... All the noblemen's
dicks are this energetic...
I prefer the smaller one...
Noblemen-samas, please let me
have lots and lots of fun with you!
I thought you were mere dancers,
but who'd think you were like this...
Honestly.
The Baron's breathing is getting heavy.
It's because lately he's shut himself away...
There, there...
The dicks... They're delicious!
To think Bunny-chan would do us all this happily...
Quite the party, isn't it!
Renka-tan, I'm about to cum!
Let it out! Let lots of sperm
out into Renka's mouth!
Ahh, Renka!
Renka-tan, I'm cumming too!
Me too!
Like this... This is for the best...
I'm not fit for Kis-sama.
If I get stained like this... If it can help me forget...
Why are you here?
I'm leaving locking the house up to you.
Father!
Why did you marry my mother?
She was a good parent. And we
got along well. That was all.
If I dare say so myself, that was
a perverted woman...
Hmph.
Did a nobleman's dick feel good?
Next is my turn.
It feel like my dick's about to explode
Fucking this mature servant
girl from behind is the best!
No, no... The feeling of this little one's
young tender pussy, too!
A lot is coming out...
Me too!
No!
Here, we've collected our some of
our sperm in these cups for you!
Thank you very much.
Ushh... This is the worst...
Here, have seconds!
You're being a good girl...
Seriously, give me a break... Drinking a
ll this will destroy my stomach...
That's good...
Well, then...
I'm exploring her asshole!
Aaahh... She got twice as tight!
How is it, Bunny-chan? Are you happy
being gangbanged by noblemen?
Yes. I'm so happy.
A perverted Bunny-chan, aren't you?
I'm about to cum...
Me too... Me too... I'm cumming too!
Goodbye, Kis-sama... Please become happy...
Hahaha... Nanaly, tonight's show was a huge success...
Let's see... This time I'll take real good care of you...
Kis-kun!
I don't appreciate having others enter
my private space, even if it's you..
Geez... Young noblemen nowadays
don't know how to behave... Huh?
Why?
Let's go, Nanaly!
Y-Yes!
Reynold-san... I'm sorry, but I'll be taking Nanaly back!
Because she's the person who will
become my precious wife!
Don't fuck with me, kiddo!
I don't care about our deal anymore!
That brat... Punching a nobleman
like me in the face...
Security! Security!
Search the mansion and catch those rats!
A reward for whoever catches them!
Kis-sama...
What is it?
The painting...?
He only used that as an excuse...
I don't want to ignore my feelings
towards you, and towards my mother.
That's why it's ok.
When you catch the woman, bring her to me!
I'm gonna fuck her until she loses her mind
in front of the guy! I'll drive him crazy!
Renka?
Yahoo, you two!
Did you finally manage to stand on your own feet?
That's right, you need to run away too!
Oh, are you worrying about me?
Renka...
The ones who pissed him
off were you two, not me...
I'm still fine...
But...
Whatever, just go.
For a spoiled rich man's son like you to speak
up to me... You're 409 years too early!
Kis-sama...
How nice...
Even though she's stained,
she's able to start anew...
As for me, it might be a little too late...
For what I've done, and what I'm about to do...
Seibou-sama won't forgive me.
Hey...
It was fine for us to do this one too, right?
I-I really like this kind of small one...
Hey, you... Do you understand
what situation you're in?!
Dick... My dick has...!
My eyes!
Now then... Only that shitty fat bastard
left for the finishing touches!
For now, I guess...
You'll run away together
with me like this, right?
I'm the kind of human who'd
sell her own body for money.
Both my body and mind are sullied..
Would you really want such a-
Nanaly is Nanaly.
It's the path for you, who tried her best.
Kis-sama...
Let's refrain from calling me "-sama", shall we?
I want to do lots of... Lots more perverted
things together with Kis-san...
When I'm this close to Kis-san, I...
W- Wait a little...
Nanaly... If you wrap your tongue
around me like that...
I can't take it anymore... I'm cumming!
Nanaly!
At least you... Accepted it with your mouth...
You gave a lot of your seed
to me, deep in my throat.
Ah, w-wait a little.
W-What's the matter?
It's the first time for us to be together
in this kind of situation...
I feel faint... My body is thumping with joy!
Love me a lot... Love me, please! Make me your wife!
Your dick... It's going in...!
Inside of Nanaly is so hot and slippery,
it feels like it's sucking me in!
Ah!
I've always wanted to become
one with Kis-san like this!
Oh, shit... I'm cumming!
I'm sorry... I just suddenly felt too good...
For a while now, just looking at
Nanaly has turned me on...
Me too...
I'm completely devoted to Kis-san...
Please, make me forget about everything
that's happened up until now.
Then I'll really be yours, Kis-san.
I want to have you inside me always...
I know.
From now on, we'll always be together...
Nanaly is mine alone!
I'm so happy...
Nanaly... Don't say any more...
Let's always be connected!
Y-Yes!
Kis-san... Please make me all yours using your dick!
Amazing... This... Deep...
So good...
Say, Nanaly...
Our lives from now on...
I want all of you engraved into me.
Yes. From now on we'll always be together.
So good...
That's a nice smile you have on.