The Maid's Private Room Video
This... It's...!
This looks good too!
Oh, a new release!
This series too!
I-I'll take these.
Welcome.
Will you be taking them home?
Uh, n-no... Um...
If you're going to watch these here, please choose a course from this menu.
Course A lets you rent a room for 60-90 minutes. You can also receive lotion and toys.
Course B is the same as Course A, but with the addition of we maids, who can serve you drinks like milk and Calpis!
We have the special "Bipu" course available as well!
The "Bipu" Course is where we maids perform some interesting services for you!
It feels really good, Master!
Presented by SubDesu-H
Should I have watched these in the store?
You're Tanabe-kun, aren't you?
Eh? Oh! Shibuya-san!
Do you live in this apartment?
Y-Yeah, I do...
I didn't know.
What floor are you going to, Tanabe-kun?
Uh, the ninth.
Tanebe-kun, where did you go?
Uh, I went to a video store...
V-Video store? The one next door?
No, um...
How about you?
I was about to go off to work, but I forgot my cell phone...
Is that your work uniform?
Yes! It's the maid costume you like!
It's not like I particularly like...
Shibuya-san, are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
Did it break down? Or is it a blackout?
What should we do?
There's an emergency button for times like this!
Hello! Is anyone there?
Hello?
Nothing?
They're not responding...
How about you call for help with your cell phone?
Eh?
That phone, the one in your pocket.
I don't think I brought my phone since I wasn't going far...
But... What's this?
I-I'm sorry! I was mistaken!
But Tanebe-kun, you've gotten so hard...
Tanabe-kun, are you backed up?
N-No! It's nothing like that-!
It's like before...
You can cum inside, so please let it out inside me.
It feels like it's gonna burst-!
Please bear with it for a little longer...
Amazing-!
This feels great!
Shi-Shibuya...! L-Let me go!
Please feel me down there a bit longer!
Your cock is hot and so hard-!
I'm cumming!
This is wonderful!
I-I'm r-reaching my limit-!
I'm gonna let go, so please cum! Spray your semen inside me!
Shall we do something fun?
Your cock is so hard...
Hey, play with me down here, too.
O-Okay...
Lick me!
Play with me!
You're so wet, Shibuya-san...
Actually, I've been thinking of lewd things...
I remembered how much you came last time... I'll let you cum plenty this time as well!
I can see everything, Shibuya-san!
It's embarrassing if you spread it that much!
Amazing-! Your tongue is going inside me-!
It's like it's being thrust into me!
Shibuya-san, please do mine...
Amazing! Tanabe-kun's cock is getting bigger and his lewd juices are dribbling out!
If you do that, I'll-!
S-Sorry about letting it out inside of your mouth...
You're still hard.
Please do it to me next.
C'mon, hurry up and put it in!
It's hot-! It's entering me-!
W-What will we do if someone sees us?
D-Don't say such things!
We can't stop this now!
Shi-Shibuya-san-!
Do you work at a video store?
Eh? Why? I-It's not...
It's a maid cafe...
W-Why do you ask?
I actually... I have a thing for maids...!
Um-!
I see! You like maids!
I-I understand! Master!
Please give me lots of your semen, Master!
A-Amazing! I'm having sex with a maid!
M-Master! Y-You're getting bigger than before!
It's so tight-!
Master, you're being so rough and hard! It feels amazing!
Oh no, I'm gonna cum again!
P-Please wait-!
You mustn't cum yet, master!
I'll get on top.
Please lay down and make yourself comfortable, Master.
B-But-! I'm about to-!
I-I'm sorry.
S-Sorry! It's all over your face and clothes...
D-Did it feel good, Master?
~Stringendo~
Everyone's staring at me!
It's a bit embarrassing, but things like this aren't bad...
Everyone's looking at me...
It's like their gazes are violating my body!
They can see my erect nipples in this swimsuit!
Looks like they can't stop looking!
How about this?
Maybe I'll give them a bit of service...
How's this? You can see better like this, can't you?
It's digging into me!
How is it? Are you getting excited?
You're getting hard!
Kirishima-san!
Please don't go off on your own!
Let's hurry and set up the parasol.
Kirishima-san?
Jeez, it was just getting good...
Don't get in my way.
"Just getting good"?
We came so far. It would be a waste if we didn't enjoy it.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
It would be embarrassing if I met someone in this swimsuit at the local beach!
I don't think that's the problem...
Tsuchiya, rub lotion on my back.
The lotion, the sunscreen.
I'll have to reapply it constantly in this weather!
L-Lotion?
C'mon, hurry up!
O-Okay...
You can use it all, so make sure you don't miss anywhere.
Please rub it in with your palms, like you're massaging me.
Here I go.
How is it?
Yes, just like that...
Do the bottom bit too.
B-Bottom?
Oh? What's the problem? You're just applying lotion.
C'mon, hurry up!
It's digging into me-!
It feels so good!
S-Seriously?
It's showing!
Amazing!
Everyone is watching me again!
So lewd! Their gazes are piercing me!
Tsu-Tsuchiya-! That's-!
N-No! E-Everyone will see!
I'm... No...!
I-I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Hey Tsuchiya...
Eh?
Do you wanna take a walk with me to those rocks over there?
I want to go somewhere where we'll be alone...
Ki-Kirishima-san, won't people see us here?
Even though you say that, you've gotten so hard!
You mustn't-! I've been holding back!
Such a pitiful voice...
Fine then, I'll let you cum first.
Today's special, okay?
It's so hard! So lewd!
It's getting bigger!
Do you want me to suck it?
C'mon, pull it out from the side.
Ki-Kirishima-san...
Amazing, it's throbbing...
Ki-Kirishima-san-!
I-I'm g-gonna cum...!
Hold on!
Ki-Kirishima-san-!
I'm cumming-! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming-!
We're not done yet!
Hurry up and put it in!
Kirishima-san, were you craving this?
What? Don't be so haughty!
Anyone's would have been fine...
But you're so wet here, Kirishima-san.
N-No, I'm not!
That's from the s-sun oil!
You gotta move too!
You're only useful when it comes to these things!
T-This feels amazing-!
Someone might see us, it's-!
Tsuchiya, you're amazing! It's hitting deep inside me-!
So good-! It feels so good!
No... I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!