Ayaka-chan! Go on! Cum, cum-!
Darling, please stop it already!
Why are you doing this-?
Please keep clutching my breasts!
My clitoris is rubbing against you-!
Amazing, it's getting excited!
Mom... Mom...!
Oh my, you're just like a baby, Chisa-chan.
Take them off! What the hell are they-?!
A-Amazing-!
His hand...
It's entering me-!
I-I'm gonna cum again-!
Isn't it good? Isn't it good? Doesn't it feel good inside you?
SubDESU-H Presents
Taku-chan, Yurine wonders if you were surprised
when she said that she liked you?
I see! So you're childhood friends who've been living next door?
Geez, don't tease me like that!
You two are always together, aren't you?
Ayaka!
I'll tell him for you!
Eh?
It's for your own good! You have to be honest!
It'll be fine!
Wait-!
I'll be too embarrassed to go to school tomorrow!
But if he's okay with it, he'll come in through the window as usual...
Yurine, I'm so happy!
I love you too!
Oh my-!
If that happened, that would be wonderful...
Taku-chan!
Stop-!
Be quiet. Don't you dare make a sound.
Otherwise, I'll stab you with this!
N-No-! D-Don't-! No!
Stop-! No!!
I'll kill you if you make a racket!
Don't! Please stop! No!
What cute panties... And what nice thighs...
No!!
No-! Don't!
You're sensitive, aren't you?
T-That's-! No, not there!
P-Please!
P-Please let me go!
That's a nice expression...
I can see your dirty parts now...
No-!
No!
Your precious area is fully exposed!
That hurts-!
It hurts, it hurts-!
T-This is great! I can't stop moving!
Please stop!
It feels so good! It feels so good!
No!!
This feels amazing-!
Y-You came inside me...
That felt pretty good.
Don't grope me like that! Otherwise, I'll-!
N-No! I really can't bear it! I-I'm gonna-!
No, no!
Please stop this!
Forgive me, forgive me!
P-Please! Not there!
I-It's too much-!
You're moving too fast!
S-Stop it, please-!
Why am I being raped like this?!
No, no, no!
Isn't it starting to feel good?
It doesn't feel good! There's no way!
But your juices are spraying out like crazy!
Don't say such perverted things!
You've been backed up lately, haven't you?
Or do you do it with your husband every night?
N-No way! We wouldn't-!
N-No more!
No, don't move so much!
You're so good that I'm about to cum!
No! Not inside, not inside!
Okay, fine.
But you want to feel my cum inside of you, don't you?
Don't!
It's... it's coming out inside of me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming from something like this!
No!
He came so much inside of me...
I'm dirty now.
W-Why wouldn't it feel good when it's filling me up like this?
Oh? Did she break?
It doesn't matter.
It hurts! My stomach hurts!
I'm going to give birth!
P-Please help me!
An ambulance! Please call an ambulance!
I'm gonna give birth, I'm gonna give birth!!
That hurts! Damn it, let me go!
Could you show me what's in your bag?
Huh?
Isn't that an invasion of my privacy?
Hey wait-!
Just shut up and let me have it!
What's your name?
It's Hoshino.
Hoshino, what?
Hoshino Momoka!
That's a cute name...
Are you making fun of me, you bastard?!
Would you rather be taken to the police, have your parents notified,
TL note: Technically it's not illegal to carry things in your bag, it's only theft if you leave the store without paying for them.
and let your school know?
Or would you rather be raped and be forgiven for your crime?
Y-You bastard! Just rape me, then!
S-Stop it you god damn pervert-!
Stop it!
No-!
It's cold!
Didn't you want this?
N-No!
No... Don't put it in me!
Stop it! Don't put it in!
No!
Stop it! No!
No... No!
No!!
It's nice and cool inside both of your holes!
Damn you! Forgive me already!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum-!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
Please! I beg you, p-please stop!
Stop it-!
No!!
No...!
T-That feels strange!
Go away, go away!
That hurts! You're gonna tear it off-!
No!!
No...
T-That's-!
I love it that you're slightly stubborn, well-mannered, cute,
and caring towards others, Ayaka-chan!
Y-You're-!
My cock is entering Ayaka-chan-!
It's entering me-!
Ayaka-chan, we're finally...! A-Ayaka-chan, Ayaka-chan!
It's in-! It's inside you, Ayaka-chan!
No... No...
S-Stop it, it hurts, it hurts!
It hurts...
I love you, I love you! I love you, Ayaka-chan!
No! It hurts, it hurts!
It feels great inside of you, Ayaka-chan!
No! It doesn't feel good!
It hurts, it hurts! Please stop!
Please stop it, already!
I-I took Ayaka-chan's first time!
No, I didn't want this!
Please stop! Don't say anything more!
I'll make it so that you can feel me better...
See? This long thing was inside of you, Ayaka-chan!
Can you tell?
N-No...
I'll put it in now!
When I pull out like this,
I can see your cute pink folds around my cock.
It envelops me when I push it in!
N-No! It's not like that!
Hey, can you tell?
In and out, in and out...
We're having sex!
Y-You're squeezing me-!
You're squeezing me, Ayaka-chan-!
No, no more! W-Why is this happening to me?
It's because you've been a bad girl who hasn't been aware of peoples' feelings!
I-I've been caring, and kind to a lot of people, but this is-!
I know that you're a kind girl, Ayaka-chan. That's why I love you!
Who knew that having sex with someone you love is this great?
I'm-!
Not inside, anywhere but inside! Don't cum inside me!
Don't say that! This feels so good, so I gotta cum inside!
N-No! I-I'll get pregnant!
A baby with me and Ayaka-chan?
If we have one, then let's get married!
No! Please forgive me already!
I'm so happy that you're begging me so much!
I will, I will beg, so-!
Please! Don't cum inside me! Please, Misuhara-kun!
Ayaka-chan, you know who I am?
Then we must be meant for each other!
N-No!
I-I'm-!
I-I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
Ayaka-chan-!
No!!
Pull it out!
I'll get pregnant...
I took a picture of our Memorial Day where we became one!
N-No more...