Yes.
Then, next section... Shizumori-san, would you read this?
The world is a beautiful place, and its inhabitants love to...
...fight for it.
Yes, that's good.
Read the rest from there, Mizuno-kun.
Yes.
Did you see it?
Did you see it just now?
That's not...
Hmph...
I'm just being careless.
I'm glad there's no boys around.
For me, this isn't about being careless anymore.
Don't say that! Don't say stuff like that.
Let's hurry, Shizu.
We're going to eat lunch on the roof, right?
Why don't you head up first? I'm going to buy some bread at the shop.
W
Pet Life
~Miscreant~ Chapter
Jeeze, today's been horrible.
I hope nothing else bad happens.
Day after day... You're always so close to each other.
But, if you keep wearing the same white panties,
Mizuno might get tired of you, Shizumori.
Just ignore him. He's only teasing you.
Morning, Mizuno-kun.
Thanks for yesterday.
Yesterday?
She's talking about our part-time job.
It's really hard work.
Hey, Kazuya.
You haven't forgotten our promise, right?
Why's he doing something like that?
He's horrible to not feel any shame or guilt for doing such things.
But you know...
He's kind of popular.
It's not like you lost something.
Hey, you!
Oh, sorry.
Well, maybe your ass and breasts are just too big.
That's right, I've heard something like that.
There's a lot of girls confessing their feelings to him.
Is Ozaki-kun really that cool?
Mizuno-kun is way cooler, right?
Isn't that right, Shizumori-san?
Is possible that Class Prez...
...has a crush on Mizuno-kun?
Eh!?
Hey Shizu, you're going to be late for class.
Yeah, I know that!
I'll go back first, then.
Did someone leave this behind?
I'm really going to leave you behind, okay!?
That's because I need to brush my hair first.
Don't be mad.
Of course I'm mad! You can't say stuff like that to girls.
I'm sorry.
Nodoka just looked so cute that I couldn't resist teasing her.
Kazuya, what kinds of girls do you like?
Let's see...
Girls who have long hair.
Then, if I grow my hair longer, you'll like me?
Would you make me your wife?
No way, I'm going to be late.
Eh!? Where did I put them?
This can't be happening!
Is it okay if I just place these in anyone's locker?
Well, it can't be helped.
Now where did I put my bra and panties?
If Kazuya knew about this, I'm sure he'd tease me.
I need to find them quickly.
Eh!?
Ozaki-kun.
Anyways, isn't that...
What I'm looking for?
He smelled it, smelled it, smelled it!
I thought by smelling it, I'd know who they belonged to.
But it's impossible.
It's something someone left behind.
Let it out! There's more, isn't there!?
Let me have it back!
Why are you in this place to begin with?
That's because I was having lunch and looking for snacks afterwards.
T-The worst!
The rest would be in here.
Eh?
This couldn't be rest of—
D-Did you see it?
It's perfect.
Y-You're joking, right?
Erase it!
That's nice. I didn't know you were this perverted, Shizumori.
No, don't make fun of me.
What are you saying? You're practically begging for this!
W-What are you doing?
As for you...
Here's my thing. You can even touch it.
No!
I-Idiot! It's dirty—
Should I share that photo with the entire school?
But I'm sure that would become too of much a problem for you.
Shall I share it once school's over?
Y-You scum...
No way...
It's so big.
That's nice. Your face is getting red.
Have you taken interest in me yet?
That can't be...!
W-Would you stop doing this—
You're kind of cute, Shizumori. You know?
Don't joke with—
This can't be...
...happening.
N-No...
Don't move your tongue around inside.
It's my first time, after all.
No... No, that place is...
Stop it.
No... My head is going blank.
I'm losing my mind.
I can't let this happen!
I just... Kissed.
No!
You also felt it when we kissed earlier, right?
Shizumori, you're a pervert.
Mizuno-kun, why hasn't Shizumori-san come back yet?
Right, right. I had lunch alone today as well.
You've seen Mizuno's thing, right?
T-There's no way I could have seen it.
Heh. It's okay, be honest with me.
I haven't seen it.
Look closely at it, alright?
No way... What's this scent?
Then, shall we compare you with the photos?
I can see the difference from the earlier photos.
No, why's this happening to me?
You can't!
Shizumori's pussy is beautiful.
Have you let Mizuno look at it?
What'd he say?
There's no way I'd do that.
Then I should let him see the photo.
Please don't do that?
No way,
He's so indecent.
No... I don't like this pose!
He can see everything in this pose.
Shizumori's pussy is really beautiful.
I should let Mizuno see this.
He'd be excited to see.
No! I can't let Kazuya see me like this.
No, don't touch me like that!
Then, why don't we text him?
Since he might search for you and find us like this.
I'm not feeling too well right now. It looks like it's because of my anemia.
I'll skip afternoon class and rest in the infirmary.
I want Kazuya to inform sensei on this, Nadoka.
You can't do that.
Why are you doing it like this, Ozaki-kun?
I can't hold back when he puts this much pressure on them.
Have you also done this with those girls you teased?
Where do you touch yourself while alone?
I-I don't know!
Well, you should tell me.
Which place makes you feel the best?
I don't know. I really don't.
Okay, I'll have to find it myself, then.
The place you're most sensitive in.
I can't find anything this way... Is it this place?
O-Ozaki-kun, I'm still—
It hurts!
Seriously? Is it Shizumori's first time?
I-Isn't that obvious?
No...
No, please stop moving it like that.
This is such a special act, so you should enjoy it more.
Relax, relax.
Don't be so stiff.
Hmm... "It's unusual for you to get anemia."
"You should get some some sleep. I'll pick you up when class is over,"
he says.
But there's a lot of time before class is over.
We can enjoy ourselves a lot before he picks you up.
This is nice, Shizumori.
You're just my type.
I hate everything about you!
Even your voice...
...turns me on.
I said I hate—
I said... I hate you.
You should just go out with me, instead of Mizuno.
We're already having sex like this, right?
No... I'll be Kazuya's wife.
I promised him I would.
I'll be... His wife...
I'll be...
Kazuya's wife...
No!
If you say it like that...
You'll make me want you more.
No!
Just be my girlfriend, then.
No, it's too intense.
I'll rip apart.
Though you say you don't like it, I know you do, Shizumori.
Y-You're hurting me!
But, as he thrusted in and out, I could feel my body convulsing.
Come on, keep up with me.
It... It feels strange.
Is this sex?
I'm having sex right now...
What should I do? My mind's going blank.
Although I made up my mind that time...
I can't do something like this! My mind is going blank!
I'm cumming, Shizumori.
Eh?
What... What did you say?
You can't be serious!
I don't want it!
You can't cum inside!
With this, Shizumori is my wife, right?
No way, there's so much of it.
Oh, someone seems to have forgotten something.
Hey! When are you going to stop pouting?
It felt good, right? So don't worry about it.
There's no way I can ignore this.
Eh?
What should we do?
With this, we're going to become partners.
Y-You!
If you were wearing this, it wouldn't be so strange for you to be seen here.
Like you were changing, or something like that.
W-Wait a minute, this is too small.
They're from the senior class, right?
Anyways, I shouldn't be hiding here with you.
Well, I heard they also don't wear any underwear.
They're juniors, right? They can't be that careless.
It's bothersome to not use a bra.
By the way, aren't your breasts getting bigger?
Aren't your panties kind of crossing the line, too?
Well, we're having fun, after all.
But it would be bad if anyone found us out.
You look really good. I'm getting excited over you.
This is the worst possible time to say that!
Your nipples are also getting hard.
They're not—
But I didn't think they'd be so big.
Even if we compare these to the senior class, you're still number one.
I-I'm not doing this for you—
Shit, she might have noticed us.
Hey, stop this already!
With you in this kind of state, you couldn't possibly go to class.
No!
Since everyone's already left...
Don't decide something like this yourself!
How is it? It shouldn't hurt anymore.
That's not true... N-No!
Stop it. Someone's coming.
Wait a minute.
Shall I take these out?
What are you doing?
That's not important right now.
Since we're doing it like this, I thought pulling them out would be good.
I-Idiot!
Do something other than this...
That's strange.
Don't make me do this.
No way! I don't want it!
Did I drop it somewhere else?
Hey, hey... Could you take that out for me?
I'll do what I can.
Hm, that's adult underwear. That'll make any man horny.
That isn't important now, though.
But I don't blame the other men who'll fall for them.
Ah!
What a disgrace for someone to leave their panties here like this.
Eh!?
Wait, aren't those my panties?
Who do these belong to? Seem kind of plain to me.
See, you're going to lose with white panties.
I-It's getting bigger!
Our 6th period class is starting soon.
But, we haven't...
We'll look for her together, after school.
Wait a minute, Shizumori!
It's been fun. Let's do it again, okay?
What are you saying? You're the worst!
There's no way I could ever like this guy.