My name is Anna Hirose and I'm twenty-three years old.
If case you're wondering why I'm dressed like this,
it's because it gets my younger brother Yuichi excited.
When Yuichi was still a prep school student,
I saw him using my pungent and soiled panties to masturbate.
Discovering that my little brother used me to explore his sexual curiosity...
...Excited me.
After that, I went out of my way to let him "catch" me being naughty.
But as his older sister, I felt that I should give him even more satisfaction.
Thus...
How's that?
Does it feel good, Yu-chan?
Are you going to cum?
Go ahead, cum!
It's okay to cum!
After that first time, sucking his dick soon became a habit.
And then, Yuichi became a college student and got his own apartment.
He asked for more sexual favors, each one more unreasonable than the last. But even so, I capitulated because I loved my little brother.
But soon it became...
W
The Elder Sister's Free Oral Day
Geez, Yu-chan, that was the first and last time, understand?
I was so embarrassed the whole time;
there were so many geezers ogling me...
And you looked like an idiot the whole time, sporting a raging boner like that.
You really are a bothersome brother.
Ahhh! Your dick is so big and hard again, isn't it?
Hey hey hey! What do you want me to do for you today?
You'd like to start off with these first, right?  ~Jiggle Jiggle~
Ah, ah! Um, um! How does that feel?
Is your sister giving you a good titty fuck?
I've gotten better, haven't I?
Ungh, I'll make you feel even better!
You can hear the slippery sounds.
That's naughty, right? Right?
Wow! That's a lot of precum.
It looks like you might cum any moment.
Oh! But you can't blow your load yet, you've got to hold it in.
You should enjoy your sister's titties longer.
Oh! Was that too much?
Okay! I'll use my mouth now.
Hurry up, stand already; spank, spank!
Yu's dick juice - I love it!
Oh, AMAZING! Dick juice!
Little by little, more juice is coming out!
Can you not hold it in anymore?
Are you cumming? Are you really cumming?
It's fine, go ahead, cum!
Give me your cum!
Yu's sperm is like a sloppy load of tadpoles.
Give your sister lots of cum; I want to drink it!
Oh! You want to take another picture?
Okay, but you should take a cute picture of me.
"Sister and Friend". The menu is for "Drill Pizza"
Yes that's right, it's a seafood and camembert pizza.
Oh! Seriously?
Tasty... the tasty pizza is 'ERO' size.
No, not 'ERO', 'L' size.
I can't, I can't! Ah! Sorry, it's nothing.
It's just my throat acting up... Yes, yes, that's the correct order.
Geez, Yu, you're screwing around too much! I'm sure that they suspect we were doing naughty things.
Anyway, your friend will be here soon, right?
Hmph! You can't touch that part! I'll bite you!
You friend really came.
Good afternoon. Nice to meet you, Takeshi-kun.
I'm his sister, Anna. Pleased to meet you.
It's nice to meet one of Yu-chan's friends from the same school club as him.
Please get along with my brother, okay?
Um... So... You knew about today, huh?
I see that you're already in the mood...
That's right. Today, Yuichi's request was for me to suck Takeshi's dick.
Of course, I said no at first, but he just kept begging me; he really wants to see it happen.
Are you ready, Takeshi? I'll suck your dick for you.
Let's take off your underwear.
It'll just be this one time.
Promise me that you'll keep this a secret.
Uh... Your dick is stuck in your underwear.
Ah! Your dick is already dripping hot juice.
But you know, your dick is too big.
Hey, Takeshi, is this your first time with a girl?
Thought so.
Yu-chan? I'm going to suck your friend now; make sure to take a good look.
Wow, your dick is hot!
Let me take a look at your dick.
Oh, it's stinky!
What is that!? Oh my God! It smells so bad...
I can't do this; this dick is too dirty.
No, no! You have to do this; he's Yu's important friend!
Suck it up, Anna...
Takeshi, it's meal time.
Aw man, it smells, and it has a strange, bitter taste.
Bleh! I feel like throwing up!
Aren't girl's lips soft?
Don't feel ashamed if you're almost done.
How was that?
Did it feel good?
Am I not sucking you well? I'm sorry.
Hey! That was too rough!
Maybe he doesn't understand how it's done since it's his first time...
How's that?
This is much better.
I guess you use strange sex toys.
Your dick isn't very sensitive.
It's here, it's here, it's here! I can see it throbbing.
I see you're feeling good now!
How about this?
And this?
How about now? Are you cumming soon?
Oh-ho? Your hot juice is overflowing.
Now that you finally got the chance, aren't you embarrassed that all you get is a handjob?
Hold it in, aren't you a man?
You can't cum yet!
Wow! It's really throbbing now.
Are you close now?
Are you at your limit? You can't hold it anymore?
Are you cumming?
Are you seriously cumming already?
What are you doing? Don't waste this chance.
What do you want to do to me?
How do you like this?
Okay!
I'll hold it in place; you can move any way you like.
Please enjoy how my titties feel.
Are you cumming? Are you cumming? Are you cumming?
All right, I'll drink your cum.
I'll drink so much of your virgin cum. Give it to me!
Give Anna's lips your cum! Give it to me, give it to me...! Umph!
So much thick cum!
Yu-chan? You already finished!
Afterwards they did it to me again and had the pizza delivery guy watch.
The pizza guy seemed dumbfounded.
...Or maybe not. Once in a while, he might enjoy this.
Yu-chan, are you here?
"Sister and the Group
I'm coming in!
Oh hello; you're here today too.
Where's Yu?
Lately, Takeshi's been coming over a lot.
What's happening?
Afterwards, Yu told me to give Takeshi his first kiss.
But then Takeshi started acting like my boyfriend.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Yu's not here, so stop it!
Oh, fine; but just a little bit, okay?
You want more tongue? Fine.
Mr. Cherry Boy obviously has the wrong idea about us, although that can't be helped, all things considered, but...
...I still couldn't break it off with him, since he was such a worthless guy. I pitied him.
Sorry, I'm busy today. Is my friend already there?
Could you do me a favour?
Do you know Pink Salon?
I'm having a get-together with the club there.
His club mates... at Pink Salon?
Yuichi ended up not coming home all day.
I got to taste Takeshi’s cum five times today.
This is for your brother.
Hang in there, Anna!
Welcome back, masters.
Anna really loves to take care of her master's squid-smelling dicks.
I'm an ejaculation helper maid.
Masters, if there's anything that you want performed to pleasure you, please request it from me right away!
And now, without further ado, I'll do my best to service my masters!
Please reward me with lots of your cum!
Here you go! Anna's Maid Pink Salon is now open~
Hey, Yu, are you watching this?
Did you take cute pictures of me?
I'm doing my best for you, Yu.
Are you excited? Is your dick getting hard?
Look at me. Look at your sister being dirty.
Masters, this perverted maid... with your many dicks,
Please reward me with lots of your cum!
My many masters, there's only so much cum that I can take.
Sister...
Thank you...
Don't mention it. I was hungry.
Let's go eat outside.
Anna here,
Writing on her body: human toilet, the club was here, cum escape route
My boss is power-harrassing me,
And Takeshi and his friends switch their target from my top mouth to the "bottom mouth".
And Yu-chan's true feelings for me surface for the first time?
Who are you? You glasses-bitch!
In various ways, Onee-chan is in a pinch!
Or... am I?