W
I wonder if the night will provide a delicious prey for me?
Yesterday makes twelve victims!
I don’t feel safe sleeping in my own home!
Do something, will you?
You intend to let us die?
Or maybe there’s nothing you can do...
Now, now, we’ve summoned a strong ally to help.
Madworth, I hope this isn’t a useless one like last time!
Uh, well...
His lordship, Ryuuto Henge is entering the front gate!
Well, what splendid timing!
Men, be at ease.
His face may look sweet, but we have hired this man to exorcise demons.
Eh?
A Succubus?
She sucks the life out of everyone.
The men of our village are falling one after another.
We’re so fortunate you came by!
But I’m not an exorcist...
I’m merely here as a messenger for my commander.
In that case, I am your new commander.
And I order you to exorcise that demon.
I hear you graduated bottom of your class in the Royal Knight Academy.
You are a pitiful excuse for a knight.
All of your classmates have already enlisted and are doing well.
You, however, were promptly demoted to “messenger”.
Your life has already ended.
You should thank me for giving you an opportunity to die fighting a Succubus.
You wish to speak?
If I do defeat the Succubus, don’t I get a reward?
A reward? Do you actually think you can defeat her?
Why would you order me to if it was impossible?
You are a disgrace to the Royal Knight Academy!
You should be ashamed!
Get your hands off me.
I don’t wish to speak to the man who graduated last.
How pathetic!
Even if I miraculously become King someday, you’ll always be an errand boy.
I hope you’ll serve me well then.
Garlic and crosses don’t work.
I guess not.
Was that the man who just came from Oto?
Hi. You’re late.
Um... Who are you?
I’m Shamsiel Shahar.
It’s a bit long, so you can call me Shamsiel.
Are you a prostitute?
Maybe I am...
Your face says a lot will come out.
A lot of what?
Semen.
Are you a girl from Boan?
You’re really cute.
Really?
That's the first time a human has called me cute!
“Human”?
W-Wait, are you... a demon?
A Succubus, to be precise.
So those twelve dead villagers...
I didn’t WANT to kill them, really.
I was just sucking out their semen a LITTLE bit... then they died.
Y-You’re a monster!
If you’re unsheathing your “sword”... I’d prefer the other one.
W-What are you going to do to me?
Whatever it is that a Succubus does, silly.
Tit-ty-fuck-ing.
It feels very good.
And if you end up dead like the other twelve men,
then I’m really sorry!
Well, you’re so hard.
Let me go.
You want me to?
Hey, do you?
Do you? Do you?
I love titty fucking.
Because human men love to have their dicks massaged by huge tits.
S-Stop it.
You honestly think I’ll obey a human's order?
I think you’re almost there.
I’ll rub it hard.
This feels so good I might die.
Then die. Die!
Die between my tits!
Oh no... I’m c...
So much came out!
Delicious!
Ah?
Oh? You’re not dead!
I wonder if I can get much more out.
Stop it!
It’s really sensitive...
Yeah, I know that.
Come out, come out!
It’s cumming... again...
Wow! Even more than last time.
I want more.
P-Please, stop moving.
Nope, I’m gonna keep moving.
Whee!
Seriously! Lots is coming out.
I’ve never met a human like you before.
Maybe I’ll give you a special service.
Since you came a lot, I’ll suck on it.
Doing this with my tits and mouth is like Heaven for you, right?
It’s Hell...
I know you want it faster.
Like this.
It’s futile to hold back when you’re fucking a Succubus.
Come on!
You’re cumming already?
I’ll do anything you ask... so please, just stop!
...Anything?
Then I have a favor to ask!
W-What?
Cum all you can and die, ‘kay?
This time I’ll suck out all your cum and you’ll go to Heaven for sure.
This last suck will be my parting gift. Be sure to cum lots as you die.
Farewell.
My deepest apologies.
I know your hidden agenda was to have him set you free.
There are many other men waiting to take his place.
More importantly, is he coming tomorrow?
Yes! He is.
Then I can finally return home to Oto.
I’d never spend the rest of my days in Boan.
Lots came out.
That was so yummy!
I’m very impressed.
No way...
He’s still not dead?
My titty fucking usually sends them straight to Heaven.
But this guy... are you actually human?
D-Do I look like a sheep to you?
Now it’s decided.
You have an unusually high amount of semen.
So I’ll fuck you with my pussy as a special service.
You might die the instant I insert it...
But you must realize how lucky you are.
You’re about to melt inside of me, you know?
My demon pussy is the best!
You’re about to cum already, aren’t you?
Was this your first time?
This feels great...
If you cum a lot, maybe I’ll let you touch my tits as a reward.
You love tits, don’t you?
Come on, come on.
Will you touch them?
Will you be able to touch my tits?
No way... what’s happening?
My tits feel too good!
W-Why?
Why do my tits feel so wonderful?
It’s melting...
Her tits feel so good.
My hips... is moving on its own...
You touching my tits... feels too good!
No, stop moving your hips... I'm cumming...
I’m a demon, but a human’s penis is making me cum!
I’m cumming...
A demon can never cum from a human!
This feels great.
I’ll die!
Help me!
A demon... a demon can’t cum... can’t cum...
I’m cumming!
I’m cumming...
W-Wow!
So deep... so much is going in...
Her pussy... is sucking me in.
I want more...
There is no more.
I’ll die.
What’s your name?
Ryuuto...
I’ll remember that... for you...
Welcome... to Heaven.
How is the rebel army doing?
No change.
We're still insisting that all noblemen return from wherever they are and come back to the homeland.
We aren’t sure about Gladys.
After two years of rebellion, Oto still has not been attacked.
Merely having a lot of noblemen does not keep a kingdom strong.
It is because the Royal Knight Academy turns out so many great knights to protect us that our kingdom is strong.
We must suppress the rebels to protect our knights.
Where is Bobon?
He's in the nearby kingdom of Ringobalt.
His Majesty apparently granted him leave.
He who is worthy to become King is he who possesses a Kingly body.
Not a sheep’s body.
Yes, but...
Are you saying that the kingdom should go along with it?
As long as I live, I will not allow Bobon to succeed me.
Good morning.
Th-There are Succubi in Heaven too?!
You’re not dead.
You’re still in Boan.
Eh?
And I decided to stay here.
I like your dick, Ryuuto.
W-What?
If you’ll let me titty fuck you every day, I won’t attack humans anymore.
But if you won’t let me, then I will attack them.
...I don’t suppose me exorcising you is on the table?
But you did!
I came a lot!
That-is-why...
I’m gonna be your sex slave!
Eh?!
Is that really the Succubus who killed twelve men?
Yes... She promises she won’t do it again.
But I can’t trust the word of a demon.
What a foul-mouthed human.
I’ll eat you up!
So, I want my reward.
R-Reward? But you didn’t exorcise the demon!
My lord...
Oh, you have more brains that I give you credit for.
As a reward, I will let you be my wife’s bodyguard.
Eh?
She departs this afternoon.
Report to her immediately.
I trust you’ll take good care of her.
She has been celibate for a while, so we’ll need you to take care of THAT as well.
She has an unusual body composition - stroking makes her cum very easily.
Sir Ryuuto.
It has been a while since I have made love to a man of Oto.
What huge boobs...
I hear you exorcised the Succubus.
Well, not “exorcised”... more like “befriended”.
You must have surprised them, seeing as how you have an unremarkable past.
I didn't know he had a wife.
Please, call me Roxanne.
Men of Oto sure are good with their jokes.
You two, a little drink before the journey...
I served the aphrodisiac. All that remains now...
Is to observe the infidelity.
Then ask for divorce.
And then, the knights of Oto will be yours!
Are you okay, my lord?
I’m fine...
We’re leaving.
Secret... discovery!
Her... Her boobs feel great.
They’re bigger than Shamsiel’s.
I really, really want to touch them.
I’m sorry.
My chest hurts.
Are you okay?
Shall we rest a little?
Where were you?
Getting something good.
Something good?
That nobleman, he was planning something awful.
Look!
What... is this?
A reward for lots of cumming!
Sir Ryuuto?
You summoned me?
I want you to help me...
With what?
Will you touch my boobs?
They are so sore that I thought perhaps having them squeezed would ease the pain.
Y-Yes, but...
You are a knight. Do you intend to abandon a damsel in distress?
Please, harder.
L-Like this?
I’m sorry.
Sorry for making such naughty noises.
That’s okay.
Is the pain gone?
I'm fine. Please, continue.
This noble wife... she’s really turned on.
And just touching her boobs makes me hard.
Please, be sure to squeeze the tips, otherwise, the pain will remain.
T-Then...
Y-Yes! Milk is coming out!
S-Should I squeeze more?
Yes, squeeze more.
If you squeeze that hard... then my breasts... my breasts...
Sir Ryuuto, you are so skilled.
Are you okay now?
I'm fine.
But your manhood... it is so hard.
It must hurt.
Ah, don’t worry about that. It’s a strange illness...
If you are ill, then I must tend to it.
Wow!
Sir Ryuuto...
My lady...
My lady... you mustn’t... do this...
You are wounded... I must heal you.
I’m sorry.
Were you in pain?
It has been so long since I have tasted a man’s penis.
Your tongue...!
You must release your white seed soon, or else...
Sir Ryuuto, you like this, correct?
Your penis is throbbing and trembling.
My lady... you mustn’t... not so...
Please, let it out... into my mouth... let it out into my mouth.
My lady!
This noble lady... is drinking my semen...
It’s you!
I’ve been waiting for this moment.
I knew that you would...
My lord! My lord!
What is the meaning of this?
Were you setting me up?
This guy tried to trap you,  Ryuuto.
Why don’t’cha just confess?
H-How did you get that?
Gee, I wonder.
I wonder if he’ll fall for it.
Don’t worry.
Did you contact the soldiers?
Yes.
Then please hide yourself.
I am Lord Aboine.
If I start a rebellion, you will take my side, correct?
Yes.
The Bobon empire will rule the world - of that I am certain.
You think so too?
After all, Oto’s knights are far from popular.
If Boan joins the rebellion, Oto will surely panic.
Please, give me proof of your word.
You will profit.
Once I am King, I will make you my chief confidant.
Thank you very much.
By the way, Denka, have you heard of that idiot, Ryuuto Henge?
Yes, I have. He was in my class and scored the lowest.
What kind of face does he have?
The sort that only a mother could love.
Could it be...THIS kind of face?
I can’t move...!
This man, along with Lord Aboine, has set up a foul conspiracy!
This conspiracy will now be undone!
Send him to the dungeon!
Th-That’s unfair, Ryuuto!
Denka, the one who instigates conspiracy is the unfair one.
Take him away.
Do you know who the hell I am?!
Is this what you wanted?
Great!
You must be tired.
Please, get some rest.
Okay...
Goodnight.
M-My lady...
Please don’t leave me alone.
Make love to me.
Y-Yes, but...
Even now... do you wish to run away?
Suck me.
No... suck harder.
My lady, you really do like your breasts played with.
Well, it feels great.
Suck them more.
Sir Ryuuto, you’re drinking my milk.
Don’t suck too hard.
N-Not again... milk is coming out.
Milk is coming out...
N-Not so... both of them at the same time?!
Sucking both of them... yes!
Ah, suck more!
My breasts feel so good!
Your milk is delicious.
I’ll cum... from having both my breasts sucked...
I’ll cum!
Oh dear. I can’t hold back anymore.
Sir Ryuuto, please...
M-My lady!
Squeeze my boobs! I’m lactating... lactating...
Fucking while sucking my boobs...
My lady, you’re squeezing so tight.
But, Sir Ryuuto, you’re sucking both tits at once.
Tits are meant to be sucked simultaneously.
Suck my boobs harder... and your dick...
Sir Ryuuto, you’re amazing!
Please... my boobs... keep sucking my boobs...
Suck them... suck them!
I’m cumming!
Then cum... cum!
Cum inside!
I’ll cum inside then.
Yes, cum.
Sir Ryuuto, your dick feels good.
I’m cumming! Cumming! Cumming!
Cumming while my tits are sucked!
Cumming!
Amazing...
Sir Ryuuto, you’re...
Sir Ryuuto... you were wonderful.
You as well, my lady.
I loved your naughty voice.
Sir Ryuuto, please never forget me.
Are you certain?
Yes.
How preposterous!
That he would scheme against the crown.
Who captured my son?
His name is Ryuuto Henge.
He graduated bottom of his class from the Royal Knight Academy this year.
What?
The Knight Academy?
Call him here to Oto!
I wish to speak to him at once!
To think that a graduate of the Royal Knight Academy would be praiseworthy.
I only hope that he is complete as a knight.
That is all His Majesty orders of you.
I never thought I’d see you again.
I never thought you’d come to see me, Isis.
You may relax the rest of today.
Reward time!
His Majesty wishes to see you, Ryuuto.
Maybe he’s going to appoint you as his bodyguard?
I’d rather be a commander than a bodyguard.
I’ll come to Oto with you!
I can’t breathe.
Are you certain?
Yes.
The General himself told me to inform you of this.
Understood. Good work.
Yes, ma'am.
A bodyguard is in Boan?
That is rather strange.
kawaita kaze tokasu me
The eyes that melt the dried wind
kanashii oto ai sazu mo no hiza
Raise sad sounds on the loveless lap
nurumu hitomi sono ato otte
Chasing after the wet eyes,
sore wa itsumo totsuzen no koto
Everything always begins suddenly.
ototoi to kinou, kyou, asu ni tsuzuku kaze no ito
The thread of wind connects the day before yesterday, yesterday, today, and tomorrow.
sugu itaku tenohira kasane awase
Place your pained palms together
susunde ku kumo no obi
To see the flowing thread of clouds.
hitoiki de oenuku you ni
As if one breath can blow through it,
mou ni do to tomaranai so crazy
It can no longer be stopped. (so crazy)
sora ga umi ga kibou no sewa ni dasu yo
The sky and the sea will take care of hope.
hoshi no matataki to kodou o awaseru you ni
Just as the sparkling of the stars is synchronized with the heartbeat.
nagareteku hoshi no obi isshun te o nuketa nara
If you can release the thread of falling stars for just an instant,
kitto kaze tsukameru sa
Then you will surely be able to grab hold of the wind.