But let's do it again, okay?
My name is Miyazawa Akina.
I'm the captain of the softball club at college.
I've been doing very well lately,
and we finally won the tournament for the first time!
I also got a boyfriend, who happened to be my childhood friend,
I'm just so happy!
I won a two-day, one-night hot springs vacation at the shopping arcade, too!
Celebrating 120 years!
Chichino Hot Springs? I haven't really heard of it, but oh well!
I'm gonna go relax with my boyfriend there!
Alright, let's have sex with Akina at the hot springs!
SubDESU-H
Akina to Onsen
de H Shiyo!
Start!
I see, so this is Chichino hot springs.
I wasn't expecting much since it was a lottery prize,
but it's quite nice, isn't it?
This luck is because I'm a nice person, right?
Don't you think so too?
Very good! Let's go on in!
Now that we're settled in...
We came to the hot springs after all, so we should change into yukatas.
You're gonna get changed too, right?
Is this the one for females?
The size is...
Here, this is yours.
Also, even if we are lovers, you can't peep.
There!
Oh, if you're finished changing, could you close your eyes for a moment?
Tada!
I didn't know that people wore this kind of thing these days!
H-How do I look? Don't these clothes suit me?
Really? I'm so happy!
Now then, shall we go bathe in the hot springs?
Oh? It says "Table tennis area". We should try it out later!
Huh? Are you questioning my table tennis abilities?
How rude of you.
I'm great at all ball-based games... Hey, what are you looking at?!
Private open air baths
Perfect for families or couples
Please contact front desk if you wish to use
Private open air baths?
D-Don't tell me that you want to go in this one...?
We mustn't!
I can't do something so embarrassing without being drunk first!
Well, it's not like I'll do it even if I am drunk...
Jeez! Fine, then!
But you have to promise me that you won't stare!
Where? My breasts and...
Hey! Don't make me say it!
It's quite large, isn't it?
Stop staring at me
and get in like you promised!
S-Sorry to make you wait...
I-I told you not to stare at me...
I-I'm gonna go wash myself!
Huh? Hey!
Eh? You'll wash my back? I-It's okay, I can do it myself...
H-Hey...!
D-Don't!
I-If you do it that roughly, then I can't keep my voice down!
Someone might hear us!
Stop it!
Don't squeeze me like a cow!
S-Stop it!
Don't do that to my nipples!
Stop rubbing my nipples together!
H-Hey... don't think you can get away with everything...
It's still daytime, and if anyone hears us doing it here, then...
Jeez, don't get all depressed like that!
It's like I'm the one at fault...
It can't be helped. Just this once, okay?
Your thing is getting bigger...
Are you feeling aroused by my breasts?
If it feels good, then you don't need to hold yourself back...
If it's you, then I don't mind.
Y-You can cum as much as you want, okay?
Eh? You're going to do it yourself?
O-Okay...
I-I've never done something like this!
This is a bit...!
You're being too rough!
No, don't be so rough!
No, this feels good...
My breasts...
My breasts, my breasts are being violated!
N-No, so sudden-!
Jeez, we came here to bathe, but I'm all dirty now!
You silly.
Whoa! What a feast!
Now then, cheers to our first hot springs vacation!
Cheers!
This tastes great!
Can I get another beer?
Eh? I shouldn't drink too much?
I'll be fine! There's no way that I'd get drunk just from this!
Oh yeah, that's right. Table tennis...
We were gonna play table tennis...
What?! I can kick your ass at it even if I'm drunk!
C'mon, let's go!
Table tennis area
Let's play
ping-pong!
Now then, let's begin the table tennis match.
On that note, the loser will have to do whatever the victor says!
Okay, let's get started!
Get some!
You're quite good!
Y-You did quite well!
I-I know, a promise is a promise...
C'mon, just say it already.
Ehh?! T-That's-!
I-I couldn't!
I-It's too embarrassing! Even if I did promise I'd...
B-But...!
F-Fine, then! But only this once!
D-Doing this in a place like this... If someone sees us...
Fine, I'll put them in my mouth.
Does this really feel good?
Deeper? I can't...
Huh? Do it harder?
Hey, are you gonna cum soon?
Something is coming out...
This is...!
You mustn't!
Not so hard!
Paulownia room
Miyazawa-sama
Whoa, this room has a nice atmosphere...
It's like we're in a movie!
Are you getting excited, perhaps?
I knew it.
Hey!
Uh, ah... Hey, you, please calm down.
Hey, you! W-What are you going to do to me?
Please calm down...
Hey! What are you doing?!
Y-You mustn't!
N-No need to get all hasty, right?
Let's take it slow...
No-! H-Hey! I'm not wet!
Huh? I'm not wet!
I'm not! I can't possibly be...!
T-This isn't right!
There's no way that I'd be pleased by someone doing it to me so roughly!
I-I said that it doesn't...!
No! This is...!
I-It's so deep!
I-It feels so good! It feels amazing when we do it!
I love it, I'm loving it!
It feels so good...
I-It's going in so deep,
Your cock is g-going into me so deeply...!
I-It feels amazing!
No, it feels too good!
If you thrust up like that, I-I'll break!
We're doing it like animals...!
It's great! It feels amazing!
I'm getting so aroused!
I-It feels so good!
P-Please, please do it harder...
Please pound me harder!
Yes! That's it!
D-Do it harder! T-Thrust against my pussy until it breaks!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum from doing it this wildly!
I-I'm cumming!!
So hot!
Jeez, you silly...
Please be gentle next time...
Hey...
I want to do it nice and slow this time...
Can we? Let's have sex slower this time.
You're still so hard down here...
It's throbbing!
Hey, do you want to put it in?
Do you want to put your rock-hard cock inside me and mess up my insides?
But I won't let you. It's my turn.
Can you see it? Your cock is going in and out of me!
There are lewd sounds coming from where we're connected!
I'll make you feel even better...
No! You're not allowed to move!
I-I was-!
H-Hey, does it feel good?
Please say it does!
K-Keep thrusting inside me while we kiss!
Jeez, you really like my breasts...
Please do it gently...
I said that you can't-!
It was my turn to make you feel good!
N-No! Y-You idiot!
A-Are you taking the lead again?
I'm going to be under your control again!
Am I going to be played with again?
I-I'm gonna cum again!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum from your rod again!
Stop it! Don't push it in so deeply!
I-If you do, I'll break-!
I'm gonna break! I'm about to cum! I'm...!
It's hitting against my deepest spots!
I can't remember how many times I've cum!
No! I'm gonna die!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna...!
Huh? W-What are you...?
No! Not so quickly!
No! Stop it!
No, this is...!
Stop it, I'm out of breath...
I-I'll go insane!
I'll break apart!
It's overflowing!
Your hot fluid is overflowing!
It's being mixed up inside of me!
It's squishing inside me!
No... My insides are going to be filled again!
My mind is going blank...!
N-No! A-Are you going to cum again?
If you fill me up more, I'll...!
I'll get pregnant!
I might have a baby!
I'll become pregnant with your baby!
It's coming out! I-I'm cumming!
No, y-you still came so much...
You silly, you came too much... You...
Hey, are you still awake?
I wanted to hang out with you more... You're so mean!
Well, it did feel good, but...
Um, let's go to the hot springs again, okay?
L-Like, on our honeymoon...
Y-You idiot, I was kidding! Good night!