There's a secret event in our Tennis club.
When the male tennis club member reaches a new rank,
the three highest ranking guys enter into a weekend mini game.
The guys select a girl they like,
and receive a sexual service.
Of course,
the guys are all desperate for this.
And the selected girls too,
each have their own feelings about it.
So those three made it this week.
Well then, I wonder who they're going to select.
Hogura-senpai.
Alright, so it's Hogura with Asahina.
So Kawakita, who are you gonna decide on?
Eh? Umm...
I'm...
Damn.
I wasn't fast enough to decide on Kazuno.
What am I gonna do now?
If you have no preference,
are you going to let a girl select you?
Because there is one that has selected you.
Huh?
Se-Senpai!
A-Amazing.
It's... it's rubbing against me.
What's it rubbing against?
I won't know if you don't tell me properly.
That's...
That's embarrassing to say.
That won't do.
Say it properly.
A-Against my...
P-Pussy...
The net...
is rubbing against my pussy.
Your pussy is already this wet.
You're a lewd girl, Ayumi.
Y-Yes.
I'm sorry, Senpai.
Ayumi is a bad girl, so please,
punish me more.
Well then, how about here?
Th-That's my butt.
It's hot and twitching.
You've been wanting it here too.
Something like this...
My pussy and butt are being attacked at the same time.
Even though it's my first time getting it in the butt...
Anal...
Anal feels great!
Say it out loud when you're cumming, Ayumi.
Se-Senpai.
Ayumi is cumming. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming...!
Being seen by everyone made you this hard?
You're a real pervert, Asahina.
I love you, Haruka-sama.
What are you so confused about that's making you confess now?
That's pretty bold.
Don't make weird sounds.
Does my tit job feel that good?
Yes, Haruka-sama.
If I do this,
I can feel you getting harder with my tits.
Pervert.
I can feel it.
I'm a pervert.
Ah, it's twitching.
Seems like it's cumming already.
Haruka-sama!
Really...
Just how much semen did you save up?
Hey, no, wait...
I just came a second ago.
You're saying that, but you're already this hard again.
That's... but...
We're still not done yet.
I won't let you go until I'm satisfied.
Umm, Kawakita-kun.
Thanks for accepting my selection.
But, I wasn't expecting to be selected by you, Nakayama.
Unexpected, hmm?
Because you're different from the other girls,
you seemed serious and not interested in sexual things to me.
W-Well I also...
do have a normal interest in them, you know?
If it's with someone that I like, then I would want to go it.
Na-Nakayama.
Yes, it's okay.
But it's my first time,
so we can do whatever you like, Kawakita-kun.
Nakayama.
That's...
Beautiful.
I'm hearing Nakayama's lewd voice for the first time.
It's so sexy and cute.
Come on, come on.
Make your dick bigger.
I'm doing you a service here.
Haruka-sama.
Your dick is getting hotter and hotter.
Seems like you're gonna cum.
It's gonna cum.
Yes... I'm...
Amazing. The insides of my pussy...
It's hitting them...
So hard.
So-Sorry.
I can't hold it back any longer.
It's okay. Give me even more.
You managed to make me feel good,
and so I'm gonna make you feel good too.
Senpai.
If you do it this hard,
Ayumi's ass is going to become...
Still, you seem to like this Ayumi.
If I do this to your nipples...
B-But...
That’s the racket you're always playing with,
if I think about what you're doing to me with it,
it turns me on so much.
Hmm?
There's something amazing happening here too.
Yes.
Ayumi's pussy has become wet and wants a dick too.
I'm getting it in the ass and it feels good.
Just like this, just like this.
Ahh, Senpai.
I-I'm going crazy.
Kawakita-kun, how is it?
Does this, feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Nakayama, you're actually kinda bold.
The others from the club...
I want to show them that I'm having sex with you...
You know, there are quite a lot of other girls that also like you...
Hey, that's dangerous!
If you're doing that I'm not gonna be able to...
I wanna have sex with you too, Kawakita-kun.
It's coming in!
Are you okay?
It hurts a bit, but I'm fine.
It's like it just slipped around it.
It feels weird.
Can I move?
It's okay, move.
Let's feel good together.
Nakayama.
Amazing.
It's grinding in me.
It's wrapping around me, it feels great.
I'm...
My pussy... by Kawakita's dick...
Is getting it so much.
Your pussy... amazing.
It's too good... Nakayama's pussy feels unbelievable.
Pussy, pussy, don't say it that often.
It's embarrassing.
But she said it herself. That's too cute.
Amazing, I didn't expect Momoka to like it this rough.
No... I'm... just...
What's wrong? Did you feel embarrassed?
But... this...
But look, your nipples became like this.
It's true, lean feel that my nipples are hard and erect.
Being looked at like this turns me on.
Isn't it good that they're paying attention?
You wanted to show it to them all, right?
But... actually...
If you dot that to my boobs...
Please show me more of,
your embarrassed looks, Momoka.
Kawakita-kun called me... Momoka...
This can't be...
It's my first time, but it feels great.
I'm feeling weird...
Look, Kawakita-kun.
How lewd I am...
Look at me... look at me a lot.
I'm looking.
My boobs, they're bouncing around.
You're making them happy.
Everyone is looking at your pussy, Momoka,
and getting excited, I know it.
I'm getting excited too.
Being looked at like this.
I'm shivering. I can feel how...
y-your dick is hitting deep inside my pussy.
Kawakita's dick feels great.
Momoka.
Kawakita-kun.
I love you, I love you.
I love you.
I love your dick too.
I can't take it anymore...
I'm cumming.
Wait a second!
Why are you still so energetic?
Even though you came so many times.
I can still go on, Haruka-sama.
You're making me cum again.
Haruka-sama.
Me too...
It's okay.
I'm letting you cum inside.
Hurry! Fast!
Inside Ayumi...
There's a dick and a vibrator...
Moving around... rubbing around...
Senpai.
You're pussy is unbelievably tight, Ayumi.
I'm making it tighter... I'm making it even tighter.
Please give Ayumi's pussy your semen, Senpai.
Alright, I'm gonna make you cum together with me, Ayumi.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm...
Kawakita-kun, please.
Give me your semen inside.
But... that's...
It's fine. I'm fine with it.
Because I want to totally embrace you, Kawakita-kun.
Because I want you to fall in love with me...
Momoka.
Please, cum.
I'm cumming, cum with me Kawakita-kun.
Cum. Cum!
Cum...!
Haruka-sama.
If you do it so hard... I'm gonna...
I'm giving you a clean-up blow job,
and you plan on cumming again?
B-But...
Until I've cum,
you're not allowed to cum, Ayumi.
Please, Senpai.
Please, cum fast.
I'm about to cum.
Sucking dick next to each other...
My heart is beating faster and I'm feeling lewd.
Momoka.
Even though it's my first time...
I won't be the one that fails.
I'm definitely going to make Kawakita-kun cum.
Amazing.
It's hot.
Kawakita-kun.
Next time, it has to come from your side.