Chiba Kagetora, the scion of the president
of the japan premiere group.
He has an idiosyncrasy that the woman
who soaked up with his sperm will get hot
and be a slave of the sexual desire.
He played a lot of girls with his ability
and the financial power...
But his father got mad.
And he will be forcibly study in
the Prestige College, Royal Viccia Academy
located in the foreign country
of uperclass people will gather.
He hide his nature in the academy.
He show him self as clown.
He’s being scorn and despised
by the people around him but.
The destiny of encounter has born.
The princess from small country.
Ridim, the silver yuki hime.
Princess of Victorvarg.
Shasty, The Golden Rose Princess.
The daughter of big company.
Yukino, The black orchid princess.
Kagetora, his heart been taken by
the 3 girl student who’re the other
student honored them as princess.
And at the same time a dark desire
creeped out deep inside heart
His going to show his true nature
To obtain those girls
He let his devoted maid Meirin to help him.
And made his move by taking the advantage
of his ability and used this to make those
beautiful princesses fall into his hands
Eww, it’s the clown.
He’s still bringing his maid here, he’s like the upstarting countryman.
Don’t mind them.
Leave them alone.
Yes.
Hmm...
I don’t know who cum first but.
Silver yuri hime, how wierd.
Ridim-sama, are you ok?
No... its nothing
She can’t handle the effect of my sperm.
How long can you handle it?
Princss Ridim, the flower in the party.
Thank you Shasty.
Oh, its Shasty-sama
Next is the princess of this country
Golden rose princess, Shasty
It’s the golden rose princess.
Wonderful.
But it’s like its start ripening.
Maybe its already the time to harvest?
Ok, how about the other prey...
She’s not here.
Chiba-sama.
I’m a messenger of Yamato.
I have a letter to give to you.
From Black Orchid princess Yukino?
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
Gakuen 3
Karei Naru Etsujoku
Translated by SubDesu-H
No...
My body is reacting...
No, I must not do this in office!
But...
I’m on my limit.
Come in...
I’m coming in.
What a great honor to be called by you black orchid princess.
So what kind of business we’re going to talk?
You know that already!
The maiden clothing fits you Yukino-sama
That’s what I expect from president of Yamato.
The traditional dress looks good to you.
Even you confuse me with that kind of compliment.
Do you really wanted your dirty body to be purified? You even wear those clothes.
You wanted mine so badly since I take away your virginity right?
N-no.. its not.
I’m not feeling good so that’s why!
That’s why?
The one got soaked with my sperm will look for my hot dick.
You will get hot even the sperm squirted to the body.
But you can’t handle it if I release it inside.
That part is still tingles even now right?
No, its not!
Then? What’s the business for calling me here?
The medicine, give me another medicine that eases this ache.
This one you mean?
Yes, that is.
You really wanted this?
It tingles more after the effect of medicine ran out.
I can’t even sleep at night.
This one is diluted with my sperm.
It can ease the symptom for awhile.
But the more you shot this the more you’ll be my slave of my sperm.
You already used the entire one I gave?
This one is not the one I can give easily even you princess.
I have no money but for exchange let me do this.
Hey, what are you going to do princess?
For the cost of the medicine, let me do it with my mouth like before.
I smell the sperm.
Please give me the medicine.
It’s a big difference than before.
I can’t think this the one done by Yamato Nadeshiko.
If you wanted that much, then I’ll release it a lot.
Here!
Please give me the medicine.
What are you saying?
I can’t satisfy if you do the same thing.
No way.
What are you... ah
You must pay with the mouth on the bottom today.
How brave are you to call a man without wearing a panty.
No, its not.
For most time is...
Its all wet already.
How good of you that you bear it all this way.
Stop this already..
Don’t say stop this if you feel it so much.
I’m not feeling it!
How strong are you to be tough?
Its not clean there.
No...
Please don’t touch there.
What are you saying? You’re always feel it in this part.
Yukino is a pervert that likes to be touched in this part.
No-o-o.
This sensitive body, it’s not only because of my sperm.
Are you satisfied with this?
What are you saying? You’re only the one who cum.
Are you going to have sex with me?
Of course.
I only raped you few times but the pussy adopt it so easily.
The first time was just a tight hole.
Ouch, ouch!
Stop it!
No...
No-o-o...
This man’s sperm is going inside me.
What’s this? Its still releasing.
I’m going to break.
My purity is ruined by this man.
No... don’t thrust it like that.
I’m becoming a knothole by having sex with a man which is not my husband.
I...
I’ll release it inside again.
Are you going to release it inside mine again?
Don’t do it...
I’m going to break if you do that again.
I’ll release it directly to cervix and make you pregnant.
What’s this?
I’m going to break.
No-o-o!
Stop this!
My cervix will break.
Be pregnant!
My cervix is cumming.
The sperm is transported inside me.
I’m going to be pregnant!
The cervix is full of sperm.
There’s no time to rest.
Next, you’ll pay with this hole.
In ass hole!?
As I expect, you like in this part too.
Stop it, putting a dick into asshole is ruining the modesty of Yamato Nadeshiko.
So what if Yamato Nadeshiko.
You’re feeling it as you’re being thrust in the ass hole.
No its not.
My mind is all white as the dirty hole being thrust with that big dick.
My ass will become a ruined hole if we continue this.
I’m going to pass out with this immodest doing.
Let’s finish this!
No-o!
Here it goes!
A lot of sperm going to my stomach again!
Its harder than the constipation.
Plenty of my sperm soak in your front and back right?
Its coming out.
The sperm is coming out from my ass and pussy.
It’s ejaculating from the cervix.
The sperm is coming out.
It feel so good.
Meirin, please take care of the rest.
And share the semen ampli to Yukino.
Yes, sir.
How long can you resist with the sexual desire.
Stop it!
If you release it more, I’ll really be pregnant.
You’re the one who said put it in the front right?
It’s because I’ll be no longer my self if you do it again in the ass.
I can’t be no longer a Yamato Nadeshiko.
Then be quiet and got pregnant!
No-o-o!
I can’t make a baby yet
No-o!
Don’t thrust deeper.
I’m going to cum.
I’m going to be raped again!
He ejaculated again this much.
No-o-o-o, It feels so good and I’m going to break
You lost you’re consciousness.
Then I’ll take the main dish.
I’m here princess.