I don’t know what got into you.
But I didn't think you're the one who comes to me.
Anyway, you’re welcome here.
Is the date with Kou-kun not satisfying?
Bingo?
You don’t have to be embarrassed...
Just be honest and ask me...
“Master, please teach me a lesson”, like that.
Teach a lesson!? T-That's...
SubDesu-H Presents
Osana Najimi to Doukyuusei
childhood friend and a classmate
nd class
love = pleasure
Wear it.
You’re a whore from now.
What are you saying?
No...
No!
Raise your ass.
More.
Don’t let it go, suck it!
Good, suck it more.
Shun-kun, sorry for the disturbance, but can I come in?
Sure.
S-School principal!
My, my...
She's quite the slender and dirty whore, isn't she?
It’s a great honor to be praised by you, sir.
How about the training?
Check it for yourself, principal
You...
What are you saying?
I’m not a dog.
Oh, the whore just moaned a cute voice.
No-o-o...
Stop it! Stop it!
Instead of just moaning, can you put on a performance, cute doggy?
Show some performance to the school principal.
Shun-kun, don’t be rough...
...be gentle, be gentle.
Now then, try putting your hands here.
Good, doggy, good.
You did well.
Then the next is...
...the dick.
Wow...
Good, this is good.
She’s well trained, Shun-kun.
Oh, it's good that you like it, school principal.
Oh, it seems that it’s her time to go c.r., school principal.
Oh, ok.
Next, let's spread your legs and have you moan.
No! I can’t!
No...
You just need to follow what your master says.
Shun-kun, don’t be violent.
Be gentle, be gentle.
Crawl.
How beautiful...
...the pink skin is shining.
Ohh, I want to lick the syrup flowing from this hole!
Good, suck it deeper.
Cum quickly, you dirty whore.
Good, now raise one foot.
This is good.
How about this?
No..!
Here I come...
You dirty whore...
You're so good at squeezing me tight!
I’m cumming!
Long time no see.
How is she?
Let him see it.
Hmm, she’s good.
Wear it.
Good, good, spread your legs more.
Yes, you’re cute, good.
Oh, Shun-san, long time no see.
Oh, yes, it is.
Its just that...
Yes, so can I request that?
Really?
I see! Then how about tonight?
Good.
I’m Sakuragi Miu.
My hobbies are reading books and arranging flowers.
And... my special skill is archery.
And I want to go to amusement park next.
Oh.
Can you take me?
That’s...
I’ll think of it.
What happened to you?
In a place like this.
No...
Hey.
Someone might see us.
How is it?
Did you follow the orders?
Yes, Master.
Let me see it.
Y-Yes..
Wow.
It’s all wet.
I’m embarrassed.
You did well for following the orders, so I’ll give you a reward.
It's good.
Good!
I’m going to cum!
I can’t hold it any longer.
Miu-chan.
Manager’s dick is hot.
I’m going to release it!
I’m cumming!
Miu!
Kou.
There's been trouble! Shun got caught by cops!
Kenjou!?
Shun’s house?
I have something to show you.
This way.
What’s this?
Is this the room you wanted to show me?
I’m sorry Kou, but I’m already a dirty and messed up girl.
But I love you so much.
What do you want me to do then?
I want Kou...
...to do the same thing.
O... Ok.
Stop...
How is it Miu? Is it feels good?
Look, its all clear.
That part is completely naked.
I'll let you drink from the mouth at the bottom as well as the mouth at the top.
No-o...
Oh, you’re still fine.
No-o-o, stop it.
I can’t hold it!
Maybe..
You’re already at your limit.
No-o-o...
I’m going to pee!
Good, release it!
N-Next will be in the ass hole.
What a troublesome anus.
A girl with a dirty anus...
...must be punished.
Good, you've endured the punishment, so I’ll reward you
Oops...
Here’s the reward.
I drank so much of Miu’s pee that- I’m going to release mine too!
Wow, it's squeezing me, it feels good!
I don’t understand anymore, it's my first time...
...this is amazing, I’m going insane, Kou.
It's squeezing, it's tight...
I can’t hold it any longer!
Miu!