www.SubDESU-H.net
Science Room
U-Umm... Jun...
You know...
It's your birthday next Sunday, right?
Won't you come over to my house?
W
Unsweet
Stolen Fallen Women
Stolen, Fallen Women.
Female Teacher
Female Teacher,
Kurose Katsuko
Kurose Katsuko.
Jun, it's okay. Come.
S-Sensei, actually, it's my first time...
...so I'm not sure if I can do it properly.
Jun, it's alright. This is my first time, too.
So, Jun, let's do our best together.
Sensei...
Come, Jun...
Jun...
Sensei's body...
...feels really tender.
This is embarrassing.
S-Sensei... I-I want to get inside you.
Okay, Jun.
B-But Jun, can you please put this on?
I'm sorry...
But if we don’t use this,
I might get pregnant.
Come.
Sensei...
S-Sensei, I-I'm sorry! Are you okay?
I'm alright, Jun.
B-But...
I'm okay, please continue.
Sensei...
B-But it's also my first time, so please do it gently, okay?
Sensei!
J-Jun...
J-Jun!
Sensei...
Sensei!
Jun, does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good, sensei.
That's good.
How about you?
Yes.
At first... it felt... quite painful...
But if you feel good, then that's all that matters.
Sensei...
Sensei!
Jun...
It is okay, Jun.
You can move faster.
Sensei, I love you!
I love you too, Jun!
Jun...
Jun!
S-Sensei, I'm already...
Keep going!
Sensei...!
Jun...!
I'm happy... that I became one... with you...
Sensei, it was really your first time?
To have a relationship with my student...
I'm a failure as a teacher.
That's not true!
I'm the one who desperately confessed to you.
Yes, I was happy.
I also had a different feeling towards you compared to the other students.
That's why it was good that I was able to give my virginity to you.
Sensei...
Well then, let's celebrate your birthday properly now, shall we?
Happy birthday, Jun.
This feels somewhat unbelievable.
What is?
For Katsuko-sensei who's strict at school to act like this.
And you've been bashing students during class, too.
That's because the one getting bashed is at fault, you know.
And Kazuya always gets the most strikes.
Those frivolous types are the ones that I hate the most.
H-Hey, can we do it one more time?
We can't. It's going to be painful for me.
Then I'll just look at it.
I can’t do something that embarrassing.
Do it, please...?
Maybe just a bit...
Y-You said you were only going to look!
S-Stop it, Jun!
It's getting a bit wet, sensei.
Stop, stop that!
But your insides are...
Stop!
It's squeezing my fingers and I can't pull out.
Stop, Jun...
You can't...!
No!
N-No!
Jun...
I can't... I can't!
It's over already!
What?
Then how about tomorrow?
Can we do it tomorrow?
Okay. Okay already.
I love you, sensei.
Yes, I love you, too.
Monday
Science Room
What's that weird voice?
Hey, stop that...
But I can’t control it any longer.
Idiot, it's still lunch break!
It's Katsuko-sensei and Jun!
We can’t do it here.
If someone sees us...
You’re getting wet already.
Stop it, Jun.
Stop already.
Stop...
Stop it.
I can put it in right, sensei?
Stop fooling around!
I will stop then!
I'm sorry, Jun.
This is my first time in a relationship.
What should I do, Jun?
Katsuko-sensei...
Shinohara!
What were you doing?
S-Shut up!
Don’t call me by my name.
It’s disrespectful!
I had also wanted to grope this butt.
I'll be calling your parents tomorrow.
Prepare yourself.
Oh, really?
I found something interesting.
How will about the fate of this woman this time?
This English sentence is translated as:
What will be the fate of this woman this time?
Your face seems like you've just quarreled with your girlfriend, Jun.
It's nothing like that.
Jun seems to be angry.
Look at that, Jun.
Katsuko-sensei's breasts and butt really are the best!
We're in class, Kazuya.
I've decided now!
I'm going to confess to sensei.
You’re not going to succeed.
I'm not so sure about that.
Are you worried?
Not really.
Kurose-sensei!
I'm sorry for what I did earlier this noon!
Apology accepted, so hurry up and leave!
I hate carefree students like you.
Please, don't say that.
I want to consult with you about something serious.
That depends on what you're going to say.
Well, it seems that a certain student fell in love with you.
How stupid.
And a mobile phone was left in the science room...
Jun's cellphone...
I happened to peek at it and I suddenly knew...
The name of the student that holds feelings for you is...
...me, Shinohara Kazuya!
How was it? Were you shocked?
So, you really want me to tell you who it is?
The relationship's still not that deep, right?
And it seems that you had an argument in the science room.
We were seen...
I even told him that I was going to confess to you,
but he didn't say a thing.
No way... Jun...
You...!
Me, too. I also love you, sensei!
W-What?
Quit joking around!
This is a crime already!
Hey, hey, I was just thinking of your welfare.
Isn’t it also risky for a student and a teacher to be in a relationship?
Don't worry. This will also benefit you and Jun in the long run.
For Jun's benefit...
I'll properly open it up for you.
Then Jun will also be pleased.
Just think of me as you sex friend.
Is that okay, Kurose-sensei?
Well then, open wide!
It's different from Jun's.
I'm scared.
No, he's going to put it in?
It hurts...!
Sensei, your "mouth pussy" is great.
"Mouth pussy"?
I'll have you remember the taste of my cock.
What's this taste?
It's salty, and my mouth's getting slimy.
It's painful.
Kurose-sensei's mouth is a toy to enliven my cock, you know.
A toy? Don't joke around!
My breath...
Oh yeah, I also need to return the favor.
Kurose-sensei, you're getting wet.
So sucking my cock got you aroused.
Your clitoris is protruding.
You're quite lewd too, aren't you?
Here, let me give you your reward.
It's coming out!
So this is the taste of semen...
It's stinky, smelly, and it feels like it's going to melt.
No...!
Pull it out!
Right now!
Stop, Shinohara...!
S-Stop!
I don't want to.
Not until you moan from my cock.
Stop fooling around!
Huh? You're not a virgin?
But it's still quite tight.
How many times have you done it already, sensei?
I can't possibly tell you that.
I-It hurts...
It hurts!
So I'm the second one?
Then I'll just have to mold your pussy to my cock!
Oops, gotta ease your pain down a bit.
Shinohara, stop!
Stop it already!
S-Stop!
First shot!
Did you feel it?
It just hurt. G-Get off me now!
How cold of you.
I liked it though.
The only one that I like is Jun!
Then, let's have you like my cock first!
I can't continue with this anymore...
Please...
Stop this...!
I won’t be stopping until you say that you really like my cock.
I would never say that!
I might finish fast, but I can keep on doing this forever.
Katsuko-sensei's pussy feels really great!
Don't call me by my name!
I'm getting pushed around by this guy...
How pathetic of me.
It'd get all the way through if I push, right?
Wh-What's this? I feel tingly inside.
Oh, I found your weak spot!
No, it didn’t feel like this earlier.
Your pussy's gushing, and making erotic noises, sensei.
N-No... I'm not feeling good at all...
I don't feel good with this guy...
No...
My head's going blank...
I'm scared...
No!
I'm scared!
We're out of condoms already?
I'm... not...
You were really into it the last one, right?
I wonder if you'll completely open up by the twelfth time.
I'm not feeling good... with this...
Woah, your pussy is being honest, sensei!
Don’t tell anyone about what happened here.
I'm sorry, Jun.
In exchange, I'll return tomorrow.
The one that I love is Jun.
See ya later, Katsuko-sensei!
Jun...
Self-study
They said Katsuko-sensei won't be coming to school because she is sick?
Tuesday
Yes. It seems so.
Oh yeah, Jun. This is yours, right?
Eh, this is my...
You dropped it in the hallway.
Thanks, I'm relieved.
Be careful with that.
I'm sorry, Jun.
Why did this happen?
I'm going to be screwed by that boy again tonight.
We're out of condoms again.
Katsuko-sensei, I think you've got the feeling already,
but you're still not going to please Jun with that.
It's okay to just act it out.
Men will back off if you don’t show that you're a perverted woman.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Act?
Yep, you've got to put on an act.
Let's try it out then.
There are no condoms anymore though.
Th-That can't be good.
That's not what you’re supposed to say.
Now say the words...
...by yourself.
Please teach my novice pussy unprotected sex.
Please look at my inexperienced and wet pussy.
I want Kazuya to teach me raw sex using his cock.
I can’t wait any longer...
Is this your first time without using a condom?
It's my first time...
I want it!
What do you want?
I-I want that.
What exactly do you want?
I'm saying... I want that.
Do it as I had taught you.
No!
No...
I-I want that...
Do you want this cock?
I want it... Your raw cock.
No...
This can't be.
What am I saying?
It feels really good without a condom, sensei.
It feels good...
No...!
It feels good.
It feels good...!
My cock's getting in and out completely.
Are you happy?
I'm happy...!
N-No...
A raw cock...
Raw cock.
Raw cock...!
I feel it...
It feels hot.
Is my body yielding to this?
Your womb and my cock are kissing directly!
Does this raw kiss feel good?
Raw kiss.
Raw cock.
Raw kiss!
Raw cock!
Raw kiss...!
There, you can say it properly, sensei.
I don’t want this anymore.
No...!
N-No...!
You are really a cock-loving, and slutty teacher.
I'm a slutty teacher!
Aren’t you embarrassed thrusting it in by yourself?
Sorry, but I just can’t stop.
I can't stop!
I can't stop...!
That's right. You have to express it clearly in words.
It won't stop...
My hips won't stop!
No!
It feels so good.
I can’t stop!
Then why don't you try saying those lines?
No...!
Come on now.
My...
Your?
My pussy...
Your pussy...
...loves my...?
My pussy loves your cock!
That's why...?
That's why even if I am inexperienced,
please make love to my pussy even more!
That's it! Well done!
I'll be releasing my seed inside you.
Is that okay, sensei?
You have to act, remember?
No, I don’t want you to release it inside me!
Making babies is just for married couples!
Then let's get married!
Don’t joke around!
Here's another raw kiss!
Wrap your legs around me tightly, so my semen can get inside better, sensei!
The one that I love is...
It feels like my womb is going to suffer for this.
I get it already.
Then let's just pretend.
Come on.
Pretend?
Please release your youthful seed into my womb!
Am I going to bear this guy's child?
You're a slutty teacher!
For you to feel aroused while saying that...
I'm a slutty...
S-Slutty...
No!
I don't feel good with this!
I don't feel good with this...
Jun...
You want to be fertilized with my seed, right?
I'm scared...
I don’t feel good...
It's okay to release it inside, right?
You can’t!
My body just gets aroused on its own.
Katsuko, you want to be filled with my seed, right?
Jun...!
I'm sorry...
I'm going to plant my seed deep inside your womb!
I got... his seed...
I love you, Katsuko-sensei.
I'm not lying about this.
I also already liked you ever since I came to this school.
So I don't have any plans of telling this to Jun.
I'll be teaching you more things for you two to get better.
If I get pregnant...
Then you can just marry me.
Oops, it seems like I want to do it again.
Here.
One more time, okay?
Okay.
Call Alert    Jun
Wednesday
Missed calls
Unread messages
I didn't go to school again today.
Jun seems to be calling me over and over, but...
I can’t really answer the calls.
How will I ever face Jun?
I don't know...
He'll come again tonight to do it with me until dawn.
The one that I love is only Jun.
I'm sorry, Jun.
Save me...
Thursday
Katsuko-sensei's been absent for three days already.
It's just a cold, but...
Mail
Message
She doesn’t answer my calls,
and doesn’t reply to my messages.
Is she still angry about that?
Maybe I should visit her.
I have to properly apologize to her.
And I am also worried about her condition.
It feels good...!
More...!
I want more...
I can't think straight anymore.
I don’t want to think of anything anymore!
N-No way...!
If my mind goes blank with this,
I won't have to worry about things anymore.
No, not again...
I'm going to cum again!
I'm sorry, Jun.
I love... you...
If we do this every day,
you won’t have to think of anything anymore.
Geez, standing 5 hours in the shower just to cool your head...
Are you an idiot?
Shut up.
It’s all because of you.
Here, fix your pajama. You’re going to get a cold with that.
I'll be going home then.
Hurry up and leave, you idiot.
This hole really has become mine now. Hasn't it, Katsuko-sensei?
S-Stop that, idiot.
Bye now.
Y-Yes.
Jun...
www.SubDESU-H.net