Ryuu-kun, wait a min-
It's going in, Ryuu-kun's penis.
Ryuu-kun's huge penis is all the way inside my pussy...
It's tight inside you...
Your huge penis is far too big for me.
It's way too big...
No!
It's getting bigger!
I'm your sister,
but I'm letting my little brother's penis cum inside me...
My breasts, too.
My pussy feels good...
I'm gonna go crazy!
You're so perverted, feeling this way from your little brother's dick.
No!
It's not... Like that... I'm not perverted!
I'll make this perverted body take all the cum from my huge dick!
I'm not a pervert!
No... No... My pussy feels...
Ryuu-kun came a lot inside me.
Ryuu-kun filled my stomach with his sperm!
Oppai Heart
~Her Beastly Sexual Excitement~
Hey Miya, get up quickly! You're gonna be late!
Ryuu-kun, wait for me!
You're useless, sis, didn't I tell you not to be late this time?
Hmph... Come on.
Eh?
Ryu... Ryuu-kun?
Ryuu-kun's holding my hand...
Alright!
We're gonna have to hurry!
Sure!
Hey, that's enough Miya, let go of my hand now.
I'm getting tired and my feet have gone numb.
I won't be able to walk if you're not holding me like this.
I see that the two of you haven't changed a bit, still holding hands like a couple this early in the morning.
Wh-Who are you calling a couple?!
There's no one else here like that besides the two of you, right?
Hey, Miya!
Couple...
You're getting happy...
Though she's also on the student council after all.
When I see Miya-senpai, I don't want to make her help me at all.
I know that you only want to play with her, right?
I keep messing up!
Don't keep yelling about something like that, it will just take longer if you don't get on with it now.
I want to finish this assignment quickly before it gets late...
It's not getting done at all.
Hey, if you have time to complain about it, why don't you give me the next paper?
Hmph, you're so cold.
Even though your onee-chan is all depressed.
Why don't we get this done quickly, I'm gonna help you too.
You always help me, so this time I'll do it by myself.
That's what you're meant to do anyway, isn't it?
You're so mean, Ryuu-kun.
Ah, that's right!
Hey, hey... I don't want you to help me.
Hug me.
Eh?
If you're hugging me then I'm sure that my work's gonna get done faster.
You really are...
Can't I?
Ryuu-kun!
I'm just being too kind to my useless sister.
You just have a sister complex, don't you?
Wh-What you're saying?! You have a brother complex too!
Hey, did your breasts get bigger?
Maybe they're getting bigger after all...
My body gets hot when you're hugging me like this.
Are you getting like that again? You're getting horny a lot recently.
It's only because of Rieko-sensei's virus.
We should make a child quickly, right?
Ryuu-kun, my body's getting hot.
I want your dick.
As I thought, you dressed in preparation for this.
This is Rieko-sensei's.
She said it would make you happy.
What a troublesome teacher, did she's actually enjoy being like this?
Ryuu-kun's penis is thrusting between my breasts.
Your penis is moving in and out...
It feels so good like this...
If I get pregnant, the virus should go away, right?
Just cum inside me, so I can get pregnant quickly.
That's easy for you to say...
There's something sour coming out...
That's because your breasts feel so good.
You're making your sister's breasts feel good too!
Miya, it's gonna come out!
Ryuu-kun's sperm~
It's okay, give it to me!
Cover me with that sticky stuff from your huge dick!
It's getting big... Ryuu-kun's penis is getting big...
Miya-
I never thought that I'd like your cum.
Ryuu-kun, I want more of it.
Please make me dirtier with your huge penis.
Of course I will.
Ryuu-kun's penis is deep inside me!
Your penis is reaching my womb!
Good...
My pussy is spreading.
Ryuu-kun's penis gets big when we have sex like this!
Is that so? Though I don't feel any different.
That's not true, It's a huge penis after all...
Huge...
Huge!
It's reacting to Miya's words.
No way, it's getting too big for me!
It's stretching... My pussy is stretching from it!
Your penis seems like it'll jump out... It's like 3D!
You... Stupid... Sister!
My pussy is drenched from all your thrusting!
It feels so good, Miya.
You're going so deep inside me!
More of this...
I'm gonna cum!
Your huge penis is too intense inside me, it's making me so wet!
Miya, it feels so good inside you!
Ryuu-kun, it's ok to do it harder. It feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Me too... Almost there... Let's do it together.
Ryuu... Ryuu-kun~!
Together... Let's cum together...
There's a lot of it...
You're cumming so much, Ryuu-kun.
It's over.
Good work then, shall we go home?
Sure.
Miya, why don't you take a bath?
Hm... A bath...? Sure, I'll have one right now.
Eh? You're... Already done?
Yeah... I already washed earlier.
Do you want to go to sleep earlier?
I'm getting tired from having sex with Ryuu-kun.
Don't... Don't say something like that...
Geez...
Good night.
Good night, Ryuu-kun.
I don't think she needs me in her bed today.
Wait for me!
Hurry up!
Don't keep saying 'nya-nya' and just hurry up!
Huh... I'm just about safe for today.
Hmph... I should make that useless sister wake up earlier.
Though she's kind of a useless sister, I can't let her out of my sight.
W-Wait a minute... It's in the middle of classes, you know?!
What would happen if a student council member were to skip class?
What's wrong with you, Ryuu-ya? Is it possible that you're going to poop?
You idiot, girls shouldn't say things like that.
You could at least say take a pee, right?
Little poop.
Huh?
Hey, over there!
This isn't good.
Sensei, I'm sorry.
My stomach started hurting.
It's poop after all.
Miya?
Eh?
Eh-
Ryuu-kun...
Miya!
It hurts...
Geez... Would you look where you're going?
Ryuu-kun!
Why are we in here?
I'm the one who should be asking that.
Are you hurt anywhere?
It's nothing.
Your... Your breasts are getting bigger, did the symptoms start again?
Ryuu-kun's too excited down here.
We couldn't have sex in a place like this, you know?
There's no way that a student council member would skip class and have sex like this, right?
You don't have to hold back when it's getting big like this.
You can leave it to your sister.
You idiot, it's way too dangerous in here.
I want Ryuu-kun's penis already... I want you to make me feel good.
Just hold back a bit, you stupid sister.
Geez... You never learn, after you got teased by Matsuri.
Hold back-
Ryuu-kun's penis is great!
My pussy is drenched because of Ryuu-kun's penis.
No... It's intense... I'm going crazy because of your huge penis.
My pussy is crying out for it.
I can feel that your penis feels good too.
Ryuu-kun...
Eh... Ryuu-kun... What is it?
Don't tease me like this, I want you to move like you were before.
That's true, it's for yourself after all.
I'll do everything for you, I want you to thrust that penis inside of me.
I want to see how you pee.
Eh?
Pee...
Wh-What... Ryuu-kun is perverted!
It's ok if you don't want to show me.
You're way too mean to me... But you're not gonna have sex with me if I don't do it, right?
If I don't show you that, then you won't thrust your penis inside me, right?
You'll really do anything when you're this horny.
So you're okay with anyone?
Eh, I got it. I'll do it for you.
I'll do everything you said, since I'm your onee-chan after all.
S-Sure.
It's embarrassing for me...
Ryuu-kun!
No!
It's... Gonna come out-
It's coming out... With your hand!
It's out... The pee is coming out...
Though Ryuu-kun's watching me...
It's not going to stop at all!
It's too sudden-
It's great!
My drenched pussy's getting all stirred up by your huge penis!
You're cumming inside... Deep inside me.
Cumming!
I'm gonna cum from this huge penis.
It's getting big again... The huge penis is gonna fill me up again!
I'm almost there, Miya. So let's cum together...
Together with Ryuu-kun.
Cumming... Cum... Cumming!
Cumming!
Hmph, Ryuu-kun is such a pervert.
I'm sorry about that... But it's okay since I'm the only one who gets to see it, right?
Even so, it's still far too embarrassing for me!
I can't be a bride after letting you see that kind of thing.
Hmph, you say something like that, but you're gonna get excited when you look at the other men, right?
There's no way I could do that... I've only looked at you all this time!
H-Hey... I was joking...
Uh... That's true, right?
That's right, actually someone called me.
See you, Ryuu-kun.
Ah... Hey!
Ah... It's bad!
Eh, Miya?!
Where she's going?
Akino's little brother!
What...? Rieko-sensei?!
Where's your sister?
Miya is... Someone called her just now.
Just now?
She said that she'd meet me when class started.
What's going on with Miya anyway?
Hm? She didn't tell you about it?
Or should I say that she's unable to talk to you.
The virus infecting your sister has got far worse than I thought it would.
Her condition right now is really unstable.
Her symptoms are getting worse every day.
Today, she's gonna talk about it with me.
Damn, what the hell am I doing?! I let Miya suffer like this alone.
She's in a condition where she couldn't even stop her sexual feelings towards men,
even if they're not you.
That's why I called her when during class, so she wouldn't meet with the other boys.
Damn, so I got in her way of meeting with Sensei before?!
Miya, where are you?!
What should I do?
I'm too much afraid to pass the class and I ended up running away from school.
Are you okay?
Do you feel sick or something like that?
Eh?
Ah... No... I'm fine.
Be careful!
Miya!
It smells good...
Did you already wake up?
Eh?
I'm getting tired holding you like this, why don't we take a break in here.
Huh?
Eh... Is this the place where we're gonna have sex?
I'm gonna have sex with this old man?
I'm...
Here you go.
Ah, Ryuu-kun!
Hello!
How's it going in there?
Sensei... She hasn't come back home yet.
It would be good if we knew where she was going...
Damn it, where are you Miya?!
Why?
What I was thinking back there?
He's not following me anymore...
Ryuu-kun!
This... This place...
So you're okay with anyone, right?
With anyone? This feeling only happens because of Ryuu-kun.
But I feel that excitement, even though I'm not with Ryuu-kun.
Within me...
If it's like this, I don't want to see anyone ever again!
I just want to disappear like this!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm fine... Just leave me alone...
That's why-
Miya, get a hold of yourself!
It's me!
No... No...
Ryuu-kun?
Ryuu-kun...
Ryuu-kun... Ryuu-kun!
I was afraid.
My body was acting strangely... Even though I wasn't with you...
I don't want to be like this... I don't want to feel this way!
Miya.
It's ok now.
I'm here for you.
I'm gonna protect you forever from now on.
Ryuu-kun...
I'm so sorry, Ryuu-kun.
It's okay, I know that you can't control yourself with this condition.
I never thought that you'd know about this place.
Of course I know about this place.
Eh?
I know that this place is your second most important place after our home, after all.
I feel that way about it as well.
You told me that this was the place where you'd hide when we were just kids, right?
The little Ryuu-kun said that.
You remembered my most precious memories...
Ryuu-kun, thanks for picking me up back there.
It's my duty to keep you safe after all.
Yes, I'm the one who's always getting help from you.
From now, I'll make sure to protect you all the time.
Ryuu... Ryuu-kun...
You look like you're about to confess your love to me, right?
It doesn't just look like it, I do confess it.
Eh-
Ryuu-kun.
Ryuu-kun...
Ryuu-kun,
I want to hear you say it once again.
After you show me your perverted appearance.
I'll... I'll show it to you.
We're always having sex like this-
I want more, just for me.
Only for you...
I'll do this for you.
Should I say it to you?
I really...
Really like you!
Ryuu-kun.
I can't...
I can't hold it anymore!
It feels so much better than before!
Yeah, me too.
Together... Together with you!
I'm cum... Cumming!
Eh? Pregnant?
Yeah, we're finally past the first stage.
Hmph... It feels strange to think about it.
Though you don't realize it, you're gonna have a restless mind when you're pregnant.
I'm sure that you're having a hard time with that nasty virus inside your body.
I know that you'll be able to suppress it.
Sure, I'll be fine from now on.
That's because I'll have Ryuu-kun there to protect me.
Miya, you idiot-
Eh?
Is it possible that-
Heh...
Hm...
I'm gonna be protected by Ryuu-kun all the time...