C'mon! Show me your breasts too!
Hurry up and take it off!
It's okay to cum inside her pussy and ass without protection!
Her mouth is also godly! There's no need to hold back, either!
All this for 10,000 yen!
No wonder she gets a lot of customers!
Hey, hey! How long are you going to take? It's my turn!
You just went!
I-I can't hold back!
I-I'm gonna cum!
H-Her tongue-! It's-!
Me too!
Hey! Shake your hips more!
I'm cumming-!
She’s really drinking it up...
I'll have a shot from behind...
But before that, it's our turn.
Take good care of us, you hear?
Y-Yes...
What a beautiful moon... However... It's too bright for me...
It feels like its pure light will burn my body and soul.
No, I would like for it to burn me up.
Since today is the last...
But, I have a more suitable ending...
If I take one step forward, everything will end...
It's not like I regret it...
But... I don't think I can bear it...
Today is graduation...
It's a good time to finish things up...
Goodbye.
It's not possible.
There's no way that Onii-chan killed himself.
He wanted to be a teacher so badly!
But, within a year, he...
I can't believe he would jump from the top floor of the school...
I’ll get to the bottom of this.
I definitely will.
Alright!
SubDESU-H
I am Misawa Raika, who will be joining you today.
I like sports, and my favorite food is egg on rice...
Umm, nice to meet you all.
Looks like I'm not that welcome here.
Oh, so you're my roommate.
I'm Hiiragi Nozomi. Just call me whatever you want.
Oh, sure thing Hiiragi.
Oh, and one thing.
If you want to make friends in this school,
you're better off not getting too close to me.
Eh? What do you mean?
You'll soon find out.
Looks like I've cleared the meeting stage.
I think I can keep it up.
Now, how should I find out about Onii-chan?
I guess I have to ask around gradually.
Right then! I'm gonna do my best!
Oh, hello Amagiri-sensei!
Oh, er, was it...?
Right, I'm Misawa Raika.
Eh? Ra-Raika?
U-Uh, it's nothing, its just a similar name to someone I know...
Oh Haruna-sensei, what good timing.
Oh, how are you, Maiko-sensei?
I was going to ask if you're free for lunch.
Oh? Who is this?
This is Misawa Raika-kun, the transfer student.
This is the school nurse, Mamiya Maiko-sensei.
Nice to meet you!
Eh? Wh-What?
What is she-?!
You've got nice, sharp eyes.
I've taken a liking to you. Why don't you join us?
C'mon, you two!
Oh? Hiiragi!
Oh, is he your friend?
Yes, he's my roommate.
I see, then you're coming along as well.
Eh? What's this? Hey! Misawa?
Infirmary
Don't hold back and eat up!
Yes! Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
By lunch, does she mean these?
This has strawberry jam in it!
Mine has green tea and red bean paste!
This milk chocolate pudding one is good too!
Oh, this is caramel!
What's with this sweetness?
The tea tastes great too!
It really calms you down!
Did you make these cream puffs, Maiko-sensei?
That's right!
Amazing!
They're very tasty!
Thanks!
Maybe I should make sweet rice balls next time?
Mamiya-sensei!
Oh, Jounochi-sensei.
Are you ill?
No no, I just wanted to see you.
Well actually, I saw that transfer student from my class with you,
so I was worried that you were teasing him.
No need for worry.
I see, that's good. See you later, then.
He's got a fresh look and seems nice,
but for some reason, I can't bring myself to like him.
Oh! Haruna-sensei!
Oh, hello Misawa-kun!
Maiko-sensei's cream puffs were delicious, weren't they?
Y-Yes!
Haruka-sensei, why are you standing there?
Oh? Who're you?
Oh, this is Misawa Raika-kun. He transferred here this term.
I'm the student council president, Horiguchi Kenichi.
Nice to meet you!
In this school which enforces self-motivation,
it is my job as the student council president to be a substantial leader.
So make sure you follow my orders when necessary, okay?
If you listen to me, something good might happen... Right, Sensei?
Y-Yes...
Hurry, the others will be waiting.
What a nasty guy!
SIGN: Resource room
I might be able to find something about Onii-chan here!
It's locked, huh-?
Normal students aren't allowed in there.
Oh, Hiiragi...
The library is on the 4th floor.
Student council meeting room
Now then, that concludes our meeting.
We shall move on to our regular schedule.
Are you ready, Haruna-sensei?
See? The upperclassmen are waiting for you!
Now then,
how about you start off by stripping today, Sensei?
Eh?
Didn't you hear me? I told you to strip.
U-Understood...
Now, since you're wearing such cute underwear,
please start the lesson with them on.
That's no good, Sensei...
You must say "Thanks for the meal" before you put it in your mouth...
C'mon, what's wrong?
Th-Thanks for the meal...
That's good, Sensei.
How is it? Does my cock taste good?
It does!
C'mon, Sensei! Take it further!
Do it till those big breasts of yours squeeze against me!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum...
More, more! Lick it more!
You have to drink it all, understand?
Aren't you going to thank me for the meal?
Th-Thanks for the meal...
Now then, how about we get to free time?
Everyone's eagerly waiting.
Go on, give Sensei a good time.
N-No-!
I'm going first-!
I'll take the butt!
Put it in your mouth, Sensei!
This feels too good! Sensei's pussy feels incredible!
Her butt is nice too! It's squeezing me-!
I can't hold it back!
I-I'm cumming-!
Me too-!
Now it's my turn!
C'mon! Get up, Sensei!
Hey Misawa, are you still in the bath?
When I'm with her or Maiko-sensei, I get out of shape...
Well, as long as I accomplish my objective, then all of that doesn't matter.
So, when it's like this...
One week in, and not even a clue.
Oh, him? We weren't very close...
...And that is how it's explained.
Haruna-sensei said something similar...
Maiko-sensei and Hiiragi just arrived this year, so they don't know anything...
The other students seem to be avoiding the topic.
Maybe the student council president will know!
Better not.
Ouch-!
What are you doing here?
Uh, I'm sorry, Tanemo-sensei!
Actually, I...
What the hell do you want?!
Why are you so worked up about him?! Eh?!
I-I can't breathe...!
He doesn't exist anymore!
Listen here. Don't speak of his name again! Got it?!
Wh-What's with him...?
No...!
Sensei, that tennis apparel suits you too well!
We can't study when you've got such an erotic body, can we?
There! Fondle her breasts!
They're so large!
It would be such a relief if I could die right now...
But... I can't die! I mustn't die!
You're the best, Sensei...
I... I have something I must protect...
That's why I-!
Since I made a promise...
I wonder what that was all about?
What about Misaki Yasuji?!
He doesn't exist anymore!
Listen here, don't speak of his name again! Got it?!
Something is wrong...
Even if it's not about Onii-chan's death, he must know something about him...
He sure is taking a long bath...
How can I find out? What should I do?
I don't think I can get it out of Tanemo-sensei...
Also, I think he touched my breasts when I ran into him...
It'll be fine, right?
H-Huh-?
T-This might be bad...
Hey Misawa, are you okay?
I'm coming in.
Mi-Misawa...?
What should I do?!
Hiiragi found out!
Misawa!
Are you awake?
Maiko-sensei...
Hey, why did you come to this school?
Eh? I-I...
This is a school for boys.
Y-Yes, it is...
D-Did she find out?
You mustn't make fun of the school nurse...
Um, Sensei, I...
It's not manly of you to eavesdrop!
You had a little sister, didn't you Sensei?
You promised you wouldn't touch her!
That's if you keep your promise.
I'll let you go if you can work out the answer before I cum...
No-!
A love letter? As if!
Monday, the day after tomorrow,
come to the specified classroom after school
and I'll tell you about Misaki Yasuji.
If you tell anyone else, the deal is off.
If you don't show up, I'll tell everyone about your true identity...
Is this it?
Come in.
I’m glad you came. I was beginning to think that you wouldn't show up...
Shut the door and come over here.
What's with this guy?
Why is he wearing a mask?
Why do you want to know about Misaki Yasuji?
I don't need to tell you that.
So then, what do you want to know?
The reason for his death.
What would you say if I said I knew?
Then I'll get it out of you no matter what!
I see, I'll tell you.
But I can't do it for free.
Eh?
I'll take your body.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I bet you think that you've cleverly been passing it off, but I can tell.
You've sure got some nerve to come into a boys' school
even though you're a girl.
You've got proof?
I praise you for your nerve,
but I think you should learn that things don't go quite to plan in reality.
Don't mess with me!
Take her down!
I'll give a prize to the first one who gets her!
Shut up!
L-Let me go!
Then let's see your true identity.
D-Damn you!
It's a girl!
He really was a girl!
Oh my, aren't those cute panties?
S-Stop-!
Stop-! Don't look!
You've got quite a nice body, don't you?
It would be a pity to let you keep acting as a guy.
Now then, let's get started.
Eh?
Wh-What...?
No!!
Oh? What a cute response.
I see. I'm honored that I get to be your first!
S-Stop it! Lemme go!
What a beautiful pussy this virgin has!
I'll make you into a woman now!
No! No!!
Hey, don't struggle so much! It'll start to feel good!
Hey, you! Make sure you get a good look!
It's rare to see a girl lose her virginity!
No, no-!!
Hey, it's going in!
Here I come!
Virgins sure are tight!
This one's quite good. How does it feel to lose your virginity?
Not saying anything?
Right, here I go!
That's a good expression. It's turning me on!
Go on! Scream more! C'mon, c'mon!
What's this?
You're crying because you're so happy that you got to graduate from your virginity?
Or are you crying because it feels so good?
I can't get enough of you squeezing me like this!
I'm gonna cum-!
No! No!!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming! I-I'm gonna cum inside!
Stop-!
Not inside! No!!
No? You really don't want it?
Make sure you're watching, guys. I'm gonna cum inside her on her first time!
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
No!!
Oh, we're not done yet.
Eh?
No-!
N-No!
I can find out about Onii-chan from this...
That was pretty good, but we're just getting started.
Eh?!
D-Don't tell me...?
That's right, you're going to please every single person here.
No way!
Okay, the two that caught her first, come forth.
Wh-What are you going to do?
Going one at a time will take too long.
That's why we're going to use everywhere that we can.
Ehh?!
Now, please change clothes...
That suits you, Raika-chan!
I think it'll be more erotic here!
C'mon! Reveal the bottom bit yourself!
More! Do it more!
I-It's so tight!
Her butt feels great!
I-It feels like my cock's gonna melt!
Her mouth hasn't learned, yet...
I-I can't hold it in! I'm gonna cum!!
M-Me too, me too! I’m cumming!
It my turn now. I'll cum plenty inside of you.
I'll shove mine into her butt!
I'll take her mouth!
Stop it...!
E-Ehh?!
No, no-!
It hurts-! It hurts!
I-I'm cumming-!
Thanks for today, it sure was fun.
Y-Your...
What did you say?
Your...
Your promise... Your promise!
Promise? Oh, it was regarding Misaki Yasuji wasn't it?
Fine then, I'll tell you.
Misaki Yasuji didn't commit suicide.
W-Wait-!