Sensei.
It's ok..
Please feel good..
Sensei’s so big..
Sensei’s dick is so hard.
Sensei.
SubDesu-H presents:
JK to inkou kyoushi 4
Original Animation Video
Doku mo Seika - Namaiki Moderu no Seikuhakusho-
Sensei.
Nice to meet you.
A transfer student? At this time of the year?
It’s sudden.
We had some issues that’s why, I’ll leave it all to you.
O-ok..
This All-girls school is so beautiful.
I’m glad that I transferred here.
Is that so?
Why did you transfer at a time like this, the Vice Principal is also acting strange.
The school I went to before was full of vandals but this place is so nice.
Sensei also.
Sensei, please give me a tour around.
Please.
Please teach us anything.
Nice to meet you.
They are models?
I see that’s why they are so restless.
Thank you so much.
By the way Sensei, do you know who our attendant is?
Huh? Attendant?
Were you not told by Vice Principal?
What should I do? I’m going to work now.
I’ll go ask him.
Ok then, I’ll to go to the photo shoot.
Later Sensei.
Let's go Satsuki.
What do they mean, attendant?
Good..!
Smile!
Good...
You’re shining!
You’re like a goddess!
You’re the best!
So, beautiful.
Ugh, I’m tired.
Their skills are so poor.
I give up.
Are you ok, Satsuki?
Yes, I’m fine.
Sensei? Why are you here?
The Vice Principal told me to take care of you girls.
So, I came here.
I see...
The Vice Principal said he would assign an attendant immediately.
Oh yes, he said I’ll would take care of you as an attendant.
Huh? What!? I don’t hear about that.
Satsui, have you heard anything?
Nope...
Wait, is this a joke?
Vice Principal?
You know the agreement right?
Yes.
It doesn’t match.
I thought of a young and handsome one..
Huh?
How about the young and handsome..
Huh? That’s your problem right?
I can’t agree with that.
Huh? Are you planning to set me up?
Did you think that we’d be deceived that easily?
Hey, Tagai?
Shut up! Keep quiet, we’re talking about serious matters here.
You fatass.
Wakao, what happened to Takai?
I can’t withdraw right now.
Ok then, I’ll ask others for some accommodations.
What the hell?
I told him to keep his promise many times.
That stupid bald, don’t mess with me.
Hey!
He’s looking down too much on me.
I can’t bear going along with this fat ass.
Hey, Tagai, uhm..
Shut up! Can’t you keep quiet?
You’re too clingy you know.
This sucks.
I’m tired.
I’ll go home and rest.
Lets go!
Hey, Tagai, are you not going back to school?
I’m not in the mood.
Go back alone.
But..
You’re persistent.
What? Do you really want to go with me that much?
Huh?
I see, maybe you got horny when you saw me in a swim suit.
You’re disgusting.
So you’re watching me with lewd eyes.
I could have guessed something like that though.
You bitch!
It's annoying that I’m being watched by those dirty eyes from now on.
Satsuki, try pulling him.
You.. huh? Pull?
With that reaction, are you still a virgin?
Hey wait! What are you talking about?
Besides, I’m not a virgin.
Why are you getting serious?
You’re annoying.
You..
You’re really disgusting.
Your face is like you’re proving it.
You’re not like me though.
Be thankful that she will pull it out.
And it's good timing for Satsuki.
Ok..
So I’ll be going home then, take care of the rest.
Wakao, does Takai hold some weakness of yours?
Uhm, no it's not like that.
Sensei.
Hey, wait Wakao.
If I don’t do something, Shizuka will scold me.
Ok?
All right, I understand.
It’s awkward here so why don’t we go back to school?
Ok?
Yes.
After all she hasn’t changed her mind, and are you always doing something like this?
No, we’re not.
This is my first time.
Then, you’ll be looking until the end right?
No, if that time comes, Shizuka will protect me.
If something happens to me, she said she will not do it.
Even she makes you do something like this?
She said I must experience something like this.
Takai said she’ll protect you huh,
If you oppose, you’ll be kicked out right?
Yes.
Oh, It's so hot.
You’re going to cum right?
Sensei’s is great.
Is that so.
But the great part starts here.
No.. Sensei what are you doing?
..Please stop!
If you keep going, I’ll tell Shizuka.
Sure.
Takai’s work will only be affected by this.
That’s none of my business.
I don’t have any attachment to being a teacher anyway.
No... no...
Sensei, stop it please!
We can’t stop now you know.
No way..
This is also an experience.
Ouch...
No...
It hurts!
Ouch...
No..!
It hurts Sensei!
You’ll get used to this in awhile.
No..!
No... Sensei... you can’t...
I don’t want this..
I won’t tell Shizuka so..
I'm grateful for that, I’ll release a lot inside.
No, you can’t release it inside.
I’ll get pregnant.
No.. no...
Please, Sensei...
No-o-o!
It's twitching inside.
Your cruel Sensei.
If you tell anyone, Takai will also be in trouble.
I'll be fine either way.
Ok.. your right
Something like this will happen if I’m with a man.
Yes..
So if Takai has a sexual desire then you’re going to pull it from now on right?
I understand.
Sorry, I have some business with Sensei, so I need to go.
Be thankful that I’m friendly to you.
Who are you to call me by my first name?
You’re really like that.
What’s "you"?
Call me Shizuka-sama.
You’re too impudent being an attendant.
Before that, I’m a teacher.
Hey, where’s Satsuki?
Satsuki is with her friends?
What? That Satsuki..
What?
Are you being Satsuki's lover just being pulled by her?
Congratulations...
That’s what amateur virgins are.
Huh.. you’re always complaining.
You said "you" again!
How many times do I need to say it that you’ll understand?
So you lack something on the inside and out.
I’m full of stress.
Because of fatasses like you!
You!!! Do you know that I’m the victim here?
Because of you I...
I said Shizuka-sama.
Being on your knees is fitting for trash like you.
You’re impudent to kick a teacher.
I thought you understood by kneeling down.
If you say "you" again..!
You...
I can’t calm down even though you’re kneeling down.
I’m going to the toilet.
Why I’m being toyed with by that bitch?
What is she thinking going to the toilet at the end?
Huh? She’s not here?
Where did that bitch go?
In a place like this...
No.. I can’t stop..
What are you doing?
What are you saying? I’m here to accompany you by order of the Vice Principal.
I see, well then let's go.
What!? Let me go!
If want to go, why did you come here?
What are you saying? I’m going home.
So let me go.
No, what are you doing?
What are you pretending?
What’s this?
Stop it!
If you continue this, I’ll kick you out.
I don’t care about that.
I can quit being a teacher anytime.
But I’ll quit it after playing with a girl like you.
Hey..!
Did you feel good by rubbing it on the edge of the chair?
Who are you to let a person wait while feeling good alone?
You don’t care about the place eh?
If you want to be messed up, then...
I’ll let you cum here.
Hey are you kidding?
Hey stop!
I don’t want to.
Really, I’m serious.
Why should I have sex with you?
I’m serious too.
No-o-o, it’s really coming inside.
I said no.
This is my first time.
Hey!
Why should a fat ass like you be my first?
It's too sad.
You really have a foul mouth, and a bad attitude.
You’re really the worst.
Calling a person a fat ass or disgusting.
I’m sorry about that.
I’m sorry for calling you fatass.
You’re not that fat, it's just you’re chubby.
I’ll take back what I said.
It’s just you’re slow.
I’m really sorry.
It’s a mistake that I’m cute, right?
I’ll do it in moderation from now on.
Even I say that maybe I’m exposed.
That’s why.
What do you mean by "that’s why"?
What kind of education where you taught?
You must be punished.
It’s coming.
Didn’t I apologize?
Didn’t I take it back?
Hey, I’m apologizing, so you must forgive me.
You can understand that right?
You’re really annoying even when you’re apologizing.
Why?
It's coming inside me.
It hurts.
Please stop!
It really hurts.
Please!
I’m sorry.
Please forgive me!
No..
It’s really coming inside.
You’re really a pervert.
What’s this?
Why am I doing this?
I said stop.
Really..
Please stop it already.
You pervert.
Your letting your voice out much more than before.
What are you misunderstanding?
I’m not feeling it with a fatass like you.
I won’t feel it with those poor hip moves.
How can you compare mine if you only know my moves?
It's sad that the semen of that poor guy will enter to you right?
Hey..
Are you kidding?
I can’t accept that.
Hey, stop it!
Hey.. no!
No...
Stop, stop-p-p...
You should stop this.
You’re kidding right? You released it inside me.
No way..
You... messing with me..
You’re really not honest.
Even if your feeling it this much.
Once more.
No..
What’s this?
You’re going to continue? Are you still backed up?
Sto-o-o-p..
Hey!
I think you can’t handle it anymore.
Shut up!
Don’t mess with me.
You’re still active, let me ejaculate once more.
No.. it's already full.
I don’t want it.
Don’t hold back.
No..
No..!
You’re releasing a lot inside me..
Your pose can still be sold eh Model-san?
Don’t mess with me!
You really are a damn dirty guy.
You eat stinky foods before coming here.
Then?
Why were you rubbing the edge of the table?
Shut up!
It’s none of your business.
I’m just having fun.
I understand.
To remove my stress.
When I’m upset, all the stress will gone if I do it...
All the girls of the same age as me are doing this.
It’s not a weird thing right?
I see...
Don’t worry because I’m going to remove that stress from now on.
What?!
What are you saying?
Is there some mushroom growing in your brain?
You must go to prison and eat some stinky foods.
If you report me, I’ll bring this issue to the publisher.
Starting from you attitude, your masturbation, all the things are going to be reported.
Then go ahead.
Huh!?
Then I’ll be selling myself, there’s no minus in my cuteness.
What? Did you think that you can scare me with that?
You’re too simple.
Trash is really trash.
You must reflect on yourself inside prison.
I see..
So let's puts aside feeling good.
Huh? Feeling good?
Pf-f-f. I won't feel good with you.
But your body is honest.
You came on your first time.
That means we are a match.
What?
Doesn't it feel better than doing it alone?
It removed more stress right?
You can feel better from now on.
It's not possible to feel good when you’re forced to have sex.
I can even remove the stress by getting a boyfriend.
Oh...
Do you really think that you can have sex with your boyfriend just to remove your stress?
I think he wouldn't like that.
I can be a tool to remove your stress.
Hmm..
Then it's better to masturbate by myself.
You just need to arrange your things.
That fat ass..
It still hurts.
What should I do?
This pain doesn’t disappear even if I let him eat stinky foods.
Damn!
What is he saying, a tool for removing stress?
I gain more stress with that.
No.. who is he?
Are you kidding?
Why is he here?
This ain’t a joke!
He’s insane, he’s insane.
No.. stop..
Please stop..
You’re cute Shizuka-chan.
You’re shaking cuz you finally met me.
Please stop!
We’re lovers so you don’t have to be scared.
No!
Please!
What’s this stinky smell?
Hey, you..
..you..
..you..!
Are you really Shizuka-chan?
This smell is a smell of a whore.
You whore, you’re not Shizuka-chan.
Hey?
Pervert!
What do you mean?
Takai, are you alright?
Sensei.
Y-Y-You trash! Fatass, where have you been?
At the time when I’m in danger?
I’m sorry.
You’re my attendant right?
Why are you not with me?
It's just..
You thought that it's ok for you if I’ve been raped?
You’re really a trash.
Fool!
Fatass!
Pervert!
You must rescue me before someone attacks me.
No.. there..
My stress won’t be removed with that.
It’s coming.
Fatass’ dick is coming inside.
What’s this?
It hurts but..
No!
We're really a match.
You feel this.
No, it's not..
No!
This..
Stop!
No, stop!
No!
This..
You are no use besides this.
This dick is only used to calm me down.
Be thankful that I’ll forgive you for this.
Good.
Thrust deeper.
More!
Wow!
I’m going insane.
Good.
Deeper.
More!
I’m cumming.
I’m cumming!..
Wow!
Good.
Thrust more.
More!
Release a lot inside me.
No..
This..
I’m cumming!
I’m cumming!..
This feeling...
It's impossible...