www.SubDESU-H.net
So?
My cock’s quite tasty, isn’t it?
Having Onee-san's cock for your first fellatio experience...
The experience is nothing short of special, I am sure.
You see, I have the best of both worlds.
It so happens that my female body has a cock attached to it as well.
But it ejaculates just like any normal cock.
My, you’re quite good Mitarai-san!
W
“Sensational” Practice
Sawatari-san, Mitarai-san.
The newcomer’s practice that we just started today,
as you can see, it's actually a form of sex lesson.
This service will be your first priority as employees here.
In order to master the routines,
we will have continuous training sessions until you are fully comfortable with it.
The results of your training,
will then be properly utilized in the upcoming party.
If you do well, Sawatari-san's wish for a car
and Mitarai-san's need for money for her brother's operation,
will be properly taken care of.
Sawatari-san.
Release your cum on my face whenever you want, okay?
Mother’s face looks really erotic.
You can’t hold it anymore, right?
It's okay.
Think of my mouth... as a vagina.
Good... it's good.
It feels so good, Mitarai-san.
I’m also about to let it out.
Give it to me!
It's okay, please give me a lot of your cum.
It’s hot.
Your cum feels very hot, Sawatari-san.
O-Oh no!
I’m also... about to cum!
Well, I guess making my sister cum makes you satisfactory, at least.
Makoto is a Mother-complex pervert
and he's always ready to erupt like an overflowing milk tank when his mother is putting on a show.
So I guess it's no wonder someone as experienced as Sachie made short work of his ejaculation.
But you!
This hag made you cum so quickly,
isn't that a bit lame?
But even if you say that–
Aren't you soft a bit too soon?
Mother!
What is it?
Isn’t fellatio treated as a first course in a party?
Yet the most important thing is the stamina of the body that will be entertaining the guests.
In other words the body’s potential.
So you want to move to the main course already?
I agree.
It’s important to measure that physical “capability” properly, after all.
Now, get ready.
Then get your unpeeled raw cock into my luxurious pussy.
A special body like mine is something that a commoner like you usually wouldn't see, let alone have sex with.
You should be grateful until your death.
My feet smells good, doesn't it?
To be aroused by the scent of just my feet,
aren't you a real pervert?
Now my body’s starting to heat up as well.
Here, these are my cute nipples.
Don’t touch them!
Touch it and I’ll choke my feet down your throat!
Instead,
I’ll let you inside my pussy.
Now, undress me.
We’ll have to evaluate your potential as well, Mitarai-san.
Kyouichi, want to come first or last?
Of course I’ll be first.
Hey, widen up.
Umm, but... that’s...
Oh yes, how about going for this position Mitarai-san?
Wa–Wait.
My mind isn't prepared for this yet...
But your pussy is ready, isn't it?
My, your pussy has a few wet strings.
Seems your body is plenty ready.
No...
There, look.
Kyouichi’s cock is already going inside.
No, don't!
Please don’t do it raw!
How is it, Mitarai-san?
The sensation of Kyouichi’s cock inside you.
I don’t know, about that...
Oh, is that so?
But you’re really dripping wet down there.
No!
Good.
It feels good!
More!
Do it more!
This cock feels great.
Done already?
You always end up ending it abruptly.
Weren't you interested at all?
Shut up.
I guess it's okay since you’ve enjoyed it.
Okay, Makoto-kun, you’re next.
Ah, okay!
You really couldn't wait to put it in, right?
It’s a bit bigger than usual.
No.
Not something that big!
It’s okay, Makoto-kun.
Put it in.
Okay!
No.
It’s tearing me apart.
It’s okay Mitarai-san.
Your pussy’s still very wet.
Kyouichi's cock wasn't enough for you, right?
What’s with that?
Your cock, that was a virgin not long ago, cannot wait to jump into action now.
You can put it in if that’s what you want.
However you must tie your cock tightly with this first.
Okay, we’re ready.
Put it in.
My... My pussy...
It feels like heaven, doesn't it?
Came already!?
Just how much of a premature ejaculator are you?
The ribbon is working as intended, so you better move no matter what!
I haven’t cum yet.
So?
Feels good, right?
Your penis... just couldn’t resist the pleasure.
You’re just a commoner
and yet you’re getting a taste of this very high-quality first rate pussy.
You should be so tear-glad.
You may be the best one around,
but you still haven’t satisfied me.
Do it with a little more finesse.
If you’re going to be this useless,
then I’ll just cut down that cock of yours.
Not bad.
But at this rate,
do you really think you can make me cum?
You are at your limit you idiot commoner.
See, you’re the one who's about to be done.
Go ahead.
Cum all you want.
Wa– that's...
Don't!
Frustrating...
It feels good.
It feels good!
No.
Cumming! I’m going to cum!
From now on,
you will follow every single order of mine.
Understood?
Y-yes!
Sawatari-san seems to have an outstanding talent for this.
I truly agree.
Really, these are some interesting turn of events.
Please stop it already.
Please!
Stop it already.
Mother!
It seems that we have modified Makoto a bit too much and he might have gone nuts already.
I guess it can’t be helped.
However Mitarai-san seems far from falling apart.
It looks like we’re already going to have great potential pawns after just one day of lesson.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Are we going to continue that every single day?
I wonder if I will be able to handle it.
There is still some left.
It’s still coming out.
Mitarai-san.
More...
I must clean all this...
If I push this in...
It feels good.
The size is about the same as Sawatari-kun's...
Good.
It feels good.
Sawatari-kun...
Sorry.
I have bad eyesight
so I’m not sure if it's thoroughly cleaned or not.
I want you to help me.
I want you to clean me here.
Use your thing to clean me inside here, please.
Please!
I’m going in.
Please.
Good.
As I thought, the real thing is good.
It's coming out.
I’m so glad.
It’s all coming out.
More intensely....
Please use your cock aggressively and push it all out!
Not my breasts.
My breasts are sensitive.
A–Amazing.
Oh no!
This feels too good.
I never thought...
I never thought it would feel this good.
So this is, real sex, right?
Give it to me, Sawatari-kun!
Release it inside me!
B–But...
It’s okay.
I want you to release it inside me.
Clean my pussy with your semen.
I understand.
Here I go.
I am releasing now!
It's so hot!
It's coming out.
It’s getting released inside...!
Yes?
What in the world are you dozing off for?
Come to my room immediately!
Right away.
I haven’t washed it so it must be stinkier than yesterday,
but this kind of work really fits commoners like you.
Now, open your mouth wide.
My personal toilet Sawatari-kun.
You’re not getting away today if you spit it out like yesterday.
You understand already right?
www.SubDESU-H.net