Eri-chan?
And Satsuki-chan, too?
Kanae.
How've you been?
Yeah, we can return to the art club.
"I want to be acknowledged by Kawai-sensei.", she said.
Dr. Fujimi said...
...that saying we'd be in your way...
...might be a prejudice of Kawai-sensei, but...
...it might also be a problem with us.
You? Problems? That's absurd.
No, we also did it wrongly.
We might have been too cautious of each other.
Exactly. Because of this...
Huh?
You will be able to read each other's feelings again...
...if you all experienced the same thing.
Like this, doctor?
Yes. First, move your body into a comfortable position so you can relax.
Okay then, now you'll be training with this.
A first experience for all of you together, got it?
Yes.
First up is...
And with this, you've all become real friends.
W
Hypnosis
Humiliation School
Episode Two
Substitution
Hypnosis
Excuse me, Dr. Fujimi...
Hm?
I'm sorry, it's about a counseling matter.
Ah, you are, erm, Uehara Miyuki-san, right?
Yes. Are you closing up already?
No, it's all right.
I didn't have enough courage to come with a problem totally unrelated to school stuff.
Don't worry.
It's no use discriminating worries.
You can't agree to your mothers remarriage, right?
I was going to accept the death of my father, but...
..it hasn't even been a single year.
Your mother has moved on from your father.
That's what you must've felt.
Yes.
Did you love your dad?
Yes, of course!
Well then, close your eyes.
Yes.
You see...you have a slight schizophrenic disorder.
Everything I say will become reality for you from now on.
When you open your eyes, your father will be there.
My father will?
Grasp your hands when you're mentally prepared, okay?
Okay.
Okay, open your eyes.
Your father is right in front of your eyes.
Father?
You've grown, Miyuki.
Father!
Shirogane-san from the student council, am I right?
I saw Uehara Miyuki-san just a while ago.
Oh, yes she's taking my counseling. Is there something wrong?
Hearing that a class representative is undergoing counseling...
...just made me a bit curious.
Wow, the student council even wants to control people's privacy?
No, enough of that.
Have a good day.
Hm, still sleeping?
Hm?
Thursday will be good for the experiment.
It's also important to get along with the parents.
Excuse me, Dr. Fujimi.
Yes?
There was a call from the mother of one of my students, Miyuki Uehara.
Miss Uehara?
Yes.
It was something about a request for a house visit.
She wants to check your social status as she told me.
Oh, that.
I trust you and your capabilities, but...
...what is this about?
About what?
You plan on entering their home without even getting permission from the homeroom teacher?
It's the way counseling works.
She's agreed to it herself, no?
Sure, but things like this should be more orderly, don't you think?
As a homeroom teacher, isn't it common sense to worry about...
...a house visit that's taking place without one's knowledge?
Is it?
Why are you so relaxed?
Listen!
Excuse my rudeness, but you are a counselor for school related problems.
Please stop invading the student's privacy.
Let's think of a different policy then.
I'm sorry.
You got scolded by Akiko-sensei because of me.
Nevermind that.
Rather than that, let's think about your father.
About father? What are you talking about, doctor?
Have you forgotten already?
About the secret relationship you have with him?
A secret relationship with father?
Father!
I'll tell you something really important tonight, now that you're old enough.
About the correct behavior of a girl, that is.
Of a girl?
Well then, take off your clothes.
The clothes?
Yup.
It's your dad's penis.
Look closely and try touching it.
Yes.
It's hot somehow.
It's twitching.
It's because your hand feels good.
Okay, now try stroking it softly and slowly.
Okay, like this?
Wow.
It's getting bigger and bigger in my hand.
You're such a good girl.
I love you when you're listening to what I say.
Really?
Sure.
Let's make ourselves feel good together, huh?
Okay.
I want to feel good with you.
Good. Don't let your teeth hit.
Your tongue movements are good.
Miyuki!
This is father's?
Exactly. It's semen.
It tastes...
...strange somehow.
How does it feel having your pussy and your breast assaulted at the same time?
This is new for you, isn't it?
But I haven't been touched before.
Stop it, father!
But you see, Miyuku, you're quite wet down there.
That can't-  I'm sorry! I...
You touched your fathers penis and you sucked it. That made you feel good, right?
Yes. I'm already so muddled.
Father, this is amazing. Please become one with me.
I'm...
I know.
I'll always be there for you when you need me.
Father...
...I'm so happy.
Well then, would you let me put my mark on your most important place?
Yes. Please do as you wish, father.
Try allocating it to your special place.
Ok.
What a nasty sound.
It's because you're so wet.
No- Fathers thing is entering inside of me.
Okay, I'm gonna lift myself up.
I became one with father.
Exactly. Now you are my woman!
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good inside of me, father?
Yeah, feels really good.
I'm fine...
...you can move more.
Be patient.
It's fine at your pace.
Fathers filling up the inside my stomach.
Father, I'm going nuts.
Fathers thing seems to be exploding inside of me.
Father...
...please...
Cum! Cum!
Do as you wish!
How often do I have to tell you?
Do the stroke more gently.
See, again. You can't see anything except for beards.
Enough. Do some self study.
Everybody, I'd like you to fix your drawings.
That was quite offensive, Kawai-sensei.
About Modokawa-san and Nonomona-san from the art club...
...didn't they come to you to apologize?
Yes, they came.
I took care of their counseling.
I gave them advice according to my analysis.
I told them to solve their personal problems and go talk to you then.
Do you think the two, including Yasuda-san, are progressing well?
It seems so.
Kawai-sensei, you're feeling great stress lately, aren't you?
Your mind and body seems quite exhausted.
Uh-huh.
That's why I'm an expert. Should I teach you a way to relieve your stress?
Relieving stress?
Yes. It's actually quite easy.
For starters, relax.
Dr. Fujimi!
Oh, Uehara-san.
About the home visit...
...and what I heard from Kawai-sensei this morning.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
I'll talk to the staff again.
I'll come by with proper permission.
Oh, okay. I'll tell my mother then.
Yeah. Oh, and you should put this up somewhere in your house.
It smells nice, and has a relaxing effect.
Thank you very much.
...And you can also have some fun...
Dr. Fujimi!
Kawai-sensei, this is the men's restroom.
Uhm, this is...
The stress built up, and you're taking care of yourself to relieve it.
Correct?
Yes.
Dr. Fujimi!
Yes?
It's no use, the stress is...
My body is hot.
I'll help you.
Yes. I wanted this.
Wow, a man's scent.
The scent of a penis.
Did you have some trouble again?
Did your body start aching while you were irritated?
That's because...
...I didn't have someone to fuck, so I had to do it myself.
It's so wet down there... Please, put it in. Okay?
Your penis is huge!
It's hot...
...very hot.
Pound me harder!
Give it to me!
There! That's so nice!
Kawai-sensei.
Yes?
You don't mind me doing the house visit at the Ueharas, do you?
Wha-?
Why are you bringing this up now?
It's fine to let me handle that case, right?
Oh yes!
I apologize for the delay.
It's fine.
I also understand Miyukis feelings, so...
...I feel sorry that she has to suffer from the fact of me getting remarried.
But...
But.
There are in fact personal matters.
There are two younger daughters...
I see. So it'll be your daughter and twins?
Yes. They're Miku and Nami.
I was playing with them today to get to know each other.
Those two agree with the remarriage...
...which helps a lot, but...
If Miyuki-san isn't convinced...
Yes.
She understands, I think, but...
...it seems she holds her bygone father very dearly.
Excuse me, but there's one thing I'd like to confirm.
Yes, what is it?
Do you yourself oppose this family recreation in some way?
That's... that may be the case.
I can't say that I'm not attached to my dead husband anymore.
That's what I expected.
Huh?
I think that Miyuki-san can see that point in you.
Even more so, she can't forgive you deceiving yourself.
I'd like to suggest something.
As a simulation...
...would you like to meet your dead husband and confirm your feelings?
Simulation?
Exactly.
As psychotherapeutic hypnosis I can let you meet your husband slumbering in your memories...
...and help you fixing your consciousness of reality.
Consciousness of reality?
Exactly.
On my signal your dead husband will appear in front of your eyes.
The person you want to meet the most is going to appear.
It's been a while, Kazue.
D-Dear. It's my dear, right?
I'm so happy to see you again.
Oh, sorry about that.
How was the welcome back kiss?
I mean, the reward kiss, how was it?
Oh I see, reward.
I'm so happy.
What a lewd couple they were.
She's...
...amusing.
It's been a while since I've had your tits.
It's great.
I was about to forget this feeling, too.
You mustn't forget!
Look at me while serving me with your tits.
I will. Here, feel better.
Are you feeling it too?
You penis feels good.
Ok, use your mouth too.
Amuse me with your tongue.
Ok.
How is it?
It's nice.
It's the best, Kazue!
Kazue!
Yea?
Take my cum!
Your cock smells amazing.
The long awaited semen smells nice, right?
Yes.
But, more...I want more.
That's my Kazue!
I'm home!
Are you there, Dr. Fujimi?
Doctor? Mother?
Hi Miyuki, what's with "I'm home"?
Father!
That's some erotic underwear there, Kazue.
It's a design you liked so much...
...I've been wearing them since...
Mother picked them always for you, father.
I see.
The new to-be husband must've thought that you were seductive.
Oh no, you're mean.
Mother looks happy.
Have a look. I'll make her look happier and happier.
Here, touch her.
She's so wet down there.
Harder, do me harder!
Mother...
This feels so good!
Did you have a good look at my shameful self?
Well then...
...shall we all make love together?
Sure.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Uehara...
...and her Mother?
About the remarriage case... Dr. Fujimi took care of us.
And we came to say thanks today.
Remarriage? Oh I see.
Is it alright to wait here for his arrival?
Yes, that's fine.
You two came.
Excuse me, everybody. It'd like you to focus your attention to me.
These two here...
...want to thank you all for your hard work.
As they say.
What?
If it's fine, I'd like everybody to accept their gratitude.
Uhm, Dr. Fujimi?
Well then, you two, prepare.
You're going to serve the teachers with your bodies.
Yes.
What's up with you two?
Don't worry, Kawai-sensei. Don't let it bother you.
What are you saying?
Dr. Fujimi!
Come on, don't get angry.
If you feel stress from this....
...your body will...
...get sick.
Now teachers, please take their gratitude.
I'm getting wet from this.
How about you join the fun?
Good!
Dear, hurry up and put it in!
Father, it's so good there!
You fat thing's so good!
Fathers scent!
It feels so good to relieve stress!
Remarriage is unnecessary, am I right, Kazue?
I was hasty with the new husband.
Me too, I like our daddy more.
More teaching leadership please!
Arimine?
There was a report about trouble at the art club room.
Yes. Kawai-sensei, who's in charge of the club, expelled one of the members.
And, how did it go?
That's...
...it was solved with the guidance of counselor Dr. Fujimi.
It was?
Curing man hate...
...and solving private matters, personal matters, and club activity issues as well.
"He's skilled." is what I'm supposed to say, huh?
It's time...
...for an invitation.