W-What was that about?
I-If...
If you keep thrusting against my uterus, I'll-!
I'll go crazy!
I'll turn into a loose woman from such an indecent thing!
You're very perverted, aren't you?
Rubbing your clitoris like that...
Shut up-!
I'm not-!
I don't care what you say! This is all I'm doing!
Amazing-!
No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Your semen is pouring into my deepest spots...
That Gertrude-nee-san, the one who dislikes battles the most...
She was putting on such a dirty expression...
What's this?
Every time I think about Gertrude-nee-san, my body gets-!
Furthermore... Grimgerde...
What was that about?
She's a valkyrie, but that was-
Who is it?
Sigrun...?
What's this? He doesn't seem the same...
Svanhvit-nee-san, so you were here.
Yes, I was just enjoying the evening breeze.
Evening breeze?
I know you were just trying to calm down that lewd body of yours!
Wha-?!
Peeping isn't good, Nee-san.
You need to be punished.
W-What are you talking about?
Me? Peeping?
Anyway, who are...?
I guess you can tell, given in the situation we're in.
But...
No mercy from you, as always.
Oh? I take that as a compliment.
Y-You're?!
The one from Helheim...
Why?!
You know a little too much, so we're gonna punish you.
Be obedient, will you?
Although a valkyrie will recover fast.
Now then, let's have a bit of fun...
I hope you understand.
If you hurt her, I won't forgive you.
Sure, whatever.
Hmph, don't lose yourself in the aphrodisiac and the pain.
SubDESU-H
That a good expression! Those eyes! I love it!
Hey, hey. I'm the one who's supposed to be having fun here...
You're being annoying, be quiet!
Looks like you're feeling good with this mix of pain and pleasure thanks to the aphrodisiac...
What's this?
Something greater than pain is welling up inside of me!
Saying that I could have a fun time and all...
Darn it.
We're not making any progress.
Sorry, but I'm going to put it in you.
No-! Why am I being treated like this by my younger sister-?
It's your fault, Nee-san!
Nee-san?
Grimgerde...
Since you don't like taking baths very often...
I'm going to clean you up.
That's because my body got so hot, and-!
But-! Who would have thought you had such a fabulous toy?
It's wonderful that you're so lewd, Nee-san.
It's going in! It's entering me!
Your cock is stirring me inside!
It's fine!
Please feel even better, Nee-san!
So good! It's so deep! It's knocking against my uterus!
The key doesn't seem to be activating...
Why?
No-!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
Why?
I thought she was feeling good.
Wasn't it enough?
Grimgerde-nee-san said something that day.
If I weren't transferred to this body, I would have died.
With all that training, I thought she was one of the top valkyries, and...
I remember now...
Gertrude-nee-san!
Why don't you come on in?
I've wiped her mind, but I guess her body remembers.
You look like you can't hold back.
Your body is throbbing, isn't it?
What's with that thing of yours?
This is my toy.
A toy that makes you feel good.
That's why Brunhilde-nee-san is like this.
D-Did you do, uh... it to Brunhilde-nee-san?
Don't worry!
I'll be good to you too, Gertrude-nee-san!
You won't be satisfied by simply cumming on your own.
It must be with me.
W-What are you-?!
It's not good to restrain yourself!
Your nipples have gotten hard, haven't they Gertrude?
Nee-san, please make me feel good as well!
That's it!
You're good, Nee-san!
Does this feel good?
Your cock tastes delicious!
That feels so good!
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Go on, no need to hold back!
I'm about to cum too-!
N-No-!
Nee-san-! I'm gonna cum!
You should get Gertrude-nee-san to make you feel good too!
Yes...
Nee-san... It feels great!
That's it, Gertrude!
D-Don't-!
Doing both my pussy and butt at the same time-!
I-I'm gonna lose it!
Go on!
Nee-san, please lose yourself!
You taste good, Nee-san!
Don't-! Don't suck on me!
I knew she cared for her sisters, but I didn't know it was this much!
Nee-san, I'll make you go even crazier!
No! That's-!
Not there!
Hey, not there! Please!
No-!
I'll take your virginity here as well, okay Nee-san?
D-Don't-!
It's too tight-!
It's nearly in!
It's inside me! It went in my butt-!
It's so tight-!
I'll make you feel even better!
I-It hurts, but it tingles!
No-!
Your cock is entering me!
Something so thick is entering Nee-san's butt...
Nee-san! Please feel better and lose yourself in the pleasure!
No! This feels strange!
It feels so good for you to twist up my insides!
No-! My mind is going blank!
It feels good! My butt feels so good!
No-! I'm gonna cum again!
I'm gonna cum from this-!
That should have over-written Brunhilde's key.
Half of them left, huh?
I should do Kamio so I can complete my destiny...
Hey, hold up.
Svanhvit-nee-san?
How did you get her?
It wasn't me.
Ask her for the details.
It seems things are going well for you.
She has the next key.
Nee-san? What does all this mean?
And what's with this guy? Isn't he from Helheim?
Yes, he is from Helheim, but he's not going to try and take over here.
Eh?
It was under my orders, right?
Command?
When you lost your body ten years ago, I lost mine too.
Likewise, Sigrun perished as well.
And I, Hel, was given her body.
Hel?
She's my younger sister.
N-No way...
Then why were you with us all along?
It's simple! It's because it's fun!
I don't care about Helheim or Asgard.
It was just entertaining.
Moreover, he's the one that made that god's destiny thing up anyway.
Hmph, that was ten years ago; after you recovered.
Even though only your soul remains now.
Well, that doesn't matter anymore.
It's your own fault! I told you not to hurt her.
Like hell I can resist with such a delightful dish in front of me!
Y-You bastard-!
That should make you repent for your own stupidity.
Were you surprised?
You should rest for a bit.
I can't do anything like this.
I have to hold off until I recover.
Now then, shall we finish up unlocking these keys?
U-Um-?!
Haven't you recovered enough to change to your true form?
Yeah...
Yeah, I remembered after I unlocked Brunhilde's key.
Lets get started.
Y-You're...?
Don't worry, just leave it to him and you'll soon recover!
I-I see...
I removed her memories of Freyja.
When did you learn such tricks?
I've done everything up till now, so you just have to fuck her.
Hey-!
Jeez...
A-Are you sure that you're supposed to touch there?
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
Just trust me.
No...!
Stop-! I can't hold my moans in!
It's okay, moan all you want.
D-Don't bite me!
Get on with it!
You can't hold back, can you?
I-It feels good-!
It's hard to breathe-!
I guess I should do it soon...
I'm putting it in.
It's entering me-!
Does it hurt?
D-Do you think such a small pain will hinder me?
You'll feel good soon.
I-Is it in?
Yeah, it's in all the way.
T-This is too much-!
No-! No more!
It's okay, go ahead and cum.
If you do, you'll feel much better.
No-! My pussy is so full!
Something deep inside me is getting hot!
No! I can't hold on any longer!
No-! I can't-!
We're not done yet.
We'll make you feel better.
You're not done yet either, are you?
Pour more inside of her...
So much so that she might get pregnant.
Yeah, we're just getting started.
Amazing-!
T-This feels too amazing-!
More! Do it more!
So good!
This feels better than before!
It's so much-!
I-I'm gonna-!
My body, it's-!
It's nearly done-!
We're the ones...
... who unlock the key!
No-!
I'm gonna lose it again!