I wonder how everyone’s doing...
There's something I can do for them...
If I do my best here, my boss and the others at the firm… will be saved...
Since I've been going around living with relatives after my parents died,
I'm quite used to adapting to the situation, but...
I wonder what they're going to make me do here...?
I'll be fine... I'll be fine, right?
Tsuruma-san, umm... What is this place?
This is your new workplace; it's the stage.
The stage?
That's right. First, lift up your skirt and show me your underwear.
What?!
Didn't you hear me? Hurry up.
W-Why must I do such a thing?
It's a test required for this job.
B-But why do I have to show you my u-underwear for a test?
If you don't want to, then I don't know what’ll happen to the people back at the firm...
N-No way...
I-Is this okay?
T-This is so embarrassing! What kind of test is this?
Pull it up a little higher.
Y-Yes...
Okay, now turn around.
Wha? Y-Yes...
No, make it so that I can still see your underwear.
Y-Yes-!
I guess that's okay. Face this way.
Y-Yes.
Your lower half passes. Now for the...
U-Um! What kind of job will I be doing here?
I'll explain that later.
Now it's time for your breasts.
M-My breasts?
Stop asking so many questions and hurry up.
But... Um, what should I do...?
Fold your arms under your breasts.
Now, raise your arms like that.
Stay like that for a moment.
Can I stop now?
Sure.
Um, so about that...
Your breasts pass, too. Now... Are you a virgin?
What-?
I'm asking if you've done it with a guy.
I-I haven't...
Really?
Yes!
I see. Well, we can find out for sure anyway.
Huh? Find out?
You do this.
W-What are you-! P-Please stop-!
This is the last test. You can refuse, but...
I have to try my best-!
That's right, don't move...
Otherwise-!
That hurts!
C-Can we stop now?
Hmph, I guess you are a virgin.
Although, that doesn't concern me.
Oh, by the way, you passed the test.
You're going to work here for us.
T-Thank you very much...
A-And so what am I supposed to do?
You’re going to care for the people here.
Well, care as in relieve their sexual desires...
What? R-Relieve their sexual desires?
It's something like this...
What?
Put it in your mouth!
Huh? No-!
He's making me suck his cock!
I haven't even had my first kiss...
And he said I'm going to relieve people’s sexual desires!
From now on, you have to suck it daily. Get used to it.
It's painful-!
It's painful! I can't breathe!
Someone... Someone help me!
Hurry up! Hurry up and make this end!
I'm gonna cum.
Y-You're gonna cum?
Don't spit it out, drink it all.
Drink this stuff? It's disgusting!
But if I don't, the other's at the firm will be-!
I'm gonna have more fun with you,
since it was difficult to get hold of you...
Huh?
P-Please wait! Not that-!
No!
N-No!
No!! No!!
It hurts, it hurts! Please stop! Please stop!!
You've got a good voice, as expected of an idol.
It hurts, it hurts-! Don't move!
This is good, it feels great inside you!
I beg of you, please stop thrusting!
Pull it out, please pull it out! It... it really hurts!
Is it heart breaking? Does it hurt?
It's really fun for me to watch you squirm like that! Entertain me more!
No, No way!
C'mon! Show me your breasts, too!
Don't thrust so deeply-! It's painful-!
Hurry, hurry up and make this end!
I’ll, I'll break!
Oh yeah? You want it to end that badly?
Yes! It's painful! Hurry, hurry!
Then, as you requested, I'll finish up by cumming a lot inside of you!
What-?! Y-Your cum? I-If you let it out inside of me, I-I'll get pregnant-!
Yes, you might!
We can't have that! You mustn't! You mustn’t cum inside me!
I don't think so.
I can't stop, I'm gonna cum! Make sure you take it all!
Don't, don't! You mustn’t! Don't cum inside me!
No-!!
It's coming out, it's coming out inside me...
No, no! I'll get pregnant, I'll get pregnant!
Is this going to be my job?
I can't bear something like this!
What are you hazing out for?
C'mon, we're not finished yet.
No way, this isn't the end...?
Why would it be the end?
You're going to be the plaything for a lot of people.
C'mon, raise your ass!
No more!
Please, please stop!
Make sure you move your hips!
Don't you want this to end quickly?
You're moving already?
You're quite adaptive, aren't you?
N-No, I'm not-!
And you're tightening around me so much! I'm about to cum!
No-!
Huh...? W-What are you...?
Please stop this!
We’re going to do it until I'm satisfied.
Let's see, I think I can do it about five more times.
N-No way!
Don't break, will you? Keep me entertained!
No, no-! No!!
Rena!
Yes, warden?
Take care of the rest. Also, start it beginning tomorrow.
Understood. We shall begin Sakura's work tomorrow.
Sana...
She'll finally be mine!
Toriko Hime
presented by SubDesu-H
http://h.subdesu.org/
#subdesu-h@ic.rizon.net
This is Seinanjo Academy, a private high school.
It’s known for its skilled students,
and is responsible for its graduates
filling top jobs in the political and financial worlds with talented people.
Furthermore, with its strong emphasis on sports, many female athletes have graduated here.
Within such an acclaimed institute, one student stood out among the rest.
Shizuru-san!
Thanks!
You're amazing! They all hit the target!
That's nothing, I've still got a long way to go. I need to try harder!
By the way, I hear that you have some business to attend to today?
Please excuse me.
I'm glad I made it!
Himeno!
W-Why are you here, Shizuru?
I heard that you were announcing a new performance, so I came to watch!
What?! T-Then were you watching me...?
It was wonderful.
I-If you're coming, then please tell me beforehand...
But you didn't tell me about it...
Please do so next time!
Yeah...
It was really beautiful.
I-I still have some areas where I need to practice, so I'll be off.
Himeno, I'll be waiting, so lets go home together!
Okay?
Sure.
Sorry to make you wait!
Let's go home, then.
What should I do about
getting love letters from girls?
You should reply to them properly.
W-What's with that attitude?
I know you get way more than I do!
I reply to all of them!
Oh really?
Yes! Oh yeah, how about I write one to you, Himeno?
What?!
If I did, I wonder what you'd say?
Hey, if you were going to write one, isn't there someone you'd rather give it to?
Oh, it's Onee-sama!
Oh, what are you two doing?
When Himeno and I were about to go home, we saw you...
So we took the opportunity to watch you!
You two sure get along; it's almost like you're lovers.
W-What are you saying, Senpai?!
We don't look like that, do we Shizuru?
I'm okay with it, if it's you.
What?! W-Wait, Shizuru-!
Looks like she's serious!
I'm joking!
Geez! Of course!
Although, I'm a bit jealous. You two look good together.
Yes.
Geez...
Oh, do you have more training to do, Senpai?
That was actually my last jump.
Then would you like to go home together?
Really? Won't I get in the way of you two?
W-What do you mean, "get in the way"?
If you could come as well, I'd be happy.
Then could you wait a moment? I'll be back shortly.
Yes.
What's up?
I'm just happy that we can all go home together.
I guess...
Hey, I've been waiting for you Shizuru.
Huh?
Tsuruma-kun?
You're pretty late, Shizuru...
Don't call me by my given name!
We don't know each other that well!
Stubborn as always, aren't you Shizuru?
Like I said, please don't call me that...
Anyway, I can hear a good reply
from you today, right?
If it's about that, I've already declined your offer.
If you go out with me, you'll be happy.
Hey, if she's declined, then leave her alone!
Hey Himeno, do you want to go out with me too?
I'm fine with two girls.
Stop with the jokes.
If you're going to hit on girls, isn't there a better place to do that?
Oh, if it isn't Inui Ayane.
You sure have some nerve to speak like that to a stranger. Who are you, anyway?
Oh? You don't know about me?
No, I don't.
I see, I see... Then ask these two.
Looks like today wasn't so good.
I'll come back later.
Think of a good reply for me by then, Shizuru.
Like I said-!
See you later, then...
Who is he?
He's the son of the owner of Tsuruma Consulting.
Oh... Just as the rumors...
How do you know each other?
Uh, um... Actually...
I see...
I've declined many times,
but he doesn't get it...
Exactly. His father isn't any better.
Like that incident recently...
An incident?
You remember that famous entertainment company
that was bought out by the Tsuruma Corporation?
Oh yeah.
Apparently, the boss committed suicide!
I heard that as well.
I didn't know that...
That's not all, um...
What happened to her?
She's the idol who was employed at the company. She went missing too!
She went missing?
That's why you have to be careful with him.
Y-Yes...
She went missing, huh?
Happy birthday, Shizuru!
Congratulations!
Huh?
What do you mean "huh"?
U-Um, it's not like I forgot...
Were you more worried about whether you could meet your father?
Uh, y-yes...
Since your father is a politician...
Is he really that busy?
Yes... It seems it was hard for him to make time to see me...
You're going to be together
when you get home, right?
So we're gonna have a party of our own!
Himeno insisted that we celebrate.
W-Well, it wasn't exactly like that...
Thanks a lot!
W-Well, it's fine! We don't have all day,
so let's get started!
This is for you. Since you're probably gonna eat one at home, this is smaller...
Thank you, Onee-sama!
Attention Minase Shuzuru-san of the second year C-group,
please come to the staff room immediately.
Father collapsed? I must go to the hospital immediately!
I'm sorry. I’m in a hurry, so...
There are a few things we would like to ask you about your father...
U-Um, I'm about to go see him!
Then we'll come with you!
Let me go!
I need to visit Father-!
Quiet down!
Let's go!
You'll finally become mine, Shizuru!
Where am I...?
Huh? What’s this?
Oh, you've awoken?
U-Um, where am I?
Welcome to our prison!
We're delighted to have you here.
Prison? Um, I must go see my father!
I can't permit that since you're a criminal.
Sentenced for the attempted murder of your own father? That's a pretty big crime.
Attempted murder of my own father...?
What?!
Oh? Looks like you're properly awake now.
Um, what do you mean about a crime? And where am I?
It's just as you heard. You were sent here because you tried to murder your father.
No way! Why would I-?!
Rather, where is Father? Is he safe?
Moreover, your conviction has already been finalized.
You're going to live your sentence out in here.
N-No way! What's happening?
You're finally aware of your situation?
Oops, I still haven't introduced myself. I'm Chief Nasukawa.
Nasukawa...?
The one that was in the same
political party as Father?
But Father found some sensitive
information on him, and he was caught...
It seems that you remember me...
But who would have thought that the daughter of such an honest and caring politician
would be charged for such a thing?
No, I haven't tried to kill my father!
Say whatever you want, you're still a criminal.
You're going to pay amends for your offenses here.
No way...
What on Earth is happening?
Father! Himeno! Onee-sama! What should I do?
Yo, you look good like that.
Huh? Tsuruma-kun? Why are you here?
We were waiting for you, Young Master.
You look puzzled, Shizuru.
D-Don't call me by my given name!
I'm looking forward to seeing how long that attitude will last.
Yes, I was thinking that we could get started once you arrived...
Then I guess we'll have a good look at you.
Young Master sure does like these things...
P-Please stop! What are you-!
Let go! No, stop-! Stop!
No-! Stop that!
It's a bit suspicious here...
No! Don't touch me there!
You're acting quite naïve, aren't you?
Isn't this a daily routine?
I've never done such a thing!
You're a virgin, huh?
Then maybe I should be more thorough?
Please stop it!
What's wrong? Are you hiding something in here?
Stop it, please! Don't put your finger there!
I must remove clothes that get in the way...
No, no!
Stop it! Please!
The polite high-class missy has a classy pussy too!
D-Don't look, don't look...!
T-That's-!
I'm gonna put this in to search your insides!
You get it, don't you?
N-No way...
No! Please don't! No-! No!
I thought you'd be the withdrawn type, but you're quite feisty!
This'll make the search more interesting...
No, this is wrong!
Wrong? You're the one who's wrong!
Trying to kill your own father...
I-I...
Be easier on yourself and admit it.
Say: "I did it."
That's right, if you admit your wrongdoings, then we won't have to search you.
Well? Do you admit it?
I...
I'll never admit it!
Oh, I see. Well, whatever you say,
you're still a criminal.
Are you ready?
No-!
I-It hurts-! My body is being torn apart!
You're so tight! As expected of a virgin!
So she really was a virgin.
That's a good expression, Shizuru. I can't get enough of it.
It's painful-!
I knew that this was their intention, but I didn't know that it would hurt this much!
Now we're really getting into the search.
Young Master, please.
I just have to search her behind, right?
Yes...
What-?! Not there!
No! Don't touch there!
Please stop-!
Hey, you need to relax.
I've put on lotion, but you’ll rip your rectum.
No-! I don't want it-! No!!
That's a good expression, Shizuru.
I'm nearly cumming!
Me too!
W-What are you-?!
We're going to release lots of the test solution called semen.
If you're lucky, a new life could be born!
If that happens, do I have to
call that bastard my father?
A new life?
A child?
That was their original intention?! No way!
No, stop it!
Please stop it!
Not that, not that! No, no! No!
That reminds me; today is your birthday, isn't it?
Is that so? Then we have to celebrate!
This is our birthday present to you!
No! I don't want it!
No, no-!
The search is complete.
Next is introducing you to the others.
Who are these people?
They're your fellow inmates.
Now we'll begin your sentence.
Sentence?
You're going to take good care of these prisoners.
Or rather, take care of the lower half of their body...
How about we get started?
No-! Let go!
Noo!
Shizuru-san, please get used to it quickly.
Get used to it like me, then...