This beauty salon is...
One that I built enduring many hardships.
This store is my pride.
All the craziness started...
Half-month ago...
When that man...
Started to came to this salon...
SubDESU-H Presents
Yubisaki Annainin Shirudaku Settai Okawari Sanbai-me
指先案内人 汁だく接待 おかわり三杯目
It's long... you're going to release it inside right?
Go ahead and release it...
Faster...finish it quickly...
It seems your pussy already recognizes mine...
Erika...
His name is Dokushima Nero.
He is a wanted for raping many women.
If you ask me...Then I will end it quickly.
My wet and perverted pussy...
Thrust it harder and stir it all you want.
Being raped day after day...
I already...
Have become a slave to his body...
I cumming.
Hey... hurry up and change your clothes.
The next customer is about to come right?
He...
Isn't satisfied by just raping me.
He also has eyes for the customers in the store,
and then stings them in.
Uhm...
I'm Akizawa who called in a reservation...
Welcome...
You're Akizawa Haruna-sama who is reserved for the bridal course right?
Yes... I'll be in your care...
Please come this way...
I see.
Your getting married in 4 months...
Yes...
The wedding dress I ordered was backless...
So I requested for a back massage...
Ok... I understand...
By the way... you have beautiful skin...
Yes... My husband also told me that.
Oh no... I called him my husband...
It's weird that I'm the one to say this but...
He... can work... and is handsome...
He also cooks for me and he has a nice attitude...
He's such a nice guy...
That's why I...
Wanted to become beautiful for the wedding.
It is my duty to become a gorgeous wife.
Ma'am? Can you also remove your underwear?
Eh? But...
It's alright...
There's no one coming in to this room except for me...
Yes... you're right...
Ok then... I'll leave it to you...
How is the smell of the oil...ma'am?
Yes...
It smells so good...
I mixed rose and jasmine into this oil..
There's a perspiring effect if you use it..
That part...
It's alright, there's nothing to worry about...
You'll become beautiful for your fiancé, right?
The wedding ceremony...
I want it to be successful...
Please relax...
It's like... I feel weird...
My body is getting hot...
What an effect...
This...
If you already feel so good, I don't mind if you sleep...
This girl... her boobs are so hot already...
So dirty...
By the way... your really cruel...
She's even your important customer...
Aren't you the one who told me to do it this way?
Ok then, let's start tasting her...
Hello? Finally awake?
What...?
Sensei... what's the meaning of this...?
No... wait...
Sorry... but it's alright...
No... let me go...
Why... why...
No...
What nice eyes...
I feel excited...
N... no...
I have a fiancé!
Why am I going to do it with you?
Stop... stop it...
Is your fiancé really looking forward to your wedding?
For men, house, wife and children are...
Just taking away the freedom of men right?
Men just want to do it with women.
The merit of the wedding is just...
To make a pussy which he can do it for free.
No... that's... impossible...
Hamaji-san is... not that kind of...
No!
No...
Ou...ch...
It hurts!!
Look, it went in to the deepest part...
No...
It's coming in... ouch...
No... No way!!
I'll record it so make a nice face!
N... no...
Stop... this kind of thing...
Please... stop it...
Don't struggle so much ... you'll just suffer more.
Don't move it!
She's squeezing me a lot.
Here I go!
Please... don't do that...
How is it? To get married means doing this kind of thing.
I am going to teach you about a mans body...
Your such a dirty girl who making a lewd face...
I will send this video and pictures to your fiancé and your friends...
Haruna?
This is...
I receive a picture and a movie and...
In the mail it stated that I must cancel the wedding with Haruna.
He won't pick up and I called him many times.
I want to believe Haruna but...
To tell the truth, I don't know what to do...
Kaho-san...
Hamari-san...
I... I am going to comfort you...
Eh?
I loved Hamari-san since before...
But Haruna was there and I stayed back...
But I won't hold back anymore.
Hamari-san's dick...
It's so hot...
It's so hot and hard...
I always imagine Hamari-san's penis and masturbate...
Please... let me suck it...
It...sucks hard... Tomo-san's mouth...
This...
I'm glad...
Just to make Hamari-san feel good,
I will do anything for you...
My dripping wet pussy...
Please penetrate it using this hard dick...
Now... please...
Give me Hamari-san's hot thing...
Hamari-san... It's so big...
It went in...
Into my dirty pussy...
Hamari-san's dick...
Kaho-san... I...
You're dick is pumping inside my pussy...
Release... release it inside please...
Eh?
If... I do that...
Please...
Please fill my pussy with Hamari-san's sperm!
It's coming out...
It's coming out... into my womb...
So much of Hamari-san's sperm is coming out...
My pussy...
Was it good?
Please... please give me more...
Please give me more Hamari-san's sperm!
Kaho-san...
More... more...
I don't care if I'll get pregnant so release more inside...
It plays excellently.
The recent hidden camera is high tech you know.
Do you think this video can be sold?
Yes of course.
We can put a high price for this kind of girl.
Really...
If I listen to you for today...
Yes...
We won't lay a hand on you anymore.
I will also give you the data of your pictures.
Doing such a cruel thing...
I will...
Report you to the police!
Are you sure? Your getting married soon right?
If you make trouble maybe your wedding will be canceled...
T...that's...
I think it's best for us to... keep this thing silent... Ma'am...
For today, there is also a special guest I invited.
Come to this room...