Just so that you know, right now we're in a serious predicament.
Our latest project failed, so we didn't get paid.
If our next project were to fail as well,
that would be the end of our company, Flower.
Our next release needs to be a success.
Everyone, we're gonna have a meeting right now!
Please, gather in the meeting room!
Shut up!
Shut up.
W
Eroge!
H & Game Development With the Three Sisters
~Himeno Kisara Love, is Started Chapter~
As you might have gathered from our last H-soft release,
we can't fail this time.
We're gonna challenge ourselves with new scenes,
like rape and so on.
Then, what's this?
Ah, this boy is-
From today, I'll be in your company's care.
Eh? Say that again?
From today onwards, I'll be working with you in this company,
my name is Mochizuki Tomoya.
Please get along with me!
EH~?!?!
Working? As an employee? Part time?
No... No... Both of you, are you sure about this?!
We don't accept this kind of thing here-
Hiyori-san, please say something!
Himeno Kisara (21)
I'm Himeno Kisara, I'm responsible for artwork.
That's it from me, okay?
- Responsible in Art
- This is the 3rd projects
- Having her own popular circle for doujinshi
Virgin
What's with you? Don't look at me with that weird face!
Fujiwara Momoka (20)
I'm Fujiwara Momoka, I'm responsible for writing.
The end.
- Scenario Writer
- Being popular from her writing novel
Virgin
I'm Kosaka Yuri, a Graphic Designer.
Did I fall asleep?
Kosaka Yuri (25)
- Graphic Designer
- Having connection in digital works
and have her own circle to sell some doujin.
Virgin
Sunono Nene (32)
I'm Sunono Nene, as you know from our previous interview.
I'm this company's president, and a super lady!
- The president of the company
- Director
- Scripter
- Wroking this company as to fullfiled
her contract with another company
Virgin
(nigriV) Virgin
Then... Mochizuki-kun's job would be-
Nene! Where's your handsome new recruit?
Re-Reina-chan, what are you doing here?
Are you going to shut our company down?!
Good work, you can go home now.
I thought you could use some refreshment to open
your mind, and spark your imagination!
Here you go!
You're kidding!
Thank you, Reina-chan.
Then everyone, now's the time to have a break.
Let's party all night long!
Geez, you're a man right? How can you get dizzy
just from drinking one can like this?
Ha...
Shouldn't you be made of stronger stuff than this?!
Kisara-chan is tough as usual, you know that
I like tough people like you.
That's why men are useless.
Hm... I'm getting hot from drinking all of this beer.
Hey... Hey... Everyone, pay attention!
I'll strip down!
Reina-san, you can't do that here!
Eh... It's fine, isn't it? We're all women in here
and no one's gonna bother peeking at us.
...My existence...
Tomoya-kun, I'm sure you've brought such an amazing thing with you...
That penis of yours, is it still a virgin?
Hey... Hey... You're sexy!
Huh, appearing confident
is also part of your job, you know?
Eh? Sure... I get it, then...
Before now, I've played various erotic games.
Of course, I've played erotic games from
this company too.
I think that maybe the reason why you failed
is that the art, the scenario, even the graphics don't have
much eroticism to them.
I may not be able to do any art, scenarios, or graphics like all of you can,
but I won't lose in my passion for erotic games!
If you're saying things like that, I bet
you've had real experience in it, right?
That's... I'm still a virgin.
Then I wouldn't talk about it so easily, if I were you.
Then, is everyone here experienced?
Well... At the moment... We're busy with our jobs here...
It's not like we have to do it...
That's a lie, isn't it?
Perhaps, but I'm sure you wouldn't mind
sharing it with us, right?
Huh?
Wow, can you all feel the same passion as he does?
Wh-What are you talking about?
This thing doesn't mean anything to me.
Hm... Hm... So this is a real man's penis.
What... What's this thing? Please hurry and put it away, Reina-san!
So, it's getting big like this...
Well Kisara-chan, I'll give you a chance
to punish his raging thing.
Eh?! Su-sure.
Ju-just leave it to me, or something like that...
Wh-what is that?! Don't make weird noises like that.
So-something like this-
Th-this is...
It's delicious to see you all covered in sperm.
So it really happened... What I did.
I want to help that company, even though there's nothing I can do there.
Okay!
I'm really sorry about that!
You... Dare... Come in here?
Well... Well... Mochizuki-kun is also the victim, after all.
That's why we can't trust men.
I have something that you all need to see.
Eh?
Eh, what's this?
That's the data of the art from various popular erotic games
all of which I've played before.
You should look through all of it.
Aegi Goeya script data?
Hm... So we can also expand that...
He~ data on erotic game sales.
You've been... Gathering this much?
This is amazing, Mochizuki-kun.
I thought that since all of you are women,
you don't know the true nature of erotic games.
So you can't make an erotic game,
If you don't know anything about eroticism itself.
I want Flower's next project to be a success!
You're really an erotic game nut, aren't you?
I understand... Thank you.
This is some data you can use.
Even though there'll be a mosaic,
people will realize what this is.
Then... That's safe to use, so if Kisara-san wants to use it-
You think I would use that?!
There.
Mochizuki-kun will be checking everyone's work from now on.
Eh?!
Don't you think this guy is still too new at this?
Everyone in here has barely played erotic games before,
so the one with most experience
in erotic games would be Mochizuki-kun.
Hello, this is Flower.
Ah, I'm in your care.
If you please.
Eh... Huh.
Um... President.
Yes, yes, what is it?
Don't you think this room is a bit hot?
Eh?
That can't be right!
Th-that's right!
It's true it's hot, b-but...
This isn't broken, right?
Momo!
Okay!
If we were to turn on the air conditioner at the same time
as everyone's using the computers,
it will trip the breaker.
You should tell me about that sooner!
But, what did you do last year?
That... We...
The truth is, everyone would take off-
Nene-chan!
We took off our clothes, right?
If it's getting to be too hot, then we're
only gonna wear our underwear.
Something like that?!
Tomoya...
Can you check my art quickly?
That's not fair, you should check my scenario first.
Tomoya, I thought I should paint this part the same color as my nipples...
Tomoya-kun, please hug me.
What're you smirking for? You're making me feel sick!
Hmph, could someone do something about this-
Eh?
Huh?
Yes, it's too breezy.
Huh... We don't really have any choice in here, we can't let
those two take all the good things for themselves.
I suppose...
Am I dreaming?
It's unfair otherwise, so take your clothe off!
Okay...
Here we go!
Everyone in here has talent in their positions, but it's not
that they're working here because they like erotic games.
I know that this wouldn't be worked out
with our current position as game maker...
I... I understand.
Good work today!
I'm first.
Then, I'll be going to the public bath.
Yes.
Good work from you, too!
Why can't I draw it properly?!
Hang on!
You've been looking at my drawing since this afternoon, right?
Y-yes.
Then, what's your opinion?
Eh?
I want you to give me your opinion on it!
Yes.
While it does make Mayuri more erotic,
this tit fuck scene is bothering me.
Though it should be like moving the penis between the breasts,
it feels that it's just in the same position
the whole time.
Ah, if you say something imaginary like that
I can't understand it easily!
Um... Well.. If you had experience in it,
you would be able to understand it.
Then, let's try it out!
What?
I can only experience it with you!
Let it out right now!
That's...
I'm gonna do the tit fuck with you!
That's fine, I'll do it with you.
It's all for my data after all.
I'll put up with you as my partner in this.
Eroge.
Why should I do something like this with you anyway?
You're gonna do it properly, right?!
If you don't do it properly, I'm gonna cut you to pieces.
You can't even put someone else's face in the picture, okay?
Y-yes.
Well, what should I do?! I've never done something like this!
Move it to the top of it-
Wh-what is this? It's getting big!
A man's thing is very sensitive.
With even a little stimulation,
it becomes like this.
It's still getting big?!
Don't let it get out of control, it makes it difficult
to put it between my breasts.
This just something we're doing for the data we need.
It feels good, right?
This can't be happening...
This... This is the right way to do a tit fuck, right?
Yes, please do it more intensely!
Then, how about this?!
A man is so perverted, to get so excited from something like this.
The right expression would also get it more excited.
Eh? You're saying that my face won't do any good?
It's not like that.
In many erotic games, there's a scene where the heroine
looks at the main character while she's doing a tit fuck.
Look at him... You mean like this?
Could you make your expression softer?
There's no way I would have a soft expression
when I'm doing something embarrassing like this!
You know, I don't have to hear all about tit fucks from you!
Himeno-san, could you be gentler?
Wh-what do you mean by that?!
Didn't I already do that?!
I couldn't stand it with her angry expression like that.
You're making too many demands, even though you're a newcomer.
What's this?! There's something coming out from the tip of it.
It's dripping onto my breasts...
This is what men do.
Shut up! Then be a man and look at the way I'm doing it!
It feels good-
It's definitely... Gonna... Come out...
Three.
It's really dripping a lot of it.
Two.
Are you listening to me?
One.
What just happened...
What's this...
It's hot...
You just... Spread it again... On me..!
Eroge.
Geez, you made me drink most of it.
Why is there no bathroom in this room anyway?
I only let you see my breasts because we needed it
for the data, you know?!
I'm sorry about that, I just couldn't stand it with the heat before.
What're you talking about, it'll get clean
when we take a shower after this.
If it's still dripping a lot, then I'm gonna hit you again.
Even though you just hit me...
So that's it for today, I want to take a shower as soon as possible.
I'm going home.
Yes, thanks for your good work.
But since she agreed to a photoshoot like this,
is it possible that Kisara likes me..?
There.
It's cold.
I'm sorry, Momoka-san.
Why are all men are like this!?
It's still not real enough for me.
That's something I agree with you about.
Shut up!
Um... Please don't make the room dirty...
Just shut up, I'm only throwing away a little!
You, be sure to leave it with me!
Sure...
Hm... So that's the right way to draw it.
Hey, don't move it around! I can't draw it properly.
Even if you say something like that, this position is...
The back of my feet feel hot, this is
what you called feet stimulus, right?
You're feeling good from this?
Of course!
Is there a name for this kind of thing?
It's called a footjob or something like that...
It's black and dirty, but it's getting excited from my feet.
It's weird, but it's interesting to do this with the penis.
So do you want to let it out from the stimulation from my feet?
Yes...
You're so hopeless...
Yeterday I wasn't able to get a good look with all the shock,
but today I'm gonna get a proper look.
There, if you want to let it out then say so!
Here!
Hmph, you let out a lot of it again.
I can't use my socks after this.
W-well, I got more information from this,
so I'm gonna forgive you for now.
It's good, your drawing looks just like a real one.
Heh, with my skill I can even draw something like a penis...
That's the way it works, we need to apply more eroticism to
the art, scenario and the graphics as well.
With this, please remember the basics of erotic games.
What is this? Penis... Semen... What game is this..? Puss-
I can't say something like that!
It's our job!
Pu-pussy...
Please say it out loud!
Don't get full of yourself!!
This is a fellatio scene, isn't it?
Ah, I know what you're gonna say about that!
You must think about how to make it more erotic by yourself.
I understand it!
Like... Like this?
You should use your whole tongue.
I'm licking a man's penis like this; I wonder if the others
have done the same thing as I'm doing right now?
But, it somehow feels strange inside me...
Did I get used to doing this with a penis?
It's not that I don't like it at all...
It feels so good, you're so erotic!
Who are you calling erotic? There's no way
I would let you let it out inside my-
I'm sorry, it feels too good.
Who said that you can let it out?
There won't be any data from that!
Let me do it again!
Eh... Is this me? I'm licking that penis like this...
You can't let anyone see this,
and of course that means you too!
But I've already seen the live version...
You can forget it, right now!
Here, I think you need to apply more colour
within the area of the pussy.
Hm... Then it would be better to add some
semen in here too.
Oh Momo, you've got a great, erotic scenario here.
And maybe you could add a part where the man
says that he doesn't want it, but the truth is that he really does.
That's from my experience, anyway.
Y-your experience?! As expected from Kisara-san.
S-sure.
Hm... Hm... I can't lose to them as their president.
No, it's gonna be a problem in many
ways for the president.
Kisara-san is working hard to learn as much as possible
about erotic acts.
She's sharing her erotic opinion with everyone
about their work.
This is gonna sell well, I know it.
This is going smoothly, but the scene after this would be...
Well, how is it?
My art up 'till now.
Ah... Yes, it's getting better.
With the tit fuck,
as well as the footjob.
Fellatio too.
I think you've done it all perfectly.
I hate to admit all of that we've been doing,
but I can see the result of it right now.
You say that, but the next one would be...
S-sex.
What is it? Just spit it out!
There's only the two of us in here.
Um...
I can think of what you're gonna say
from the look on your face.
Yeah...
The next one... Would be... Sex, right?
Um... You can get some data from adult videos as well.
It's okay, just do it.
Do it... That's not a simple thing to do, you know?!
What are you saying now? You've been using my body
for your masturbation all this time!
Why don't you just do it without complaining like before?!
You know that I want this game to succeed!
For that to happen, even sex is not a big deal for me.
From now on, I want more-
real experience with my body.
It's fine if you don't wanna do it,
I'll find another man to do it with me.
That's... Are you sure about doing this with me?
It's... Not like that! It's also your first time, isn't it?
That's why... It's the same... For me...
I... I understand.
Please sit here.
Eh? Wait a minute, this is for my data, so you should close your eyes.
But I can't move it properly-
There's no such thing as good or bad with the first time, right?!
Please don't say something like that when you're still a virgin!
Though you're also a virgin.
It's... Rubbing it-
The next one would be this...
So this thing's gonna be inside of me.
Kisara-san, are you afraid?
There's no way I'm gonna be afraid of this,
it's not a big deal for an adult.
That's one thing for sure.
That's enough, then... That's...
Just put it inside me... You want to, right?
Then I'm gonna put it inside, okay?
Don't ask about every little thing!
Sorry, I got it.
It's coming inside me...
It's really gonna go inside me...
Now... I've finally taken Kisara-san's virginity.
There's really blood coming out...
With your penis inside of me... I'm...
You're so deep inside.
That penis is going inside me...
Right now...
This is sex, isn't it?
Kisara-san.
It hurts-
Your penis is inside... Inside of me...
It's so tight... The penis is... Deep inside me,
it's going in and out...
So this is how a penis feels, that's fine with me...
There's nothing to worry about-
It's gonna be bad.
I'm sorry for being a virgin!
You're joking, right?
It's spreading inside of me... Hey, didn't I tell you
to say when you're gonna let it out?
S-sorry.
That really shocked me, that's why a virgin like you...
Though I'm not a virgin anymore.
Did it feel good, being inside of me?
Of course...
Then, there's no reason not to forgive you.
But, it's unfair for you to feel good by yourself.
Then, this would be okay.
Eh?
No... I'll be seen in a place like this!
My nipples shiver when they touch the cold glass...
It feels like the pain is cooling down and it feels so weird,
with all the sperm in my pussy,
I'll go crazy from this feeling!
I can feel so much love coming out from inside Kisara-san.
Th-that's a lie! I'm not perverted like that!
You have to look at yourself right now and draw that!
I can feel the hardness of your hair and
the shape of your penis inside my pussy.
I'm gonna let it all out right now,
let it out inside of you!
Let it out? You're gonna let it out again?
You're gonna let that sticky sperm out inside me?!
It's so intense... It keeps rubbing inside me...
No... NO~!!
It's coming out... So much is coming out...
It's filling me up inside...
Kisara-san, I'm going in once more.
Eh?
Please let me go... Let me take a break...
It's good to have more data, isn't it?
You're going deep inside my pussy!
It feels good!
It hurt so much the first time, but when your sperm filled me up
I couldn't think of anything but sex after that.
Your penis is rubbing inside my pussy.
It's making me so wet!
The inside of my head is filled with penis and pussy!
The way Kisara-san should draw is like this,
the way the heroine feels good from a big penis.
Kisara-san, are you ready to draw?
You've already let out a lot if it inside me...
It's fine with me, If you want to do it again, I'll be there for you.
Here I go...
Here I come, Kisara-san!
Don't move it too hard...
Coming out... Something's gonna come out!
It's coming... Coming... I can't... I can't hold it!
H-hey, there's a scene after the heroine getting raped
where she's being filled with sperm.
That would be good data, right?
That's... That's right.
My body feels hot and I can still feel
some sperm left inside of my stomach.
Are you sure you're okay?
What are you saying? We've had sex before, right?
This isn't a big deal for me...
It isn't.
It's not good, she's too cute.
Though her attitude is a bit harsh,
she doesn't want to lose to anyone.
I really like her a lot.
What should I do right now?
Should I confess it to her?
Um... The truth is, I'm...
Eh?
Don't get the wrong idea, it's not that I have feelings for you.
I'll be troubled if you take this thing seriously.
You and I are work colleagues, you got it?!
That's why I've told you before.
I... I've already warned these two.
I told them earlier than Nene-san.
IDIOT~!!!