It feels good...
SubDESU-H Presents
Maid Ane
1st Day
It's falling over towards you there!
Looks like this year's gonna be a good harvest after all.
Yeah.
Okay, let's get it finished before dark.
Then, see you tomorrow!
Sure, see you tomorrow.
Is that so? Hm...the city certainly is high class, isn't it?
It's not like that...
But, It's true...right? Even someone like me
couldn't do that.
I'm home...
Welcome home, Master.
I'm home...Aki-nee.
What was the matter with your face just then?
You're so noisy, mother.
But it's true, isn't it?
It's been a while, Yuu-kun.
Um...yes...
She said that she's working as a maid in Tokyo,
don't you think she looks lovely?
Please stop saying that, Auntie.
Don't say something like that when I'm wearing such a dress as this.
Yuu-kun as well...
You've growing up into such a sturdy man,
though you were so cute before.
That was way in the past, Aki-nee.
Anyway, why don't you take a bath already?
He's still acts like a boy to me.
I'll take one after this, don't treat me like a kid!
What're you saying, doesn't your body smell like sweat over there?
Then, Yuu-kun. Do you want to take a bath with me like we used to?
Eh?! What...are you...
Of course I was joking.
Then, I ought to be going home now.
It hurts...
My feet feel numb, guess I failed as a maid...
I'm sorry that I took so much of your time, Akie-chan.
Forgive me, okay?
Aki-nee...
You've gotten so beautiful...
How many years have past since that time?
We used to play a lot together.
Aki-nee...
Yuu-kun, what do you want to play today?
Hm...what is it?
Are you interested in my breasts?
Then...
Yuu-kun, do you...
Wanna play doctor...
With me?
Yuu-kun.
You've also had an interest in here, right?
How is it, can you see it clearly?
Here, inside too.
This is an important place for a woman.
Then this is the place where the penis goes in, okay?
Do you see that, Yuu-kun?
Hey..can you see in my thing?
Yuu-kun...Yuu-kun...Yuu-kun...
Then, I'll be home late again.
Sure, here's your lunch. Have it with everyone, okay?
Good morning, Master.
Oh, Aki-nee.
You're working today for the festival, right?
We're making a shrine pillar.
We're gonna finish it today, since it might rain tomorrow.
That's hard for you...why don't I make some lunch for you?
I already have my mother's lunch.
Is that so...then next time.
Sure, then I'm going now.
Yes, Master. Please be careful.
Hey, I've seen her before.
That's Aki-chan, right?
She's gotten beautiful after coming back from Tokyo.
But, she's wearing a weird dress.
That's a maid dress, Aki-nee is working as maid there.
Hm...I don't really get the workings of the city after all.
She doesn't have to show that dress around the village...
She even called me Master.
Okay, let's take a break for lunch!
Huh?
Aki-nee.
Good work from all of you, I've brought a pot of tea here.
Here, be careful it's still hot.
Please...
Ah, thank you.
Aki-chan, you're looking very provocative right now.
Right?
It's not like that, please don't tease me.
Hey, It's spilling over here Aki-chan.
Ah...please forgive me.
Please give me a break...
Good work, Yuu-kun.
Aki-nee, what's wrong with you?
What're you saying, It's a maid's job to serve like that.
Here, tea for you...Master.
Sure...thanks.
Then everyone, please do your best!
Sure!
Thanks for coming!
Let's get back to work then!
Hey, when are you gonna stop looking at her?
Our afternoon work is gonna start right now, Master.
Aki-nee...
Aki-nee...looks like she did in my dream last night.
No...
My Master...
Master...
More of it, Master!
What's with Aki-nee?
So...some...something like that...
Aki-nee...
What should...what should I do?
I've accidentally looked at Aki-nee's thing.
It's not working, It won't calm down.
What should I...what should I do?
More of it, Master!
My Master...
Aki-nee was saying "my Master"...
Is it possible...
She was talking about me?
Yuu-kun.
A..Aki-nee?!
Why you're dressed like that?!
Aki-nee's job is a maid, right? That's why
I've come in here to wash my Master's back.
So..so..it's true that I'm the one whom you're referring to as Master?
Yuu-kun, so you've seen me before?
Then, would you come in here?
That's...not necessary.
But, Yuu-kun...
What...what is it?
If you don't come here...
Aki-nee will feel cold down here.
Ye...yes.
How is it?
Is it getting clean enough?
Breasts...Aki-nee's breasts...
Please don't touch me like that!
Why is that, Yuu-kun? It feels good, right?
Or would you prefer to do it with this one?
D...Don't do that...
It's okay.
Great...It feels great...
Amazing, It's getting big.
Aki-nee...wait...please...wait...It's gonna come!
No, you can't. Hold it a little bit.
It's coming...It's gonna come out.
Um...Yuu-kun, then why don't you face this way?
Aki-nee...
I'll do it with my mouth for you.
It's also getting sturdy down here.
It was such a small and cute one before.
It feels like it's trembling at the tip.
You're gonna swallow it, Aki-nee...
That's amazing, you're swallowing it all.
It's gonna come out...
I'm cumming!
You've cum a lot. Does it feel good?
Yeah, It felt like it was gonna melt.
Aki-nee, I'm...
Of course.
You wanna put your penis inside of this, right?
Ye...yes.
That's...that's right...just push it in like that.
It's in...It's inside...
It's...okay...just move slowly when inside of it.
It's all the way in...Yuu-kun's penis...
It's rubbing inside of me...
Amazing...It's amazing...It's moving inside of it...
Aki-nee!
I can't...
I can't hold any longer.
You can't...you can't just come...
please come inside of me deeply.
No...It's hitting...your penis...It's hitting inside...of my womb...
Wait...
Please wait...
Sorry, Aki-nee. It feels so good and
I can't stop it.
No...no...please...please...Yuu-kun...
Cumming...It's gonna cum again.
Wait...wait...
Cu...Cumming!
Aki-nee...just a bit...just a bit longer.
Yu...Yuu-kun.
Again...
You're going inside that deep again...
The sperm is overflowing...
Yuu-kun's penis is going inside of me again...
Ye...yeah...It feels like I'm gonna cum again...
Inside of Aki-nee.
Is that so...
Cause your penis feels so good...
More...I want more-
Amazing, inside of me is going to break apart...
It feels so good!!
It's inside...It's inside all the way...
More...more...intensely-
Good...
Yuu-kun...
Cumming...gonna cum...
I'm gonna cum...
Me too...I'm cumming.
Cumming...cumming!
Did it feel good?
Yes.
Look.
There's a lot of it inside...
If I'm gonna get pregnant from this, then Yuu-kun
would be Aki-nee's true master.
Ye...yes.
Aki-nee...
Good morning, Yuu-kun.
Did you sleep well?
Working for the festival everyday should be hard for you.
A dream...
Aki-nee...I'm...
Hm...?