Although I know that everyone has a couple of skeletons in their closets...
Right now I'm about to take a bath with my father.
Miyuki! Come here, quickly!
Just wait a minute, okay?
Your body is giving off such a sweet scent!
Hey, you!
It's because it has been hot today, right?
There's a lot of sweat here, the smell is so sour!
What do you mean by that?!
You're really-
You perverted old man!
W
Triple Ecchi
Miyuki's Chapter
Hmph...
It's so indecent of him.
Ah, sorry about that, it's been a while since we took a bath together.
So I'm just...
If you do it again next time, it will also be the last time.
Hot!
You know, it's strange doing this together.
I'm not a little girl anymore.
Taking a bath with your father at this age is really embarrassing! I can't let anyone find out.
That's... That's not true! Everyone takes baths with their family!
It's just skinship!
Then why are we keeping it a secret from Mother?
Well... you see... there could be misunderstandings.
Of course there would be, since you're only my step-father.
Mother is coming home late today, right?
Yeah, she said that she is going to a school reunion.
Maybe Mother will meet her first love again...
Aren't you worried?
I dont mind, as long as I'm with you.
You've really grown up to become a beauty.
You're on another level to your mother.
Father, stop sweet talking me!
You have such lovely breasts.
It feels so good, touching your nipples like this.
You're tickling me!
But you know, we can't go on like this forever...
Eh?
I want a boyfriend and someday I want to get married...
You've got to let go of your daughter too-
Mi-yu-ki~!
Miyuki, please don't leave me!
Please don't cry, all that is a long way off...
This reminds me of that time...
Miyuki, please don't throw me away!
Okay, I won't!
Thank you so much, Miyuki!
Miyuki!
You know, this is a special treat, just for today. So this isn't going to happen again...
I understand, I just want to make some memories with you!
Although I said it wouldn't happen again...
Ah... scrubbing my back with your lovely breasts...
This is true bliss.
Alright, next, do my front.
Having my daughter clean my genitals with her breasts,
I really couldn't be happier.
You say that, but I know you're only interested in perverted things.
That's not true! It really makes me happy when I'm doing it with you.
Hmph...
What is it?
When you're doing that, you look like a baby.
Is that so? But, you know, babies don't suck this way.
Here you go.
Don't do that to my nipples!
Your nipples are really sensitive, right?
I was right before, you really are a perverted old man!
It's beautiful.
You're already wet, aren't you?
Idiot, don't say things like that!
You haven't changed one bit! I'm so glad.
Today, I'm going to make love to you for even longer!
No...
If you do something like that...
If you start licking it... I'm going to-
The juices coming out of you are so sour.
I can't stop myself drinking it!
No...
I'm going to lose my head...
Miyuki.
Come over here.
OK...
You're really going to put it inside me?
You promised! I was really looking forward to this, you know?
Although it's the third time I've done pervered things with my father, it's the first time he has penetrated me without a condom.
I can't hold back from your raw pussy.
It's going inside of me...
We're actually doing it...
Miyuki...
You're not gonna move it?
Hm... sure, but I want to stay like this for a second.
I want to remember this.
Is it possible that you're about to cum already?
How is it? Does it feel good?
He-hey... Miyuki-
I can feel it throbbing. It feels so good.
Stop... stop... if you do that, I'm really going to-
No can't do.
This is punishment for a father who likes to taste his daughter's pussy.
I'm going to rub it around inside of me!
Mi.. Miyuki...
But, when you're doing it without a condom, it feels totally different.
I can't hold it, I'm going to cum too!
So, you're going to cum? Then just let it out!
Father...
I can feel my father's thing, going in and out of me.
Doing it like this is so much better!
Miyuki.
You're sucking on my breasts, whilst hitting my womb!
Don't thrust like that! You can't let it out into my womb!
Inside...
It feels like my womb is going to melt!
Miyuki... I'm gonna let it like this, okay?
No, please don't do it inside me...
Why? You promised that you'd let me cum inside you today.
That's true, but I'm afraid!
It's not safe...
I might get pregnant, that's why!
Please don't cum inside me!
Me and Miyuki's child...
No way! Why are you suddenly thrusting like this?
Miyuki's child... Miyuki's child...
No...
I can feel your penis getting stiff inside my pussy!
I won't forgive you if you cum inside of me!
No... it's hitting deeper!
Miyuki, I'm gonna cum!
No, pull it out! Pull your penis out!
No~!!!
No! I'm gonna get pregnant!
Hmph... you're terrible, I told you not to cum inside of me.
So-sorry about that, Miyuki. I was trying to pull it out,
but it just wouldn't come out.
You're such a bad liar. I know that kind of thrust was meant to make me pregnant.
So-sorry! It's true, I'm really sorry!
After that, I've had raw sex with my father countless times...
Even though I said I wouldn't.
No...
Don't lick inside of my pussy...
It feels strange...
But if he licks me for over 30 minutes, I would give in...
Even me...
It won't calm down!
I can't hold it anymore!
Give me your penis!
Please put your penis inside of my raw pussy!
Hm... Miyuki, didn't you say I couldn't do it in your pussy without a condom anymore?
I want it raw...
I don't want a condom!
I won't let you put it inside with a condom on!
Mi-Miyuki!
Miyuki... Miyuki!
Father, your tip is so deep inside! It's too much!
No~!!!
From that day on, I let him cum inside whenever he wanted...
We did it all the time.
What should we do?! I'm really pregnant, after all!
If we don't do something, my stomach will start getting big, and people may find out!
Why are you worrying about that?
If you're pregnant, then we could do it without a condom as many times as we want!
No, wait-
It's spilling out!
Mikyuki's milk is so tasty!
No~!
I'm going to put it inside of your womanly pussy.
Your milk is making it so slippery.
Idiot~!
Miyuki, I'm going to cum! Where should I release it?
No way...
Outside...
Hm? What did you say? Inside?
That's not...
It's not...
How many times has his penis kissed my womb?
I feel so bad, but I can't resist it anymore.
Just let it out inside of me!
Hold me tightly and let it out!
Miyuki!
You always finish off inside of me...
So much milk squirted out.
Well then, after cumming inside of you,
I'll replenish myself with your milk!
Ah~ you really are a stupid father!
Indeed...
Idiot Father...