I'll be waiting...
So please stay in contact with me!
Sorry about last night...
That person is the cameraman who's helping out with the advertising campaign.
However, sometimes he can be a bit persuasive...
But he's not a bad person!
He's just the type who's easily misunderstood.
Go on!
He's here!
Hurry up!
SubDESU-H
I have to get up early, and sometimes I come home late.
So since I entered this school, I've been allowed to use the outhouse freely.
Over there, Mikiyo-san!
Did you see it?
Chii... I mean, young hostess...
It's about the night I came back...
... And he said that he was sore there, so we ended up going, and guess what?
They were selling those sweets that were in the magazine!
Oh really?
They were so cute!
And when I tried eating them...
Geez, it's your fault, Mikiyo-san.
I got a bit flustered.
And...
Please call me Chitose when we're alone!
I ended up not asking her...
Hey! What are you doing?
Please stop!
T-That guy!
You're nice...
Don't!
Don't you think she has a nice body?
Her breasts might be even larger than Young Hostess'!
She has nice hips, too...
I want to strip her naked!
Grab that big ass, and do her from behind!
Oh well.
If I asked her about that night,
I wonder if it would be over between us...?
Why? With that guy?!
Chii-chan...
Young Hostess? Are you awake?
I'm sorry, I slept in...
Understood. It shall be arranged like so.
I can't leave it like this...
Young Hostess still seems to be asleep.
Hello? This is Chitose.
Sorry to call you so early in the day.
You're too held back about these things, Mikiyo-san.
I'm fine with you calling me anytime.
It's because Nakai-san said you were still asleep, so...
I'll come out in a sec, okay?
Sorry, I just put on what I could find, but maybe this is too inappropriate?
That's a strange shirt...
It looks like a man's...
Don't tell me it's his-?!
Oh? You're finished talking to him?
He hung up saying it wasn't important...
Hey-! Why am I telling you this?
Apparently guys that converse quickly only have simple sex.
Could you wear this?
I wonder if he can satisfy you...
Since you're so lewd, Chii-chan.
I can't wear such a thing during work!
But you were wearing it when you went to school.
I've seen you.
Don't be mistaken!
I heard that men who get like this in the morning have a hard time.
That's why I want this to end so that I can quickly go to work!
What's the meaning of this?
Getting me to change into this so suddenly, what are you-?
No-!
I wanted to confirm what you said before.
Did you say that your boyfriend chose it for you?
Jeez... You didn't let me finish down here, that's why it's...
It's hot...
For a nasty person like you, being your sex friend is enough.
*S-Sex friend?!*
I won't tell my boyfriend, either.
T-That's-! I'm sensitive there-!
C'mon, let's see that tongue.
So, I guess you admit that we're sex friends...
Putting on such a lewd face...
Do you crave the taste of this already?
It was right after you saw off your boyfriend too!
Was that the Young Hostess
who was so lewd that she opened her legs wide when I kissed you?
It's okay.
I don't mind if you're an easy woman. I'm fine with it!
I-I'm not that kind of woman!
Don't! If we do it now, it'll crumple my uniform!
Isn't it fine? Why don't you tell them this?
"We make love every day in my school uniform."
Let's show off for your classmates and that other guy!
You're going to cum, huh? Your pussy is throbbing!
I-I'll break like this! I'm gonna die if we keep going-!
Amazing! That feels too good-! No more!
Then are you going to tell your classmates?
E-Everyone already knows!
E-Everyone knows that I'm like your girlfriend!
They kept interrogating me!
You said that you were my girl, didn't you?
That's because we've already had sex!
We've already done it, haven't we?
I'm too sensitive to pleasure... But I really like it!
You like me? Do you like me that much?
I-I don't!
I-I have someone I like-!
The only good thing about you is your body!
I-It's just your cock!
Apart from that, I hate you! But-!
But it feels so good!
You're so mean!
Getting me aroused like this and making me do things.
You've made me remember such pleasure!
Your expression is nice, Chitose.
I can't get enough!
N-No more! I'm gonna go crazy!
S-Something is coming! I'm gonna cum!
My pussy is getting too pleased with your thick cock inside of it!
N-No, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
No-! I'm gonna cum!!
You've calmed down, huh?
Have you had enough?
No, I can still keep going...
I still have some time before work, so...
So...
Sorry about being so late...
Are you finished?
He was with you, wasn't he?
All I know is that I walked past someone.
You like him, don't you?
No need to restrain yourself.
I-I can't do that!
I'm the hostess here!
And...