Reijoku no Yakata
Part 1
W
Jounouchi
Residence
Tsubame-sama, as I remember I cleaned your room just three days ago.
I don't remember that.
My life-style doesn't have a night and day,
so I don't feel the day, it can't be...
It can't be helped.
Eh? Shunchin is so scary.
Aside from that... Hey, can I?
Really, you can't be helped.
Same goes for you too, Shunchin.
When I do it with Shunchin... It's like...
I feel good quicker.
Like I am a virgin.
Amazing... touch my pussy too...
No... just your finger...
I'm... cumming..
No... I'm cumming..
cumming.. cumming..
cumming..
I'm cumming!
You know, Shunich's easily goes up to my cervix,
so when you put it in...
NO!
Not yet... If you pull it out...
It will rub my clit...
Your dick is pushing...
I can't pull it out and I can't put it in...
So what should I do then?
N-No... I want both, but...
Please... please wait a bit longer...
Because, it's so good it will be a waste if we don't do it slowly... ah...
But... I can't hold it you know.
Shunchin, you're really mean.
You're doing me this intensely.
If I'm penetrated like this...
I can't speak about love.
Love?
What are you saying?
Shunchin, you're really overreacting.
You know, I don't desire that...
Just... It's just...
I wanted to see your reaction when I said that.
Then...
Let's continue to have sex just for our pleasure.
The thing that benefits both of us...
If you're doing this for your pleasure,
I think this "box style" suits us more than a human relationship?
Maybe... so...
Like primitives...
Dogs can't speak!
You don't have to be strict.
Ouch... no...
Don't...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
Why Shunchin... why...?
Tsubame-sama, did you cum when I spanked you?
You're really like a dog.
Shunchin, you're really a villain.
You didn't cum with me.
It's like I'm being experimented on by Shunchin.
I haven't cum yet though.
No... this time really...
I just came a while ago.
I'm still sensitive.
Noooo!!
Round two!
Shunchin's is still inside me.
And it's about to flow out...
You know, Shunchin is cool but sometimes your evil side comes out.
It's easy to understand that I must not judge you on your appearance.
What are you aiming for?
What do you think?
Hmm... let's see...
Like the entire Jounouchi family?
Bingo.
I think it's alright.
I'll give it to Shunchin.
But you're not the head of the family.
Then why don't we try to use Shizuru-neesan, the head of the family?
Approaching her to become a successor of her deceased husband?
I'll help you out.
My, my...
What are you aiming for?
I don't have any target.
It's just I'm in love with Shunchin.
My work went smoothly... Just to be with you...
I want to help you as repayment.
Well, maybe I can be inspired by Shunchin's picaresque story though.
For me, those are important to me.
You're trying to use your real sister in exchange for means of making a living.
You're really a bad person.
Shun... don't let yourself be carried away or else...
You'll be tripped up.
So, Tomoe-neesan are you telling me that you'll show your loyalty,
and report to the Jounouchi family that,
Shun is a dangerous man?
How foolish.
It's just my opinion.
Knowing that the key to this family is those five sisters,
It's not that you'll succeed if you hold those girls.
Oh? Are you worried about me?
When Shun becomes number one,
they will do something good with my employment agreement right?
That's why.
Well, let's see about that.
No.
I will let you try your best.
Yes, your best.
Good morning, Rei-sama.
Good Morning.
That night...
Shizuru-sama.
Please do it properly, use your mouth.
Good Shizuru-sama...
I'm so happy that you suck my dick this hard.
Is it since your husband is gone?
That you want to suck a dick...
Don't talk about him.
You remained faithful to him.
I think it's pitiful, to do something like that...
But, even you can't fight your body,
if you do some playing on your own...
Darling...
So I was watched...
Yes. I saw the indecent Shizuru-sama with my own eyes.
You noticed the gaze right?
That's why you got that lewd.
Then, please do the rest.
Good...
I'm about to cum...
Shun-kun, it's great.
If I accept it with my body... I...
It went in smoothly even though you're satisfying yourself everyday.
It's not that I was satisfying myself...
Shun-kun's...
The tip of your dick is touching the end...
I feel it touching inside your pussy.
Not there...
It's coming to the opening of the cervix..
No... no...
Don't thrust that much....
The tip of your dick...
This feeling...
It's the first time...
I see...
Your husband wasn't any good...
Don't talk about him...
I loved him, really.
But Shizuru-sama wasn't satisfied even with that feeling.
No... No... No... No...
If you thrust in my womb that much...
I can't hold it...
It... hurts...
Ouch...
Even if you say that...
Shun-kun, stop doing that...
Something like that...
Shizuru-san...
You're cute.
But I won't be easy on you.
Because I'm doing this for you.
No... Shun-kun... stop...
It's painful..
But...
Those painful things make you happy, right?
That's not true...
Is that so?
Anyway, I don't intend to stop though.
Shun-kun...
I know what Shizuru-san needs...
Something like this...
No way...
Because... If I don't do this...
You can't cum because you feel like you're betraying him right?
So good.
Thick dick..
I'm being stirred by Shun-kun's dick...
Your dick is rubbing and...
I'm cumming...
My stomach is getting hot...
It's making dirty sounds...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming..!
Shun-kun...
What is it?
Thank you...
Even though I'm an old woman...
It's alright.
The other night
The tea will get cold.
I'll pour it for you.
No!
Hina will pour it.
You're saying... you prepared this for me to drink?
I learned how to make a delicious tea.
I want Shun-san to drink it.
I called you for that reason...
I see.
Then, since you want to do it, please go ahead.
H-Here...
Thank you so much.
Uhm.. How is it?
Is the tea delicious?
It's fine...
It's delicious.
Sheesh... you're really cruel Shun-san!
Sorry, did I take the joke too far?
Oh... no, me too, I said too much.
No...
Shun-san...
Stop it...
This kind of thing...
No..
I don't want this...
You want me to stop?
But I know Hina-sama is interested in something like this, right?
No I'm not.
Yes you are.
If you're not, you wouldn't have watched the act between Shizuru-san and me right?
So you noticed.
Yes.
So I'm doing this to Hina-sama too.
Oh... it's big...
It's alright... I'll let you get used to it slowly.
Y-Yes...
Then, try touching it.
It's hot.
It's alright.
Continue.
Y-Yes.
Wow... It's throbbing..
Yes. Hina-sama's hands feels so good.
Next, try moving your hands up and down.
Ok..
It seems you're too nervous...
Try to enjoy doing it.
Ok, I understand.
Yes, good, it's good.
Please stop for a while.
Eh? Did I do something bad?
No, I don't mean that.
I want you to do it with your mouth next.
W-With my...
Mouth?
Then let's stop here.
Eh? W-Why?
You can't suck it, right?
So let's stop here.
No way...
Uhm... Can I ask for a favor?
What is it?
Please be Hina's... Be only Hina's Shun-san!
Sure.
If Hina-sama wishes for that.
How foolish.
Then here I go.
Ok.
Shun-san's is getting bigger.
Hina-sama, I'm going to release it!
It all came out.
Please drink it Hina-sama.
You drank it, right? Thank you so much.
Next, it's my turn.
No...
Hina-sama, you got horny while licking mine, right?
No I'm not...
Is that so?
How weird.
I need to see it directly.
No...!
No!!!
It's embarrassing.
As I thought you're already like this.
No!
You...
What's with him?
Hina-neechan is mine...
She's mine yet...
Shun-san... you can't...
If you do that much.
Hina will cum.
Hina-neechan... she's already...
If I see that.. I'll... I'll...
I'll cum quicker.
No...
Hina... Hina....
Will cum...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!!
Hina-neechan came.
Me too, me too, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...
I'll cum together with you....
Hina... Shun-san is drinking my pee.
Shun-san is... Shun-san is really only Hina's.
Tsugumi... the reason I set up this surveillance system...
Is not to peep on Hina.
Do you understand?
Why are you letting that man do what he wants to Hina-neechan?
If you combine my system with the anti-crime device, then he'll...
Tsugumi too, don't misunderstand.
That is what Hina wants.
Above all, Hina is not Tsugumi's.
Or do you want Hina know that Tsugumi peeked...
I get it!
Listen.
This is what we need.
Take this into your heart.
Are you thinking that you're about to bury them?
There's some stinging words in your sentence.
Are you saying you're jealous because I didn't entertain you?
Don't make a fool of me.
Why would I...
Hmm?
Shun, it seems you're ok with plunging Shizuru down,
but don't you think that the detached room is the center of this family?
Detached room?
What is in the detached room?
To be continued...