Within a short time, you'll achieve your dream.
That's what this oracle glass ball said to me.
You're slowly getting to understand,
what it means to be released.
Anyway, that super model...
She's got good composition on both her breasts,
also her eye-shot is filled with lascivious feelings.
She's always on a pinch time, to hide her own secret.
How about I use her and make a holy release with that?
Ichinose Anna's Agonizing Cries Chapter
W
Did Onee-chan and I really come from the same blood?
We've got difference in our body and style.
Even though I'm walking inside the
same path Onee-chan took...
When I'm working on my job,
they always talk about Onee-chan.
The one who's standing in here is Anna.
It isn't Riko.
Anna-san.
Eh?!
It's..Err...
You've got the eyes of a worried person.
Onee-chan, doesn't know how I feel...
How she's gonna know... about it...
It's in here, right?
To achieve your happiness, you've come to me
for your self-release, right?
E..Eh, self-release?
Anna-san, I see that you have some difficult
problem in the charm of your shoulder.
You've got a hard life by your shoulder's
charm in your body, isn't?
But then again, you've got some complex matter
with something that make the reason of your's.
Am I wrong about that?
No, you're right about that.
Why do you know about that?
I got a dream that I have to walk the path
which Onee-
which my sister walked in the past.
I can't be completely perfect without her appearence.
Even though I'm joining a model
office with Onee-chan's help...
The one who people admire is only my sister, Riko.
My presence for the ordinary thing
is only the little sister of Riko.
Anna-san.
Yes.
Anna-san, do you like being a model?
Yes, I really like it. Even though now
I'm just an ordinary gravure idol...
Having fans and a lot of mail from them,
gave me more strength to move on.
Then now, I want you to pose like you're
at your photo session.
Eh?
Why?
That's how we will connect with your self-release.
And that would be...
You don't have to understand it right now.
But that's the only way, to make your
complex problem disappear.
You're gonna pose, right?
Yes...
More boldness!!
Like how you want your ambition
to come true!
As I thought, Anna-san is...
You don't really understand about
your own charm, isn't it?
That's... That's something I don't have!
Anna-san, do you want to exceeds your sister?
That's... something...
I want it too...
Would you like to receive my guide?
Yes.
Take care of me.
Come in, please.
Anna is...
This is...
What's going to start after this?
You don't have to be afraid.
We're making preparation to make ourself
get self-release with each other.
Zenko-sama, is it okay?
No...
Let's start it.
No~!!
Now, you shall feel it and release it all.
Why don't we start with your clothes?
No! Stop it!!
No..No-No~!
Please, don't look at it!
No, don't touch me there...
No...
Now, quickly accept us, it's for your own good.
Oh? This fluid came out before
we even got some release...
Anna-san,  you're...
Eh?
No..you can't..do that,
don't take it off~!!
You're really pervert, aren't you?!
No, don't look at it! You can't look at it!
Anna-chan, why don't you calm down?
You want to exceeds your sister's presence, right?
What a beautiful body and lovely breast...
I can't hold it!
You can't... lick over it...
As I expected of the dirty bitch, Anna-chan,
you know what it takes to release.
I don't know something like that.
Is that so... Then I'll release that from your mouth.
Zenko-sama, the preparation is complete.
Bring her here!
Eh?!
No..no..I beg you...
Any more than this... is impossible.
Anna-san, you don't have to worry about anything.
I'll take the rest of your heart from here,
You just have to let your strenght out and feel the release
which we're gonna start after this.
No..I don't want it...
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry, I don't want to exceed Onee-chan any more!
That's why... that's why... help me, Onee-chan~!!
Then Anna-chan, why don't you accept Zenko-sama's guide
and take the holy release within you.
Anna-san's naked body is unbelievable,
especially your wicked breasts...
No..you can't...
touch it...
Before we start it, I'll let you release with this.
No... you can't... stop licking it,
I beg you...
My nipples are getting hard...
Your lovely pussy...
It's drenched this much.
It looks different from the shape
of the ones in the animes...
Zenko-sama, It's about the time...
Anna-san, with my penis connected with you,
in a short time you're going to fully release.
Connected...?
You don't...
No... you can't... I'm...
I don't have any experience doing that...
Tha-that's why... I'm a virgin!!
Please, stop it! Stop-
Anna-san, after this you're going to realise on your
own the charm inside you!
No~! You can't... you can't do it!
More than this is... please...
This can't be stopped, Anna-san.
No... It's going inside...
More that that is... It's gonna tear apart!
I'm gonna break apart...
No~!!!
It hurts...
It's gonna rip apart... stop it...
It's really gonna break...
Why don't you put yours inside of Anna-san's mouth.
I... I understand.
How is it, did you feel the pleasure already?
Don't be motionless, use your tongue.
That's... That's the way it is.
This is bad, Zenko-sama... I can't hold...
I don't mind it, release it out!
Thank... Thank you very much.
It's been a while, Anna-chan
since I felt this satisfied on release.
Now way... It can't be... It's dirty...
Then, just a little bit more Anna-san!
It hurts... No- don't move...
Why is it so hot...
My inside is gonna tear apart... I'm gonna go crazy...
Anna-san, that pain it's an important thing
in releasing it with me.
You do understand it, right?
I'm gonna release it soon.
No, pull it off!
You can't release it inside. No~!!
Release!!
How is it, Anna-san?
Did you feel that the limit
in your heart has been broken?
With a look like that, I see that you haven't
fully received self-release within you.
Anna-san, why don't you bring yourself here next week
and we'll do more with your self-release.
Anna-san, just a little bit more.
Just throw your worry away,
and get the truth of release.
I'll make you more brighter than anyone.
I want to exceed Onee-chan.
Anna-san, I've been waiting for those words.
I can't make you feel the truth of self-release
without you wanting it yourself.
I'll work harder...
I understand, let's enter the boarding course
next week from now.
Boarding course?
Please take care of me.
Is the preparation okay?
The one that we're gonna do right now,
will surely change your future.
I'll let you experience many ways of release after this.
Ye-Yes...
If you can just overcome all of that,
you're gonna be have more charming than your sister,
and more confidence with yourself.
R-Really?
But, if you don't listen to what I say or if you
even disagree with my guidance,
If I don't...
You'll lose your existence as a human!
What are you doing?!
I'm just helping you.
That's of course, for your own self-release.
That's not needed.
Why should I do it with you?
If you'll always keep that attitude, then I suppose
I'll change your next course...
I... I understand.
T-Take care of me.
Then, shall we begin with accepting
our release with your body.
What... what are you...
It feels good, Sakaki-san.
It's out-
It stinks!
Then Sakuma-san, please accept it.
Wait- what?!
It's for the release.
Please drink it.
I can't... With this dirty thing.
It's delicious, okay!
That's enough, then I want you to lick all over this.
I'll do it. I just have to do it, right!?
Eh, again?
You're still being yourself.
If you want to pass your limit,
you must depend on the others and you can't
let your heart waver for anything.
Then, Anna-san...
Let the hell boarding course begin!!
Anna-san, let's decide your resolution!
That's a good look, Sakuma-san.
If you don't use your tongue, It won't be cleaned up.
That's good, that's the way.
I released it again. It felt good.
Then...
Why don't you drink all of that
inside your mouth?
Sakuma-san, If you drink a man's sperm like this
it will make your heart break free.
Or is it that you wanna come
back to the general course?
Wh-Why should I?
But that girl...
She's going to feel something more horrible than this.
It stinks...
Anna-chan, you're a lewd one.
The real ones are the lowest.
I'm sorry.
Anna-san, I feel good condition in you
from your women's liquid.
It's gonna be complete soon.
N-No...
You've got yourself a delicious body, is it?
No... please, stop it.
It hurts!
Don't bite on my nipple!
Fusion with me will be your path to your self-release.
Then, shall we together release the holy nature!
Please wait!
No~!
No... No, you can't!
It's feel tight!
It hurts... please don't put it inside!
Anna-san's inside is climbing up on my penis!
Anna-chan, why don't you make us
feel good with your hand?
Grab it tightly.
No, I don't want to!
Even if it's real, I'm feeling excited.
My penis is already thumping around.
I can't stand enough of your face.
You can't look at it...
Please don't look at it.
Don't do something like that to me!
Anna-san, are you feeling ashamed?
But, you can't do it without being seen right?
Being seen is the job of a gravure idol!
I don't want to been seen in this appearance.
I don't have any confidence...
If you move any more...
There... There... Until Anna-san worries is gone,
why don't you get some confidence in that.
No... No...!
Majima Sensei.
Anna-chan's breasts are shaking around like a balloon.
I'm gonna cum from just looking at.
Her woman's liguid is drenched a lot
along with Zenko-sama's penis.
Amazing, the sound of that drenched liquid
is really erotic!
Anna-chan is really erotic~!
Don't look... please don't look.
Looking like this...
I don't want to be looked at!
I can't hold it anymore,
I'll let it out, Anna-chan.
I'll spread it all over your body.
I'm gonna cum too.
Me too... Anna-chan... Anna-chan...
Erotic Anna-chan!
No-!
You can't~!
No... I feel like I'm in a mess, it feels nasty.
Why... Why should it be like-
Even an old-man like me,
want to move my hips like this.
It's only for you, Anna-san.
For me...
That's right, It's for your own confidence.
For something substantively like that,
look at my penis.
My penis is hard as a steel post.
Yes, It's really hard.
These people are excited by you,
that's the proof that you have
your charm inside of you.
I have charm within me?
Please more beautifully, I think my penis
really understands you.
Now, do you already feel your confidence?
No, I don't really want it after all...
Please stop it...
Is that so, but your pussy feels more wet than before.
Lie... That's a lie!
I don't feel wet... I'm sure I'm not drenched!
I never lie about myself.
Anna-san's pussy is drenched a lot
and it's slowly self-released by yourself.
It's a lie.
To feel drenched by something like this...
It's got to be a lie!
But...
Even though my body rejects it, I can't stop it.
Even though I don't accept it,
somehow I know it.
My pussy is gonna be something amazing...
No... I don't want it anymore...
Majima Sensei, I beg you, please stop it!!
Anna-san, why don't you tell me
what masturbation is?
Something like that... suddenly... why-
No... please stop Majima Sensei's big penis...
It's for opening the door, so I can't.
No... I can't... It's impossible...
Onee-chan, help me!!
It'll rip apart!
Feeling what a man desires will surely connect
to bring your own self-release, Sakuma-san.
With something like this, there's no way
I could have myself-
That's right. It's true as you said.
If I don't do it more intense, it can't be released.
Then, I shall get serious!
There... there... there...!
Wait... stop it... stop it!
It's too big inside of it...
It's too strong...
If it's Sakuma-san, I don't think this level
will be enough for you.
Please accept it quickly!
Did you already feel it?
Then shall we release it!
It can't be... again?!
Wait... Don't... Please don't let it out inside~!
You don't have to worry, with this kind of act
it should bring release within you.
Too intense...
It's coming!
It has come.
Please accept it!
Don't do it inside!
No... you can't~!!
Release!!
It came... It came inside.
No...
Inside of Sakuma-san's really feels warm
and it feels good.
That's... inside of me...
I don't want to get pregnant!
Don't do it inside~!
Onee-chan...
Help me...
I'm not gonna say it, something
embarrassing like that...
Then will you say it if... there... there...
No!
No... no don't!
I'll say it.
I'll say it...
I'm...
I masturbate while thinking of Onee-chan's boyfrend!
My, Anna-chan is really a bad little sister.
Do you want to sleep with your sister's boyfriend?
As I thought animation is better.
It won't betray you.
It's a secret that no one should know...
An awful little sister...
Right, I'm no good and an awful little sister...
Right... That's right, I'm really an awful little sister!
But, Onee-chan is...
Onee-chan is... Onee-chan is...
She's too perfect for me to beat her!
I'm...
I don't want Onee-chan's thing to get dirty...
Anna?
Anna~!!
Anna-chan, I'll go once again.
Anna...
Onee-chan?
I finally won against Onee-chan.
Anna...
The only one in this world...
My one and only cute...
Little sister...