www.SubDESU-H.net
Why did I have to catch a cold right after having sex?
Yano-san.
Class President-san?
Fukuhara, it's Fukuhara Shinobu.
Do you have a moment?
Hey, Yano-san, are you going out with Igawa-kun?
It's impossible for me and Igawa-kun to have that kind of relationship!
You're right, he's such a idiot.
I'm absent half the time and don't have any friends,
so that's why Igawa-kun talks to me sometimes.
Really, that's all.
I wonder if that's all it is...
You know, I've always been with Igawa-kun ever since we were kids.
I know quite a bit about him.
Actually, a lot.
Um, does Fukuhara-san love Igawa-kun?
Yes, I've loved him for a long time. I really love Igawa.
How about you?
I...
No, no, no. I really don't have any special feelings for him.
Yes, I think he's kind and a good guy,
but I don't think that I love him or anything like that.
I will support your love, Fukuhara-san.
Are you sure about that?
It has nothing to do with being sure or not.
I think Fukuhara-san and Igawa-kun are a good match.
That reminds me,
there will be an event at the Anime shop in the front of the station this weekend.
I think Igawa-kun likes that stuff,
so how about inviting him?
Part 2
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Even if it's
a little rotten,
it's delicious
isn't it?
Part 2
W
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming. I'm gonna cum... Igawa-kun.
I'm...
c-cumming!
What's this? Even though I came, I don't feel pleased.
I don't feel right. I feel rotten inside.
Why did I say that to her?
First, sexual desire, then food desire...
Oh, I'm so simple.
I think I'm gonna go buy some food at the convenience store.
Igawa-kun? Why are you here?
I thought you were with Fukuhara-san today?
How did you know that? We were together a while ago.
She said she wanted to know more about Anime and games,
so I told her to come to your house,
but she went home because she remembered some appointment.
Wha—I can't believe you!
How dare you invite her to another girl's house while on a date with her!
It wasn't a date.
You know, she loves you Igawa-kun.
Go home and apologize to Fukuhara-san!
Why are you mad?
I'm not mad!
Are you crying?
I'm not crying.
No, you look like a wreck and I don't understand if you are angry or crying!
It's okay if you don't understand; I'm just an otaku anyway.
And a moody and boring one too!
I'm dumb even though I'm a girl with glasses,
and I'm a pretty useless girl!
A lewd one too!
I know... I know I'm just a...
I love you. Please go out with me.
Yes...
Okay!
Oh... I feel relieved.
My uneasy feeling is gone.
What's this?
What do you mean? This is what happened: I confessed and you said yes.
Now we live happily ever after.
Isn't that backwards?
Backwards?
Usually, don't you confess before kissing and then move from there?
Is that so?
Anyway, that settles that.
I feel like I've been tricked...
On second thought, that one doesn't count.
Let's do it again properly!
Igawa-kun, I like you.
I love you.
I won't pass you on to another girl.
I love you so much.
You want to take back what you said?
Last time I said I didn't have any special feelings for Igawa-kun.
But the truth is, I'm...
Wait!
You know, I figured it out when I saw Igawa's stupid face.
Didn't I tell you that we've had a long relationship?
The last time I asked you, I wanted to know if you were serious or not,
so I'm a bit pissed off you lied to me.
Um... I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize, because thanks to you, I've made my decision too.
Isn't it obvious?
I've felt this way for too long to give him up so easily to some dummy girl with glasses.
I'm not so simple that I'll just say, "Here you go!"
That being said, if you are careless I will steal him from you, let's get along!
I-I'll take you on.
Welcome, Igawa-kun!
Hel-lo.
Fukuhara-san? Why are you here?
We accidentally met on the street,
and she said she'd come with me when I told her I was coming to your house.
So I came along. I'll be intruding, in ways more than one...
You know, it's a holiday, but...
we're healthy teenagers, so why are we staying in the house and watching Anime?
It's all good, since it doesn't cost anything.
We'll do many things after we're done watching it, right Igawa-kun?
Oh, is that so? Ha-ha-ha, I think I'm thirsty.
Oh, as a present, I brought some drinks.
Japanese Sake?!
Why would a student like you bring Japanese Sake to your friend's house?
It's best to drink this while sharing our problems.
What a nice way of drinking...
I was called Megu-chan the Intense, back when I was a kid.
C-Can I go home?
You go buy some snacks!
Yes!
Argh... this is annoying!
Remember when you were a kid? You said you'd be my husband?!
But now, you've fallen for this filthy girl with glasses who came out of nowhere.
Are you listening? It's you I'm talking about, you stupid Igawa!
I'm sorry. Forgive me. I can't drink anymore.
What's that? You can't drink because of me?
Hey, don't meddle with other people's boyfriends!
What's with the "boyfriend" rant? I don't accept it.
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?!
What's this, you ask? It's a kiss between lovers. You got a problem?
So what if it's a kiss? Even I can do that...
What are you doing?!
What's this, you ask? It's an intimate fellatio moment between lovers.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
It's not love! It's weird!
I can't believe it! What are you thinking?
You're not an animal,
and even if you're lovers, you shouldn't do it in front of people.
You're just perverted!
I'm not perverted.
I'm lewd.
That's stupid.
It's totally stupid.
Your penis is so good.
Yano...
Igawa-kun likes being squeezed by breasts, right?
Do you wanna try it, Fukuhara-san?
Igawa-kun's penis is so delicious.
You are stupid for doing something like that!
If it's just touching...
Igawa-kun's weakness is this nerve bundle.
There's...
Does it hurt?
No... it's just...
Is this ejaculate?
Is it okay to suck that?
Here you go!
No way, I swallowed it. I swallowed Igawa's sperm.
See? Isn't it delicious?
I don't know, but I feel dizzy and excited.
Note : Yes, Ejaculate contains testosterone which stimulates a girl's sex drive, too.
I felt strange as well which makes me wonder...
Is there some drug mixed in Igawa-kun's sperm?
Are you stupid?
Igawa-kun, look here. Fukuhara-san's pussy is so amazing.
Don't look at it, stupid!
Shinobu, you don't have any hair here.
No, don't look at it!
No!
No, it's dirty...
No...
I am kinda envious...
Igawa-kun... me too.
Yano... I'm going to put it in.
Yes...
No way... that thick thing went into her pussy, to the root, it's amazing.
It's amazing!
It's coming out.
It's hot.
It was so good, but the more I move, the more sake spreads into my body.
Wha—Shinobu?!
Igawa's is still big enough.
Igawa, me too. I want it, want it... inside of me!
You sure it's okay, Shinobu?
It's okay since I love you too.
You can do it as much you like.
Shinobu!
Igawa... amazing. This is...
It's amazing...
Love... I love you...
Love it...
I love you!
I also love him too!
Yano!
You can't!
I love him more!
Igawa-kun...
Igawa...
I'm...!
The finger...
The finger is rubbing inside me...
Oh boy... I'm about to cum!
Is your sperm going to come out?
It's alright, let it inside...
You can...
...release it.
What a great ejaculation...
It's pumping inside me...
How was Igawa-kun's taste?
No, I can't. This is too good...
Here we go...
Then it's my turn next.
Eh? Wait... please stop. I can't do it anymore...
Please do it to me again.
Eh?!
My, my... Fukuhara-san has also become a slave to the penis.
I can't help it. It really felt too good.
I was thinking, we should stop fighting over him.
You're right.
So I have a suggestion.
Why not share it, instead of fighting over him?
That's a good idea.
Is that so?
What is this, am I just a penis to my childhood friend and my girlfriend?
What are you saying? These two cute and sexy girls are so in love with you.
Be thankful and let us have more and more wild sex, or else you'll be punished.
For now, we will take him on alternate weekdays, and we'll have threesomes on the weekends.
That's a good idea!
Please give me a break!
www.SubDESU-H.net