Oh, you're here!
Captain has already left, though.
She looked a bit tired.
That's why let's...
Have stretch time together!
Although, all we're going to do is stretch individually.
Oh, let's start stretching while we're still warm!
First, open your legs like this, and then reach to your left.
Then reach to the right, like this!
Finally, we'll stretch in the middle, like this!
When you first start, you're not as flexible, so you won't be able to do it like me.
However, if you keep at it,
you can become very flexible!
But start by doing what you can.
Get ready...
Go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Okay! We're going to go again!
Go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Okay then, we're doing it for the last time!
Go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
That was good!
There are a lot of variations to this stretch.
Close your legs,
and do something like this, too.
Try doing these stretches in various pattens.
When you become flexible, you are less prone to injury.
So make sure you do it everyday!
Now for the second stretch.
Umph!
Hold your legs and bring them in,
then hold that position while you're on your back.
We're gonna keep hold this for ten seconds in sets of three!
Okay! Are you ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten~!
Take a breather.
This type of stretch works on your back and hips.
Now for the second set.
Are you ready?
Go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
That feels like being a bug on its back, doesn't it?
Let's begin the last one!
Okay, go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
We're finished!
Okay, next is neck twisting!
Change directions when we get to five, okay?
Are you ready?
Go!
One, two, three, four, five-there!
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
Okay, we're going again!
Go!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a... breather...
Okay! Last time!
Go!
One, two, three, four, five-there!
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
We're... finished...
Let's finish up by taking deep breaths, okay?
Upsy daisy...
Inhale deeply-!
Exhale...
Inhale lightly-!
Inhale deeply-!
Exhale...
Inhale lightly-!
Thanks for watching today!
Oh yeah,
keep this a secret, but...
Did you know that Captain Hiyoko always asks me "When will that 3D person come by?"
Lucky you!
For you to win over the hearts of two beautiful 2D girls...
How vexing! Geez...
What's this? You don't seem that happy...
Hm? "They look alright, but I wouldn't call them beautiful"?
Huh? What?!
Geez!
That's so mean!
Even though we're in a "naked" relationship...
Hmph!
If we don't change soon, we might catch a cold!
Okay, we'll leave off here!
We'll see you in the next Hinako Bath episode!
Hmph! I'll tell you off next time!
See you!
Bye bye~!
You can't look, okay?
Oh, Captain!
Huh? Didn't you leave?