With this kind of financial power,
anyone can do whatever they want, huh?
Whatever they want...
Don't tell me you want that too, Sawatari-kun?
No.
I didn't mean it like that.
You're the only one I can rely on.
So please...
It's okay. Don't worry.
Let's pull ourselves together and see it through till the end.
No resting until the party begins.
Everyone, please concentrate on your lessons,
and improve your sex techniques.
Hold on, Mitarai-san!
I-I can't...
I'm... I'm at my limit...
Resisting your natural bowel movement,
sure makes me envious since I am usually
constipated most of the time.
Mitarai-san...
Just a bit more...
Just a little more...
The Golden Lady
It still stinks a bit.
I'm sorry, Marika-sama!
It's true. Please, believe me.
I honestly never had any bad intentions.
There were some weird sounds,
and I just went to check it out.
I already told you not to enter that room, didn't I?
Yes!
That's why...
Hey...
Can you take off your panties and go on all fours?
Yes.
What a supple and beautiful pussy.
Regardless of the circumstance,
you still treaded on the forbidden line.
Naturally, you'll be punished.
I never intended...
So please, forgive me...
Nope.
Prepare yourself.
Hey, now.
If you don't relax, it won't get in.
I'm not comfortable 'coz it's my butthole...
Then all the more reason for me to continue.
This is your punishment,
so if you don't open up this hole and release it,
it'll be more painful later.
Later?
You can guess what it is, right?
Now, then.
M-My butt hurts!
There.
It's building up nicely.
Hey...
Which number would you like first?
I guess we'll have to go for number one first.
Th-The hole... is widening!
Now, how many balls can I fit here?
Marika-sama, please...
Gently...
Please do it more gently...
Oh my, so instead of asking me to stop shoving,
you wish me to push more in, huh?
I understand.
I'll take it slowly then.
It's gotten a bit tight.
I hurts...
Okay.
Three balls have entered nicely.
You still have to hold on from this point though,
because I'm also going to ram mine into yours.
What a nicely stuffed butt you have there.
It looks yummy.
Normally, you're stiff.
But thanks to this,
Your pussy's already warmed up anyway,
so it's already a good time to do it.
I'll be thrusting this inside then.
That's quite an interesting sensation down there.
Oh?
That won't do!
Put it in properly.
The pressure inside the butthole is quite good.
It seems like even this thing of yours can be useful.
Don't hit me too much!
Hey, it's coming out again.
Try to put more effort in your pussy and butthole.
Try and tighten up both your holes!
If I find you pushing that ball out one more
time, I'll punish you more severely.
Here I go.
The balls in your butt are also rubbing hard.
My pussy is also being rubbed intensely.
Hey, wrap me up more!
It hurts...
It hurts,
but it also feels good!
I'm cumming...
It's cumming inside me!
I came a lot.
Wait, anymore and...
Hey, there's still something else coming out, right?
Ah, the secretions and excretions of the youth.
Nothing beats a glass of that in the early morning.
Everyone, in anticipation for the regular party tomorrow,
this will be our last session for today.
For you two newbies, there will be a performance exam.
I want all of you to give it your best.
Oh, seems like it has finally come.
It really has.
This is great!
It's probably just a false alarm.
Mikako-san.
Is it true that you also will be going
with us for the party tomorrow?
Yes.
To put it bluntly,
we weren't able to pay our debts,
and the only thing left was for the both of us to sell our bodies.
To sell? What a terrible way to put it.
Excuse me, Mikako-san.
I'm going to the toilet for a bit.
Okay.
Oh my, Sawatari-san.
You came at a good time.
Please, I want you to help me out here.
What is it that would need my assistance?
Just a bit more.
It's almost there, but it's still not coming out.
That is why
I would like you to strike the final enema for me.
Enema?!
You're going to pee, right?
Would you please release your urine inside my ass?
Even if you say that...
Just do it. Here.
Umm, I am going to pee, but...
I said I'm going to be your human urinal.
Oh, but it won't fit inside like this.
Here, get bigger...
Mistress...
Okay, it's ready now.
Being young is really wonderful!
Now, hurry up!
Here, Sawatari-san.
Release everything inside me.
Oh, Sawatari-san!
Lower your hips more!
It's the lower hole.
Not my pussy...
But my butthole...
Well that's fine, I guess, Sawatari-san.
If you want to do pussy-enema instead,
then you better make sure your push
me to the edges of ecstasy!
Yes.
My Mistress...
Hey, Sawatari-san.
What do you think of my pussy now?
I-It's the best.
It's the pussy of the leader of the great Mamiya Group,
so just do it all the way.
Yes...
This is great!
Thrust it deeper in me!
My pussy's hot, right?
Your cock feels like it's melting, right?
There, that's right.
You need to thrust inside the pussy at varying angles.
Do you want to cum?
Do you want to release your semen?
Yes.
You can't do that.
I told you that you won't release it in my pussy, right?
Insert it in this hole this time.
Here.
Drive your grotesque cock into my butthole here.
Getting one's constipated butthole
penetrated by a cock is the best!
Your thick meat is rubbing and stimulating
my rectum intensely.
My insides feels good...
So good...
The tip is touching and pushing the stuff inside.
I'm about release it...
I'm going to release it.
It's going to leak out!
My, nearly done already?
Okay, then.
Even if it's your pee or your semen...
I don't care, but just release it in me. I'll take it all.
His semen's coming out!
Cum is gushing out!
Inside me!
There's still more, right?
That's good.
Just release it all!
A full anal ejaculation...
I just can't help but love it...
My Mistress...
What is it?
This time, it's...
Wow, lots of pee!
It's just going inside me!
This is...
What great amount it is...!
Mistress...?
This is...
This time...
It has finally come!
It's coming.
It's coming out!
Thank you, Sawatari-san.
I've never felt this refreshed in a long time.
Now we can fully work through the last lesson!
But before that...
I'll leave the cleanup here to you, okay?
Yes...