My dear, if you do something like that...
If you rub my penis like that...
Darling, my penis feels like it's gonna cum.
I really want to cum soon.
Even though we're newlyweds,
you left me here all alone.
I don't want to be alone like this.
Your wife's penis is going to feel lonely because of your absence.
I'm sorry, my sweaty perverted penis.
I'll let you cum using my husband's mouth instead.
I'm sorry.
I'm just such a lewd wife~!
Cumming... cumming~!
Cumming...
My wifely penis is cumming~!
My wifely penis is cumming from all this stimulation.
Sex~!
I want to have sex with you.
I want to have sex with my husband's real penis.
The feeling when my penis meets his penis...
The feeling when his penis sticky sperm is within me.
It's deep inside of mine.
His sperm is inside my pussy.
I want to get pregnant.
I want to get pregnant from your sperm.
Pregnant... pregnant.
With this, I'll get pregnant
from my own penis~!
W
Asa kara Zusshiri Milk Pot
Second Time
It's already time.
I should hurry.
This balls bra really fits me.
It's good that I picked this size beforehand.
When my penis gets big like this, this is the right size.
No way, I'll be meeting a lot of people with this kind of dress.
Making my balls wear this bra is kind of a perverted thing,
but it's really cute.
This part is also perverted.
I'm letting my nipples almost be seen with this kind of dress.
I never thought it would be like this.
I just tried to remodel my maid dress,
but now I look like a real bitch.
Let me rub it.
Let me rub it just once.
So cute.
I'm rubbing it in front of my mirror.
I'm getting big like this.
I'm such a perverted girl.
Angel... I'll be an angel.
I'll be an angel who's ejaculating over someone's body.
Ejaculation angel.
No way, It's too indecent.
Ejaculation angel is too indecent.
Ah, I souldn't let myself fantasize like this again.
From now on I'll be Alice,
I'll be the net penis idol, Akanemi Alice.
Alice.
You're so cute, Alice.
You're so cute.
You want to cum, don't you?
You want to cum to Alice being reflected in this mirror, right?
Alice-chan, evening.
I've been waiting for you to come.
She's come!
Good evening, thank you for coming to this Alice chat room tonight.
What a beautiful dress.
Here comes Alice-chan's raw penis.
Today, I'm wearing a maid dress.
This time Alice is a perverted maid.
I'm just perverted maid who likes cleaning, cooking and such.
How is it? Is it cute?
So cute!
That's good!
Good...
Thank you so much.
I did my best while making this dress.
That's right, I also made bra for my balls.
Up until now I let it be loose,
This time I'm just doing a favor for it.
I made this cute lace bra for my balls.
Do you feel excited from this, my pervert master?
Let's masturbate together today.
Ok.
Ok... Ok.
I'm so happy.
My penis is getting big.
Look at this size.
Round... round.
Everyone, how is it?
Ok, I just finished.
Even though you just came, do you want to give us more?
Eh? Wait a minute, would all of you calm down a bit.
Alice-chan, you're so cute.
Thank you.
For you to join me here,
I'm so happy.
On another note, I really want to fuck Alice-chan.
Pussy... your pussy.
Hey,
does Alice-chan want to get fucked with another penis?
Getting fucked with another penis?
If there was two of me, I wonder if I could get pregnant from my own penis.
Iori and Alice the idol.
Having sex together.
How lucky of me, even though it's just live event, no one is around backstage.
Alice-chan.
Akanemi Alice-chan, right?
I'm your biggest fan, Alice-chan.
If you'd excuse me.
Wait, what are you doing in here!?
I'm sorry, but I want to meet you for real.
Touching and smelling your body.
Alice-chan has a penis!?
Penis is great!
Beautiful.
It's Alice-chan's raw penis.
No, this isn't...
Alice-chan's penis...
It's okay, right? Sure it's okay.
Please let me lick all over it.
It's embarrassing.
You're even make it wearing this ribbon and bra,
Alice-chan, this is so cute!
Alice-chan's penis is so big and tastes good.
No way...
Isn't it strange for a woman to have penis?
It's okay, it's all good to me.
Because it's really good.
I have this kind of penis as well.
No way, you're also hermaphrodite?
That's right.
I'm just as strange as you.
There's someone like me out there.
I'm so happy.
No, if you're sucking it that much-
I'm gonna meltdown.
No, you can't suck it that hard!
I want to cum!
It's gonna... It's gonna cum~!
Thank you so much, It's really delicious.
It's been a while since I felt this good.
This time let me repay your kindness.
Then this time, let me fuck you up with this.
Is that true? I'm so happy.
Iori-chan's pussy is already this wet.
No, your juice is already coming out and touching my penis.
Then I'll put it inside your wet pussy.
Penis... Alice-chan's penis is within my womanly pussy.
When I fuck your pussy, there's a lot of juice flowing out.
There's a loud of perverted sound coming from my pussy,
I can hear it since you fucking my pussy this hard.
Iori-chan's pussy feels good.
The tip of my penis feels really hot because of it.
I feel good as well.
The way your penis is inside of me,
I want to put my penis inside Alice-chan's pussy as well.
Inside Alice-chan's pussy.
Let it in!
I want you to cum inside my pussy too!
Inside Alice-chan's pussy-
Your hot penis is going inside of me...
Iori-chan's penis is-
Our penis and pussy are fucking each other like this.
You're fucking me, yet I'm also fucking you.
Our pussy... with our pussy!
Alice-chan, I want you to cum inside me...
I want Alice-chan to cum inside of my pussy!
Iori-chan too, let's cum together.
No, my penis feels good.
My pussy also feels so good.
Cumming... semen is gonna come out.
It's gonna explode.
Cumming... cumming.
Cumming... the milk is gonna-
Cumming inside!
Inside Iori-chan, your balls juice is gonna fill me up.
Alice-chan's semen is coming inside of my pussy, your sticky
semen is coming inside~!
I'm gonna get pregnant from this penis milk.
I'm gonna get pregnant~!!
What play... what play is this?
I couldn't hold it!
What happened with her?
Everyone, I'm so sorry!
Be careful on your way, my lady.
I did it again yesterday.
I hope everyone will come again.
I wasted their time with that kind of foolishness.
I'm such a fool.
Am I doing this for my own pleasure?
At school and even at home...
What's left is I've never done it on a train like this...
Molester is it...
I wonder if I could ever get molested on this train...
Hey, don't move.
Stay still.
I'll make you feel good right now.
Molester!?
Don't look at me.
Do you think that this kind of molester always appears on a full train?
You let your guard down.
But... we're completely visible right now.
It'll be much hotter if it's completely visible like this.
No...
What a cute ass you've got, little girl.
I'll fuck you in here soon enough.
It hurts.
Didn't I tell you to stand still?
Your hot... your hot thing is touching me.
Looks like I need to punish you a bit.
Yes...
What soft skin you've got.
Your perverted hand is touching me...
You're putting it deeper inside of me.
If you can't hold it,
I want you to let out your satisfied voice.
This isn't gonna make me feel good at all.
His finger is inside my asshole...
You can't do something like that...
You can't take off my panties like that!
While we're at it, I'll put mine inside of you.
No... my ass is completely visible.
You should let it loose or you're not going to feel good at all.
No, you can't grope my ass like that.
My penis is getting big from the way he gropes my ass.
No, that place...
No... that hole... is my asshole...
I'm weak there.
No, you can't touch in front of it.
That place...
It'll be so much fun in this hole.
I'll make you feel better with this.
No... you can't do it with my asshole.
You can't put your finger inside of it.
My asshole...
Anal is...
It's already inside of you.
No, it's inside of my asshole.
I can feel it inside of me.
My asshole is being teased like this...
Penis... my penis is going to get big...
What a great motion you've got, little girl.
I feel sorry for you, but I don't have much time right now.
Hey, why don't you spread your ass wider?
No way, I couldn't spread my ass wider than this on the train?
It would be too embarrassing.
You're an honest girl, aren't you?
Then.
Your penis is inside of my asshole...
My ass is going to break apart.
No... stop moving inside of it.
It feels good...
I feel good from getting fucked on the train like this.
You can't... you can't touch that place, I'll let you do that later.
Alright, I'll do as you like... anal loving little girl.
If he find out that I'm a hermaphrodite,
If someone finds out that I'm getting fucked on the train like this,
It would be too embarrassing for me.
But!
My penis is getting big while my asshole is being fucked like this.
Is it the curse of being a hermaphrodite!?
It feels good...
It's cold yet I feel so good.
No way, they are looking... everyone is looking at me.
You're a perverted one, aren't you?
I'm sure you're getting excited while everyone is seeing you like this.
Right... that's right...
I want everyone to look at me while my asshole gets fucked.
My asshole is getting fucked.
It feels too good.
Yes, It feels great.
I feels this good as well...
Even though everyone is looking at me... even though I'm getting molested like this...
Cumming... I'm gonna cum from this.
I'm gonna cum with my penis while my ass is getting fucked.
I'm gonna cum for sure!
My penis feels good.
It really feels this good.
Is that so?
Your asshole feels really good.
More deeper,
I want you to stir up the deepest parts of my asshole.
Your penis is so great.
My penis juice is coming out so much, while my asshole is getting fucked by his penis.
It's coming deeper into me.
I want... I want your cum inside...
Cumming... your erotic semen is cumming inside of me.
My asshole is filling up with unknown molester-san's semen.
Your sticky semen is coming inside of me.
No... No~! My penis milk is coming out~!!
My penis is also cumming~!
Eh, you're a boy?
No, I've been found out.
My secret has been found out~!
I'm sorry... I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry for not telling you about this.
Eh?
I did it again.
I let my guard down and fantasized about being molested on this packed train.
It's so embarrassing for me.
I can't believe that I think about getting molested by some unknown person like that.
I'm really hopeless.
There will be no one who cares about me anymore.
No one anymore...
I'm getting lonely.
No... you can't!