There's a demonic essence lying inside Tachibana Yamato, born of human father and demon mother.
The soul of the demon was temporarily sealed, but...
It grew inside Yamato's body and finally came out.
Please tell me how to save Yamato! I'll do anything just to save him!
Yayoi-san, please tell us..
There's one way to seal the demon soul of Yamato...
The Special Demon... The one human breed. We'll use three kinds of them to seal the demon.
Special Demon?
That Demon was called Hamiko in ancient times, bred by a human with a high spiritual power.
To save Yamato, I'll need you to breed those Demons.
Only you two girls are able to do this.
I'll do it... If it can save Yamato, then I'll do it!
I'll do it too!
I see. Thank you, girls...
But we need three different kinds of demons for the spell, right?
Who will be the third one...?
I asked Yu the psychic to be the 3rd one.
Yu-chan will?
SubDESU-H Presents
Yu and I researched this kind of spell and
She agreed to be a Hamiko if needed.
Just accept what you are right now.
I am a demon and you are yourself.
It is better to live as you want to.
My life was already set out for me, as I was born in the family of Psychics.
I've never even thought about being free.
Yamato... san...
So you're all here. Mikoto, Takeru, Yu, are you ready?
Wow, a cat-ear girl, you're really cute Yu-chan!
A psychic ability... So you possessed yourself with an animal spirit...
I'm weak if I only use my power...
We don't have much time, let's start it now.
This place is...
Mikoto, that's the demon that's used for our spell.
Don't worry, it won't harm you.
I chose a type of demon which only has a small tube.
Ok..
This is for Yamato... This is to save Yamato!
No...
It's gross!
But this is for Yamato... I need to bear this!
What's this?
This is... the demon's...
Why does this... feel so good?!
It's... coming in...
No... don't push the tip deeper..
Don't move it...
It's in my womb! The tentacle is in my deepest place!
The demon is going to...
It's hot... don't move so much...
I'm going to break!
This is the demon's egg...
It's coming inside my womb... the demon's egg is coming inside me...
The egg is coming inside my womb!
Noooooo!
No... stop...
Don't be violent!
It's hot...
It's coming out inside my body... Inside my womb!
The sperm and the eggs are inside my body!
So you're the demon who put an egg inside my body...
Even I know that this is bad but I've already been raped once.
I can't forget how it felt with the demon before...
Let's have sex as Yayoi-san told us to...
I can't stop imagining the feeling of being raped!
So please have sex with me faster!
I can't be satisfied with just a human!
That's amazing!
Please... give it to me faster...
Big... It's big... that's great...
This one... I wanted this one...
My ass... good... I like it... I really like it in the ass...
I... I feel so good being raped by this kind of demon...
Pushing my hips into the demon.. I like this kind of feeling..
Hey... Rape me... Please ruin me!
That... That's good...
More... More!
Twist it... Twist it deeper!
This is my first time...
Don't stop... Please... Keep going!
You're really a perverted one... It's alright... You can touch me more!
Good... Please give me more!
This is so perverted...
My boobs... I feel it in my boobs...
It's coming out from my boobs... No...
No...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
No...  I'll leave it to you...
No... it's so good!
Good... My boobs feel like my pussy...
So good...
It's so good - my boobs, my ass, my pussy, it's coming inside so much!
So good... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
These filthy liquids...
It's coming out... Sperm is coming out from my boobs!
I'm dying... I'm going to die!
I'm going to breed a Special Demon to save Yamato-san!
But that Special Demon is for my own good too.
It's needed for the powerless like me to seek freedom...
Yu, are you alright?
Yes...
Then first...
Like this?
Raise your ass more.
What's the matter?
Um... It's embarrassing...
This is to save Yamato. Do it.
Ok...
Good, can you spread it until I can see your asshole?
Even this is embarrassing...
But this is for Yamato-san!
This will be a bit cold.
This is my special lubricant.
I put a mixture of the love drug and anaesthetic on it.
There shouldn't be any pain.
Thank you so much...
Are you alright?
Y... yes...
I can't take this...
My ass...
I'm feeling it...
I'll apply some here too.
Ya... Yayoi-san...
N..o..
Yayoi... san?
I'm going to summon the demon.
You're already wet, so I don't think there'll be any pain.
Yes.. I don't feel any pain.
It's coming in...
My body feels hot..
It's weird... My womb feels hot!
It came in...
Don't worry.
The two demons will fuse inside your body and form a new demon.
Ok...
It's cold...
When will this be done?
I'm at my limit...
I can't
I can't take it anymore!
Help me... It's coming out!
It's coming out... Someone...
Forgive me... Forgive me!
My stomach is going to break!
I can't take this anymore!
My stomach hurts...
I want it to stop...
Please bear it until it fuses inside your body.
Even if you say that..,
I can't hold it anymore!
It's coming out.. I want to go to...
No...
It's coming out!
It won't stop coming out!
It's so good... It's coming out and I feel so good!
Good job! The fusion was successful.
Mikoto, Takeru, are you two ready?
Yes...
No problem.
Good... Start it.
Keep it up Makoto, control your breathing.
No... My womb is opening...
It's..
Coming out! It's coming out!
Well then, let's start it...
Who are you?
Mikoto!
Come... Please lend me power!
The spirit lying inside Yamato..
You're a demon; a bad omen. Let yourself sleep in the hand of the demon god!
What!?
Takeru!
You're an invisible spirit that roams freely, and you must be banished.
Let your body be still, let your body be unseen, let your body be gone from this world!
Yu-chan!
Opposing seal, grand seal, sexual seal!
This place is...
Yamato!? Yamato, Yamato, Yamato!
What the hell happened...?
I'm glad... I'm glad!
Let's leave them alone.
Yes, you're right.
Ok...
Mikoto... You're beautiful...
Stupid... Don't look at me like that!
It's alright, it won't disappear
It will...
Mikoto... You're wet already...
No... Don't say that...
Mikoto... Please make mine wet too...
Yamato...
Let's do it...
Come... Yamato...
Yamato... Yamato..
Yamato's dick... It's so big!
It's reaching... It's reaching deeper!
Yamato... I... I...
I'm about to cum...
Release it inside...
It's hot... It's hot!
So good...
Yamato... Yamato...
Yamato!
It's so intense!
More...
Don't do... That much...
My pussy... My pussy is going to break!
I... I...
I can't... think of... anything else...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Yamato!
What!?
Nee-san!
Yamato-san!?
It's good... It's so good!
More... Thrust my pussy more!
Hey... You're late.
How are you?
Yamato...
As I thought, it's my turn!