SubDESU-H.net
Why...?
Should have... powered up... from eating nikuman...
Looks like the drug-filled nikuman I planted worked like a charm.
Well then, I look forward to tonight’s punishment.
W
Aku no Onna Kanbu
Chapter Two
「Slut Beast’s Whipping」
This punishment’s session really needs a stage.
Come. It’s punishment time.
It's about time you opened your eyes.
Katsuma...
Where am I?
A park, as you can see.
What am I doing here?
Eh? A collar?
N-N-Naked?!
How can I take a slutty bitch out for a walk without her collar?
I’m not a slut!
What do you mean... a walk?
Are you okay with yelling like that?
People will notice.
But I’m not... a dog...
Why are you doing this to me?
It’s embarrassing!
Shit. You won’t get away with this!
Hey, cut out the barking, will ya?
This is punishment.
What should I do?
There’s a tree over there, right?
Now, if you’re a dog... well, I’m sure you know what to do.
What do you mean?
Marking.
You don’t want your territory stolen, do you?
Stop joking around!
No way would I do that!
You're a dog right now.
No one cares if a dog pisses.
But I’m NOT a dog!
I don’t want to be watched!
Come on, let’s start.
Easier said than done... I don’t have to go right now.
I see... Then let’s walk you until you feel like it.
We’ll walk to a place with lots of people.
I’ll do it!
I’ll do it right here!
It’s coming... almost...
I’m peeing... it’s so warm.
So much is coming out!
I’m embarrassed!
Please... finish... why is there so much?
My pussy is all wet. How gross.
Wow, this bitch actually pissed herself.
And there’s so much of it too.
Don’t watch... don’t look...
Just let me off the hook already!
Here, suck it.
Lick my dick clean.
And remember my scent.
This... is humiliating...
Oh, you’re pretty good at it. Do you like sucking cock?
No... but I can’t... stop...
It’s hard... I’m not sure why, but...
I can feel it throbbing in my mouth...
Wow... a man’s thing... becomes like this?
It gets this big?
It somehow... feels good to lick it...
It’s twitching so much...
That means it’s going to come out soon.
“It”? You mean semen?
The stuff that makes girls pregnant?
That’s right.  If I cum in your mouth, you might get pregnant.
What should I do?
I’ll squirt it on your face, then you won’t get pregnant.
But...
You need to remember my scent.
Here I go.
So hot... and also...
It’s sticky...
No!
It stinks!
Lick it clean. This is your punishment.
But...
Don’t “but” me!
After you “accept” this, your punishment will be over.
What? You can’t mean...
You're joking, right, Katsuma?
No, stop... stop...
For some reason... I can’t move...
Ow, ow!
So this is the flavor of an unsullied virgin, eh?
Thought it would feel different.
Stop it.
At least make it feel good.
Ouch!
Move slower...
It hurts, but... huh? That’s strange.
Your pussy isn’t just wet with blood.
You’re enjoying it, aren’t you?
I’m not... sure...
No, stop...
You’re pretty tight, considering.
Don’t look...
No, not so rough... if not I’ll...
I’ll fill your uterus with my cum.
No, no, I get pregnant so easily! That’s why I haven’t fucked anyone yet!
I know I’ll get pregnant!
Please, please, I’ll do anything else you want.
Just don’t cum inside!
Then today I’ll shower you with my cum, so you’ll remember my scent.
N-No, I don’t want that either!
I don’t want to be sticky and smell of cum!
You say that, but look at those hips wiggle!
I’ll get so dirty with your juice.
Emblem Steal!
It’s so stinky...
Stinky, but...
You really fucked me up just now!
Just you wait, I’ll fuck you up next time!
I think you should call that off.
W-Wait a minute!
What’s that mark?
It means I’ve absorbed your mark completely.
Y-You can’t...
Once an executive has lost her mark, you know what happens, don’t you?
Until then, you must be my guard dog and serve me.
Well then, I will give you your first job.
Discover Oboro’s weakness for me.
And so...
Why do I have to dress like this?
Why else? It’s the punishment style for this round.
Even so... these clothes...
It’s just in horrible taste!
I covered up your private parts – you should be pleased.
No way am I pleased!
Hey, don’t look at me!
What a nice view, Oboro.
Don’t look at me!
Do you want to die?
Shut up.
You failed in your job – don’t be rude to me!
That was a mistake!
Thinking about it now, it’s still unclear why our Jin was broken!
You’re painful to look at, Oboro!
You loser-rabbit!
How disrespectful!
I will NEVER forget this!
What is this? What?
You feel the electricity pulsing through you, right?
It’s holding back your “esteemed-life”.
How could you... use electricity... for this...?
It’s so shameful... to have such strong currents...
Flowing through me...
Please stop it...
It’s throbbing...
Oh, my, oh my,
I didn’t think the Oboro of the crescent moon would respond to such kinky play.
That’s not true.
I’m being forced to feel it.
I’m not enjoying it!
No, no... stop it!
P-Please, stop it!
Stop it... stop it, please!
Please, please.
Stop it right now!
Hurry!
No... oh no...
Don’t watch, please don’t watch.
Why do I have to pee now?
Why is so much coming out?
I-I told you to stop!
I peed myself in front of you? Oh, I want to die!
Doesn’t this satisfy you?
I have endured your punishment,
so please set me free!
Huh? But we’re not finished yet.
And here I went through all the trouble to get the proper costumes for the ceremony.
P-Put that away!
It’s disgusting!
What do you intend to do?
Y-You’re not... don’t do it!
Anything but that!
No...
That hurts!
Oh? From the way you shoot off your mouth, I assumed you had experience.
But this is your first time?
Y-You will pay for this!
For stealing my first time... from me like this!
This sort of punishment... I have never seen or heard the likes of it!
The emperor will punish you severely for this later!
Let him. If he can, that is.
Ouch... don’t move!
Oh, fine, I’ll be gentle.
W-What’re you say-
It’s throbbing!
Not there...
I’m starting to feel strange.
How is it? Feels good?
Katsuma-san, for some reason, what you’re doing... feels good...
This sort of thing... I thought all it did was hurt...
But I feel... it moving inside...
Seems like you’ve learned to love my flesh-rod.
Your face is looking pretty naughty.
I am not making... that face!
But I do feel like I’m losing my mind.
I’ll make you cum.
But you’re raping me... no way would I cum...
Why?
It’s my first time, but...
I’m not sure what to do...
I’m going to cum!
Oh no, my head is going blank.
I’m cumming!
Oh wow, wow, I can’t stop myself from cumming!
You came in me. it can't be...
I hate it... I hate it, but...
The semen flowing in me feels so good!
It’s coming in me, and I’m cumming!
Emblem Steal!
Not like this... Why did I have to be soiled like this...
If you get pregnant, will it be a bunny?
Don’t even JOKE about that!
How dare you...
How dare you rob me of my chastity!
Not even the strictest of punishment will ease my suffering!
I will inform the emperor of this and have you executed!
Oops. That won’t do.
How did you... I thought your mark was the crescent moon.
Then why are you... explain yourself!
I stole your mark from you.
Which means you are now markless.
But how did you even-
You KNOW what happens to those without marks in this country, do you not?
W-Well, I...
What are you demanding that I do?
Just do as I say for a while. That is all.
So I suppose I must do your bidding...
Good girl, Oboro. You catch on fast.
Starting tomorrow, you’ll be my slave.
Kazuma-san, are you not here?
That idiot!
He called ME here.
Why isn’t he here?
Ever since then he’s had me do nothing but naughty things.
Huh? Is this his suit?
It really stinks.
Katsuma-san’s smell...
It’s making my head throb.
Oh no... why am I being so slutty?
But I can’t hold back,
this smell is driving me mad.
This smell is making me throb.
I’m getting hotter and hotter and I can’t stop it.
Katsuma-san, your smell. It’s making me go crazy.
This feels great!
Oh no, I’m going to cum.
Smelling his sweat is making me cum...
Looks like you’re enjoying yourself, Oboro.
N-N-N-N-No! What’re you...
Female executive Oboro had a smell fetish?
Let me go!
Wow, you’re really wet.
Did you get that turned on by the smell of my sweat?
Not at all!
It smells... so strongly... of your sweat...
So this is... the smell of a... dick.
It’s... smelly...
Your dick... tastes yummy...
It’s stinky, but... your smell...
It makes me feel good.
I’m gonna bury this stinky thing in your pussy.
Yes... no... I mean, I can’t think anymore.
It’s inside!
The smelly dick is in my pussy!
I’m doing so many perverted things again...
Your dick... your dick... it’s making me crazy!
But it doesn’t hurt.
I-I feel strange.
It’s driving me crazy!
Your smell is making me your slave!
Wow, Katsuma-san, your dick is so deep inside.
Your stinky dick... is it making my pussy stink too?
My pussy is being filled by your stink!
More, more, I want your stink inside of me!
Wow, for someone with a cute little face, you sure are a dirty whore!
N-No, you’re wrong! From having my chastity stolen so quickly, I’ve lost my mind.
So it’s YOUR fault!
Do you think I DON’T know about the number of times you came from my smell?
You stink fetish whore!
Please don’t say things like that.
Oh no, I’m losing my mind.
Yes, oh yes.
Do me more.
It feels great.
Oh, oh, I can’t take it!
I’m going to cum. I’m cumming, cumming!
I’ll cum plenty inside of you.
Not inside!
But... oh, I’m c-c-c-c-cumming!
Ah, lots came out.
You probably got pregnant.
I...
How dare you, how dare you, how dare you!
You stole my body and my heart!
You will pay for it!
I haven’t finished yet, Oboro.
Oboro...
You really are a slut, Oboro.
No!
Wh-What are you doing here?!
Katsuma stole my mark too.
Sorry, Oboro.
It can’t be! Was the breaking of Jin YOUR fault, Selena?
H-How cruel you are!
I don’t understand what you’re talking about.
So Oboro, Selena,
as my fellow slaves, I want you two to make nice.
Selena... I’ll give you my sex.
Katsuma had been fucking me all day before you showed up, Oboro.
Katsuma has been ordering me around this whole time.
And Oboro, you’ve got an amazing smell too.
Oh, do I smell that bad?
You are so fluffy and soft.
The rest of your body is so muscular, it would be unfair for only your breasts to be soft.
You’re so pretty and sweet.
If I do this more, will you become sweeter?
S-Stop it.
If you keep doing that, I’ll... I’ll...
Just from a little licking, your nipples are already so hard.
Are you really that weak?
Selena, your reactions are so hot.
Oboro... I’m so turned on...
You’re just a stupid dog, how dare you say that – how rude.
Oh no!
But Selena, if you look at me like that, it makes me so happy.
I can’t hold back...
Oboro, you’re unfair.
I want to pay you back...
No!
You’re pulling too hard!
You stupid bitch!
Revenge, Oboro.
Oh no.
If you do it that strong, my nipples will stretch!
Yes! I love it, Oboro!
Oh yes!
Me too! Selena, I feel so good.
Selena, the smell of your ass...
It’s so sweet.
Stop smelling my ass!
Oboro... I’m all soaked.
It feels like I peed myself.
Me too. Let’s feel even better together.
Oboro, this is too rough!
My clitoris is dying from the stimulation!
It’s falling apart!
My clitoris... it’s falling apart!
Oboro, Oboro, it feels so good!
Selena!
Oboro, Oboro!
Selena. Selena!
It’s no good. This feels too good!
I’m going to cum. Cumming...
I’m cumming!
M-Me too!
Katsuma... I feel...
Inexplicably hot... and I feel strange...
But you’re on the job now.
You’re not supposed to question it.
B-But you did this to me, didn’t you?
You made me addicted to you.
Your dick... I want more of your dick!
You really want my dick in your pussy that much?
You’ll get pregnant.
Pleasuring myself doesn’t work anymore.
I need you to fill up my pussy.
Otherwise I can’t be satisfied.
You can cum inside me.
So more... your dick...
Oh yes!
I love this so much.
More, more, fuck me harder!
You fucking bitch!
Stop calling me a fucking bitch!
I am a proud female!
This isn’t the real me!
But my pussy is driving me mad.
This isn’t how I really am, but... I’m cumming!
You stupid dog!
Where the hell are you?
This is Selena... I’m a bit busy at the moment...
Is something wrong? Are you okay?
N-No, I’m okay...
So big... too big!
Too big? What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Hurry and report to me at once, Selena.
Okay. I’ll cum!
I’ll cum, okay?
Selena...?
Hurry, cum. I need to go join Oboro.
I’ll cum over and over.
How many times must you cum?
After you cum this once more, you have to go back to battle.
Just hurry and cum in me.
You want me to cum inside you today?
Yes, yes, but I’ll get pregnant, so no.
Then I’ll pull out like I usually do and spill it all over your body.
No. More, I want your dick in my pussy more – don’t take it out!
It’s throbbing and rolling around inside of me.
I’ll cum! I’ll get pregnant.
Pregnant... but it’s okay.
I want your hot seed... in me... deep inside...
It’s coming... the sticky, hot... hot!
My pussy is filled with semen!
It’s falling out.
I’m so happy, I’m so happy. I’ll get pregnant from you.
You simpletons! Abandoning your posts, what are you doing?!
Oh, you want to join in?
I’ll take good care of you just like her.
Come to me.
What the hell?
You don’t want it then?
You shouldn't shove it in so suddenly!
Why not? You’re certainly wet enough for it.
But that’s only because you were near me!
Your smell...
And it’s outside... doing this... doing this is making me crazy!
Oboro, your pussy is amazing.
It’s making such naughty noises.
It’s so shameful.
While listening to my pussy, you’re masturbating.
Why are you embarrassed? We’ve had sex in front of each other many times.
Don’t say that!
Wh-Why must I be shamed so?
Huh? It’s because you’re cute, Oboro.
Don’t call me cute!
Katsuma... I want...
Selena, you’re cute too.
Katsuma!
Katsuma-san, you fool!
I’m about to cum.
I’m c-cumming. I can’t hold back!
No...
D-Don’t, you’ve turned me into such a little slut.
So much hot stuff... hot stuff inside.
I’m cumming again.
I’m cumming!
He came so many times inside... I’m probably already pregnant.
If you’re pregnant, let’s have our babies together, Oboro.
Don’t say such stupid things, you stupid dog.
From now on, you’ll do as I say.
Yes, Master.