W
Oku-Sama wa
Michael
The wife is...
Michael!
To the next person!
Congratulations!
No...
Don't turn it on.
Eh?
If it's bright...
It's embarrassing.
You look beautiful.
Really?
I'm so happy!
Hold me...
Look at your pussy, Mika.
It's getting wet.
No way...
Do it more...
Do me... do me from the front!
W-Wait!
It feels... good!
No...
Today too?
Sorry, Mika.
It'll be a bit cold at first.
Excuse me...
So as usual, your appetite is...
Yes, I can't eat anything.
Then let's check your stomach.
No...
Anekawa-kun.
Get me the usual... vitamin injection.
Sensei, how about we test Mishima-san's medicine?
Eh?
Anyway, please use this, Amano-sensei.
It's a new one that's guaranteed to work.
But...
The ingredients have to be tested by the admins...
Don't talk like a government official!
If it's recommended by someone trustworthy like Amano-sensei then it's bound to get through the process.
And my medicine which is guaranteed to work is bound to save the patient's life!
Can't you see that my skills will be beneficial to everyone?
Amano-sensei! I will service you with passion if you do it for me!
I'll give it some thought...
Yes!
Here we go, Komori-san.
You'll better in no time. Please loosen up.
No...
Mika's ass... it's so big and soft...
It feels so good!
No...
Mika, did your ass get bigger again?
No way...
Did you gain some weight?
You idiot!
Sensei...
Komori-san is...
She doesn't look very well.
Give me the written data for the medicine.
I don't think we've been given it yet!
Anekawa-kun!
Komori-san!
No!
No...
Asano-san!
Don't use my medicine without my permission!
Geez...
Asano-kun!
Amano-sensei.
It'll become a problem later.
That troubled look on your face...
I'll keep it a secret.
Eh?
Endure it! Endure it!
This is my responsibility, but as long as my team hasn't finished the research on your drugs we can't use them!
If you use a untested drug in the clinic and something happens...
Even I won't be able to cover for you, Yoshima-kun.
My underwear is gone!
My favorite underwear that elegantly wrapped my gorgeous ass and boobs is gone!
Huh? What could that be?
What a cute apron!
But who could it belong to?
Could it be a present?
Could it be?!
That Shinichi-san!
Honey!
Dinner!
Enjoy it.
M-Mika!
Oh no, you're such a pervert!
No!
No... what am I doing?
Pervert.
Oh? Is it a string piece?
Eh?
Huh?!
You!
Eh?!
No...
Now I'm angry!
Don't do such a dangerous thing!
W-What?
Oh no! What am I doing in this clothing?!
You don't only attack me, but you try to hurt yourself as well!
Is someone there?
Don't look... eh?
Hi! Nice to meet you.
Um...
You're Amano Mika-san, right?
My name is Furuu.
No way... I'm seeing things.
I must get myself examined after Shinichi-san comes back.
Hey...
Ok! It's not time to play anymore. I have to start making dinner.
Eh?! H-Huh?
Where is this?
I'm on the roof!
H-How can this have happened?
Hello!
H-Hello.
Eh?!
No! No way!
W-What...? What's happened to me?
I can see some weird things... and did I get onto the roof dressed like this?!
It's normal, don't worry, Amano Mika-san.
No...
No! A ghost! A ghost!
Calm down. Please calm down and listen to me, Mika-san.
You're such a troublesome person!
Huh?
Wait, what are you doing?
Calm down...
We need to sit down and talk.
No!
I am Furuu. In your language, I'm an alien.
I want you to help me.
What the... I'm flying?!
No, no! Why? Amazing! What is this?
Alien!
So... So I'm going to get abducted in a UFO in this clothing?!
They're going to experiment on my body...
And make me have sex with their weird and scary experiments!
Shinichi-san, please forgive me.
Let's go back for now.
Um... I don't know what to say this time.
I'm so sorry.
This is something that affects the clinic's reputation.
You won't get away with this, Mishima-san.
Yes, I know.
Mishima-san.
Please tell Asano-kun your address and other details please.
I understand.
Sensei! Mishima-san isn't a medical specialist! She's just an amateur!
No, please let me help you!
Yes, please.
And so this is how it is.
Do you understand, Mika-san?
Is this apron really you?
Well... in this situation, yes.
But the UFO that crashed in the hills,
and the corpse that was discovered were all crushed by the rubble.
My real body is what you guys call "clothes", so I need a vessel.
No way! So I'm just a vessel for you?
Why are you so hesitant to answer?!
While I was trying to get a physical body,
my space ship broke down and crash landed on this planet.
With no physical body and no ship, I have to contact my comrades and get back somehow!
I don't really think I can be of any help, though.
But don't you think it suspicious for clothes to wander around in the streets?
That's not what I'm saying...
Ah well.
Housewife's job number one!
Today's handmade special is for getting up his stamina!
Shinichi-san, make sure you eat it all!
Yes.
Ah, Shinichi-san?
I cooked some delicious chicken today.
Eh?! I made it with all my love and you're not staying?
No, come back!
I'm sorry, Mika.
Shinichi-san!
Amano-sensei.
Mishima-san!
How are the results?
Mishima-san what are you...?
Sensei!
Why...?
Please stop!
Mishima-san!
I've always had my eyes on you, sensei!
I don't care if it's just for the moment. Give me your thing.
Wait... You can't...!
I just got married!
We are newlyweds!
Look how low a lady from a brothel has fallen.
A beast must obey a whip!
My my, was it that good?
But you still aren't satisfied, are you?
Whee!
Chew properly or else you'll mess up your digestion.
What are you doing?
I thought you would be sad eating by yourself.
Mind your own business!
Thanks, you're very kind.
You're welcome.
Alright! It's also a wife's job to bring her working husband food.
But maybe not in this clothing...
A leotard is the best thing to wear if you want to sneak around in the dark!
All right! Let's go!
Mika-san, we cant fly in this costume!
Oh no, why?!
To fly we need to change clothes!
I don't care, just fly... fly!
Roger that.
I thought I would die for a second there.
Wait for me, Shinichi-san!
What a pervert!
Don't put it in without my permission!
No way...
I can't...
Hurry...
What a naughty girl.
Not yet!
It seems that your mouth is empty.
Yes... keep going.
You want more, don't you?
You want more treatment! More! More!