Shun-kun... Kiss me...
Kiss me...
Reijoku no Yakata
Part 2
W
Shun-kun...
I'm having sex with...
Shun-kun... and...
I feel like...
What do you feel like?
It's like I'm being sucked in.
If you say so then let's change positions.
Uhm... Shun-kun...?
Hey, Shizuru-sama.
I want you to tell me something.
If you tell me...
What is it?
What's inside that detached room?
I don't care about that woman...
Well then.
Shun-kun!?
It's alright.
Shizuru-sama's place is already prepared because of all the excitement.
No... No I'm not...
No! no no no!
It's in my ass!
Are you feeling it?
Shun-kun... come...
It's about time to start moving don't you think?
No way...
I wouldn't do something which is not good for Shizuru-sama.
But...
Then I'm going to move.
It doesn't hurt right?
No way.
This hurts so much!
Shun-kun... it's weird...
Even if it hurts, it feels like...
Oh?
Are you going to cum with anal?
No...
Even you can't cum with anal?
I'm only giving you that today.
Can you bear it?
Hey... don't make that face...
No...
I... my stomach is so hot.
I'm going to cum.
With Shizuru-sama's ass.
I'd be happy if Shizuru-sama cums with me.
Shun-kun...
Me too...
Me too... I'm going to cum.
With Shun-kun's dick, my ass is being rubbed.
It's so good.
I.... I'm a pervert who likes anal sex!
I was too rough.
What is it?
About the detached room you talked about...
The person who lives there is,
Our mother.
I see that's why it's in the center.
Even if I say that, It's not organized properly.
That's why... yes...
That place is like a Japanese style prison.
A Japanese style prison?
You see, as the first head of the Jounouchi family,
It would look bad if she was in a closed room in the hospital right?
Is it really in the center?
I had already forgot about it but,
It's been like that since before.
Then why does Shizuru-sama seem to hate that person?
That's... because that woman did that to that man!
She said that he was not suited for the Jounouchi family.
If you want to look at that place,
I'll arrange it for you.
The security... yeah, we need to make it private.
It's rare for Tsubame-sama to wake up this early.
Wrong...
I just finished my work so I'm about to go to sleep now.
Well, I expected that though.
It's seems you're making an uneasy face?
How rare for Shun-chin...
I didn't think that Tsubame-sama observed me that much.
Yeah, I'm always watching you.
For me, Shun-chin is my important...
Yes... Important...
Oh my Tsubame-sama.
You were ready for this huh?
Your not even wearing any panties.
Or maybe you expected this?
That you were going to be touched?
Oh, did Shun-chin not believe me when I said I'm so in love with you?
You're really malicious.
Let's do something new today.
Who is it?
You're Shun-chin right?
I'm peeing...
I'm always being beaten up by Shun-chin.
Oh?
Shun-chin really seems to be feeling uneasy.
Don't you have a sense of danger?
Sense of danger?
This Jounouchi residence is the world's safest place.
But I'd...
Oh yes...
I'll bring some guide and tell him to do something vulgar?
It's not a 0% possibility right?
And Tsubame-sama too, you also think of that that's why,
You got that horny right?
You know I...
I have a need for something.
Which a normal person can't do.
I'm looking for someone which will pull me down into the darkness.
That's why when Shun-chin did that to me.
I have thought maybe that's the one.
Like what is written here?
Oh~
Well... where should I start?
That thing was written by our mother.
First, I must tell you the story of our parents.
I'm changing the topic now,
but you know, the ancestors of the Jounouchi family, were also very strict.
Well, the person who only thinks about the family tradition and doesn't know anything about
the outside world is the head, so it's obvious that they can't cope with the change in society.
In short, even if something happens, they were very straight forward.
And at that time our father, a nouveau riche, appeared.
Our father had the common nouveau lineage complex,
And the Jounouchi family wanted that money so bad.
They each had the thing the other most desired so,
Our father made a upper class company as he joined them to be dried like a sardine.
But to be a son-in-law, you must surpass the obstacles of the family.
Well our father was suffering in many ways.
Our mother was in the cage of the good family and
Our father became a nouveau-riche from a turd.
They weren't allowed to sleep together to make a baby.
There were making a baby without love...
What a naive mother.
Well, it's hard as a man right?
Then the kind mother, to remove stress from my father,
made a naive decision to find a woman who looked a like her to have sex with him.
Well, if you receive that love from my mother, it would really affect you right?
I know that Shun-chin who read that understands.
Sex, like rape, is really primitive act.
All of them are doing it you know.
I don't know what she is thinking.
Maybe our mom learned to have a turds sexual body?
Well she might be watching some porn and maybe she recorded it.
And then the result of the combined work of our parents
is the thing which Shun-chin read.
It's just, my mother who is isolated,
Seems like it affected her a lot.
The woman who looks like her was being devastated... her body and mind. She was watching her break.
And in the end she broke too.
In the closed room of the hospital is...
Ah... I see.
You heard something from Shizuru-neesan right?
Her husband being murdered.
Is just a hallucination from being damaged.
You know I...
The person who forgot the faces of her daughters and
doesn't get the difference of the Jounouchi family and it's tradition..
I was still young and I read that.
I became like this and I simply can't get out from this situation.
She's really a disgusting parent.
Who passes her curse to her daughters.
Does it seems boring to Shun-chin?
Well, it's nothing if you open the box though.
Yes you're right.
I see... Shun-chin thinks there something important in that place.
Yes.
Sorry.
Well, Rei and... I think it's another method for that girl though.
If you pull down Tsugumi, the Jounouchi will be Shun-chin's.
Well, I think so.
Is Tsubame-sama...
Waiting for the God's Wrath?
You even left your loving family and being a bad person.
I'm not that magnificent.
It's thankful for the people trapped in the abyss.
But I think that is...
I can't express it properly but...
It's an opinion from the experienced.
Yes, I was saying it on my own,
but maybe I was right?
Tsubame-sama's thing is something Messianism.
Meaning, you're looking for the right moment and...
But you're also afraid of it.
So your also wishing for it not to come.
Is it Messianism without Messia?
I don't think your near it but,
you're getting near to it no matter what.
This is really...
Beyond my expectations?
Oh!
Tomoe-neesan, so you really came.
When I heard of this place from Shizuru.
I think it's strange.
It's very different from what Tomoe-neesan said.
Someone is bringing some thread and
it's hard to made it to the conclusion if you're lying.
Tomoe-neesan if you remain silent...
I'm sorry, Shou.
But I don't have time to hear your theory.
I don't want to kill you,
so give me the key and move.
Thanks.
I don't know what Tomoe-neesan wants to do.
There's no meaning in it even if you let that old woman live.
If she wants to be a criminal then I'll just leave it to her.
Do you want to come in?
Why?
You just let the plebeian enter right?
Well then.
I didn't think there's a part of you that would moan like this.
What?
Why is it so funny?
Oh, it's seems you're still calm.
Then it's ok for me to be even rougher right?
I'll release it inside.
I'll release it inside even if it's still your first time.
Give me... I want that.
I want it Shun-niisan.
Hey, by the way, a while a go, Tomoe...
That's Shun's right?
Is it ok for you not to pick it up?
Yes, hello?
Why did that woman do that to my name?
My name...
What did I do!?
Hey Shun!!!! Answer me!!!!
Tomoe-neesan, what are you saying?
Tomoe-neesan!?
Then there's still some secrets!
In that place!
What are you going to do?
I'm not comfortable if I'm naked.
Also I'll catch a cold, right?
Hey, how much do you know?
The one who's living there is the first head and
she's sick.
Hey, why do you think Tomoe entered to that place?
I see, it's revenge.
Right.
It's revenge for our mother who was murdered by our father.
Then why?
Is it really our mother who is there?
She found a woman who's look a like as her.
I see, a replacement.
As I expected from you.
To show us the revenge was successful and
what a hobby to kill your own mother?
Well, for us, we don't care about that.
But she desired for it.
And I let her do that.
That's all.
Wait.
Then is the real first head is still alive?
No, didn't you say it?
That she's a replacement.
So she replaced that woman and got murdered by her husband.
He seems like a Homo.
and hmmm he seems to have received a punishment.
What do you mean by that?
She died as a result of throwing her body for his loving husband so I think she's a homo.
Even if it was a rude sex.
It's a sad thing that.
You want to release all your emotion against your partner.
Loved?
I heard it that it was an undesired marriage.
Not all the emotions will appear in the front right?
Maybe she was a Tsundere.
Then the punishment, what is that punishment for?
It's for having sex with an outsider and committing a crime.
I feel that there's the blood of an outsider flowing in our body.
I see.
The one who murdered Shizuru's husband is...
Your really great.
I think it's important that you have to twist your brain into full gear.
Then are you going to kill me?
The one who wants to obtain the Jounouchi.
Why?
Shun-niisan is the God's wrath we're looking for.
I don't want to get involved in the lineage of the old family.
You saying you don't want this Jounouchi family?
Do it Tsugumi.
Hina-sama, what are you doing?
Making Shun-niisama happy.
Well, can you move a bit?
No, I don't want to.
It's because Shun-oniisama is only Hina's.
That's...
It's a new love drug.
I was worried if it would take effect.
But I'm relieved that it worked.
You let me drink that?
Yes I wanted Shun-oniisama to be only mine.
Ah! Hina-neesan, you're doing it again with Shun-niisan.
You... You're only mine you know.
It's not that I desired this.
Shun-oniisama, you're cruel.
Look, Shun-nii is a cruel person.
So do this to him.
Look Hina-neechan, even I touched it with my foot.
It's still hard.
It's like an animal.
Sorry, Tsugumi-sama's foot is like jelly and so stinky.
Ah! take it back! My foot isn't stinky.
I ran so much today and
I sweat a lot but,
Yes you do.
You. You. You...
Hina-neechan, this is amazing, it's pumping.
Yeah, this is great.
Shun-nii's came a lot.
What should we do Hina-neechan?
Even you say that..
Hina, Tsugumi.
It's hard for Shun-niisan if you take it easy.
Right?
Yes.
Shun-niisan, this is so good.
As I thought, Shun-niisan is really important to us...
Hey Shun-niisan, I...
Kiss... I want to kiss.
Shun-niisan, it's still not coming out right?
I think we can still enjoy this.
What am I thinking?
I'll tell you some old stories.
My mother has a big brother.
The two of them got into a forbidden relationship.
What are you trying to say?
There was a general election for the brother and
The love between them didn't take long.
Hey!
The two woman are being frozen.
Hey, Shun-niisama.
Do you have a memory of the time when you were still an orphan?
Damn!
Including the memory of the orphanage, the unreasonable bad intention didn't just come to Shun-niisama.
Don't say that!
The bad intention that makes you want revenge against the Jounouchi family.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Can I make a baby?
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!
Welcome back