Sto-sto-stop it-!
Hinako-bath~
Full of steam, Hinako-bath~
Seems visible, yet unseen~!
Hinako-bath~
Feels so heavenly.
Welcome.
[Welcome!]
Hinako-bath
Bath fee
10,000 yen
(tax included)
Rewards
Able to enjoy bathing.
Able to train your body
Welcome to Hinako-bath,
the fee is 10,000 yen.
Thanks!
I've always been waiting.
Isn't this 10 yen?
Soap two: Animal juice treatment
Baths are so comfortable.
I'm so happy when I'm soaking in the bath!
It must be because I'm Japanese.
Even though I'm an anime character at the moment...
Those eyes, aren't you making fun of me?
Geez...
Take this, take this, take this, take this!
A hit!
If you make fun of me, I'll do it again.
Since I've been in here for a while, why don't we start soon?
?...What?
Well, if I say together with Hinako...
It's implied that it's "that", right?
It's "that". You know, "that".
No...
Geez.
It's training, of course!
Training in the Bath
First part
Arm stretching good for the hips and shoulders
Put your fingers together,
and raise your arms upwards...
Count to ten each time.
Do it three times, okay?
I'm starting.
Okay, one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
No matter what exercise you're doing,
you shouldn't hold your breath, okay?
We're starting the second round!
Okay!
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten-!
Take a breather.
When you've gotten used to it, bend to the right and to the left while in the same position.
Like this.
It's okay to twist a little.
Well, let's start!
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Okay, that's it.
So...
Training in the Bath
Second part
The second part!
Chest stretching for better posture
Chest stretching for better posture!
Well then, place your hands behind your back.
It feels like you're bending your shoulders.
Stick out your chest and take deep breaths, okay?
It's a chest-stretching exercise recommended for those with a lot of deskwork.
Do three sets of ten counts, okay?
Let's begin.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten-!
Take a breather.
This supposedly has bust-enhancing effects.
Hey! Where are you looking?!
Pervert.
Geez.
Come on, round two.
Let's go, ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
Oh yeah.
While you're doing this exercise,
you shouldn't move your hands from your back.
Well then, last one!
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
Well then, next!
Training in the Bath
Third part
The third part.
Underwater sit-ups for the abs
Put your hands on the rim,
or place your arms within the bath.
Also, remember to hold your knees and stomach together.
Like this.
Oh, you don't understand?
Aww, I have no choice then.
Hold them together like that.
Consciously contract your abdominal muscles, okay?
Since they're sit-ups after all.
Also, three sets of ten counts again.
Well then, let's begin.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
If your bath happens to be bigger,
stretch your legs out a little more.
It might be a good thing to try.
Okay, let's start the second round.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Take a breather.
If your stomach starts feeling uncomfortable,
don't try too hard, okay?
Okay then, last one.
Let's go!
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Okay, moving on.
Training in the Bath
Fourth part
Part four, it's the last one!
Body twist to relieve swelling
Body twist to relieve swelling.
Try crossing your legs.
Hang the opposing arm on top of the upper knee.
All that's left is to twist the body.
Count to ten for each set.
There are two sets for each side.
With that, let's begin.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Oh, while you're exercising, be sure to stretch your back and neck properly.
We're going to do it in the reverse direction next.
Rearrange your arms and legs.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
It's time for the third set.
Rearrange your arms and legs again.
Well then, let's start.
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather.
Just one more time and it's over.
The one we're doing now can be done anywhere.
When you're not taking a bath, try doing it in your room.
Rearrange your arms and legs.
Well then, last one!
Let's go!
Ready?
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Take a breather...
End of training!
Thanks for the hard work.
All that's left is to laze around in the bath and relax.
Shouldn't Captain Hiyoko be...?
Salute!
G-Good evening.
Good evening, Captain Hiyoko!
Good evening, private Hinako.
How many times have I told you not to call me by my name?
Ehh?! But isn't it cute?
Geez, I've always told you that I don't like that.
Okay! I'll take care not to do so!
I've always thought this, but this bath sure is cramped, isn't it?
That's not true, you know.
Though I'm supposed to have entered the bath, it feels kinda springy and bouncy.
What a weird feeling.
That's because Captain is sitting on top of me...
Ahh! So that's it?
This is the cause of the springy feeling?!
Here too.
Over here is a little...
Over here, too.
Hey, that feels good...
Hinako is developing really well.
Hey, over here.
Your movements are dull because you have so much fat.
T-That's mean, Captain.
Teasing me about things I have issues with...
Furthermore, you did it in front of other people.
Ughh, that was rude.
Showing such ugly fat...
Uwahh! Captain!
Hmphh.
Could it be...
Captain has yet to start growing,
so there's no need to be anxious!
W-What are you talking about?
Ah, Captain, you seem so worn out.
Shall I give you a massage?
I don't need it.
I'll do it!
Hey, come on.
I said I don't need it...
S-Stop it!
Stop, it tickles!
Stop it, idiot!
Ah, Captain.
You've been exposed.
Did you see anything?
I can't get married anymore.
Please take me.
Since you've seen every part of me, please marry me!
Captain...
So that's it, you don't need me right?
After all, I'm so small.
C-Captain...
I have no choice but to destroy you.
Geez, Captain. That was a joke!
Come on! The steam makes everything misty and you can't see anything.
I've been exposed a little bit.
Eh, the steam is so thick, I can't see anything~!
Captain, Captain, where are you?
I wonder where Captain is.
Okay, I understand.
Where could the Captain be?
I understand already, stop it.
I found the Captain!
Come on, stop it.
Captain, we've got something good.
Something good.
W-What is it?
A beauty's bath
Just by being in the bath you get prettier...that would be nice.
Today's a mixed bath.
Eh, umm.
I-I-It's a mixed bath.
Soap two: Animal juice treatment.
Let's get to washing ourselves, shall we Captain?
I'll wash your back.
I'll do it myself, it's fine.
Besides, I haven't forgotten what happened earlier.
I'll make sure that I wash you properly this time.
I understand.
In that case, please do.
Yay!
For Hiyoko's use
Tada! Next up is shampoo!
Hey, we don't have to use that.
Don't we always use it?
It's fine! I'm not a kid.
Okay, okay. I understand.
Captain's acting weird.
Keep trying, Hiyoko!
This is the first step on the road of adulthood!
Even though you don't have to bear with it...
I-I'm not bearing with anything.
Yes, yes.
Just say it once!
Yes-!
Don't drag it out!
Well, it's Hinako's turn next.
Yes, please do so, Captain!
In that case, the other side too!
I'll give you a special dietary massage, Hinako-chan.
Really?
Thank you very much.
And with that, let's start.
It's good-!
Captain! It may hurt a little bit!
The more it hurts, the more effective it is, so bear with it!
Y-Yes!
It hurts-!
Captain...
That's enough.
The real deal starts from now on, you know...
Ehh, stop it!!
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Okay, it's done.
Well, let's use the bath, shall we?
Yes...
I somehow feel tired,
but bathing together with everyone somehow feels relaxing and fun.
You're right; I'm feeling in high spirits!
Well, let's count to 100.
Uhm.
If the heat gets you, don't overdo it and get out, okay?
Uhm, uhm.
Also, while in the bath, stretch your fingers.
Due to the effects of the water pressure, it will improve your grasping ability.
Count together with me and try it for yourself, okay?
Okay then, let's go.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen fifteen,
sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four, twenty-five,
twenty-six, twenty-seven, twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty!
Thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three, thirty-four, thirty-five,
thirty-six, thirty-seven, thirty-eight, thirty-nine, forty!
Forty-one, forty-two, forty-three, forty-four, forty-five,
forty-six, forty-seven, forty-eight, forty-nine, fifty!
Fifty-one, fifty-two, fifty-three, fifty-four, fifty-five,
fifty-six, fifty-seven, fifty-eight, fifty-nine, sixty!
Sixty-one, sixty-two, sixty-three, sixty-four, sixty-five,
sixty-six, sixty-seven...
Erm, Captain?
I'm heading out first.
You two can stay in there.
See you later, then!
Okay!
sixty-eight, sixty-nine, seventy!
Seventy-one, seventy-two, seventy-three, seventy-four, seventy-five,
seventy-six, seventy-seven, seventy-eight, seventy-nine, eighty!
Eighty-one, eighty-two, eighty-three, eighty-four, eighty-five,
eighty-six, eighty-seven, eighty-eight, eighty-nine, ninety!
Ninety-one, ninety-two, ninety-three, ninety-four...
Don't lose heart!
Ninety-five, ninety-six, ninety-seven, ninety-eight, ninety-nine, one hundred!
We made it!
Captain is still far from reaching the 100th count.
Bath time is over!
Please don't go yet, stretch exercises await.
Okay then, see you soon!