All of you...
Don't think you can get away with this!
You're betraying us!?
What've you done?
Y-you insolent fool!
Doing something horrible like this...
You're a dead man!
No, you're a corpse!
Die, just die right now!
No... No...
What a healthy girl you are.
Your impatient attitude is kind of like someone else.
But, you know?
It seems you don't even know,
what kind of situation you're in right now.
All of them...
They've wanted to screw you so badly for ages.
It's really helpful for us that these beasts could come over so fast.
So I'll let all of you do as you like!
That woman is going to be your reward!
What's with that!? There's no way I would be their reward.
It's not something you could decide-
Let me go!
I'll let you know who's in charge soon.
For what you've done with humans like us.
St-stop it... stop it...
Origa x Kuroi Dark Castle, Break Chapter
～ The noble saint cloudy stain ～
Kuroinu
In this vast land,
exists one nation, larger than the others.
It's called the great Eostia
In the north of this nation lives a race of beasts.
They were born the same day as the land came into existence.
To the other races,
they are seen as an evil blighting the land.
They captured many human women,
and made them their slaves.
They defiled their bodies,
took their virginities,
and took away their peaceful lives.
But a revolution happened after the long battle
with that race of beasts.
One hundred years ago, in the north of that land,
a huge castle, which came to be known as the 'dark castle',
appeared from inside the earth.
There's a barrier around the castle
that protects it from outside threats.
The effect of its appearance
makes the sky red in colour,
whether it's day or night.
The air is hard to breathe,
and the land around the castle is slowly dying.
There's nothing that land could do
to halt these effects.
There's a rumour that the owner of that dark castle is
the beautiful dark elf,
known as...
The Dark Queen.
Stop it!
You insolent fools,
you dare do something like this to me?
What... are you doing...
Don't... don't look! Don't look!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Then, my lord,
your last order.
Stop it!
That big thing,
wouldn't fit in-
It's too much big,
my stomach,
it's filling it up.
My breath...
won't go out-
My-
Queen...
Hey, get up!
Get out!
Inside me,
those penises keep going inside me.
I look like a slave.
My mouth...
Even my pussy...
Those filthy beast penises
keep fucking me.
I just...
can't feel or think...
about anything else.
No, it's rubbing inside me.
These dirty penises will explode,
and I'll feel it.
Why?
It's not like that!
Don't let it out!
That dirty penis milk inside me... inside my pussy...
No...
I'm going to break.
It'll break apart!
No... you can't, if you let it out...
I... I'm...
If you let your penis milk out,
I won't be able to hold back from cumming!
That's why... spare me.
Cumming...
My Queen, please forgive me.
Please forgive my...
lewdness.
That penis milk...!
Cumming...
Inside my pussy...
It's cumming!
The penis milk is filling my throat.
It feels good...
I can't hold it!
The Dark Queen holds dominion
over all of the evil things within her land.
She has enough power to do anything she wants.
Some people who oppose her have begun to attack her.
However,
the ones who oppose her can't beat her so easily.
These people who oppose her
are planning to defeat her and the evil race as soon as possible.
There are seven princess knights who think
that there's a reason for the change of
the sunshine movement.
The goddess who has been reborn
as the high elf.
The high elf who built the saint church,
seeing the fate of the dark castle,
or even what would happen in the future,
and that no one would be able to do it like her.
The high elf soon built her Order of Chivalry,
comprising of the princess knights from various nations.
Then, from the day they united in the saint church,
the same day their bonds were formed,
from the seven different nations,
the Order of Chivalry was born.
During the long battle,
mercenaries also had their place.
Their existence in the battle
is leading to defeats for the saint army.
They're just doing it for money,
and everyday is about spending money for pleasure.
That's how mercenaries live.
However,
one day a man appeared,
who would unite the mercenaries under him,
into one big association.
His name is
Volt.
Volt-sama.
Give me a reward.
Your close associate's voice,
I'm sure you heard it inside your head, right?
She's the reward for those beastly guests in here.
No...
Give me more penis-
I called you in here just to make sure about something.
There's something I would like to ask you.
A Dark Elf like you...
You could bear children from a human, right?
Yeah!
Cih.
Huh?
A lower kind like you couldn't break me so easily.
I'll have it back.
What is this!?
Alicia nee-sama
I'm sorry for yelling.
But I couldn't really forgive this kind of thing!
Eh?
You're broken, my Queen!
Elf te reverte hecerive...
Eh?
It's my last resort for you.
This is...?
It's the seal for her womb.
I got it,
so it's a seal to make her pregnant.
I seal this dark spirit within my body,
it won't let you do as you like right now.
I understand.
Now we've got ourselves time to screw that seal from her.
Listen to me all of you!
This high dark elf,
is a beautiful woman and surely a virgin.
I'll let you have this dark elf queen!
How good looking.
A queen like you would be screwed by these men in here.
I can't hold it, I just want to screw her so badly.
Well, we should give this queen some time to think.
Never thought that we could do it with a high dark elf like her.
Don't you think that her seal would make us enjoy this time?
Then,
let's try it right now.
There!
I could smell her delicious pussy by now.
I can't hold it!
Commander, please confirm her virginity!
Let me see.
I'm being looked at by them.
These lower human kind are looking at my pussy.
As I thought, I'm losing my power too much, with this...
This is really a sparkling virgin pussy.
It's not a joke anymore.
Then, shall we begin?
Here I go, my Queen.
Don't say it over and over again!
It's deep inside.
Even though...
No matter how many times you screw me,
as long as this seal is present...
Your filthy cum.
There's no way
it would defile my womb...
at all.
Commander, could we also screw the queen?
Even if it's just her tender breasts?
Alright, all of you may do as you like.
Finally!
What a beautiful face you have.
I can't hold it.
Look at me!
Stop it, that dirty thing-
Rubbing inside my pussy...
Doing something like that.
Know your place.
You worm!
What you're saying!?
Just calm yourself.
Don't you want to screw her pussy? Just let her talk that way.
Cih, I don't like the way she speaks to us.
All of you, enjoy yourself.
If you want to cum, just spread all of it in her.
It's okay to put your penis inside of her.
All of you, do it right now!
No need to hold back!
You can screw her everywhere within her body!
This is how the queen's pussy feels.
I can't hold it.
Quickly, change over!
Don't rush me, get in line!
Her mouth is so warm.
Don't choke on it, okay?
These lovely breasts.
Alright, it's my turn, get out of the way!
Enjoy your time with her, since it's rare to do it with the queen.
We'll cum all over her body!
Do it, do as our commander said!
Next is my turn.
How long will it last...?
They're doing as they like with my body.
It seems that you like what they did to you, my Queen.
Heh.
E-even though you put me in this shameful position,
I still won't be defiled by you.
How much longer will you be able to talk like that?
As I thought from the queen.
Though she lost her virginity a while ago,
her pussy is still tight like before.
Th-there's no way...
that my pussy would be...
like that.
Your harsh words will end right now.
The preparation is done, right?
Ostalas estas el he bisoe...
Then I can cum inside her as much as I like.
No way!
There's no way that you can cum inside me!
My pussy...
There's no way that my pussy would bear
filthy human children from you.
How sad.
Such a high quality pussy
will have my sperm
inside it!
Don't you know how I feel!?
To bear this shame,
for the rest of my life!
Let's finish this!
All of you can enjoy her pussy till the end.
You'll get a second chance with her high quality pussy!
St-stop it... stop... No...!
Don't bite it, okay.
With these filthy penises,
my womb will be
defiled.
It's out... I'll let it out!
Receive it with all of your might, okay!?
Hold it down, alright!
Yeah!
Stop it-
Stop it!
It's out...
It's flowing through me...
My womb is...
defiled by...
human sperm.
Each person came ten times inside her!