Himegaoka Central Hospital
Why am I here?
It's because I called you.
Why?
I want you to know our true self.
Eh?
We are prey.
Weak and cowardly.
You can play with us any way you want.
The thing inside the nurse uniform...
I think you don't know about that.
You don't know our true self.
But...
But?
Anata no Shiranai Kangofu
~Seiteki Byoutou 24ji~
Chapter 1
The Real Faces Of The Angels
Going over the boundary between the patient and the nurse.
At that time, I didn't know what's the meaning of that.
Shiratori-san, I...
Juumonji Yousuke
Juumonji-san.
I like you, Shiratori-san...
No...
Don't say that anymore.
Why?
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry, I'll teach you.
Please stop!
Don't do things like this!
I love Shiratori-san.
No!
There...
Shiratori-san, you're beautiful.
You're sensitive.
No way... I'm not!
No!
Stop!
You're wet.
The nipples are also hard.
You're feeling it, right?
That's not true!
Ju...monji...san...
I...
OK then...
It's coming in!
Are you alright, Shiratori-san?
I'm not.
I didn't think that it hurts so much.
Sorry.
It's OK.
I'll move.
Does it still hurt?
I don't know, my body is numb.
Then I'll move more.
No... Stop... I'm going to moan!
It's alright, let me hear it.
Don't do it too much!
I'm going crazy...
Shiratori-san, I...
Juumonji-san, me too!
It's hot!
You came a lot!
This is... sperm...
It's sticky.
Since that night, something strange happened.
What is this?
"The nurse became like this because of her mistake."
Huh? Are you kidding?
How foolish.
I think it's just spam.
Oh, maybe I'd better go to C. R.
This is morphine.
And...
This is treated heroin.
It's only this?
OK then, this is the reward for today.
Only this?
We can't help it because you only gave me a few stocks of the medicine.
Because... They might notice if many is missing...
If you want more money, then bring more medicine.
I'll still accept with the other thing...
Emergency exit
I heard it.
I didn't think that an innocent nurse would do such vulgar things.
What are you talking about?
I didn't think that a nurse is dealing narcotics from the hospital.
No... that's... that's...
Please, don't say this to anyone!
My sister can't live on her own if my mom dies!
What are you saying?
Please!
Please... please don't say it to anyone!
Aren't you asking too much for overlooking you while doing bad things?
I'm sorry!
You must compensate if you really feel sorry.
"The people being hunted down won't change."
"Don't forget what happened three years ago to nurses from Himegaoka!"
Hey... What!?
What is it, Juumonji-kun?
What do you want?
Don't joke around!
I can't bear it anymore, because Akira-san always seduces me.
Don't mess with me!
Let me go!
By the way, does Akira-san know about the nurse rape incident which happened 3 years ago?
About the nurse rape incident...
What's that?
What are you talking about?
Huh? So strange, I thought Akira-san would know that.
Can't help it, I'll just ask Akira-san's body.
Hey, Juumonji-kun...
Do you think it's alright to do something like this?
Stop it!
Wait!
Stop!
You're cruel!
I see, it hurts.
Well then, I'll make you feel good.
You shouldn't...
It's not that wet yet!
It's fine. Here I come, Akira-san!
O...uch...
I can't... Please, take it out!
No!
Does it feels good? Does your pussy tickle?
Anybody would react if you touch it like that!
You're right, your nipples are also erect.
You're always touching my boobs.
Are you only thinking of that?
Then, I'll just have to move.
Is that OK with you?
You'll do it even I say no.
Yes.
Wow... Your wetness is great!!
Are you going to cum, Akira-san?
I'm not!
Is that so? But the way you shake and this amount of juice...
Oh? Don't tell me...
Yes, it's about to leak!
What will leak out?
Pee... I want to pee!
That's why you should take it out already!
Oh, well then, I'll help you with that.
Eh?
I don't want this!
What happened, Akira-san? Just release it!
What are you saying?
I can't release it from this position!
Is that so?
No...
It will come out!
Is that so? Then I'll forgive you.
If you call me "master".
I can't... say that...
Hmp, it's alright if you don't want to.
I understand, master.
Please, stop it already!
Hmmm, what should I do?
Didn't I tell you to take it out?
You're not saying it with your heart.
How is it? Do you feel that good?
No...
Master... please...
Help me!
It will come out!
OK!
Just release it here!
No!
I'm cumming!
Noooo!
It's smelly, Akira-san.
Yes, my pee surely it's smelly.
Nurses in this hospital can't oppose me.
I make them spread their legs when I want to.
And enjoy their dirty body.
Oh?
Hm?
You must not enter there, though.
It's alright. It's just for a moment.
I wanted to enter here once.
Why have you changed so much, Yousuke-san?
I didn't change.
You have.
Is it really my fault?
Is it because I can't approach to you kindly?
Right?
Yes. It's your fault.
Because your body attracts mine. That's why everything got crazy.
It's true, Amane. It's your fault I became like this.
No way...
Your body... Your ass must not be like this.
Yousuke-san... no... in such place...
And these boobs are the best!
You're putting the garters properly...
Good girl...
Amane, you're beautiful.
I don't want this appearance...
Give me back my clothes.
Just face to the front.
I can see your asshole clearly.
No!
Don't look!
It's cold!
What did you put in?
You're a nurse, you should know it.
Oh?
It's still a beautiful pink color.
Yes, you were still a virgin the last time.
No... don't put it in!
You were masturbating...
Don't look!
Hey! Why are you hiding it?
I'll rip the nurse uniform if you hide it.
Do you want to walk naked in the hospital?
I don't want that.
Then, let me see it.
Good...
You are cruel!
We have just started, Amane.
This is... great...
Your body is hot, Amane!
You're horny, right?
It's because Yousuke-san is doing something like this...
What happened, Amane? Are you alright?
It's strange, is the stimulation still weak?
It hurts!
Stop it, please!
I'll just thrust you with this.
Noooo!
No... I'm going crazy!
This is my first time!
The electricity flows through my body!
My body is weird! It's strange!
I didn't think Amane likes this kind of play.
No... I don't like this!
Don't lie!
Nooo!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
There's a lot of sperm inside me...
Amane-onee-chan is having sex with onii-chan, too...
Nana-chan?
No... this is...No... this is...
It's alright, onee-chan.
I'm already like this, too.
Nana-chan...
Why...?
Amane-oneechan...
Nana is in pain...
Hey...
Are you listening, onee-chan?
I can't hold it anymore!
Then I'll let Nana-chan join us.
Nana-chan...
Stop this, Yousuke-san!
I feel sorry for Nana-chan!
You feel sorry?
How is it, Nana-chan?
It's big and hard, onee-chan, but I'm alright.
Why?
I'm a bad girl.
That's why onii-chan is going to punish me!
Nana-chan, what do you want?
Please, move it!
I like my pussy to be stirred!
Please, stir my pussy!
I understand, Nana-chan.
Onee-chan, my pussy feels so good and I can't bear it!
Nana-chan!
Don't say that!
Nana-chan, make Amane feel good as well!
OK...
There's still onii-chan's sperm left in onee-chan's pussy...
You must not lick that, Nana-chan!
There...
Not there...
We must stop this...
Are you feeling good, onee-chan?
Don't suck it!
Nana-chan, no!
Please!
This is fun!
More... more!
Do it more!
I don't care if I break!
Hey, don't just moan, make Amane feel good, too!
Yes!
I don't need it anymore!
No...
Onee-chan, please feel even better!
But Yousuke-san is already...
Onee-chan!
The stimulation is strong there, I'm going to cum again!
Let's cum together, onee-chan!
It's hot inside, Nana...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too!
Nana-chan...
I... I...
Noooo!
Onee-chan...
I'm happy that I came with onee-chan...
This is the best...
Nana-chan...
"Himegaoka hospital nurse escape incident"
"The hospitals and nurses that have been raped left."
"Ayanuma Chitose, the head nurse at that time, knows everything."
Oh, it's already late.
Where did Nana-chan and Shiratori-san go?
Slowly... gradually...
I'm feeling I'm touching the nurses' hearts...
I want to touch more, I want to know more...
Their hearts...
Their real faces...