www.SubDESU-H.net
That’s rich people for you.
What a huge mansion.
Who’re you?
What do you want?
Um... I came here for a job interview.
Interview?
Did we have any male applicants?
Well, whatever.
Come on in.
Hurry, get in.
My sister and I need to interview one other applicant.
So you go wait in Mother’s room.
Are you listening to me?
Yes.
It’s the first room on the second floor.
Just get up there.
Okay!
Jeez.
W
Mansion of Immorality
Four million?!
Yes.
Does that dissatisfy you?
O-Of course not!
It’s far beyond anything I could have imagined.
Oh? But I thought this was stated in the advert.
Two weeks as a live-in servant.
Compensation is four million yen.
...I thought it was four hundred thousand yen...
And even that is a fortune to a college student.
Mamiya would never be so cheap.
We are deep in the mountains and our servants tend to quit on us, so we’re prepared to offer a sizeable salary.
Well, this only concerns you if you pass our entrance test.
Entrance... test?
We have two applicants today.
The other applicant is currently being interviewed by my daughters.
No matter how much money we have, we would rather not waste it on useless employees.
Yeah...
It's not a big deal.
This job is very physical, so we’re just giving you a health exam.
Oh...
So... take off your clothes and masturbate for me.
Mastur... bate?
Correct. Mamiya’s employees are always given this test.
So that we can observe their body's endurance.
You have a fairly nice item there.
Unfortunately, it’s a bit covered.
Um... Will you please let me stop here?
No, I won’t.
To check its health, I must see it erect.
That’s easier said than done...
Good point.
I suppose doing this alone is difficult.
Mikako-san?
Yes...
This is Nonohara Mikako-san.
Hey, Mikako-san, could you show Sawatari-san here your naked body?
Huh?!
Very well.
Wait... um...
Oh, Sawatari-san, is this the first time you’ve seen a naked woman in person?
You didn’t strike me as being a virgin.
No... well, I...
Now, look.
Her flesh is a bit saggy, but her body still has plenty of life in it, no?
Now, next, masturbate for us.
You’ll do it, won’t you?
V-Very well.
If it is what the Mistress wishes of me.
Very nice.
You can see her naughty pussy.
Come now, Mikako-san, you must beg.
Please... watch me masturbate... Watch until you feel good.
Mikako-san takes care of her bikini line, but she still has hairy armpits.
How vulgar, no?
N-No.
Oh? Sawatari-san doesn’t seem to mind your armpit hair.
How nice for you.
That pleases me.
I’m such an old lady, but please enjoy watching me.
Hey, Mikako-san, there's a vibrator under the cushion, yes?
Yes.
Then let’s give him a better show with the vibrator.
Okay!
Yes... yes...
Mikako-san...
Mikako-san, you must inform us when you’re cumming.
Yes, ma’am.
Sawatari-san... please enjoy watching Mikako being so naughty...
Please watch me...
I’m cumming...
I’m cumming! I’m going to cum...!
Cumming!
Oh, how wonderful!
Such thick semen!
Looks like your bodily potential passes.
But this doesn’t quite show me how good an employee you’ll be.
You need more?
I only saw  it coming out.
I need to taste  it now.
Taste?
The smell of a virgin’s dick. So refreshing every time.
This... feels good...
This is still just a warm-up. The real thing begins now.
Delicious.
Your dick is so delicious.
Mistress... I can’t... I’m going to cum...
Very well.
Cum in my mouth.
The taste of a virgin’s dick and balls in my mouth... it's fantastic!
Sawatari-san, you look tired.
But we still aren’t finished.
You’ve always wanted to have sex, no?
Allow me to make that wish come true.
How does my pussy feel?
So hot.
Amazing, Sawatari-san...
You came twice already, but you’re still so hard.
Then I’ll put it in.
However... In a different hole.
Yes.
Your first experience will be my butt-hole.
Now, Sawatari-san, this ends your virginity.
Sawatari-san, you’re no longer a virgin.
Though not entirely...
Wh-Why so suddenly... in your butt?
I haven’t pooped in days.
I think that if you thrust yourself into me like this, I’ll get better.
You’re talking... like this is clinical...
Well, how does a woman’s anus feel?
It feels too good.
But let’s make it feel even better.
Oh, this sensation.
I can’t handle it.
It feels like I’m taking a huge crap over and over.
So exhilarating!
Sawatari-san, your dick fits my anus perfectly!
It feels great.
The intensity of it hitting my insides... I think I’m going to cum.
I think I like it.
Well, that’s...
This thrill... feels like a perfect defecation...
My butt loves it!
Anal sex while constipated is the best!
Mistress, I can’t hold back...
Just a bit longer...
Hold back just a bit longer.
We’re almost there.
Yes...
My butt...
I’m at my limit.
I’m cumming!
Very well. Sawatari-san, your semen enema... shoot me full!
It’s coming!
Sawatari-san, your hot semen... into my intestines...
So good!
Sawatari-san, your dick will come in very handy.
You’re hired.
Mother, we’ve finished our interview.
How were things on your end?
We think she’s a good match.
Um... your name is?
Mitarai Yuuna.
Her bust size is more than satisfactory.
And her pussy was also pretty.
But she hadn’t shaved her pubes, so we waxed them off.
Oh dear, you mustn’t do such cruel things.
But it seems both of them are great employees.
Huh...
Ah, you’re awake, I see.
Um... where am I?
My room.
I’m Asagiri Sachie.
Nice to meet you.
Sawatari-kun, do you know Mitarai-san?
She was the other applicant who was interviewed separately.
Y-Yes, I was.
But I was a bit out of it – I don’t remember much.
Well, you’ll be fine.
Don’t worry about it.
And also...
Sawatari-kun, your hair-down-there.
Mistress ordered you to have it shaved. Please, I hope you understand.
Now, now, it’s time to prepare for dinner.
Let’s go to the dining hall.
Now that I’ve had some delicious wine, let’s have the main course.
Hey, Mikako.
Yes, Kyouichi-sama?
This doesn’t concern you, so hurry things along and take care of me.
Very well.
Kyouichi, perhaps it’s because  he’s the youngest child – I think I spoiled him.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Um, didn’t we just finish dinner?
The next course is you.
No, I meant Mitarai-san.
Don’t you feel a bit anxious right now?
Actually, I found in our interview that Mitarai was still a virgin.
So I was thinking of giving her a graduation ceremony right here.
Her partner will be another almost-virgin, Sawatari-san.
Wh-What are you saying?!
I can’t move...
I mixed something in with your drink – it seems to be taking effect.
Marika, Marisa.
Take Mitarai-san to the table.
Yes.
As you wish.
Wh-Why are you doing this?
You must be crazy.
Oh, shut up.
You’re going to have this man break your hymen.
You should thank us!
A virginal man and woman have their first taste of painful love.
Ahh, just the thought of it makes me wet
Yes, yes, you were soaking wet earlier.
Please, don’t say strange things.
If you want proof, just look.
Is that... how did...?
The tea we had you drink before the interview. That's  how.
We released the sleeping desires in you.
We revealed your true colors as a lustful slut.
You should resign yourself to it.
This man is already hard and is waiting for you.
No!
Hey, we should have her prepare herself to accept Sawatari-san.
Oh, Mother, what a great idea.
Do as you wish.
No... I couldn’t...
Everyone is watching me... I should be embarrassed, but...
Yes... I can’t stop my fingers.
People are watching, but...
You’ve been wanting to do this the whole time.
Her sex-switch got turned on, I see.
Mother, we need to hurry this up before she cums on her own.
Mitarai-san looks like she’s ready.
Now, Sawatari-san, it’s your turn.
I want you two to be good coworkers, so we need to work on that relationship...
You understand, no?
But, this...
Stop moaning and just do as we say!
At this rate, she’d squeal with joy at anyone’s dick being shoved in her!
So all you need to do is fulfill that duty!
And it’s your big chance to ditch your  virginity too.
Hey, if you want, I can trade places.
Come, Sawatari-san, you must hurry or something strange might happen.
Mitarai-san, you really want to experience sex, no?
S-Sex...
You want to know the feel of a dick, don’t you?
Y-Yes, I do.
Sawatari-san... please put it in.
Your dick... into my pussy...
I want it inside.
Then I’m putting it in.
It’s coming in!
Sawatari-san’s hot...
My first dick...
Are you okay?
It feels strange, but... good... I think...
Congratulations, you two.
First dick and first pussy. Enjoy it, ‘kay?
It’s my first time... but it still feels so good...
Makoto-san, all is well with the filming, yes?
Yes. I’m getting some wonderful shots.
Yes.
Your dick... is hitting so deep...
Sawatari-san’s dick is hitting my uterus.
So good.
My pussy is throbbing.
Sex feels so good.
You’re turning out to be a good specimen.
Mitarai-san, you must keep this up until you climax.
Okay...
So hot...
Just drown in your own ecstasy.
Harder... harder, deeper, please!
Mess up my pussy!
My pussy... it’s melting...
Harder... harder and deeper, please!
Mitarai-san... I’m about to cum.
N-Not inside!
Please, outside... cum outside...
But I can’t pull out.
It’s cumming.
No, pull out!
But your legs are holding me in.
But I’ll get pregnant!
Holding back is bad for your health.
It’s coming!
Sawatari-san’s semen... it’s pulsing inside!
But it feels good.
Sex is perfect.
That was very good, Mother.
Their first time was a big success.
Sawatari Yukito
Mitarai Yuuna
Yes.
I look forward to the lessons for the party.
www.SubDESU-H.net