Take this!
Helmwige-nee-san! You're engaging them at too close range!
I'm fine!
Asgard, the realm of gods, Helheim, the realm of the dead, and Midgard, the realm of the humans...
At the center of the realms lies the world tree, connecting the three kingdoms.
However, the peace between them has started to crumble, even after the hand of God killed the Heretic...
W-What's happening to me down there?
Something inside me is getting hot!
What happened then?
When my blade touched him...
What happened to my sisters-!?
No! I can't stop myself-!
I-I'm cumming! No-!
N-No...!
What is this?!
Why did this appear?
SubDESU-H
Please thrust harder into my pussy!
It's reaching so far into me...!
It's gonna enter my uterus!
Do it deeper!
Thrust your cock deep inside me and give me your semen!
This feels so good!
No-!
I'm gonna cum!
Please let it out! Pour your semen deep inside me!
No! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Helmwige-nee-san!
Why was she like that?
I-I can't move by body-!
You're-!
Do you seek the truth?
What on Earth is happening?
You know of your destiny.
Destiny?
What do you mean?
What was that-?
Your memories have already been restored.
You will follow your destiny as a god slayer.
Huh?
The god rapes the child of a god,
and the man who did so will destroy the god.
Is this...?
But isn't this a man?
Why would I have such a destiny?
There's no way!
What does this mean?
Is this the solitary castle of the emperor's son?
Sigrun-nee-san!
Grimgerde! I was looking for you!
I was surprised when you disappeared during battle.
I'm not sure what happened, either.
Where are we?
This is the solitary castle of the emperor's son.
Although, I heard that it was destroyed by Helheim many years ago.
Destroyed by Helheim?
Why was I sent to such an ancient castle?
I wonder...
It's strange that you appeared in such a place.
Unless you were associated with Helheim!
Why would I be allied with Helheim?
That's what the higher-ups think.
I was sent here to capture you.
No way! Why would I be allied with Helheim?!
I guess you're right!
I don't think that you could pull such a thing off, anyway.
T-That wasn't a very funny joke, Sigrun-nee-san!
But it's true that you're under suspicion.
Also, Helmwige, who was with you, hasn't returned either.
Eh?
Helmwige-nee-san hasn't come back?
No way...
So that was-!
Do you know her whereabouts?
Eh?
N-No...
I was able to find you by asking the way of the dead oracle.
Eh? Dead oracle?
That's right, they told me that I'd find Helmwige here.
Helmwige...!
Hold up, Gertrude. Protecting this place is your top priority.
But-!
The barrier around Yggdra castle has weakened.
I know it's painful, but please bear with it.
We have to leave it up to Sigrun for now.
So, what is... the meaning of this?
Grimgerde! Answer me! What are you-!
No-!
What is this?!
My body, it's-!
No-!
What is this-?!
Eh?
I-Is this an aphrodisiac-?
I can't let her do what she wants!
Hey you, stop-!
No!
Don't!
D-Don't-!
This is torturous!
N-No-!
No-!
N-No! Don't lick my pussy so much-!
I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm gonna cum!
W-What happened to you, Grimgerde?
Doing such things so suddenly...!
W-What's with that thing-?!
I see, so she possessed the destiny of the god slayer.
Who would have thought that the power I lost 20 years ago
was resting inside the Walkure.
Now the gods will die and Asgard will be destroyed.
A-Amazing-!
G-Grimgerde! Hurry up and get ahold of yourself!
What's with that body-?
Why do I have to have my virginity taken by my younger sister?
Geez! I guess you won't understand in the state you're in, but-!
I-It hurts!
Is this the feeling of losing your virginity?!
No-!
I-It's so big-!
It's going in so deep!
I'm gonna lose it-!
This is-! It's so deep!
So deep...
No! It feels too good!
It's hitting my deepest spots-!
No! Thrust it deeper!
No!
Don't-! I'm gonna lose it!
My pussy is feeling too good, it's so deep-!
If only you were conscious... I'd...!
It feels so good!
Why does it feel so amazing?!
I can understand the legend of the god slayers now!
I-I'm-!
I-Is this the key-?
I'm gonna cum, I'm cumming!
Your semen is shooting out inside me!
Huh? Where am I?
Sigrun-nee-san! W-Where are we? And what happened to me...?
I guess you don't remember anything.
I-I'm sorry...
Wha-? Helmwige-nee-san!
She'll wake up!
What's happening-
Why am I like this-?!
It's funny seeing you embarrassed after what happened...
We made love so passionately...
You even took my virginity...
No way! Then that was-?!
It wasn't a dream.
It's what you did.
Helmwige as well.
But-! Nee-san's virginity?!
Why would I...?
No-! Nee-san! That's-!
I guess it's not here anymore. That's too bad.
No, don't-!
Sigru-!
Don't-!
So you were the one in possession of the destiny of the god slayer.
Sigrun-nee-san, why do you know that?
The god rapes the child of a god, and the man who did so will destroy the god.
It's that old legend.
However, 20 years ago, such a thing did happen.
God tried to kill that person, however...
No way!
Then that scene was...?
You must not have been alone.
Yes, the weapon you carry now is of the divine spirit...
The original Grimgerde perished when the magic exchanged your bodies.
So that scene really happened?
My memory, it's...!
So she was a victim of the aftermath of god's whim?
Then I will deal with god...
So that's why if you're going to pursue that destiny...
I'll help you, okay?
Sigrun-nee-san!
It'll probably be quite interesting.
Besides, I don't think we can win against Helheim without you!
Don't blame me when you regret it!
It's something that I decided.
And nor would I blame my younger sister, so don't worry!
To get to the god's throne,
we must activate the keys of our sisters and our mother.
So that light was...
Yes, the key is overwritten if the bearer feels aroused.
That's a magical seal, so it's inside here...
Helmwige and I have already been overwritten.
We should return to the castle now.
Also, you might want to alter Helmwige's memory with your magic.
It should be fine if we alter the others' memories for that period too.
I'll put some aphrodisiac into the food and deliver it to you later.
You're not in the complete form either, so be careful.
Jeez, Sigrun-nee-san is enjoying this far too much!
If it isn't Grimgerde.
I heard from Sigrun that we have something to talk about...
However, I also have something to talk about...
A talk with Gertrude-nee-san?
I heard that you were with Helmwige... Um...
Y-Yes, I was with Helmwige-nee-san all this time...
With her, I...
I-I see, so you and Helmwige...
Jeez, Gertrude-nee-san. Are you jealous again?
D-Don't say such idiotic things!
Grimgerde, are you making fun of me?
It's the truth!
You always stare longingly when Helmwige-nee-san and I are together...
I-If you're going to make fun of me any further-!
Oh! How scary!
Being jealous doesn't suit you, Gertrude-nee-san.
How about this?
Damn you-!
H-Hey! Stop it-!
I did this to Helmwige too...
D-Damn you!
Why are you-?!
I comforted Helmwige-nee-san with these lips...
My saliva will make you sensitive.
S-Stop it!
No more-!
S-Stop-!
You're sensitive, aren't you Gertrude-nee-san?
Just like Helmwige-nee-san!
Just like Helmwige...?
N-No! Stop this! Stop this at once, Grimgerde!
Your body is being honest, though. It's very cute!
Stop this!
You're not so convincing when you're like this down here...
Don't! That's-!
I-I haven't had a bath yet-! Stop-!
Gertrude-nee-san, I can smell your sweaty scent. It tastes so good!
You're going to cum just from having your clitoris played with?
It's a different shape from Helmwige-nee-san's...
Yours might be more beautiful...
I-I can't bear this any further-! Seriously, please stop!
You have to be honest with yourself, Nee-san.
Otherwise, I'll have to punish you!
W-What are you doing-?
I've got an interesting tool.
Helmwige-nee-san likes it too!
Grimgerde! Why do you have such a thing?!
Isn't it well-made?
The oracle gave it to me!
Although, it's apparently the tool of judgment.
The oracle gave it to you?!
That's crazy-!
W-Wait-!
If you do any more, I'll-!
Stop, I beg you! Please stop this, Grimgerde!
Please, no more!
Nee-san, you're being too loud.
I already said that I'm putting it in.
Grimgerde! You-!
If you're wondering about the pain,
it'll quickly heal and you'll start feeling good!
Stop-!
Don't-!
Stop!
Your feelings and your body are acting differently.
I suggest you obey the latter, Nee-san!
Don't touch me!
T-This isn't-!
Doesn't this feel good?
In that case, I'll make you feel even better!
How is it, Nee-san?
Oh no! I'm peaking too!
Don't be stupid!
This is too much-!
Nee-san, please be honest already!
This is nothing-!
Why are you still saying that?
No-!
Stop-! Not so hard! It's too much, stop! It's-!
This is-!
Stop it!
Gertrude-nee-san, if you won't be honest, I'm going to stop.
Nee-san...
Please ask me properly.
Please stay...
I can't hear you, Nee-san.
Then I suppose we're done here...
Wait-! Please keep thrusting, Grimgerde!
Please thrust harder and deeper inside me!
This is amazing-!
So deep, it's so deep!
It feels good! Thrust harder!
This feels incredible!
You're rubbing against my insides and hitting against my uterus!
Your pussy is so wet, Nee-san!
It's like your insides are crying out in pleasure!
It feels great, Grimgerde!
Your cock is twisting my insides-! No-!
Nee-san, you're going to cum, aren't you?
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Me too!
I'm gonna cum!
I-I can't hold back! I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
It's pouring into my uterus...
My memory, it's-!
I see, so this was what was sealed inside me?
Nee-san, I'll comfort you again.