As the train runs through the city,
you're hemmed in by a crowd of strangers.
A bunch of people you don't want to be touched by.
Even cute girls are shoving you...
You must not touch the skin of those maidens.
Manabe Yuuka
Occupation: Office Lady
Blood Type: B
Hobby: Shopping
Within this enclosed space within society,
This lonely city makes your son grieve.
Katajima Kumi
Occupation: part-timer
Blood Type: O
Hobby: Listening to Music
You're damned if you touch,
and you're damned if you don't.
Mitamura Hitomi
Occupation: 3rd Year High School
Blood Type: A
Hobbies:
Reading books and watching movies
If you don't listen to me, "the finger" will attack you.
molester group
Chikan Juunintai
Ten
We will be experiencing an emergency stop due to the stop signal.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please wait for a while.
The train will now resume it's scheduled run.
Sorry for making you wait.
Tochi, we'll be changing the schedule.
How many seconds has passed?
You just passed by billboard 2-7.
About 1 minute and 30 seconds.
That's a bonus.
I can do it once more if there's time.
I can do it again twice.
The girls will hate you if you're like that.
The young men must prefer frequency than the length of time.
You can't bear with it if you do it too many times.
Yeah, I can't do any more.
You just passed by billboard B.
We're almost on the next station.
The door will open on this side
30 seconds remaining.
Put her clothes back on.
Damn! (?)
Chikan
Juunintai
Appears
W
Here comes the next one!
Here!
Hey Amemiya!
Ouch!
Why are you always watching the girls?
You're such a pervert.
It's not like that.
If you really want to see, this one is more erotic.
What's this?
It's an American DVD I bought from the internet.
It's uncensored.
No way! Really!?
Yeah, I just got it yesterday.
Their porn is uncensored you know.
Well, the concept comes from Japanese anime though.
What? It's from an anime?
You don't know, do you?
It's so erotic.
Ouch...
Buy the real one.
Rather than drawings.
Are you alright?
The real one's better than the video right?
Have you ever done it for real?
Do you know about the Chikan Juunintai?
Chikan Juunintai?
What's that? An ero game?
They're real! They grope inside trains.
No way!? All ten of them?
Stupid! It's not like that.
They give money to the victim and she'll let them do it.
The 10 of them surround the victim to make it unnoticeable.
Really?
Yeah, for real.
She lets them do whatever they want.
Won't they get caught?
I don't know, probably not since there are 10 of them.
A girl from section 2 was attacked.
Really?
If you let them touch, they'll give money.
That's great!
I'd like to try that.
It's said that it costs quite a lot.
It's cheaper to find some prostitutes.
What? How foolish.
Some people prefer molesting than doing some prostitutes you know.
Takahashi Investigation Company
Takahashi Investigation Company?
Do you have some business with me?
You don't have to run away.
How cold.
You can tell us right?
There are only two ways to track us.
First is from our customers.
Second is the cops.
You don't have any money even if you're a customer.
Doesn't seem like you're a cop either.
I saw it.
I saw you guys molesting this morning.
What a coincidence.
Yes, I saw it too.
You groped someone this morning too right?
I didn't do anything of the sort.
Oh, but you tried to, right?
Amateurs should be more careful.
It's dangerous if you get caught.
Calling someone an amateur, who are you guys anyway?
We are the pros of molestation.
The pros of molestation?
Yeah, we are the...
Chikan Juunintai
Special Company Takahashi Investigation Company
President Takahashi Ganari
Takahashi Investigation Company President Takahashi Ganari...
That's my business as a front.
As for my other business, I help with the molesting.
It costs quite a bit though.
Including taxes, it's about 1010k yen.
1010k yen!?
So much...
20k for each of us.
The remaining 10k is for the girl.
Well, since it's a special hobby, you can't do it if you not willing to pay for it.
If you want to become a man, don't push yourself to try to molest.
I can introduce you a nice store.
Yeah, I know a cute beautician nearby. It's much cheaper there and you can enjoy it.
What? You're telling me about this kind of store?
Didn't you say you can't do it unless she's Japanese?
Please stop it.
I don't want to touch women.
Please stop talking about prostitutes or molesting.
What's this?
I'm the one who bound her.
Isn't it cute?
I don't know which part of her gear broke
She can't stand up normally.
Men won't be satisfied if she can't stand up you know.
Well, I'm expert at binding from there on.
Not all woman will let me bind them though.
That's all, isn't that cold?
We are... here to fix the broken gear.
If you change your mind, you can come back anytime.
If you'll pay us, I'll teach you a part of yourself that you don't even know.
And we'll have a good time.
Is that so?
Amamiya-kun.
Eh?
Are you going home now?
Yes...
How did you prepare so much.
Did you do something bad?
It's my savings, from my new year's gift and my allowance.
Ah~, kids from rich families really are different.
I wanted to be born in that kind of family.
Once you hire us, we can't refund your money if you cancel.
I know.
Here's the transmitter.
Just do as we rehearsed.
I won't show my face and I won't leak my voice.
Yes.
We can't make our target just any person.
You must touch the ones who won't panic if she's being touched.
Do you get it?
Well, kinda.
It's my instinct from many years of experience.
Maybe we can go for her, how about it?
I see she's not your type.
How about her?
That one?
How about... that one?
You're really picky.
If it was me, I'd go for her.
What's your type?
Uhm...
I see, it's her...
I can't?
You've got some nerves.
Let's do it.
Yes.
Ok, let's roll.
Hurry!
Oh... ok.
Ansenbou, please stay behind yellow line.
*censored*ya, *censored*ya.
Target, lock on.
Negotiation Successful.
Please have fun.
30 seconds remaining...
Make it quick.
Well, don't be down.
Don't mind it.
You still have time.
Do your best next time.
Hey, I think she's your type.
How is it? Wanna try?
Yeah.
Well, if you don't cause problems to others or to society.
Your freedom will be respected.
Oh my, keep yourself up.
I think this is no good.
He's not the type to get into this.
He should give up early if he can't.
Yeah, if he cross the dangerous bridge, even if he can't do it,
We might also be in danger.
It's the job we accepted.
We must continue until he succeeds for this day.
Eh?
Ok?
It's the order from our team captain.
Keep your spirits up.
Alright.
Didn't I say keep your spirits?
You'll fail if you're careless.
Hitomi-chan...
Kick off.
Eh?
Come.
You want to touch her right?
The negotiation was successful.
Hurry up kid.
No... I really can't...
We are experiencing an emergency stop due to the stop signal.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please wait for a while.
Good job, you had quite a problem.
Well yeah.
He meddle a lot though.
Even though you said that, it's good that we can earn 100k yen for just standing around.
Ah!
What's the matter?
I gave him twice the allowance so I receive got 8k yen.
It's alright, you had fun anyway.
I didn't have fun!
This is work!
Wanna have have drink?
I'll treat you for today.
As I expect from Shima-san, you're so nice.
That kid... will he be alright?
He might regret not losing his virginity.
That's not what I mean.
What was he thinking?
Stop it, we have to stay away from it.
Well it's normal for kids like him.
Are you going home now?
Eh?
Yeah.
Amamiya-kun too?
Nope, I skipped today.
No way...
Eh?
Why?
Because Amamiya-kun is such a serious guy.
No I'm not.
I'm quite a bad guy you know.
Eh?
Thank you.
This is the first time we had to talk.
Yeah.
Go!
13th train going for *censored* the door will  now close.
Please stop rushing in
Countdown start, time remaining 5 minutes and 30 seconds.
Well then, let's roll.