Yuu...
I'm sorry...
...about today
Yuu...
Yuu... Please...
Yuu... I feel it!
Inside me, Yuu is-
Yuu...
It's so hot... It's hitting me inside...
I'm becoming hot too...
So deep...
I can't...
Yuu...
I...
Yuu's...
... Big...
Good...
Yuu... It's so good...!
This strong feeling...
Your feelings and her feelings...
That's why it reacts this much.
Because it's you, who spoils her without saying anything.
That's why...
At this rate, you'll really...
If not, both you and the girl will...
I'm sorry... Onii-chan...
SubDESU-H Presents
Original Video Animation
Cool Ponytail's Miserable Begging
～Loveless Magic Uniform
♥～
Just as always...
It's morning!
You'll be late!
I'm leaving ahead of you!
Hi there, Rie!
Wa-... Ayaka?
What's wrong at this hour?
I kinda got a little curious, you see...
About if your beloved boyfriend has been here all this time...
W- What...?
He just went home...
You love him that much?
Yup.
I can't... suppress my feelings...
I'm sure you're not fit for each other.
You'll only hurt each other!
We... Won't...
But I know you will! When I look at how you are now, you're only getting worse.
And, It's this town...
Even if you say it like that...
Rie...
So this is the reality?
There's no way he'll forgive me...
All the way...
...deep inside...
Come!
Deep... Deeper... Please...
Like this...
With you...
I'm sorry...
I love you!
I love you because you're you!
I'm sorry...
Calling you out at a time like this...
I made you skip a class...
It's bad of me... Doing that...
Would you prefer me in swimsuit?
Kinda... You wouldn't want to see this old lady in a swimsuit...
I love you...
Eh...? Maho-san?
Your feelings are overflowing.
If you don't end it now,
Everything will disappear.
Think about Yuu.
She really... Noticed after all...
Why do I have to...?
Even though I love him so much...
It's so... hard...
I'm sure you're not fit for each other.
That's not true...
Yuuji-kun!
Sensei? Kirisaki-sensei? Are you alright?
Sensei!
At a time like this...
Is that right?
Yuu...
Come...
Yuu!
I'm sorry...
Yuu's the only one who can do this...
Thank you...
All the way in...
Good... Good...
It's good...!
More... More...!
Yuu... It's amazing...
As long as I'm here, I'll always... always...
Even if we're connected, I will...
It's alright... You can cum already.
Onii-chan...
It's you, okay?
It'd be bad if you stayed here...
Her status... And there's your status, right?
I'm sorry, but for tonight you'll have to go home.
Her feelings were overflowing.
That is...
Tomorrow you'll understand... About her, about everything.
Sensei! Good morning!
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
I only fainted.
I'm sorry for making you worry like that...
Class is starting, you need to hurry up.
Yes!
Good morning.
You need to hurry too, Touno-kun.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Are you ok?
Yes, I'm ok.
There's nothing to worry about.
Her feelings were too strong.
She doesn't remember you anymore.
The too strong feelings were making her suffer.
And the place to be released from that is here.
I'm... Sorry... If I'd have known It'd turn out like this...
From the start I would have...
I knew you were wrapped up in such strong feelings...
And yet I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything...
Onii-chan...
I'm sorry...
I love you...
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan... Onii-chan...
Onii-chan... I'm sorry...
Ending up like this...
The truth is, I-
Onii-chan...
I'm sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's fine... How're you feeling?
I'm fine.
You worry too much, Ayaka.
Really?
Maybe you're right.
You want to go drinking or something?
What are you saying? You've just recovered.
Hmm... I'm kinda relieved...
Maybe it was because I slept in a hospital?
Hm? What's the matter?
It's nothing, I just thought I smelled a nostalgic smell...
Come on, let's go...