Houkago Nyan Nyan
......
Um, you know?
I have a favor to ask, Ryuu.
SubDESU-H
Presents
Houkago Nyan Nyan (Afterschool Nyan Nyan)
You really want to do this?
Yep. After all, you said you’d do it.
I did, but...
And besides, no one comes by this classroom, so we’ll be safe.
It’s locked, too.
F-Fine, I’ll do it, but...
Yay!
Even so, saying "let me watch you masturbate" out of nowhere...
What kind of sexual harassment is this?
Well, people have described it to me, but I can’t tell what it’s like unless I watch.
You’re the only one I can ask, Ryuu. Please?
I think I walked right into this one.
It’s true. It looks different from in the books.
It’s getting bigger!
Can you keep quiet?
I can't concentrate.
Okay.
It really is starting to get hard...
Just like the others in class said.
Shit. I wanna finish fast!
C-Can I touch it?
Finished?
Th-That should do, right?
I’m leaving now.
It was over much faster than I thought.
Much faster...
Hey! One more time, okay?
Please, please, please?
Isn’t it okay?
In which case...
Come on, Senpai.
This is embarrassing.
Well, I showed you mine.
Show me yours.
You’re right, but...
You said you’d help me out.
So do it fast.
L-Like this?
Th-The real thing!
That’s right. Keep going.
It’s gotten hard again.
So boys really do do things like this.
H-How does it feel?
How?
Good, I guess.
R-Really?
Wait...
Don’t touch it!
But it’s wet.
Not so...!
Don’t!
It’s dirty!
What is this? It tastes erotic.
This... Is this okay?
It’s dirty!
Senpai, you’re being really erotic.
You pervert, Ryuu.
B-B-But you...
Horn-dog! Pimp! Ero-sorcerer!
S-Sorry.
But...
I didn’t mind.
G-Go slowly okay?
Yes!
I don’t want it to hurt.
I’ll try.
Huh?
It’s inside.
But...
I’m... I’m fine.
T-Then... I’ll start moving.
It’s so...
Senpai... You’re so wet.
It’s thrusting so deep...
I want to go in deeper... It’s so different from when I’m alone.
Go slower! I’ll melt!
S-Senpai...
N-No! No!
I guess we did it.
Sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I said I didn’t mind.
Yes, but still...
Close your eyes.
If I do that, I can’t see.
Never mind, just do it.
Her blushing cheeks got redder.
And her voice got higher.
That’s how it began.
Nao, my parents are going to be on business trips for a week, so...
So, when they’re gone...
I couldn’t believe it.
Azuki was always so shy and serious.
And before we started dating, she didn’t even know how to have sex.
I want you to do nasty things to me.
She became that way after only a week alone with me.
Lovely Day ~ My Seven Days Alone With My Girlfriend
S-So, I’m starting.
Are you sure you’re okay?
Yes.
See? You’re still nervous and stiff.
But, this is okay.
I can do more than usual.
Awesome!
This is the first time I’ve seen it.
Um, listen...
I might scream out "no," but keep going.
I’m fine with it... Because I love you... I want to...
Um, you can make noises.
Okay...
Expose her pussy, spread her legs wide...
...And then eat her out.
Oh... Not there!
Not my butt!
Hey, my fingers... They're inside.
Can you see?
Yeah.
Azuki...
Do you want me in there?
Tell me to and I’ll do it.
Come inside me.
Then, I’ll put it in.
Azuki, your pussy is so wet.
I’m coming inside.
I wasn’t able to do this earlier because I didn’t want her to hate me.
But I still wanted to because I love her.
And now she's says it's okay, so I’ll do anything.
No, slower...
Keep going.
Nao!
Nao! Nao!
But, hey, why did you say that all of a sudden?
Um, you see... We’re a little behind, right?
I-I guess you’re right. Though, I’ve been wanting to for some time now.
My friends, you see...
They say it’s weird for people our age not to do it, especially boys.
So they said that you were losing patience, and that you’d leave me for someone else.
And that’s why you asked me to?
You shouldn’t have!
But listen! I really enjoyed it.
I was a little scared, but...
But, when tomorrow comes, I want to...
Yeah.
The next morning, I woke up to the smell of my precious girlfriend making me breakfast.
I thought I was the luckiest guy in the world.
Nao, wake up. It’s breakfast time.
Wow, this is really good.
Really? Thanks!
I cooked your favorite foods, Nao.
And there are seconds if you want.
Azuki is so sweet.
A good cook, gentle, mature, and so pure she puts others to shame.
But her body is...
I want to do many sexy things.
Do what you want to me.
Do what I want? If she suggests that... That means I’ll suddenly do things like this.
Nao... We’re still eating.
Her breasts... Even though they’re big, they've always been embarrassing for her.
She’d never let me touch them before.
What a waste.
They’re so...
What?
I could even do this.
No!
I’m scared!
Awesome.
I can’t stop.
But... Still...
Will you suck on it this time?
H-How should I do it?
I’ll show you, so suck it.
The mouth that was just eating breakfast is now filled with my dick.
Just like that.
What an erotic face.
She probably doesn’t even realize what she’s doing.
But her mouth is so slobbery and hot.
I can’t stand it.
S-Sorry!
I didn’t mean!
I’m really sorry!
Um, sorry!
I went too far that day.
But the next day, first thing in the morning...
Can I?
I-It’s okay.
Oh, I can’t do this.
Keep at it.
Oh, that’s gross, Nao!
But I’ve always wanted to try this.
And I’m sure you're interested in it too.
Yeah, but...
It’s sweet all the way inside.
No!
Not that.
Azuki, did you just cum?
Did that feel good?
Nao! Not this pose!
It’s weird.
Weird? It’s not weird. It’s normal.
Everyone does this.
But, Nao...
It’s so deep.
Super slutty.
Nao!
I-I’m scared.
Hug me.
Azuki.
Azuki...
Let’s go in the bedroom.
Yeah.
And three days passed in a flash like that.
But, I still had four days left with Azuki.