Senpai's penis is totally amazing!
Penis is good.
Please let me off, Kaneda-kun.
It's only 3 times, so it's okay...
My test grade is really bad, so anymore...
If I'm found doing something like this,
I'll be expelled from here.
Don't worry about it, I'll help you with that.
What are you doing...?
Sport's club play is somehow more active, isn't it?
The sportsmanship inside those boy is
going crazy within all of them.
It's something that exceeds my imagination of their play.
Leona-sama,
If we're talking about physical exercise, It's because
all the girls in the sport clubs are joining us.
So it's unavoidable.
The rest out there would be from the culture club association,
so what do you think about that?
That's right, It's about time they came here.
Let's pay a visit to everyone's place, shall we?
I can't wait to see...
What kind of things we're going to experience there?
It's about Culture Club that we're talking about,
hence the lower half of their body must be somehow intellectual.
Yamanaka-san, what do you think about this culture club's hunt?
At the same time, I feel sorry for Leona-san though...
Don't you feel that way too, Yamagata-san?
You're with the tea club, right?
Yes, we are...
Is that so...
Err... Is there something you need?
Wha... What is it?!
Sorry about that,
We're interested in your tea club's stuffs.
Like this hard tool in here.
Do you feel this hard already?
Let me make you feel better.
I understand,
I'm gonna lick it soon.
There, It feels good right?
Hey, don't come that fast!
I'm sorry...
Tea club aren't you?
Why don't you show me the way?
No, don't do that!
No~!
I'm cumming!
Drink my coming tea!
With this, your thing is gonna be longer than before.
No~!
Don't squeeze that hard on my breasts!
Something rough like that...
It's fine, touch it as you like.
What do you think of my breast?
I feel weak at my nipples...
Aren't you interested in my pussy?
Look, your penis is getting big.
If you want to lick it, then do it already.
Hey, you down there! Lick my pussy!
Ye..Yes!
Good... It feels good!
Tea club's penis doesn't seem bad at all.
Hey, splash me... splash me with your semen!
Good~!
Semen...
Splash me!
Splash me!!
A lot of semen, It smells good.
This semen is good...
This penis is also good!
You still can do it, right?
Hey, don't you hold back.
If you want to come, let it out inside of me.
Good... good... It's good~!
If you want to come, just let it come out already!
Amazing, It feels so hot!
It's hot, my pussy is burning!
Hot... I want that hot thing~!
It's still not over, you know.
Even though you've come this much, It won't be over this way.
It's great, let's do it more!
It's irritating me.
They dare to do something to me, Morimoto Leona.
I told them to hunt some prey and bring them here already,
but no one came back.
What do you think they're doing?
What are you smiling for?
Are you fooling around with Morimoto Leona?
Matsuno, let him lie down there!
Hey... hey..., does my heel make you feel happy?
Kaoru, do you know your place?
I love... I really love... Onee-sama.
You're my pet.
A pet's job is to be obedient to what their masters tell them.
I'll be obedient... I'll do whatever you tell me.
That's why, please don't hate me!
Kaoru.
Kaoru, pull down my underwear.
Yes, Leona-sama.
Look up here.
Clean that up.
Yes...
It's stink, right?
No...
It should stink,
It's because I played with them since yesterday
and no one came inside of it.
No, It's my favorite smell indeed.
What, do you feel good with my whip?
You really are a pervert.
Kaoru, do you want to come inside me?
Yes!
Do you want to come inside Morimoto Leona?
What are you thinking?
That's because I really love Onee-sama.
A pet wants to come inside of their master?
I want to make Onee-sama feel happy.
Don't get me wrong.
What makes me happy would be your scream!
There... there... why don't you let me make it better.
What is it, you want to cry already?
I'm masturbating on top of you,
How lucky are you?
Yes!
You can't!
I'm doing it with my own pet, kinda like someone and their slave.
Onee... -sama, I can't~!
Kaoru, you're really some animal aren't you?
You're spewing out a lot,
but you're still doing fine.
If it's for Onee-sama, I'll do anything until I die.
Then, can you do your best with this?
This... is... something I didn't expected.
Onee-sama... Onee-sama...
Kaoru, inside is...
Onee-sama!
Please forgive us, Leona-sama!
You refused to do what Morimoto Leona ordered,
what exactly do you want?
Please forgive us!!
This academy is a property of the Morimoto's family,
So I am the superintendent of everything
inside this academy.
I don't forgive any rejection.
I'm sorry, but why are we part of this too?
You're also guilty of participating in their act.
Well, I don't really have any interest in a weakling like you.
Then, we'll think...
We'll think of something that would make you happy.
Hm... what is that?
Hey, what about Saori?
Don't worry, I'll give her some sleeping drugs to make her sleep.
Let's work hard out there!
Played... played it out!
What are we gonna do?
It's only Otokawa-kun in here.
I don't want to think of what Leona would say,
if we don't bring someone in there.
Don't have much choice, let's bring her then.
So, that's all that you brought for me?
Forgive me, we lack people out there...
So let's wait for a little while.
Is that so?
Matsuno, insert that thing into them.
Did we put it in too much?
Quickly spank it and make them wake up already!
We're gonna start it soon.
She's moaning too much because of the drug's effect,
did it work too much on her?
That woman, somehow made me develop feelings for her.
Hey, let me have it!
Ah, good sound down there.
You're wet already.
I'll make out with you.
It feels good in condition.
It's good pheromones...
You like to be violated, right?
How about in here?
No, It's hurts...
Hm...
Where is it?
I'll taste your breast, okay.
Women like you, don't have to be ashamed at all.
It's amazing, your pussy is drenched like this.
No... no...
There, you can touch  my pussy too...
Yes, that pussy down there.
It feels so good.
Eh, this one is a virgin?
It's rare these days
for a big girl like this to be a virgin.
So at the same time, we can rob you of your virginity too.
You... don't you touch there!
No, not anal!
I said no...
I'll take that too.
Hey.. If you let your guard down,
it will be loose from the inside.
We can use this tool for something like this too...
Good...
Sorry, Otokawa-kun!
Good... you're even using your tongue...
Otokawa-kun!
Eh, what am I doing out here?
Well... It's okay.
Hello, Onee-sama.
As what Onee-sama's been told, there's no problem with the social club.
There's some good friends inside of it too.
Of course, that's someone I properly picked.
The Academy and the social club are already in our hands.