No. He's forcing me!
Damn you... Enough already!
Don't hold back.
It feels good, right?
Don't kid yourself.
It doesn't feel good!
For a pig to have his way with me...
You're dripping wet.
Shut up!
Why is my body feeling this way?
My body is...!
Fatso's dick is poking me.
How does it feel being raped on your own desk?
I'm not being raped!
I'm letting you fuck me.
Who gave you permission to kiss me?
Don't act strong when your face looks like that.
Hey!
Don't move so suddenly!
Stop it!
Cum inside me... Reaching so deep...
CUM! CUM!
Your sperm is deep inside me. I might become pregnant!
Geez. Attacking me anywhere...
You don't care if people see.
Come on. Class is ending soon.
Just go already!
I'm going back too.
Sensei...
Oh... It's Satsuki.
Don't surprise me.
In fact, since when were you here?
It's not fair if you only do Shizuka.
It's soaked in perverted juices.
Satsuki, I can't anymore.
When did you and Shizuka become so close?
Did you enslave Shizuka with your dick?
It doesn't concern you.
You're right...
I'm sorry.
It doesn't concern me.
When did it become hard?
It's alright, don't hold back.
I am yours to control.
Your dick is coming inside me!
Your dick is amazing!
It's Sensei's treasure, after all.
Idiot! Keep your voice down!
What'll we do if someone comes in?
Sensei...
Your dick...
Satsuki...
Huh?
I thought I heard Satsuki's voice.
I wonder where she went.
Sensei's dick is pulsating.
It'll be bad if you don't cum soon.
I know.
My pussy is being fucked by your penis and it feels good, so rough.
Better than when I did Shizuka.
Sensei...
It's alright.
Mess me up.
Be rougher and tease my pussy more.
Fill it up with Sensei's sperm.
Cum anytime, my pussy is only for you.
Sensei's sperm...
There's so much inside my pussy...
You're still big.
But I have a photo-shoot after this, so maybe next time.
Alright?
SubDesu-H and HentaiFreak presents:
JK to Inkou kyoushi 4
Original Animation Video
Continuation ~ Satsuki ~ Sexy Model’s Inviting Huge Tits
What happened, Satsuki?
That was amazing, did something happen?
I just wanted to go all out... I was in that mood.
You get what I mean?
You're lying.
I'm sure something definitely happened.
Shizuka-chan...
Are you ready?
You're being called.
Yeah... See ya.
It's big.
Won't Shizuka come back soon?
In that case I should make you cum soon.
Sensei's dick is really big.
Are you really that aroused because of Shizuka?
N-No, this is just...
Why am I this popular?
I'll make you cum a lot.
Okay.
Let's work together again.
Now to make Satsuki confess.
I'm sure that something really happened.
Changing Room
Satsuki...
Why are you here?
You finished?
You came again?!
The manager said that you didn't have to.
Oh. I know.
You wanted my body again?
You're wrong.
I have no choice.
Beg for it and lick my feet.
Sensei's dick got bigger again when Shizuka came.
You should be happy that you're able to lick my feet.
There's no need for that today.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Wow. It's becoming harder...
Don't get ahead of yourself, trash!
Shizuka is still talking.
I'm fine with being trash.
Never mind that, could you buy some juice?
Huh? I'm a gofer?!
You sure have guts.
Your penis feels like it's about to explode.
Did Shizuka leave?
Sensei's dick got really hard when you were talking with Shizuka.
Sa-Satsuki...
It still hasn't calmed down.
What's wrong with me?
This is enough for today.
No way...
You were looking at Shizuka, right?
A-About that...
You can't be selfish.
Geez...
Enough already.
Sa-Satsuki?!
Did you lay your hands on Satsuki again?
That's not true!
Wait. You really did become a gofer!
You're the one who told me to buy it, trash!
Anyways, you and Satsuki...
I'm alright, Shizuka.
He didn't do anything to me, okay.
Later.
Wait a minute, Satsuki!
Here you go, it fell over here.
Geez. Falling so deep in here...
Just a little bit more.
What the? It's wet.
What the hell is this?
Could this be?
Hey, pig. Don't tell me you were masturbating here by yourself!
Hey! Where do you think you're touching? You pig!
Hey! Stop it!
Don't do as you please!
Showing off your ass...
I can't help but think you're seducing me!
Screw you! I'm not seducing you!
In a place like this, stop it, you pig!
Looks like you're wet already.
Now who is the one that's doing what they want?
What the hell are you saying?
Of course I'm not...
Hey... Wait!
Stop!
I told you to stop it, there are still people around!
In a place like this, listen to me!
Too late, after being shown an ass like this...
A guy who doesn't put it in is gay!
Coming, it's coming in...!
Your penis is inside me in a place like this...
Even though I told you not to...
You're turned on already? You sure love it, Shizuka!
Who is?
Don't call my name so easily, you idiot!
People will come!
Enough already!
I won't stop until I cum!
Even you'd like to cum, right?
Geez. You perverted old man...!
Stop it!
Hey, fatso. What are you doing?
Someone is coming!
No way! It's Senpai and the others!
I'll be fired if they see me like this!
Man, that sucks. Yeah, it does! I mean, he was really...
What the hell is this guy thinking at a time like this?
Wait...
What the hell?
You can't be serious!
He’s just too forceful...
No. He's forcing me... Ew, my nipples are erect!
She's getting popular.
Do you mean Shizuka?
Yeah, she's becoming popular lately.
She's getting ahead of herself.
She's popular, but she'll fail soon enough.
She's too friendly as well.
You won't be able to know how girls like that think.
She's just a child, so I bet she's treating this as just a part-time job.
By the way, there's a girl that's always at her back.
Oh? You mean Satsuki-san?
Yeah, the image doesn't suit her.
Come to think of it...
That girl is stiffer.
You're right about that.
Hey! Calm down!
Let's go, we still have to wake up early tomorrow.
Are you alright, Shizuka?
Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
I'm not frustrated!
Th-They are...
Calm down.
As if I could!
Fuck me already!
What?
I'm telling you to make me feel good!
That's the only thing you're good at anyway.
It's reaching all the way inside me!
Be rougher!
More, make me feel better!
Mess up my pussy with your dick!
Geez, getting aroused this much...
You're getting so wet.
Shut up! Just move your hips and blow me away.
My pussy is being penetrated!
Keep at it and mess me up!
Even though it's the fatso's penis, it feels so good. Searching through my pussy...!
What? What is it?
Hey!
Beg for it!
Huh?
Come on, if you want me to move, beg for it!
What the hell are you saying?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
Move it already!
Beg for it. I'll make you cum if you do.
Alright already.
Please Sensei, do it!
Come on, I already asked you.
I personally asked you already.
Well, that's about what I can expect from you.
Hey, so suddenly...
What's wrong? Tell me what's wrong!
My pussy is tingling.
No way!
It feels so good!
Come, stinky sperm. Fill me up!
Make my mind go blank!
No, what's this?
Amazing, it feels so good!
I’m blanking out...
Fatso's dick came out!
Geez, you really have no integrity. You fatass!
Just because I'm cute, doesn't mean you can do it in a place like this. It's not normal!
Same goes for you.
Though I heard something interesting.
Something wrong?
Just a bit.
They were Senpai, so I trusted them.
I didn't think they thought of me that way.
It's because I'm cute, isn't it?
Hey, Shizuka...
We're shooting on location tomorrow, so don't be late.
I'll forgive you f or not using honorifics too.
Smile, please.
Good.
Sensei...
We finished early yesterday.
Was it alright?
It's alright.
Don't worry about it.
You did it with Shizuka.
What are you saying, Satsuki?
You know that's not true.
You're right.
I'm in charge when you get aroused by Shizuka, right?
Come on. Fuck me already!
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Shut up! It doesn't concern you!
Satsuki is getting popular too.
I know. You can't be honest about Satsuki getting popular
It's like you want to separate yourself.
Sh-Shut up!
It's not like that!
Come on.
I know you want to do me.
Something grotesque is going to penetrate and make me feel good!
It's coming in!
Do it all the way inside!
It's inside me...
Something grotesque is entering...
My pussy...
is liking it!
This is bad!
This is really bad!
It's messing me up deep inside!
It's coming!
What? No way!
Why are you stopping, fatty?
Do it all the way until the end!
Sa-Satsuki?!
Um... this is...!
What are you doing, Sensei?
Is this what they call sex treatment?
N-No. Th-This is...
No. Wait. What?
Shizuka...
It's not good...
that you're the only one feeling good.
What are you doing, Satsuki?
Guys need to feel good too!
No way...
She's licking that part...
Sensei will get bored if Shizuka's the only one getting satisfied.
So fast...
Shizuka isn't skilled...
Why with Satsuki?
When did you two become so close?
I also...
It may be too soon for you, Shizuka.
No way...
Sa-Satsuki...
He's big again!
Feels good...
Sensei's dick...
Is a perfect match with my pussy today as well!
Today as well?
Wait, Satsuki?
Does that mean...?
Great, it feels good!
It feels better than usual because Shizuka is watching.
Sensei...
Your dick feels good!
Something hard is coming!
Wait! I'm watching, so stop it!
You're up next in the shoot, Shizuka.
What? Why didn’t you say so sooner?
Shizuka, I won't lose!
Geez. Was that a good idea?
Showing off to Shizuka...
I won't hand over Sensei's dick!
It's mine!
Sensei... Cum a lot!
There's a lot of sperm inside me...
This is a problem.
What should I do?
Satsuki?
She's probably around here somewhere.
Hey, Satsuki. Are you being bullied?
Could it be Shizuka?
She's jealous of you.
That's not true.
Shizuka wouldn't do something like this.
I'm the one.
Doing something bad to Shizuka.
I wanted to be like Shizuka.
Shizuka once said to me:
'If you say I'm your rival, I'll gladly accept your rivalry.
Let's both do our best!'
Shizuka acknowledged me.
I really think that being together with Shizuka is good.
Shizuka is a wonderful girl.
I understand why you like her.
I still haven't been able to become a professional after all this time.
I want to catch up to Shizuka.
What are you saying?
You're wonderful too, Satsuki.
Wait, Sensei!
Y-You can't!
We're in the classroom so you can't!
Shizuka will...
Satsuki is a very wonderful girl too!
No!
That's a lie!
You're lying!
No way, Sensei...
My breasts are showing!
It's embarrassing!
Put it in yourself, Satsuki!
Sensei's dick is entering my pussy!
It's entering perfectly deep inside!
It feels good to be inside you!
No. It's a bad thing, but I can't stop!
It feels very nice, Sensei!
I can't think of anything else!
Shizuka will find out!
She'll see that I'm having sex with Sensei again!
Geez. Hiding it in a place like that. It's annoying.
Satsuki...
Here you go!
Shizuka...
Wh-What?
What are you two doing?
W-Wait!
Hey!
I'm already here, so stop it already!
Don't look, Shizuka!
D-Don't look at me having sex with Sensei!
It's too much stimulation for Shizuka.
What are you saying?
I can handle something like this!
No!
If you lick me there, Shizuka...
Don't...!
I won't lose to you.
It feels good!
Shizuka is licking me!
Amazing!
You're so wet, Satsuki!
Looks like it feels good...
Even though I'm in front of Shizuka, I can't stop feeling so good!
Sensei, I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!
Even though I’m being watched, I’m gonna cum!
Here it comes!
The thing that messed up Satsuki is inside me!
It feels so good!
My pussy is going to cry!
Give me a lot!
A lot of cum inside me!
Fuck me harder!
Come...!
It's coming!
It feels good!
I can feel it deep inside my womb!
I want to experience something rougher, together with Satsuki!