www.SubDESU-H.net
The last episode presented us with a climax and a considerable end to the story,
of the OAV of "Eroge! The joy of sex and game development".
But let's roll back time again
But let's roll back time again.
Yes.
Yes!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Limited Company
I, who loves H-games more than anyone else,
was barely accepted to work at Flower, a H-game company,
Limited Company
though it was already at the brink of bankruptcy.
If their next game doesn't sell well,
Himeno Kisara
Original Artwork Designer
Her 3rd Game in the Making
Her Doujinishi's are quite popular,
and is a member of a well-known circle
Virgin
the company will be completely busted.
Fujiwara Momoka
Virgin
Scenario Writer
Would occasionally
write BL stories
for magazines,
which are quite popular
Would occasionally
write BL stories
for magazines,
which are quite popular
Also, the staff team is an all-female one,
Kousaka Iori
Virgin
Graphics/Layout
Designer
Earns a reasonable
amount in her
Digital art/image
doujin circle
Earns a reasonable
amount in her
Digital art/image
doujin circle
but their knowledge and passion
for H-games is sorely lacking.
Konono Nene
Company President, Sales Manager,
Director, and Scripter all in one
Always stays and sleeps at the
meeting room due to her managerial work
If this continues...
For the sake of creating truly erotic H-games,
32-years old
VIRGIN
I'll have to do my best!
I'll say this straight: Momoka-san hates me.
Wonder if I ever did something to her?
Well, I did, but...
The fact that I ejaculated in front of them was of course bad,
but that was not completely my fault.
Eroge!
Excuse me...
The hardest part is being completely ignored.
W
Original Animation Disc
Eroge!
SubDESU
presents
The joy of sex
and game development
Original Animation Disc
~ A peach-colored sigh, once again?! The newest H-game is filled with Momoka!! Chapter ~
Eroge! The joy of sex and game development
Could it be that she actually hates boys in general?
The text she writes does have that kind of feeling.
Her distaste is not really obvious here,
but it feels like part of it tries to detest men,
or is trying to reject their existence.
How can I tell her about this?
Eroge!
Um, Prez, I'd like to inquire about something.
Is it okay if I do it here?
Oh yes, you can.
Guess I'll just go home.
I'll just think about it at home.
What's wrong?
You were referring to me earlier, right?
It seems that you've even read my novels.
Care to tell me why?
Well that's...
About the scenarios you've written,
they don't seem to be intended for a nukige...
TL Note: Nukige (Eroge meant for masturbating)
No need to poke at those points unnecessarily.
Just please concentrate on your own work.
But, our upcoming game is a nukige!
It's an absolute must for the game to make the guy jack off.
With this script it is highly likely,
that this game will turn out to be just the same as the last one.
We can't let that happen!
Those rough and ugly jerks can masturbate to just about anything, right?
We don't.
And we can't, unless you change your attitude towards men.
Well that's right!
I hate 3D men!
All men are just idiots.
Besides, there's actually nothing good or bad in a script.
They're idiots, so you simply have to lead them on.
It's very easy to make them cum.
No, that simply just won't do.
At the very least, I'm not—
Sorry, I said too much even though I'm still quite new here!
So, please don't hurt me...
What are you saying?
I just said it earlier, right?
That it's easy to make you guys cum.
Cocks are easy to handle.
Because men are simple.
My favorite maid costume,
and she's even handling it well.
It's already gotten this big.
I know that it's already very lively.
This, feels good.
Why don't you just cum and stop resisting?
You can cum anytime you want to.
Even if you try to spray it all over me,
I won't be affected!
It can't be...
His raw cum...!
This raw stuff is going inside my body.
How about that?
That's what I can do to you.
What is it?
It's my flawless victory.
A result that I had perfectly anticipated.
And with that, I'd like you to refrain from giving your cheeky opinions.
Now then, I'll be taking my leave.
Man, I'm tired.
But to try and reflect scenes from eroge scripts may be the best way to let her learn more.
I've already read through the plot.
Though it's still, well...
There's still something about how the guy is treated in the story.
What is it?
Do you still have something to say after losing to me?
It's still too early to declare victory,
if you didn't even learn to handle your partner properly.
I thought you were going to say something more outrageous.
Of course, I already noticed that.
That's why I simply allowed you to do what you wanted these past few days.
Guys really are simple.
W-What? So you just intentionally let things be all this time?
Our battle has just begun.
And soon you'll be bowing down in acceptance to your utter defeat.
Are you trying to soil my breasts with your dirty, stinky thing?
Don't...
If you do it intensely like that, my nipples...
Stop kneading my valley so much.
That hurts.
Pull it out.
It's this stiff...
You really are a beast, aren't you?
This raw smell, and it's hot...
Oh no...
What if it enters my mouth?
You're really doing it....
What are those?
I thought about this while checking the script you wrote.
It seems that you still don't know much about women's pleasures.
A Certain
Secret Room's Electric Chair
presents
Magical Girl
Cynical
Sari
A's
It may only be a few, but I assembled an OAV package here
Molest on Big Breasts
Ai**tsu Begins
Kujou Sakura's
Limited SP Card
Included!!
I hope that you'll be able to obtain the necessary materials to...
My Childhood Friend
can't be this sadistic
Is that so?
Thank you for your concern.
Are you taking me for a fool?
I already said that I can do it myself, right?
I don't want to be smeared in lust from tainted things made by men.
Instead, I'm the one who's going to smear men in lust!
Shall I do it? I'll do it now!
I can do it!
Momoka-san, are you really going to do this?
There's no question about it already.
I'm doing it.
I'm going to do it.
And I can  do it!
Here I go.
That was easy.
It went in smoothly.
How disappointing for someone who's always complaining about me.
Even with this insignificant thing you're already...
Are you alright?
Does it hurt?
I'm fine!
It doesn't hurt at all.
Even if you speak calmly like that...
I can still see what you want to do!
You'll feel a lot better if you just take it easy.
Are you about to cum as I move?
You're at your limit already, right?
You'd really look pathetic if this ends quickly.
That hurts...
That's why I'm trying to go easy on you.
Oh? You're starting to look even more pathetic now.
Fine.
I can make you cum instantly the moment I become serious anyway.
Then I'll make you regret that you ever gave me a chance.
Those hip movements...
It... doesn't feel good at all...
It's pushing inside...
As someone who hates you,
I'm really not affected by all this.
Your cock though, just needs to thrust inside to keep getting aroused.
Hear that? Just go deep inside my pussy.
You're just a virgin guy.
Virgin cocks can't resist pussies such as mine.
I'm not trying to act tough!
It's entering me.
There, I can see it clearly.
The part where your cock rubs in hard into my hole.
Oh crap, I'm about to cum?
What? It's getting even bigger!
You're cumming?
I see.
I guess cocks tend to cum right after they get stiff, after all.
It's inside... It's moving deep within me.
This thick cum inside my pussy... feels great...
My pussy shouldn't have been... shouldn't have been... and yet...
Momoka-san?
What? I'm just fine here!
Instead of my pussy, is your cock okay?
Mine is still inside as you can see.
Your cock's really disgusting, you know?
This is nothing to me...!
Let's see if you can still say those things after I just came!
It's coming.
Your cock is trying to pour your cum into me again.
Your semen is going inside!
Your semen is...!
My pussy feels great~!
Lots of cum is flowing in.
Your semen has just tainted all of my insides.
Not bad, you cock-loving sadist-pussy queen.
You're quite good, you imbecile masochist-cock pig.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Eroge! The joy of sex and game development
Wow, that's amazing!
Well done!
Congratulations.
You really did it!
You're becoming a real pro now, Momo.
Thank you everyone.
The BL novel that she was writing during her spare time.
It has apparently become quite popular, and will be serialized into separate volumes.
But, working on the books while writing our game script might really make my schedule tight.
I want to let you concentrate on just your books, but unfortunately it's impossible deadline-wise.
Please don't worry, I just need to extend my hours here,
so that I'll be able to eventually complete both works.
Well, it might even become some sort of advertisement for our game,
so I'll give you my approval.
Advertisement?
For an eroge... in a BL title?
I'm sure you can do it.
You can be lightning fast on the keyboard sometimes.
You've been really doing great lately.
Your scripts have also become more and more erotic.
That's right, there were lots of really great nasty lines.
I mean, I think we should even make it more obscene to make it better!
I think I'll have to study well for my part as well.
Hey, what are you acting all busy for?
Why don't you say something here?
I'm not acting busy.
I really am  busy here.
Okay, okay, fine, fine.
I just wanted you to say something as someone close to her.
We're not actually that close.
That's right.
Well putting that aside...
Momoka-san, congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Um... Nomura Tomoya-san, right?
It's Mochizuki.
Congratulations, really.
I'm sorry.
I'm not good at remembering men's names.
Mochizuki Tomonushi-san.
What is big boobs trying to do?!
I'm going to pay her back later.
This is all for the game, and isn't some revenge prank.
I don't really want to do this.
Just watch.
Who are you?
So it's true that there's a perverted woman living here.
Wh-What is it?
Don't come near me.
No! Stop!
Just who are you?
Stop this already.
I'll scream for help!
Do you really think someone will come for you in the middle of the night?
How naïve of you!
I don't understand a word you're saying.
Now, let's see how your pussy is doing.
Oh? It's already very wet.
Guess you really wanted to do it huh, lecherous woman?
Okay, I'll thrust my cock in as you wish.
Wow, you're really squeezing me tight.
Never thought you liked cocks that much.
Hmm, the pussy is alright, but your expression is still a bit stiff.
Though I heard that you are really awesome.
Hey, you love getting cocks thrust into you, right?
Make your pussy wetter and look happier.
I-It's really soft.
It must be hard for you to find bras because of these amazing pair.
Look, your nipples are also this stiff.
Oh I see, so this soft play is still not enough for you?
Then...
Huh? This is weird.
Well, if I cum she'll just ride along with it I think.
I'm going to cum.
Better ready your pussy to take all of it.
How's that?
Your favorite sticky cum... huh?
Huh?
Woah, sorry...!
Sorry, it's me!
W-Why?
I'm sorry.
I thought you'd be able to quickly tell.
I never intended to scare you like that.
You...
You really are such a...
You stupid...
Super total pervert!
I'm very sorry!
What is it?
Answer me honestly, you dunce.
It's your fault, right? That Momo looks gloomy today.
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
Even someone as dense as you should know it!
She's been like that for a few days already.
What?
She's not even telling us anything, even though we've been friends for a long time.
It becomes even worse when you approach her.
What... what is that?
I'm really sorry, it's all my fault.
So please, return to your normal self already.
I'm willing to do anything.
Anything, you say?
Yeah, anything.
Then go...
... go out with me.
What?
You said you'd do anything, you idiot!
Liar!
Bum!
You penniless H-game lover!
Okay, I'll go out with you.
Really?
Let's go out for real.
Why?
Why would you go out with me?
Why you ask?
Anyway put the hammer down.
Because I think I'm in love with you.
Sorry, did you not want to hear that from me?
No, it's not that.
It's because I love you too.
I'm going to make you feel good until it's carved into your mind.
I guess it's like this.
Could this be... even worse than before?
It's entering deep inside again.
It's already...
It's going straight in.
My pussy's being drilled inside.
It's being pierced.
It feels cold, and the sensation of having this inside me is different.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Into your butthole.
This shamefully twitchy hole of yours.
If you know what that part is then please stop!
If you try to push it inside there...
My butt.
My butthole...
Push it in more.
Something thick, is trying to open it wide.
I'm at my limit.
This thick thing is...
Even though that obscene hole is being caressed, it still feels good.
No...
Please let me be...
Your cock.
Your raw cock is hitting deep inside me.
It's really stiff, and thick...
I'm about to cum.
Are you about to cum?
I think I'm going to cum if I get cummed inside of.
Please don't look.
My thing is not that perverted!
I'm cumming.
Oh no!
I can feel the ecstasy flowing round my body from my pussy, and I'm going to cum because of it!
I'm cumming.
My pussy is about to cum~!
Your thick cum, coming from your thick cock...
It's flowing inside my pussy.
Again...
Your cock... I'm cumming~.
That's not true.
You're just forcibly...
No, it doesn't feel...
Pull it out!
Pull your cock out of my pussy.
Actually, Momoka was supposed to supervise the voice recording session,
but she's currently very busy with her two jobs.
So I was chosen as an emergency substitute.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming~.
Thank you very much.
What are you doing here?
Well, umm...
That was actually my first time supervising a voice recording session.
From the great experience in doing it,
to the opportunity of watching you perform,
I really thought it was amazing.
Thank you very much.
It's all because of your passionate guidance.
If it's okay with you,
why don't you guide me in my other works from now on?
I want you to guide me more.
There may be more lines that require shouts and moaning.
Someplace where we can be alone together would be nice...
I'm sorry, I still have a job to do today.
Remon-chan?
Received Message
From : Aizawa Remon
To : Tomoya
Message:
Thank you for yesterday.
Come with me again next
time, okay?
Remon
Thank you for yesterday.
Come with me again next time, okay?
Well this is troubling...
You came back late, right?
That must have been really enjoyable for you.
No... that's...
It's a misunderstanding.
What's a misunderstanding?
I haven't said anything yet.
Which means you've actually done something that could be misunderstood, am I correct?
No, that's not it, Momoka-san.
Nothing really happened.
So please forgive me already!
No.
Please, I'll do anything!
Anything, huh?
Anything, right?
Okay then.
Oh crap.
Oh crap, oh crap.
What if other people come here?
No, someone will definitely come here eventually!
I hope she goes to the other cubicle...
I hope she goes to the other cubicle.
Wait, don't open it!
Don't open it please!
It's all over now.
It's all over for me now.
Feeling guilty now?
Good.
From the look on your face,
it seems that you've been behaving yourself there.
You're currently a 'girl' with a cock,
yet your hips are moving like crazy.
Do you really like rubbing it into my pussy that much?
Not there...
Don't, don’t...
You can't play with my breasts.
Don't suck so strongly.
Your tongue is sloppily going around my nipples.
You're even banging my pussy like you're some ape.
There, squeeze my breasts more.
I'm usually the one squeezing milk out of you,
and yet I'm now the one being squeezed.
You want to cum, right?
It's okay.
Cum if you want.
I want you to cum inside the pussy of the one you love, inside this toilet cubicle!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming~!
My pussy is being stirred up by your cock,
and it's melting!
Master completion
That's not true.
No.
You're just forcibly...
No, it doesn't feel...
Pull it out.
Pull your cock out of my pussy.
There are no more problems, right?
We really did it.
Our game.
It’s alright.
Everything is A-ok!
We did it!
We sure did it!
We really did it!
Now I can finally sleep.
No surprise that they're really tired.
Finally, finally...!
The first game of the new Flower company is now complete!
Hey, stop pausing and keep your hips moving.
It's our day off, why don’t we go out somewhere?
No.
I'm already on top of you.
So please move your cock already.
Your cock is amazing.
This morning cock.
I'm going to take it every morning.
The sensation is even better and it has a unique stiffness.
All the flesh is being squeezed inside.
No, not there.
Not there.
Again it will...
It will...
It's going to come out.
My breasts are going let it out again.
My breasts are coming quickly like how fast you cum.
Don't thrust it inside me—
— while my pussy squeezes and gets drenched by my squirting breasts.
If you keep drilling like that,
I won't be able to stop cumming.
I want to have more sex with you.
I want your cock and my pussy to be one and rub together more!
Oh, are you about to cum?
Please, give it to me.
Give it to the one who's currently drowned in the pleasures given by your cock.
I'm cumming.
There's going to be a lot.
It's going to come out of the cock that I love, even in my dreams.
I love you.
I love you Tomoya!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming~!
Cock, cock, large
cock, very thick
cock, stiff cock,
Ohhhhhh.....
Next Time
It's the long-time-no-see, spray over cum, inside announcement.
Here we go.
What?
The screen's turning black?
Again?
Oh well.
Majin Mabel.
A year and four months after its hiatus,
it was resumed once again as Ero Majin.
One of its partners,
Liquid, a new Dark Eroge-based company,
has developed a new game that became quite popular which is entitled:
Kuro Inu - The High Holy Women Tainted in White.
It was announced to be re-released as a short anime series.
The first story starred Origa and Kuroe, the Fall Down chapter.
Next was Alicia and Prim, the Resistance Chapter.
Volt, the leader of the mercenary organization Kuro Inu,
declares the establishment of the "Service Country".
In this country, a dubious law was made,
that states that females will be forced to service men sexually.
The heroines of the story, which aren't present in the last work
Kaguya, Ruru, and Maiya,
will be completely driven deep into the white and sticky pit.
The creatures of the dark countries.
Beasts who hold carnal lust.
Further ahead is what lies beyond the female's protective garments.
Their soft and tender skin.
Which will be the first to burst?
The mind, or the body?
Original Animation Disc.
Kuro Inu - The High Holy Women Tainted in White.
Kaguya, Ruru, Maiya.
The worms that squiggle in the soft skin.
The night of the wild and mad beasts chapter.
Kuro Inu
The High Holy Women Tainted in White
Kaguya, Ruru, Maiya
The worms that squiggle in the soft skin
The night of the wild and mad beasts Chatpter
On sale on November 29, 2013.
On sale on November 29, 2013
www.SubDESU-H.net
Don't forget about Collaboration Works too.
Kuro Inu
The High Holy Women Tainted in White
Kaguya, Ruru, Maiya
The worms that squiggle in the soft skin
The night of the wild and mad beasts Chatpter
On sale on November 29, 2013