This is me.
And he is my boyfriend Takeru's...
Penis.
The peaceful lovers.
Peaceful
But to tell you the truth,
To protect peace and fight bad guys,
I’m a super beauty who fights for justice,
Kogerion!
But she was captured by the suicide robot made by Satsurina and…
She died…
I took Makoto's scattered body and ran,
to Makoto's father,
the expert in bio-engineering,
Professor Daiginjou.
I became depressed and,
just waited,
for this sadness to end...
Then, an unbelievable thing happened.
But the new me was powerless.
But even like this, Takeru loved me a lot.
And then, a power even I didn't know of awakened.
Suddenly, she became really powerful.
Yes Sasurina…
That’s the power we were looking for.
The Okotamite?
But that power must not be used yet.
If she found out about her power now…
You know what I'm talking about?
How do you know my name?
Oops, the details will be played in the middle of the show so have fun.
Ok then Makko-chan part 2.
Start!
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
W
Shoyonoido
Makko-chan
Is she a friend or foe?
Shogonoid appears
I’m going.
Oh, take care now.
Yamane-kun.
I think I’ll tell Makoto about that today.
You already prepared it right?
Saiki station
Ok, you guys keep quiet.
Listen, today’s mission is really important.
Listen carefully.
Kogerion a.k.a Daiginjou Makoto,
She rides the next train every morning.
Around this time, the train gets really crowded.
Using that opportunity, lets follow her.
And take her to the locked room.
Can you imagine what will happen next?
Nooo stop!
You understand right?
The train will be arriving soon.
Look, its coming!
Start the mission!
Get on!
What!?
Its hot…
Can’t they do something about this crowd during rush hour?
In this crowded situation, a molester's sure to appear.
Hey wait, I might not be able to go home if I don’t finish work early.
Hmmm... I think that’s already impossible.
When am I going to be able to go home and get some sleep...
I’m at my limit.
I don't want to go with them...
Did nobody in the crowd think to leave a little earlier?
Why don’t they use cars?
Or maybe I should be the one to use a car?
No I don't think there are any places to park.
That’s reminds me, my neighbor rented a parking lot to park his bicycle and he doesn't even have a car.
What a fool, such a waste of money.
No no! Why am I thinking about the life of the business man!?
Its hot...
Can’t they do something about this crowd during rush hour?
Today’s train is especially crowded...
What? Minions!?
What are you doing here?
So there you are Kogerion!
How sad, but this is your it!
This crowded train car will be your grave!
You’ll be raped by these guys and,
Sprayed all over your body!
And die!
Oh, we’ve arrived.
Eh? Hey! Where are you going!?
What...
What am I going to do?
Stop right there! You idiot! Kogerion!
Hah… that was dangerous.
I should recharge or else I’m just an ordinary girl.
I think I’ll visit takeru’s house later.
Failed... eh?
General Shigoku! Please forgive me!
Don’t punish me Shigoku sama,
I can't do anything about your punishment.
No way...
Please forgive me Shigoku sama.
If you use that on me... I...
I didn’t fail because I wanted to.
I overdid it and brought too many of my men.
There were also a lot of others...
But... I…
Did my best.
I really did my best.
Hey, please forgive me Shigoku sama.
Oh! By the way, it's still experimental but...
I have a trump card.
Shigoku-sama.
Look at it first before you decide.
Occupied
Sasurina-san’s top secret notes
Look at this.
This is my latest top secret project.
2 cool slash
With this, 2 cool will fight and,
unfinished
unfulfilled
Next time, we can finally put end to this.
And I am sure about that!
Oh…
Then what’s the plan?
The plan is bank
Yes.
To fight against her.
The minions we have right now is no match for her.
So using the full armor body of the previous loser robot 25.
I decided to make a super robot.
We chose the best among the minions and,
put the penis... no... we remodeled him.
penis
With this, that filthy Kogerion,
A.k.a Shoyonoid Mako-chan.
We will fuck her a lot!
android soldier
I can expect good results from it, right Sasurina?
Of course!
We will blow her with the great one and
Finish her!
With Nu~ku’s most powerful soldier
new android
Shogonoido!
Yay!
It’s a call from the professor.
What is it papa?
Emer-
Is it another accident?
gency.
I have something important to tell you.
Emer-
Come back to lab immediately!
gency.
To my house?
Did something happen?
I’ll tell you the details later.
Don’t hang around on the way home.
Ok!
So...
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Ok, see you tomorrow.
Bye bye.
It seems.
Makoto changed recently.
Yeah.
It seems like I'm not getting along too well with these friends...
Should I make friends with others similar to my size?
Oh?
That’s...
What happened to you?
I’m Mako-chan.
The people's savior.
Ahh, I see you were peeing behind the truck.
The truck drove off...
And you were exposed, so...
You panicked, and when you got up,
your panties got caught on the wire,
and got in this mess right?
Let me see...
Onee-san will take care of it.
Hoop
Hop
It's out!
We’re done.
Daiginjou Makoto detected.
Eh?
I’m Daiginjou Makoto.
Nice to meet you.
I see you’re Kozue-chan.
To tell you the truth, I died once.
Kill makoto!
Kill Daiginjou Makoto!
Watch out!
Eh?
Kozue-chan!
Kozue-chan, are you alright?
Watch out you fool!
Wow, Kozue-chan is strong.
I see.
Are you really alright?
Why don’t you get checked out by a doctor?
Oh, how about my father?
Are you sure?
Oh, lets get a band-aid from Takeru’s house.
Ah… I’m so happy that I made a friend this strong.
Hey why don’t we fight for justice together?
Is that so?
I’m glad.
If Kozue-chan is my ally, that will be a great help.
Alright then, I need to recharge so...
Can we go visit him?
Sorry.
Takeru’s house
Ok then Kozue-chan, please wait for a while.
Hey Takeru!
Give me energy!
Do you really want energy?
Or maybe you came here just to have sex?
You’re bad.
I will never suck it!
Oh sorry!
Its just a joke.
While Kozue chan is waiting,
It's time for letters!
Mako-chan and Sasurina san,
Who’s better at blow jobs?
That’s Takeru…
I accept that challenge!
Eh? Challenge?
I won’t lose!
Look at this!
I’ll go first!
It's full of sperm and I'm licking it.
Kids, don't try this at home!
It’s too bad that we can’t air this without censors...
You’re just sucking it without love.
You must suck it with love.
Or don’t you know about love?
Grrr...
What are you saying?
Who am I to not know love at this age?
Then this is it.
The crystal of modern science.
The fascination of adult woman.
1. 2. 3.
It's 3!
3 Big and thick penises!
Oh this is great!
This is really amazing!
You can’t taste these so easily.
Don’t say that there’s no love.
Don’t say that there’s no love!
Calm down Sasurina-san!
Hey wait, If I look at it closely...
Only my legs are showing!
Hey everyone watching tv, do you see it?
Hey don’t ignore me!
A blow job is love!
It's not about who’s better, and we know what’s important.
You’re making fool of me right?
Alright then, have fun with the main show!
Here we go!
Just wait for me in the main show!
Takeru right now, the me right now or the me before,
Which one do you like?
I love both.
I got used to this body too.
Takeru you pervert.
But...
If I can,
I want to see the other one.
I see...
Hey Makoto.
Please do it again with the mouth.
Sure.
Takeru, you sure like this.
Oh? Makoto! There! There!
Kozue-chan?
Uhm... this is...
Kouzue-chan, no!
Don’t look at me like that or else...
Do you want to do it too Kozue-chan?
Makoto!?
What are you saying?
Makoto, a bus jack incident occurred again by the nu~ku.
Get ready to mobilize immediately!
Good timing!
Lets go!
Kozue-chan.
And also, Makoto, didn’t I tell you not to hang around?
Where are you now?
Eh?
I’m on my way to the site.
Bye bye.
Shoyonoido Mako-chan.
You finally came Kogerion!
That girl...
Why are you with her?
Enough talk! Tou!!
Mako-chan punch!
Why!?
I have been defeated!
What are you doing!?
I’m going to punish you when we get back to base.
Say bye bye to her now.
Bye bye.
Bye bye! See you again.
She’s a really reliable friend.
What!? She’s recharging before the fight?
So what’s that?
She’s saying she can’t but she’s doing it.
Ok then, it's simple.
Let's not let her recharge.
Just wait Kogerion!
I’m home!
What’s wrong papa? What happened?
Yes...
What do you think of that body?
What?
I wish I had bigger boobs...
That’s not what I mean...
Are you okay with that body?
That body with which you must put aside all your daily routines.
You can’t eve get along with your friends with that body.
It's not like that.
Someone told me...
You’ll have great fortune while you are alive.
And...
I have Takeru.
Takeru is always the same.
And I’m satisfied with that.
Besides today I made a new friend.
If you can go back...
I can?
Of course, not everything will be the same as before but...
Most of your body will be made as the same as your body right now.
Is there any menstruation?
We don’t have to include it if it has no use but...
Uhm... I mean about the baby...
Don’t worry, those parts will be the same as before.
Yes?
Oh? You’re... Kouzue-chan?
What’s the matter?
Makoto isn't here.
What are you looking at?
Eh? No...
You want to do it right?
What?
You’re thinking you want to have sex with my body.
You’re haven't forgotten the feeling of my pussy in the last time.
You… you're pretty smart but,
It's not good to mess around with adults.
The adult is erect while looking at my body.
It's alright.
You want to have sex with this body right?
You’re thinking that you want to put this into my small hole.
You want to thrust a lot and rub it all the way and release it inside right?
Here, it got bigger again.
Don’t tell me you’re going to cum?
You can release it you know.
But...
You want to release it inside me right?
I... didn’t...
It's alright.
You can release it inside.
Takeru~~
You know...
Run Makoto!
This girl is nu~gu’s minion!
Kozue-chan!
What are you going to do to Takeru?
If you’re here, I don’t have any use for him anymore.
You're my target!
Kozue-chan, why?
I failed in our first meeting.
So I was remodeled by Sasurina-sama.
There’s no need for that dumb attitude.
Why?
Why are you saying such things?
Last time’s Kozue-chan was more human compared now.
Human?
I don’t need that.
I’m an android.
Made just to defeat you.
I am a Shogonoid!
Shogonoid?
Be obedient and die.
If you do that I’ll spare this man.
Maybe that’s humanly way.
No. This is just practical.
If your answer is no, I’ll just crush this man’s penis.
Kozue-chan!
Let Takeru go!
Makoto!
Don’t mind me and run!
Are you thinking of threatening me?
Even you don’t have the courage to be crushed.
Don’t say such courageous things.
Let Takeru go!
You don’t have any intention to die.
You’re just doing something useless.
You can’t win because you haven’t recharged your energy.
Even if it's like this… I must fight!
I’m a fighter of justice, Shoyonoido!
Makoto!
That girl named Kozue,
after she ripped Makoto apart,
did nothing to me and just walked away.
I grabbed Makoto and went to professor Daiginjou’s place.
And then...
The days without Makoto continued.
Takeru, my body can make a baby.
Hey Takeru! Lets do it!
W-w-wait!
Let's use contraception.
I don’t know if that time’s Makoto’s decision was,
the decision of risking her life or,
The decision that she was prepared to die...
But...
That tiny Makoto.
Became a memory.
From now on, I think of being together with Makoto who has regained her former body.
And I remember sometimes.
That I had once a powerful tiny girlfriend.
Sasurina-sama!
We’ve detected Kogerion’s existence again!
Whaat!?
Finish