www.SubDESU-H.net
W-Who are you?
Please... stop this.
I'm going to... shout.
No, the way you fondle...
Stop.
Don't...
W
Afternoon Blush
~More than Just Pure Love Mellow~
Stop this...
Don't please, not that—
Please, take it out...
I beg you...!
This... feels good...
Not there...
Breast maniac...
Down there, too.
No way, if you move that aggressively...
I'm already so wet.
No!
Your cock is... getting bigger!
It's over, right?
No, don’t do that!
No, my butt will tear apart!
Is my butt that arousing to you?
It's going deep!
Your dick in my ass is making so much noise
My insides...
What is this... feeling? I am having a weird feeling inside my stomach.
Please don’t say that anal sex is good.
No... It hurts.
Even though I'm in this state...
I am getting wetter...
I can't show this side of me... to that person.
My insides are getting full.
Is this...
... what I really am?
Am I really this perverted?
What's that?
Something's coming.
Even though it's my ass, yet something is coming inside...
Rattle me inside.
What's this?
I haven't felt this before.
I didn't know this would feel so good.
I'm cumming!
This felt really good.
Am I getting sexually frustrated?
Dear,
could you come home early tonight?
Sorry.
I'll be coming home late again today.
Sorry. Go to sleep first if you want.
I see.
I'll be going.
I love you.
Have a nice day!
Good morning, Yayoi-san!
Naoki-kun, good morning.
Going to club practice?
Yes.
Even though it's a Sunday, you're quite passionate, aren't you?
Do your best, okay?
Yes.
Have a nice day!
Yes!
I know he is quite busy with his work for our sake,
and I am quite grateful for that.
But we're not having sex lately.
It's getting a bit lonely.
And I even bought a new set of lingerie for him.
Something that could fire up his erotic desires.
Oh my... It's still daytime.
Seems I just won't be able to hold it in.
I think.
Why don't I try the one that I recently ordered?
No doubt, Yayoi-san is really pretty.
Have a nice day!
I'm able to overcome my hardships during practice because of her.
Ah crap!
I'll try to get in and out fast, without creating any disturbance.
Oh, there!
Please, give it to me already.
Dear, I can’t hold it in anymore.
Please insert your cock into my w-wet and erotic p-pussy already.
I want it now, please.
Dear, I can't wait any longer.
It's in!
Your cock...
No doubt, the feel of a cock... is the best.
It's pushing into my womb.
Your cock is sliding into my pussy.
Do my breasts feel good?
Does it feel better since we are in the middle of sex?
Doing it from behind feels great!
It hits other different areas.
My hips are moving on their own. I can't stop...
Please, look at my aroused face.
What?
Oh no!
Please, wait! People will...
I don’t want people to see me like this!
No! I don't want to be seen!
No, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I am really going to cum!
I am going to get exposed.
This feels great!
No...
I'm about to cum.
I'm almost there!
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!
I'm cuuu—
I-I beg your sincere pardon.
No, don’t go!
Please, wait!!
No way I just...
This is...umm...
My husband is quite busy these days with work so... you know...
So... umm... that's why...
Please, don’t tell this to anyone.
Wait. Did she not notice me masturbating?
Could this... be an opportunity?
This guy... has a hard on.
Amazing. His young cock gets bigger and bigger.
It looks like it might burst if I touch it.
Would you let me have sex with you?
Am I getting ahead of myself?
I can’t go all the way with you, but...
... i-if it's just fellatio...
Oh no! Dear, I'm very sorry.
This is...
Yes!
It can’t be helped,
because I got caught by surprise.
Ya...Yayoi-san...
Amazing.
So this is a sweaty cock of someone after club practice.
No, I'm getting aroused.
It might be bigger than his.
This is amazing, Yayoi-san.
It’s been a long time since I had a cock.
This is bad.
Yayoi-san, this is bad.
It's been a while since I saw a refreshing cock.
It's kinda twitching.
It feels good right, Naoki-kun?
Yayoi-san, I'm about to...
Oh gosh... I'm about to get a taste of young man's semen.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I-I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
Amazing.
No way, it's still spurting out?
Yayoi-san, I'm...
Gosh, I am beat.
No way.
It's my husband.
He said he was going to be late today.
Anyway, you must hide right away.
Where am I going to h-hide?
Inside! There's a toilet inside, over there!
Okay!
Hurry!
Oh, welcome home dear.
Ah, so you were in the toilet?
You're home quite early today.
Ah yeah, I had forgotten the papers that I needed for work tonight.
So, you'll leave again?
I'm really sorry.
I would have brought them if you had just called.
Well, I happen to have something to do outside as well.
Eh?!
Naoki-kun?
My husband is just there.
Are you okay?
You sound like you are in pain.
I...I'm okay.
Nevermind that, did you find the documents already?
Yeah, I found it.
That's great.
I'm going to head out again.
But if you need anything, just call me.
Okay, thanks.
W-Wait...
My voice...
It feels really good inside you, Yayoi-san.
He's still there.
Naoki-kun, please...
No, not that please.
Naoki-kun.
No!
Y... Yayoi-san.
I'm sorry.
But I wasn't able to hold it in.
But since your husband didn't find out,
I think... I think it's alright.
Yayoi... san?
Because of you, Naoki-kun,
my switch got flipped.
Be sure to take the responsibility, okay?
Now, it's my turn.
Payback for what you did to me earlier.
Okay?
How is it, Naoki-kun?
You can feel the end of your cock kissing my womb, don't you?
This is...
Every person I went out with,
including my husband,
pale in comparison to this.
Naoki-kun's thing is really big.
It’s shaking up my insides.
Your massive cock is filling me up inside.
Can you feel it?
Yayoi-san.
Milk won’t come out even if you suck that hard.
It's good.
My nipples feels good.
You're too erotic, Yayoi-san.
But you're... you're a bad kid, too.
I already said to stop.
But you still kept thrusting this big thing in.
Especially,
after that aggressive fuck session.
How can I still resist after that?
Amazing, it's getting bigger inside again.
Yes, I'm...
You’re about to cum?
You’re cumming, right?
Yes, I'm cumming.
It’s alright.
Me, too.
I'm about to...
It's c-coming out.
Let it out.
I'm cumming.
I'm also cumming.
Umm... A lot of things happened here,
but let's keep this a secret between the two of us, okay?
It's a bit weird to say this after all that,
but Yayoi-san, for a long time I have been in—
Don't say anything more.
Afterall... I'm already married, you know.
Indeed...
I'll be taking my leave.
But...
I think it’s okay for you to drop by... from time to time... I guess.
Yes!
www.SubDESU-H.net