It's been a while...
But it hasn't changed one bit!
The student disciplinary committee has been revived,
so I guess I'll get started with an umph!
On patrol for the first time...
Things can get uncertain during lessons, so I gotta watch out.
There will be no ditching classes or guys trying to get into the ladies changing rooms allowed.
It sure is peaceful.
Although there were some guys causing trouble before...
No, no!
Peacefulness is best!
I am a student disciplinary member who keeps the peace at school!
This floor only has an empty classroom, huh?
Well, I'm sure there's nothing going on, but...
W-What are you doing?!
Tsk, someone found me.
That guy...
Don't tell me...
SubDESU-H
Diabolus Kikoku
I can't permit violence!
But, that guy...
Huh? No way, it can't be!
It's been a while, Madoka.
Sa-Sayako!
You haven't changed much, have you?
When did you get back?
I was able to get some time off, so that's why I came to visit.
Oh really? So I guess you haven't returned to become a student.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it!
I'm just happy that you came by.
Thanks, Madoka!
Oh, look at the time.
Sorry, I have to go on patrol again.
I'll come with you!
No no, you stay here, Sayako!
This is my job.
But...
Besides, you're an outsider here,
so it's best not to wander around.
It can't be helped.
Then I'm off.
When I come back, let's chat some more, okay?
Sure!
See ya then!
The only place left is around back...
I have to hurry because I bet Sayako is getting bored...
A scream?
No!
Stop it-!
No!!
No! Stop it!
Run, hurry!
N-No~!!
You bastard...
Getting in my way again...
I guess I'll take you instead of that girl.
Hey-!
S-Stop! What are you-
I'm gonna play with you.
N-No!
S-Stop it-!
Not there!
S-Stop it! Don't rub that thing against me!
N-No, anything but that!
Shut up! I said I'm gonna play with you.
Madoka...
Why... do you know my name?
Asahina Yuuki.
It can't be...
Madoka! Hey, Madoka!
What's up, Madoka?
Thinking about something?
Oh, it's nothing.
I have to make sure that I don't worry Sayako, since she came to visit me.
Are you sure you're not worrying about something?
It's nothing!
Oh yeah, I have to go look around. How about you join me this time?
Can I really?
Sure!
What's up, Madoka?
Sorry Sayako, I forgot something important!
I'll meet you back in the student disciplinary room, okay?
Madoka...
Is that little one your friend?
Does it matter?
I've got somethings I want to ask, too. Who are you?
Are you Asahina Yuuki?
Asahina Yuuki? I don't know who that is...
Then you're not her?
Then how did you know my name?
Your name? How would I know?
Lies! That time you...
"Madoka..."
I'm not lying. I don't know who I am either.
When I came to, I was like this.
I can't remember who I am, or why I'm here.
However...
For the time being, it seems like my identity is to violate women.
No... No way!
That girl who was with you, can I do her?
Don't be stupid!
I guess I don't need permission...
W-Wait!
Then are you willing to take her place?
N-No, don't do such a thing!
I don't have anything else to do.
What?
N-No, don't!
Use your tongue more!
C'mon, swallow it!
Hey, I said to drink it!
I can't do that!
It's too thick and it gets stuck in my throat-!
Tsk...
You're boring.
I guess I'll do someone else.
N-Not Sayako!
Sayako protected me that time!
Now I need to protect her!
Then you have to satisfy me!
Fine then.
What a tease!
He let it out just a second ago...
But it's still hard!
I wonder if this end can satisfy me.
N-No no!
No!!
It's tight-!
Even though I'm in the student disciplinary council,
for me to be doing such things at school-! It's humiliating!
Out of all the girls I've violated, you're the best!
No! Not so rough!
Don't be so selfish!
No! It's hitting the end!
That's it, let me hear your voice, Madoka!
He said my name again...
Don't cum before me.
I hate it when you don't cum at the same time.
Even if you say such a thing, I-!
This bitch, she's clinging onto me down there even as she gets more turned on.
No, I'm gonna cum!
Although I'm meant to be on patrol, I'm-!
I'm cumming!
No... Wait...
Sorry, Sayako...
Sayako?
Sayako...
It's okay.
I'll be sure to protect you this time.
Is she that precious to you?
You're similar to him in your stupidity, too.
Hey, princess will wake up.
W-What are you doing?
I wasn't satisfied.
I'm gonna have a bit more fun with you.
S-Stop! If we do this here, Sayako will-!
Don't worry, it'll be over soon.
Just don't wake her up.
She'll wake up if you're too loud.
N-Not here... You can do me anywhere else!
Anywhere else?
You sure are perverted.
How did you come up with that?
If someone wants to have sex anywhere, that means they're lewd.
Speak for yourself.
That may be true.
Oh, you're a pervert after all.
N-No! This is your fault!
I doubt that, you're already this wet!
I can smell the womanly scent...
S-Stop it!
I told you not to make a racket!
Well, I don't care either way.
Hey you're being loud again...
She'll probably despise you if you're having sex with a random guy.
I can't let Sayako know!
To protect her, and for her to not despise me, I have to bear with this!
You're quite good at being tolerant.
Tsk, this is boring.
Sure is dirty, do I have to find it in here?
W-Why are you here?
I'm quite sensitive about you.
D-Does that mean you...
You smell sweaty.
I-It can't be helped! This is P.E. class!
I like it better this way than a doll without any scent.
Stop it-!
Not in such a place, what if someone comes in?
It's full of junk here, if we go in further, then they won't see anything.
B-But...
If you're so worried, just make me cum more quickly.
I-I can't do such...
I guess I'll get you to use those massive breasts.
Who do you think you are?
Face the other direction.
I can smell the womanly scent again...
This time you better drink it all.
How do I taste?
There's no way this thing tastes good...
Anyway, that's fine isn't it?
We better get out before someone-
Hold it right there, I'm not satisfied yet.
What?
Look at this.
I think we have to fully do it.
Get on top.
Fine, then.
Wait a sec.
What is it already?
Don't take off your gym shorts.
I can put it in through the side.
You... Pervert!
I think that someone being so lewd that they're doing me in gym clothes is more perverted.
Shut up!
Does it matter?!
It goes in easily now, huh? Are you used to it?
Shut up! Stay quiet, will you?
Your expression says that you've become engrossed in this!
No that's-!
Madoka? Are you done yet?
Madoka? Are you in here?
That's strange... I wonder where she went...
I don't think she'd skip classes...
Let's stop this!
What are you saying? You've been constricting around me.
C'mon, quit stalling and shake your hips!
It's almost as if I'm starting to feel good every time I do it with this guy...
Even though he's doing it forcefully...
Once his penis is in me, I become like this...
This is amazing... Your body is great!
D-Don't say such-!
I'm gonna make you cum like this!
No, not so rough!
I'm gonna cum!
No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
Yuuki's semen is filling me up...
What's this? It's warm...
Oh, Madoka! Where have you been? Geez...
Sorry, sorry!
Sayako didn't come today...
Is she mad at me because I've been neglecting her?
The way he talks and his attitude...
He must be Asahina Yuuki.
This can't go on! I have to confront him.
I wonder where he would be...
Anyone who looks like Asahina Yuuki here?
It's you, huh?
Did you... do this?
Yeah... I can't help myself after doing you...
What are you gonna do about it?
That's... Not my fault!
Well whatever, if I can do you, then everything will be fine.
Noo!!
S-Stop-!
No-!
You're the best, Madoka!
I don't want to be praised for such a thing!
I-It's deep!
Do my pussy more!
No, I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum with you! I'm cumming!
No...
It's fine.
Do me until you're satisfied, if that removes your pain.
Yuuki...
Dammit! What are you?!
Why?!
Yuuki...
W-Why is he here... And what about Madoka...?
I have to do something...