No!
I didn't thought I'll be able to have sex with Mayuri-chan I adore.
Is this also because of that pendant?
Inmu Academy
Translated by SubDesu-H
This is Seiou Academy.
It has a history as a girls-only school for noble families.
This girl is Tendouji Mayuri-chan.
She's cute, stylish and comes from a rich family above all.
You there?
Can you call Mayuri?
She is Aika-san.
Mayuri-chan's elder sister and the president of student council in this academy.
She's beautiful and has a good style.
She is the center of attraction among the students.
Sis!
In short, those two are a prize beyond everyone's reach.
God is really unfair.
This infirmary is the place where I work as an attendant.
Excuse me.
Oh, Sugawara-kun?
I see, you're the attendant here, right?
Yes.
I'm cleaning up.
Oh, have a sit.
OK...
The teacher is not around?
She's went to the faculty meeting.
To tell you the truth, I am extremely sociophobic.
Especially when I face a girl, I can't speak.
I've never had a girlfriend, so it's a miracle for me being able to talk with Mayuri-chan.
Well then, I'll go back to club activity.
Thanks, Sugawara-kun!
OK... Ah...
Jeez... You really don't like girls, do you?
Hayama-sensei, when did you...
She is the only girl I can speak to.
I also consulted her regarding my sociophobia.
I think that somebody like you needs this.
sugawara
This is...
That's a pendant which makes you have a dream about the girl you like when you wear it.
Dream about a girl?
Sugawara-kun?
Why?
Please, get out from my room.
You're cruel, Sugawara-kun.
Why are you doing this?
It's because Mayuri-chan is cute.
No!
Please don't do such bad things anymore!
Someone, help me!
Sis!
No, don't look!
Please stop!
No!
I don't want this!
I know you're feeling it, Mayuri-chan.
Your nipples are getting hard.
No, it's not!
Stop!
No!
Stop, that part...
That part is...
Nooo!
The underwear is all wet because of Mayuri-chan's dirty juice.
It's a lie! It's impossible!
You're cruel, Sugawara-kun!
No!
No! Stop!
Please stop!
Stop it!
You can't!
That part... No!
That part is...
There's a lot of juice flowing out from Mayuri-chan's pussy.
No, it's not!
Here, look at this.
I don't know!
I don't know about that...
You're kidding, right, Sugawara-kun?
No, you shouldn't...
I... This is my first time, so please forgive me!
No! Wait!
It hurts!
I don't want this anymore!
Wait!
Don't move, it still hurts!
Be more gentle!
Your pussy is getting used to the feeling.
That's enough, please stop!
Too fast!
I said, be more gentle!
I can't hold it any longer, I'll release much inside Mayuri-chan!
Eh? That means...
Please stop! Don't do it!
No! Please, take it out!
You must take it out!
No!
It's hot...
You're cruel!
I said not to do it!
You released it inside...
Sugawara-kun!
No!
This pose, it's embarrassing!
It's coming in again!
It's so good inside Mayuri-chan!
No, it's not!
Wait!
Too intense!
Be more gentle!
I think you're starting to feel good.
No, I'm not!
You want me to thrust here right?
Don't do it!
This time... Please stop!
Let's cum together, Mayuri-chan!
Don't make a fool out of me!
Saying that we should cum together... I don't know about that!
I can't bear this!
I'm going to break!
I'll pour a lot inside of you again!
No, please! Don't release it inside!
My stomach is hot, I'm going crazy!
Mayuri-chan, you came from mine, right?
I... Sis...
Was it really just a dream?
Maybe so, but I was like another person.
Oh my God! I overslept!
Mayuri-chan is strange.
I think she was looking at me.
Impossible...
I think it's my first time to see Mayuri-chan sleeping in the class.
Sugawara-kun?
What's the matter?
Something's strange.
What happened to everyone?
Don't worry, this is just a dream.
A dream? This is a dream?
Yes, so it's fine whatever we do.
By the way, why are you distancing yourself from me?
I'm not distancing...
No! Stop!
Please don't do rude things to me again.
What do you mean by again?
Because you came to my room yesterday...
I see... In fact, I forgot something yesterday.
Forgot something?
Yes, for example, making me feel good by getting this licked and sucked.
If you don't want it, I'll release a lot inside your pussy.
No! Stop it!
Then, you'll do it with your mouth right?
No way...
Will you forgive me if I do it with mouth?
If you satisfy me, though.
What should I do?
Try licking it first.
Next, try sucking it.
But...
I won't feel good if you don't do it like that.
That was too much...
We won't finish if you do it like that.
Puck your mouth more and suck it.
Drink all of it!
Oh my, you're spilling!
What are you going to do?
Didn't you say you'll forgive me if I do it with mouth?
Didn't I say if I was satisfied enough?
It's unfair!
No!
Don't touch it!
I said no!
Hey, Mayuri-chan, are you excited because you're in front of everyone?
No, I'm not!
Please stop!
But this part says the opposite from what Mayuri-chan said.
It's coming in!
No! Stop! Don't take it off!
Now everyone can see your boobs.
It's embarrassing!
Don't touch it, my body is getting numb!
My voice, even if I don't want to...
Nooo! Not there! I can't hold it!
I'm going to cum!
Please don't release it inside!
You're hopeless, OK then, I'll release it outside.
I'm cumming! My stomach is weird...
You can cum, Mayuri-chan.
Cum, you say?
I'm cumming in the classroom.
What's the matter, Tendouji?
Nothing...
I'm not feeling well, so I'm going to the infirmary.
Health attendant, go see her state.
OK.
No... I can't cum with my fingers.
Sagawara-kun?
What are you...?
I was told to stay with you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Mayuri-chan?
I know that this is weird, but...
I can't bear this anymore.
Please put Sugawara-kun's inside me.
Are you sure?
Please, make it faster or else I'll call somebody!
Mayuri-chan, calm down.
It's a lot better than doing it alone.
The juice won't stop coming out.
Faster, using Sugawara-kun's...
Wow...
That thing will be inside me.
It's coming in!
Sugawara-kun's hard dick is coming inside me!
It's amazing, it's thrusting deeper!
A real dick is coming in and out!
Mayuri-chan is a real pervert.
It's Sugawara-kun who taught me that...
There... Dick... it's so good!
Mayuri-chan, lower your voice down, or else someone might hear us!
I can't!
I can't control my voice, because it feels so good!
I feel so good!
Don't look at my perverted face!
Here I come, I'm going to release inside Mayuri-chan!
OK, cum inside me using Sugawara-kun's dick!
It's flowing in, it's soaking inside me...
I think this is really influence of the dream.
I didn't thought that Aika-san would call me...
I heard it from Mayuri.
Really, you've done such a ridiculous thing!
Oh... Uhm...
Mayuri can't be a match for someone like you.
You knew it yourself.
People need to know their place!
Uhm...
You're not qualified to like Mayuri.
Don't go near her from now on, do you understand?
Eh? Uhm...
Your reply?
OK...
Really, why this guy...
Eh? Why are you here?
Of course, to help president out.
It's always like this, right?
Is that so?
Now, quick, the report.
Yes, I know.
Good morning, everyone!
What?
Please, start it immediately.
Everyone will think something's weird.
I will start this week's regular report.
First, the personal property inspection last time... ah!
About that... Students bringing unnecessary things increased...
I think that...
I...
Need to...
No! That part...
Stop it!
I'm thankful that you're servicing me with your dirty butt shaking!
Who is doing that!? Let me go!
Tell the report, you're not doing it well.
You...
My, my, you must understand your situation.
No! Wait!
My body...
There's no use in resisting.
Please, notice it already.
Stop it!
What are you thinking?
Now... I'll put Aika-san's favorite dick inside.
Ouch!
Stop it, this...
I think it's your first time, but it went in smoothly...
No way...
What!? I can't say that!
Tell them the wrong example.
If you don't say that, we won't finish.
To all students, I will say this to you.
If you're walking around without underwear...
Your pussy will be raped by dick just like me...
You boobs will be touched...
And it will be the cause of having sex
Everyone must be cautious not to be like me!
That's what I expected from a nasty president!
What a nice example you are!
No!
Stop!
Don't move!
You're really a nasty president, getting horny by being watched by other students!
No, it's not!
No!
Please cum in front of everyone!
Noooo!
This is my first time, and...
No...
I'm being watched...
This is where you cum, Aika-san!
I'm so glad you showed me such an intense cum scene.
But, we're not finished yet.
I can't move anymore!
We'll finish if I cum.
I don't want... this... intense...
You came again?
You really can't bear it.
I can't...
Stop it!
You're unusual.
Please show me your courageous side!
Aika-san, I'm going to release it soon, so...
Please take it all!
Not... inside...
I can have any girl I wish with this pendant!
In dreams, of course... but, even in reality!
infirmary
One week has passed.
I raped them every night.
Actually, I only raped them halfways...
You've prepared it just as I said.
What a nice view!
It's suffocating because you're only watching it!
Hurry up!
It's embarrassing...
OK, I will go with Mayuri-chan first.
It's coming in!
Your dick! It's so good!
How is it, Mayuri-chan?
It's thrusting deeper!
It's hot, so good!
Mayuri-chan is also great inside!
I'm glad... Thrust me more, bully me more!
Mayuri-chan likes this part, right?
There!
Good!
I'm going numb, so horny!
And crazy!
She's making such a dirty voice...
Master, I'm cumming, I...
Sure, cum in front of your sister!
Look at me sis, I'm cumming!
My pussy is cumming!
OK, Mayuri-chan came, so...
How about you?
I...
OK, then I'll do it again with Mayuri-chan.
Eh? Wait!
No way, do it to me, too!
What do you want?
I want it!
Your dick...
Please put it inside my pussy!
Alright then.
It's so good!
This...
It's numb...
I don't know this...
I'm going numb and crazy!
Ah... you're amazing, sis!
Mayuri, don't look at me!
It's embarrassing!
You're beautiful!
I can't look away...
No... more...
Sis...
You have such a perverted face...
I'm sorry for being a dirty sister...
You're beautiful.
Show me more of your perverted side!
Alright, look at me...
My embarrassing look...
More!
Aika-san...
How is my dick?
Good!
It's so good!
Your dick is so good!
I'm cumming, both of you!