A molester?
No...
Please. . stop it already!
He’s a molester!
I’m...
Shun-kun?
It will be troublesome if we go deeper with this.
I’ll take you to your house.
Just give up, you pervert!
It’s a false accusation!
SubDesu-H Presents
Osana Najimi to Doukyuusei
Shun-kun, thanks for earlier.
No problem, I just did what had to be done.
We need to punish those kinds of men.
And how was it?
Was what?
The feeling of being mo-les-ted.
Don’t tell me you got horny from a stranger?
What a shame.
I didn’t think a pure beauty with excellent grades, top of the class in archery and flower arrangements
would get horny from being molested.
It’s hard to believe, isn’t it?
I got Sakuragimiu-chan's, the academy’s idol, first kiss!
But what a shame, this beautiful thing being molested.
No!
Oops.
Sakuragi-san, your bag...
You forgot your bag!
Here’s your bag.
Thanks.
Kou...
Miu?
Kou!
What are you doing there?
I lost my house key.
It can't be helped, you can stay at my house until my aunt comes home.
My Mom will be home late, so I'd be grateful if you made me dinner though.
Sure.
Huh?
There’s nothing here.
Uhm, I think I heard my Mom say she would buy stuff before she comes home tonight.
Wait for a bit, this won't take long.
Did something happened after school?
Why?
I noticed you're not acting like yourself.
Kou... I’m sorry... my precious first kiss has been taken.
Miu, did you forgot?
That I kissed you when we were bathing together as kids because you were so cute?
You were so mad at that time, but it was your first kiss.
Kou.
Are you really sure?
Yup.
No...
Good.
I can’t hold it any longer.
Kou... please come.
Kou... it's not there.
A little bit lower.
A little bit farther up.
Here, It’s here.
Come.
I’m cumming!
No.
Not yet!
Sorry.
I’m alright.
You can be rougher and make yourself feel better.
Good.
I love you.
Ok then.
See you later Miu.
Kou...
Sakuragi-san.
I’m sorry about yesterday, are you still mad?
Angry or not... I...
Maybe you went all the way with your childhood friend Ueshima Kou-kun?
That's...
Congratulations!
For atonement, can I take you to my house?
Huh?
Kakiyazaki-sensei, the great artist in the Japanese flower arrangement association, who inspired you,
will be at my house tonight for a meeting about the party to be held next week.
Is that true?
Truthfully, I told Sensei about you and she said that she wants to meet you.
I-It can't be...
I’m... I'm Sakuragi Miu.
Sensei saw your entry at last national tournament.
Really? I’m embarrassed.
I've always been impressed with Kakiyazaki-sensei's beauty of the environments and the abundance of ideas for a long time.
Thanks.
I have a ton of questions to ask if I meet her.
Thanks for inviting me.
But I can’t give up on you Sakuragi-san.
What are you doing?
Oops.
So all in all you’re not mad at me.
That’s... it's just... I got a little dizzy.
Where am I?
What’s this?
I’m naked!?
So you're finally awake, Sakuragi Miu-san.
You’re...
Shun-kun!?
Welcome.
This is my private room and I took that machine from my Uncle who is an Obstetrician.
You deceived me.
Ok then.
Let me check if you’re still a virgin.
Stop it!!
What’s this mess?
There’s a lot of blood everywhere.
Damn!
So you gave your virginity to Kou.
It hurts! Stop it!
What’s this? You’re not wet.
Stop it!!
It really hurts!
It felt good when the dick was being thrust inside right?
Ouch! Please stop it!
Ouch!
Did Kou touch your boobs like this?
Stop it!
No!!
Shun-kun?
Put it on your neck.
What are you saying?
Are you insane?
Attach it. I’ll teach you something.
It fits you.
Now, crawl like a whore.
Do as I say.
It's time to walk.
Ok, stop.
What a view Sakuragi-san... no, I mean Whore-san.
What are you going to do next?
Shut up, whores must not talk back.
I’ll just put your favorite thing in your ass.
Stop it!
I won’t.
I see, your ass is still a virgin.
My my, you even peed, what a troublesome girl.
I think I need to punish this whore.
Ok then, suck your master’s dick.
I can’t do... it.
Suck it.
Finally you've become honest with yourself, you whore.
Don’t let it go, keep sucking it.
I’m cumming!
Why didn’t you drink it? You whore.
Maybe you need to be punished more.
Hey, raise your ass.
You’re such a dirty whore who got horny being fucked in ass.
Tsk, the pure and beautiful idol of the academy is a pro at masturbating.
D-Don't say that!
I didn’t think that the academy’s idol would pee this much.
I think this whore needs more lessons.
Sakuragimiu, you’re already my slave.
Miu, did something happen?
Why?
Nothing, today's date was really fun but...
you become silent when you're about to have fun.
Eh? Did I behave that way?
Please tell me if something bad happened.
We’re childhood friends you know.
No, your just being a worrywart Kou, don’t cross your bridges before you come to them.
Kou, please.
Miu, I’m going to put it in.
Kou, come.
Good, I feel it so much.
Kou, you can do it more intense.
No, I can’t hold it any longer.
Come!
Cum inside!
I’m cumming!
Kou, more... cum more...
What’s happening?
What’s this unsatisfied feeling?