www.SubDESU-H.net
This guy is...
A molester!
How foolish.
He doesn't know that I'm a member of the karate club.
Okay then.
I'll let him go a little further before he gets it.
Now!
Hey, you molester!
Liked the taste of that?
Quite a nice elbow strike there.
However, I was able to successfully block it.
So you’re a tomboyish gal, huh?
You need a little punishment then.
I can't believe this!
Someone!
There's a molester! There's a molester here!
With that cute girl...
How terrible...
Now, get off at the next station.
I'll be pushing you out.
I wonder about that.
Sorry, but I have this item with me.
Special Molester
Permission License
Sawanagare Taichi
What's that?
A molester license.
That's what it is.
W
Molester
License
No...
You can't--
Stop!
Wait!
S-Someone, please!
This man is a molester.
A molester!
Someone, please!
Wh-Why?
Why is everyone ignoring me?
It's useless.
As long as I have the molester's license,
no one can stop me.
Wh-What in the world is a molester's license?
As you can see,
no one will come to save you.
Besides,
you have been getting horny for a while now.
That's not... true...
Shall we check then?
No!
No way...
For me to have my breasts exposed inside the train...
No way!
Don't play with them like that.
How is it?
You're still getting aroused from this, right?
That's not true!
Oh no, my nipples are getting stiff.
Am I really getting aroused?
There's no way...
Now, look at your reflection in the window.
How does your face look?
My face... looks really lewd.
So I'm really getting aroused getting done like this.
No, not that part...!
Please...!
No!
My private parts are being fondled inside the train...
I don't want this!
That intensity... I'm losing strength...
Don't...
No...
No way...!
Don't play around with it like that!
I'm getting really wet!
Why am I...?
I don't even want to get aroused by a molester.
Stop...!
Don't push it inside like that!
Don't play...
Don't play with my pussy!
Okay, you seem well prepared already.
It can't be...!
Didn't I tell you?
It's punishment from earlier.
No!
Please stop...!
You can't!
Stop!
Stop?
Do you really want me to stop?
I already said it earlier.
You're no longer in control to what happens to your body.
There's...
There's no way that...
Stop already, please.
I don't feel aroused...
At all?
Stop...
Stop!
But you're really wet and totally asking for it down there.
No!
You can't!
You can't...!
No way!
No...!
Please, pull it out!
Pull it out!
It hurts.
Please, it hurts!
Is it because it's your first time?
If you don’t relax, it will hurt more.
Stop!
Terrible! This is terrible!
Getting fucked by a molester...
In this place...
That part is getting warmer.
Your cock is shoving me down.
I'm going to break!
No...!
Why...
...am I feeling good being done like this?
No way...
It feels good!
I'm really feeling it...
I'm starting to feel weird.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Okay, good girl.
I'm going to step it up then.
It feels great!
Please, end this already!
I'm going to feel weird if this continues.
No...
I'm already...
Please...!
I'm going to...
No...!
What was...?
I'm sticky all over.
Terrible...
This is terrible.
Let me go. Please, stop...
Please let me go.
No...
St-Stop!
No... Someone...
Someone, please save me!
Please, save me!
Why?
No way...
It’s useless.
No one will come to save you.
Why?
Why are you...?
No!
It's painful.
And this thing stinks...
The back of my throat hurts.
I feel like letting up.
It's like I'm being used as a sex toy.
I don’t want this...
It feels like my consciousness is slipping.
Okay.
I'll be releasing everything in your mouth now.
No, no, stop!
You can't release your cum in my mouth!
Okay, good girl.
Now, it's your turn to feel pleasure.
Wh...What are you...?
What are you planning to do?
Please, stop this already.
Please, let me be.
I'll make you cum...
...until you lose it.
What is this?
It's shaking me up badly.
Don't...
No...
My nipples...!
You can't.
You can't...
It's tingling.
It's paralyzing...
No...!
It's still too early to moan loudly.
We're yet to go into our main course.
Oh? You're already wet down there.
No way...
D-Don't put it there.
No...
Don’t raise my legs...
Came already?
So it felt that good.
It does not...
Stop, please stop...
No...
Don't push it too much.
I'm already feeling weird...!
No...
Not there...
I already came so... forgive me!
Don't...!
This is weird.
This is weird...
I can't stop cumming.
It keeps going on and on...
Stop...
In that case, let's finish this last round with a bang.
No...!
St-Stop it already!
No... No...!
My butt...
Don't play with my butthole!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
Again and again...
How's this?
No!
It's coming...
I'm already...
My pee...
I'm peeing.
It won't stop.
I'm sorry...
So you felt it to the point of peeing?
Did that feel really good?
This just...
You just can't easily get away with this...
I can get away with it.
As long as I have this license.
A Molester's license...?
www.SubDESU-H.net
We would like to thank all passengers for riding the second central line today.
The next station is...
Wait...
Mr. customer, you can't...
What was that?
Oh, wow!
What's wrong? Are you feeling it now?
No.
I'm not feeling...
No!
Other customers are looking...
I don't like this.
Even if you say that, your nipples are already growing hard, you know.
You can't.
Stop!
No...
Wow!
In that position...
She's really feeling it!
Please, stop!
Why are you...?
No!
No...
Please remove your fingers.
I beg you!
Don't stir my insides up.
If you do it intensely there...
I'll... I'll...
No!
There, why don't you expose more of yourself?
Don't...
No way.
Don’t look.
Don't look at me...
Don't widen it up...
My insides...
My insides will be seen...
Aren’t you nearing your limit already?
No...!
I don't want to cum.
I don't want to cum...
Please, don't look!
Aoi Onee-chan?
Homura-chan?
No, don’t look Homura-chan!
I'm cumming!
Aoi Onee-chan...
Onee-chan, that's amazing...
What are you doing?
Please don’t do any more weird things!
For our dazed perverted train conductor,
I'll have to give the proper punishment.
What is that?
Stop!
D-Don't widen my butthole!
I don't want to...
No...!
What are you putting inside me?!
Don't inject something weird in my butt!
Something...
Something is weird...
Stop...
Aoi Onee-chan...
Is she going to be done in like I was?
But, her butt's being played with.
Stop, stop!
Maybe she'll experience something even greater?
My insides...
My insides feel weird.
I-It's painful.
It's going to...
Come out...
Shall we plug something in it then?
No!
Stop that!
It hurts!
It’s stirring me...
If I get stimulated like this...
I'm going to...
I understand. I'll pull it out now then.
No!
Don’t pull it out!
I'll get stimulated even much more...!
Aoi Onee-chan...
What a soft voice...
A very erotic voice...
It's cute.
No.
Stop it!
Anything but that.
It's my first time...
Please!
What are you saying?
Look at your sister.
Homura-chan?
It’s going in... It's going in!
Inside my pussy and my butt...
Something really thick...
Two big cocks
are entering me!
It’s good.
It feels good!
More!
Please thrust into me more!
Stir me up!
My breasts...
Suck my breasts!
Lick them!
Do it more intensely.
It's good!
Homura-chan?
The efficiency of the molester's license is really great.
I just raped her once and she's already like that.
You raped Homura-chan?!
That's why you're also going to...
It hurts...
It hurts!
Wait!
Don't move like that...
I'm going to break!
No!
Even if you say that, my cock's sliding in easily all the way.
Look at your big sister.
You love pussies as well, don't you?
Just like yours.
Onee-chan...
It's my first time seeing your pussy like this.
It looks cute.
No, Homura-chan!
Don't...!
Homura-chan...!
Aoi Onee-chan...
Please, do it to me, too.
Homura-chan...
Your pussy looks beautiful...
It feels good!
It feels good, Aoi Onee-chan!
I love you very much!
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan!
More, please lick my pussy more!
Continue thrusting into me at the back, too!
I'm going to be torn apart!
It's good!
Anal sex feels good!
Aoi, do you want to make it seem as if nothing happened here?
With this molester license, I can make it so.
Can you really do that?
Of course.
That is if both of you are willing to become my sex slaves.
Sex slaves?
I don't care if you don’t want to.
It's just that this incident will surely spread through these two.
Please wait!
Okay then.
Homura-chan...
What is it, Onee-chan?
Are we really okay with this?
Yeah. We don't have any other choice anyway.
I guess you’re right.
But is Takako-chan alright?
She's quite the soft type.
I'm a bit worried.
You're right.
I'm also worried about Takako Onee-chan.
But Takako Onee-chan's seems like it will be...
...very delicious.
Well then, Mihashi-san.
We're going already.
We'll leave the rest up to you.
Thank you for the hard work.
Something's really weird here.
He's widely continuing his molestation
and still no one's stopping him.
I remember that his name was Sawanagare.
If I could find a good clue on the net...
Because I was done in on the train like that,
I'm already...
I know that it's prohibited to do this in the office, but...
No...
I'm going to cum...
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
www.SubDESU-H.net