This is a small island located in the south pacific.
This resort beach is located in the B district.
We, the gravure idol unit Live un veil,
Hoshizaki Nanami
are having a photo shoot on this island.
We are having a 5 days and 4 nights photo shoot tour
Sena Nagisa
here on this island with the fans chosen in the raffle draws.
This must be an enjoyable event, but...
Kaede
But this event and photo shoot are ruined by that pervert.
Kurobane Kaede
Bichiku Beach
Subdesu-H
~southern island boob shame photo shoot~
Please take a photo of my naked body
Our bodies get hot when that pervert takes pictures of us
and we can’t subdue our dirty feelings?
No…
Erotic juice will flow out from that part...
Hey Kaede-tan, you’re too erotic.
That pose... is that a sister character?
I... I need to bear it.
They'll notice!
W-Will there be a photo shoot tomorrow?
Stop doing weird things.
You’re still horny, right?
This needs taking care of before going back to work.
No!
Kaede-chan, you can relax more.
I can’t.
Because...
B-Because...
I won’t stop until you say it.
No!
If you stimulate it more… I…
It will come out!
What will come out?
P-Pervert!
Even though you know what I mean...
I’m asking you because I don’t know.
The pee...
What?
I can’t hear you clearly.
The pee... the pee will leak out.
Please let me go to the bathroom!
Don’t worry.
No one is here.
You can do it here.
N-No way…
Stop...
My my... just give up and pee.
It will flow out...
No...
No 4x
It’ll come out!
It won’t stop!
No!
Don’t look!
Wow!
It’s the urine of a active gravure idol!
I can’t hold it any longer!
What?
No!
W-Wait!
At least, wipe my pee.
Put me down...
Put me down!
You’re still horny and won’t subside even after you've peed.
No way...
This is cruel...
This juicy pussy needs to have sex because it's pitiful.
Don’t... suck it.
Are you feeling good?
It's so good!
If you suck my nipples, I...
Deeper!
It's thrusting deeper!
What and where is it thrusting?
There you go again, letting me say that...
Of course...
Your dick is thrusting...
the dick is thrusting inside my pussy
Kaede, you’re really sexy.
Don't say that...
Don't say those dirty things...
Noo!
I’m going insane.
If you do it that intensely my pussy will break!
I’m about to cum!
I’m going to release it inside!
No!
D-Don’t release it inside!
Stop it!
Noo!
No... way...!
It’s flowing!
The hot juice is flowing inside...
This way your excitement will subside.
P-Pervert.
You’re a pervert!
N-Nagisa-chan, smile more.
Oh, ok!
You’re so sexy, Nagisa-chan!
That’s...
No, this swimsuit... that man made me wear this forcibly.
Nagisa-chan, by any chance... are you horny?
Hey!
Let’s take a lot of pictures!
I’ve been taken.
They're photographing my embarrassing expressions!
You!
What are you doing?
Get away from Nagisa-chan!
Nagisa...
You understand, right?
Y-Yes.
E-Everyone, this is not what you think.
This is...
this kind of photo shoot.
What!?
This is a special event where you can take photos of m-me in ways you usually aren't allowed.
T-This guy is an actor.
Really?
E-Everyone, please feel free to c-continue taking photos.
Hey,
what are we going to do?
If Nagisa-chan says that...
This is going well.
T-They're watching me.
I’m being watched!
This is too embarrassing!
Not yet.
The real show starts here.
A-Are you really going to put it in?
Are you really?
Hey… are you kidding?
Anyway, we’re going to shoot this!
Go deeper...
It's tighter than before, are you excited Nagisa?
No it's not,
I-I’m not dirty.
You’re dirty, Nagisa-chan.
So sexy,
so sexy!
They’re taking photos me.
They’re all taking photos of me having sex.
This pose...
It's too embarrassing!
Hey, there’s still something you should tell them.
E-Everyone, please take more photos of my naked body.
Too dirty!
My boobs...
And my pussy too...
I will show them for as long as you want!
Well said, Nagisa.
I will let you cum in front of them as a reward.
Ok...
Here is the finishing touch!
E-Everyone, I-I’m about to cum!
Everyone, please take a photo of me cumming!
Please take a photo me being full of semen.
No!
Nooo!
I-I’m cumming...
I’m cumming!
They took more...
Of me cummy, my boobs and my pussy...
They all took it.
Here.
Hurry up.
I know.
I-Is this alright?
It won’t be a tit fuck if you won’t rub it properly.
You can stop if you don’t want to.
I’ll do it, I must do it, right?
No!
Stop it!
Don’t excite me anymore.
Continue.
We won’t finish if you won't continue.
No...
Why?
It's embarrassing but,
my boobs are hot, the n-nipples are erect and numb.
Your boobs are so weak for this.
No, it's not...
this is because... you took the picture...
It's no use even if you lie.
No!
My nipples...
Don’t touch my nipples!
My my, if I can’t cum from the tit fuck, I'll put it in.
No way...
Because,
if you won’t hurry, the photo shoot will start.
I-I understand.
Do as you want.
You can rape me.
No...
Please,
don’t tease me so much.
The swimsuit will stain.
You’re already this wet.
That’s what I expect from pervert.
Nanami!
Don’t tell me you came?
A-As if...
Don’t lie.
You came right?
Because... you put it in so suddenly...
Nanami, you're so perverted, cumming just because I put it in.
Don’t say that!
I’m not perverted or sexy!
You’re the one to blame for this!
No!
My boobs...
I’ll finish this before the photo shoot starts!
I’m like an animal in this pose...
Holding onto the stone.
It feels good, right?
I-It's embarrassing!
Please finish it faster!
I’m about to cum, Nanami!
Cum with me, ok?
Together?
Will it satisfy you if we cum together?
I’ll cum with you, I’ll listen to you.
S-So p-please forgive me!
I-I’m cumming!
I’ll cum with you!
You’re really stupid.
I won’t forgive you just because we came together.
You’re cruel.
I still have a photo shoot and you ruined the swimsuit...
Don’t worry.
I’ve prepared a new swimsuit for you.
What?
T-They’re watching me...
This swimsuit is dirtier than being naked!
Hey Nanami-chan...
That swimsuit is amazing!
Y-Yes, it’s a bit daring,
I’ve done my best for everyone thats supporting me.
Is it weird?
It's great! Please show us more daring poses!
Eh?
But... in this swimsuit...
You’re always doing it!
You can’t?
That’s not the problem...
Nanami-chan?
I-I’m fine, I’m ok.
W-Well then, I’ll give you a special service today.
Nanami-tan!
This is embarrassing...
It's too embarrassing!
Don’t look at me with those perverted eyes!
I need to finish this quickly!
I’m going to be excited again!
From then on, we were being played by that pervert’s camera.
We had our dirty expressions photographed so much.
Our boobs and our pussies, everything...
But its strange, its was embarrassing at first but...
It's so good to be taken by fans in these poses.
We can’t go back.
I want to continue this secret photo shoot even after we go back.
If it's ok for you, you can come here also.
I-I’m cumming!
I-I’m cumming again!
Everyone, take a photo of me!
Take a photo of me cumming!
My dirty body!
Please take more!
Please!
You too!
You can release it everywhere you want!
Release the semen!
OVA  the origin of the bichiku beach is here