I should go check on the building.
That's...
SubDESU-H Presents
Seme Chichi
Sucking me off while comforting
yourself... What a thorough girl.
Now, next is...
Yes, Master.
How is it, Master?
Is it... Does this please you?
Ehm...
Keith-sama, right?
Eh... Yes.
I've heard about you from Master.
Eh, mhm.
Master is waiting in his room.
Exactly how long do you plan
to keep playing this game?
You're probably thinking that opening the art gallery is a little game between friends.
It's about time that you prepared
to follow in my footsteps.
The answer to that is... No.
Well, whatever.
You're probably expecting a little from it, right?
The world isn't easygoing enough for you to be able to get by just by playing around.
Father!
My apologies.
I had no intention of sneaking up on you...
It's alright. Thank you.
Ehmm...?
I'm sorry for introducing myself so late. I'm Nanaly, and I'm in the care of the household.
You're a painter?
I've still got a ways to go though.
Of course, I don't know whether I'll succeed in the future or not, but ...
I wanted to test my own potential.
And yet... He didn't have to put it that way. Damn.
I'm kinda only complaining here... Sorry.
I know...
It must have been fate that I met you.
If it's alright with you, um...
Could you be the model for one of my paintings?
-Oh.
-That's...
Ahh... This sensation of naked skin against naked skin. So wonderful, I can't get enough of it!
But...
-Today it feels a little different than usual.
-Eh?
Doing it forcefully like this is nice as well.
Ah... No... Master... Doing it this violently to my boobs...
I'm cumming!
No!
Master came a lot tonight as well.
It seems the smell of sperm makes you revert back to your old self...
Now, my Nanaly, let yourself
be fucked by me, your master!
Yes... Nanaly is... Nanaly is... A dirty maid who loves her Master's dick!
Please give this bitch your sperm!
That's a nice posture, Nanaly.
Your breasts are hot with passion, and that breathing... That body of yours which just wants to be abused...
Mmm... You're really a perverted girl!
I can't take it anymore... Hurry, not just your fingers, I want your cock as well!
Your dick... Your dick... It's going in... Going in me...!
Eh? That... All of a sudden... How mean!
Were you surprised that I did it so suddenly?
Either way, the way you let yourself be so shamelessly fucked is so indecent...
Inside you is the best!
I'm going to cum inside you...
Yes... It's ok... It's amazing...
Master... You're thrusting deep inside...
All the way to my cervix...
Master ...
Every time the candle wax hits your naked skin your pussy tightens around my dick!
Every time you shove your dick in, you hit all the way inside my pussy!
I'm sorry, Master!
Cumming before your master...
You're a failure as a maid...
No! Please, let me rest a little first!
I've got to punish a maid who can't do her job!
I'm happy knowing this kind of thing is something Keith doesn't like... We'll show that guy who knows nothing of the world your perverted nature!
Doing such an embarrassing
thing to the innocent Keith-sama is...
Did you get invited to be the model for one of his images or something?
Bullseye... Your red face is as good as admitting it...
The truth is, I was happy  to be invited,
but it's not love at all!
You're being honest, aren't you?  But it doesn't seem like I'll be tired any time soon...
Yes... Thank you very much... Please punish this lewd maid even more, Master!
I-I'm about to cum again!
That's nice... Such an erotic voice... Entertain me...!
Amazing... It's still coming out... I haven't been this horny in a while!
Master... I'm so sensitive since
I just came a little while ago...
Master... I'm so happy that you'd
give me your cum on my face...
This is what covered the front of your breasts with cum. Clean it up.
We had lots of fun tonight as well. I'm satisfied.
Yes. Let's do this again sometime, please.
Keith-sama... It's morning.
Mother...?
Good morning, Keith-sama.
Oh!
My apologies. You wouldn't wake up, so ...
Didn't you sleep well last night?
I see... This is the mansion...
Hmhm... So you're my new master, huh?
I'm pleased to meet you. My name is Renka.
From today on I'll be serving
you to your heart's content...
Master.
I see...
Quite a nice looking guy, aren't you?
Well, then, I'll be doing
the laundry, so let's undress you...
-Come on, come on, undress!
-Wait!
What are you doing, messing around all of a sudden...!
-Ah, I undressed you.
-Stop it!
Wait! That is...
How cute...
Father!
What the hell is the meaning of this?
What's going on?
Have you forgotten that this
is the time normal people work?
S-Somehow the maids have increased by one
Because now that you're here as well, Nanaly alone won't be able to handle everything.
While you're here, you should
have Renka here look after you.
-I'm already done here...
-Or would Nanaly have been better? If so, then you can have her.
No... That's not the problem,
it's... How should I say it...?
You've finished your conversation, right? Then...
Please take care of me, Master.
I don't know what to do about that maid... She's completely different to Nanaly...
Even at this time, you're working hard, aren't you?
Eh, yeah, it's for the upcoming art exhibition... Eh?!
What? Do you hate this kind of thing? Or could it be...
You don't get turned on if it's not forceful?
-Who would...? Put clothes on!
Geez, what're you doing?
-What am I doing? My job, of course.
Keeping you company at night is a maid's job as well.
That wouldn't be a maid... That would be a prostitute, wouldn't it?
Of course. That's the kind of maid we are.
Wh-What?
I was originally that kind of person. If I do it as a maid, I can join guilds as well.
If I do that, then there'll be a lot more houses willing to hire me, right?
What about her? What about Nanaly?
Yes, she's like that too. Probably.
About now, she'd be doing that perverted old geezer again, wouldn't she?
You are... Money is your goal, right?
Exactly. In this day and age you wouldn't
make that much money from doing a normal
job... Selling your body is the quickest way.
But, what, you're feeling pity for us?
Who do you think you are?
You don't even have the courage
to confess to that woman...
You like her, right? That maid?
I can see from how you act ... "Ahh, rich people have it nice, don't they?"
Painter or whatever...
Trying to escape from reality,
playing the lovesick fool.
You're not even standing on your
own two feet. You only know how to
leave your laundry in a pile for us to wash.
That girl is here because she chose to be.
She's much more mature than you.
She'd never accept a little kid like you.
What?! After I said all that, are you angry?!
If you're angry, then show me you're at least
able to make love to a prostitute like me!
It's ok.
If you really like her, then just don't pay attention to other things and let her know your feelings.
Renka...
You almost said something nice just now.
Wait... Hey! Are you serious?
Hello, Mr. Penis!
What? You were hiding this splendid thing all the time?
Well, then, right away...
Amazing...
The precum is overflowing as you try to hold back from cumming...
But don't hold back, just fill
my mouth with your sticky cum!
Renka... I'm about to... Cum...
Sheesh. You came too much... With this much, it'll get stuck in my throat...
There's so many things I can
teach such an eager master...
Amazing... So thick!
It's bent oddly, and it's hitting me where it feels good!
How is it? Can you see? That thick thing is entering me, so I'll spread my ass wide!
How is it? Doing it gently to a girl like this?
Hey, Renka... You're too rough... And besides, your way of teaching sucks...
Aren't you one to talk? Even though you're just about to take your first steps...
-You...
-Wha...?
So you really can let out a cute voice!
Sh-Shut up! Even though I'm just
teaching you some things...
Gently apply pressure like this, and apply a little love too, and from time to time fill up your pussy...
Renka-sensei...
Th-That's it. Hey, you're quite good at this, aren't you?
Oh, no, it feels so good...
-I'm... About to cum...
-It's ok, fill up my pussy with lots of sperm!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Was it alright to cum inside?
Yes. It's alright.
You filled me up so much...
Thank you, Renka... My emotions
have settled down a little.
Hmph. You were just so pathetic that it pissed
me off. Besides, I didn't do anything
to deserve thanks, I only did my job.
Even so, it's nice.
I've decided to follow in your footsteps, Father.
That's sudden.
Yeah. I've sorted out my feelings.
Really? You'll have to prove it to me.
Yeah. I know.
However, I want to paint one last painting for the upcoming art exhibition.
Well, that's fine. Just don't forget what you've just decided.
Yes. I know.
I'm sorry, Nanaly, calling you out here in the middle of your work...
It's fine, I had some free time anyway.
What did you want to talk about?
I'm sorry. Inviting you to be
my model the first time we met.
I'm not particularly bothered by it.
You look like her... My deceased mother...
Ever since I was little, I've loved painting.
For my sick mother's birthday I thought I'd paint
something for her, but... I didn't make it in time...
I've always wanted to finish it,
but... I wasn't able to paint at all...
That was probably what made me want to be an artist...
And then, when I saw you, I thought I could find what I was missing.
So that's how it was? But, if I can be useful to Keith-sama, then I don't mind at all...
-You're wrong...
-Eh?
I saw my mother in you, and tried
to take advantage of you.
I was only thinking about myself. I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
Huh? That was what he meant
by 'confession'? That idiot...
Ehehehe... Hi.
I'm returning to my room.
What's the matter? Aren't you feeling well?
No. I'm just a little tired from being stuck in here the past few days.
Ehm... Keith-sama. I'm sorry about earlier.
I knew it... I made you mad, didn't I?
No, that's wrong. I did that out of pity.
For Keith-sama to be so nice to a maid like me...
I think you're a very nice person, with a very kind heart, so please don't blame yourself.
I believe one day you'll paint a wonderful picture for your mother.
Thank you. Hearing you say
that made me very happy.
No, I'm sorry for bothering
you while you're feeling tired.
Good morning, Master.
I'm sorry... I really didn't want
to do something like this, but...
That's the reason...
There! Please do me more with your finger!
-How conceited...
-Making me this horny... This is
an unbelievably lewd maid!
Don't pull it that much...
Huuh? What's the matter? I haven't even shoved my dick into you, and you're already about to cum?
Yes... When you rub the inside of it, ahhh~
She likes being done like this... From time to time she lets the guys from town do her like this...
You're seeking that girl's body, right?
This is like a gift from me.
Now, Nanaly, this time it's this customer's turn. This man is a pervert who longs for you.
Y-Yes. Master.
Good evening. You're breathing this heavily... You don't have to be nervous, you know...
Ah, amazing... It's expecting to be fucked, and it's getting this excited...
I'm putting your penis inside me, ok?
Ah, amazing, it's hitting me all the way inside!
This is the worst thing that could happen...
Your penis is throbbing, saying it wants to cum...
It's ok. If you feel like cumming, then please cum inside me without holding back. If you don't listen to your balls you won't be able to cum inside me!
It's coming out... Inside me, the sperm is coming out!
Please, let me see your face.
-Now then... This, time you're
going to keep us company!
-No...
He came a lot inside you, didn't he?
We'll make you feel good soon!
No... In front of Keith-sama... Stop it, please!
I'll treat you well with my dick!
Here we go!
No!
Don't look, Keith-sama... Please don't look!
Your pussy's getting so wet... You're
enjoying being watched, aren't you?
Y-Yes...
Dicks. Dicks feel so good ...
Now that I think of it... You were looking forward to
using Nanaly as the model for a painting, weren't you?
Isn't now the perfect chance?
Luckily, the tools you need are here too!
So good... So good... More... Mess me up more... So good...
It's amazing ... My anus feels so good...
It feels so good... My butt... My anus...
Your dick... It's so delicious!
So hot... My entire body is so hot!
I came... In front of Keith-sama, I came so much...!