A salon, popular among the beautiful.
Its reputation spreads by words of mouth.
Young and beautiful women gather.
A store where you can't easily get a reservation.
Its popularity is always rising.
There was a man named...
Dokushima Nero, a rapist, is eying the women in the store.
He is...
Sorting all the customers with reservations
and sinking his teeth into them...
Translated by SubDESU-H
Yubisaki Annainin Shirudaku Settai Okawari Sanbai-me
指先案内人 汁だく接待 おかわり三杯目
She said this is a special course...
So I thought it would be a different person...
I see so you already want another man's dick...
Really, you're such a perverted woman.
N... no I'm not...
It's... it's touching so deep.
You...
Like the back part of the G-spot right?
No!... but inside there...
You're rubbing it...
You're saying things like you weren't a virgin just a few days ago...
It's not that... I feel good...
Then why is this wet pussy sucking in my dick?
I don't know about... ah...
Ah... wow... it's thrusting deeper...
Please... forgive me...
If you do this any more I'll...
Well then...
Using this special DVD...
I will let you feel even better...
I want to believe Haruna but...
I don't know what to do...
I...
Hamaji-san...
I will comfort you...
What's this...?
I've loved you Hamaji-san since before...
I won't hold back anymore!
Kaho!!...
Hamaji-san's dick...
It's hot... it's so hot and hard...
Please...
Let me suck it...
Stop... this...
No... no... nooooooo...
Even if you're saying no, it's still squeezing mine.
I told you right?
Men just... want to do it with different woman...
Your fiancé is the same too.
My wet pussy...
No... no way...
Please thrust it with this hard dick...
No way... this is impossible...
No...
No... no... noooo...
Hamaji-san's hot thing...
Please give me a lot!
No... stop... no...
Hamaji-san... it's... so... big...
It went in deeper...
Inside my pussy... Hamaji-san's big dick came in...
Hamaji-san... it went in further...
You want it to be even deeper right?
It's coming in... it's stirring inside my stomach...
It's a lot... it's too much...
Rub it... please satisfy me...
Release it... release it!!!!
Since you're starting to get used to this...
Then let's ask for the instructors of the special course to train you.
Is it our turn now?
We can do anything we want right?
You're cute...
She's had a lot released into her pussy...
So dirty...
Special instructors...?
Homeless people...?
Why?
You haven't taken a bath for awhile...
So stinky...
No... I don't want to...
Don't touch my boobs with your... dirty hands...
Hey...
You're not using your mouth...
What's this... it's rotten and... stinky...
It's stinky...
She sucks so well...
She's cute and her mouth is small it's so great!
Amazing...
Her tongue technique...
Is better than a prostitute...
If she sucks this hard...
Ricchan will... release it inside her small mouth...
So good...
So stinky...
What are you doing?
It's just...
Please don't rub me with that dirty dick...
It will stain...
It's alright.
If it's just this, you can clean this up in the fountain at the park...
Here...
Here???
No... don't put it in...
Don't put that dick in...
Noooooo!!!
No... no...
It's big... your dick is so big that I'm going to break...
It's... it's so great...
Young pussy is so tight and fun to rub.
Don't move it...
No... no...
I'm going crazy...
It's so dirty and stinky.
So big and... I... I...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!...
More... more...
Please give me more dirty and stinky dicks in my pussy.
Please give me a thick one and release it inside...
If you release that much inside, she'll get pregnant...
More... a thick one...
Give me sticky thick stinky sperm...
More!!!
Then...
We'll release many of them...
So much it will come out from your tits...
This one too...
I will send this one to your fiancé properly...
Nero-san...
Please rape me inside the store...
Are you thinking that I'll leave you?
I... I didn't think about that...
Sorry to say this but I already accepted another reservation.
Eh?
Is she the one?
Female lawyer.
I saw her in the magazines.
She seems to be popular in a sexual harassment trial.
She's an allies among females.
You must be careful with her.
She hates men so much and is a stubborn one.
That kind of impudent woman...
I want to make her moan all around...
Hmmmm.
So this is the salon which one can't get a reservation that easily...
Are you the female lawyer Nikaido Mutsugi?
Ah... yes...
We already finish preparing for you up grade course.
Ah... thanks...
Nikaido-sama...
Let's start our massage after you change your clothes into this.
Eh... oh... ok...
Sorry... I'm not used to this...
It's weird...
Oh sorry, I didn't mean in a wrong way...
It's my first time in an aesthetic salon...
I don't know what to do...
It's alright, you don't have to worry.
Leave it all to us staff.
Ok... thank you so much...
Excuse me... Is this alright?
As I expect from Nikaido-sama.
What a nice dressing...
N...no I'm not...
Then, you can now enter the massage room...
Oh... ok...
We'll let the body fill with oil...
Uhm... Sensei...
Why am I being blind folded?
This way, the sensitivity of the skin increases and...
It can receive more stimulation...
Nikaido-sensei...
The work of being a lawyer.
Is there any thing that makes you afraid?
Work that makes me afraid??
Yes...
Like you'll be threated depending on the details of the work.
Like will there be any violence...
There's some people like that but...
Even they do any kind of thing to you, if you'll just have to believe in your justice.
There's nothing to be afraid of...
Nikaido-sensei...
I'm jealous of you...
You're strong and beautiful...
You're smart and...
No I'm not...
Sensei... that part is...!!
It's alright...
B...but...
Next... I'll massage the hole in the ass...
Eh...? W...wait...
The ass... it went in inside my ass...
It's alright.
As we stimulate the ass hole,
it will increase the metabolism.
Ouch... that hurts!!
Take it out... Ouch!
Se.. sensei!!!??
Eh!?
It seems there's a bit of a wart.
Lawyer-sama is always sitting while at work so how troublesome...
What!? Who are you anyway? What are you!?
You're called the lawyer who is the friend of all women right?
So simply, am I the enemy among the females?
You... you must be the criminal that has raped many women...
Yes.. I am Dokushima Nero...
No... stop!!! Stop it!!!
Eh...? Why...?
This kind of thing...
Sorry Nikaido-sensei...
Just think that you're unlucky and please give up...
You can't escape... Ms. lawyer!!
N...no...
D...don't touch me!!! You pervert!!!
Your massage is not yet done...
What kind of massage is that!? Don't make fool of me!
If you prove me innocent in the court then.
We can stop here though...
W... what!?
I got tired of having to escape...
I'll surrender so.
Defend me and prove me innocent...
What are you saying!?
You know I can't do that right?
Then...
I'll just have to put this in...
How unfortunate for you...
S...stop...
Alright I understand! I'll prove you innocent.
So... let... let me go!!!
I'm glad to hear that!!
Ohhh?
I see... you're still a virgin...
Why are you putting it in...?
Didn't I tell you that I'll prove you innocent?
My actions will be proved innocent right?
Then this act too will not be counted as a sin right?
N...no!!
Noo...ooo...
Innocent innocent innocent innocent!!!
That kind of thing...
How regretful...
Being raped by this kind of guy...
Stop... I'll make this... ah...
Stop this already...
Hey... hey...
What's this...
You just lost your virginity but you are feeling good already?
No...No I'm not!
It hurts...
S...stop...
I can't hold it... it hurts...
I'm dying...
It hurts and I'm going to die!
No...no...
Ah... faster... finish it quickly...
Good... I'll release it...
I'll release it all inside!!!
Here... I'm going to release it...
I'll release it!...
Virgin internal cum shot!!!
No...no... no!!!...
Noooooooo!!!!!!
Nooooo!!!
She's even said she'll prove me innocent.
This is great...
It's cold...
Ah?
I won't forgive you...
To you...
I will surely pay you the noise of the society!
Definitely!!
It seems you still don't understand where you are standing...
I will let you stay here to do aesthetic camping...
By this,
She's being locked in the underground of the salon.
She being trained until she know how to obey orders...
You can do anything you want.
What ever you do to me... I will... I will never fall!!!
You don't have to do this to me, I won't even escape!
I'm not afraid to you!
Do what ever you want quickly!
You're really a stubborn one.
You'll just going to rape me anyway right?
Why are you letting me wear clothes?
You pervert!
Yeah... yeah...
The perverted me wanted to rape Nikaido-sensei so baldy.
So I wanted you to wear the clothes.
What are you talking about...?
And then...
Ripping off those clothes and squirt sperm on your body.
I'll just have to enjoy this...
No!!!!
I will introduce to you the Sensei here too.
Eh?
What a cute girl she is...
So hot...
Anyway... let's squirt on her...
No... no way...