A little more...
Nice...
Good...
Deeper...
Its thrusting in deeper...
I shouldn't be doing this but...
What am I doing?
I'm doing it here with a boy younger than me...
This time...
It's only this time...
I'm cumming...
No...
I-I'm cumming...
Is it only me...?
Oh? Is It Kirisaki-sensei?
Oh sorry, I was about to go home but I forgot something.
I can't immediately find it,
so I will lock the doors later.
Oh ok, good work.
Then I'll leave it up to you.
That surprised me.
My heart is beating.
Its amazing, isn't it?
The beating won't stop.
The old guy might come back again so lets do it quickly.
Its great...
I’m being thrust in the part that feels good.
Good...
You're getting better.
No... I think I'm about to cum...
It's alright, you can cum...
You can...
I'm also about to...
It was great...
It's still alive.
Hey...
Lets do it once more.
W
Private lessons of my English/science teacher
~My elder girlfriend who pouts cutely~
W
But you know, sensei...
It's really like a lie.
Its troublesome, right?
Hmm... I don't know.
They listen to me very well.
So I think you still got a long way.
But you have a boyfriend, right?
Is it your colleague?
Or perhaps something meeting up?
What are you saying? Something like that...
A boyfriend...
You don't have to hide it.
Or is it something like a bad relationship?
Don't tell me...
Hey, don't say such weird things.
Generally, about the bad relationship...
Even now it's...
Now it's...
So you do have, right?
So how does he look like?
What is he teaching?
N-No... uhmm...
He's not teaching anything...
Or maybe your partner is a student?
H-Hey are you sure?
I think that's illegal.
Illegal?
That's because...
Hey what is it?
Onee-san will teach you...
Are you doing something like that?
Ayaka...
You just got married.
Don't say such weird things.
That's it, ain't it?
My, I think its kinda fun.
Are you going to take the younger ones as your interest?
Don’t say such foolish things.
Geez... How dirty.
That's...
Its alright.
You're thinking about it right?
He seems cute.
W-What are you saying?
Well he's cute but...
Here she comes...
But, you have to put an end to it soon.
You're the older one you know.
Shut up.
I know.
Well, don't get burned.
Or I should say don't let him be.
Hmph, its none of your business.
I know that.
I know.
Work report
I prepared for it.
That's why we promised that,
we'll do our best.
He's doing his best, right?
Guidance counseling room
Ah... That surprised me.
Don’t push onto the one who's about to go home.
Sorry.
I ran out because I thought I was going to be asked to do some work.
No... no...
I get week when I see his face.
Now then, you know the reason why you were called, right?
That face...
I think you don't understand.
Oh no...
He's making a crying face...
So cute, but...
What should I do.
10:05.
11:17.
13:42.
14:32.
What were you doing?
He's confused.
What should I do?
When I see his confused face, it turns bad...
You were sleeping, right?
You said you'll do your best, right?
For both our sake, you'll do your best in your studies, right?
I was happy at that time.
I heard about it from the other teachers.
Lately, your grades have not been so good.
You should really do something about it.
If this continues...
Really.
That's why...
I'll give you a special teaching.
So that you'll study properly.
Eh?
You're saying you'll do your best in the next exams?
Are you sure?
Ok then...
Prove it to me on the result.
How ever...
You must prove it on your attitude too.
Sleeping in the class...
I-If you're my boyfriend...
I don't want you to do that.
Ok?
Prove it now on your attitude too.
Ok, you've passed.
I'll be looking forward to your results.
It's already big.
Are you holding it?
You must not show such a crying face.
It's gonna make me want it already.
Its coming out already from the tip.
Hey, please....
make sensei feel good too.
Good...
No... don't...
No...
Don't...
I...
It feels like its better than before.
You're so good already.
You were more like a dummy at first.
This one too.
It's always thrusting into the part which I feel most.
You're getting older with this.
Well, I'm the one who made you an adult though, right?
No...
You're so good in kissing too.
Geesh, I’m about to cum...
The boobs too...
Good...
If you suck that hard...
Move forward your hips.
Its pumping...
Just wait, I'm going to put it in now.
No...
I came a bit...
Please feel it more...
No... it's thrusting deeper...
It's so deep...
My pussy...
My pussy is about to be filled up...
No... My boobs are being sucked hard too...
Don't...
My nipples are getting erect.
No...
Why does this feel so great?
It's amazing than before.
No... It's thrusting in deeper...
and I’m about to cum...
To the cervix... its thrusting...
The part where I feel good the most.
Doing it while kissing...
It's so good.
I can’t hold it...
No... I'm cumming.
Hey...
I...
Together...
No...
I can't...
No... I'm still cumming...
It wont stop...
No...
O-Oh no...
No!
Ah... I did it again.
Even though I should not do this...
From now on, really... for his sake...
You must put an end to it soon.
You must stop the wound sooner.
It would be too late if something happens.
I know.
But...
Oh? We're already here.
Always...
we can't walk together.
Yes...
We'll go apart from here...
A teacher and a student...
We can't go beyond this...
We can't...
You even said you don't have any interest in younger ones... you changed so suddenly.
No can't...
No...
We can't go any further than this...
Hey...
Do you want to come over to my house?
I want to be with you more.
That was refreshing.
Oh? You're doing your assignment?
Good boy.
Hm?
Which part don't you understand?
Uhm... This is...
The assignment...
No...
Wait...
You can...
release it...
You could still release this much...
Good...
More is coming...
I can't stop this...
You have the attitude of one who doesn't see their surroundings.
You must not move forward without thinking.
But I can't...
I can't let go.
I don't want to let go.
I love you.
Only you...
Good...
Come in deeper...
There...
More...
Deep...
He’s thrusting in so deep...
No...
Its so good.
This is so intense...
I’m going crazy.
Do it more intense.
Make me go crazy!
No... I love this so much.
I love this with my whole body.
I...
Good...
Release as much as you like...
It's good... It feels so good.
A little bit more intense...
No...
I came a lot...
We must not fall asleep...
You're asleep...
I see.
You said you could sleep here today.
It's the first time...
That you've slept by my side.
How cute.
Just now you had the face of a man.
You... just got started.
He's not the same as you and he still has a long future.
You must end it, ok?
I know that.
But...
I can't let him go anymore.
I love him so much.
If you have that age gap, he'll easily get bored soon.
You're an old lady you know.
Maho
Maho?
Is she his sister?
Maho
Damn, don't fool withme
Whose house are you staying at?
I won't forgive you if you're
in that woman's house!
Give me a call you stupid!
I will come fetch you.
That woman?
Does she mean me?
Eh?