The night of the day I lost my virginity...
...I masturbated very, very hard.
Even though I came a lot that evening...
...I just couldn't stop.
While I kept on stroking my completely depleted dick...
...all I had in my mind...
...was Konome-senpai's face, and the softness of her hands.
The Syousengakuen graduation album...
...consists of two versions.
One, containing class pictures...
...and pictures of the culture festivals.
The other containing pictures of female students.
Extremely erotic pictures one can't take his eyes off.
The "Hamedori" graduation album.
I'm in charge of completing this album...
...and get to cooperate with the captain of the Kendo club...
...Kiritani Konome-senpai, whom I really admire.
The first part of my work is to collect the photos...
...of the girls that already have a partner to have sex with.
Class 3-A
Female Basketball Team
Sayama
Saya
Pisu
Sub
Hame
Desu
!
-H
W
Speaking of which...
...the day after the one on which I lost my virginity...
...my situation began to change.
What? Me?
Yup.
I don't have a boyfriend right now, you see...
Sex photos are a bit too much, but...
...a nude picture will be okay, I guess.
Class 3-A
Going-home-from-school Club
Matsudo
Iori
Will nude pictures be alright?
I guess so.
We have an exclusive room prepared for the photoshoot...
...I can take the photos there for you.
Um... but it's embarrassing to strip in front of such a beauty like you, Kiritani-san.
Th-That's not true!
*Gulp*
So I was thinking that a boy might be better company for that.
W-What should we do?
G-Give it your best shot!
Y-Yes!
Photo shoot in progress
Do not enter
I'll start shooting then.
Yeah. Take nice ones.
Yes.
I'll try my best to take good ones, but-
Why...
Why do I have to be naked to take them?
What?
It's embarrassing to be the only one stripping...
...and I'm a friend of Michisato Madoka, you know.
I've heard a lot about you.
Yours is... "amazing"... she said.
Wha-
I'll do my best to show you my embarrassing spots, so...
...stroke yours while you take pictures.
What the...?
It's up to you how far we can go with the pictures.
Let's give it our best.
You're taking so many... and you're so hard.
I'm shy, so I might cry. I'm sorry.
No, I love it.
This turns me on.
Really?
Look, I'm taking it off.
Here, you're welcome.
Pussy!
Seeing you this excited makes me happy.
I might play with myself as well.
Can we do it together?
Y-Yes.
Don't hold back.
Can you see it?
I love to rub my clit while sticking my fingers in there.
I never thought...
...that girls masturbate that hard.
Tamao-kun, kiss me!
Senpai, I'm about to...
It's okay.
Cum!
Cum for me!
Shoot it over me!
Decorate me with your sperm!
I came on her pussy!
Um, wait, I'll be taking that.
Look, it's in!
My stomach is full!
Matsudo-senpai... this... wha-
You're somehow cuter than Madoka told me you were.
I'll let you take a lot of sex photos of me.
I... came... again.
I'm gonna explode soon too.
Wow, your penis is changing shape...
floattt...
I came three times so my pussy might be loose...
...but you can cum in me.
Pushing my hips hard against you feels so good.
Matsudo-senpai...
...this is great. This feels so good.
Where can I cum?
I-Inside's okay.
Inside's good!
Wow.
I'll get some amazing photos out of this.
I'm cumming, senpai!
I'm sorry, senpai. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, senpai...
Don't worry about that.
After doing my part as a member of the graduation album committee...
...I got wiped clean by Konome-senpai as usual...
...and indulged my fantasies as usual.
The part where
I put my pants
back on is
always embarrassing...
We got a lot of photos, didn't we?
Y-Yes.
Including the photos we've received from the girls themselves...
...we have about a third of the Third Year female students.
The remaining ones refused to provide pictures or didn't respond.
So there's only a few left.
I guess so.
There are many things I learned since I joined this album committee.
There are two versions of our school's graduation album.
Students who don't provide sex photos will receive just the normal album.
Students who provided photos, however, are added to the Hamedori Album, and receive a special copy of it.
And that's one reason why they're participating.
There are many who want to see sexy photos of their classmates.
What is Konome-senpai going to do?
She is not someone who'd make others submit photos...
...without submitting any herself.
Someday she and her fiancé will...
Tamao-kun?
Y-Yes?
I-It's nothing.
We'll be meeting up with the captain of the swimming club late after school tomorrow.
Let's go together after club activities.
Yes!
We've been neglecting Kendo practice lately because of the graduation album duties.
Let's train hard tomorrow.
Y-Yes ma'am!
We'll meet up after the end of school at the pool.
Could you change into your swimsuit and come right away?
O-Ouch...
I couldn't get even one point from Konome-senpai today, either.
Her speed and technique are both better then mine, but...
...it's not just that.
Her strength is...
...different from me and all the other upperclassmen.
But just what is it that's different?
Konome-senpai in her swimsuit!
I'm sorry!
No, it's not "Don't look!" or something like that... um..
...I was late and didn't have time to have a shower.
I might smell, so-
KABOOOOOM!
If you say something like that I'll start noticing it.
Hey there, finish your chatter.
What are you doing there? Getting all excited before the show.
Today's the swimming club's third years' Hamedori party.
Class 3-A
Oda
Kaede
Class 3-C
Hoshizaki
Misaki
Class 3-B
Swimming Club Chief
Shimada
Ryou
Class 3-D
Suenaga
Moe
Class 3-B
Makabe
Mai
Girls' changing room
Wow, so hard.
So big...
...I haven't had something like this for a while.
Putting it in...
First man in a year!
I'm seriously excited - let's fuck hard!
A kiss... let's kiss.
I-It's the first time for me using a condom...
..but this isn't bad-
Come on, these are breasts.
Go ahead and play with them.
Oh wow, he's put his arm...
...under my swimsuit.
Tits!
Everyone was really looking forward to today.
Feels so good. It feels so good!
Have lots of fun, too!
Yes~
Thanks for letting us take the photos.
Oh no no, I should be thanking you.
Us third year swimming girls are a bunch of bitches.
Even so, they trained hard all year.
They were all pretty weak today so we're gonna train until dusk.
You can't really find or meet a decent man around here.
What about the boys in the swimming club?
Well, our boys are more like-
Wow, so much!
But still hard!
Hard as before.
Preparations for next round complete.
So that's the underclassman people have been recommending.
He certainly has got an amazing thing there.
Put it in please.
My swimsuit is torn by my pussy, so...
You can tell?
Well, not as much as you probably can, but yeah.
Yeah, he's amazing.
When we train, I can really tell.
It's as if I feel my own pelvis is going to break.
It's tightening up!
Yeah just like that! Squeeze him!
But is this okay with you?
Hm?
Well, us keeping him all to ourselves.
Huh?
Well, what I'm trying to say is... aren't you going to come and have sex with us as well?
What?
How is it? How does it feel?
How does his cock feel?
It's hard... feels awesome...
No, I have... you know... a fiancé.
Wha- That's...!
I felt really good, so I'll please you now.
Tamao-kun, it seems to be an all-night training session.
...give it your all, give it your best!
The condom inside me is filling up with sperm and twirling around.
Do me with your arm.
Wow... so good!
The condom and cock are twitching.
When you cum, please do it on my face!
Y-Yes.
Oh, just like that. Make me cum with cunnilingus!
Oh yes! Oh yes!
Don't stop moving your fingers. Keep fucking my pussy!
Oh no, I'm cumming again!
Oh no, again...
If such a large one does this, I'll split open.
I won't be able to be satisfied by a smaller one.
Oh no, I can't stop moving my hips!
Cumming inside feels so good...
Here's the list and the pictures of the people who agreed to participate.
Student Council Room
There might be some more later, but...
...I was thinking about producing the album with the pictures we've already taken.
Um...
There's not enough...
I can't even express how much you're lacking.
Your work is only half done, Tamao-kun!