www.SubDESU-H.net
I have been waiting for this moment!
Die!!
W
Brain Jacker
Vol. Two 「The Captured Beauty Goddess and the Imprisoning Past」
You've done well despite the circumstances.
My lady.
Your fighting spirit is quite something.
I cannot say that I was going easy on you.
As expected of the talented lady of the Lin family,
and also, my angel.
Shut up!
How dare you put me through something so shameful!
Gerald!
Calling it "shameful" is quite hypocritical, you know.
Didn't you shake your ass so much towards me,
and derived pleasure from it?
There is no way I would enjoy such a torture by shaking my ass towards a monster like you at all!
Not only me,
but you also betrayed the Lin family,
killed so many of my subordinates,
and then completely stole the Ruin Arms technology!
Gerald, the princess's personal tutor,
was nothing but a disguise.
However,
my true appearance,
this beautiful legendary creature... the Pegasus,
has continued without changing from the past,
and is in love with my lady.
You're out of your freaking mind!
Now...
My beautiful angel that I love.
Not only will you surrender the Ruin Arms buried in that arm, but you will also submit your tender heart to me!
Wha...
No doubt it's appropriate that I claim my lover's flower garden.
Surrender your body and everything to me.
An existence where there's only two of us, and nothing else matters.
Because you have Ruin Arms,
you can withstand this aroused penis of mine.
The fact that my lady became the owner of Ruin Arms
proves that the my existence in your life was fated to happen!
I already know your plans.
First, you lure me out and,
then get your hooves on the Ruin Arms.
But I will never give up Ruin Arms!
To snatch that Ruin Arms from my lady's body,
won't be any trouble at all.
You are misunderstanding something it seems.
How pitiful!
N-No way!
I had you analyzed,
and created the perfect method already.
The technology that can remove and transfer Ruins Arms to another being has already been completed.
T-Then why are you keeping me alive?
Just kill me already!
As I mentioned before,
I adore you, my lady.
It's only right that I love you not only as my angel,
but also as someone who wields the Ruin Arms.
Now. It's time I pleasure you, my beautiful companion.
Don't!
Something that large is impossible...!
Impossible! Impossible! I'm telling you I can't!
Don't move it!
No! No!!
I guess, if I am too aggressive even a Ruin Arms wielder like you would probably die as well.
Let's take it easy and slowly while we have fun!
Shit! I won't forgive you!
I will never forgive you!
My heart is in pain when I see my lady's suffering.
Let's soothe it with this medicine.
What the hell is that?
W-What is that!? Stop!
This aphrodisiac's effect is amazing.
For it changes your feelings of pain into an amplified form of pleasure.
Now,
I will have you accept my love!
W-Why?
Does it feel good?
I-It's good!
It's good. It feels so amazing.
Even though it's impossibly large, my pussy does not feel a shred of pain.
Amazing! So good!
My body has totally gone crazy now.
My stomach is bloating up so much.
I'm losing my mind!
It's good!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
It's good!
I'm cumming!!
For someone of your high stature, you are disgraceful.
It seems you want to feel a deeper sense of pleasure.
Then...
No.
I would never lose to someone like you!
Why are you becoming full of yourself?
Such a nuisance.
Fine.
I will take you to a place where there is so much pleasure you could die.
I'm going to die. I'm going to die!
You can't suddenly put that large thing so deep!
No!
My lady,
From now on I am the only one who is going to fill your womb up with my semen.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I would like you to be happier!
Me, having your child...
No!! Noo!!
No! No!!
N-No!
Now,
lets finish this!
It's coming in! The hot stuff is flooding in!
I'm going to die. My stomach is going to get burned!
Take it out! Take it out!
Quite the splendid reaction you gave right now.
Even though you resisted and protested so much,
don't tell me, you climaxed right after receiving my semen?
Its the fault of aphrodisiac - no no, it's the love that my lady and I share.
You're wrong! You're wrong!
I would never surrender to a worthless trash like you.
I am...
I am the next heir of the Lin family.
I am Lin Kaifon!
Oh look, someone who gets angry when toyed with!
The one being toyed with is you!
As Roy Roland's puppet,
becoming a no-good impostor,
right now you're nothing but  a horse monster!
You are disgustingly stupid.
Intoxicated by talent,
addicted to authority,
you suddenly became a disgusting monster!
And the one who doesn't realize is you!
You are the one being used by Roy Roland!
Very well.
I am going to let you suffer a fate worse than death!
What?
These guys are...!
Don't touch me!
No! No!!
Now!
Fuck that cheeky woman like a sow she really is!
What's wrong!?
Fuck her more aggressively!
That's what she wants, too!
Have you noticed it yet, my lady?
These orcs are the research subjects that were under my lady's direct supervision.
They must be thankful to be able to get naked and rub against my lady,
since it is... the annoying girl that treated them with nothing but ignorance.
They are the best tools for revenge because of poor treatment.
Now then my lady,
you are to drink the semen everybody put so much love into.
You are to swallow it all!
Please, forgive me.
I was wrong!
No!
N-No, impossible!
Stop! Stop! I beg of you...
Please! Forgive m—
A-Amazing! My pussy and my ass feels so good! I'm going numb!
Hurry and fuck my pussy!
Fuck me more with your cock!
It's good, so good!
The large cock is filling my stomach. It's aggressive! It's so good!
Too amazing!
It feels so good, I'm going to die!
I-I... I'm cumming!
I'm going to die! I'm going to die!
I'm going to die!
But it feels so great... I can't anymore...! It's impossible!!
I'm cumming! Being subjected to this... I'm still going to cum!
No!
I'm cumming!
Have you decided not to be as rude as before?
It's not over just yet.
You fucking cheeky sow!
I'm cumming!!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!!
The training up until now is just the beginning.
From here on, it's the real thing.
Can my lady handle it without dying?
Now!
Destroy this slut's heart and soul!
Forgive me! Please!
Forgive me!
Forgive me, Pegasus-sama.
I was wrong.
I was wrong for challenging you.
Are you really remorseful?
I will never stand up against you again!
I am a sow!
I am Pegasus-sama's slave!
Alright, alright. I get it.
I guess we can forgive you.
But... since they were such great tools,
in strengthening the bond between my lady and me...
For discipline purposes, let's continue the training till the very end.
N-No!!
Help me!
Help me...
www.SubDESU-H.net