This is a place, where demons and humans
coexist in a lawless society.
I, Tachibana Rikurou
was almost captured to be sold to a slave trader.
But I was saved by the one known and
feared as the Steel Witch Annerose.
I then became her servant.
Then one day I caught sight of her very
erotic defenseless sleeping body.
I was unable to resist her lewd boobs...
Then, I unconsciously took her virginity
What lies ahead of us now,
is a life that transcends the simple relationship between
master and servant, a lovey dovey erotic life!
Riku...
Yes!
You better replace those sheets that you
have deeply stained with your semen!
And try to put a leash on your "outbursts" too.
Good grief.
And here I thought I'd just became a special someone to her.
Now I'm just treated as a man with
no control over his carnal desires.
You're in the way stupid human!
This is Michiko.
A maidservant of Annerose.
She also lost her virginity because of me,
but her attitude towards me hasn't changed.
What are you looking at?
The White Snake of Kuurou Organization,
Lee Mayfeng.
Annerose's sworn enemy.
Your black overall looks as ugly as ever.
Annerose the Rusty Steel.
It's far better than trying to hide one's deeply
tainted nature under a hide of white,
Mayfeng the Mud Snake.
Shut up!
Just hurry up and bring out that crazy machine gun girl!
Machine gun girl?
Could she be...?
Oh yeah.
There were a few thugs from the Kuurou organization there
that were injured.
Oh, the one Riku calls Miki?
The one who came to Amidahara and requested
that we find her lost brother.
The girl with giant breasts that tried to attack
the entire Kuurou organization, right?
That's right.
I noticed that there was a strange person around my place.
Why hello there.
Miki-chan!
We promised to meet at the bar, didn't we?
But the brown lady said that this place is the safest.
Aish-san again?
Instead of being safe
you were almost made into a porcupine
by Mayfeng's blades though.
Hand over that girl to me.
If you don't,
we will consider you as enemies and kill you.
Though, I would rather like you to resist and be killed actually.
If you think you can kill me then try it,
Mud snake.
Don't call me that!
Rusty steel!
Annerose!
Let's go, Riku, Michiko!
Annerose the Steel Witch
02 The Vexed Witch
Are you okay, Riku, Michiko?
Where are they?
They went off somewhere.
Damn those kids,
forcing me to babysit this girl...
Get a move on already!
Please don't leave me!
Now we're separated from Annerose!
So it's my fault now stupid maid?
What did you say stupid human?!
What a sight for the great Steel Witch.
That's right.
If you just stay still
I'll give you a treat.
I'll pierce those haughty eyes of yours.
Oh, but I guess this one's better after all.
You have the worst hobby.
These needles actually feel good you now.
Just look forward to it.
I'm going to push it in further.
Okay, insertion complete.
Poison insertion complete.
Now this is the end for the tomboy witch!
Mayfeng, what did you do to me?
I injected an arousal poison in you.
I got your pleasure nerves all crazily fired up.
You're soon going to ask for a cock like there's no tomorrow.
If you don't kill me now
you're really going to regret it!
I heard that really well.
Those lines sounded exactly like you're some underling.
Let me hear some more.
Come on, come on!
This poison...
My, my, you're trying really hard.
All of you over there, come and assist me here.
Now, let's show Annerose the iron hand of justice!
Stop that.
Stop touching me you trash.
Let me go!
I can really hear it.
You're getting really aroused,
as your big boobs bounce around like that.
Oh, what now, what now?
Could you be... already wet down there?
You're getting aroused from this crude foreplay?
I'm not the slightest...
What a great view.
The great Annerose is getting aroused like a wild pig.
I'm not...
This is, not me...
I feel that my efforts have really bore fruit.
It's a special poison that was specifically made
to make the great Annerose realize what a wild pig she really is!
Now I'll add three more.
It's a piercing that is truly befitting for a wild pig.
No way, it doesn't hurt...
Rather, it even feels...
If you're going to cum, you have to say it properly,
you pig woman.
Snake woman!
Now then, since we're finished with the appetizers,
we'll be heading to our main course.
What are you...
Hey, widen your hips more.
Open your thighs too.
Stop! Stop!
Oh my, even if I gave you such dosage of my arousal poison,
this much secretion is still...
Don't look... Don't look!
I'll have you expose that as wide as possible.
And have a look at how your pussy has sex with a cock.
This is the best!
Your pussy is twitching all over!
My pussy, is being totally penetrated...
Can't get enough of it, right?
You don't need to hold back.
Shut up... Be quiet!
You're the one who can't keep her voice down, right?
Getting soaked wet with your own juices,
how much more lewd can you get?
Remember this.
I'm defintely going to kill you.
Look, look, you seem like you're ready to cum.
His cock's constantly rubbing inside you,
while you continue secreting wildly.
Your pussy is about to cum!
I'm cumming!
Something hot is being poured inside me.
He's releasing it in me.
I won't... I won't let you release it inside my...
You really liked that, didn't you? The semen.
Injecting it in you was not enough.
Since you even came as it flows out of you.
Don't try to hide it.
We're just getting our special wild pig cock party started.
There's one more right, my princess?
A hole where a cock can be inserted.
That's...!
In my butthole?
That's not the right one!
That's not the right hole!
Yes, it's the right hole.
I said it earlier, right?
Wild pigs have another hole that can be used.
My, oh my.
The precious semen that we injected inside is spilling out.
Don't use my hair.
Don't use my boobs either.
My butt... hurts...
Oh, it hurts for the wild pig?
Then it can't be helped.
What are you...?
It's a potent special arousal lotion.
You already know my ability, right?
Wild pigs just love this thing.
And I can make an unlimited amount of it.
– Now, take this.
– Stop!
I'm going to insert this now into the wild pig's pussy.
That's...
Not my butt...
That's my pussy!
That's right.
It's the horny witch's lewd pussy
that was given away to the man who's in your butthole.
Oh no...
Don't stir it up.
It's spreading...
It's spreading inside me.
Let's loosen up your stinky pussy hole with your orgasm!
It's touching...
You're using the flesh inside my pussy
to touch the cock at the other side!
My butt is...
My butt...
No way, you even squirted your juices on me.
What a dirty way to cum.
Preparations are already complete over there, right?
Here, here, here!
Cum some more!
This wild pig here will cum until she goes crazy.
My ass...
My pussy...
Go crazy, you wild pig!
Climb to your climax from this dirty hole sex!
I'm cumming with my butthole.
If this continues I'm going to cum with my butthole!
That's what I've been saying!
This wild pig should cum through this dirty hole!
Oh no!
The pig's really cumming!
She's cumming with a cock penetrating her butthole.
No don't...!
I'm going to die, I'm going to die!
Stop, stop!
Does it feel that good?
Being stirred up by a woman
while being impregnated through
the other hole with a man's cock.
Now, now, now, now!
Say that this anal sex feels good.
If you don't
I'll inject more of the arousal poision in you.
No more of the arousal poison...
Then say it!
Say that it feels the best when you're penetrated anally!
Anal sex feels good.
It feels the best when I get penetrated anally.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming while being cummed inside my butthole.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Amazing.
That squeal was just fantastic!
The orgasm level of this wild pig is getting even higher!
That was wonderful Annerose.
I think I might just like you for the very first time.
I can't take this anymore.
I can't...
Listen up boys.
This wild pig witch is asking for more cocks.
Make sure to treat her well.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die...
Good work, Annerose.
You sure did your job well.
Stop this... already...
That was very splendid, even if I did say so myself.
Annerose-san!
You two are late.
Please don't look.
It is as you see it now.
I'm going to bring a few more men and beasts, so just wait there.
How dare you do that to Annerose-san!
Riku.
Pain is a type of body limiter.
Part of a mechanism that dictates a person's physical boundaries.
But if death was at the limit of pain,
then how can we describe being immortal?
It's being able to surpass your limits.
Such is the true essence of an immortal.
To surpass the limits of pain...
What is this?
I am an immortal.
One who has surpassed the limit of pain...
Transcended his existence as a human.
I am who has exceeded my very own limits.
I will protect the ones I love,
as the true immortal
The poison inside lady Anne has been completely removed.
So is Annerose-san safe now then?
That is what I just said.
Also, you need to make her take this.
Annerose-san, how are you feeling?
Woah, who... are you?
I see.
So Annerose becomes like this
every night of a new moon.
That's right.
It's because the Kongou Yasha's powers weaken at this time.
So that's why Mayfeng was able to...
Regardless however,
for you to have forgotten who your master is
just because of a mere change in form...
Geez.
But, even the way you speak has changed.
Why is that?
That's because, well...
It's a way of expression.
So that means,
you're now trying to get along with my preferences?
Why would I do that?!
I was already like this!
It's a special soup made by Neu-san.
Here, say "ah".
Now you're treating me like a child...
It's hot, it's hot!
It's too hot, I can't eat it!
Why don't you check first if I can eat it properly?!
I'm sorry.
Then...
I can't believe that you just tried to
take your master's lips like that!
Even though you're just a servant, you impertinent fool!
I want some more!
Just feed me already!
Okay, okay.
I'm on it.
Don't twirl your tongue like that!
I want to have sex with you now, Annerose-san.
It's okay, right?
Why should I be doing it with a lowly servant?
If I kiss you some more, would you feel like doing it?
He's sucking it...
Can you suck my lips this time?
You fool, why would I...
You're good, Annerose-san.
Of course, this is nothing to me...
What is it now?
Annerose-san, you're going to have sex with me.
Right here, right now.
Sex, with my servant..?
What are you..?
How much bigger are you going to get it?
You fool!
We're now about to start a copulation
between a male and a female!
Just wait Riku!
It's tight!
Annerose-san, your pussy is very tight!
It's getting opened
My pussy is being opened by force.
Idiot!
Huh? I'm sure I'd already taken your virginity once.
Is it that bad?
When my body changed and got shrunken like this,
my virginity also came back.
Really?!
What's with that face?
So that means I can always take your virginity once a month?
What, I will not allow such...!
I've just lost my virginity again.
– Don't move around!
– Annerose-san's virgin pussy,
is my personal pussy!
I'm going to...
I'm going to break!
Stop knocking deep inside me constantly.
It's going to pierce through...
Your cock is going to pierce through my womb!
It's in.
Your cock is entering my womb!
Annerose-san, I'm going to impregnate you!
I'm going to release it all inside your womb!
No... I won't allow a servant to impregnate me!
His cum is going to burst inside me...
My womb is going to be penetrated by his semen!
Please be my personal pussy!
It's flowing inside me!
Something hot is entering into the very insides of my womb!
And when something hot gets released inside there...
I'm going to cum!
You just came earlier...
Don't move...
I still want to have sex.
Please remember the taste of my semen in your womb!
What are you saying?
If my womb remembers the taste of your semen...
I'm going to...
I'm going to...!
This is humiliating.
But tonight's Annerose-san is very cute.
You're just my servant, so stop saying such conceited things.
It's so full.
I'm going to make you feel better.
What are you...
Oh no...
Your semen, is rubbing the insides of my pussy.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming from the outflow of semen!
This time, please clean my cock.
You're going to pay for this someday.
Remember that.
Then first, we'll have to get a prediction
on the whereabouts of Miki's older brother.
Good morning.
I overslept!
You're late stupid human!
Seems like you need a serious beating.
Lady Anne, do you know something
about the unknown sorcerer named Barde
that has appeared in Amidahara recently?
No.
I somehow feel a bad premonition about this.
Don't worry old lady.
We'll try to investigate about it
while searching for this girl's brother.
Barde Barde.
My longstanding desire,
The philosopher's stone, is in that building.
Riku...
You're making that little cute face.
Could it be that you're a lolicon?
Huh?
Hey, what are you smiling at stupid human?
Well, that's because I now get to take Annerose-san's
virginity once every month!
I can't wait for it!
Did you really feel that good with me?
Well, definitely!
Die, stupid human!
That's right! That's right!
What are you guys doing here?
In any case...
Well, even if you ask me that...