W
Please stop it...
That's... no...
Stop it!
It's hitting me deep...
Inside my womb...
It hurts... It hurts... My nipple's gonna rip off!
Please... I beg you...
With that... That dirty thing...
I'm gonna cum again, even though I don't want this...
It hurts so much...
Why my body keep getting hotter...?
I'm becoming so lewd...
Please... you can't do it... on there...
I can't hold it...
My stomach... is being penetrated...
No...
Don't suck on my breasts... so roughly...
I can't... hold...
it anymore...
No... my body feel like it's breaking...
shattered into pieces...
Seito Kaichou Hikaru
Part 1
Public Loss of Virginity!!
Lewdness|Demon|in|Academy
Summon! Sacred Wing!!
Demon extermination! Expel Darkness! Secret Cross!!
Gaoryuu's secret technique, Cross Fire...Light!!!
Even though, you're the strongest... Is that all you can do?
Izumi Hikaru.
Why we can't exorcise any of these demons?
I can't believe that the academy's protection didn't work at all!
You can't lose hope!
Seira-chan! Yuki-chan!
We'll just defeat him... Defeat that Barms.
The barrier should break as well.
Interesting, then you can try it.
Gaoryuu's ultimate technique, Senkaku Spirits!!
Won't let you do that!
Haven't I told you before?
When you're using the Senkaku Spirit, you leave your side unguarded. So you have to be careful with that.
Ko... Kotone Sensei...
I won't let you interrupt Barms-sama plans.
That's... Why would you do that?
Did you fall to the demons?
I receive dark powers as pleasure from Barms-sama.
I'm in total ecstasy right now.
I'll let you feel this too.
How is it, being abused by a weakling like me?
This is nothing to me.
But, you don't have any power left to fight, don't you?
Wha...What is this?
Stop it!
There... princess Seira's embarrassing part is in full view.
You coward!
Do... Doing something like this,
I'm not ashamed at all.
There there... If you feel it then say it out loud!
Don't fuck with me!
I'm not feeling anything from this!
Even though my body's getting abused like this,
My heart... would never...
Pretending to be strong, huh?
It will be more exciting this way.
Then how about in here?
In there...
What is it, you're feeling it more in here?
Stop it...
Teasing me with something dirty like that.
Sto...Stop it...
You're princess, your asshole still stinks.
Shut your mouth!
You... pervert!
That's good.
Then, why don't you let me take your virginity first?
Sto...Stop it... you can't...
My ass... fucked in my ass...
Pull it out... please pull it out...
Stomach... the inside of my stomach...
Please don't move around inside...
Here...here... It's getting tight.
Aren't you feeling better already?
Don't say things like that as you please...
It doesn't... doesn't feel go-
There's no dirt inside of it, right?
It's slowly going inside of you.
Lies... It can't be...
In my tentacles, there's a lewd demon poison inside of it.
If it completely infects you, your body would become,
Someone who's just as lewd as us.
You're feeling it after being fucked in the ass.
Now you're becoming lewd demon, Lewd one!!
What are you... gonna do?
I'll make your breast bigger with these hands of mine.
Stop it.
I won't forgive you for tainting my body like this...
I feel something going inside...
No~ No...
Something...my breasts... Somethings going inside my breasts!
There we go, faster...faster...inflate!
What is this... breast... my breasts...
No~!!
He...he...It's coming out!
No, I can't stop it!
Coming... It's coming out~!
From now on,
You're going to be a love slave and also a slave cow as well.
No...don't suck it... I don't want my breast to be sucked...
It's delicious.
Soon your breasts will fill up with demon poison inside of it.
My breasts are tainted with this demon thing...
Even though you're a demon hunter, you have quite a nice body.
Do you feel it?
I'm not gonna feel anything from being touched with those dirty hands.
It's the worst feeling!
Now is your only chance to say something like that.
How is it?
Embarrassed and unable to fight back?
Ba...Barms...
Hm...what is it?
I'll make you feel more pain after this.
What's that?
How does it feel?
To be shocked by my lovely tentacles in your sensitive part?
I'll let you feel all of the misery you gave me.
It won't end just like this.
Your armor spirit is already slowly starting to weaken.
While lowering your spirit power within your body,
Your nipples and clitoris for example,
Even your ass and the way you pee,
You should be getting more sensitive to all of it.
Even when you're just walking, your pants will be drenched and you're gonna feel the ecstasy.
I'm not... gonna be like that...
Last one, I'll remake you with my own hands.
What is that?
Stop it!
Rest assured,
I'll leave your virginity for now.
The best part will be for later.
What're you gonna do...
Please don't tease my body any more than this!
How is it?
This is your womb, right?
Don't touch it, that place is important for girls-
From now on, I'll let your womb feel more of it.
Stop joking, that's something...
No, you can't...you can't...you can't~!!
What a great expression, Hikaru-san.
If you're really hate us, then why don't you kill us already?
I don't need your life, you know?
Barms-sama's plan is to get all of the student council members to bear next generation of demon children.
You can't deny Barms-sama wishes now,
If you want to save all the lives inside this academy.
Hey, why do you all look so ashamed?
Just say it quickly.
Student Council President Izumi Hikaru-san, if you would say it right now.
We're from student council and we will do something for the boy student in this co-ed academy...
We hope... it can get rid of a little of your anxiety and that this is would be some of recreation for you...
Now...we're gonna show you...the real thing...
Hey...hey...is this for real?
The student council members are gonna strip?
What are they doing? I can't hold it!
I'm getting a hard on.
Hey...hey... what is it with you three? Your hands stopping, aren't they?
I understand.
What is it with those panties...and their bras?
The Student Council Prez is wearing something like that,
It's really erotic~
Hey... Were Ayatsuji Yuki's breast really that big?
Her bra is too small to cover her breasts.
Hey...hey... look at Seira too.
She's got such a lewd ass on her... I couldn't even imagine!
Are they gonna show inside of it?
Well, we'll start from Yuki-san.
We're...gonna show... the wonders of a naked women's body...for you...
Yes, next one's Seira-san.
If any of you still don't have a girlfriend,
we, the student council... will take responsibility.
By offering this body to you.
What do they mean by "offering"?
Explain it throughly, Hikaru-san.
If you want us to do it, we'll do any lewd things for you.
I'll be marked as a pervert with this,
Even though I don't wanna say something so embarrassing like this...
Hey Student Prez, you'll do anything right?
Ba...Barms...
Then why don't you leave nothing on your body?
That's...
Naked in here...
We can't-
Huh, you can't do it?
What's that, is the student council just all talk then?
That's right...that's right... Since you've come this far, why don't you show us all of it?
Show us your breasts... breasts!!
Pussy too...pussy-pussy!!
Hey, just... take it all off!!
I got it, we'll strip everything.
If we're just...show them... that's okay, right?
What's wrong Hikaru-san? Just take it off.
You said you would didn't you?
Yes...
Well... Yuki-san too.
Yes, Seira-san too.
You should remember this!
Oh... all of it is showing...
Seira's body is somewhat erotic, isn't it?
Don't look at me with perverted eyes.
Ayatsuji Yuki is amazing too!
Those breasts are totally oversized.
Her nipples are also getting excited and standing up.
Don't stare so much.
Izumi Hikaru too is incomparable...
Student Prez's breasts and pussy looks great...
As I thought, that dark long hair is good after all...
It's not like we like doing this...
It's a beautiful view, isn't it?
Anyway, lets turn this pleasure into something more exciting?
Okay~?
No...
Stop it!
Hikaru-san!
Shut up you two!
Wha... What is this?
No... No~
I won't let you disturb Barms-sama, okay?
Hikaru-san!!
Hikaru!
Let me go... stop it!
What do we have here?
What's with this sweet and sour smell in here?
Hey, look over here!
There's a virgin smell coming from the student Prez's pussy.
Prez's a virgin?
Wow... a virgin pussy!
No, don't look at it...
Don't lick it... stop it-
In there...
Don't lick... don't lick it...
Stop it... that's...
No...No...You can't!!
What's the matter?
Did you feel it even though you're a virgin?
I'm not gonna feel anything from something like this.
I won't lose against someone like you...
Don't lick there...
Tongue... don't put your tongue inside...
Your perverted juice is slowly flowing out.
It really tastes like a virgin.
Why is this?
Even though I'm being abuse like this.
I'm feeling this perverted sensation...
I'm going to go crazy soon.
No~!!
Well, shall we let the others see what your virgin juice is like?
No...No... everyone, don't look at it!
Amazing, It's drenched.
Student Prez, let me see the proof!
The proof that you're a virgin!
That's right, show us your virgin's mark!
That's something I can't show-
You should answer those requests.
I can't do that!
Then I'll just kill them all.
That's...
Then why don't you spread your legs and show them your virgin's mark?
I got it... I'll do it...
Show it all!
I can show it all...
Virgin's mark.
That's the student Prez's virgin's mark?
Then why don't you explain to everyone, so they can understand it.
This is my... proof of Izumi Hikaru's virginity... Hikaru's virgin's mark.
You're able to say it.
Then as a reward, I'll let you be my woman.
Well, just do it quickly!
Right, you can put it in by yourself.
Hey, say what I told you before!
Facing everyone!
Everyone... I'll now let this penis slowly penetrate my pussy,
Then let it take my virginity.
Please look... at me losing my virginity... right now...
Okay, put the penis inside!
Put it inside!!
Something so big, It's impossible for me...
Hey...hey... you didn't even put it inside yet.
Let it inside...inside!
No, It won't fit in...It won't fit inside...
Here you go!!
It's hot... hot...
Ripping... It's gonna rip apart...
My pussy gonna rip apart...
Stop it... pull it out... pull it out...! It hurts... It hurts...!
Stomach... is coming out...my stomach is coming out...
With this, you're the perfect woman,
This is an important task as demon hunter.
Don't joke with me! I won't be beaten by you... even if I lose my life,
untill the end...
That's an interesting condition you have!
It's intense... too intense...
Stop it!
It's intense... so intense...!
Rest assured.
Your body won't break from just this.
Your body is filled with the demon spirits from before!
At the same time, you won't forget this feeling, so you won't able to leave me anymore!
I won't be...
I won't be something like that...
You will be!
When I fill you with my semen and you bear my child!
Stop it, don't cum inside!
You're... I don't want to bear your demon child.
I'll release a lot inside of you!
Inside... no... inside... stop it... No... No...!
No~!!!
Hikaru!
That's cruel.
If you release that much...
I'm gonna get pregnant.
After you lost your virginity, you got pregnant, that's good isn't?
Quickly! Pull it out...
I'm gonna... gonna get pregnant...
What are you saying?
Today won't finish just like this.
That's...
Amazing, just how many is that?
She's been fucking forever.
My stomach... it hurts... it's in pain... It's gonna break... gonna break...
No...
Please pull it out... I beg you...
Pull it out... please let me rest a bit...
Don't worry, I'll energize you with this pleasure.
You're feeling it, right?
Right now, your womb is your weakness after all.
My womb will die...
My...womb...gonna die...
die...my womb...my womb...
I'm gonna die~!!!
Let's make it flashy!
I'll release it once more inside!
No... you can't... If you release it inside again...
I'm gonna pregnant...
Please... please stop it already...
Hikaru-san's been fucked for so many hours...
If this continues, Hikaru would surely break.
Don't worry, It will soon be replaced by pleasure.
It's the same with me.
No... It won't... the hot feeling in my stomach won't go away...
It's about time, I'll take it from behind.
Eh?
Even though it's your first time, it looks like this.
No... not in there... stop it!
Oh, It feels really good in here!!
Hey, suck this too!
Rubbing... the inside of my ass is rubbing it, It's gonna rip apart...
From my ass to my womb, It's all fucked up!
Hey...hey... the upper mouth is still open, isn't it?
Here, suck it up!
Hey...hey... It's a foursome now, right?
Even though she says no, she's still sucking it all up.
Maybe she's totally lewd?
Maybe our student council president's a total pervert after all!!
It's not... It's not like that... It's for of your safety, that I endure all of this shame.
Cruel... It's just too cruel for all of you!
Se...Seira-san, everyone... looks kinda strange, don't they?
They're all being sucked in by the demon spirit.
How does it feel to have all of your holes fucked?
I'm almost at my limit!
I'm ready over here too!!
Take it!
Doesn't it feel good, being fucked in both your mouth and ass?
But I'm the one who make you feels good, right?!
Your penis is number one!
Here... Suck it up, suck it like a whore!
My pussy feels good... feels so good!
Penis... inside my pussy... really... really... really...
Bear it... bear it... bear the demon child within you, Izumi Hikaru!!
Bear it!!
That's...
Hi...Hikaru!
You're next you know?
Seira... Yuki...