Hello there! It's been a while, Shirakawa Kyouko here!
Hey! This is Ryouko! We meet again!
And over here is-
I-I'm Anzu.
Thanks to your support, we're able to bring you the sequel to the first Anejiru OVA!
So, we're going to show you some things that happened in the previous episode!
O-Onee-chan! That's fine, but...
Why does it have to be in a bath?
Oh? In order to service the viewers, of course!
So then, I'll go first.
Tada! How's it look? Doesn't my moist body look great?
Even my breasts are just as bouncy!
So how about I start with a back shot?
Feel free to get a towering erection, guys!
C'mon Anzu! How long are you going to wear that towel?
No wait! Give it back!
Geez, this is embarrassing!
Oh, right! Since this is hentai animation,
there isn't going to be any lame censoring, like steam!
Huh? N-Noo! What is this?!
Geez, no need to be so restrained...
However, I'm not sure if Anzu's body will be of any service to the viewers!
T-That's not true!
Some people like it this way!
Then you'll need to try your best to please such folks!
Fine then, I will...
P-Please don't stare at me,
it's super embarrassing.
I'm just doing it specially this time.
Also, please take care of recapping our previous episode!
Eh?
Right, um, so basically...
Our non-blood related little brother found this strange jar...
Anejiru: The Second
Oh, right! Wasn't the jar called "Nectar of Inana"?
If you touch it, you get cursed or something...
Father sure uncovers the strangest things, doesn't he?
So, to lift such a curse, the... uh, love juice of women was necessary or something...
One time, he played with me with a toy while I was drunkenly sleeping.
For some reason, he was very good at it.
He made me cum while watching I was watching a super lewd dream!
Mine was when we were on the bus. He did some molestation role-play.
He was completely different, and he was aggressive compared to normally.
Just because of that, I became very wet!
N-No! This is embarrassing!
Oh no-! I'm getting wet!
Oh look, something is dribbling out of the tip of your-
When Yuu did it to me, it was my first time, and he was taking my juices!
No, this is too much. I can't stop moving!
It's fine, so cum again! Let out the juices that have been building up, okay?
Even Yuu was very hard that time.
Geez, we got all sticky from each other.
No, I'm going to cum today as well!
Even though Yuu said that he had to keep the whole thing a secret to prevent the curse,
don't you think that he wasn't telling the truth?
You think so, too?
If he was open about it, I could have done a lot more!
Exactly! I would have given him all the love juice he wanted!
N-No! That's not what I'm talking about!
Oh? But you said that you were highly aroused by Yuu-chan being so aggressive!
W-well, that's true...
Also, that jar does some funny things when love juice is collected...
During my time with him, his penis became as big as a plastic bottle!
Although I had sex with him...
No! My hips are automatically moving!
I thought that he would break me down there
Please cum wherever you want!
When it was my turn, Yuu-kun said that he didn't have any experience,
so I gave him a tutorial in the bath.
Likewise, we ended up having sex.
Let's cum together!
Because he was so cute, I felt like I wanted to do anything for him!
Let it all out!
Moreover, it is Yuu's fault!
Although he could have just collected the juice from one of us,
he chose to mix it all up!
Anzu, you sure are a lewd girl!
But didn't we end up enjoying those activities?
Geez, Onee-chan!
That's right!
If we came all at once, things usually reverted back to how they were normally.
This made it particularly exciting, somewhat!
That's amazing!
So much is coming out!
I feel something warm inside me...
B-But, even with the curse lifted, we did plenty of other lewd things...
Such as-
That's enough Anzu-chan~! Stop, stop~!
We've got to leave something for the viewers to go back and enjoy!
What?! All that embarrassing stuff we've gone over is going to be viewed again?
So, we'll tell you what happened after the curse was lifted, okay?
We'll help you masturbate, so please stroke yourself freely!
P-Please don't stare at what's going to happen, alright?
-Anejiru-
Hey... What'cha looking at?
Geez, it can't be helped.
You said you were going to sleep naked,
so I came to help you out!
It's fine.
I'll help you with your masturbation tonight,
so hurry up and take out your cock!
I'm going to pretend that this is your cock and stroke it with my breasts,
so you should imagine that I'm doing it to you!
My breasts are...
warm, large, and slippery!
C'mon, look here! See your cock being stroked by my breasts?
How is it? Are you getting hard?
When I'm doing this, I start to feel good too.
Can you see? My nipples are getting hard!
I'll rub it with these too, okay?
How is it? Doesn't the stiffness feel good?
I feel my breasts and nipples getting hotter from your cock!
Look all you want, look at your lewd sister!
Let's both get aroused, okay?
If I do this, it'll feel like lotion, and it'll feel better!
Can you hear this squishy lewd sound?
I wonder if you've got pre-cum coming out?
To tell you the truth, I'm getting very wet down there as well!
So much so that I can feel the juices flowing out.
If you feel like cumming, do it when you want, okay?
Please dirty my face and tits with your semen!
Whoa! You sure released a lot...
You wanna keep going? I'm sure you want to release more!
I'll help you, okay?
The smell of your semen...
It excites me as well!
See? I'm all slimy from your semen.
Please keep stroking yourself! I'll show you all of my embarrassing parts!
Please cover me more with your semen!
Are you about to cum? Isn't your cock pulsing and quivering?
I'll watch you cum... I'll watch all of it when you cum!
Stroke it harder, stroke it more!
Stroke it, stroke it! Stroke it more!
I can't hold back anymore!
Please, let out your semen! Cover me with your semen!
Well? About to cum? Please, let it out!
Let it out, let it out, let it out, let it out!
Oh, you covered me again...
Even though you've already cum once, it's still so thick and hot...
Hey, I can't hold back any longer...
This time, let me cum with you, okay?
C'mon, watch me,
I'm putting it in.
I'm putting your cock inside me, okay?
It fit right in! Since I was so wet, it went in all the way!
Can you imagine it? Can you imagine your cock messing with my insides?
No! My hips are moving on their own!
Oh no, my mind is swimming!
I'll show you all my embarrassing places, okay?
My clitoris is hard from this sensation...
Even my asshole is quivering from the stimulation!
I-I'll tighten around your cock even more!
So please, please feel better from it!
Hey! Are you stroking yourself properly?
I won't forgive you if you don't feel good after all of my work!
Knowing you're looking at me, my body feels hotter and my head is getting full of sexual thoughts!
My breasts and my pussy both feel good from you looking at me.
I'm sorry, even though I said that I'd help you with your masturbation,
I-I'm feeling good before you are-!
N-No! I'm going to cum, I'm about to cum!
My pussy is making lewd noises from the juices!
My pussy feels tingly...
Please, keep watching me...
I'm really embarrassed, however I don't mind you seeing me cum.
P-please, let's cum together from watching my embarrassing bits!
I'm about to cum! it's coming, something is coming!
I’m about to cum like crazy! My pussy might be ruined!
Watch me, watch me!
Watch me watch me, watch me!
I came...
It felt so good.
I wonder if you came too.
If you want to release your load again, come to me, okay?
Next time, I'll do much more extreme things!
So lets both feel good again, alright?
-Anejiru-
Wha-!
What is this?!
N-No way, a penis...
Why is it today that such a thing is attached?
H-Huh? This penis looks somewhat familiar...
Yuu?
I-Is this Yuu's penis, perhaps?
D-Don't tell me that this is due to that magical jar!
Geez, cut me some slack!
Why is it today that I have to deal with this?
A-Anyway, why is it so big?
I-It's not like I'm aroused or anything...
W-What is this? I-It feels like I've been electrocuted-!
O-Oh no! This actually feels kinda good...
I-I can't stop myself-!
This b-bit at the top, it feels good when I rub over it...
Is this how boys masturbate?
N-No! I can't do it... I'll become a pervert!
Oh? You're doing something fun!
I totally didn't know that you had  kind of fetish.
N-No! You've got it wrong, this is...
This is, some kind of curse from that jar, and-
Yes, yes. I get the picture,
Since that penis looks like Yuu-kun's,
it's got to be that jar again, doesn't it?
O-Onee-chan?
Well, if that's the cause,
to turn it back to normal, we'll have to relieve it, right?
N-No~! Don't stroke it like that!
Oh? Even though you were doing it yourself before?
N-No! Your fingers, it feels too good!
No! I think I'll start feeling funny!
Your voice is too cute!
If you make such a cute voice, it will make me really want to be aggressive!
Hmm? So the other thing is still there.
Is it as if the clitoris has gotten bigger?
Onee-chan! Please don't stare at it, it's embarrassing!
Oh, you've gotten so hard and towering!
I know you want me to play with it.
No! Please don't lick it!
It's starting to feel strange-!
Amazing... I didn't know that fellatio felt so good for boys!
I'm a bit jealous Anzu, this feeling is something rare for a girl to experience.
N-No! It's being sucked!
Onee-chan! Please don't lic-!
P-Please forgive me! Please don't lick my penis!
D-Don't do it so aggressively, otherwise I'll start to feel good!
Anzu, don't just let yourself feel good, please lick me down there as well!
Huh?
Onee-chan's pussy, it's overflowing...
T-That's it, Anzu. Lick my pussy and make me feel good, too!
Today is so extreme.
While I'm licking her over here, she's sucking me down there!
T-This pose, it's embarrassing!
Huh? W-What?!
S-Something deep inside my penis feels strange,
It feels like something is coming!
No, Onee-chan! If you do that there as well, I'll-!
No!
D-Don't play with my pussy!
M-My body is about to go funny!
You're about to cum?
That's okay, show me how you cum, Anzu!
N-No! I don't want to cum...
My penis is quivering-!
C'mon, don't hold back, let it all out.
Cover me with your semen!
It's coming, something is coming, it's going to come out!
Onee-chan~!
Noo~!!
Impressive, Anzu!
Did you cum with your pussy as well?
I-I can feel something hot coming out of my penis...
Is this what ejaculation feels like?
Looks like you're still large here.
Okay, I'm going to take your virginity!
It's going in!
It's going into Onee-chan!
M-My penis is going into her...
See? With this position, we can watch where we're connected.
D-Don't say that! Please don't watch something so embarrassing!
How is it, Anzu? Does my pussy feel good?
Is it exciting to feel your dick going into my pussy?
This is amazing, Onee-chan feels so warm and squishy and is tightening around me!
It sure feels a little strange for you to comment on how my pussy feels.
Onee-chan! Please don't move so much!
I just came before, so I'm really sensitive at the moment!
That's good, feel better and better!
Show me your face as it gets more lewd!
No! I said no!
No! it's rubbing against- I'm getting aroused by my older sister!
Oh? Isn't it the opposite? Your penis is arousing my pussy!
So good, it feels so good!
I'll cum again if I keep going!
You say that, but you've been shaking your hips too!
I-I'm sorry Onee-chan, this feels too good!
Wait?! Anzu!
I can't stop myself!
This feels too great! If you keep going, you're going to make me cum too!
I-I'm gonna cum, I'm about to cum again!
Onee-chan, please, let's cum together!
Your penis, it's hot! It's hitting me in my deepest spot!
No! I can't hold back any longer! I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum inside you!
I'm going to cum inside your pussy!!
Huh? Onee-chan?
I wonder if she went back to her room...
What?! Yu-Yuu?!
Oh, I guess he turned back into his normal self.
I'm glad.
If that was still stuck on me,
I wouldn't be able to have sex with you, would I?