Hey, why are you crying?
Well you see, since I moved, I lost all my friends.
How about me being your friend then?
Really?
I'm Kazuki.
And that girl is?
That's my sister Rinka.
Otome-nee, pass it! pass it! ...Here I go.
It's quite big.
Now you've done it!
Commencing counterattack!
There!
Congratulations, Otome-nee.
Yea, thanks.
And just like that you became a high school girl.
Yea but it makes me nervous somehow.
Hey, Kazu-nii don't peek at us. That's creepy. Come over here.
Rinka, you're pulling too much. That's dangerous.
But you're so slow.
How about searching for a place to sit down?
What? You didn't come up with anything?
Yea..
It somehow doesn't ring a bell when thinking about what I'd like to do.
You can't set a direction without a goal, they say.
I know that much, but...
...one year will pass in no time.
But you know...
...there was this time when we wanted to know who Kazuki would marry.
Eh?
He instantly chose Otome-nee back then.
S-Stupid. Of course I would. You're my sister, you see?
I wonder why you became so indecisive...
I wonder how you can remember this old story.
What? You also remember that one.
U...Um...
If you're fine with that...
...let's go to the same school.
You know...
...you get anxious when left alone.
And there goes the first love's premonition.
Rinka!
Rinka-chan!
Oh, so scary!
Man...
But...yeah.
It's true that I want to stay with you forever.
What?!
No, I mean...
...how should I put this...
Since a long time...
...I've had-
My words stopped at that moment.
But people who believe themselves to be the center of the universe...
...are actually just going with the flow without stopping even once.
W
Part One   Rondo of Purity
Kazu-nii, wake up.
Rinka...
Don't. If you mumble so much...
...it entered...
Hey you two, how long are you-
...you nose is a litte bit...
No!
Jeez...
You're fucking around too much this morning.
What? I'm the victim here!
Aw sorry about that.
But...suffocating by his sisters panties. Kazuki's the real thing.
Oh come on...
Oh, Kazu-nii. Your necktie is loose.
Huh?
Oh.
You're gonna look like a slob.
T-Thanks.
Hold still, okay?
Wow, her breasts are about to touch me.
Speaking of which, her breasts are really amazing.
Eh?
Oh no, Kazuki, what are you looking at?
What? You got to be kidding me...
It's gotten hot here, you two.
Already newly-weds mood?
Wha-?
I-It's not!
I mean he looked slobby, so-
Otome-nee, my collar is tightening-
Stuck like glue, you two.
I got it, I got it...I was wrong.
Okay then. Let's keep going or we'll be late for school.
Mkay'
But at this rate I might end up going out with her...
...and then...
Kazuki, I'm all right, so...
...come.
If it comes true...
...that Kazuki wants me...
...I'll probably end up giving everything to him.
Okay, I'll put it in.
Yeah... Okay.
Slowly, okay?
W-Wow...Otome, you're amazing!
Hey, we'll be late for real.
See you later.
Bye bye.
They could have told me they were taking the lead home.
Huh?
Didn't Otome-nee go back before me?
What? Who's that old man?
Wha-
Touching her breasts?
Otome-nee!
Hold on. Where to?
Wait up, Otome-nee!
Kazu-nii!
Did I scare you?
Rinka... That aside, over there Otome-nee is...
Otome-nee?
She's not there.
What?
It could've been my imagination.
If I had realized the truth at that time...
...it probably wouldn't have ended like this.
Oh, mail for me.
"DVD inside"?
DVD says, "To Kazuki-sama"
It's porn!
I must say high school girls are tempting.
How do you like this sold body?
It's as if you'd be born to this world to have sex.
That's not true.
Now spread your legs and lift up your skirt.
What? Oh no...
Hey, do you understand the situation you're in?
Y-Yes...
What's with that girl? She's got an amazingly sexy body.
A-About the promise...
Oh don't worry about that. You can leave everything to me.
I knew it all along, but your breast size still impresses me.
Soft! Wow, they're so soft!
No...hurts...
It's awesome.
Down here too.
No!
What the-
Otome-nee!
W-What are you-
Well then, Otome-chan.
Oh no, what are you doing?
Let's have lots of fun tonight!
U-Um...you said you were "just going to watch"...
I'm sorry, Otome-chan.
There's no way we can hold back here.
I'll take off your panties in the meantime.
That was delicious.
Well then, it's time.
Time for the main event.
What? What do you mean, main event?
Isn't that obvious?
We've been withholding ourselves from masturbating for a week just for this day.
Everybody wants you so bad...we can't change it.
All right, I'll take good care of you.
I'll let you cum in no time.
Here, here.
Yea! Cum...cum more!
She's cumming, she's cumming!
Now fucking you will feel the best.
Looks so tasty.
Please!
Heave-ho~
I want to have my first time with someone I love!
Comfortable at last.
So please, everything but that!
Well then, here we go-
H-Hurts...no way...what's that?
No way...no...you've got to be kidding me.
Well, so much for your virginity, Otome-chan.
Now, I'll get going.
Come on.
Is this supposed to be my first experience?
Your breasts bounce too much, Otome-chan...
You're the best, Otome-chan.
What's up with this guy?
He's desperately trying to make me feel good.
I wanna cum already!
Idiot! Switch...switch!
Otome-chan...Otome-chan!
I can't believe how elastic your tits are. Just how fucking sexy are you?
If they use me like this over and over again...
...my body will be split in half.
What are you-
But, my, fucking you... makes me feel like a kid again.
My cock's in ecstasy.
I know what you mean. It's as if you can't bear the urge to cum inside.
But she's so cute. So I guess that figures.
Oh god, you're creating slippery pussy juice inside. This feels too good.
Aw shit. Already switch?
I'll be the last one, Otome-chan. You'll take everything of me, right?
The first ejaculation will cost 300.000 Yen.
Note: 300.000 Yen is about $3.765
Shut up. I'll pay no matter the price.
Oh no, he's sticking it in right below my womb.
I'll die if this keeps going.
Here I come. Otome-chans first cum!
It's here, right? Your important room is here, right?
No, don't cum!
No, don't do it there!
I'm cumming!!
Hot...inside me...
My cum is saying that it wants to meet your egg cell.
Idiot...I said don't....idiot...
I'm pouring more and more into you.
Wait until I put every last drop into you.
Let there be life!
This is a dream.
I need to open my eyes...
...and go wake up Kazuki.
I'm next.
No, stop it!
Kazuki!
Wake up. You'll be late!
Oh you're already up.
Hurry up and wash your face. You look horrible.
The DVDs were delivered on a weekly basis.
Oh, you look good in that.
This is my daughter's...
...but it fits perfectly.
Today we'll be going by family setting, Otome-chan.
Wh-What are you saying?
We'll start with suck exercise with dad.
What? No, impossible.
Giving up before the challenge even begins...
...I don't remember my daughter learning this.
You see? Your mouth even feels so good, dad's gonna cum straight away.
I'll let you drink plenty of dad's milk.
Well then, brother is gonna drink Otome-chans milk then...
...well there is none, yet.
But don't worry.
Brother will fill you up with semen so you will be able to give milk.
Here it comes. Dads milk...here it comes.
Otome!
What's this? So bitter!
Ok, next is your lower mouth.
Come on, Otome, call me papa.
Papa...papa...
...you shouldn't do this to your daughter. It's forbidden.
No, that's wrong. There's still a wall between us.
We must become one completely.
Papa...
Oh no, this guys penis isn't normal.
It's searching for a way to make me pregnant.
...at this rate...
You're getting off? Dad's happy!
Wha- No...I'm not getting off or something.
Making lies. You're a bad girl, Otome-chan.
Such a bad girl needs punishment.
Don't...it's coming...it's coming...
His penis is coming inside my womb.
I can feel by his pulse. It's about to ejaculate!
There's so much coming inside.
No...
Her shirt says "Otome"
That was awesome, Otome-chan.
All right. Next up will be school swimsuit play with your brother.
Here.
Here!
Here!!
Brother's not gonna lose to dad and will cum inside, too, Otome!
But being able to see your tits when you got your back turned to me...
...just how fucking sexy is your body?
Brother's so happy to have such a stupid father who gives you away and lets me stick it in.
What's with that look? Are you mad?
That's nice!
Brother loves to cum inside of such a revolting little sister.
Well then, here I come.
I'll cum straight into your baby room.
C-Come on...you'll say it, right?
You've been bullied again, right?
It's okay. Just spray everything into your big sister.
Otome-nee!
You're the only one who understands me!
Oh no, what's with this guy's thing?
It's too long. It reaches into my womb.
Nee-chan, you're amazing.
It's as if there was another pussy deep inside your pussy.
Don't say it. Don't say such a thing to your big sister.
But I know. I know that there will be new life if I spray my white stuff inside you.
That's right. That's why you absolutely must not do this!
Bear my child, Nee-chan, bear it!
No, I don't wwant it! I don't want to make a new life!
I...
Well then. Shall we go all together for the end?
Please...let me rest a bit...
At least one after another.
No no, we have to use every hole there is.
Front and ass too...I don't want this...
I'm about to...
Me too!
But you really are something, Otome-chan...
...pleasing us three all together. The three of us are so proud of you.
No!
Why, Otome-chan?
Cumming!
Here it comes!
You're so sexy when you're feeling it!
I'm feeling it...I'm feeling it.
Actually I came countless times. So please let me go.
So cute, Otome. This will be the last one!
There is the pulse...
...although there no space for more...
...although I'm so full...
Oh no, I'm cumming...my mind's going blank...
...no...I'm cumming...
...cumming...cumming...
I'm cumming!!
I'm home.
W-Welcome home, Kazuki.
It's been a while, right?
Rin-chan asked me to do her a favor...
... I'm going to cook something now. So if you have anything you want to eat-