It all happened on this night,
It started from something lewd and cruel.
Come on, open your legs wider!
No!
According to the contract, you will be reawakened!
Amazing, it's totally swallowing me.
It hurts!
There's so much juice it's sopping wet.
No! No!
No! Don't cum inside!
W
~ Awakening ~
Today's worship will take place in the auditorium,
due to unforeseen circumstances.
"Circumstances"?
What does this mean?
Having an investigation from the police is, well...
How shall I put it... we can't overlook it at this rate.
But... still... there have been... strange rumors.
Our lord's company will lose face.
We could request the special staff to investigate...
How would that be, Mr. Chairman?
Special staff?
The Ministry of Education, Culture, Sports, Science and Technology-
-has an expert at this kind of crime under their direct control .
However, requesting someone from the outside to do an investigation is definitely different.
Yes, sir.
What is it? You seem in a hurry today.
Did something happen?
Is that what’s messing with your libido?
Never mind that.
Now, Hikaru, I'm going to make sure you enjoy it plenty today.
Come now, you're already this wet.
No!
It's so pretty, Hikaru-chan.
Truly pretty, a naughty p*ssy.
It feels good!
Just as you were told, you didn't take a shower after P.E.
Good girl.
You're such a pervert.
You like it that way.
This hole, too.
No! It's embarrassing!
Don't open it so wide!
Don't!
It feels so good!
Delicious.
You're getting better... have you been studying somewhere?
Hey, Hikaru?
What are you saying?
You're the only one for me oji-sama.
I'll believe you.
Ah, looks like I'm about to cum.
Make me cum with your mouth. You haven't done that in a while.
Rest at ease. Today, I think I can cum two more times.
Okay.
It's coming out!
This time, make me come.
Here I go!
Amazing! The inside of my body is so hot, it feels so good!
Oh, really? Me, too.
I can feel your long thing deep inside me, all hard.
At this rate, the inside of my body will go numb!
Yes!
No more! I'll die!
Okay, then, I'm going to cum.
Come!
Hey oji-sama, what sort of incident happened?
Something at school?
No, it has nothing to do with you guys.
Nothing but lies. I always know immediately when you're lying.
Your ears move.
See?
Hey, tell me, what happened?
I guess I have to. Don't tell anyone, okay?
This is still classified information for the faculty members.
I know.
Ooh, scary! The culprit was a cat-burgler, then.
It's not a prank?
The circle in the chapel?
That's some kind of magic circle.
And it's important to note that it was a virgin's fluids mixed with the blood,
but not necessarily ones from a human.
Amazing, you know so much!
Did you possibly do it?
Bzzt! Unfortunately, no.
I was hanging out with Ishihara until this morning,
so I wouldn't have had that kind of free time.
Well, whichever it was, the school doesn't want to go public,
so it'll look into the circumstances for now.
Having this kind of thing happen so close makes me shudder.
Tell us as soon as you have new information, okay?
Sure! In exchange, absolutely do not pass this on to anyone else!
We get it!
What's going on, you guys? Looks like an interesting conversation.
Tell us, too!
I guess it can't be helped.
This stays among us, okay?
Mutsuki... Jouji-san, right?
Did you want something?
No, I didn't exactly want something...
Just that your name keeps appearing right before mine on the books I check out.
I read lots of strange books, books that people wouldn't read.
I didn't know that there was anyone else in our school with the same interests.
I have this mysterious feeling...
I read indiscriminately, and there's only one copy of those books.
It's nothing particularly mysterious.
Sorry. I'm in a hurry.
And I worked so hard to build up the courage to speak to him...
My name is Shion.
I'm the only child of a family with a thousand-year history of greatness.
Naturally I was raised lovingly and very sheltered.
Until now, I never had a friend with whom I could share my vulnerable heart.
My best friends were books.
Through those books...
I found the first person who might be able to be my friend.
Hey, you'll do me tonight, right?
Not tonight.
No! But I can't bear it!
If you can't do tonight, then do me right now!
It's stood up, all healthy! Hurry up, hurry up, put it in me.
You have a sinful body.
Yes, I'm such a horny girl.
I can't hold it any longer, put it in quickly!
Yes, yes, more, more, rougher! Amazing!
More of your penis, please?
Who is the culprit? However, what happened that night...
And how is the girl doing now?
Let's go back two weeks to the start of it all.
What’s this?
He had found a magic book with ceremonies written in it,
the doing of which would the students into sex slaves.
However, he would not be satisfied with making a slave of only one student.
Excuse me!
Who're you?
This is on school grounds, in the sacred place of the chapel.
An appropriate place to undertake a ceremony.
Though killing you as a sacrifice would be the best use of you,
I don't think I'll go that far.
So listen quietly to what I have to say.
Understood?
O spirit I desire, I call upon your powers of eternal malice, and summon thee.
And I grant this request unto thee: give me your power!
Release these powers by thine own power.
And be touched by the spiritual energy from me to be awakened!
Yes, that's good.
Raise your spiritual energy with me.
According to the magical power, tonight you become my slave.
From here on, you live for my sake.
Until you die, you'll do as I wish.
Yes.
Wonderful. This desire is the best!
More... rougher, please!
Make me your crazy sex slave with your magic dick!
Good.
My body is burning up!
And now, you will take my sperm inside your body.
I assume you will be grateful!
Thank you very much!
Shoot plenty inside me!
The next stage follows immediately.
Not there!
It's going in!
O spirit, I summon thee!
Grant me the skills with which to wield my true power
Send me your divine wisdom!
No! My insides... hurt!
It's coming out!
It can't be helped...
Let's start the Special Interest Investigation.