Are you doing well, Mikio-san?
I've gotten used to the hostess training I've been in since graduation.
Now I've earned the nickname of young hostess.
Anyway, college has a summer break, right?
I wonder when you can consider coming back.
It's been... half a year, hasn't it?
When you're on break, please contact me, okay?
And also, I want to properly thank you for the ring.
Yours, Chitose.
Can I really... have this?
I'll hold it precious, it will forever be my treasure.
He's the worst, the very worst!
Just as I imagined him.
Mao?
If it isn't Mao! Long time no see!
Welcome! Thank you for coming all the way from Enpo.
Please make yourself comfortable.
Welcome!
Geez, I haven't prepared anything since I thought you'd call first.
I don't know if I can take any time off either, since it's busy this time of year.
Eh?!
It's someone’s fault for coming out of the blue!
I have yet to thank you for this as well...
Um, eh, forgive me for coming here so suddenly!
I'm not a kid anymore!
I am the hostess of this place now!
You sure look like the young hostess I heard about.
Chi-
Chi-chan is forbidden!
You're late!
I said I'd just pop in quickly!
Didn't I say that if I didn't hurry back that gramps would be waiting to have dinner?
Were you even listening?
Sheesh! You think it's okay to leave a lady waiting!
You.. have grown properly, haven't you?
What?!
How lewd! You pervert!
Geez! Take some responsibility!
Even if we're cousins, we can still get married...
Chi-chan...
Oh, that?
Apparently some people affiliated with the hostel made it.
It looks too indecent, I don't approve of it!
Young hostess?
She should be back in her room at the outhouse.
The outhouse isn't that way.
If you're out sneaking around at night, why don't you check it out?
Move! I'm going to take a bath.
Do you even know what that means?
If you join me, you might find something out.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Mikio-san?
Huh?
Is this guy your boyfriend?
T-This person is here because of that modeling appointment...
Isn't that right?
Excuse us, the cameraman and the model have some things to discuss.
Take this instead of my card.
Let's go, Chi-chan.
Y-Yes.
The freshly graduated schoolgirl,
in amongst the hard work of running an hostel.
This is Chitose-chan, the hostess.
With her in a beautiful swimsuit,
she gladly answers the hopes of the cameraman by brazenly expressing her body.
Her gradual exposure is the best!
What the hell is this article?!
Don't you need to chase after him and make excuses?
Mikio-san... is different... to the likes of you...
If I talk to him properly,
I'm sure he'll understand.
Even though he sucks at kissing.
You shouldn't peep on people! It's indecent!
Even though you looked displeased.
W-What are you say-
Isn't my kiss better than your boyfriend's?
K-Kissing doesn't determine a mans value!
Noo~!
Oh? Didn't you say that I was better?
Yesterday, and just before.
You're getting better at using your tongue.
It's because you come on too strong, I ended up learning it too!
Ah! N-No!
Oh? Aren't you a lewd girl?
Even though you're a virgin, you like having your ass played with?
Also, what a vulgar expression.
If your boyfriend saw you, I bet he'd be shocked!
I-It's because I'm sensitive! This is unfair!
Even though you're an unfair woman.
No, my voice is-!
Noo!
No, stop!
No-
We can do it, right?
It's been a while since we've been dating.
W-We haven't be dating!
No!
Please stop-!
What are you talking about?
Every night, isn't what you're doing something an unfaithful wife would do?
Wife?
N-No, that isn't true!
Hey, no!
My hips, hug my hips with your legs.
Noo~!
Looks like you've finally graduated, Chi-chan.
Your hard penis is entering me!
The tip is so deep-!
Noo~! I'm going to start feeling funny!
An unfaithful... wife.
No! Y-You can't!
Please don't move!
If you move, I'll really lose it!
You're the same as you were in front of the camera,
go ahead and throw away your shame!
I-I'm not throwing away my shame!
Like when you exposed your breast in my car.
That was because you took my swimsuit off.
You even went for a piss.
That's because you were spying!
And also, your pussy has been sucking me in.
Huh? N-No more!
Don't make me into a shameless woman!
A woman who doesn't admit her shame, how wonderful!
That reminds me, there was another one...
Stop doing indecent things toward the young hostess at Kinpouro!
-Is what she said.
No no!
Noo~!
That brat, I sure wanna peel her and expose her squishy parts!
No more! Someone will see us!
Then we're going somewhere we can be alone, isn't there a suitable place?
T-Then, in my room...
Okay, then I'll play with you as a stay over!
No, no stay overs!
Mikio-san is here, too!
Since this is your first night, you've got to remember the taste of a cock.
No-!
No! Please stop making me experience such lewd things!
No! Please forgive me, I'm going to feel strange when Mikio-san is here!
Don't you like doing indecent things?
No, I don't-!
That's right! Does your pussy not feel good?
No, it doesn't-!
Then we're gonna do it until you do!
No no! Forgive me! I have Mikio-san!
Even so, I'm... I'm... I'm going to cum!
No!
I'm gonna cum!!
Noo! I'm cumming~!!
Onii-chan should notice soon enough.
I hate you Mao, you sinful woman.