www.SubDESU-H.net
Ryuuto Henge, eh?
What a troublesome man!
That he was promoted by that military scum...
What a shameful mark this leaves on the Knight Academy!
I will give him a task he cannot handle,
thus causing him to fail miserably...
This will get him out of the way.
Choose well.
Will you name your director?
Or will you die in silence?
You have failed me as a son.
However, I cannot make this information public.
If I do, the rebel forces will be emboldened and they will gain support.
It's a bit too late to return the nobility to center stage.
So it is vital that you complete your knightly training.
By the way, I owe you a reward.
I would like to assign you to the covert forces.
Would it not be better if he were to be discovered by Byusten Harter?
I don’t suppose you’re asking me something so absurd as to promote him to general to subdue the rebel forces?
Is there a problem with that?
Even for the current general, it was impossible!
And you dare suggest I entrust the task to someone with no experience?
Naturally, I will appoint a skilled general to command the forces.
If a graduate of the Knight Academy is able to subdue Gladys - someone who has never been defeated before -
it will be good publicity for the Knight Academy.
Um... I will accept this task... on one condition.
Return this letter to Wang Quan.
Aye.
And also, I want you to join him as his guard.
As you command... my lord.
He jumped into the trap all by himself.
Ryuuto Henge is a fool.
Become a prisoner of war and die for all I care.
While I'm still alive, I must force the Knight Academy to make a grievous error.
So who will the new general be?
Depending on who he is, I might return to Oto.
I’m not such a fool that I would put up with a fool.
Speaking of fools, I heard there was a huge fool who graduated from the Knight Academy this year.
Don’t make me remember...
Ryuuto Henge, eh?
Wang Coin! Is he not here yet?
General Ferzen, it’s Wang Quan.
I believe he’ll be arriving shor-
I-It’s you?!
May I present our new general, Ryuuto Henge.
Wang Coin! Surely you jest!
It’s Wang Quan.
This decision was made by the King himself.
By the King?! Is he a fool?
I’m leaving!
He thinks I’m going to sit back and take this insult?
I am no dog!
General Zanto... and General Shirab, not you too!
Ryuuto... You’re a popular guy.
“Hurry and make the new general disappear”.
When a plain-faced nobody becomes general, it’s unavoidable.
Ryuuto, your dick, it’s the best!
I’m gonna rub it harder.
Won’t you touch my tits?
My tits... feel so good.
Ryuuto, squeeze them harder!
Ryuuto, your dick is amazing!
My tits feel great.
I’m cumming... cumming... cumming!
Wow... Ryuuto, you’re amazing.
Shamsiel...
I came... again.
Me too. I came lots.
Graduated at the bottom of his class?
I hear his low grades in every subject broke records.
I take this as a personal insult, then.
They think that Gladys is so insignificant that a fool is more than enough to dispose of her?
What shall we do?
I always accept a challenge.
Here. Ahh.
You summoned me?
What a horrible battlefield.
They were out of explosives, but it’s almost like they were doing a battle test.
Do you think it was an inside job?
They're still out of explosives.
Why doesn’t Gladys invade Oto?
Is it a matter of logistics?
It is not an answer your puny brain can comprehend.
Oh? Here to pay your respects?
I’m here to ask you to resign.
Quit your post as general here and now.
What if I don’t wanna?
I don’t think squabbling amongst ourselves is a good strategy for winning against the rebels.
Perhaps tomorrow I’ll go investigate the situation at Bunderwald.
There are some things I’d like to make certain of.
Your “investigation” would yield nothing.
Draw your sword.
Lemme eat this bread first.
You damn stubborn fool of a man!
I’ll cut you down where you sit!
Urgent news!
The enemy has breached our line!
How many?
Just one.
Of all the luck...
Isis! Come.
The enemy’s invading, I hear.
The demon is about to invade too.
She’s already invaded.
Are you Ryuuto Henge?
Yeah, that’s right.
Wanna eat breakfast with me?
You’re even more a fool than the rumors say.
Why do you think I’ve come here?
To discuss strategies of how to break up the rebel forces.
You think...
I came to discuss strategies...?
You are far too carefree, boy.
Your life is in danger.
Oh, really?
What sort of sense do you have?!
...This sorta sense.
I no longer feel like killing you.
I’ll take care of that later.
Ryuuto, you sure are funny.
Who was that just now?
You didn’t know her?
Shall we go investigate?
So you are the envoy.
You have no weapons?
Only the one between my legs that grows and shrinks.
You vulgar scum.
Enter.
Hey you! It's your turn!
I will listen to your case.
One of your clan has invaded my castle.
So I came to inform you of that.
What?
It’s you...
Long time no see... though I guess we just saw each other.
So you were only acting incompetent?
Well, you fooled me.
You’re a beauty.
Is that another part of your “act”?
Do people often talk about your huge tits?
I can’t tell whether you have any openings or not.
I think every inch of me is open.
What’s your bust measurement?
If you want to know the answer, then defeat me.
I hear you only recently graduated from the Knight Academy.
Do you have any combat training?
I don’t. I was hoping you’d teach me some tricks.
You want me to teach you?
I’m not sure whether you’re stupid or a genius.
Can we speak in private?
Do you hope to take my head now?
I just wanted to make certain of something.
The reason you haven’t invaded Oto during these past two years... it’s because you simply don’t want to, yes?
If you wanted to expand your kingdom, you would have invaded Oto long ago.
I can take Oto whenever I please.
And you commanded the rebel forces because there were too many independent rebel groups roaming freely.
The division was leading to anarchy, and you were trying to prevent that.
So all together, if the disparate forces were united,
it would prevent foreign powers from invading.
You can also nip a sudden violent reform in the bud.
Wouldn’t you like an unconditional surrender?
Do you honestly think I would?
Well, I made a promise to the King, you see.
If I capture you, the death sentences will be lifted.
The rebel soldiers will be forced into labor, but they won’t be sentenced to death.
If I assassinate you, a second and perhaps third “Gladys” will appear,
the rebellion will escalate, and foreign countries will be able to easily take us over.
After all, Prince Bobon has received help from Ringobalt to join forces with Commander Boan to stir up a revolt.
They were piggybacking off your rebellion.
To commend you for your bravery and honesty, I will return you alive.
This ends our chat.
A pleasure to see you again, milady.
You again?
I only hope she surrenders.
Though I guess it’s impossible.
Ryuuto, so you really are a genius.
What are you doing here?
Demons can go to church.
Though the environment makes my tits bigger.
It’s bad to be thinking this in a church...
But I wanna play with them.
You can suck them if you want
Ryuuto, you’re so cute.
My milk...
You’re lactating.
Don’t forget this tit.
Harder!
Drink it!
Ryuuto, you’re so good at sucking.
Even though I’m a demon, you’re turning me on.
My tits are stretching out.
Your tits are tasty.
This feels great!
Shamsiel.
Come to me. I’ll titty fuck you.
Ryuuto, your dick is throbbing already.
My pelvis is going insane.
Move your pelvis.
I’m gonna pee...
It’s okay, pee.
Fuck my tits more.
I’ll help you cum more.
Not that!
Cum! Just cum!
In front of God, I want you to release your seed.
No, Shamsiel.
I’m gonna cum!
Ryuuto, you’ve already gone this far.
So just cum. Just cum!
Cum lots of semen!
Healthy boy!
I came a lot again.
Ryuuto, your dick cums a lot, so I love it!
Single combat?
Yes. There is to be single combat between the general and you.
Did Bernstein order it?
For the general, yes.
Well, isn’t this convenient. The general in question just came to visit me.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
It can’t be!
And so... how do they want us to fight?
I just don’t understand challenging Gladys to single "combat" with chess.
Gladys is not only a sword master, but a chess master as well.
He’s sure to lose.
Only one choice remains.
If she loses, her forces will surrender to us!
And if he loses, the ridiculous general is executed.
And we surrender.
Wang Coin!
I don’t suppose you orchestrated this single combat on purpose?
It’s Wang Quan!
I was merely acting under orders from the crown!
Well, squabbling over it won’t fix anything.
Let’s go to bed early tonight.
You think sleeping will fix anything?!
You're as good as dead!
But not today. Tomorrow, right?
Until the time comes, I’ll kick back and wait.
I’ll need to make sure Wang Quan is punished later, too.
Punished?
You were lying about receiving this order from the crown.
Do you still believe the lie that I infiltrated?
You bumped into a traveler when it happened, didn’t you? That was me.
Did you actually infiltrate?
Isis, take him to the dungeon.
I’ll leave the punishment to the generals.
Hey...
Have him swallow this.
Who’s gonna let him drink some nasty poison?
I’d rather he drink an aphrodisiac and fuck 'til he drops!
Are you seriously going to fight Gladys tomorrow?
You’ll die.
Guess I will.
Haven’t you considered running away?
Not at all.
But you’ve made it all the way to general... Don’t you feel like you’re losing out?
If I die without touching your tits, I’ll feel like I lost out.
You fool.
What a strange smell.
Isis?
Don’t look...
Ahh, I went through the trouble of adding an aphrodisiac and Isis took it instead.
You put in an aphrodisiac?
A super-strong one, too!
Is there an antidote?
If she’s fucked good and hard, it’ll go away.
Ryuuto, why don’t you fuck her?
Me?
I can’t hold back!
Touch me.
Amazing...
I know it’s just the aphrodisiac, but Isis herself wants me.
You fool!
Not there.
I feel her nipples hardening under my fingertips.
You fool.
Not there... not so hard...
Don't...
No...
Not my nipples again...
Don’t pull them too hard.
Not your fingers... fingers...
You’re amazing, Isis.
Not your fingers.
Lick them.
You fool, that’s not what I want.
Suck them.
No...
Not just my tits...
Ryuuto... put it in.
Amazing.
Her tits are shaking.
Not my tits again... Ohh...
Not my nipples.
Don’t tease my boobs.
But you want them teased and you know it.
Don’t go too deep.
My pelvis will melt!
No! Not so deep!
I’m cumming...
No! Not inside!
Not inside...
No...
I’m cumming!
I’m really cumming!
I wonder if the aphrodisiac wore off by now?
Fuck my tits more!
Fuck my tits with your cock!
Isis, your nipples are so nice and hard.
Don’t fuck my nipples!
Not so hard!
Fucking your nipples feels so good.
Ryuuto is fucking my nipples...
I‘ll cum in your boobs.
Don’t cum...
It’s coming.
Don’t cum in my nipples!
I’ll cum... I’m cumming again...
Me too... I’m cumming!
No...
That’s my Ryuuto!
Your life ends tomorrow.
You may have acted cool in front of me earlier,
but I know you won't sleep peacefully tonight.
I commend you for not retreating.
You've heard rumors of me, have you not?
If I win, can I touch your tits?
Are you a fool or a genius?
Choose whichever you prefer.
I wonder why...
My hands are hot.
You’re sweating already?
Your fate is already decided.
I see the gallows right in front of you.
My hands sure are hot...
I wonder if I’m okay?
You’re just fine!
You were reborn as... ah!
Reborn?
General Ferzen, how is Ryuuto doing?
Much better than expected.
Just what about this guy is “bottom of his class”?
He seems like a top student to me.
Could it be... he’s been concealing his true abilities from me this whole time?
Am I actually going to lose?!
I, someone who has not lost a game of chess in five years, will lose?
This guy...
Checkmate.
Each of his moves was exemplary.
Not even I can compete with that.
I lose.
Do as you wish.
However, leave my soldiers alone.
If you want a prisoner, take only me.
It’s a promise.
Ryuuto won!
I’m so impressed.
Yes, indeed...
Hanging me in a dungeon? You have strange fetishes.
Do I really?
You were able to defeat me in chess, but I wonder about the “other thing”.
Wanna test it?
Whichever of us cums first loses - how about that?
You're on.
So big.
How many inches?
I only tell that to men I love.
No man has touched my tits and lived to tell the tale.
Then I’ll die, I guess.
You like it, don’t you?
No I... don’t!
You’re good at chess, but you suck at lying.
You’re releasing some pretty sexy noises right now.
I was only breathing!
Gladys, you’re much more sensitive than I would have expected.
My breasts are not sensitive.
Then... I guess that means I can tweak them as much as I want.
Stop it... not my boobs!
Squeezing them so hard- it’s unsportsmanlike.
Stop it! Not my boobs!
Not my boobs!
See? You came.
I-I didn’t... cum...
What a stubborn girl.
Oh, you’re turned on.
I’m not!
Stop it!
My boobs are stretching out!
No... stop it... Don’t move your tongue.
Don’t move my tongue?
Don’t suck my boobs.
Stop with my boobs...
Stop sucking so hard.
My boobs... my boobs!
Now will you admit that you came?
I didn’t... cum.
Stop it.
Not there...
You’re so wet.
Don’t use your tongue... it’s unsportsmanlike.
If you want it unsportsmanlike, I’ll put in my dick!
N-Not that!
Wow, your boobs are flopping.
No... don’t suck my boobs!
Your pussy is so tight. It feels good.
Stop it. Don’t stimulate both at once!
Because you’ll cum?
Who would... cum from that?
I’m begging you, don’t suck my boobs!
Stop sucking my boobs!
Gladys, you’re so sexy.
You idiot!
I’ll punish you later for this.
Too strong!
You’re like a cannon. You’re making me cum again!
You’re squeezing me tight.
Your semen...
Gladys... you...
Don’t make me say it - you were my first man.
I will no longer oppose you.
I am your woman now.
M-My woman?
Hurry, take the chains off.
Then I can embrace you.
All women wish to embrace the men they love.
Ryuuto sure is popular!
Wh-What?!
He converted Gladys?!
A ceremony.
Prepare for a ceremony at once!
We must also have a parade.
It’s the birth of a new hero!
Aye, sir.
He turned the trap back on those who tried to trap him, and did quite well for himself too.
Damn you, Ryuuto Henge, next time for sure you will be destroyed!
www.SubDESU-H.net
sore wa itsumo totsuzen no koto
Everything always begins suddenly.
ototoi to kinou, kyou, asu ni tsuzuku kaze no ito
The thread of wind connects the day before yesterday, yesterday, today, and tomorrow.
sugu itaku tenohira kasane awase
Place your pained palms together
susunde ku kumo no obi
To see the flowing thread of clouds.
hitoiki de oenuku you ni
As if one breath can blow through it,
mou ni do to tomaranai so crazy
It can no longer be stopped. (so crazy)
sora ga umi ga kibou no sewa ni dasu yo
The sky and the sea will take care of hope.
hoshi no matataki to kodou o awaseru you ni
Just as the sparkling of the stars is synchronized with the heartbeat.
nagareteku hoshi no obi isshun te o nuketa nara
If you can release the thread of falling stars for just an instant,
kitto kaze tsukameru sa
Then you will surely be able to grab hold of the wind.