Misawakun’s…
His use of violence against us teachers…
Gotten more severe.
No...
Stop it.
What are you doing?
No!
Let me go...
Can’t you hear me?
Stop...
Finally you calmed down.
I'll never forgive you for this...
Slapping me...
I’ll never!
Saya...
Even though you say that...
I know you're getting horny.
It hurts...
This… hurts and it's disgusting.
Then, how about this place?
H-Hey...
Don’t touch it...
Hey…
Stop it...
I think...
Its time for you to show me your precious place.
No...
Shut up!
No!
Please...
Stop it...
Stay still!
It's slippery.
I never thought that...
An impudent teacher's pussy would be so cute.
No…
Don’t look at it.
Don’t look at it!
Dirty juices are flowing out from your slippery pussy.
No...
Stop!
Its all wet.
No...
If you show such a cute face...
...I can’t hold it in.
No way...
W
Mesu Kyoushi
Injoku no Kyoushitsu
Part 2
I can’t go back anymore...
Stop...
I’m going to put it in.
It hurts...
No!
It hurts!!
As I thought...
Your slippery pussy...
Is so tight inside.
It hurts...
No no no no...
Don’t move.
It hurts!
No...
No way...
Impossible…
This is impossible...
I don’t know what kind of family you came from but...
You'll be punished for making a fool out of me!
What…
Did I do to you?
I don’t like your…
Eyes looking down on me like that...
No…
No way...
I’m going to break...
Its too deep...
My cervix will rip…
It hurts...
My stomach hurts...
Be happy Saya.
I’m going to.…
Release all of my sperm inside your slippery pussy!
No...
Don't... Don't do that...
Leave it to me.
I’ll release it all inside your cervix.
No...
Forgive me...
Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Please...
Stop it...
No…
You really released it...
Inside...
Eh?
What are you doing?
Just look at it...
I’m going to tell everyone that Saya-sensei is a lecherous princess.
How long are you going to be in that pose?
Another guy might come and rape you again.
Please...
Forgive me already.
This is his way of doing things...
Taking pictures of us...
And blackmailing us.
Saving
Saving.
Saving..
Saving...
The teacher of the only girl appeared.
Thrust out my hips towards the student.
And the carrot has been inserted by us.
The hole is cleared in the hips.
Part of the stockings...
And crossed and moved and inserted it.
Ritsuko-sensei?
Should I continue reading?
S...Sorry.
You can sit down.
Okay.
Uhm...
Okay then.. I’ll put a point up...
Sensei... what’s wrong?
Nothing...
Sorry...
I’ll continue the class.
The 2nd line in the end...
Means “after all”.
The next line is....
Hip.. a straight for…
This time the 4th line… "student"…
What happened to her..?
The sentence that continues...
Sensei!
Sensei! Are you alright?
Sensei?
Sorry...
My stomach hurts...
You need to go to infirmary.
I’m alright.
If I hold on a little bit...
I’ll be fine.
I’m really alright.
Please go back to your seats.
Please...
Even you say that
Sensei, are you alright?
Sensei.
girl basketball club room
Why am I in this costume?
Don’t ask questions and keep going.
How about this?
What are you doing?
You like this right?
It hurts...
Please stop.
Sit down and keep going.
Its embarrassing, so don’t look so much.
Shut up and suck it.
You’re perverted teacher.
No I’m not...
It's all wet...
You perverted teacher.
Use your boobs too.
It seems like you’re turned on.
Stop...
Please.
Stop it.
It will break...
You perverted teacher.
You like it right?
I know you do.
No I’m not...
The milk is flowing because you're feeling
Hey don’t forget your service.
It's my first time being this hot.
I’m cumming...
I can’t hold it...
I’m cumming too!
Drink it properly.
He’s going to release his hot and stinky sperm.
He’s going to release it.
Its pumping...
Hot sperm...
Cum!
Release it!
I want...
I want the sperm!
Let me drink your hot and stinky sperm!
It's so thick.
Are you satisfied?
Yes…
Me too.
He's going to rape me...
You’re early.
I think that uniform makes you look like a student.
Stand up.
You’re ready, right?
It's embarrassing, so don’t look so much.
I need to teach my cute slave again today.
Miyuki-sensei.
No...
Stop...
Oh you’re already feeling it?
No, I’m not...
Hmmm?
You’re still saying that you're not feeling it?
Don’t touch there!
It's embarrassing...
Let me go.
Your top and lower body is already wet.
Miyuki-sensei.
I’m filming it properly so...
Don’t worry.
Please...
I'll listen to what you say so please don’t film this.
Shut up!
Suck this...
No...
You’re leaking.
My boobs… my boobs...
This is a good movie recording.
Please…
Stop this cruel thing.
Hmm, lets see...
If you can satisfy my dick.
Maybe then, I’ll forgive you.
No way...
No!
I can’t hold that big thing.
I can’t…
Stop it...
It doesn't sound like you hate it.
No way…
No...
It hurts…
It's rubbing.
It's so intense...
Are you going to release it inside again?
My boobs...
My boobs!
It's coming out...
It's coming!
I’ll take another picture.
No… I’m cumming...
I’m cumming!
Hey! Why did the slave cum first?
What are you going to do about this?
Slave…
I’ll record the internal cumshot properly.
No…
I’ll get pregnant from that.
I don’t care about that.
No...
Don’t release it inside!
If you have problem with that...
I’ll release it until you get pregnant.
No you can’t!
Stop!
No!
No no no!
I’m cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My stomach...
My stomach is so hot inside...
It's coming inside...
It's coming a lot...
I want it...
I want the...
Hot thing...
We get raped like this and...
I noticed that my body's going numb.
I'm... no, we're...
Our hearts and body's... turning into dirty whore sluts.