www.SubDESU-H.net
Eight a.m.
I force Ippei out of bed.
Sit down to a prepared breakfast.
The one I woke is engrossed in watching TV.
I spent the whole night thinking it over.
Thinking what over?
About Sakura-chan.
About whether or not I'd rape Kujou Sakura.
Most people would never  get a chance to fuck an idol.
...Are you listening?
Yes. I require more toast.
Hey, listen  when I'm talking to you!
You want to rape her. Correct?
Good for you.
Yea...
I require more toast.
Oh, you...
Um,
Sari-sama?
What is it?
I intend to carry it out today.
Is that so? Good. Go get 'er.
Aren't you gonna help me?
Don't make me coddle you, idiot.
I know the sort of perverse actions you intend to take.
And I don't wish to assist you.
She refused me right when I needed her the most...
Well fine, then.
I'll go out there myself.
Wait.
I'd forgotten to inform you of something vital.
Yes?
I need a food stipend.
Take care of that yourself.
Would you rather I make a phone call and inform someone of my imprisonment?
When pushed against a wall by those words,
Ippei had only one choice.
She arrived on schedule.
Good evening.
Ippei's prey - the girl-next-door idol - Kujou Sakura.
Welcome!
Today I will rape her!
I came to return the DVD I rented yesterday.
Okay, I'll just need to enter that in the log.
What do you do on your days off?
I often spend the days watching DVDs and movies I've recorded.
Didn't expect that.
I'm a bit of a shut-in. I don't really have many friends.
Is that so?
Then does that mean... she's a virgin?
No, that's too good to be true.
Well, I'll be back soon.
Wait, I can't let her escape.
Um!
Yes?
Are you free later today?
Well, I just thought maybe we could grab some dinner.
Ah! I went over the line, didn't I?
Sakura-chan, you're just so easy to talk to - I forgot that we're not even friends!
Sounds good.
Eh?
I haven't eaten dinner yet.
So let's go have some dinner together.
Really?
Yes.
It's a dream come true.
I'm gonna have dinner with Sakura-chan!
Well, shall I wait somewhere for you until you're off work?
Nah, I'll close up shop early - don't worry!
But...
It'll just take five minutes!
Please wait just a moment.
You don't need to hurry so.
I'll finish right up!
Ippei feels validated when a pop idol...
...accepts the invitation of a boy she barely met.
He is certain that she wants to be raped.
I'll finish  right up!
Sorry to drag you out so late.
But, to get an idol drunk at his hour...
Well, I guess it's time to go home.
It's time, eh?
Okay, I'll walk you home.
I'll be fin-
Watch out!
H-huh?
You can't let her go home alone.
Her home is your hunting ground, Ippei.
Walk her home,
then invent some excuse to go up to her room with her.
And then...
Please, won't you let me walk you home?
I see your point... Okay, please walk me home.
Thanks.
W
Please Rape Me!
Original Animation Video
~Kujou Sakura says, "Please *beep* my *beep* with your *beep*!~
On the path in a dark park,
Ippei walks a weak and vulnerable idol home.
Do you want to have a little rest?
Over there...
Sure.
Do you feel a bit better?
Y-yes.
Thanks.
Uh, um...
I would like to try something.
Will you promise not to laugh if I tell you?
Sure. What is it you want to try?
Well, you know, "love"...
But my agent says that is forbidden.
They are marketing her as the girl-next-door, after all.
Kujou Sakura might be that way.
But Ohno Sakura isn't.
I'm interested in romance.
And I have a sex drive just like everyone else.
Wha..?
Ah, forget that last part!
Eh... ah, sure. I understand.
Oh dear, I really am wasted...
Even for someone who's wasted, you sure are letting yourself be too vulnerable.
Arrrgh, what am I saying?
Well, I never thought...
That she'd say that much to me...
Well, shit, why not just fuck her here?
Or should I take her home as planned?
And rape her there instead?
Osaka-san?
Sakura-chan.
Y-Yes?
Can you hear that voice?
Hear what voice?
Listen.
Is that what I think...
Lots of couples like to do that sort of thing in the park at night.
Th-They do?
When it's this late, not many people are around.
I want more cock!
Oh, wow, she's being so loud.
Deeper...
Deeper
Go all the way inside.
My boobs also...
Play with my tits too!
This feels great!
As she listens in,
the female seems to get more and more uncomfortable - fidgeting and squeezing her legs together.
In the same way a child acts when she needs to pee.
Please Rape Me!
Um...
Just take a look.
Um, I don't see anyone
Hozaka-san, wait...
... a minute.
No, no...
No!
Don't...!
I'm sorry.
As much as I love movies,
there's something I love even more.
Wh-What is it?
It's rape. I love rape.
N-No way!
This girl told me, see?
That this world was filled with girls who wanted to get raped.
Th-That can't be!
The girl who told me about this has a special ability to pick out the girls who want to be raped.
What does all that have to do with me?
She told me something.
Top Idol: Kujou Sakura, new maxi-single on sale!
That when she saw you on TV,
No!
She said,
"That girl wants to be raped".
C'mon.
No.
Let me go.
No one's coming to save you.
You're lying.
What about that couple we overheard?
Will you be fine with that?
If the public finds about this...
How hard do you think it'll be for your agent to clean up the mess?
Well, I...
No!
You can't!
I mean it!
Look, this thing is going places...
D-Don't!
Don't put that thing inside of me. No! No!
Here we go, Sakura-chan.
I'll put it in slowly, okay?
Don't
Don't do it!
Not any further...
Don't come in any further
It's all going in!
D-Don't put it in!
No more. Don't put any more in.
I...
A man is inside of me...
So you were a virgin, like I thought.
No... take it out!
Take it out!
You want me to take it out?
Ouch!
Do not move!
Which is it?
Don't move!
It hurts!
But it won't end otherwise.
No... I don't want that...
Then I'll move slowly.
That hurts!
Sakura-chan, your pussy...
It's so hot.
And feels good and tight!
No way...
It's like it's ensnaring my dick!
No... don't say that!
P-Please...
That's enough, isn't it?
Sorry, Sakura-chan!
Ah, no!
It hurts! It hurts!
Feels so good.
Please, I'm begging you, be more gentle!
Sorry, but that's impossible!
"Impossible"?
Seeing the look on your face...
It makes me...
... even more turned on!
And I just can't... stop moving my hips!
No!
Sakura-chan!
Sakura-chan,
Your tear-stained face is so cute.
Oh... it's coming.
No! Please, no.
Sakura-chan!
No! Not inside!
Please, cum outside!
You just can't cum inside!
It's coming... coming out!
No!
Not inside.
You can't cum inside!
No!
It's flowing inside.
It's so hot.
And it's going inside.
Going inside of me.
Still more...
It's going, it's going inside.
Man's seed is flowing inside of me.
It's being sucked out.
My insides are so... hot...
I told you not to cum inside.
That felt perfect, Sakura-chan.
Just get off of me.
If you're finished, get off.
Wait, before I do...
There. I can blackmail her with this photo just in case.
Well, see ya later.
I am the sole holder of this limited edition photo of her immediately after she was raped!
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Oh look, outside the window.
There's a woman who definitely wants to be raped.
What?!
Hey, d-damn you!
You believed me, idiot?
You're a home-run idiot, aren't you?
I was wondering what this was...
Give it back!
Whoosh
You bitch!
Slip
You little... ahhh.
Yeap...
It seems you really went wild there.
This perverted act is very "you".
I'll ask nicely, please return it.
So? Are you going to use this photo to rape her again?
That's why you had it photographed, right?
I hadn't thought that far into it.
You're a beast, you know that?
B-But, you're right! That's also an option!
Kojiro Manager calling
Well, you see,
There's this place I want you to stop by before coming in today.
Sure.
Ippei-kun, you've heard of Reikyou University, right?
Yeah.
That's where,
To Kojiro-dono.
Even though autumn is upon us...
Kojiro-dono, I hope your health is,...
a friend of mine is.
it's easy to get a summer cold so...
I want you to borrow DVDs from that person.
Sure, I don't mind.
Thanks!
「Loli-loli Chomp ~ In that tiny mouth of yours ~」
I finally got my hands on it, which is why I wrote to you.
Whenever you're free, please stop by the university.
I hope you've enjoyed the summer.
August 31, 2012
I'm counting on you!
So, what's the DVD about?
Reikyou University, eh?
Interesting timing - being sent to the college, those girls attend.
This must be destiny! Sweet destiny!
The God of Rape must be saying, "Here! Come rape these girls!"
But where should I start looking?
Guess I'll ask the woman over there.
Um, excuse me...
Yes?
S-Sakura-chan!
Seriously?!
I get a bingo right at the start?
Fancy meeting you here.
What a coincidence.
What are you doing here?
I was just thinking I could rape you.
But we're at a school.
I don't care where it happens. As long as you want it.
Just stop it! I don't want it at all.
Is that so? But even so, after you were raped,
you had such a satisfied look on your face.
What should I do...
Eh?
Will you delete that image?
Let's relocate first, okay?
Eh?
There's a classroom not in use this time of day, right?
No one uses this classroom during this time.
Um, Hozaka-san?
Sakura-chan.
Right here and now, I'll rape you again!
W-Wait, please wait!
C'mon, show me your tits.
No... please stop.
Last time it was dark and I couldn't see very well.
But your tits sure are big and pretty.
Please don't look at them...
That's an idol's tits for you!
Wow! It's like my hands are imprinting into them.
Are we really going to do this here?
Of course.
B-But there are students just outside the classroom.
But you're already so wet.
Please don't say strange things.
Then, shall I check?
Just as I imagined.
Even though you were a virgin not long ago.
P-Please don't put it in.
I'm begging you.
N-No...
Oh, shit.
I hear someone outside.
Oh please,  I've got work that day and they know it.
But see if I care, really.
Wow, that's lame.
Is this classroom gonna be used later today?
No!
You're aroused now!
Aroused?
See?
If you make a noise,
people outside will notice.
Then we shouldn't...
Still fucking in these circimstances sure gets me off.
Not me!
Really?
I'm not like that....
Your pussy it tighter than the last time.
Don't say-
I knew it, you're aroused too.
Y-You're wrong.
I'm not aroused...
But look at how hard your nipples are!
No...
See? Your are making cute moaning sounds.
Knowing people are close by gets you off, doesn't it?
It does no--
I think that scream was a bit loud.
If you just admit it, you'll have fun, Sakura-chan.
Admit what?
Admit that you like rape.
That being raped,
makes you happy and you can't help but love it!
Admit it, Sakura-chan.
No, "Sakura"!
Do you really want to be seen that badly?
No! I don't want to be seen.
I don't want others watching me!
But...
"But"? But what?
I can't control my voice...
Do you hear those noises?
No!
I shouldn't be doing this.
I shouldn't be making those noises...
Very nice.
Now, scream as much as you want.
What kind of scream does Kujou Sakura make when she cums?
Let's answer that question for everyone outside!
No! I can't!
No, something's coming.
No!
I really am gonna loose control...
Are you about to cum? Are you cumming, Sakura?
I am. I'm cumming.
Very good. Then cum, Sakura!
Cum from being raped!
Oh no... I feel so weird...
Me too... I'm almost there...
Outside... p-p-please cum outside...
Yes!
Alright, I'll spray it deep inside your pussy.
No!
I'll c-cum!
I'm...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming - oh, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too! Sakura!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming... cumming...
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Oh, Sakura!
Cumming!
It's all over my pussy...
It's no use.
I can't think of anything else.
It all came out.
I sprayed it all inside your pussy.
Sakura.
You came, didn't you?
To Sakura, as she lay in the lecture hall,
Ippei's voice was inaudible.
3 Days Later
About the plan...
I've sent emails out to those I targetted.
Were you able to get us a stage?
Yes. I just talked to the manager.
He said his friend will let us use it for free.
I'd brought him a certain someone's candid naked shots just in case...
And it definitely had the effect I'd envisioned.
Though I didn't tell any of this to the "model" of my photos.
The only person who'd think of this,
would be a top-dog, outside-the-realm-of-common-belief pervert like you.
Um... was that a compliment?
It seems that all the panties I put aside for washing this week, seem to have vanished into thin air...
Would you know anything about that?
Gulp!
Maybe... the panty-thief has made a comeback?
Well, no matter. When the culprit is caught, I'm sure he will be brutally punished for this deed.
"Brutally punished", you say?
Like killing him after death.
Or perhaps making him buy a hundred puddings and one thousand unmaibo  sticks of each variety, and then...
Y-You are gonna buy that much?!
Hmm?
Well...
...That's what I thought the culprit - if he were here - would say.
Okay...! Okay! This time for sure...
Yes, I think she might be Sakura.
I've heard those rumors.
Sensei! "Saku-chan" is not "Sakura-chan"!
Saku-chan is seriously pretty! Seriously my angel!
Pretty Saku-chan, moe!
That scared me.
Oh, it's starting.
Good evening, everyone!
Saku-chan! Good evening!
Saku-chan, you're seriously pretty. Moe !
Boys, thank you all for coming to my secret concert.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm the pretty idol who loves showing my pussy to everyone - I'm Saku!
Wow, what an intense costume.
A rotor around her chest...
And a vibrator in her crotch?
Here's her bitchin' self-introduction!
Seriously bitchin'! Seriously itchin'!
Today, I'm wearing a costume I think you all will like.
Just look.
I've got rotors on my tits.
And I've got a vibrator in my pussy too!
Saku-chan! You're so cute!
Moe!
They're not switched on just yet.
But it's going to switch on with the musi--
Sorry about that.
Looks like somone flipped the switch early.
What if I cum...
... in the middle of a song?
Show us your cumming face!
Saku-chan!
I'm a bit embarrassed to show you my cumming face.
But if cumming is my only option...
I'll cum, ok?
Well, without delay...
My first song...
Iku yo!
Note - Iku Yo: Translation "I am cumming!"
Go ahead and cum, Saku-chan!
Yeah!
I wanna sweet your rape-me yume miru
I want you to rape me sweetly, I dream of it,
Arienai story
This impossible story.
Anata ni kitai suriru ga hoshii
Your anticipation, is the thrill I desire!
Tsuretette
Take me there.
Onna no ko wa igai to hevii
Girls are hornier  than you might expect.
Demo ne naisho
But that's a secret.
"Kuchi ni dashite" nante ienai no desu
We can't just say, "please cum in my mouth".
Arikitari ja akitari suru no
We get bored with just ordinary moves.
motto ne gyutto ne
Love me more, squeeze me more.
Kiita koto nai himitsu no tobira kagi o sashite
Let's put the key in the door that leads to a secret world no one knows.
Afure dasu koukishin
My good-girl heart is radiating out.
Mitsukete muriyari
Let's find it, and force it.
Tsutsuki mawashite
To be pecked and whirled around.
I wanna sweet your rape-me, hajikete
I want you to rape me sweetly, pop it open.
Love, love beam sakuretsu
The love, love beams explode.
Anata kara "suki" ga hoshii
I want you to say you "love" me.
Please, please rape me, uchi nuite
Please, please rape me, thrust through.
*** shite *** ga ii
Please *** me and *** me.
Anata no haato tsuki ugokashite
I will stir up your heart.
Sora takaku
And send it to the sky.
www.SubDESU-H.net