Vampire
#
So now, Serena is taking interest in that man after all?
It's something you should laugh at.
But we can't deny that he didn't die after that.
Till that time, we've only thought that Yuuto
was Serena-sama's sacrifice.
Is that so?
For Serena, this kind of incident will lead her to freedom from this house's curse,
so she thought that he was her savior.
Is that what you mean?
Yes.
Okay.
Shall I try him out before she take his "part"?
You can't do that! The two of you might become mere humans.
That's the thing...
I... I'm just making fun of you, okay?
Do you have any idea how to work it out?
Shall I make sure of it then?
Huh...?
What proof do you have!?
Even if it's you, I wouldn't allow such words like that!
Hey, old man!
You don't know anything, because you always stay in your room everyday.
Even when Serena sucked out his life, he didn't die after that!
Then shall we bring out Serena's true form?
You should face this reality right now.
Then I shall kill him right now, and we could live like before.
If Yuuto really is the descendant of our king, what should we do?
We haven't any proof of that.
I'm sure that Mizuki is mistaken about that kid.
There's no way that kid is our king's prince.
Th... That's...
But, there's rumor that he had son before.
Do you think it's mere coincidence?
I'm not going through this again if it came from Mizuki's mouth.
After all, this is impossible talk.
That Mizuki, at a time like this...
Then, shall we wait another day? That's not going to be any problem, right?
What do you want to do then?
I'll find some proof for you, of course.
Um... Mizuki-san?
Mizuki... -san?
Yuuto!
Yes!
Is it okay for you not to get ready?
You'll be late for your morning duties.
Yes.
Yuuto idiot, die!
By the way, where's Marie-sama?
Yuuto!
Yes!
It's not proper to ask something like that.
Ah, erotic sister.
Who are you calling erotic sister!?
It's my mistake.
Sister-san.
What is it?
It seems that your master has abandoned you.
Faithful dog-kun.
That's my fault, I'm just useless dog.
Even I look like this,
I'm always listening to any students confessions―
at any time.
Thank you so much, Sister-san.
I... I'm...
No!
What's the matter?
Just let me do it.
Wa... Wait, Sister-san.
Stop it, Sister-san!
It's your fault after all.
You made me like this.
I fucked this servant's penis.
You... you can't do this, Sister-san.
It's great.
Servant's penis.
Servant-kun is boobies lover, right?
You're always look at my students' big breasts.
Tha... that's not something I do...
Ah, servant-kun's eye color has changed.
Awesome.
You're fucking me from behind like this!
It's thrilling...
Your penis...
Is going to make me cum.
It's good.
Penis-kun.
My pussy...
feels good.
Your penis... with your penis... I'll cum!
I can't.
My god, I'll be cumming soon.
Yuuto, where have you been?
The thing...
is...
Right, It's confessionals.
If I confessed my sins...
Yuuto should just walk home!
Serena-sama,
wait a min-
What do you think your work here is!?
Tha... That is...
I'm really sorry about that.
Serena-sama, I beg of you.
That's my fault after all.
About that time as well...
Eh?
By the way,
what I did...
I... I'm...
No!
Hm... I don't know either, I'll just sleep then.
Um...
Hm, what's the matter?
Did something happen?
The descendant of king, is it?
Eh?
Did something weird happen lately?
Something weird?
He... He...
As I thought.
Nothing happened at all.
Shall I take the hard way then?
Yuuto.
I want you to look at my eyes.
E... Eh?
What's that!?
Yuuto.
This isn't...
It's too intense!
Sto... Stop it...
This is...
If you suck it that much...
Your penis!
Inside of my pussy.
No!
You can't!
This aura is-
Cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
You insolent fool!
Retsudou-sama!
Serena-sama.
What's the matter with you?
What's with that look?
Serena-sama, I'll call a doctor right now.
You don't have to yell like-
Yuuto's hands are really warm.
Ah...
Why should I save a cheater like you?
You don't have to talk, Serena-sama.
Hey, Ojii-sama.
Why don't you forgive Yuuto?
Don't talk, Serena.
Yuuto.
Don't you let your hands go.
Serena!
Serena.
I won't leave you alone.
Wait for me in that other world.
But before that, I want you to stay away from Serena!
You...
Wait, old man!
This is!?
All hail my king,
who'll lead us through darkness
and give us freedom.
Hey, Mizuki?
But, I shall talk about our history right now.
Mizuki, what are you saying?
I'll accept Yuuto as my king,
and I'm thinking of going back to the demon realm!
You bitch, has your mind gone crazy!?
Why don't you calm down for a bit?
Mizuki, have you lost your mind!?
Shall I talk about the old story first?
Then, why do you think that Yuuto's father has betrayed our king?
I don't know such trivial things like that.
That day, the king...
we couldn't even detect his presence
among us like this.
I thought so.
What do you want to say then?
I don't think that Retsudou-sama couldn't feel the presence of king at all.
What's the connection with this?
It's the same thing as what we saw before this.
Why don't you look at Yuuto's power?
That's something only our king has.
From the first time, we don't even know
if his father really betrayed our king like that.
So you know the reason of that then?
Why that time we didn't feel our king presence at all,
then we didn't even know if that was really our king.
I shall be quiet, after all our king is an undoubtable being.
Our king is an eternal being-
It seems you've noticed that.
That's...
Impossible.
Is that so?
The time that our king reached the limit of his body?
That's right.
That's why our king left his son to his faithful servant,
and raised him since then.
He knew that he couldn't keep his son,
so he left his son to this realm
and raise him as human!?
That's true.
Why he didn't tell us the truth then?
It's for the safety of our prince after all.
Then our king lost his power and our kingdom also fell down.
That's something we couldn't deny.
That's right.
That's also for Yuuto-sama as his descendant.
What have I done...
It's all for our king's wish!
Serena-sama.
Serena-sama,
you're already awake, aren't you?
Serena!
Serena-sama!
Serena...
Ojii-sama.
Yuuto isn't wrong at all, right?
Ye... Yes...
Then,
I shall get married with Yuuto!
Eh!?
Wa... Wait, that's...
That's because Yuuto is our king, so you don't have to argue about that.
Bu... But...
I'll hate you for the rest of my life...
No...
Hey Serena, wait a minute.
What is it Onee-sama?
If we're talking about marriage,
shouldn't I be the one who has the right as the first daughter?
Wait, that would be weird for Onee-sama.
No... No... No... It's not gonna be like that, since you haven't done it with him.
I've done it with him, right.
Onee-sama isn't the first one to do something like that, right!?
Every girl always waits for her prince to come over her.
Onee-sama is a girl?
Serena,
maybe I should let you learn what I'm capable of.
Onee-sama as well, don't you feel ashamed about taking something from your little sister?
What!?
What's that!?
You're so insolent,
saying something like that to your big sister!
What? Don't you think that you should act more honestly with your little sister!?
What's your problem!?
Good morning.
My-hus-band.
Serena-sama.
I see that your penis needs some release,
right?
It's not right.
It's just a common thing in the morning.
Don't you feel happy when your wife is coming on to you?
My husband...
We haven't gotten married yet, right?
We haven't? Then, shall we get married then!
Serena-sama.
Why don't you cum?
My husband.
Hey, Yuuto!
It's morning!
Wait a minute, Onee-sama.
Shouldn't you knock before coming in?
Yuuto was looking at me
then he couldn't hold it
and he came, right?
That's impossible, right!?
Anyway, you always disturb us.
I haven't got...
any chance...
That's not my problem.
You're not cute at all.
Well... well... you two.
Which one are you gonna choose!?
Eh!?
Both of us, right Serena?
Sure, Onee-sama.
We won't let you have one of us alone from now on.
Today for sure, I'll let you have my first time.
That time, It was also my first time after all.
Eh!?
Yuuto, do you feel good?
Yuuto, you're so cute...
I'm going to be cumming soon...
I've been feeling lonely since then, as you never touched me again.
Yuuto, I always thought about giving my first time to you.
I want to be your true wife.
You two,
are okay with that?
Hmph, don't make us say that twice!
It's embarrassing.
Is it really...
okay?
Then, here I come.
We're finally becoming one.
Are you okay?
Yuuto!
Give it inside me!
I want you to release inside of me!
I want to bear,
your child!
Here I come.
Hey.
Why don't you give some to Onee-sama?
Onee-sama's nipples are really hard.
You idiot!
Don't say that-
Is it possible you feel embarrassed in front of Yuuto?
It's not-
No.
You can't do that!
That's going to make me pee myself!
My pee is out~!
I said you couldn't do that!
No way, you're so indecent.
Then Onee-sama, why don't you suck it up.
Yuuto's penis really feels good.
Onee-sama has all of it...
It's not fair.
That's right,
Yuuto is for all of us, right?
Yuuto... Yuuto...
Our only prince...
That's good, Yuuto, more...
Yuuto, I love you~!